You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the mindless.
You're a crap monster.
Recording now.
Are you eating a pickle?
Patrick forgot how to get down there.
Oh, did you get one of those jaw trainers?
What do you mean?
Oh my god, he's using a fucking jaw...
Oh, that's gonna sound horrible.
It sounds really gross.
I'm trying to look smacks right now.
Caleb, those don't work.
I'm trying to max my looks out.
Those things don't work.
It's not going to make your jaw look wider.
Excuse me?
Sorry, are you seeing these gains on my face?
Hold on now.
Hold on.
Yeah, sorry.
Do you want to take back what you just said and stop slandering this company?
No, I'm not going to take back what I said.
It's because your teeth are going to fall out.
Your front and bottom, your top and bottom front teeth are going to fall out.
It's actually improved my life in every single way.
It fixed my oral fixation so I don't have to eat pussy all the time.
and then plus it fixes my TMJ too. I have less jaw pain.
Oh, does it really? You know what? If it does fix, I have TMJ pretty bad.
That's the reason I got it. But actually, I did it for the looks maxing.
Oh, wait.
Because we have...
Do you hear that?
Stop making nasty jaw sounds, dog.
That's my jaw clicks. I don't know why.
Stop making disgusting noises.
Guys, listen to this crazy noise that my jaw makes. That's what happens when I chew.
Yeah, but the noise comes out of my ass. I have to put the microphone really close to
ass but I'm just clicking my jaw now I have to look smacks cuz we got live
shows coming up. Imagine if you sit down to dinner at a restaurant and just start eating and every time you chew your food is just like...
People do it dude. People with rude manners. Eating a slice of toast at breakfast it just sounds like...
yeah just the driest thing in the world yeah yeah it's a cracker yeah yeah sir
Did you bring those cheez-its yourself?
Where did you get those cheez-its? I don't shut up there dude. They're Gushers cheez-its. They have slime inside
Yeah, the new
Gushers X cheez-its drop
Rye's it's street wear drop. Can you imagine how the cheese stuff would be inside of the Gushers?
cheese it. The cheese it is fruit flavored and the slime inside is cheese flavored. It
would just be a combo. They've already made Gucci's. Combo's suck dude. That's a bad snack.
Oh man, I can never eat pretzel combos again. Pizza combos. The pretzel pizza ones. Make
up your mind here pizza popcorn popcorn popcorn pizza
why can't you eat a bed pretzel I know they're like a they're like a dollar at
like 7-eleven or whatever combo flavor for you bacon and eggs yeah scrambled
and eggs you know like a hard-boiled egg kind of has that combo middle
consistency on the yolk. Exactly. You could put some bacon inside of it. You could put some Gushers eggs.
Gushers eggs would be fucking genius dude. You crack it open and instead of a yolk it's like
it's like fruit. Yeah but it is still a yolk. An egg full of raspberry jelly. That's actually a good idea.
We're inventing British food as we speak right now. We're adding to the canon. This is crazy.
Oh man. Well it can have a different flavor inside of it. What would that be called? Egg Gusher.
funky flopper yeah yeah that's probably probably the Queen buddy Queen's pieces
buddy rumkin Queen Queen's pieces really good yeah smelly tincture yeah just eat
all that dude sounds so bad their tins bit restrooms be light
Worcestershire sauce. Worcestershire sauce. Worcestershire sauce. Worcestershire sauce.
- But most people-- - Worcestershire.
- Most people-- - Worcestershire, sure, sure.
- Most people have never learned that word.
- So?
- So I'm just saying.
- Learn it once, it doesn't take you that many fucking times.
- If you weren't from New England,
like you being who you are,
if I tried to explain to you that there was a silent C
in the middle of that word,
you would be like, that's bullshit.
You would be one of the, absolutely,
if you were from California,
you'd be one of those people who can't pronounce it.
- No, that's not true.
- Unquestionably, dude.
- No, I watched too much Monty Python as a child.
- That might be a problem, yeah.
Okay, but also in this reality,
you've never watched anything,
you've never said a word before.
- Okay, so I'm learning English from the ground up.
- And you can't read and you have no mouth.
- Yeah.
- You're learning English from the ground up
as in you are in the ground.
- Okay.
- You're underground, in a hole, you're dead.
- And every time I learn a new word, I rise up.
- No, that's how you should have to learn English.
- Yeah.
buried in every word that you learn you get to go up one inch right until you
finally ascend and become a real person who knows how to say all the English
words it's true right what's the last word hey that's how I learned last last
word is your size house honestly real dude I love all that what sauce what
about sauce was was this was the sauce I think it's I think it's regional I think
it's like local to New England but it's this sauce called a so sauce asshole
sauce yeah that's yeah that's my whole you stole my joke in the past yep I hate
you yeah asshole sauce let me go back and steal your jokes it's a good it's like
it's like a char siu like barbecue sauce char siu is that how do you say it no
no you missed another pretty this is exactly what I can make a different
language as Chinese or Mandarin or I don't know tread carefully here ah they
might they might get you dude I get you for that one yeah yeah we might have to
cancel the live show. Charsey suit. Oh yeah we mentioned yeah so we're doing a live show.
We have some time next month May 27th. Yeah May 27th. I told everyone it was the 28th.
Who is everyone? We've known for like 12 hours. Who is everyone? I hate you. The 27th at the
hideout the White Bull Tavern near like Faneuil Hall 8 p.m. be there. Boston. Let's go Boston,
Massachusetts America. Yes, sir. The earth the earth
I'm gonna be fully on by then. Oh, I think I should be facts. We should all be back
None of us will be vaccinated. Yeah, we will all be very sad and you cannot wear a mask at this show folks
No, dude, I want to see those smiles
How am I gonna know you like the show exactly if I hear laughter and everyone's wearing a mask
I'm gonna think they're pumping in the laughter from speakers. Exactly and then I'm gonna get embarrassed. Yeah. Oh
Man, I've not done
I'm so I'm so nervous for this show. I'm nervous too dude. I'm gonna get staged
right I'm gonna cry. Oh man I I think it'll be the first time that I've talked
to more than two people at once right in a year. Yeah hopefully it doesn't like I
mean hopefully it's not like a too many people. Yeah hopefully nobody comes to the show.
I'm hoping to. I'm like I'm so nervous about like
pandemics like what if somebody gets COVID from our live show?
Then that'd be f*cking epic.
That would be, that would stay with me for the rest of my life.
By the way, Pat, you are a terrible salesman.
We're supposed to be pushing tickets to this show
and you're like,
you're like, "Oh, I hope nobody gets COVID at this show, you f*cking retard."
What are you doing, dude?
We are being recorded right now.
What is wrong with you, dude?
Oh, yeah, by the way, the stairs are slippery and the drinks are too expensive at the venue. I hope
nobody comes
Okay, what is wrong with you? Oh my god. I'm not concerned about any of that
It's a bit it's all part of a bit
So much stage fright that it's gonna suck
No
I'm gonna when I get on stage. I'm gonna get so scared. I'm gonna have to cover my face with my hands and start shivering
Here's a trick. Here's what I learned didn't stand up. So you have to give yourself an erection
15 minutes before the show no no you told me this
Yeah, yeah, no, I know what it is what you talking about yeah, I know it's no called it
You're acting like you invented it you act like no Gus Fiveros invented it
Yeah, just invented Gus five arrows told me to do that before I got on stage
Yes, the playboy from the Patrick goes to Jollibee video. That's yeah. Yeah
Invented fucking jacking off just not I mean not fucking trying to come here not like looking at well
You can look at a little bit of porn just like get your fucking thing hard. I'm not gonna great imagination
I am NOT I am not
Other you got to like throw some chairs around and stuff. Yeah, that's what you do
see my comedy comes from love and not anger it's not anger it's pain what do
you mean no no that's perversion no it's love pure love that I'm making in my hand in the
multi-stall bathroom just a little bit though don't I'm not okay okay I'm the
fucking bad salesman you're telling the fucking venue that you're gonna jack off
at their place here's I'm gonna say this much don't shake my hand after the show
you will regret it I will be fully vaccinated you're still not gonna want to
shake my hand you're not gonna like it don't do it and don't touch the
microphone after for the people who work at the venue we're gonna do like a
name don't talk to us cuz we're shy yeah yeah and don't turn around and not look
at the stage because of how shy we are and we'll talk if nobody's looking at the
stage we'll talk like this normally but if even one set of eyes is looking at us
close your eyes yeah if you try to try to fucking if you try to fucking talk to us
while we're on the stage you try to heckle us I will have my uncle's gun yeah
hey man and if I see you texting during the show I'm grabbing your phone I'm
telling your mom you're dead uh-huh yep that's right I'm saying excuse me mrs.
stupid cuz that's your last name yep mrs. Obama your son we can decide in a car
crash this is an EMT also you are so beautiful from your contact oh yeah I
can just tell by how by your contact photo which is very small how beautiful
you are I can just tell by the eloquence with which you text your son dinner is
ready please come upstairs it's chicken nuggets and also what if what a man you
have a beautiful name what is that French mom it's yeah but your son is
dead do you want to see a picture of his blood and entrails on the street do you
want to see a picture of me next to your son's dead body. He drowned eating poop
out of the toilet. Would you like to see a photo of his body?
It's like damn this sucks!
With his son's car.
We were doing it on the show.
He just sent the picture of Chris Farley.
We will be faking somebody's death at the show.
Some lucky person in the audience will have their death faked.
On the house this time. We'll do the first one free.
Yeah, normally you gotta pay.
But we're excited. Please go get tickets. They're on Eventbrite or something.
What's the deal with the tickets?
We'll put them on the cast of that list.
Oh yeah, you gotta buy them in groups.
Because of COVID, there's something where you can't sit like two people from different
parties at the table. So bring a friend. You gotta have two people with you. Anyway, we
can stop plugging this now. So that Pat doesn't make it sound even worse.
I feel like that was a pretty important thing to bring up.
bring mace too yeah it's a very dangerous neighborhood yes and also it's impossible to get to
through public transportation you're gonna want to bring golden armor and some kind of boat that can swim in lava
I'll figure out how to be a good showman pull up in a bulletproof vest stay strapped
you're gonna want to just in case you get at Faneuil Hall you get breakdanced on
it's because the Christmas tree falls on you oh no if you see that
that's up right now that living statue is gonna steal from you yeah yeah the tin
man's gonna know there's some let me tell you so there are some dangerous teens
that shop at that new break comics and they're gonna come after you with Rick
and Morty shot glasses not gonna throw them at you and look that hard rock
cafe you know what they sell heroin to rock stars I mean here's the thing hard
rock I mean what's more dangerous than that you know you know I like to call it
I just call it gangsta hard rock uh-huh because of how that there's often gangsta
kind of sub sub themes into the gangsta is the same as gangster but it's different
for those who don't who aren't hood like me there's basically you drop the ER and
it makes it even more street more gangsta more flow and yeah more urban
kind of more word you know yeah a little more word on it a little dope a little
bit dope and a little bit fly so all my gangsters and gangsta it's like come out
to the show no cap come out to the show if you're vaccinated and nope no vaccine
necessary come out fucking spitting coughing fucking please I want this to be
I want this to be as safe as possible I'm gonna be wearing a big hazmat suit
the whole show I want you to die I'm trying to kill Pat as soon as possible if
anybody could come with maybe a new virus we live next to each other you
could kill me whenever Pat ain't no HIV vaccine buddy and I'm gonna stick you
with it so you might want to watch out.
- Come on.
- That's right.
I'm gonna hire a bushman to shoot you.
- I'm gonna keep feeding you.
- I'm gonna have a vaccine going once,
vaccine going twice, vaccine going twice.
- I'm gonna hire a bushman to sit in the back
of the audience and shoot you with a dart full of HIV
out of a bamboo stick.
- Yeah, that's so sick.
- And you're gonna go, "Ah!"
And die instantly.
- I'm gonna drink a bunch of HIV
and then I'm gonna sit on a hot plate
and diffuse it into the room so you breathe it in.
- Oh, that's a pretty good idea.
- You won't even be able to detect it.
- Yeah, that's a really, really good idea.
- And then I'll fuck you too, just in case.
- See, that's why I have it,
and that's why I fucking jack off
before I start doing standup,
'cause walking around with a loaded gun.
- You're doing too much of this HIV stuff.
- Why?
- It's a serious disease.
- Tell me what's--
- Yeah, and you're gonna die from it.
- Yeah, it's gonna be fucking serious when you have it, bud.
not enough chicken soup in the world for that. What do you mean? I mean you're gonna be sick.
Yeah. You're sick sick. You're gonna be lying in bed with a hot compress on your head. Yep.
And a mercury thermometer in your mouth. Yep. And you're gonna say, "Mom, I can't go to
school today." Yeah, she's gonna say, "Why?" And you're gonna have to explain to her. I'll
never go to school again, bitch. Don't talk like that. Yeah. Don't talk to me like that.
What's up? What's up? Don't "What's up" me. What's up? Don't say "What's up, bitch." What's
What's up you?
What's up bitch?
I'm fucking down the street from you dude, I'll crack your shit.
Come over right now, we'll fight.
That might be pretty good actually.
What, you're gonna leave and then come fight me?
Yeah, that might be the best episode ever.
We just cut and then it's just, I mean it's not gonna take long, I might beat his ass
up.
No, I have stuff to do tonight, I don't want to sit here and wait for you to walk over.
I have stuff to do, I gotta beat Pat's ass.
You can walk over there if you stay on your phone the whole time and we don't have any
down time, but I refuse to let you do that.
Pat, how about we just play in a fight and we'll record it then.
- Okay.
- Alright, sound good?
- Me, you.
- You guys better not fight without me there.
- How about at the show?
- Okay, that's a good--
- How's that sound?
- We were trying to brainstorm what to do.
- Yeah.
- What if I just beat the shit out of Pat?
- No, you've done that before.
- I'm gonna put you in the ambulance.
- Oh yeah, when I fight clubbed you.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, when we went and visited Pat,
just every time that we walked outside,
I would say fight club and punch him really hard.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and he didn't like it.
And then me and Cam teamed up on him,
and he wouldn't let us in to the apartment.
I was so scared.
Yeah, you fucking fight clubbed me.
Yeah, you fucking got your ass kicked.
Fight club's cool, dude.
Yeah, dude, it's called respecting your brothers.
Yeah, it's called Project Mayhem.
I already got blood in, blood outed.
No, I'm gonna put some blood in you and you're not gonna like the kind of blood that's going in.
Come on, just don't bring this back up.
It's Spider-Man's blood and you're gonna turn into Venom.
Oh yeah, not so fucking, oh, don't talk about this now, huh?
I bet you're fucking excited.
Can we not talk about the Venom Symbiote?
Please?
Yeah.
I know somebody who got it.
Who?
Who do you know that got the Venom Symbiote?
Magic Johnson.
Alright.
No.
No, Patrick.
No, he got the fungus, dude.
That's different.
Yeah.
He got the fucking fungus.
Yeah, Patrick just saw a black guy and he was like, "He must have the Venom Symbiote."
No!
You, you're a fucking idiot.
You're racist, you have AIDS, and you suck at selling live shows.
Fuck you, Pat.
And I'm gonna beat your ass.
You ruined my life before this show.
Three weeks.
Oh no.
Fuck you.
That's right.
Come on, man.
That did not happen.
People are gonna keep saying that at me.
If anything, I'm the bad one in this situation because I said it.
guys can attack me and leave poor Patrick alone. He's an angel. That's right, Pat's
such an angel. Yeah, he's totally never done anything so evil. Because I'm not fragile and I will not cry if you say
mean things to me. I won't cry, I just get upset. I won't either, definitely won't cry, I won't. He just
turns red. Mm-hmm. You know, starts spinning really fast. Yeah. Dude, he got the carnage
symbiote. I hold my breath. Yeah, he just holds his breath until somebody says I'm
sorry yeah I get really blue in the face you ever do that when you're a kid you
ever just act like a complete psycho oh my little brother used to like like he
would be he wouldn't be allowed to like go outside or like play video games or
something and he had like kind of like a speech impediment when he was younger
and he he would sit there and like scream at my mom he's like I've got a
hold my breath my little brother we would we would do a lot of pranks from growing
up we would like duct tape him to a wall in his sleep because he was like such a
such a heavy sleeper that you could just completely pick him up and attach him to
the wall and he wouldn't wake up so we might win my mom would like come upstairs
to wake him up for school maybe duct tape to the wall yeah and then he would
get so mad that he would get you'd go down to breakfast before us and he would
eat me and my older brother's food whoa that's diabolical yeah like is that
also that's an uncomfortable amount of food for an eight-year-old eat right like
He was fucking scarfing it down just to throw it at our faces.
It's nice that you just had food waiting for you when you were younger.
Yeah, well it was made by my slave.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, I used to have to just make my own cereal or whatever.
Yeah, I used to have to dig up nuts and berries from the forest to have them make cereal.
I used to have to forage every morning.
Yeah.
It was annoying.
Yeah, yeah.
So, recognize your privilege, Caleb.
My dad used to have to hunt my neighbor's dog to get some meat.
We'd have to wait fucking months for them to get a new one every time to eat dinner.
Oh man, it was the worst.
You ever had boiled dog?
It's not that good.
Yeah.
And it's like, we spent all this money on a Gatling gun and the dog dies after like
two bullets.
Not even fucking worth it.
What a waste.
Yeah.
And going over to the neighbor's house, "So, you thinking about getting a new dog?"
Since the other one ran away mysteriously.
You know, I feel like if you got five dogs, it might keep you even better.
It's like a breeding thing, you know, and then you could sell off the dogs. It's a Gatling gun with like a silencer on each barrel
Like yeah, I don't know we had an electric fence and everything I don't know how he got out. Oh
Man my tooth is hurting. Oh, oh shit. I can't I should recommend something real quick. I was supposed to go to the dentist yesterday
Yesterday
What's today that yeah, I was supposed to go fuck dentist dude, you don't need to go to the fucking dentist, dude
Wow, I had to get like some fucking yeah, I have some like serious fucking dental shit I have to go do
You have a tooth sticking out of your forehead I do know I have I had to get like like
Injected something injected in my gums cuz I have periodontitis
Yeah, you have a period for sure yeah, and I'm squirting it on you
I'm spraying my period at you. I'm thinking this is a relaxed episode. I'm thinking I'm gonna. I'm gonna pop a beer. Oh
Caleb with more props it's a beer up first
I got my fake eyeballs my my chew toy, and I got my beer, and I'm ready to go dude
I'm ready to record are we going yet? Yeah, we're recording. Oh fuck you uh
You guys want to start the list? Yeah, dude, let's go now that I have this beer. I've been drinking
I've been drinking these non-alcoholic beers. I got yeah
Something called nature's nature's beer. It's a Nalgene water bottle filled with oh man, dude
I 500 milliliters of water. Yeah, enjoy all those micro plastics in your ass pussy. I got it
They're gonna turn me into a Gundam. I'm gonna start. I
They're not an upgrade. They're upgrading my body. I'm being coming a cyborg the micro plastic attachment
you're gonna look like a wait for Cameron to become a big plastic cyborg. They're giving me huge robot powers like not being able to have a baby.
The first step to becoming a cyborg. They're giving me infertility. Yeah.
Yeah my sperms are pixelated now they can't do shit when they get in there.
Damn.
Alright. This list is
top ten zoo animals. They just, they turn, when they go into a woman they turn red and they fly out like Mario
touching lava.
A-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
they're fucking doing gallagher your girl yeah yeah
are number top ten zoo animals number one the penguin
is the top comment
never doubt the penguin penguins deserve the number one spot and are not just the
best animal in the zoo but the best animal in the world it's about time
penguins get the respect they deserve they're the only reason i ever go to
zoos penguins are the cutest most interesting animal ever vote penguin
disease best animal ever
i mean i i can't really argue with that i the only time you're ever going to see a
penguin is at a zoo. Not if you live in Far Astica. Unless you live in Antarctica or something
or fucking North Dakota. Do you think penguins are truly as crass as that movie portrayed?
Yeah. You think so? Yeah. Are you kidding? I'm gonna sit on this egg because I'm gay.
Yeah. Yeah I remember that. What an amazing film. Yeah Bob Saget directed that I learned.
I never knew that. You learned that in school. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah, it was on the quiz.
It's like, you have to recite the first like five lines of the Declaration of
Independence and who directed Farce of the Penguins? Yeah, it was a math problem
where X was Bob Saget and it was like solve for director of Farce of the Penguins.
Here's a comment from this from Penguins. One time a penguin got out of its
enclosure at the zoo and I was terrified lol
we should you know what seeing a penguin in like in your face like a penguin I'm
I mean it's already documented depends what height you are I don't birds that's
true you have a fear of birds not like I don't know I don't like a penguin I mean
you can't even fucking free and fly feel like I feel like if I looked at a
penguin for long enough I would start getting freaked out by it you ever see a
Swan in real life you ever get close. I'm not like it's not like a debilitating fear
It's not like I mean the truth is that pretty much every animal looks fucking creepy if you look at it for long enough
Yeah, yeah animals are meant to be seen in photos. Yeah. Yeah, and I got your door if I do it
If I ever saw a condor in person, I would run away. Well condors are not very big. Are you?
They're very small
Condors are huge!
Are you thinking of a bacteria maybe?
Yeah, sorry, I'm thinking of a mycelium.
Mycelium?
Me. Hello, I'm cilium.
Hey! It's me, cilium!
No, condors aren't that big. I think they have a big wingspan.
But they're not like, big.
What? Okay, okay.
Let's see condor weight. If it weighs under 30 pounds, I win.
Of course they don't weigh much. It's a bird.
I'm not arguing.
Condor with big wings.
You said they were small.
You didn't say they were light.
They're small.
Anything that's 20 pounds is small.
Not true.
So you're small?
You admit it?
I'm not 20 pounds.
Okay, so you're 300 pounds?
I'm 174 pounds.
You're either 300 or 20.
Pick right now.
300, easy.
Best, easiest decision of my life.
You're this big.
You have the density of a neutron star.
Nope.
Yep.
Yeah, so what?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, so what? I'll fucking pull you up.
Okay, Caleb.
I'm doing a research and I'm excited to see Penguin our number one.
Condor running towards you, like full, full arms out.
You're not afraid of that.
Nah, dude. I do the unstoppable force.
That's true.
The only thing that can stop a condor is an unstoppable force.
I just hit him with the unstoppable force.
Fucking start scissoring my legs and fists.
Palm in the air.
Like this.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, that's how you defeat any sort of wild animal.
animal yeah it's true yeah it's true it's true I could fucking I could hit a
pain you know what I okay I'll get freaked out by a penguin but if it like
charged at me I would kick it yeah I mean that I would kick anything that
charged at my charge and fucking waddles and slides okay slides
penguin of doom just jump over oh the pain all right well that's kind of
different I'm charging at you it's so easy to defeat a penguin due to the fact
that they are they are earthbound right and I humans have invented flight so I
would simply I would simply maybe hot air balloon and glide away on a hand glider
and jump over so easy you're setting up a hang glider cuz a penguin is just
walking towards you just when you are you charging I don't you don't get to
switch now be like oh you want to get out of the way okay but yeah about a
Penguins charge, right? Think about how slow it would be.
I would joust the fuck out of a penguin.
Yeah?
I'd fucking...
With what?
With a jousting stick.
With another penguin.
What are you talking about? Yeah, with a...
I just wanted to see what you said.
Jousting stick. What's that called?
A lance.
A lance. Fucking lance him, dude. Easy. Penguin kebab for dinner. Easy.
Penguins are pretty cute, especially the jackass penguin. Would you eat a penguin?
I would eat anything.
I've heard that penguins are bad to eat.
Of course they're bad to eat, dude.
The only thing you need is like chicken and beef.
Well yeah, but you would think a penguin, it's a bird, you think it would taste like poultry.
Why? No, dude, it can't fly and it's got like seal skin.
I wouldn't think it tastes, I mean...
I personally think pengies are boring. They make these screeching noises.
Just throwing in some penguin comments.
I love penguins.
Me and my friends said that when we grow up, we're gonna have a fairy penguin farm.
my favorite bird and they're so fat and cool the movie happy feet has come to
life that's like my mom didn't think a narwhal was a real animal for me yeah I
didn't think it was either yeah I had to I had to convince her one time and it
was the same car ride I owned my mom twice in one car ride where we we were
talking about like we drove by like Gettysburg and she was like Abraham
Lincoln it was not real no my mom was like it's like me and my brother just
like laughing and like the names all the headstones and shit she was like well
you have some respect millions of people died here I was like I looked it up it
was like 15,000 fucking guys million if you'd like just for inflation yeah that
- That's a really good point.
- That's true, guys were worth a lot more back then.
- They were worth way more, yeah,
'cause you didn't have China and India
kinda inflating the numbers on guys.
So it was just, 15,000 was a ton of people back then.
- Here's a comment from Ernest the Chihuahua.
- Okay.
- I went to the zoo today and chilled with the penguins.
- Yo. - Get it?
- Do you guys get it? - Ernest, you motherfucker.
- That's pretty good, dude.
- You silly fuck.
Silly fucking freak.
- You fuck freak.
you fuck me do you fuck me now why do i suddenly have this urge to play club
penguin says roger mcbaloney what is this wait i just this comment this comment is
in french and i put it into google translate and it translates to my no
hope mike no hesitation my no hope my no hope
That one was written by a panda dude. Yeah. Or a penguin. Panda! I read pandas. Somebody
says pandas should be number one. Kind of I would say cousins in a way. I let that
slide and I was like. I just wasn't paying attention. Yeah. Yeah I should I should have
just not I should have just let it go. I would have owned you guys. Sorry dude
I've had two sips of this beer and I'm so drunk. Oh my god. I would do it say anything
right now yeah yeah hey come over okay to fight you no I'm gonna kill you no number
two goat hey yo that should be number one if you think about the name uh goat of
all time yeah that's actually the go to this Oh
oh I don't like anything that'll eat your t-shirt I think goats are cool
because they're like the devil yeah they'll just like run into people it's
pretty yeah my my mom's friends had a farm with goats and they just act like
dogs except they headbutt you - yeah they'll fuck you up - yeah it is that the
devil was like a goat like it's the most like I don't know I've never really put
any thought into that just like a goat man fucked up looking animals dude they
have the weird-ass eyes and horns they look funny to me I don't I can't look at
you you must be evil if you think that honestly yeah goats actually funny to me
I'm actually... hmm. Do you think you think mass shootings are funny too, you
fucking weirdo? Huh? Answer me! Stop! You're dancing around in this thing right now!
You think the devil is funny? Those are not equivalent. Those are not equi- a goat in a mass
shooting? You think a pedophile is funny to you? So you think a mass shooting is funnier than a goat? Okay, so let me get this straight.
No, I don't think- You think mass shootings, tsunamis, warlocks, all this is funnier to you than a
goat I mean yeah evil stuff you know warlocks wizards so you think like you
think the Holocaust and and and deadly diseases and and nightfall you think
these are all you think the Holocaust to you this is like a type 5 you honestly
think that no let's go to wait to you
Patrick, Patrick, Patrick.
- False equivalency.
- To you, a sorcerer is a clown?
- Yeah, let me see, let me see.
- It depends on the sorcerer.
- Okay, climate change, climate change.
What's this, a Will Ferrell movie to you?
What's this, Anchorman 3?
- Okay, wait, hold on, hold on now.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Imagine if it's-- - Will Ferrell--
- An inconvenient truth?
- That might be a pretty funny climate change movie.
- Maybe it'll make you laugh,
but it'll also make you think.
- That would be a pretty good idea.
We could maybe change some minds.
- Oh my God, wait, hold on, okay, okay, okay.
Cameron, pull up the climate change facts.
okay we'll do some jokes and then we'll throw climate change facts in between
shut the fuck up you know we have them
open the pdf
okay yeah
number one
patrick thinks climate change is good and funny
that is actually okay i'll play the heel
i'll play your heel with my tongue
i'm gonna play it like an instrument dude i'm gonna have you squeaking and squealing like an oboe
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Oh, fuck.
- All right, let's talk about goats.
- Goat tacos are awesome.
- All the comments--
- I wouldn't eat a goat taco.
- All the comments are just like,
the goats are the best. - I might eat a goat.
- They are hilarious.
Goats love penguins.
- Is that true?
- Have you ever eaten goat?
- Yeah, goat's good.
I used to have goat a lot as a kid.
- What?
- Oh yeah, there's like goat curry and like--
- I had goat stew. - Oh yeah, I guess there is.
- Goat stew, very common meal in my house growing up.
- I should go get some goat curry.
I guess it's not different from lamb. My mom made this goat stew with peanut butter.
Oooh. So good, dude. That sounds, yeah, it's just, she just took like a goat leg and put
peanut butter on it. And Cameron was like, "Mmm!" I love this! I haven't had goat in a
really long time, but it's good. Yeah. I like the normal meats that have been extruded from
something. Lamb is, I think, lamb's really good. Lamb is really good, too. But lamb I
only, I like in like a gyro. I'm not too crazy about shrimp lamb. I like lamb because of
how evil it is to eat it. It is pretty, yeah it's like lamb. Oh it's the most evil thing to eat.
What if we killed the babies too? Yeah. Might as well. Let's kill the babies too. They probably taste even better.
It's like, do you, I remember like the first time I heard what veal was. Yeah. Jesus Christ dude. Veal is the most evil thing to eat.
It's like yeah basically we do Chinese water torture to a baby cow until it gets
so sad that it dies of depression. Yeah. And that's what you eat in your pasta sauce.
that's like foie gras right yeah we basically take a duck and we just kill
all its family yeah duck full of we pump this duck full of shit yeah air and we
let it float away we do the human centipede down duck and then when it's
dead it's we take its liver out and feed it raw yeah yeah we're basically the most
evil people all time oh man you ever if you think about meat for long enough you
just realize I remember one time I went to a Brazilian steakhouse with my
grandfather and he ordered chicken hearts and it's just like just seeing a
bowl full of chicken hearts is like yeah I'm dude come on chicken hearts chicken
gizzards all that shit is so good yeah it's really good it's like it's
literally like just like it's like a sorcerer collecting souls and a crystal
good a bowl with like a lot of lives of a hundred chickens yeah yeah that's the
other thing we need something like chicken hearts you realize like oh I've
this is a thousand chickens right these are so soon they're all like they're
farmed from like fucking like like yeah the worst they just they just grow the
chickens in the cube from cube yeah and if the chickens escape then they'll like
like the lattice cut scene exactly yeah yeah that's that's how you get chicken
nuggets yeah and then like like wagyu beef like the best beef in the world
it's like we got these cows so fat that they can't even move right and then we
kill them yeah I remember reading about about like how they breed turkeys and
like they breed turkeys to get the most like meat they breed turkeys to be so
big that they can't fuck so they there's a person on a turkey farm who has to jack
off the turkey oh yeah oh yeah turkey jack the fucking turkey jerky man
fucking jack up a bird that's your that's your job you fucking I mean imagine the
suicide rate of that imagine that guy's fucking like dating a profile kind of
guy who gets a job doing that does not need a dating app profile he's happy
forever he's like yeah yeah as a bird dick in his hand whenever he wants and
gets paid for it he's in the factory he's like one for the boss and one for me one
for the boss it says here on your application mr. gonzo number three
didn't even finish that joke giraffe would you eat a giraffe every every
fucking question I don't know I guess I would I would literally I would eat if
you put the animal meat in front of me I don't eat it oh no I'm not think about
if you don't make me think about the implications or like the yeah if you
literally you hand me a plate of this something and be like oh this is a baby
giraffe I'd be like yeah I'll eat it right yeah exactly it's not kill I'm not
gonna go I wouldn't go in and buy like no no I would never buy love to kill it but
I'm not somebody yeah somebody buys alligator for the table I'm not gonna
not oh but alligator it's killing something that's evil it's true yeah you
know killing any sort of lizard is fine because those are like the most like
evil creatures in the world a lizard a bug these things should die and they
should be eaten as fast as why that's why I eat lobsters cuz it's a bug it's a
sea but it's awesome dude you read that on crack.com no that's really that's
really cool yeah it's intriguing
yeah it's like a sea brooch once I saw a giraffe that was sniffing another
giraffes but so funny how'd that get his whole other ones but you wanted to do
think drafts do you think they like do you think they get freaked out when I see
like other animals yeah like I would I feel like I probably have the same
feeling that I have when I imagine a monkey just reminded me speaking of that
like a monkey I I don't know if you guys saw Godzilla versus Kong yet yeah I saw
it but like there's the whole thing is that like Kong has like is like friends
with this little deaf girl who uses like sign language to like communicate with
him and like there's a whole sequence where she's like telling him where to go
and she's like oh you have to go into this like tunnel to go inside the earth
because your your family like might be living down there and I was watching
with my dad and he's like this is the craziest thing ever to put in a movie
because that's like if an aunt started telling you that your family was in a
giant hole it was like yeah man you should go down there I think you're I
think your family's in that hole you should come down our hole your family's
down there. Your mom's in here. Your mom's making us cookies. Come on, come in our hole.
Come in our anthill. Come on. Come on. Oh, gee, I don't know. I don't know if I want to
hang out with all you ants down there. It's just a cliff. No, seriously, it's like the
best anthill ever. Oh, yeah, your mom, your uncle, all your friends. Dude, everybody. No,
this is where you were originally from. You were in here before. You've been here. No,
No, no, you were a baby, but you were here.
Yeah, you just don't remember.
There's a flat screen TV down there.
I'm serious, it has all the channels.
It's playing all the Workaholics shows at once.
It has HBO, it has Workaholics On Demand too,
so you can watch the same episode twice in a row.
It has Adam Devine's house party.
You can just fucking sit in there,
hang out with your mom and dad, laugh your ass off.
You know, it might be fucking inappropriate for them,
but you know, maybe your mom and dad
won't get millennial fever.
Yeah, your family can't come up and like say hello
to prove they're down there, but they might be down there.
Yeah, they love it.
because I love it down there so much I'm throwing my hand into the other room I
didn't realize that he was he went full Coco in that movie he does dude I mean I
guess I don't want to spoil anything for anybody mm-hmm but he but God's a
language Godzilla fucks him and by Godzilla's ableist and that's why he's
destroying the world and fighting King Kong yeah number four polar bear what do
you eat a polar bear yeah as long as you're not drinking a coke oh man could
you imagine how much that the coca-cola would tenderize the polar bear meat no
but here's it I was a Google Foods experiment he's wanted alive the coke
yeah bear yeah I can't can't kill the coke polar bear no you can't no fuck
that's like killing the ground you know that's like killing Punxsutawney Phil
You can kill his cousin who drinks Pepsi. Yeah, that's fine. But the Coca-Cola polar bear,
I mean, I'm gonna take him home and I'm gonna put him in an aquarium in my house.
Yeah, well, okay, I've got a night, okay, Pepsi, if you're listening to this, so you got the Coca-Cola
polar bear, right, so they come this winter. The Pepsi penguin.
Pepsi penguin, it doesn't make sense, how's he gonna hold the fucking glass of Pepsi?
Like an egg. Like an egg, yeah.
On his feet. He's gonna sit on it?
No, they put them on the top of their feet. And then they drink it?
against their stomach. He can have a straw? What are you guys even talking about?
The Pepsi Penguin. The Pepsi Penguin. It doesn't make any sense, dude.
Fuck you. It makes sense. A penguin isn't smart enough like a polar bear.
You just hate when something rocks your world. You're right. I'm sorry. My initial reaction
because something rocked my world was to fight it, but you're right. The Pepsi Penguin is a perfect
idea. Make 21 comments. I love bears and I love white furred animals, so polar bears have
always been a great zoo attraction for me. You love white bears? It's nice, it's
perfect. Yeah. What's up? You're gonna love me. Here's a comment from Trigger Trash Kid,
"They are white and cute, no racism."
I love him dude. Trigger Trash Kid is just, I mean one of the all-timers. We should get him on the
live show. He should be our guest. Absolutely. Number five, lion. Yeah. I
would need a lion. Why not? We've done this before. We've talked about eating animals we
would eat, right? A lion, yeah, a lion, I don't know. Too gamey. I would need a cat, I
guess. A cat doesn't sound very delicious to me. It doesn't matter if it's
delicious or not yeah you know what it's just about yeah it's about if you put if
you put it in front of me I would eat it you could put you could like be like
here's lion meat it tastes absolutely Cameron gusting I would eat it I have a
plate of poop right here for you that's not meat it's dog meat okay I'll eat it
Patrick me this is I need your meat I put sausage casing on it you think human
- It tastes very good.
- I've heard that human tastes like pork.
- Tastes like pork, yeah.
That's why they called it the long pig.
- What?
- That's what they called it back as a euphemism.
Back when there was cannibalism.
Yeah, well no, back when people would eat it
because of starvation and shit,
they would say, oh yeah, they ate the long pig.
- Would you guys ever eat me?
- Yeah, if it was served to me, I'd eat it.
I don't know how many times I have to say it.
- But why would it be served to you?
If it was me?
- I don't know, you figure it out.
- You cut off your leg.
- I guess I cut off your leg in some way,
so it's kind of my fault.
- You cut off both your butt cheeks.
- I guess if I had to have my leg amputated,
I might eat it.
- Have you ever been like cooking something
and then like cutting something up and be like,
"Man, if I cut off my finger right now,
I would just throw it in the pot and just see what happens."
(laughing)
'Cause I've thought that before.
- Oh yeah.
- It's like, if it's an accident,
like I might as well throw my finger
in this chicken quesadilla and just see what's up.
- Yeah.
- I mean, how much of your finger do you really need?
Exactly. I would say you need eight fingers. Uh-huh. Any more than eight you're kind of bragging. Unless you're a guitarist. If you're a guitarist
you need 12 fingers. You ever know anybody with the extra fingers? I did. I knew a kid who had an extra finger on each hand.
Yeah, there was a girl at my school had an extra thumb. And I just say you fucking freak.
I'd go to his house. His dad was from New Zealand.
I'd just fucking laugh at his hands and his dad would scream at his mom and it's pretty fucking funny.
if Devin's listening we should we should link up dog I like messing with lions at
the zoo I pretend to be a lion and pretend to attack them she's getting
mauled yeah a lion's roar equals the price of admission to a zoo every time
it kind of sucks at the most fun thing you can do at a zoo is try to get one of
the animals to attack you yeah every time I've been to a zoo which haven't been
in since I was a kid I would just be like I'm gonna try to get this gorilla to
think he can kill me I went to the zoo last week I accidentally
wandered into the Central Park Zoo we have in Wilmington there's like a
there's like a very evil zoo called the Trigimbo Animal Park where you walk in
and like the monkeys are fucking smoking cigarettes and they're all just want to
kill themselves the stone zoo used to be evil they've been trying to shut it down for 20 years
and just yeah the stone zoo it used to be like like that they would just have all
the animals in like concrete rooms that were painted blue like a child's
wallpaper. It was so crazy. They still have some of those rooms but some of the
animals have better like space now but it's pretty fucked up. I remember
seeing, because the goat enclosure right is like yeah yeah you can see that
from like the highway yeah yeah the fucking road yeah yeah this is a snow
leopard too. That's the thing about the zoo. When we went there, we went there and we saw
that the Jaguar was just walking was pacing back and forth literally like just
five foot like just the entire time that we were there yeah it was the most
depressing thing that's the thing about zoos though is that like they're they're
just completely illegal you can just you can just abuse the animals all you want
as long as they don't die. It's so it's so yeah to go in there and like try and
justify it yourself and be like well like these animals they're probably like bred
in captivity like they would die if you put them in the wild and then see like a
jaguar just eating its own poop and throwing up over and over again be like
Oh, man, it's like come on. I can't writing help the city the city that the zoo it's like
Where the zoo is depends on how good the zoo is gonna be
Like I feel like the Central Park Zoo is probably like they probably like do a pretty good job cuz it's like there's so many people
There it's like if we fuck up like a bunch of people are gonna see so many people in New York
We'll be like oh you
With the cattle
But then if you're like a monkeys part of they you have to teach him as alpha by hitting them with a big fly
So exactly exactly it's actually helps the monkeys stay in line
If you wear one of their faces like a mask and then acts like you're part of the monkey tree
Yeah, they'll listen to you monkeys actually need a certain level of electric shocks to stay alive exactly
It's actually they're helping. It's the same thing as putting a pacemaker and grandpa. Mm-hmm. Yeah
We're actually we're actually letting
letting the monkeys kind of...
One lucky fan into the gorilla enclosure.
Monkeys actually love pranks and it's part of their culture.
We're giving the monkeys some enrichment by letting them into the herpetarium to play with the frogs.
Because frogs are pretty much nothing so...
And you know there's a video, I mean...
It's water and slime, that's all that's in there.
There's a video of a frog and a monkey playing on YouTube, just look up.
Look up "Monkey Plays With Frog, Very Fun".
That's the title of that video. Number six is Tiger. Who likes penguins when you have
got tigers? All penguins do is waddle around quaking. Whereas tigers are so
sweet and are fluffy, elegant, and cute. They also need our help seeing as they
are close to extinction. Would you rather have a fluffy genius or a quaking
penguin? I would choose. Would you rather? Or basically like a look-smacked lion.
when you think about it.
- Oh man, dude, tigers are--
- I wanted him to do this for a while.
- Stop it.
- Why?
- It's gross.
- You don't wanna see me be beautiful.
- Tigers are amazing, I love tigers.
- Yeah. - Tigers are cool.
- More importantly, would you eat one?
- No.
- What if a viking threw his head on a table
and he said, "Eat!" - My dream, my goal,
dream, dreamed goal, okay?
I move to Russia, where it's legal to own a tiger.
- Yep.
- In my house.
- And then I let it eat me.
(laughing)
- All right, it's a horrible dream.
- I'm not letting it eat me, but like, it happens.
- So you wanna be eaten to death?
- I wanna have the companionship of a tiger for long enough.
- Yeah.
- He gets eaten, what do you fucking?
- I live inside the tiger.
- You could live in his stomach like Jonah the Whale.
- Uh-huh, like Eddie Bull.
- Yeah, that's not a bad idea.
- That's a weird reference to Bull.
- I don't know who Eddie Bull is.
it's from Crash Box on HBO oh I remember Crash Box yeah absolutely psycho show oh
that's what I showed cam he would have known it as a child oh I didn't know you
liked Crash Box I love Crash Box dude the fucking creepy snake guy the
revolting slob dude you remember it's so disgusting oh man this guy's my favorite
it's my favorite as a kid such a love that guy mm-hmm he would sit there and
just go like "RAWR!" and they're like "What are you even talking about you slob?"
His attitude is A) atrocious B) like...
Yep. It makes sense if that was like most of your schooling experience was watching Crash
Box. Yeah. That's why I'm so smart. That's why you got so smart. It's an HBO show dudes
for the... It's prestige television. Intelligentsia. It's produced by Martin Scorsese.
Number 7, Red Panda. I would not eat this. I would not eat a Red Panda. I would not eat
a red panda. I'd eat it. Wow. What the fuck? Oh well you know what? I guess you're really
sticking your guns on this one. I mean I don't, yeah. Why wouldn't you? Would you fuck one?
No. Okay. So it looks like that's a bit of a double standard on your part. What is your
reason, if somebody handed you a burger and said this is made out of red panda? I don't,
it wouldn't taste good. I like things that taste good. I like cheese and I like taquitos.
I don't want to eat a fucking red panda burger.
How does that make any sense?
- Because it's cool.
- I want to eat nachos.
- It's cool to eat an animal.
- I want to eat fucking carne asada.
- Hey man, if anything, it's actually even more ethical
to eat something like a red panda or a tiger
'cause they're not factory farmed.
So you know they lived a good life.
- It's true.
You know what?
- They lived a good life,
they got fucking shot with a crossbow.
- You don't know that.
- You don't say, here's the thing.
People say this about like farm raised animals,
like oh they lived a good life.
But if your grandpa died by having a bolt shot into his head,
you'd be like, well he lived a--
- Yeah, but I don't think people are raising tigers on farms.
- They are.
- No, they're not.
- They're in the jungle, that's the tiger burger.
- No, they're raising tigers on farms in various places.
- I'm gonna raise a tiger in your apartment.
- That'd be fine, I'd probably get a long one.
- I'm gonna raise it from the dead.
- Probably teach him how to love.
- Shit.
what did you learn about the dentist again no I learned about crash box it
was not produced by Martin Scorsese I don't remember why yeah I didn't sound
right yeah I was like I I remember I I was like maybe there's somebody on the
cast that's named looks like Martin Scorsese cuz now I'm just like oh you're
thinking of Marlon Corcrezi ah yeah that guy's nuts he was crazy
yeah he was insane he would just yeah that's why he made fucking crash box
Yeah, exactly. He twisted mine. Marlon's so crazy.
[Laughter]
Number eight.
Number eight. I love being able to get close to an elephant. They don't seem it,
but they have skin that feels like a tire. I know because I got to pet one.
Would you, okay, you'd eat an elephant, I know this.
Would you drive an elephant car?
Yeah.
Ooh, yes.
Where you have to put your feet out of the bottom.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Exactly. Yeah, I would drive it. I would put elephant skin tires on my shit.
Dude, oh my god. An eleph- imagine bringing your elephant through the drive-thru.
Well no, I'm saying would you like an ele- like you kill an elephant, you turn its fucking skin
and bones into a car. You contact Toyota, you have them custom build it for you.
Okay, I yeah, I completely didn't understand what you were talking about.
An elephant car, not an el- not just an ele- anybody can ride an elephant.
I thought you meant like an elephant with big wheels, like a monster truck elephant.
Like a fucking like an axle from twisted metal with an elephant? No! That would make sense.
I mean that is kind of fucking sick actually. Now that I think about it, yeah let's do that instead.
Would you drive that? Yeah that's what I was thinking. Dude I'd drive anything as long as
you put in front of me. Yeah once I get my license it's my first car. Yeah this here's a call to
action on this one. Elephants are like really big sweet babies. If you are gentle around them they
will be gentle with you. They are so sweet. I love elephants. They are amazing. Also please go to
a world best dog breeds and vote for boxers no best animal poachers hunters
circuses need to all go to hell and same with elephants predators they can't help
it dude poachers they can't know the predator the fucking like a lion that
eats an elephant oh that thing doesn't need to go to hell yeah it's true that'd
be kind of funny though if the hell was like all humans and then some Tigers
like I guess that's part of it yeah true yeah they might like that actually number
nine skrillas yeah I yeah gorillas don't scare me as much learning that they're
like five five yeah yeah well I mean a six-foot gorilla that's a fucking that's
a problem a five five gorilla you know it's easy to yeah I don't know I think I
I think if I'm if I'm tall enough his arm span he won't be able to rip me in half
right because I don't know short guys are short guys are angry no they're not yeah
not no they're not tiny guys okay a tiny guys get really mad at a jacked tiny guy
like a five foot five jacked guy you really really be angry a really weak guy
who's one inch tall usually gets angry when people say stuff about him on
inter yeah recording they also love to pretend they don't know what's going on
I know exactly what's going on right now it's one of the craziest things which is
so fucked up about yeah and also I'm like the same size as Pat and I'm not
skinny I'm fucking humongously fat no and I
skinny let's not get ahead of ourselves. You called me skinny and you can't take that back.
I did not call you skinny. I'm gonna stick it in my head. I called you one inch tall.
You think that's skinny? Yeah. Well if you're one inch tall. I'm not. So you don't have to go any
further. I'm speaking hypothetically here. Okay all right I'll give you a hypothetical. Yeah if
I was one inch tall. Hypothetically if Caleb was five foot nine. If I was one inch tall then you'd
be point nine inches tall. No uh shut the f- shut your fucking mouth. That'd basically be the deal.
no no we're no your your wife measured us and you're the same height I don't
remember that on this again it's okay no no that one is one is one is wise to him
about about the other one is two inches tall have you guys ever heard of a
little something called mental stature
cuz mentally I'm five mental mental stature was a pitcher for the Pittsburgh
pirates in the 1900s. I want to get to my favorite comment on here. Okay,
number 10 giant panda. Here's the top comment. Oh, really? Pandas totally are
incredibly awfully insanely terrible. It was one of the worst animals in the
universe. Everybody say these cute little darlings are the best and are so
good and they could kill anybody. They are the most endangered animals. No,
that's not even true. There are a kind of hammerhead shark that have only have
one eye and there is one of them left. That was way more endangered than these dumb butts.
I have a list of which animals do you hate most. Top one, bugs. Top two, pandas. Top
three, rabbits. Top four, koalas. Top five, deer.
Deer? Bugs is kind of a wide net to catch there, partner.
A huge top one. That's like most of life on earth.
Also, putting pandas and koalas is so funny. Just being like, "I hate these endangered
animals because there's actually a shark that's more endangered."
deer though I'm taking deer is weird - no I'm on his side fuck you no no no I
think deer my favorite favorite run in front of cars yeah it's not cool there's
fucking lemmings they just love to kill themselves
uh-huh it's spiritual dude that is ever looked at a deer and that's a it's it's
Native Americans used to run over deer with their cars and it was actually a
very it was a very spiritual and intense moment dude have you ever looked at it
just like seen a deer just walking or just eating out of the woods or whatever
yeah they look like shit they look really awesome dude a doe look at a doe
in the eyes seeing a love with a deer you fucking weirdo deer with big antlers
while you're camping is so cool I hate deers one time I fed a deer an apple out
of my hand and I said I hope this apple kills you I hope you fed you the wrong
kind of Apple no and it fucks you up for me fat deer fucking deer it's yours so
cool here's your they're also pussies dude they just run away no stand here and
fight me dude if you going up against a buck I've killed you've done the deers
oh do you hunt no I've never gone hunting I figured you would I'm too
scared I don't want to you have to wear that orange hat but I'm worried that
somebody will think I'm an orange deer and shoot me in the head number I'm
I'm just scrolling through here.
Number 50 is goose.
- You skipped, you skipped meerkat.
- I skipped a lot of stuff.
I went to 50, do you know what I'm talking about?
- Yeah, I know, but meerkat, that's like the best.
- Number 50 is goose. - That's number one for me.
- And the top comment is, dude, if your zoo has no geese,
that is not our problem.
Get a better zoo.
(laughing)
- I don't fuck with geese either.
I do not like geese.
- Geese suck.
- Yeah. - Geese are the worst.
- Fucking stupid ass, man.
Shut up, dude.
Why are you honking?
Also, they get really mad if you try to steal their kids.
Yeah, true.
If you try to kill them, they get so pissed off.
Yeah, they get really pissed off.
If you try to steal a goose egg, oh my God.
Dude, do you not understand the food chain?
I'm supposed to do this to you.
Do you not get it?
I need this golden egg.
I got to kill you in this mall parking lot so that I can maybe win the egg lottery and
get a golden egg.
I need this golden egg.
Come on.
That's what happened to Donald Trump.
Donald Trump found a golden geese egg and he became the most rich guy of all time.
I'm trying to be like him.
You make a golden goose.
What are you even talking about?
I'm talking about a golden goose.
No, shut-- no. Shut up.
They have the Kimono Dragon,
the Butterfly-- yeah, Asian.
The Clouded Leopard.
They're really scraping the bottom of the barrel as you scroll down.
Number 142 is Little Penguin.
[laughter]
Number 150 is Water Rat.
Yeah, um, Weird Bear.
Number 87 is Hedgehog.
What fucking zoo has a hedgehog?
Number 60 is bongo and the only common is bongo go-go. Number 187 is fly. That's a
terrible zoo animal. The last one, the final one on the list, number 199, sugar
ants. Nobody's going to the zoo to see a sugar ant. Number 198 right before that, dog.
more
on the show.
[BLANK_AUDIO]