(singing)
Made this here with all eyes on in the booth.
Here in my balls, I'm a spur man, I'm small.
pretty good. You can just hit stop record. Start that episode over. Put Pat on
motherfucking pentatonics. Yeah? Yeah. Going on pentatonics. I'd like to audition for the pentatonics.
I realize how annoying. You guys have a beatboxer? You guys have tenors and basses? Do you have a scatter? Do you have a screamer?
This is the most annoying episode already. You can turn it down if you don't like it.
Better yet, turn it off.
Shut it off. Stop listening.
I dare you.
I'm here to audition for the Pentatonix.
[imitating a pig]
But do you guys have a...
Do you guys have a position for a pig man?
[laughing]
Yeah, I know you guys are like a Christian acapella group or whatever.
You guys ever think about adding like a guy that does pig squeals?
Yeah, like a pig-human hybrid character.
You're kind of like a pig man.
You guys heard about like these scientists that are developing pig-human hybrids for the coming war?
you guys are into that stuff you're Christian right yeah I think and also
maybe a Peter Griffin yeah anyway turn on hey soul sister here we go you know what
us three guys auditioning we should start our own band yeah Peter Griffin in
the pigs. Do you guys need a farter and moaner? I did start to as a bit I did
start like anytime I farted I'd go like oh like it hurt me and now I like I've
noticed times where I've involuntarily like I've seen you done that I thought
you had maybe a stingy butt. No no it's just like it's like a Pavlov. You know
- You know how buttholes have like a--
- Responds to my farts.
- You know how buttholes are wrinkled
so that they can get bigger and let a poop or a big air out?
I thought maybe you were born with no wrinkles.
Maybe you have a young butt.
- It's not a Pavlov thing 'cause it's just a hobby.
(laughing)
It's just something that you do.
It's not, you didn't get trained.
- Yeah, I love watching TV.
It's so Pavlovian.
Every night I watch TV, I feel like I'm Pavlov's,
what was it, Pavlov's pet.
- Pavlov's dong.
Anyone said that before?
- Come on, dude.
I'm here to audition for pentatonix and I got something you ain't never seen
before and just starts playing the pn.
Check this shit out. Yeah, wait, you guys don't have any fucking bars. What
the fuck? Where are your instruments? You fucking idiot. I'm gonna blow your
mind right now.
Now, now, now,
dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad,
fucking up 20 times in a row and smoke in the water you guys start crying
Panasonic should do like American Idol. You guys probably think I suck. You guys hate me.
They're just mean dude they might be they might maybe they have some sort of
you are they religious yeah Panasonic is a satanic name yeah it does sound like
pentagram. Maybe I'm thinking of some you've been thinking like news boys or
something news boys is on another level yeah news boys is like they want to that
Christian acapella for sure. Got a big big house where we can play football. All
acapella is Christian acapella. That's true yeah if you're acapella even if
you're like like one of these weird fucking like like yeah reddit acapella
guys and you're like an atheist or whatever you're doing acapella guys yeah
like there you know there's like the nerdy guys we went to school with
absolutely their reddit acapella guys I know exactly what it means okay but yeah
no acapella is is definitely Christian because we went to a college that was
full of like reddit guys who are like atheists. The devil wants you to use your fingers to make music.
True, yeah. Yeah, the bass, that's a devil's instrument. No god-loving man would--
You're fingering something. Yeah, exactly. And they don't like that. No straight adult man
should be moving his fingers in that way. I think actually Christians are allowed to finger.
Are they? I know Mormons do soaking. Oh yeah. You just can't move your penis? You have to be still?
Yeah, you can't move you can put your penis into the they put their penises into the the woman's
thing her what
Yeah, you just and you just kind of like stay there and don't move
It does sound like a fun game
Yeah, just fall asleep like being in the sauna exactly. Yeah, it's like taking a bath for one part of your body
You put it in just it's like it's like it's like taking a bath in slime. Yeah for your for your
Line your penis comes out all pretty
I spent too much time soaking
Fuck my penis is all small and pruney like a raisin now
Damn it. Do it was not Mormon. Oh god. Dude the priest is gonna
Inspection yeah, I'm gonna get so own let me smell your dick. I'm the priest. I'm the priest that song, but I'm the priest now
Yeah, do you remember fucking?
Remember the web redemption that song got no point no no did not need a web redemption. I'll say that
He would give web redemptions as people
That were not did not worthy of a redemption. We're giving Kyle Mooney a web redemption. Yeah, exactly yeah for being so weird
Yeah, the stuff like that
I'm gonna give one to YouTube
Yeah, it's a good idea YouTube you need to redeem yourself right now Jake Paul in the suicide forest that shit was crazy
That shit was cool
Fuckin what was that bit we were doing earlier the lady was like you were in the burrito place
But there was like a woman at the juice place very mad at the cashiers somebody messed up her salad
I have to imagine they made it out of meat. Yeah
Bra me
Yeah, I
I heard what she was saying.
She was saying something about like,
I guess they were telling her
that she has to wait outside or something like that.
- She was a lady who was speaking Spanish
and she did say cabrone, which I believe means bastard.
- But then she switched to English
and she said like, it's so fucking manipulative what you do.
- That's the ultimate disrespect.
Switching to English.
- I hate when this is a crazy juice place.
- This is manipulative.
- Yeah, but we were like sitting,
like as she was screaming, we were like.
- Yeah, we're two Peter Griffins, we're here to cheer you up.
- Excuse me ma'am, we're here to cheer you up.
We saw you were in some sort of distress with two Peter Griffin impersonators.
Yeah, we're gonna make you our Loish.
We're basically gonna turn you into our Loish.
Uh, I think you're gonna find it.
It's gonna be the most beautiful thing you've ever been a part of.
It's gonna be brilliant.
And I- can I have a bite of that salad?
Come on.
Let me- let me just take a sip of your lemonade.
I'm- I'm- I'm absolutely parched.
And remember, I'm Peter Griffin right now.
Yeah, it's two Peter Grif- you're not seeing double, it's two Peter Griffins.
Every woman's dream come true, dude.
Two- two Peter Griffins at the same damn time.
Ooh-wee!
Fuck.
and when you Griffin and Peter Griffin's
the the Peter Griffin's
the I'll hog barbecue
drunk and clam and Peter Griffin
so fucking stupid that we do this drop me off
in Quahog dude yeah oh my god do we gotta make a stop in Quahog on the way to
Boston
We should. Yeah. We should take the... Oh fuck. You should come... because you're in Boston.
You should meet us halfway in Rhode Island and we take the family guy tour.
I'm down. That Caleb told me about. I did just tell him about that. 30 minutes ago.
We're doing all that family guy crap and I was like, did you know that we could
we could do this on in a place where people appreciate it? Rhode Island on a tour. Rhode
Island is not... Hey uh... You don't go through Rhode Island to get the... Massachusetts right?
if you're coming from New York. I don't know. You can. Yeah, I think it's out of the way.
If you have a quohog state of mind, and you need it fixed. Did they do that? Because if they didn't,
that was a big missed opportunity. I got a quohog state of mind. Peter Griffin jungle,
something, something. The Peter Griffin jungle. I would not want to get stranded in there.
Brian is my dog.
Stoey is my son too.
Now you're in quo.
God damn it.
You know that song is actually, that's just YouTube like 2008 level.
So what, what have we fucking devolved into?
You guys know that that's stupider every episode.
Do you guys know that that song is actually about LA?
Not many people know that.
That true.
Yeah.
Cause the song is about, um, it's about the Hollywood empire.
Wow.
and the evil empire McDonald's.
- Wow. - Which,
don't you fucking dare.
- That's what it's called.
- Don't you fucking dare.
- That's what you say McDonald's is evil.
- That's what Rage Against the Machine called it.
- Oh my God.
- I'm gonna have to have a talking to with Tom Morello.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I don't think he is fancy for that matter.
(imitating Tom Morello)
- Tom, we all gathered here today because we love you
and we wanna be honest with you.
(imitating guitar)
- You win it now!
(laughing)
(imitating guitar)
- And that's the problem, Tom.
- Yeah.
- You keep doing (imitating guitar)
when we're trying to talk to you.
- I mean, that is one of the sickest things ever,
is turning his guitar into a turntable.
- Yeah. - So cool.
- With the fucking, he has a button
that he installed on his guitar, it's like a kill switch,
so any time that he presses it, it stops sound,
but he also has a wah pedal, and he's like--
- An excuse me, what pedal?
wah pedal so it makes the guitar go wah. That's what makes it goes wah wah wah
but then he hits the button at the same time like the switch. I like how creative
guitarists are that they named it a wah pedal. Yeah. What does this do? I guess it wahs.
It's called the crybaby. It's called the crybaby from Dunlop. It's like a wah wee wah wah pedal.
There's also a guitar pedal, it's like a distortion pedal called the metal zone
which is like a really cool name. That's not a cool name. Yeah I know it's not a
a cool it's just you know what I think is cool and that is very stupid. No. HM2. HM2? That's
a cool name. Is it HM1 or HM2? That's a cool name. It's a Pokemon. Isn't HM1 or 2 aren't
they? Isn't that the heavy metal? The Entombed one. Oh. I don't know I'm just making a joke.
It's a dumb name. It's just letters and numbers. I don't know. Didn't yeah Full of Hell has
a guitar pedal too. You know what would be sick? If we get enough money is like I just
by a bunch of I get a different microphone and I just hook myself up to
all the guitar pedals. Dude if we all got fucking huge pedal boards. Oh my god for our voices.
Distinct yeah. We each have completely different pedals.
Full sound board. This is not for Caleb this is just for me and Cameron.
I will have five Peter Griffin pedals. There's no Peter Griffin pedal. Oh yeah.
Whoa what was that switch you just did? Hey I'm using a Peter Griffin pedal right now.
Wow. And now it's off. But now it's on. And now it's off.
I'm inventing my own pitch shifter that only goes up. You can't ever turn it back down.
So once you turn the knob up one notch, you can't turn it back the other way.
So you can only use it ten times.
Whoa. I have these.
So you have to buy a new one every time you want to get low pitch again.
That's sick. I have a bass pedal. It's like a multi-effect pedal. And then I have these
two like Dan Electro Fab, Dan Electro Fab Distortion, Dan Electro, like they're like the $20 plastic
pedals.
Who the hell is Dan Electro?
It's made by Daniel Electro.
The guitars that like, I think Phoebe Bridgers uses one.
She smashed a Dano, she smashed a Dano Baritone U2.
That was so disrespectful when she did that.
Disrespectful to music.
It was disrespectful to music, to SNL.
And to Dan Electro guitars.
And to just to men in general.
So four people, four important institutions.
We should bring back witch trials for people like that.
Women who think they can do rock.
I mean when Pete Townshend does it, that's different.
He's a famous pedophile.
Exactly.
He's trying to destroy the hard drive on his guitar.
He's swinging his computer around on stage and he's like, "Why'd you smash that hard
drive on stage?"
It's got my credit card information in it.
I have to smash it.
(laughing)
- It was a virus in my computer, I swear!
- I wish that we could do cool rock shit like that on stage.
- Oh man, dude, you get me a Les Paul at the live show,
I'll smash that shit on stage.
- Why?
- That's an open invitation to all the fans.
If you wanna bring me a guitar to smash at the show.
- If you guys bring me something I don't like,
I'll smash it.
- Uh-huh, I'll smash it on stage.
If you bring me a big mallet and a watermelon at this show.
(laughing)
You bet your ass I'm gonna smash it.
If you bring me a McChicken I'm gonna eat it.
I'm gonna smash that.
I'm gonna smash that shit in my belly.
You will not smash it before I eat it.
I'm gonna smash it though.
No.
I'll smash you.
I'm gonna fuck the McChicken before you eat it.
I'm gonna smash it though.
You guys aren't getting anywhere near it.
Yeah.
You guys wanna have like 20 McChickens up on stage with us so we can just eat them if
we get hungry?
At the show we should just start fucking fingering each other and go to jail.
(laughing)
- We just immediately go up.
Podcast about, oh my god.
- Oh.
What are they doing?
- So everyone leaves and then we have to go
to prison for a night.
I don't think you would go to prison for more.
- You can't go to prison for one night.
- You can't go to prison for fingering your friend.
- Really?
- You can go to jail for a night.
- You can go to jail for a night, but prison, you're--
- Do I look like some fucking drug addict
who knows what the inside of prison looks like?
- You do have the prison dot on your thumb.
- This means that I love my dot.
You love your dot. I love my dot on my thumb. That's not a... I've never been to
jail. You've been to jail. Did you think I've been to jail? You told me last night that that dot in
Texas jails, in Texas prisons, that means you're a bottom and you like to get
fucked. Did you think I knew that when I got it put on my body? No. No! I didn't
think you knew that but you told me that's what it meant. Yeah I found that
out because I went into a pool hall in Texas and a guy called me a naughty word.
heard. And I just had to kind of stand there and be like, okay.
Did he explain it to you?
No, I looked it up later.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, and I was like, oh, yeah, I totally am one dude.
No, you don't understand, dude. This dot means that I want a freckle there.
I'm saving up for a freckle.
You don't understand.
I've been going to so many tanning booths. It's not working.
This dot is so that I can go in a tanning booth, it will tan every other part of my hand
and then I can remove the dot and it will be lighter.
- Exactly, yeah.
- Yeah, I have a reverse freckle, yeah.
- Yeah, but that was not a great realization to have.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I was at a pool.
- Who gave you that tattoo?
'Cause I remember you said you woke up and you had it.
- My brother gave it to me.
- So your brother knew?
- Oh yeah.
- Your brother knew that?
- He had to have known.
- Yeah, you gotta turn that into like a,
yeah, I can fix that up for you.
- What are you gonna turn it into?
- A line?
- I can fix it up.
- Don't worry, don't worry buddy,
I can fix that. I'm gonna turn that I'm gonna turn that dot into an O and the
word bottom. I am a fucktion. My asshole open. That's the period at the end of the sentence.
Yeah I'm just gonna turn it into open. I love to fuck guys. Please don't do that dude.
Something like that. If I do go to prison people these guys might these guys these
prisoner guys you know I don't know if I'm breaking news here not the smartest
bunch they might get the wrong idea. It's a hard stance to take. Prisoners?
Prisoners are smart. How? They're so smart you know who are smart? The ones who
figure out how to turn like toothpicks into iPhones and start doing IG lives.
Exactly, yeah. People who do like they build a computer out of dominoes. You're allowed to have a phone in jail? No.
No no no. You're not? No you have to, no you you get one you get one. Oh you can
save up to buy a phone. You get a heel of bread, you get a heel of bread and you get a little
thing of gruel. Prison is basically like a- You have to wear a tunic. It's basically oblivion.
Yep. Yeah. They're giant, they have the rats from the Princess Bride. You have to save
up cigarettes but if you get too many you become over encumbered. Exactly. Yeah. And
you can't move. It is crazy just how, I mean, obviously I don't know that much about prison.
I'm an expert. I know pretty much everything there is to know. Yeah. But it's crazy how
you can ask me any prison trivia and I'll be able to answer it instantly.
My like mental image of prison is like 80s prison. Like everything I think about
like I think... Everyone slicing garlic with a razor blade and shit? Yeah, and like there's no
technology in there at all in my head. It's like the tv is like 13 inches big. There's a guy on
tiktok who makes tours of his cell with his phone and how comfortable he's made
his life yeah yeah he has like a TV and shit and it's like I think it's just
kind of if you're cool enough the guys will let you have it we got it's called
the prison fluencer and you go on tick-tock and you show off how great
prison is so we can eat the fucking prison yeah you know the industrial
complex government the politics if I get caught what's the worst thing I go to
a prison become a tick tock famous guy exactly become the most famous low
shirt. Yeah prison's just going to put me put me on my online hustle harder
exactly. Yeah, I'm going to be selling my cell mates on eBay. I made
I'm gonna be I'm gonna be listing their clothes on depop
one. What do you have
Jeff's jumpsuit
armpit size XL large blood stain on the penis vintage from twenty nineteen.
That's the fucking worst.
When somebody like, you can tell on one of those vintage resellers,
you can tell they just took the fucking Gildan tag off.
Yeah.
And they were like, oh, this is from '93.
It says like, "Ugly Guy Shirt for the Grossest Guy Ever."
And it's just like, it's like an XL shirt that's from one year ago.
Yeah.
An Etnies shirt.
Vintage.
Yeah.
If you're putting something up online and you're calling it from 2002
and you're calling it vintage, fuck you.
- What if you're a baby?
- It's true.
- Come on, man, you gotta think about this shit.
- Well, maybe it's 'cause I was alive in 2002,
but I don't think that's vintage.
- Yeah, I don't think it matters.
- Well, I think there's a distinction
between online sellers is like Y2K now.
They'll put Y2K in something,
and then vintage is anything before Y2K.
- I mean, if I see Y2K in a listing,
I'm not buying it because that scares me.
No way.
I wish I had been smart enough to defeat that.
Yeah.
Y2K?
I was actually, I did.
Y so serious K.
Come on man.
That sucks.
You suck.
That sucked.
You suck dude.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
What are you doing here?
God damn it.
So what if you went to Pentatonix and you played instrument?
Yeah.
I mean, they have to have considered it.
newsboys and gods not dead right now pentatonix I have not seen gods not dead
yeah and I don't I don't know the difference between the newsboys or
pentatonix well there was one night one of them tells the news newsies is that
what you're thinking of no one one of them I was gonna one night I was
choosing between watching nympho maniac or guys not dead and I shows nympho
maniac yeah yeah kind of the old guy because it has the funniest sex scenes
of all time. Funny. It's pretty fucking funny. The funniest and sexiest. No, they're not
very sexy. Trust me, I tried to make them sexy in my brain, but it didn't work out for me.
Who's in Infomaniac? Lars Von Trier is so cool because he's just like, he just makes
a movie, just like blah, blah, blah. It's like walking through a Halloween store. Yeah, yeah.
It's all these fucking weird shit, weird fake shit jumping out at you. It's like the Halloween
store type shit where like it's not like a werewolf mask. It's like you walk in
and there's like a hyper realistic like half like sliced up human torso. Yeah,
it's like come on no I'm not gonna wear that. Lars von Trier was in an
interview and he was just trying to be like funny and he was like I absolutely
love Hitler. Yeah, Hitler is my favorite man of all time. And then when everybody was like
hey man why'd you say you love Hitler? He was like I was joking. I was being funny.
I thought you would all understand that I was being funny and then he fucking accent is
Like Belgian or so no that was a perfect Lars. Oh, thank you. No problem, buddy. Thank you
I hope one day to become one of those psycho directors. Yeah. Yeah like hammer the
Anna Barbera
That fucking psycho that
Crazy monster on the set Tim story. Yeah. Mm-hmm
I mean, Anna Barbera, she was one of the craziest directors.
She was one of the craziest bitches of all time.
Did you see what she did to her?
Like, her, like, you think what Stanley Kubrick did to Shelley Duvall was bad.
She threw a fucking piano at Tom.
Yeah, dude.
Imagine, yeah, what if they had shown up to do a...
I mean, she's making all those guys race, and yeah, it's a wacky race, but Jesus fucking
Christ.
Some of them could have gotten hurt.
When you walked on set and you saw a pile of anvils on the corner, you knew it was going
to be a long day.
Yeah, I know one of those is gonna fly me out. Hong Kong Phu we had just a nervous breakdown too.
Yeah, you hear about that? He just wasn't in anything after the show. It's true.
I mean, I think he might have been in Wacky Racers, but everybody was in that.
Yeah, yeah, you know and then she had the gall to do it to a bunch of babies. Yeah, bunch of baby versions.
Sucks. Yeah, I mean drop an anvil on me all you want. Leave my damn kids out of this, bitch.
Leave the baby version of me alone.
- I don't, use my damn baby version alternate reality me.
Out of this you bitch.
- You wanna turn baby me into a fucking,
you want me to walk around my baby,
my baby version of me to walk around like an accordion?
- Get blown back up eyes first.
- Listen, you fuck with me, I don't care.
You fuck with my family, I don't care either.
But you go back in time and you make a prequel
where you fuck with my family.
- In 3D?
Oh hell no.
It's going down Hannah.
But you know, honestly, a trailblazer for female directors everywhere, Hanna-Barbera.
Absolutely.
And we stan.
She really brought a very female version of evil to directing.
She was one of the most evil women of all time.
All time, and you have to respect it.
She's up there with the Iron Lady.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I don't know who that is.
I guess he's a super villain.
The Iron Lady, you know.
Did she fight Spider-Man, the Iron Lady?
She was like really heavy, right?
That was her power?
Am I remembering this right?
Something about that?
Trying to think of like a funny person who would be the Iron Lady, but I couldn't think of anything.
You. Mother Teresa, how about that? That's the most obvious fucking... No.
She's a she's a gold standard of a damn lady. Yeah. Yeah, dude.
She was beautiful. Made out of grit. Remember when she stood in on top of the subway grate and the the the vent blew her dress up?
Mother Teresa? Yeah. Everyone saw her damn snatch. Yeah!
(laughter)
- Remember what Justin Timberlake did to her
at the Super Bowl?
- Showed her titty up.
Yeah, Mother Teresa, I love that crap.
Oh, Mother Teresa, you whore.
Yeah, yeah.
- Beautiful.
- Remember when she was on Teen Mom,
that she did porn?
when she was in true detective mother Teresa scene dude jumping up on Woody
Harrelson what's up mother Teresa I knew you had him I knew you had those things
out whole time that charcoal painting of her in Titanic I fucking oh my god that
was on another level dude yeah yeah and when she's saying to JFK yeah stop going
off fuck you might know what she was when she was stupid knee when she was
completely naked at the beginning of forgetting Sarah Marshall goddamn when
she showed her penis that was awesome dude yeah remember when she crossed her
legs the other way and she showed it through the white through the white
basic and basic instinct everybody's like dude she's got a good mother Teresa
Mother Teresa me oh my Jesus Christ
Wow, and then she also killed a bunch of kids in Brazil or remember when there was a thousand of her and the matrix reloaded
Birthday the Ghostbusters when she came she became huge
Damn, she I mean when she pulled out her lightsaber, and then there was two ends of it Wow both sides. I blew my mind, bro
Oh, yeah, I fucked it up
Think your knee might be getting to your brain. Yeah, I am still in a lot of pain
I might have to go see a doctor again
Well at least wait until we're done hanging out. It didn't already give you a ruling
Yeah, but I think she was just trying my dad even said it like I went in at when they were closing
And I think she was just trying to push me out doctors are notoriously evil. Yeah, yeah
And they'll do anything just to get out of working
Absolutely hate doctors dude stop trying to break shit in my house. Yeah, and it's like it's like what's it?
Well, it's like what's going on with your handwriting is that the handwriting or is it just a line?
Yeah, did you forget to write? Yeah?
Like what's up with that stethoscope?
Nice, why are you wearing that? Why are you listening to music while I'm here trying to get my fucking balls checked up on?
You're trying to listen to music my heart steal it so you can get a record deal? Stop being a doctor?
I can hear little Wayne Miss Officer coming out of your damn stethoscope.
Yeah, all I hear is "Wee, wee, wee!"
I know what that is. Why are you wearing a fucking white dress? Why is it so long?
Why do you have buttons down the front? Is that stripper dress? Yeah, we ain't at the damn fucking Met Gala right now.
Button up, bitch! We at the damn Mets game! Come on, I'm trying to go see the Mets! Let me out of the fucking doctor's office!
Yeah, that's the one. That's it baby. That's the angle. I love baseball. Yeah, doctors
are crazy. I'm gonna see the meds. God, I don't know what's going on. You gonna jump on this
list? What's up? I jump on you. Oh, come on man. Don't attack me. I'm so good at killing
bits just today I guess yeah yeah usually horrible at it I know yeah I'm usually
so good and I make the most sense that is true you're known as a guy who makes a
mess I'm known as a guy who never gets off topic I'm straight as an arrow mm-hmm
on every topic you're known for being straight as an arrow you know yeah one of
those arrows that Steve Martin would put on his head oh it's too easy with this
fucking guy yeah an arrow this goes backwards straight as an arrow yeah
backwards arrow fucking not straight in whatever way that means bitch most
smelly animal poo we've totally done this list you know you've done this list
when you were trying to order food yeah we have 100% done this already feel is a
day where I'm gonna own Pat we're gonna do it again then yeah cuz we're in
your person, so I'm going to own you yeah. I already do own him. I
signed the paperwork in person. You're not you're not a person.
Oh my God, I'm going to come into your bedroom and get in your
person. You're not no. Oh my God, the last night
before whatever
when Patrick, so I'm staying at Patrick's apartment whenever he
goes into his room and closes the door within ten seconds and
lasting twenty minutes. There's just the
noise of stuff falling onto the floor
that he goes into his room. It's just
clang boom, bow, just this shit flying
around in with one big explosion.
They've slowly fades away. It's
happened. It happened when you went to
bed last night and when you woke up
this morning, it's because no, it's I
mean it's because one I have the knee
injury. It's a reset the Rube Goldberg
device. It wakes him up. I have I mean
it's a knee injury and like I think
that's my belt buckle. I think like I
I take my pants off and I throw them on the floor.
I forget that you're a WWE world champion.
Yeah, I wear the biggest belt buckle.
Yeah, you wear the biggest belt buckle in the world.
But, that plus I'm a fucking idiot and I like will turn my flashlight on my phone and then throw it on my bed and then like go shut the light off.
But then half the time, like I'll have the light off and then the flashlight will be like on the bed.
So I can't see shit.
shit. So I like walk. I'm in my room
fucking tiny, too, but so what
happened last night? Oh yeah. Last
night we were trying to set up the
air mattress and first we got it
like we're like oh yeah. Neil's room
is like the biggest room. So we'll
put we'll put the air mattress in
in like Neil's room and we blew up
the air mattress. Neil went into his
room and blew up. So his bed is like
like against the wall and there's
like space and then the door. He like
put the air mattress down in the
space between the bed and the door
and blew it up. It was the exact
size and shape of all the space in
his room that wasn't the bed and the
door and he was like so he was like
stuck behind it and he couldn't get
out and then it's like if his show
wasn't there if his show wasn't there,
he would have been able to get out
the wall that was like blocking the
only way he get out yeah and like so
we started to move it and as soon as
the air mattress touched the shelf,
it just collapsed and all of his
books. And he just go, Oh, no,
it was so fucking stupid. And he kept trying to be like, no,
it's going to work. No. If I was like, Neil, what if you need to get up?
And he's like, Oh, I'll just climb over you. Right. It's just like,
like Neil, I think Neil and Alice,
you Neil and Alice are the only people who drank last night.
So it was just Neil. Neil was kind of drunk. Just like,
inflating an entire air mattress that filled the whole space.
It was so like, and I remember like literally the exact shape inside.
It was almost blown up all the way. I was like,
he's not gonna be able to get out.
Dude, you guys should get a bouncy castle. Yeah, we had to put the air mattress, oh
did we deflate that when we left? No, who cares. No, he's still stuck. He's
starving to death in his room. Guys, I need to get out!
Yeah, the list. Most smelly animal. If we have done this,
Okay, then you find another list right this second. Okay. Let's look at the other ones. There's one that's far as beautiful animal poops on this farts
Top 10 things you wish smarts fells farts. Excuse me
Top 10 things you wish farts smelled like
by Queen Iris ice queen
What Queen Iris ice number one you fucking pick a thing?
You're the queen of everyone fresh baked cookies. Tell you what, I
I got some pretty terrible smelling farts. I still love huffing those things though.
Absolutely. That's what it's for.
Yeah.
Smelling your own farts?
That's what... Who else is going to do it?
Dude, I'm...
Your dog.
Trying to clear the area, dude. I'll...
I hate the smell of my own farts.
Dude, I'm doing fucking...
I hate when a fart smells, but there's a very distinct kind of fart smell.
Like it's not... It's the type that like lingers, you know?
Yeah, the thing about fart smells is that like complete sorry. It's just not completely unpleasant, but it's also not pleasant
But it stays for a long well. Yeah fart smells
They're like it's like a bad smell, but it's not like I'm going to throw up bad smell unless someone's like very sick
Those are very bad my ones when you get like the flu when I'm like toxic
I'm basically trying to like mitigate casualties, so I'll just fucking throw it in my own face
Yeah, oh yeah, I try to get on it like a grenade. Yeah, use my mouth like a filter
This fucking puff it all up and just let out a little breath talk about eating farts too much. I'll eat them I smell them
Okay, okay. Yeah, it's yeah. It's like the filter in a fish tank if you okay if you had a tube
Hooked up to your to your butt Preston Lacey jackass. Yeah, - yeah, you put it into like a
It's a tube connected to a Tupperware. Mm-hmm in your in your freezer. Could you freeze a fart could I yeah?
- Yeah, would I?
- This is a question for all of our scientist fans.
- Well yeah, I mean, if it,
if you got it to a low enough temperature, right,
it'd have to, right?
I mean, 'cause you can,
right?
You can freeze, 'cause you can freeze air.
- If you're a scientist and you listen to this.
- Could I freeze it and then use it like cooking oil spray?
- Yeah, if I froze it into like a snowball
and I threw it, would it like explode into a fart cloud?
- Would it make my mom mad?
If I froze my fart and threw it at her,
would it make her mad?
It's a question for all you scientists out there.
Yeah, all the scientists that listen to this show, Dr. Kravorkian.
Let us know what you think about that.
Our biggest fan, Dr. Kravorkian.
I thought about it at one point, because I fart a lot, dude.
It's hard for me.
So I thought about getting one of those things that you, one of those, it's basically like
a pad that a woman would wear, but instead of catching blood, it makes your fart smell
like Lysol.
Is that a real thing?
- Yeah.
- You put it on your butt and then when you fart,
you're like, "Damn, this is so clean."
- See, ideas like that are a million dollars.
- Yeah, well the problem with that is that--
- Are a million dollars ideas.
(laughing)
Like that is like one of the most beautiful inventions.
- I mean, that's so beautiful, the way you put that.
Ideas like that are a million dollars.
- The thing about that is that you wear it all day
and then when you take it off
and you throw it into the trash can,
the impact, there's every fart that you let out
while you were wearing it blasts out into the room.
- I had an idea like that.
- What was it?
Okay.
Wearing that would probably grow like mold on your body.
Yeah.
On the inside.
Dude, my farts will fucking burn a hole through that thing.
This is my idea, copy written.
This gets fucking made after this.
Legally I can sue, I think.
Because you said that you can.
Because I said it on here and I'm putting this idea out there.
Alright.
Here, so this.
So this idea is a million dollars.
This is a million dollars.
- Okay, say it.
- But not for you, for him.
- So it's a Bluetooth-controlled flush-like thing,
like a Bluetooth-controlled handle for your toilet,
or like one of those,
you know how there's like the toilet things
where it's like one for pee, one for poop?
- Yeah.
- Those handles?
So it's one of those,
and then the poop one has like a Bluetooth-connected thing
to one of those automatic Febreze things.
So any time that the toilet handle
gets the poop one gets flushed it'll spray Febreze automatically or any kind
of air freshener. Why not just put an air freshener in the bathroom? Well yeah but but then you
you don't have to air freshen yourself. Yeah, if you put like an automatic timed
air freshener thing that's only go this is immediately after you poop because
that is the worst time like going into the bathroom after somebody else that's
the worst. If you did it earlier today with Neil you told them to eat fragrance.
I was joking it didn't smell that bad. I know but have you ever gone into a
bathroom after somebody's pooped? Sometimes I'll sit in there a little
extra time after I've pooped just to kind of soak it in. That's disgusting. Why?
That's a million dollars. You grow brown acne the next day.
Yeah dude you sit in there you know just make sure it's all gone like I said
huff it up. So it's a Bluetooth toilet handle. That's my idea. What about a
got a bluetooth toilet and you can play music and music comes out of the bowl,
so that's feeling on your on your toilet. If it's bluetooth connected, your
toilet could get hacked. I have a way better. Yeah, I have a way better thing
custom candle smells like your own fart.
It's not a bad idea. It's a pretty good idea. Why it's a really good novelty
idea that is that would make a lot of money. If people send that to their
friends, yeah, if you miss me, here's my fart exactly yeah yeah yeah people
about the good smells about people, but you smell the bad smells more often.
The candle has methane in it, so when you light it, it just explodes.
It's a stick of dynamite.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think I have a lot of different great
Spencer's Gift style ideas
for farts and poop. Yeah? Yeah.
I think a custom prank poop
like those custom dildos you can get, that might
be pretty good. One that looks exactly like one of
your real poops. Those are crazy. The custom
custom dildos. Custom silicone dildo
things. Those are insane. Yeah, I wonder if you can
the ratio and size it up or down or down I say yeah that's the thing about it is
like you're gonna keep your dick hard in a mold and then pour silicone in it well
that's fine it's I'm sure there's a lot of people that would be like the easiest
thing ever to do what what is the most a lot of people who can probably only get
whatever the mold is made out of that like it's gonna get in your pee hole you
got to get-- I think that's kind of the appeal, right? Is like-- Getting stuff in your-- No, but you get
your pee hole measured as well. Putting like clay in your penis hole. You are misreading me so much right now and I
don't feel like you're listening. You, there, once the, you want to, everybody wants to know how big is my
pee hole really? Because you can't see it when you're doing it. Okay, yeah. You know, so if you got--
You could get, yeah, if you get a mold of your pee hole, you get it down to the millimeter.
here. Exactly, yeah. It's a perfect, it's a machinist's penis. Do they do the balls
in the custom dildo too? I think it's extra. Balls are extra. Yeah, shafts gonna
run you about 120. Balls are gonna be extra. If you don't pay for the balls, they
automatically give you the smallest, wrinkliest balls possible. Yeah, one of the co-owners is an old old man
with tiny balls and they just put his balls on there. They give you one tiny ball. Yeah, and a
tattoo that says my weird ball on the ball sack. Yeah on your actual ball sack.
Here's a question if you got that done are you giving it to someone or are you
keeping that bad boy? Putting it up yourself. Dude hang it like a like a like
I caught a bear. Yeah like one of those like bass. Yeah exactly. Make it sing a
reggae song. Yeah that might be cool. Make it sing past the dutchie. Yeah it's the
only song my penis would sing. Yeah. Number two is cinnamon buns. Um, first I got
some, you can, hey I can make cinnamon buns out of my own farts. I'll just put
cinnamon on my thing, on my butthole. What? Calling your butthole your thing is
pretty funny. You only have one thing. Yeah, yeah you guys should have smelled a
fart that just came out of my wiener. That means my butthole. Yeah, if I could
have a perfect fart smell, I think it would be something, I think a fart should
smell really bad so I want something that I can I can garlic yeah I want
something I can use like a defense mechanism burning rubber yeah something
like that you know methane yeah something something that someone walks
in the room and like because also if your first cement that would be a good
for this kind of like industrial have you guys ever walked near like a waste
treatment plant who ever smelled like a yeah I used to live near one there the
one in Boston that's on that big island with the giant like egg-shaped things.
I don't know, that's like a really pretty walk because there's like lots of water,
but there's points where like it will like you're about to throw up like it's
like the worst smell like if you think poop smells bad you got to smell waste.
It smells so bad. The only smell worse than poop is a million poops mixed together.
versus waste dichotomy.
- One poop is weak, a million are strong.
- Did you guys hear that?
- The what?
- I said dichotomy.
- Wow, that's big.
- I'm used to you saying it now.
You said that's the second time you said it, so.
- What kind of other dichotomies do you like?
- Shit versus crap.
- Tell me what that one is.
- Pee pee versus wee wee.
- I wanna, you have to explain these.
- Okay, well pee pee is pee and wee wee is yes in French.
(laughing)
- It's yes twice I believe.
- Yeah.
- So you're kinda owned there.
I was a study by Monsieur. Monsieur? Really? Yeah, I went to France and I met a guy named
Monsieur. Yeah, that was Croc Monsieur who told me that. Number three, flowers.
Flowers sometimes smell bad. Yeah, do you know what I... There's that one
stinky penis flower. If your fart smells like baby's breath, I might report you to the police. You guys know
the stinky penis, the rotting corpse flower, the stinky penis flower?
No.
It's like a, what's it called?
It's called the stinky penis flower.
Is that the same as the tree that smells like cum?
No.
It's like a huge titan arum.
They call it a magic tree.
That's not it.
Amorphophallus titanum.
It's like a big flower that smells like rotting flesh and they named it, it's like a penis
too.
Well, how do you, the person who-
That shit look like corn.
The person who named this knew what rotting flesh smelled like.
- Like a flesh that smelled like.
- Yeah.
- So, that's messed up.
That person's a psycho.
- Due to its odor, like that of a rotting corpse,
it is characterized as a carrying flower.
- Linces-something tree?
It starts with an L.
- I don't know much about cum trees.
- There was a Mitchell and Webb sketch about 'em.
- Is that what the Japanese suicide forest is filled with
and that's why people kill themselves?
(laughing)
Ugh, it goddamn smells like cum in here.
- Oh, what the fuck?
- Thank God.
- Why do I know what it smells like?
(sputtering)
- Thank God I brought my samurai sword.
I'm on the I'm on the Wikipedia page for the dead penis flower and one of the
headings is videos and it's just a list of links to videos of the flowers like
twitch.tv links of streams of of giant dead there's one named Pepe Le Pew.
There's one named Wee Stinky. Wee Wee Stinky. There's one named
Kansas State University Gardens. I don't know man I don't really fuck with
we we plan I don't really fuck with giant dead penis and fucking all that I'm
saying it's a flower so like if you want to yeah I think for me if a fart smelled
like flowers I would be worried about the pollen content fart smelled like flour
like the yeah like baking that would be perfect cuz I've never smelled flower
releases a cloud of the room yeah yeah I guess would you trade would I do if you
if you okay would you rather have a fart that is a cloud of flour or a jet of sand
jettisoning fucking fly yeah no it's like one it's like a small
segment and yeah like a like a straight line a cloud of flour yeah but then
you're walking around you got all fucking looks like a sad not if we can
if if we could see our farts like cloud of flour style if we could see him I feel
like a lot of problems in the world to be solved and everybody had a unique
color so that you know exactly who who dealt it as it were yeah whoever felt it
yeah I can see that that has red dealt it so that one's you mom mm-hmm yeah yeah
yeah but then you got to get into like the different hues maybe like a family
like a familial mmm yeah I guess do your family do your farts smell like your
families would you rather smell you guys my brother was visiting I farted at some
point and he said he said dude I was walking behind you and I smelled
something and I was like that's my fart.
So maybe there has to be some connection there right? Yeah.
I guess if you eat the same foods that your family does.
Maybe your gut you have the same gut biome. Yeah.
When I have kids I'm gonna feed them the most disgusting food ever just
to make their farts horrible. Yeah. Just so everybody knows they
smell and they're like oh that's a very thing you say I want my kids farts to
stay oh yeah that's normal parenting shit oh I hope my kids smell so bad I'm a
tiger mom and I'm having a stinky fucking fart kids of all time I'm gonna
throw up even thinking about my farty little kids number four is perfume and
cologne. If I if I smelled like if I took it like if I farted and it smelled like
axe chocolate or something. Yeah. Yeah. That axe chocolate was fucking pungent.
That was the scariest smell. That shit'll get you kicked out the locker room. You
when you smell axe chocolate you know. I'm near. You're about to get wedgie. I
I told you guys about the time I got on the bus at like probably 7 a.m. in the
middle of the winter so freezing cold. Yeah, he told me. Yeah, somebody was wearing
Axe body spray and the driver started screaming and was like, like, "You are
going to give me an asthma attack!" and then opened like all the windows and
let every time the bus stopped at a red light he opened all the doors all the
way and it was like freezing cold and you're just screaming the entire bus ride.
bus drivers bad people yeah I'll tell you but I think fourth-class citizens
probably that probably when I like first started doing this with you guys I got
like I was waiting for the bus to go to class one morning and like the bus
driver was driving like fucking crazy like she let me on for free but she like
came off of the highway or whatever and just kind of like pulled around like
like she didn't drift, but she like she took you drifted. You can be honest.
I fucking hope I don't I don't I just remember her opening the door and
screaming get on to everybody. That's what that that crazy bus driver the
axe guy. I had him a few times. He does that too. He would he wouldn't pull
over. He would stop just in the middle of the street and then he would just
open the doors and people would just be like what are you doing and he would
go like this. He would like just move like a really angry and like beckon
with his whole arm to them like what are you doing? Yeah, that was the
I mean Boston that was a crazy bus. Yeah, it's a crazy. You guys ever get on the cash bus where you could play trivia games
I wish yeah
That would be money back. Yeah, exactly. Ooh. Yeah, you'll see one fucking cash cab since I moved here
Yeah, you gotta look for the driver dude. The driver is a telltale sign. Have you seen the QA non people?
who
like say that
Derek Chauvin was a crisis actor
actor and the guy who the crisis actor who is playing Derek Chauvin is the
cash cab guy.
Have you seen those?
No fucking way dude.
Yeah.
Dude.
I have not seen that.
That's sick.
It's so fucking funny because it's like, don't you think he's out driving
the cab?
Like what the fuck?
Yeah I liked it that.
The crisis actor thing is so funny because it's like.
This guy's turned it.
In fact, the idea that a crisis actor would be like an actor and not just like a
random person.
Right, somebody that they're like, "God damn, he did so fucking well at Sandy Hook,
we gotta hire him again."
Yeah, dude, he's like, he's like just an amazing, he's like the Robert De Niro.
The crisis actor Oscars.
No, like the idea, the idea that like the crisis actor would be like a guy who had
been on TV before and was like a known actor.
Yeah.
Yeah, instead of, yeah.
But just the crisis actor Oscars, it's a very funny.
Yeah.
award for best tragedy best news interview goes to the cash cab guy
multi-talented guy the cash cab Michael cash Michael cash the cash I want it
there's so many people I want to thank yeah yep I want to thank all those
people who had to die I want to thank the devil first of all I mean look give him
Stand up, stand up Lucifer! Thank you. Stand up, Bolak! Oh no, it's too much, it's too much.
You two are my best friends. I couldn't have done this without my
executive producer, the devil. And now I'd like to end my speech with a trivia
question. Who is my best friend? Me! Me! The devil! Yeah dude, if you got approached to be a crisis
actor, would you do it? Yes, 100%. Especially with everything I have going,
I like hey, haven't I seen that yeah can I dress up like it's the renaissance
fair, though, so doing a crisis actor audition self tape and it's going
oh God, it's so scary. Every time my girlfriend comes home, I'm pretending to
be dead somewhere preparing for the role.
You don't understand it's really hard. It's method being on being on on your
audition tape where you're pretending to be dead and somebody's tickling you and
I only laughed once. That's the yeah yeah we need to get and this is this is if
Robin Williams was dead. Oh yeah I'm just doing different doing an SNL real shot
I've been shot.
Saturated away.
Yeah, I think that I'd probably be an amazing crisis actor.
Probably because I mean it's a shame I'm not such a good drag queen.
I'm easily disguised.
Because you look like Trixie Patel.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm very easily disguised.
Any sort of wig or prosthetics would probably fit pretty well on my face.
We gotta go to the wig store here.
I'm trying to get a giant devil costume.
Yeah?
Yeah, with like a full facial makeup kit and shit.
Yeah, like a Tim Curry legend.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
One of those full like thousands of dollars.
I was looking.
Oh those the Star Trek prosthetics. We should get him. We should get him Ferengi'd up.
You trying to Ferengi me?
You would be an amazing Ferengi.
You mean it?
Yeah. My interview of my crisis acting career.
This is if a Ferengi got killed.
Casualties apparently over 80 people and one Wookiee on the scene has died.
Just watching the news.
I was watching the news and just like, "Wait, hold on."
"That's me! That's me!"
"Is that a- what the hell?"
"CHEWBACCA'S DEAD?!"
"It appears Darth Maul is one of the victims claimed by the deadly shooting."
*laughter*
"You went off script, kid!"
"You're never working in this town again!"
"Oh, jeez, I just wanted to bring something to the role that no one else was doing!"
"I was trying to get noticed, okay?"
"Sometimes you gotta make big risks."
"Look, they're filming a new Star Wars movie."
I I just thought maybe they would have seen me yeah hundreds are dead
including and a green alien carrying a guy by the waist
unfortunately this tragedy took the life of the killer from scream who also had a
really cool pump that made red blood something is seriously wrong here this
slutty cop has died at two different mass shootings. Something is not adding up.
Yeah, doing a COVID interview as a nurse but just clearly dressed in like the enema of the state.
All right, number five is peppermint. Yeah, whatever. Yeah, what am I, a fucking little boy?
You know what? I have been using Dr. Bronner's, uh, like the peppermint Castile soap or whatever it's called.
Yeah, have you been eating it so you can fart it out?
No, it's just...
You know, I've- I've-
Do they still claim that you can, like, make, like, a French dressing with that and shit?
Um...
They replaced the bottle I got, at least. I think his sons, uh, the Dr. Bronner's sons have taken over the bottle.
No. That's horrible.
The Bronner brothers?
The Brawner brothers have taken over and all of the things on the bottle now are like pro
psychedelic therapy and like there's one-
Oh that was like the dad's-
I was reading it-
That was like Brawner's thing. It was like all of his thing was like,
"You can use this to brush your teeth and it'll make you closer to God."
All the closer to God stuff and like chickens are like the best thing you can eat or whatever.
All that is gone now and now it's all like,
like pretty like woke, like depression, the silent killer, like-
Working for Google cured my depression.
Yeah, just like kind of shit like that.
Like it's very sad to see all of the cool stuff on the Dr. Bronner's label.
Getting a Dr. Bronner bottle where the factory messed up and it just has the like Chipotle.
It's Sarah Silverman's Chipotle story.
"Tea's so good you'll lose your mind."
It's crazy how good you have to be at making soap for them to let you put like stuff on
on the label that you can't say on the news.
- Yeah. - You know what I mean?
Like, that has to be like the greatest soap ever made, right?
- Oh, it is. - Yeah.
- It's 100, I love using that.
Dude, get, I--
- It's the same thing with like Chick-fil-A and In-N-Out.
Like, their food is so good that they can be Christian.
That's exactly how I feel about Dr. Bronner's.
Like, that's gotta be the best soap in the world.
- Yeah, but I was gonna say,
I've been using the peppermint soap.
Kind of upsetting, I mean, I wash my ass with it.
I would think that my farts would smell like peppermint
after using it.
- Nah, Dan.
- But no, it's just a very like menthol-y, very minty,
I mean if you walk, if you put that shit on your body,
you get out of the shower and you walk into a cold room.
- Yeah, it's curtains.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, walk around, you smell like the damn candy man
in here.
- The mint hitting the cold air on your nuts.
- Yeah, exactly.
- It's an insane feeling.
- Yeah, it's not good.
Very, it's also very medicinal.
- This is Dr. Bronner's challenge.
You tell me your story.
- Put that shit all over you,
walk into a restaurant freezer,
and then see how you feel.
See if you can last 10 minutes.
- You gotta go use the shower in the back of the restaurant
that all restaurants have.
Little insider secret.
- It's like a secret menu type thing.
Like they have to let you--
- Can I use your shower?
- Let me get like a number six, two apple pies,
and a number clean.
- God damn.
I wish that they'd never learned the secret menu.
Oh, fuck.
Keep having to give people a hall pass
to walk back and use the shower.
Somebody's in there right now.
(laughing)
That's like the ice cream machine broke thing.
Yeah.
Sorry, somebody's in the shower right now.
Yeah, there's somebody in the shower actually.
We should put a secret menu on the podcast.
Yeah. There is one.
There is.
You guys don't know it.
I'm the only one that knows it.
Really? It's a secret, yeah.
Can I try?
You can try.
- Camera naked.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Sometimes you just get exactly what you want in life.
It's really a beautiful fact.
Number six is honey.
Honey doesn't smell.
I ain't no damn bee.
That's a bee's job to fart some honey out.
- Yeah, I don't think honey smells.
- Smells what?
It does.
Go smell my honey.
- I wanna smell you, honey.
- Smell my honey.
- Go smell my honey.
Go!
What?
Go! It's in there!
Go smell it!
Give it a whiff!
Go get it!
Go get my honey and smell that!
Put the mic down and go get the honey!
Put your nose in my honey!
Do it!
I hate you.
Go smell my honey!
[laughter]
Such a weird thing!
There's nothing weird about that.
It's a weird thing to say!
No.
You're making it weird, dude.
You made it weird!
[sniff]
No, you made it weird!
Oh my god, dude.
God damn, I'm so dug right now.
I'm so, I'm dug as fuck right now. Yeah I'm so dug but you made it weird. We got
insanely dug last night and I got weird too and I said WTF? WTF I'm so dug right
now. Norm Macdonald live show. Getting high. Yeah dude I was in the car talking. I was
with my comedian and we were talking. In cars. And we were getting coffee not
important. Yeah and I basically made it weird and he said WTF are you Norm
McDonald getting dug right now yeah yeah and I said I'm one of the indoor kids
pretty much that I've never heard of that yeah I said I said Rick and Morty
yeah number eight is vanilla seven seven is vanilla
number eight chocolate I don't like how much how many of these are sweet give me
a barbecue sauce fart you know just not have a sense of smell not for chocolate
I want my first smelling does chocolate smell you should be all my first to
smell like stubs barbecue sauce yeah you know that shit good sauce yeah yeah or
maybe like you know the best barbecue sauce name is Rufus Teague's Rufus Teague
made some sauce that's too long for me that's a little bit of a reddit name for
For a sauce I would say I don't think that's a reddit name. I think it is a little bit of a reddit name
It's too long. It's like dr. Maborium. Let's just call it a room T
But it's called the roof is teague made some sauce. I just leave that last part out
Yeah, that last part is kind of yeah, that's I don't need that crap. Well the worst one is bone-sucking sauce
That sounds pretty funny. It is funny, but it's like I think barbecue sauce names
Definitely too horny. Do you think I'm gonna make an operation that lets you make your fart smell like bilge water if you want
What's bilgewater? Like from a ship? Are you a seaman?
Is this something I didn't know about you? Is it the water that collects in the bottom of a ship?
Bilgewater? I'm not a pirate. Why would I know this dude?
Arrgh, they should make your farts smell like a scarlet knot.
A scarlet knot? You mean a garlic knot? No, a scarlet knot.
It's a kind of pirate knot. So you know a scarlet knot but not bilgewater?
- Bilge water. - Bilge water.
- I think it actually made up a scarlet knot, maybe.
- Yeah, it's-- - Trying to come up
with a kind of a piratey knot.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Like brine?
- Brine? - Like a bag of sand, maybe?
- Like grog fart? - Yeah, glass?
- Dog fart? - Grog fart!
- Could you make my fart smell like glass?
- Here comes Pat saying, "Oh, a glass doesn't have a smell."
- Ever had a smell of glass all the time?
- Aw, you bastard.
If you smoke weed in it, it smells like weed.
- Fruit Loops, Febreze, eggs.
- Fruit Loops.
- My shit already smells like eggs, dude.
I don't need no help in that department.
- You know what, no, Fruit Loops does have like a weird.
- Yeah, Fruit Loops has a--
- Fruit Loops has a very good chemically fruity smell.
- Yeah.
- Like when you smell, like,
I had a roommate in community college
who would vape Fruit Loops vape juice.
- I had one of those ones that looks like a bad dragon toy.
One of the like really big--
box ones yeah he had one of those. How do you carry, you need like a holster for that.
How do people do that dude? Well I mean he wore like cargo pants. Oh yeah you have
that's why those guys wear cargo pants. Yeah. They have that big ass thing. Like he would blow
the smoke and I would smell it and I'd be like we don't have any Froot Loops. Damn I'm hungry.
Every time I was just like oh yeah fucking vape like I never got used to the
smell cuz it's like Froot Loops. Somehow 13 is skunk dead animal. If my fart
smelled like skunk I would use that shit to my advantage yeah I would actually
probably live the life of a skunk yeah yeah I think about it if I had his power
but like a pet skunk yeah I'd be like I'd be like a super papa puppy pup pup
skunk number 28 number 28 is the moon smell like the moon that's actually the
key to this question is you make it smell like something that you've never
smelled before but you really want to smell exactly yeah cuz then you know
- No, you gain knowledge. - One trillion dollars.
- Yeah, I'm a little bit of a knowledge freak.
Speaking of farts, I have had to shit so bad
for an hour and a half. - I want my fart
to smell like the smell-- - Is this an hour
and a half? - That when you smell it,
you get $100.
- Yeah, exactly, yeah.
I want my farts to smell like the lottery.
- A smell so good that people will give you money
if they smell it.
- Yeah, exactly, and then I could become
a traveling farter. - What if, okay.
Fart smell-- - Tee hee.
- Like a fart that smells like an eccentric billionaire's
dead wife. So you wait, you're like a waiter in a restaurant and you're
like a night, you work at this nice restaurant and then one day you fart on
the job while you're working. Just fart on Carlos Slim's face. Yeah, someone like that and
he's just like, oh. Like a loud fart too, I'm not talking like a silent but deadly.
- They sound like her saying, "Hey honey."
(laughing)
- All your farts sound like an eccentric billionaire's
dead wife.
- And they smell like her too.
- They say, "Help, I'm trapped in this man's body.
"Help, help!"
- They say, "Yeah, help honey,
"I need you to give this guy a million dollars."
- He needs it!
I'm stuck in his butt!
- Now that idea is a million dollars.
That is a million dollars.
- Thank you for listening to this show.
We have something to plug.
Nope. Bye. Cameron's butt. Come on.