You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
I'm pissed.
- Yep.
- I'm fucking pissed.
You look like shit in that thing, dude.
- I don't look like shit.
- You look terrible.
- I look good.
- You can't, you don't look good.
- Yeah, I look good.
- You're stealing my thang and my thang.
- I just burped so much.
- And you look terrible.
- That's, Calboy doesn't burp.
cowboy hot scoops. Excuse me ma'am, I, my apologies. So when Patrick joined the zoom
call he had a cowboy hat on. Mm-hmm. And only- Caleb was not able to find one. Only because-
I guess wherever we're usually- I thought- I don't know how you didn't find one. In my
closet. I, well last night I tried to find one- Is that where all the other costumes
came from too? Yes. I tried to find- Is that you just go look? Eventually, yeah. I tried
to find one last night on Amazon that had one day shipping and it's unavailable so
I was I was fucking you know I can't leave I'm a victim I can't leave my
apartment right now I can't I haven't been able to shop for costumes there's a
lot of ways that kovat is affecting the American people where people can't look
for different how you've given out you've given out your address right
somebody could just come give me a if you know where Caleb lives can you we need
you to drop a hat to him outside the front door leave it out front you throw
some groceries in the hat like a bag and then I save me another fucking thing I
have to do oh yeah just make it happen dude I should be wearing a you can you
imagine how good and evil I would look with that hat on you look like shit you
You would not look evil with a cowboy hat on.
Dude, I would look like the baddest- I'd look like the bad- the evil cow- the cow- man- the cow evil man.
You'd look like shit compared to how I look right now.
You look- you're wearing a Rod Stewart hat underneath the cowboy hat. This is not-
Well, it won't fit over the headphones, and I'm not- my head's too sweaty.
I hate you, dude.
'Cause I was skating 15 minutes ago.
Fuck you, man.
No, fuck you.
You look like shit.
You look like fucking shit.
I don't look sick. I'm normal. I don't look sick. You look so sick dude. I don't look sick.
Yeah. No. You, your head and your shirt and your your wall are all the same color.
Yeah it's cream. It's a beautiful neutral color. It allows for a lot of interior
design choices. You know I have a loud duvet cover. You look like, hey Caleb,
if you put on if you put on that cowboy hat you'd look more like broke-ass
mountain. Broke boy mountain? Yeah. Mm-hmm. You gonna cry? Oh he's crying.
Oh he's crying. He's pretending to have he's pretending to have chew he's
pretending of chewing tobacco in his lip right now. I will say it's even more
disrespectful that Patrick isn't even wearing the hat. I'm wearing the hat!
You're wearing a hat and then headphones over the hat and then you put the cowboy
hat over both of those. That doesn't count as wearing a thing. The third thing on your
head you're not wearing. Okay, there we go. Now put the headphones on over the cowboy
hat. How's this? That's a really good look. I can't hear. You can usually make yourself
cry faster than this. What's going on pal? Are you too happy today? Yeah. I've lost my
ability dude, I'm having too much fun. Except I just remembered that Pat has a fucking cowboy
hat on and I don't. My head's cold, everything sucks dude. Fuck! I'm fine, I'm doing great.
I got a cowboy hat. You look like shit! I look good. I hate you! Check this out. Cowboys
didn't have glasses stop I don't know where my technology wasn't around
cowboy some there were prospectors with glad to be a cowboy without perfect
vision shut the fuck up you could know and even if you didn't you wouldn't wear
glasses cuz you're a cowboy you don't have to read anything you have to read
directions yeah you have to read what is the wanted posters they just guessed
they had to read the wanted posters. What do you mean they just guessed?
They would get the wrong guy a lot. You have to read the poster and see if it was dead or alive.
Or if it's dead or alive. A real cowboy didn't care!
I'm a real cowboy. You're not.
I am. I'm a real cowboy too. God damn it.
I gotta get different headphones. Yeah, you're a cowboy because you're half cow half boy.
So? I still have the hat.
That's right. That's a good point. There were no bald cowboys also I have to say.
There was like a hundred of them. Zero bald cowboys. They were a gang. They were called
the bald bandits. There was no such thing as the bald bandits. They were called the
bald bandits. The bald bandits did not exist. Snow the bald. No. There was a group of bandits
named the bald bandits mixed truth there was a group of bandits but they weren't
bald and they weren't called the bald band no it's not you're not Snopes dude
stop talking like you're Snopes the bald band is Snopes the bald bandits had a
movie written by DW Griffith about that's true Caleb's a member of a
different modern-day ball okay all right I see how this episode's gonna go now
These bald bandits hated the hair on their body so much that they would wear white sleek
sheets to cover them up.
Yeah, dude, so nobody knows you're bald.
You know?
There's definitely never been like a hot KKK guy because why would you cover that face
up?
That's why I could never join the KKK, too beautiful.
I had to take the cowboy hat off.
That's why they started cutting eye holes in there because some of them had pretty eyes.
Before that they were all just bumping into each other.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
Snopes says so.
You don't know Snopes, okay?
I think Cameron knows Snopes.
Snopes is like a Banksy or Q-type figure.
When you get the vaccine, it downloads all of Snopes' knowledge base into your brain
through microchip.
That would be so surprising to me, I guess.
While Biden did say that about black youth, he didn't mean it quite in that way.
That phrase is just preloaded into your head.
He was being sarcastic.
He was being silly.
There was no man named Corn Pop.
While Biden's mouth did move to form those words, there was a racist guy behind him actually
saying them.
He was being puppeted by Jeff Dunham.
He was doing Bubba J. Yeah, the J in Bubba J stands for Joe Biden.
Bubba Joe.
but Joe Biden. Joe Biden is the old man what's his name? Fart Walter. Fart Walter.
Yeah, Fart Walter. That's definitely, that's the real Joe Biden dude. Mm-hmm.
He's Walter for sure. Well he hates Priuses. He's a total Walter. Yeah Priuses,
he hates Priuses and phones and blackberries and Bluetooth's all this
modern crap dude whatever happened to the newspaper yeah right whatever happened
you used to call your friends on the newspaper back in the day mm-hmm you used to send your
friend used to take out an ad in the newspaper that said hey Jim hey wanna
hang out with me on Saturday March 8th that's how you would communicate back in
the day you'd fucking yeah you'd send a you'd wait for the Sunday paper to come
out you know and you kill somebody who had the name of whatever message you
wanted to send to your friends that they caught it in the obits you know yeah and
that was but by now there's still our newspapers I mean there's a huge pile
of them outside your house aren't you gonna go get them man I miss indentured
servants everything is so tough go do everything yourself dude man I'm just
life I'm just sitting in sweat right now I don't know why I thought it was a good
idea you're in a Korean bathhouse I am with your 50 best I'm in a spa oh yeah I
got the I got the Vax I got the Vax appointment coming on Lee I go back to
bathhouses yeah I'm so excited to go back to the cold sauna I just can't wait
yeah it's the cold sauna that they have in every restaurant so the cold sauna is
room temperature I'm excited to go back to the bath houses the costume shops
they've been missing me. They might be out of business. They might have been run out of
business because I'm locked inside. Yeah, everybody who buys costumes there now is
like, "Where's that that funny smell?" and they're like, "Oh, that guy who used to try
on every single costume in the store isn't allowed to come in anymore." I need to see if it fits, dude.
I'm a 31 waist, a lot of these costumes made for a much bigger man. Yeah, all the
customers miss the the way that your shoulders would would stretch out the
the suits into like sharp points somehow mm-hmm it's cuz I'm you look like the
guy it's called having high exactly the highest t people have that have just
angles all over their bodies is this a sailor outfit for a Tim
Burton character what is the geometry going on here I don't understand this
when it's on me and where all the wigs they're all gone he bought them all I
I don't wear wigs. I only have one wig. You definitely wear wigs. You should.
Oh man, you should get a wig. You definitely, when the camera's off, you absolutely are wearing a wig.
The camera? What camera? You should totally get a wig, dude. I put wigs when the cameras are on,
buddy. We should get, oh, we should get Caleb like a really like... You know what's funny?
We should get you like a wig tree, like a hat tree to put in your house, but just with a ton of wigs.
like super ornate. You remember when that fucking uh the iHeartEating shit thing went
like the iHeartEating shit tweet went viral a bunch of people thought that Caleb was um
Trixie Mattel. Yeah Trixie Mattel. That's what I found out. Is that true? Yeah that's what I found
out that I would be a perfect drag queen. Yeah. Yeah if I was like if I was like one percent more
gay I would make so much more money doing that than fucking podcasting dude. I was like and then
It made sense. I was like, yeah, dude, what a mannequin is a blank slate. Yeah
So good as a
Queen I would be like one of the best ever be like you'd be so mean to
Bitch you wear platform shoes and finally hit five six dude. It'd be great
Not sure
You know I was having fun for like one second on this episode
Then you had to take it back and make fucking make it you wouldn't even have to wear makeup, too
Yeah, face so nice. I'm gonna start doing this when you when you're mean to me
Okay mm-hmm
Fuck you dude if I was a cowboy right now
You would not be saying that shit makes out of a six shooter pointed at your brain
I've been spitting in my spittoon this whole episode. You don't have a spittoon either
If you have a spittoon show it to me.
And you can't use your foreskin as a spittoon.
Then what the fuck? I can't?
Dude, I feel...
No. Why not?
Empty it out right now. Drain it.
I'm calling Dr. Pimple Popper to come
drain your foreskin spittoon right now, dude.
She's not gonna... Nuh-uh.
She's not opening up my
foreskin spittoon.
Squirtoon.
Fuck.
She's not gonna drain your squirtoon that you've been squirting in all day.
I have to do Squirtoon again. That's lost to time forever.
Oh.
Unless it's found.
I was trying to bring it up.
I was finding it on a hard drive.
You can't bring it up.
You fucker.
Squirtoon is a lost bit because I think that was a time when Patrick died mid-recording
or something.
Yeah.
We had a really good thing about Squirtoon so you're just going to have to imagine what
that is unless I find the file and put it at the end of this episode. Maybe I will.
Maybe I won't.
Pat, you lowdown son of a bitch. If you put that cowboy hat on your head one more time,
I'm putting a damn bounty on your head.
All right, $5, dead or alive.
- Come get me.
- Green light.
- Come get me, I live.
- There's a green light on Patrick.
- No, there's not.
- Like in John Wick 2 when everyone's trying to get him.
Or is that John Wick 3?
- That is John Wick 4.
- That's right now, that's Caleb Pitts 1,
'cause I'm fucking calling out the Bloods and the Crips
and the Woo Gang on you right now, and the Cowboys.
Woo!
- What?
- The Woo Gang.
- Who's that?
a New York gang. The Wu-Tang Clan? No! The violence has been so bad lately
between the Bloods and the Crips and the Cowboys.
Yeah, you don't want to walk through that neighborhood. That's cowboy country.
As soon as you see tumbleweeds, you're wearing a red bandana? No way. You just see like a bike lane, like the bike
symbol turn into a horse like yeah hey don't fucking stop don't you might get
run up on might get tied up whatever you do not do do not walk through through the
cowboy neighborhood wearing stripes and a black beanie they're gonna and bring you
to the sheriff yeah who do you think's more dangerous ms-13 or the cowboy gang I
I don't gotta be close right yeah that's like a deadly yeah deadliest warrior
episode that is like 100% in episode of deadliest warrior. MS-13 vs one cowboy.
No it's a cowboy gang dude. Yeah it's true. Yeah well wouldn't it be a bandit? No
that's different. It's not a bandit. Oh cowboys a good guy or like a like a
neutral guy. A bandit's a bad guy. Cowboys pure neutral. He knows where the money is.
Well he's like he's like neutral good like good news it depends you know sometimes
he saves people but sometimes he gets nasty with it mm-hmm when my oh man the
cowboy gets nasty with it oh just you don't want to be around when he's when
he's when he's twirling that lasso around you don't want to yeah whoo we need to
get these lasso hey man you when a cowboy is feeling nasty you you want to stay at
least a hundred feet away because because it to a nasty cowboy every open mouth
looks like a spittoon yeah but I'm gonna go I'm gonna go make a movie where I go
into the cowboy country and I fix it up dude yeah white savior for the Cowboys
I'm gonna take care of it dude I'm gonna get that I'm gonna get that gunpowder
off of the streets and the fucking snake oil. The snake oil. Yeah my son comes home like
late at night and a stick of dynamite falls out of his pants. I'm like what the
where have you been what the fuck is that? Yeah. Have you been messing around with those
damn cowboys again? My son comes home wearing a Lone Ranger mask. He has to take it off before he comes in the door.
But dad I want to be a cowboy no fucking son of mine's gonna be a cowboy. Yeah, you're like giving like like you're uh
Like your your kid gives you money to like buy him something at like the grocery store and you like bite into it
Really yeah, you wake up when you hear your kid coming into the house and you hear the the telltale like click and jangle of
spurs on
I'm like walking down the hall to his room.
Little spurs.
You find chaps in the laundry?
Yeah.
I just walk in, I walk into the living room and just throw them on him.
Tell me what that is.
Explain to me what the fuck that is.
Barging into his room like a shirtless...
Where's the ass on these pants?
Where's the fucking ass on these?
I'm sewing an ass on right now.
No, dad, no!
It smells like horses in here.
I'm gonna sew it.
If you sew an ass, everyone's gonna make fun of me.
The next day at cowboy school he walks in, "Oh, you got an ass on your pants?"
What the fuck are you doing?
Oh, fuck.
I hate my cowboy son.
Oh, man.
He's the worst.
Don't even get me started.
Don't even get me started on my cowboy kid.
My kid the kid?
Kid the kid.
hate my cowboy kid Trevor Trevor's I like that we're going full cowboy this
episode we have a cowboy list and we're just just intro part all cowboy yeah no I
don't have time for anything else anymore dude it's what I'm focused on I'm now I
have a goal to be a better cowboy than Pat because he decided to fucking steal
my shit you know what first come first serve that's what I say about a fucking
That's what the cowboy said to serve it to you. You're not gonna serve anything to me
I'm gonna come on you and then serve my comeback to you. How how would you do that?
Scrape it off make a demi-glaze
Fuckin serve my comeback to you nasty bitch. Have you been reading that book I sent you?
No, the cum recipes
What what? Oh, no that hasn't been delivered
I didn't I didn't actually buy it. I do have a I do have a surprise coming for Caleb. I did buy him something
Please don't be a gun or a bomb.
Who knows?
I mean if he mails you a gun that's good for you, not for him, right?
Like you use that against him.
Well no, he opens the package and then the gun shoots.
Yeah, the guy, he opens the package.
Joker style trap.
But he accidentally faces the package the wrong way so the gun shoots out the window
and kills Patrick who's watching with binoculars.
Yes.
It's a bear at 50 cal.
Yes dude. Oh I just thought of something. Okay here's a this is you can imagine there's like
somebody writing this article and posting it on Twitter okay. Okay. Here's why the Road Runner
was the best cowboy of all time. Whoa. Wow. Yeah. Do you have anything else for that I just thought
of that? Uh I guess he didn't capture anyone though. I would say Wile E. Coyote is closer
to a cowboy well no he's more of like a Wiley coyote is a bandit through and
through I yeah no no he's he's like dastardly though I think Wiley coyote
would Wiley coyote is definitely dastardly I think now that Pat has
decided to be the cowboy I may have to become dastardly pretty soon here yeah
yep you're gonna wear like a top hat and tie a woman to the train tracks that I
save I may have to become very dastardly sooner than you might think
dick dastardly no you could be like him you could drive a car with your little
dog no you're chick dastardly girl yeah yeah okay that's fine and sexy nothing
wrong with that fuck you that's right Patrick learned a new defense strategy
against insults I'm completely neutered right now yep that's right you fucking
bitch yeah why would I be ashamed of that
gay why would I be ashamed of that you're you're an ass so it's important
part of the body you balls are smalls yeah that's fine more room in my pants
you you're a human bathroom yeah okay it's most important room in the house
besides the kitchen you're a human kitchen no you're a shit sandwich on a
fuck burger all right you've got to feed people you're a whole fart yeah that's
fine I'm gonna sip you source of energy I'm gonna drink you up yeah okay good
I'll hydrate you that's fine why would I be ashamed of that be ashamed of what I
I just said I'm gonna fucking kill you. That's fine. I'll you'll feel fulfilled from kids
What mm-hmm? You'll have a goal. You'll set out you'll set your goal, and then you'll complete it. You lost the plot on this one
All right
I'm the I'm red thundered up. Yeah, I'm ready to do some cowboy insults. I drank I drank a Red Bull
earlier. The competitor. I drank a beautiful glass of water. I was in the
I was in the park earlier. I was at Maria Hernandez. I was skating and some dude
came up to me and he was like, "Yo, you think I got front 180 first try?" I was
like, "Yeah, sure man. Go ahead." And I like gave him my board and he handed me his
like phone his sandwich his drink his wallet I think you robbed him dude I
said I think you just that's an exchange and then he like he kept making like
excuses as to why he didn't want to do the front 180 and he was like shit my
grandma just died yeah he just kept talking to me like about his life yeah
about his life and then he was like man you guys are too much here skating that
ledge and he's like all right fine then he finally did it and just like fucked it
up so you robbed a guy and then he couldn't even do a trick well I that's
actually a good motivator though is if you if you're like here take all my shit
don't give it back unless I land well I dropped his phone I dropped his phone and
then he was like you dropped his phone yeah I dropped he like handed it he had
his phone inside of his wallet oh and then he handed it to me and then I
dropped the phone I was like oh shit sorry man he's like no that's fine it
doesn't even work anyway you bring it around you guys are too much you can spy
on people you hold the phone to your face and make it look like you're doing
something mm-hmm and then you can listen in that was it you know who that was
Patrick who was that that was Batman whoa he had a tracking device in that
wallet if you had taken off he would have fucked you up
Batman just baiting people to do crimes.
I'm glad I didn't.
He just has like a fucking fishing pole with a woman's purse on it.
Just waiting to beat some guy up.
He does do that, dude.
He always shows up there like, he shows like some guy will kill someone and then he shows up and he's like,
"Now I can get you."
You know?
Yeah.
Just kill everybody right away.
Everybody hold this dollar.
Got your ass, you're dead.
In Batman Returns, I watched that the other day.
he just like Tim Burton just didn't he just Batman straight-up kills dudes in
that movie he kills people in the Snyder cut dude it's so yeah everyone everyone
love as always like like like once a week there's the tweet that's like um
Batman was really rich but instead of using that money to invent socialism he
actually beat up an evil clown and saved the city so he's a bit of a fascist I
think but every yeah guys so annoying his parents died he's allowed to like beat
up a schizophrenic guy if he wants to. That's fine. Also, if I was rich I'd be just so much worse. Oh yeah? I'd be a full
serial killer if I was rich. I'd be completely, I would be as evil and and I would kill as many people as
possible before they stopped me. I would have like a chain of H.H. Holmes style like hotels all around
the country where I'm just fucking farming poor people. Just turn their bones into fucking gelatin.
Yeah, yeah, it's like when you make that like villager thing in Minecraft like the villager. Yeah
Just fucking burn them like I'm just it's just a McDonald's like meatpacking plant
And I'm passionate and I'd be involved like the Chipotle CEO
I'd be stopping by all the different chains
Just making sure they have the right fucking
blood quota and shit taking pictures and taking pictures in front of the Threshers and being like the CEO stopped by today to make
sure everything was just like a picture of like Caleb holding a guy by like his
shirt collar and his jeans throwing a guy into smiling yeah and then a picture
comes out of you on safari and you killed a hippo and then everyone gets
mad I cannot believe I'd be the most evil guy of all time oh my god I can't
believe that dr. genocide killed a lion this is and I would yeah I mean that
That would be why I wouldn't get in any trouble,
'cause I wouldn't pick a kind of person.
I would just kill anybody.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like, it wouldn't matter what they look like.
I'd just fucking kill.
I would kill people on the street for no reason at all.
- Well, if you throw a pile of money on them after their--
- Yeah, exactly. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
I paid him to do this.
- Here's what I would do, I'd pay for the funeral.
- Oh, okay. - That would be my move.
And people would be like, "Well, we can't be mad."
- Well, what if you own a funeral home,
and that's like, you own a chain of funeral homes?
I own a funeral home and I kill people there.
- Yeah.
- That might be a pretty good idea.
- What would you imagine if you're like an inventor, right?
And you invent a brand new, no you're not for this thing,
okay, 'cause wait, you're gonna be,
okay, but you're gonna be in this,
so just hang on for a second.
That's a terrible invention, not an invention.
- Wait, no, that's the cross.
- Let me say this, okay?
Imagine you're, what would you,
if you're a, you are an inventor
and you just invented a more efficient shredder for paper, right?
Yeah.
And then you get a knock on your door and Caleb comes in and he's wearing an evil tuxedo with
pointed shoulders like a JRPG boss and he says, "Hi, I'd like to buy your patent for
your shredder.
By the way, can you make it giant?"
Would you say yes or no?
I would say yes.
Well, how much help would you give me?
Well, you're not, that doesn't, Caleb, you're, well you're already, you wouldn't say yes
because it wouldn't make you're the one asking the question what if you could
say yes but there's like yes but then the guy would just be like what do you why
are you saying yes yeah exactly yes I will yes yeah that would be another one
of the evil things I do yes that'd be another one of the evil things I do as a
rich guy so just talk for people yeah yeah and then I'd be like what they said
it the do ventriloquism that's pretty evil
control I mean it's evil control that you take over somebody yeah you're you're
you're like making people think that has been frozen
you're making people you're making people think that a puppet is talking
you're tricking people Pat are you back hey what's going on can you hear me
yeah you there yeah okay you just cut out for a second oh I did yeah no I
I would basically run, I would do like a,
I would do like a,
Magic 8-Ball like every morning for like a different
like small town that I would just fucking wipe out.
Yeah.
Yeah, with like something really fucked up,
like maybe like a monster truck.
Yeah.
And that's like what I would do is I just like run over
shit with a monster truck.
I'd kill anything.
You could have like a dart board that looks like the earth
and like where a dart hits,
like maybe it blows up or something.
Yeah, I just go, I just bring like a flamethrower
and just start fucking lighting California on fire.
That's like what I would do during the summer.
During the winter, I'd probably like fuck a penguin.
- It wouldn't take much to like set a wildfire
in California.
- Well, I'm gonna bring them much, tell you that much.
Yeah, I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna overdo everything, dude.
I'm gonna replace water with gasoline.
- You're not just gonna smoke a cigarette in the woods?
- No, dude, I'm gonna smoke a--
- Did you ever, when you were like 14,
well, Caleb, you smoked cigs when you were like 15, right?
No, no I was not a cig smoker until like college.
Well I used to get really scared that like I would steal like my mom's
cigarettes and then go into the woods and then I would put them out like in the
woods but then I would get really scared that like a forest fire would start.
I mean that's fair. That's a good instinct to have. That's how they happen.
See that's the kind of instinct that I would just completely lose if I got I
I don't know, $10,000.
- That's a common teenage smoker fear.
Starting a forest fire.
- You guys are telling me you wouldn't become super villains?
- I wouldn't become a super villain,
I'd become a superhero.
- I wouldn't even become,
super villains always want like fucking,
like recycling to happen or some gay shit.
I just wanna murder. - I would do something like that.
I would do something like that,
but I would do it on a much smaller scale.
I wouldn't be, I would be like,
I would be like one of those rich people
who just kind of like doesn't have a job
and just lives in a big house.
I'd be like, it is anybody who crosses my path I will kill.
I'd be the most evil.
But I'm not gonna go out of my way.
You know, if I see like somebody walking down the street
that my house is on, they're dead.
But.
Nice.
You know, just kind of like a Bermuda Triangle,
but just for my line of sight.
That's pretty good too.
I would be like, I'd be like, eat human hair.
I'd be the most evil subway manager of all time.
If you were rich.
Just running a really horrible subway.
Yep.
Just buying a subway franchise.
I would schedule people on their birthday.
but also like replacing all the meat with meat that looks exactly the same but it's like
made out of Cooper's plastic or something.
Yeah, you make the meatball sub out of the tuna sandwich.
And you just have enough money to make any negative review disappear like the CEO can't
even come visit.
Like you're just completely.
Oh man.
I would make people come in on their day off.
You buy the copyright for Subway so you have a Subway restaurant that's technically not
part of the chain so you can do whatever you want.
Exactly.
try and blackmail the subway CEO with the Jared Fogle info even if it's already public
it's like oh well if you try to shut me down I'll let something...
your employee did this
yeah I'll let my loose lips sink ships I'll say that much
that's right you made all this public now I can destroy you
we actually took a pretty big hit already I don't know why you're trying to bring this back up
up yeah I would destroy them all right cowboy insults on best - insults calm
slash cowboy - insults check it out you know usually give out the link but I
have to say such a simple this one we were we asked you guys to get a lot of
hype going for this one and I have to say I saw absolutely zero yep I think
you guys I don't say this often and I like you I've probably I'm probably the
nicest one on the show but I'm extremely disappointed in every single one of you.
I say this very often but you guys are subhuman.
Mm-hmm yeah. See I I would never say that but right now I'm I'm thinking it.
What's this the fans being absolute dog shit? Yeah must be a day that ends in Y.
If I ever saw any of you guys in real life like if you came up to me or
anything I would treat you like a dog with its legs stuck in a bear trap. I
would execute you on the spot.
- Yeah, because of this, and you would know why.
You would know why we were doing it,
and it's because you didn't do enough.
- You know, and as you're bleeding out,
I'm gonna look into your eyes and I'm gonna say,
"Ugh, your mustache has the smell
"a mildewed saddle blanket would have
"if it rides 300 miles in August
"on the back of a sore horse."
- Oh, shit! - That's right.
- No! - These are all things
we would say to you now,
'cause you didn't do what we told you.
- Wait, let me do the intro.
Yeah, read the intro.
Cowboys are usually known to have heavy cuss words.
So if you are going against a cowboy, it is best to have your
game up so you would not land a pratfall while lashing out at
your opponent.
I'm here to help you get back at your cowboy rivals.
You can cut hard, harsh, and deep at cowboys using simple and
yet classy insults on them and they are going to remember it
forever because of how deep they were cut.
right wow that's really nice oh yeah I mean I mean it's just a useful resource
for people you know cuz like how often do you go up against a cowboy one or two
times a week right depending on what part of the country you live in exactly I
mean if you're in Arizona or New Mexico I mean it's probably like three or four
times a month yeah and New York once a day mm-hmm easy dude and he's naked -
Times Square yep I'm always having a battle that naked
cowboy. Put on some fucking clothes! Yeah. You vomit. Dude, the guy dressed as Woody from
Toy Story that stands out on Hollywood Boulevard is gonna feel my wrath. Yeah, I'm gonna catch
him lacking. He is an op and he will be caught lacking by me. Alright, so Cam already did
number one let's keep it let's keep it going dude all right ready here I need
somebody to fucking just think about the fence damn it you're ugly as a burnt
boot mm-hmm that's what that's what Caleb would say to you yeah so don't
fuck with me that's kind of the and that's ugly that's wrong I would love
for like one of those like like a celebrity scandal or like somebody was
mean to their wife or whatever they leak all the text messages and it's this
shit you're as ugly as a burnt boot. John Wayne's text messages to his mistress have been leaked.
You're ugly as a burnt boot. That is a cowboy's least favorite thing too, a burnt boot. That's
pretty bad. Yeah, it doesn't feel good on your foot dude. Cowboys like raw boots. Here's
a raw boot here's another here's another insult here you will have to chew the
water before you can swallow it because it is too thick however it darn good
follow this with making an ugly face
this is more of an insult towards whatever water probably a horse yeah
yeah probably a horse that you led to water but no then it's saying the water is good
it's like they say you have to chew the water but the problem is not well they're saying
you have to chew the water but the water is good like it's the problem is not with the
water it's you yeah why is why do you have to chew the water because it is too thick why
are you getting this thick water from? The H3O. Thicket? You're drinking thicket? Is that
like a cowboy? Did cowboys come up with thicket? Well they're constantly falling
in thicket bushes. Cowboy Mio. Good point. Cowboy Mio just thickens up the water. Tobacco Mio.
Alright this one's actually pretty, this one's pretty fire dude. Yeah. I'm pretty
sure your family tree was definitely a shrub. Wow. That's right. Whatever that means. I'm
pretty sure shrubs have a pretty big... You got a small family, pal. You're not that old.
You don't have that many ancestors. You're a new kind of person, and you only started
a couple decades ago. You got parents and you got grandparents and it ends there somehow.
They never had anybody past that.
Yeah, your grandparents were orphans.
Yep.
Grandparents dropped off by the store.
Nobody had no brothers nor sisters neither.
Your family tree is just a single V. There's like five guys.
And that was your family tree, you lowdown son of a bitch.
Here's another one.
Well, when you wanna unload and clean your gun, he ain't any fit to shoot at.
Forget it, man.
That seems like it's a line from a movie.
It's like a MF Doom rap.
Yeah, it rhymes, too.
Hey, Caleb.
What?
There's definitely nothing under your hat except hair.
Uh, this guy doesn't have a hat or hair.
I have neither. What do I have, then?
Headphones.
That's right.
That's fucking right, dude.
A hog knows more about a hip pocket in a bathing suit than you know about anything.
There's a lot of hog insulars too, back to back.
Basically a hog was the stupidest thing you could be back then.
You know way less than a hog knows a side saddle.
And a hip pocket in a bathing suit is something so obvious that you would--
Something everybody knows about.
Even a hog you think would know about it, but nope.
No.
mean that's it really was just like that was the that was the dumbest guy that
you knew was an actual fucking hog back yeah hang out with I was your but you're
you're like stupidest friend I mean the town like towns back then were like 15
people so it's like it's so you can only go so long for you have to like be like
well I need a new friend group I might as well hang out with like this guy's
hogs yeah everybody had that that one hog from their hometown god forbid your
last name was hog that would have been really really bad mm-hmm yeah it was
back then whatever your last name is that's what you are yeah you know with
like you know Cooper they make barrels or whatever Smith they're blacksmith hog
you're a hog mm-hmm such a good point I know we're moving to a podcast where we
make points now mm-hmm just so you guys know it's really bombs yeah this is my
- It's a podcast about truth.
- Not even necessarily truth,
but just kind of stuff you hear and you go, hmm.
And that is--
- Interesting. - Intriguing.
- We're hearing intrigue more than entertain nowadays.
- Exactly, yeah.
- You know way less than a hog knows a side saddle.
- Okay, so that's kind of repeating the same thing
as earlier, I read that.
- A hog-- - I read that one.
I read that one while you guys were talking
they didn't realize. I'm confused by what you're trying to say right now. Never mind.
Yeah you're basically acting a hog right now. Oh no. Actin' a hog. A hog probably knows
about a side saddle. Yeah. Hogs are actually, here's the fucked up part dude.
A hog is so much smarter than a dog or a frog. He's one of the smartest hog
animals. Absolutely. And they're pretending like hogs know nothing. Hogs
actually have an extreme emotional intelligence. True. They're I think
think comparable in like intelligence wise to like a two or three year old
human being absolutely and that's intriguing yeah yeah so I don't know why
they keep because they can speak they can you know what I'm gonna read I'll
rewrite this I would say hogs is punching down in a huge way here's what
I'm gonna say I say we rewrite this insult it's and it to be like this okay
you know you know way less than a stupid person knows about knowledge that's
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
Because that makes it more sense.
I could see a cowboy saying that.
Because now we also, now we kind of have a framework that on which you could lay almost
anything to make a cowboy insult.
Absolutely.
Which is you know less than X about, that does not know about Y, knows about Y.
Yeah, and X and Y.
X and Y.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
So, you could say like, you know, you know.
And I mean, if you're looking for something fascinating, X and Y, those are also used in
algebra.
Yep.
Now we're kind of turning into a mathematical formula
about how to make a cowboy insult.
You could do, I mean like, all right,
you could say, you know less than about anything
than a chair knows about standing up.
Right, yeah.
Like there's one, you know?
I mean you can just look around.
You know less about anything than guacamole
knows about being red.
Oh, that's pretty good.
can just kind of look around look what's around you and kind of just make it from
there like like you could do like you know you know less than a hat knows
about water bottle yeah it's easy yeah less about than a
french fry knows it's knows what day of the week it is fucking idiot ass cowboy
see that's actually nothing the ad at the end
cowboy with the fucking beefy haircut get a line up come correct when you're
popping off with the saloon my boy at the saloon tonight spinning all night
long come through you know way less than Michael knows about David just you guys
in the room. Yeah, see if you know, if those are two guys that don't know each other and
they're in the room that works too. Michael, meet David. See and they already know more
about each other than you know about anything so that's kind of the point I
was making as in this cowboy voice. Look, they're fast friends. Look at them. Look, I mean
they're already exchanging numbers. You know less than Superman knows about
spider-man they're from different superhero universes exactly yeah yeah
see that's I don't know about each pretty much anything you can follow along at
home you do your own sort of mad libs thing that we got going on yeah don't
tell them to us cuz we're mad at you yep yeah cuz we're also pissed about the
lack of yeah we're still we're still so mad at you yeah I am I I'll forgive you
I'll forgive you in a week but until then if you hype up the next episode to the
point that we want yep all right here's another one yeah forget him I just
realized that he could not even drive nails into a snowbank I just realized
this yeah you know forget that guy you know what I just realized randomly right
now like right now it couldn't put a nail in us in snow I just realized it's a good
way to start an insult because it misdirects you right yeah you don't you
don't expect an insult to come after you expect a fact or something yeah you
expect them to just be like I just realized I don't like this guy or so I
just realized I left the fire on back at home I just realized that a fire truck
ain't blue and this guy knows less about what a fire truck could know about setting a fire.
Yep. And the cowboy, I mean that's like some... Cowboys like opposites. That's something when
it comes to cowboy insults. That's true, yeah. It's true. Let's see. For example,
I am pretty certain that you cannot tell wild honey from dung. That's great on a blind guy.
That's like... Yeah. Yeah. Like if you're battling a blind cowboy. That's also good
if there's someone nearby who has like really viscous like clear ish like
yellow poop for example a bee a bee is a good example yeah honey is just bee poop
yeah so really they're not that different so that's very showing his
lack of scientific knowledge you know
your face is as puckered as wet sheepskin would be in front of a hot
fire bite that see this introduces a catchphrase element where at the end you
would just say bite that bite that is a good Danny that's a really good
catchphrase I guess yeah that's biting Danny McClintock you don't want to you
I'm telling you you don't want to fuck it you don't want to miss with that you
don't want to enter a word duel with him that's what they called rap battles back
then yeah yeah yeah well me as the judge I couldn't quite make out what either one
of them just saying they said I'm dead just about the same time but seeing all
this one yet another draw that's our 20th in a row here's a really I couldn't
tell exactly what they were rapping but seeing as Slim's dead and old Joe's still
staying with the smoking gun this next one is really really something a popcorn on
fire has more calm than you would ever have Wow I mean before the right for the
throat I'm yeah fuck before the invention of the microwave I mean I guess
you didn't throw popcorn on fire huh yeah also I mean telling a cowboy that he's
not calm right yeah you got shaky hands partner yeah oh I guess that makes sense
you're freaking out you're bugging you suffer from anxiety
exciter we have a support group if you want to if you'd like to mosey on up
there here's one we meet every weekend you are you know what was sick you are
so ugly that you could back a buzzard right off a gut wagon what's a gut wagon
wagon full of guts oh it is a wagon full of guts rephrase that into a cowboy
insult right now because I'm not accepting a regular insult your guts
just about a gut wagons worth a waste you no good what
woppy willow
retry that
you're just about as
that is a whole is a
had handbag you
you carry home
rephrase that again your your good must need we don't have any idea yet
not just throwing it out here in the middle fee mario
it's a good idea to do it
you missed in my ear
you know what he did but i think the alliteration in that one
I think that's a big thing with cowboy insults too is alliteration.
Yeah, absolutely.
Like for this one here has some good alliteration.
Even if you had as many as three throws, that's the alliteration, you cannot hit the ground
with your hat.
Wow.
What does that mean?
It means you can't hoop, dude.
No, it means you have an infinite throw.
This guy can't hit three throws.
You could throw the hat out of orbit right away.
True.
every time you have a zero gravity hat mm-hmm damn yeah and it just keeps on
flying yeah you know what it means it means you live in space no ground space
cowboy oh shit oh shit oh my gosh I should make a TV show out of that mm-hmm
this is good you know what it means jazz this next one is good the one after that
I think is my favorite one so far me too section is uh you you have to sneak up
on a dipper just to get a drink of water only because of your ugliness
why do you have to sneak up on the dipper?
because you're so ugly
like a spoon?
I think a dipper is like a well type thing
oh yeah the
yeah and you have to sneak up on it because it would run away because you're ugly
mm-hmm
Pat read this next one for us
alright
I think you're gonna like this one
the best one so far
you are so mean
*laughter*
Just giving up dude.
Yeah.
Come on.
That's it.
I mean, how is that going to be effective towards a cold-blooded cowpoke?
Yeah, that's a comeback is what that is.
Yeah, exactly.
That's a finisher.
Yeah, roasted.
You are so mean.
Just destroyed.
Bodied.
Here, we have another set of two here.
These next two kind of go together, I feel like.
Okay.
sure you would give the rattler the first bite if you were in a fight with it.
Okay. The rattler is just a guy that lived in the town. Yeah. He's a guy who ran
around with two maracas and... And then the other one kind of copying that
one. "You are so mean that you could dine in the same dish with a snake." See that
also just says "you are so mean" at the beginning. Why? A cowboy's supposed to be
mean dude yeah I don't get this angle well that's what well that's the kind of
insult that doesn't hurt them like on the surface but they go home and they
think about that around the fire I changed my ways maybe I'm just a mean
guy yeah fuck maybe I should just be a hog
here's a you should be hired as a scarecrows in farms see that one's pretty
good yeah exactly you're so fat that you you could be multiple scarecrows in
multiple farms yeah across the state from each other just just stretch so wide you
covered farms from sea to shining sea. There's so many of you that you could be
multiple scarecrows. This is another kind of simple short sweet one.
You are crooked. I really like this next one too, another crooked one. Yeah. With
how crooked you are you could swallow nails and spit corkscrews. Errwha. That's what I used to say.
it's old English for you. Yeah it says ERW at the end of that one. He had a nerve to say the beans
was deceitful because they would talk behind your back. Fuck I hate the beans. Who are the beans?
Fuck dude you know the beans. Because the beans make you fart dude that you talk behind your back. The beans is the powers of the beans.
Here's the next the next one is is also bean themed. Okay. Even a beans would be more modest
honest than you god damn it I hate the beans oh man a bug dude not a beans do
when you're a cat when your cowboy fucking making you're doing your beat
and you see the beans dude fucking six shots straight that's right yeah it's on
site when I see the beans that cowboy moved with the beans yeah the next one
is really good it is good you're gonna read it well you're the one who said it
why would I go to hell with your shenanigans see this is like if you know
a prankster cowboy yeah you know yeah man that was a big problem back in the
day stop putting snakes in my peanut brittle
hell with your shenanigans yeah that was actually a really big problem I know
that you're gonna put snakes in anything dude I know that your fingers not really
coming off I know that that's just your thumb I know that pencil late made a
rubber which your shenanigans and go to hell you don't have my nose my my nose
stands square on my face I could smell you from a mile away yeah okay this one
next one um boy everyone little say the person's name is as shy of brains just
as much as a buffalo would with feathers so true this is kind of back to the other
the formula we developed also but I mean a buffalo could have feathers I don't
yeah they got wings seen yeah yeah yo that's some real shit facts Cameron's
spitting facts facts once again from cam dog I don't know what this next one means
shame on you you I bet you could not even track a bed wagon it's a wagon for beds I
guess it's a wagon that's very easy to track yeah yeah it's probably a wagon
that's like painted red what is this next one just as a terrapin is of feathers
you are as shy of brains back to the feathers okay okay yeah I'm a terrapin
now yeah okay terrapin is a station it's a turtle they they once needed to throw a
diamond hitch just to keep him in the saddle yeah that is how fat he is that
one includes a second line that you can turn and say if there's someone standing
next to you yeah which the other insults don't usually do so that's nice which is
true you'd have it if you have your deputy with you exactly yeah so you could
say the insult and then you can turn and say yeah that's because he's stupid yeah
Yeah, that's 'cause of how fat he is.
That's why I said all that crap.
That's why I'm being mean.
Here in the wild west.
That's why I'm being mean to him.
Yeah.
Even molasses would not run down your legs because of your laziness.
It'd just stick in your butt.
That's the molasses that's lazy, not you.
Yeah, that's exactly.
Here's one.
How lazy is this fucking molasses?
"The way you grit your teeth, one would think that you are capable to biting sights off a six-gun."
Oh, I thought it was, uh...
And then the deputy would be like, "Yeah! Yeah, that's because of how the way he grits his teeth."
"He's got bad... teeth or some..."
"He's got no job in his sleep."
I don't know what the insult is supposed to be saying here.
"Honestly, these cowboy insults are kinda bad."
There's, uh...
I just moved to the wild west and I don't quite understand these yet. I'm from Maine.
So I just realized that the ones we were all just reading are under the heading "the best
cowboy insults" so those are all the best ones and then there's a second heading that's
even more cowboy insults. So those were all the good ones. These ones...
Yeah, of course they were.
Are not as good.
So these are the kind of medium cowboy insults. Alright.
are a little more poetic yeah yeah a little more situational you know what I
think I kind of like the from just looking at these ones I think I kind of
like these ones better these are the British villain who lives in the West
for some reason and is like an oil baron yeah why are you not as crooked as the
snake would be in a cactus path see that makes sense yeah would it shock you to
realize that your brain cavity would not make a drinking cup for canary birds I
I bet it would not because you already know.
Ha ha.
That's actually crazy how much better that works.
I know.
These ones are good.
These are good in that voice.
I would bet your cows reason better than you.
See, these are words a cowboy would just never fucking use.
Right, absolutely.
Reason, brain cavity.
Right.
No way, dude.
Cowboys are stupid.
how you think I fear your cows control you?
I fear your cows control you.
Is it me or does someone moo around here?
Okay so whoever...
Wait these are all cows!
It is no surprising if you have behaved like cows.
You eat and sleep with them.
the next one they accidentally included. They were just hanging out with a guy in a huge
like field full of cows and they were just writing down everything he said and they accidentally
wrote this one down instead of an insult. "Whoa, careful, a cow is passing."
Dude, these are way better. What the fuck? Yeah, really good.
These are sca- Alright, I'm going to try one in a cowboy accent. I do think we need to at
at least try to do on a cowboy accent mm-hmm I'm sure your cows reduced in
number by one return to them well now let's compare it right okay yeah okay I'll
do it and down do it in the I am sure cows reduced in number by one return to
them see okay now I'm confused maybe try Jamaican okay whoa I am sure your cows
reduce the number of them seeing like this next one mentions evolution a cow
cowboy can't this one boy is never heard of evolution it also didn't believe it
this could you could also do these a nerd like you could do it like this
Whoever thought evolution could not go the other way around just needs to meet you and
think otherwise.
Damn.
The other way around?
So you went this, that's if you're talking to like a newt.
You know?
Yeah, if you're talking to an amoeba or something.
That's really good.
Yeah, a very like simple kind of water based creature.
You could say that one too.
You say it wrapped all the way back around.
You went all the way to alien and then you came back around.
If you're a nerd and you're talking to a water creature, just keep that one in the back of
your head.
I wonder if they have a nerd insults on this website.
We'll have to come back to this website.
This is the best insults.
I mean, who would have thought?
Come on, we gotta finish it out here.
Cows must think you are stupid.
I can see a cowboy saying that one though.
That's true.
Cows must think you're stupid.
That is good.
Someone bathes in dung.
is bass it's not bass it's bass. Some of them be baffin' and dung. Is it me or does it smell
like cows around here? Something is totally cow. They were hanging out with the British guy who was
seeing cows for the first time. You're a cowboy right? Yes I am. Yes I love cows.
I have this assignment for WordPress and I need to finish it.
Hi I'm a blogger I work for wordpress.com just want to get some cowboy insults out
of you. You said cow insults yes? Yeah cowboy insults. Your utters are as short as can be.
Yeah that works that's a cowboy insult we'll take that. Yeah it's like a boy cow.
one of those those those BuzzFeed videos that's like like Pakistani tribesmen try
monster energy for the first time but it's like a British fop sees a cow for
the first time and he's just sitting there just thinks it's a guy they're
going even your cows might wonder how you managed to own them this last one is the
same as the the one you just read no it's not I bet your cows control
themselves yeah that's like that's a good one though that's just that's kind of I
would say that's more of a of a compliment that's like saying you have
smart cows your cows are so smart and you've raised some of the smartest cows
you asshole you don't want smart cows and then you turn around and talk to
your deputy yeah I said that cuz he had smart cows and everybody goes yeah good
Right, good work boss.
Yeah, good one boss.
Well, back to dirt farming.
Alright, that's the end of cowboy insults.
Again, we're bummed out that there was no hype.
Yeah, and it's all your fault.
You're going to eat your words when you listen to this one.
Fuck you.
Absolutely, fuck you.
Bye.
Hi, this is Cameron on my
shitty, uh
Headphone mic. I found the squirtoon thing. So i'm putting it at the end
Fuck you
Too late now. Yeah, you chucky cheese when you laugh dude, i'm gonna squirt on you
You're gonna get squirted on oh i'm fucking squirting
Yeah, i'm squirting sam elliott
Oh, fuck, I'm about to squirt.
Oh, fuck.
Goddamn, I'm about to squirt.
You see, there's two types of people in this world.
There's them that squirts and them that gets squirted.
That's right.
Do you have a target for me to squirt on?
Oh, so I can squirt 300 yards out.
I reckon I must be your new neighbor.
I wanted to know if you wanted to see me squirt in your front yard.
'Cause I'm gonna be doing it for about 15 minutes.
Now, I reckon I lift an old squit-er-squit-oon.
squirtoon. squirtoon. squirtoon. you bust open the double saloon doors you cock your leg
and you squirt directly into a bucket. well peers i done ruined your squirtoon here take
this three dollar bill go buy you a new one. good bout cover it. fuck. squirtoon. i think
I left my squirtoon in your house.
Hey, Suzy, this is awkward, but I was over for dinner a couple nights ago.
You made the Trader Joe's soy-yaki chicken.
Yeah, I think I maybe left my squirtoon there in the powder room.
You wouldn't mind mailing it back?
Yeah, I reckon I'm your new neighbor.
I was actually, before you guys moved in, I was using your apartment for target practice
and I think I left a stray squirtoon on your wall.
I don't know if you got rid of it or anything, I rustled through your dumpster for a while,
but all I found were snacks.
(laughing)