You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts are the best.
Crap monster.
Bird.
Hello everybody.
What was that?
Yeah, what was that?
That was my British voice.
Hello everybody.
I don't know if that's...
How are you doing today?
Wow, dude, you sound like a king.
I am Hagrid.
Hagrid doesn't sound like that.
Oh, well, Hagrid does.
Hagrid sounds like this.
Welcome to Harry's.
Hand me my iPad.
I wanna play Flappy Bird.
You know what? You know what they never
really talk about in Harry Potter
but it's like, uh...
They don't touch on it.
on that it's like the 80s it's the 80s really oh yeah I guess 90s in those
movies dude that'd be so funny if they did those like they do all those
fucking like like 80s worship like what they put gave everybody the fucking 80s
hairdos and everything yeah yeah that'd be sick in the Voldemort with the like
a oh dude new wave stardust shit new wave Voldemort that would be sick he's so cool
Snape is kind of new wave yeah Snape is goth Snape is definitely a goth Snape
would be listening to fucking bella lugosi's dead in his room by himself
yeah
he'd be listening to albus dumbledore's dead
sorry for the spoilers everybody who's listening
albus dumbledore's dead
doesn't really work that well
no it doesn't really work at all wait albus dumbledore's dead?
yes
what? the actor who plays him died
but he's still alive
i haven't finished the movies
what he got he got killed i said i said sorry for the spoiler was it the i
thought you were spoiling i thought you were spoiling that's the guy
was dead yeah i thought you were spoiling that the actor died the actor
dead i think that's always a brave thing
when there's when there's if there's eight books and you're making the
first or second movie casting an 100 year old man
yeah in a role i mean like it'll be fine dude oh yeah he'll survive
What, it would probably take us what?
Six months to make the next eight movies?
Dude, they put, they put...
Jude Law played him in the like, spin-off thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Albus Dumbledore is also a guy.
It's gay sex.
In Fantastic Beasts, he was played by
Jude Law and Toby Regbo.
[Laughter]
Oh, Toby Regbo!
Oh, I love you, Regbo.
Toby Regbo!
Would you like to come on my sailboat?
sailboat he's got a sailboat Tony's got a sailboat oh Tony right movies dude what
the fuck is Tony expensive Tony Redboe sailboat come on my submarine
it's yellow would you guys buy a submarine if you're insanely rich oh no
submarine is a submarine is the number one I don't go underwater snow submarine
submarine is submarine is the vehicle equivalent of having like a compound
Yeah, that's where you do you do fucked up shit on a submarine if you're like a rich person or the submarine like yeah
You let the pressure out and your eyeballs pop. That's what you do. Do you go downstairs? That's what I call the ocean
Fucking watch porn down there. Yeah, big flat-screen. You think they have fucking internet down there, dude
You're not you're not watching anything. Have you ever gonna have to look out the window and
And have you ever heard of a water satellite?
No, no, I just invented it and I'm think I'm quitting the podcast to become an inventor
You do this every other
Way to become an inventor so off but this is this might be my best invention yet
I can come up with more inventions than you what?
We're never gonna make it the space right Mars is just not happening
I think you're gonna make it alright. I put satellites in this in the fucking space sphere
I can come up with like 10 inventions right now, ready?
Okay?
Okay.
10 inventions in 10 seconds.
USB to HDMI, HDMI to USB, HDMI to aux cable, aux cable to USB, USB to aux cable, HDMI to
Roku, Roku to USB, USB Roku stick, HDMI stick, Roku audio stick, aux, auxiliary audio stick,
cable stick, stable cable stick, flash drive.
Stable cable stick?
Stable cable stick.
a
It's called croutons.
No that's diced toast.
No.
Yes.
Well.
No that's called stuffing.
No that's crumbed bread.
You guys are wrong.
Diced bread is going to be the new thing.
Diced bread is stuffing.
Instead of making a sandwich with two slices you can make a sandwich with four cubes on
each side.
Or six.
What?
No.
Four cubes on each side?
Six.
Then you have a hole.
That's a donut.
Six cubes.
Okay.
six cubes but of diced bread around it why not go i hate i hate it like a
ruby cube let me just fucking interrupt caleb here yeah i'm off your side i was
on your side now i'm off your side because i hate this what wait what do you
hate diced bread sounds like somebody's jealous of the inventor i'm not jealous
you're starting an inventor's got a real got a real thomas edison over here i'll
say yeah gonna be just like buddy ever read the oatmeal comics I have this is
gonna be just like when fucking the phonograph in the wax cylinders I'm
gonna make something even better that's never gonna catch on they should let
Ta-Nehisi Coates read the open sliced sliced waxed cylinder okay hold up a
slice sliced phonograph infinity candle so now okay you want me to keep going
what about how about okay here we go wedding necklace it's like a wedding
ring bigger instead of breast implants breast transplants okay have you can buy
somebody else's breasts and have them put on you a video game controller that's
free got it are you putting are you are you fucking filing patents on these right
now are you serious are you fucking filing a patent about my breast
idea okay here okay no go ahead no okay if you're not all right I have another
invention and I hope nobody steals this okay I hope nobody tries to file a
patent on this right now the terrorism machine what was all that clicking
Patrick is there did someone just knock on your door
Oh open up I think I think the government might be angry at you for
I don't think anyone's there.
Did somebody in here file a terrorism patent machine thing?
SHUT UP!
SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
Wow.
I don't have to shut up, I'm the cops.
SHUT UP!
Alright, alright, I guess I'll shut up a little bit.
Are you busy?
Alright, I'm just gonna go.
Can I use your bathroom?
Yes!
Thanks man, you're a good guy despite all this terrorism machine bullcrap.
Don't!
Shut up!
You're actually a pretty good guy.
I'm not!
Shut up!
You have a very quiet yell Patrick.
It's really...
Well I'm not yelling or anything.
I'm not talking to anybody right now.
Oh, so I'm nobody now, huh?
Shut the fuck up!
I'm trying to tell that what about last night was like nobody then I didn't file any fucking patents or anything you filed them
Stop, you're gonna blow my cover. Listen, you're gonna go to jail, but probably not now. Yeah, i'm not gonna go to we're gonna talk about this
Usb netflix cable stick that's not gonna work. That's a roku sticker an amazon fire roku to netflix cable
Okay
that noise? Maka! Booo! That's actually pretty good! Dude, you can watch Breaking Bad on your
Netflix, Roku. That'd be pretty swag. Oh my god. How about Hulu Plus Plus Plus? What about
Hulu to Disney? Disney. Pipeline. The Hulu to Disney. Disney minus. Just the Simpsons.
Disney minus is pretty good. Disney minus, Just the Simpsons. That's all it is. Disney
flash drive to cable. I don't want all this WandaVision crap. I don't want all this. I
I don't want to watch some--
- Too much coffee.
I can't pay attention to fucking anything right now.
- You have ADHD, it's on your diagnosis sheets.
- On your forehead, it's written out on your forehead.
- Yeah, I don't think drinking this much coffee
was a good idea.
- It'll be okay.
- I did get peer pressured by Caleb
to drink another thing of cold brew.
- If you--
(laughing)
- Before we recorded.
- Well you never said it was another.
You just said, "A cold brew."
And I said, "Hey, you know what, sure."
Couldn't hurt.
- It's true.
- Sure it's good to have a little juice in the tank.
Yeah. Nothing wrong with that.
Oh, fuck. I just drank a 50 million gallon Red Bull.
I'm ready to record my job. Yeah, all I need is delicious water to keep
me going, to give me the energy I need. I drank too much earlier today and now that
I've had this, I'm like, I can't even sit still.
Yeah, you can do jumping jacks during the episode if you need to.
Yeah? That's fine, yeah.
I don't mind. I don't have my fingerboards here. I would
have started... Thank Christ, dude.
I would have started skating. Have you guys ever known anybody who just
can't drink normal water.
My brother's ex-girlfriend just like would not drink normal water.
She said that it had a bad taste.
That's I mean that really...
That's bold.
That's bold to challenge God like that.
I think that like because I quit smoking weed my brain has been going into overdrive to
give me the most like lame thoughts possible to make up for it.
But I was just thinking about that like yo like the world we live in right now is low-key
like a cyberpunk dystopia.
But like people who won't drink normal water that's absolutely something you would fucking
read in yeah and like a silent punk book or so it's like the most stupid it's like
you know it has to be flavored like a made-up watermelon or else I won't drink it.
This girl she would like it wasn't that she wouldn't drink it is that she could
not drink it she would like want to vomit if she had a sip of water that
didn't have Mio in it. That's literally that's just that's insane. Dude in the next
in the in the next Bible that's gonna be like the sin that made God fucking wipe the earth clean.
like Sodom and Gomorrah. That's like insane. Like I can only drink Sprite and beer or Mio.
We're living in Sodom and Gomorrah. Yeah you are. Your house. It's mostly Sodom. I'm gonna
Sodom you tomorrow. That's right. Pull up. I'm gonna pull you down. Pull your shit down.
your pants down and sodom you till tomorrow come on don't say that why
cuz it's nasty you like nasty crap dude I saw you eating trash out of a fucking
booger bin didn't see me that's what I call the trash good invention yeah but
oh dude I need a booger bin I don't remember the last 10 minutes in a month
that's okay you don't have to you don't have to say that one we're about living
in the moment but okay I that I have been thinking about like the next person who
moves into this house just like finding my boogers like in the oven yeah I'm
being like wow that's that's guy must have been a monster. That's tasty! Hello! I'm not cooking them to eat them.
I just sometimes I'll fucking pick a booger and I'm like you know what it's my own house I'll put it
wherever I want the person moving into your house loves eating boogers. Oh if booger bill moves in.
then booger bill that's bad news dude booger bill for big booger bill booger
bill tootin this pickin this booger eater in the beast in the beast that's the
booger east okay yeah so you didn't understand that smell some nuggets in
the oven in here here's a question is your boogers ever smelled have your
boogers has your boogers ever smelled?
You put one finger up to like a cartoon professor when you asked that?
But I pose this question to you.
Has your boogers ever smelled?
Hmm?
What say you?
I meant to say this in a normal, smart-sounding way.
Yeah, and you said, "Has your boogers ever smelled?"
Like a cabbage, a fucking garbage pail kid in a lab coat asking you that.
How's your boogers ever smell?
Um, but have you ever been like like I I think
Covid definitely made me realize this
But like wearing like a mask and then you're like sweating and then you put the mask back on and then just like there's a smell
In your nose, but you don't know what it is
That's your breath. No, then you blow your nose you blow your nose and then the smell goes away
I don't think my boogers have ever smelled. I don't think stinky boogers my if any if if something
Well, I mean boogers could smell.
Well, I mean, yeah, but here's the thing about boogers.
I don't think that they could because they're in your nose all the time.
It's like, it's like you don't really taste air that much.
Yeah, but maybe they smell and we don't know.
No, but they pick up maybe things that you smell.
So if you're sitting around fucking huffing pasta carbonara all day,
you might have some tasty boogers.
But if you're sitting with a mask on your damn face,
this is why I don't wear one,
with a mask on your damn face just fucking breathing breakfast breath
into your damn booger ball,
I mean, you know, I just went for the other B word there, you know, it's kind of a stretch.
It happens.
But the boogers are gonna smell like fucking dog shit.
Yeah.
I don't know.
If you want a delicious...
Maybe it's a different smell.
Maybe it's a different smell that I was smelling, but it's like...
Maybe it's their mask.
If you want delicious boogers, you gotta smell something good.
I don't know.
Maybe it's like nose sweat that I'm smelling.
Could be.
You think nose sweat?
Here, I will say this.
about once a month. I get a sweaty nose. I get a very sweaty nose. I've seen your sweaty
nose. I can vouch for that. His nose gets damn sweaty. Oh dude, trust me. Trust me,
my nose is like a fucking swamp. That's why you have such a thin, fit nose. Do I have
a thin... I've never really like analyzed my face. Alright, let's do it. I need a protractor.
Yep
It's there's certainly angles going on here. Yeah, and I don't know
angles different round parts shapes hairs are above the eyes
Several teeth did several holes in the in different points on the my my eyebrows are very big
I will say I do have big eyebrows. I got some fucking Peter Gallagher shit going on. Yep. I think that's his name
Once a month my nose will start exuding a stench that smells like a tire.
I was just talking about this.
Wait, really?
That's what I was trying to describe.
That's what I was trying to fucking describe.
No, no, no, this is not a nose sweat. My nose will not sweat. It just smells insane.
You're the one who just said your nose couldn't smell.
The outside of my nose starts smelling like...
How do you know it's the outside of your nose?
Because Jana has smelled the inside of my nose
and the outside of my nose
and it's the outside of my nose that smells like that.
Maybe I'm thinking it's boogers
but it's this outside nose thing that you're talking about.
What is going on with us dude?
Because it happens, it doesn't happen often.
But it's like a, it's an industrial smell.
Yeah.
It is not.
Yeah, you guys just live in New York.
It does not, no I've had it for years.
Yeah, me too.
I was in Boston and like Manchester and fucking wherever.
Do you guys mean just randomly smelling like burning plastic or rubber sometimes?
No, no, it's not that I smell it.
It comes off your nose.
Like people around me will smell my fucking weird tires nose.
Send us a message request and tell us it's like some condition that-
I need a scientist in my life.
Yeah, every so bad.
Even the stupidest scientists would know about this one.
I need Walter White in my life, dude.
He's a genius scientist.
Yeah.
Me and Anna went to the Berkshires over the weekend and on the car ride there,
there's a long car ride, we were listening to this true crime podcast that she likes.
It's about this crazy scam where basically this scammer tricks these low-level Hollywood
employees into flying to Indonesia for a fake movie shoot, basically.
Oh, I heard about that!
Yeah, it's really crazy. But they interview a bunch of the people who got scammed and they're
all like, "Yeah, like when I was in Indonesia, like there was this driver driving me around and I was
so fucking scared. I thought I was gonna die. Like I couldn't get out of there fast enough."
And then they interviewed this one Polish woman who's currently in, they like call her and she's
like in out on the scam like right then. And they tell her the scam, she's like, "This is actually
really crazy for me to find out. This is really weird that this is like a scam for me. Like I
I don't really know what's going on and they find out that it's her second time going to
Indonesia.
What?
What did they?
She flew to Indonesia and then went back and then came back again.
What did they make them do in Indonesia?
It's this whole thing.
They like drive them around and like have them take pictures.
It's just like, it's like this, the person is getting like some weird sexual pleasure
out of it and then they'd like money that like they pay the driver to it's very
weird but I was just laughing so hard it is like exactly she's like this is just
really weird for me I don't really know what's going on right now he's going
yeah just over and over maybe she'd likes it did maybe she thinks Indonesia
maybe she's appreciating the natural beauty of the Indonesian coast yeah I
mean I would love to go to Indonesia it's surf the waves dude no I would
never I would never go under false pretenses if I was invited to go see like
a friend in Asian Indonesia I would go I probably would too I you know I probably
would go anywhere to see a friend yeah man I'd go to hell I'd visit hell to see
one of my best friends are you kidding me absolutely no you wouldn't I would
travel there I would travel to the ends of the earth to see my best friend.
It's too hot here my nose is sweating my nose would sweat so much in hell though
You're right.
It smells like-
You're absolutely right.
It smells like brimstone.
I think it's my damn nose.
Here in hell.
Wait, shut up.
Fuck you.
You have a-
No, your nose smells.
Okay, stupid.
No, I'm not.
Alright, stupid ass bitch.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, stupid ass.
I ain't fucking with you.
Oh, God.
I ain't fucking with you, you little stupid ass bitch.
I'm fucking with you.
Fucking bitch!
That's so funny.
It's so scary.
Yeah.
scary yeah yeah like I started like six years ago and I just remembered it the
other day when he leans back and screams and then when he like sits back up like
there's just like murder and oh yeah it looks like a fucking lizard like he was
just thinking of somebody he hated a primal instinct to kill like that's all
you can see in his face yeah big boy he lost all that weight used to be like a
cheery Al Roker type for rap and then all of a sudden he lost all this weight
Oh, so it's like psycho, bro. It's like it's like a situation where he was once fat and they called him big boy
Well, yeah that imagine. Yeah, so like Al Roker same so imagine
Forever no, but what if your what if your name was fat Patrick, right?
I'm glad you guys never kept calling me Patrick or anything like that. Yeah, it was too easy, dude
I don't go for the easy shit, you know, yeah, you got to go for something complex like like a splat trick. Yeah
Splattrick has been, I've been called Splattrick by a couple people.
Slurple.
The slurpler.
That's another good one.
Due to your slurpling nature.
The weirdo Patrick, the weirdo idiot.
Yeah.
He's one that caught on.
Stupid ass.
Fucking F-A-G-I-T.
I got called once.
That's fucked up.
That's not a nickname either.
Yeah, it's not a nickname.
I hope you know that.
I hope you know they weren't trying to be friendly, Patrick.
They weren't?
No.
Oh.
We need to get you some classes.
Yeah?
Yeah, we need you to learn how to-
I have glasses right here.
No, some classes.
Oh, classes?
We need you to learn to defend yourself online.
Yeah?
We're putting you in a community- we're putting you in a Miller-Mont Technical.
Okay.
Yep.
We're sending you to-
I'm gonna learn how to make friends with the guys in my DMs calling me bad names.
We're gonna send you to Full Sail University on a $1 scholarship and it's gonna change your
life.
You're going to learn how to be a video game developer/homeless guy at Full Sail University.
On my dime, by the way.
You know what?
Did I tell you this already that I almost applied there when I was like 16?
I think so.
I think we definitely talked about this.
Yeah, I almost went to Full Sail.
Full Sail is so fun.
I almost went to Full Sail for video production.
It's definitely one of the most evil scams.
Yeah, I didn't know that until like, I don't know, I was like 16 or 17 and I was like, I
like there's no way I'm gonna get into a good college with these grades.
That's on par with their like ad campaign where they just like show video games like just to
prey on like and like you know kids who live in their parents basements like high schoolers
live in their like it's like on par with like the commercials you see on TV where it's like
a predatory like loan company and like the ad is like a 23 year old guy in his mom's basement
and he takes the loan and like turns into a CEO it's like that's just not fair you can't.
I feel like you show up for Full Sail University with like a backpack and notebooks and shit
and they're like alright first day you're pressing license plates for Arizona.
It's kind of a Mr. Miyagi thing.
We'll work up to the video game design.
Oh man dude.
Evil.
Yeah I'm looking at my DM requests.
There's been some pretty funny.
It's funny ass ish.
Funny ass ish that people have been calling me.
You know I love funny ass bullshit.
Can you just fucking spill the beans here?
What are they saying?
Patrick Fridge.
I saw that.
That doesn't make a lot of sense to me.
Because your name has nothing to do with fridges.
People love to send just funny ass shit.
Oh yeah.
When you leave your DMs open, you get a lot of funny, funny DMs from people who will love
you and have your best interest at heart.
You will not believe the memes that some of these people find.
How did you find a picture of Nancy Pelosi with giant tits?
I just don't understand.
You are crazy.
That is just it.
You're silly.
Send that to someone.
Especially having a...
You remember like a year ago or something like that?
I posted something about a, like it was a stupid like making fun of what those like, oh, if
you idolize, I said like, if you idolize Bart Simpson, you completely misunderstood the
point of the show.
And I got, that was the most anybody has ever been mad at me online.
That's why it's so psychotic that you always think somebody's gonna get mad at you because
you say Moana is a bad movie or something.
Yeah.
Is because that is the thing that people actually get mad at you for.
Oh, dude.
Yeah, this guy was like in my DMs telling me to like kill myself, FAGIT, all this other
stuff.
Yeah, I got into like a fight with him.
Like I'll say this, more death threats would be good.
Yeah, more death threats.
I think it keeps life interesting if you think that somebody's gonna kill you.
A guy sent me a complete manifesto one time and I, in a video on Google Drive Doc and
I still don't know what was up with that.
If you reach out to me in any way, I'll report your account.
I'll find something you said.
I'm going to get you off the internet.
I'm going to ruin your life.
Yeah.
Buddy, I'm a wizard on Twitter search.
You reply to my fucking Twitter story and say, "Oh, I saw this movie once.
It was pretty good."
I'm scrolling down until 2014 and your account's gone.
You're done, kid.
You are never talking to your friends again.
Remember how awesome it was when you quoted a milli in 2013?
what bud it's so that accounts getting nuked you are done yeah yeah you're
getting a good time there and I'm gonna I'm gonna be searching your username to
make sure you don't come back with the VPN it's over that's right
nothing a VPN can't so I'll do a reverse VPN dude yeah and be a TV right on you
no be on your ass no profiles of allowed I think I could become a pretty good hit
man I think I'm amazing yeah you already look like a 47 well that was maybe my
first thought but it's got a bigger sense in yeah huh cuz I also act like I'm
kind of a strong silent quiet killer yeah totally totally totally yeah you're
definitely so yeah you're definitely definitely strong yeah you're definitely
a silent type mm-hmm yeah bitch I wish you were oh she was more silent oh I'm
I'm trying to work on my silence right now.
Even when he tries to work on silence he still keeps going
*makes weird noises*
You're like the chamber.
No, you're more like the chamber.
Yeah, I'm kind of a strong silent type. *makes weird noises*
Wait, wait, guys, try to relate to the dark crystal.
There's veins popping out on Caleb's bald head
because he can't talk because he's trying to be cool
and he's just walking around the target just going
*makes weird noises*
Cookies! Cookies on sale!
You be the cashier at Qdoba and I'll be me trying to be strong and silent and I'm trying to order.
Okay.
Hello and welcome to Qdoba.
Okay, I will take your credit card and I will go home with it.
No.
Oh, I'm entering your credit card into my Amazon account right now.
Excuse me sir, can you hurry up?
Also your pants are down, I can see your ass.
I'm trying to get a burrito.
There's poop running down your leg, sir.
Sir, you're gonna have to go into the bathroom.
By the way, that's gonna cost you.
What's the code?
I lost the voice I was doing.
Sir, you're gonna have to go in the bathroom.
Don't worry, no code to get in.
Okay.
Go on in.
Can I get my Pepsi soda?
We don't have Pepsi products at Qdoba.
Do you have a Coke?
We have a Coke Freestyle machine.
I can't understand you.
I can't understand you, sir.
Did you say...
I'm a strong silent type.
Did you say "buy Human Giant on DVD on Amazon for free"?
Okay, and then another guy walks up and taps you, Caleb, on the shoulder.
Excuse me, are you Agent 47 the hitman?
Maybe.
Your cover has just been blown, sir.
Yeah, you just failed the mission.
I said maybe.
You're not supposed to speak if you're Agent 47.
Are you saying Mr. Bean?
Yeah.
*laughter*
'Cause he's a strong silent type, too.
That's all you have to do.
It's that easy, dude.
Immediately, I'd be like the head of the Hitman guild.
Yeah?
The assassin.
If you're becoming head of the Hitman guild, I'm head of the Inventors guild now.
Imagine-
You just left the Inventors guild. You can't be in two guilds at once.
Imagine Mr. Bean is a Hitman, though.
Yeah.
*muffled voice*
Can I use your bathroom?
He talks like that right Mr. Bean he does talk like that, but he doesn't say that in words.
Hello, I am Mr. Bean.
Yeah, can I use your a rest room? You're sounding like Mr. Frijole.
Mr. Frijole, is that some made-up guy?
Senior Frijole?
No. Is that the voice you're doing? Yeah. Yeah, I'm doing Senior Frijole. Yeah. Yeah, it is fun.
Do you think they call him that and like in other countries when they localize it? He's still Mr. Bean?
Maybe. Wait, that's actually... I can guarantee in Mexico he's not called
"Senor Frijole." Probably "Senor Bean." I was gonna say that's ridiculous, but they
they do shit like that all the time when they localize. So one second. Yeah, "Bob Esponja."
"Bob Esponja." Yeah. Localized. How do... Do you think it's just Mr. because it might just be
Mr. because it's a name. Yeah, I feel, you know, I feel like they just call him his name. All right,
I'm looking up, I'm looking up Mr. Bean worldwide. Just Mr. Worldwide. People get the idea.
I don't know what to search to find the answer to this.
Mr. Search, Senor Frijoles, see if it comes up.
Well, I don't want to know if it's Senor Frijoles, I just want to know what they call them.
So Senor Frijoles is a website.
It's a Mexican restaurant in Key Largo.
Mr. Bean's Restaurant?
Is it like a...
I would hate to eat there.
It's like a Margaritaville situation?
No, it has nothing to do with...
Dude, they got a pic, go to images, check out their logo.
They have like a Heisenberg type...
yeah yeah like Walter White Breaking Bad yeah oh my god dude I just I'm almost
done with Breaking Bad almost done with it and I need it I need a new show but
everybody that I know is like a big into anime so I'll ask for a new show and
they're like you should watch fucking schoolgirl sex fuck 100 it's actually
got a weird name but that art is so incredible so I need a better show to
watch I've watched all the bald guy canon I've watched you watch pranos breaking
bad the shield I need a new bald guy show you watch check it out I've been
re-watching check it out I need something with an oovla do you got a lot of
children the children episode of check it out with I bet you I bet you do want
to watch that episode oh yeah you're gonna you're gonna like that episode
Caleb I bet you will like that you will like yeah I bet you will yeah I bet
you'll like it pedophile says anything
I was prepared to go for 30 minutes.
I was too!
I was so ready!
The rest of the episode is silence!
Oh, it's too easy.
Oh, it's too easy, dude.
All right, so today's list is the top 10 best things to eat with milk.
From the top 10s by user Fox Rocks.
Milk goes great with lots of food.
What's the best?
We were at some like, a friend's birthday the other day, we were at like some like fucking
hippie Bushwick bar and our friend wanted the Mets game on and I asked the bartender,
I was like, "Hey, can you put the Mets game on?
It's channel 36."
turned it on and just every TV in the bar turned to Fox News.
Yeah.
And we were just watching the Lauren Ingram Show.
Number one, cookies.
Cookies.
Come with me.
Yeah.
You know, I mean, there's no argument here, but I mean, there is, I think there's a little,
I guess it can be disputed between number one and number two here.
Are you guys milk drinkers?
Before we move on to that, no I hate milk too.
I switched out with milk.
I would never drink, oh yeah I drink almond milk now,
but I wouldn't drink, I mean I would have milk and cereal
or like with stuff.
I would never just drink straight milk.
I drink milk after cookies have been dipped in it.
I think drinking, you know and it's interesting
'cause before I've said I think drinking a whole glass
of milk is psycho behavior just to drink milk on its own
and you know Patrick made a lot of fun of me
for saying that so it's kind of interesting
that he's turned now and seen my way of life.
Dude, I just know I know and there's actually video evidence of that too. You know, it was on stream
Well, I think it's fine to drink a glass of milk, but like oh now you can't even stick to his guns
Let me like Hillary Clinton. Let me let me clarify because
Ten minutes to fit to think of like how you want to try and weasel your way out of this one. I know
Shut up, shut up, let me let me fucking okay
I'm waiting. It's fine to drink a glass of milk, but the process in which that you get the milk is very weird
Go to the store. So now I can understand.
Yeah, like who would be the first guy who saw a cow and was like I'm gonna drink whatever comes out of milk, right?
Yeah, I've actually been thinking about this. Who's the first guy who saw a bug?
I'm saying I'm starting to see...
Who's the first guy who saw like chewing gum?
It's like I'm gonna chew this but not eat it.
I'm gonna chew on this gum.
Cameron, I'm trying to...
I'm trying to gum for nothing right now. I think I'm gonna use it to chew. I'm trying
to fix our friendship. Who's the first guy who saw a lollipop with no stick and was like
I wish I could eat this with a stick in it. Yeah, I'm trying to fix our friendship Cameron.
And I'm trying to work on some killer open mic material. So can you give some space dude?
Okay. My grandfather when him and my grandma would come over for dinner when I was growing
up my mom would make like salad or pasta or some shit and every single time my grandpa
would bring he would just walk in with a gallon of milk and a pre-made hamburger
patty every like a couple weeks and they'd come for dinner
that's such a sick move just like don't have no idea what's being served and
you're just you know what you want mm-hmm I just want to there's just two
comments on the cookies one what did Cameron say about I got distracted I
I don't remember.
What did I say?
You said something about me weaseling my way out of something about milk.
Are you serious?
You forgot that?
Yeah, I just did.
You forgot that you guys had a-
It's okay, we're not talking about that anyway.
You know what?
It's fine, buddy.
You can just do your own thing.
I don't want anyone to be mad at me about this milk thing.
I don't think anyone's going to be mad at you about milk.
Who's going to be mad at you?
I don't know.
About the milk thing.
Cameron?
I'm not mad at you.
Have you guys ever had raw milk?
I'm furious.
No.
- What the fuck is that dude?
That shit's crazy.
- I know, it's nuts.
It's so funny that people,
people break the law,
like they go to insane lengths to sell that shit.
- That shit, I've had a sip of it before.
It's like the difference between smoking weed and eating it.
- Yeah, what if I could drink milk,
but I could also have whatever pus comes out of the pimples
that's inside of a cow's tit too?
- See, that's why I switched to oat milk.
- Oat milk, yeah, it's better too.
It's like if they made like,
like flushing the toilet,
not flushing the toilet illegal
and people were like looking for toilets
filled with shit in them to use.
- Exactly.
- They were like, I have to,
I will risk going to jail
so that I can just fucking piss on shit.
- You can go to jail for drinking raw milk?
- Probably not. - Yeah, it's illegal.
No, no, you can't.
It's illegal to sell raw milk. - I don't think you can go
to jail.
- Yeah, you fucking, it's illegal to sell raw milk.
You'd probably get fined, okay, but you--
- But you get fined enough times you go to jail.
- That's true, all of a sudden, dude,
You're part of the, you're having to choose a race.
It's cause of the like, CDC doesn't let you sell it or something.
CDC doesn't let you do a lot of stuff.
It's true.
Baskin Robbins, no mask.
Can you eat your own cum?
Is that illegal?
It's illegal.
Not illegal yet, should be.
Does that break like an incest law?
Yes.
You can't cum in your own mouth?
You can't drink your dad's cum.
What's happening in this damn world?
Can't fucking drink your dad's cum or your own cum.
- He's pastored at first, that's all.
- True.
- You know what?
- If you homogenize your cum, it's probably fine.
- Yeah, I mean, Louis Pasteur was a crook.
- Great trumpet player though.
- Yeah.
- No, that was Dizzy Gillespie.
- Dizzy Lesby?
- Dizzy Gillespie.
- Now you're speaking my language.
- Dizzy Gillespie was, he had like,
I've talked about Dizzy Gillespie to you guys
before, his like big pouches,
where he would like blow into the trumpet
and his whole face would expand.
- Oh yeah, dude, that guy rules.
- Yeah.
- That guy's a fucking beast.
- Dude, his episode of the Muppets, great.
Great episode.
- Someone says, "Without cookies,
"milk tastes like nothing."
You need to go to the hospital.
- Yeah, that's--
- You think milk tastes like nothing?
- Okay, 2% milk doesn't taste like anything.
- What?
- Yeah.
- What the fuck are you talking,
milk is like such a distinctive taste.
- 2% milk tastes like water.
- Okay, you have diabetes.
something and i don't have that you have diabetes and i'm gonna chop your leg off
because if you think milk tastes like nothing you're psyched up whole milk i
don't think i don't think milk tastes like nothing but i also don't drink
plain milk so i'm not going to do it is spicy
i'll let my friends fight slain it's by a it has a lot of these places in the
civil it's
it's a little man is that there's a white color that makes it so spicy it's
really a white like a white like a ghost milk
Ghosts like a ghost pepper. Yeah, if you ever have had pepperidge farms bread can get very spicy too, especially the potato bread
Yeah, nothing is spicier than a potato. God. I ever had I have to lick the ground after I eat that shit
It's like eating it. It's like eating a fire. You ever had the hostess bread
No, is it that chocolate bread? No. No, it's like garden hostess like whole wheat bread
They sell it at like like 7-eleven whole wheat. Well, it's gotta be good for you, dude. It smells rancid
We got serious fucking summer nose vibes. It's like the fucking...
like... it's bread, right? Bread's like two, three ingredients, but hostess bread, the ingredient list is like a fucking paragraph.
I gotta give it to you, you're amazing at explaining this. It's like I'm watching How It's Made right now.
This is incredible. It's basically really fucked up the way they make this bread. There's way too many ingredients.
The amount of preservatives in Hostess bread is insane.
I mean, honestly, like, Survival of the Fittest style, if you see bread that has the Hostess logo on it, and you're like, "I'm going to buy this bread," you deserve to have pickled insides.
Yeah, I agree.
Sometimes, you need bread, and it's the only bread that they have.
What fucking store has only Hostess bread? Are you going to like a candy store or something?
7-Eleven and the convenience store that was near my old apartment.
Then go to a different one.
I didn't want to walk all the way to another store.
If you choose to eat Hostess bread.
Again, if you can't walk long enough to get normal bread and you're eating the Hostess
bread, you're double dipping in fucking carcinogens there.
You deserve to have your body be your own personal sarcophagus.
You're going to be buried.
My body's a damn temple.
Yeah, the freaking temple of doom.
I mean, what's up with that movie, Indiana Jones?
Kids eating eyeball soup.
number two is oreos. I didn't even read the comments I wanted to read. Too bad.
Let's pretend they're about oreos. I remember when I was in primary school and
when they served cookies and milk for dessert at lunch and they asked you if
you wanted milk with your cookie I would always refuse because for some reason I
don't like drinking milk out of a cup. My friend however is the complete opposite.
He loves drinking milk. Don't drink milk out of a cup. And then here's his
friend if you scroll down. Biscuits and milk is the best combination. The
The sweetness of the biscuits and the faint taste of milk, which makes the biscuits/cookies
linger in your mouth a little longer.
Ah, Moans, it's the best.
That is a very proper Top 10s user.
Vile.
Horrible.
Yeah.
I mean, vile, first of all, it's not a biscuit, dude.
A biscuit?
To have the audacity to call it a biscuit and then say biscuit/cookie after that, it's
like, no, you've made your bed.
Yeah, what's the difference between a biscuit and a cookie over there?
A biscuit is made by the poorest, fattest woman in the universe and she serves it to you at
a barbecue place.
And a cookie is a very awful word for a type of person over there.
Yeah.
What?
You know what they call, you know how we call cigarettes cigarettes and they call it something
else?
That's like how cookies are here.
That's why they say biscuits.
Ah.
Yeah.
Didn't know that.
Yeah, it's true.
So you might think twice before you say cookie from now on.
Uh huh.
Mm hmm.
Uh, number two, Oreos.
That's a cookie.
Oh shit!
Who were you saying that to?
Here's what you went for is that's a cookie.
That is a cookie.
Ugh, I had too much fucking caffeine, dude.
It's having an opposite effect now.
Two caffeinated drinks cancel each other out.
I have plenty of caffeine all the time and I don't find myself calling people British slurs. So yeah
I don't even remember what this episode is about. What are we talking about? It's about you're lying
That's the most you can scroll up on the web, but you're acting
This is like when this is like when a kid drinks a Capri Sun for the first time and like runs in circles around the house
It's like this feels like it gives me superpowers. Mm-hmm
You've never had sugar before. Yeah, you are on it's like you're it's like a sugar
it's like when you eat a brownie and you're like i'm having a total sugar
rush right now and you find out they're sugar-free brownies all along
he's never had sugar so god damn it how's he so sweet
that's me to you yeah yeah man i had some oreos yesterday and they just weren't
the same without milk so my mom went out and bought some milk
and it was instant heaven the second that milk saturated cookie and soaked
cream encountered my lips and greedy teeth
my greedy teeth lips and greedy teeth she's just mouth gash
sheesh twist yeah i just saw that twist lick dunk in milk
that's not even the one i was gonna read it's a different one that also starts that way
twist lick it and dunk it yeah baby come on vote for this if you don't then maybe you need to eat
eat some oreo and milk then you decide then there's twist lick and dunk mmm I
love it I love to leave my oreo and milk and take them out one minute later and
eat them just mouth gasms do people who fuck just eat the oreo dude yeah I can't
not do the dry oreo dry oreos delicious we talk dry oreo fucking that'll fuck
you up what you know that's that's wrong that's incorrect it'll fuck you up yeah
It will fuck you up to eat an Oreo?
Oreo no Bev, that'll fuck you up.
What?
You're eating Popeye's biscuit with no Bev?
Yes, I would, what's, what's, what?
It's so dry!
You just sit in the bathtub all day dunking biscuits and Oreos into the water?
I sit in the gravy bath, yeah.
And just fucking, you are crazy.
Oreos are not that dry compared to other cookies.
They have like-
Oreos are pretty dry.
No.
I'll tell you what's dry.
A damn goddamn Belvita, dude.
No, no, no, no.
Not compared to like fucking like Chips Ahoy.
Like any other, any other like snack cookie is way drier than an Oreo.
All cookies are pretty dry.
That's because Oreos are some of the least dry cookies.
Oreos are pretty dry.
No.
Yes.
You're stupid.
I'm not stupid about this.
You're very stupid.
You need your mouth water checked up on.
I have a lot of saliva.
Thank you very much.
- You need to get a tiny mechanic under that tongue.
- Come on over.
- I'm not a tiny mechanic.
- Yes you are.
- We're the same size.
- Okay.
- All right, I'm over.
I'll be over right after this with my little--
- Little wrench.
- With the tech deck that I use to go under tongues.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- And check it out.
- Number three, cereal.
Milk enhances the taste or cereals
while cereals make the milk taste better.
You can't go wrong.
While with cake and cookies, milk can seriously,
like spelled like cereal,
destroy the taste of the cookie.
Fun fact, the original name of cereals was Cereal
and is a Latin corruption, which means unreal
because Paul the first considered cereals
to be the unreal gift from God.
The fun fact here is however,
that my story is a bowl of bull.
- Whoa.
- Are you serious?
You're gonna tell us all this and then just lie?
- Did you guys fall for it?
- Yeah, we'll fall for it.
- Here's a great comment, "Love my milk."
- Love my milk.
- Love, I just, you know what?
It doesn't matter what the item is, I love my damn milk.
- Aw, love my milk.
- You can't eat cereal without milk,
and then it says, "I sometimes eat cereal without milk."
- Dude, when I buy a house, I'm putting up
one of those live, laugh, love type signs
that says, "Love my milk."
- Yeah.
- Like those letters you put above the stairs.
- I welcome that.
- Yeah.
- Love my milk.
In this house, we love my milk.
- I'll have another one on the other wall that says,
"I hate milk, so I will not eat or drink anything
with milk inside it's rubbish. I hate milk I'm the evil guy who lives in this house
who hates milk. The M in both of those could be an udder. That's clever that's
good. It couldn't be an udder. It's like an outside tiny udder. Yeah you've never seen an udder
then. I've seen an udder. Udders are like they're like they're like spider eyes there's like
millions of things coming off of those. There's not a million udders. Well you just put the things coming off of them.
the M is like the shape of the utter and then yeah look at look up cartoon cow
look up em look up letter M as utter cartoon cow okay looks up M utter and
I'm looking here all right tough mudder it's a obstacle race nice I was that one
of those ones where you like fucking climb through shit yeah and then so they
take photos of you in the middle and they're like this guy's basically a
marine because he did a mud run yeah or like what's that one where they throw
fucking colors on you the color run what are these people doing dude how hard is
it on a normal mile well you got to throw obstacles I mean I guess the
obstacles make it fun but like you have to run from is it like the is it like
the zone in fortnight where you have to run from the colors as they chase you I
that's it yeah I think they I think they spray them I think there's parts you run
through where they're spraying them. So does that mean that you win or you lose?
No, you're supposed to like it. Why would you like being blue? Because it proves that you ran the
run. I don't know. Just walking into the cashier, the 7-eleven after, just being
like, "I bet you can guess where I came from!" It's the same thing as like, well, it's
like, you know, being on like a bar crawl or something. Yeah. And you're wearing
like a... I guess that's true. Fucking, yeah, dressed up like a lobster or something, and
going to CVS and be like you'll never guess what I'm doing right now yeah and
they're like didn't ask yeah no seriously try and guess yeah try and guess what I
know is a shit about that like the Santa con stuff like yeah okay let's let's
hold up Santa comes actually pretty fucking cool it's kind of a testament to
Santa con is not cool it is cool dude said one of the few Christian holidays
that are left I I want to I don't want to derail but I do you we were talking
live laugh love stuff and how there's like one good one and one evil one.
Yeah.
Do you ever think about how if you had like a live laugh love sign if you look at it in the mirror
it says evil evil.
It's true.
That is so true dude.
Damn.
I didn't even think of that dude.
It's so cool.
Wow.
Imagine going to the bathroom and you look in the bathroom mirror and you just see a
sign behind you that says evil evil.
I would run out of there instantly.
Or you get pulled into the mirror universe and it says fucking die scream fart.
You get pulled into the mirror universe and it says live laugh love again.
And you go oh.
Yeah, you go wait a second. I'm just in the normal universe.
Fuck. I needed to go to the mirror universe to get a backward soda.
A backward soda?
It's just an idea, you know. Like I said, I'm a casual inventor. I just throw them out. I don't
I don't worry about that patent shit.
I leave that for the nerds.
- Yeah.
- I'm kind of a creative genius like Walt Disney.
- Water, soda, adapter.
So you can put soda in a water cup
or water in a soda cup.
- How about a soda scream?
- Okay, hold on.
- 'Cause it's already making a noise,
but you press that button down, it goes.
(screaming)
Huh?
- Maybe, yeah.
- How about a scream scream?
- Maybe tone it down.
- Okay.
- What about scream?
What about whipping scream?
Scream 2.
What about scream of tartar?
Okay.
You know?
What is scream of tartar?
It's a weird fucked up little dust that you fucking put on shit and it makes it bubble
or something.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's white too.
Number 4, brownies.
I don't like brownies, dude.
I don't either.
I don't need that.
Really?
I don't need that in my life.
I don't like sweet bread.
- No, no, no, sweet bread is good, but like,
brownies and like cake, I hate.
- I like brownies a lot.
I don't really care about cake,
but brownie with ice cream, that's very good.
- I don't eat anything fudgy.
- It needs to have the other thing.
Like, it needs to have like--
- Yeah, I mean, I still would eat a plain brownie,
but a brownie with ice cream is another level.
- A waffle with ice cream on it, amazing.
A brownie with ice cream on it, amazing.
- Waffle might be the most versatile food.
- Oh yeah, waffle on its own great,
but brownie on its own, no.
- No, agree.
- I disagree.
- But like a cookie, if it's like a double fudge cookie
where the cookie itself is chocolate, I can't do that.
But if it's just like a chocolate chip cookie, that's good.
- I'm not a huge chocolate fan, dude.
- Me neither.
- Yeah, I don't have any ailments that need to be cured.
- I'm a gummies guy.
That's my sweet.
- You're a gummies guy?
- That makes sense.
- Yeah?
- Makes a lot of sense.
- 'Cause you're a little gummy bear.
You put a gummy worm on the end of a fishing rod
and stand in an alley and--
Yeah, you could catch me.
And dangle it out in front of the toy store.
You catch yourself.
No, you do that.
No, I don't do that.
You set up a whole Rube Goldberg machine
to catch you with a gummy worm.
That's what you do.
It's the only way I can eat gummies
without feeling guilty about it.
Yeah, 'cause somebody else is doing it.
You know what I had last night?
I had the Haribo fruit mix.
That's my recommendation for the week.
You said that like you just had
like
Nerds Rope? Is that what it's called?
It's to die for, absolutely. It's beautiful.
And you open the Laffy Taffy and you look at it, and you look at the wrapper of the Laffy Taffy and there's a little joke on the wrapper.
And you can read it to your friends and you can have...
It's amazing. It's absolutely amazing.
It's great for a social situation.
It's amazing for social scenarios.
A perfect dinner party hors d'oeuvre.
Like this one, this one, it says here, it says here...
Oh fuck I don't know any.
I don't know any Laffy Taffy jokes.
What did the girl say to Pinocchio while he was fucking eating her out?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Laffy on Laffy Taffy.
Lie to me Pinocchio. Come on Laffy Taffy let's go.
Dirty Laffy Taffy.
She said Laffy Taffy.
Laffy Taffy let's go.
Lie to me Pinocchio. Fucking put your nose in my cunt.
Come on Laffy Taffy.
Laffy Taffy.
Laffy Taffy Pinocchio.
Pinocchio! Laffy Taffy!
Laffy Taffy!
That's one of my favorite Laffy Taffy jokes.
I got a Laffy Taffy for Pinocchio.
It's a really long answer, it's like a whole paragraph.
Come on Pinocchio, Laffy Taffy!
Using a jeweler's loop to read it.
I think that they should put
at the end of the Snapple Facts
they should put "Snapple Out".
That'd be pretty good.
They should put "Just Kidding" at the end of the Snapple Facts.
Just kidding, you idiot.
Fuck you, stupid.
it
out dude snapple sarcasm snap all should do to do like false facts like yeah like
disinfo for April Fool's Day that'd be a man and then people would like hoard
them and put them back on store shelves like in other times you put April or
snapple fools on the wrapper snake label snap roll fools snap roll juice juice
excuse me juice like juice like what's that police saying on the
disinformation ones they should say snapperel juice. No juice. All right I
don't know what you're getting at. That's all I heard I'm just saying that
that kind of came off weird. Yeah. I'm gonna give you I'm gonna give you a pass.
I said juice. Number five cinnamon rolls. What did you say Patrick just now?
What was that? Because I said juice but I know that you did not say juice. You're saying
nazi jews now what are you fucking what are you talking about man you need it you
need it you need drink less coffee next time okay you're really you're really
freaking me out you're freaking me out I think you're losing it face cinnamon
might be choosing it what did you say to the hell I think the Jews might be doing
this is what I said you must have misheard me I think all the juice that
Patrick did drank did do this you're right yeah cinnamon rolls I you don't
need anything extra on a cinnamon the comment on this one weirds me out to
listen to this I totally agree with you cinnamon rolls are amazing the thing is
I hate milk so whenever I get milk with cinnamon rolls I eat a million rolls and
barely drink any milk who the fuck is getting like a bunch of cinnamon rolls
that's that's like well it depends if it's the orange kind if it's an orange
cinnamon roll. The orange? What do you mean? The orange kind. The orange the orange icing
cinnamon rolls? I don't know what that is. Are you crazy dude? Not crazy, just I'm
missing, I'm uninformed. Oh my oh my god oh my god oh lord you have to try these. Yeah.
They have orange on them. Okay. And maybe in them too I've not checked. They're
those they're the fucking what's the name of the little fucking fat guy who goes
do giggles? Poo Bear? Pillsbury. It's one of the Pillsbury, you know the cinnamon rolls that come
in a tube? Yeah. His name is Poppin' Fresh, it's not Pillsbury. His name is Pillsbury. His name is
Poppin' Fresh? Yeah. I thought it was Doughboy. No, he is the Pillsbury Doughboy and his name is
Poppin' Fresh. What? I promise you. Look it up. I'd bury some pills right now. Yeah? Yeah. In my
- You're gonna bury him in my dough boy?
- Oh, come on dude.
I don't wanna put nothing in your damn dough boy.
You brought some nasty crap today
and honestly, I'm not here for it.
Number six. - Yeah, it's an off day for me.
- A cake.
- Seven doughnuts, eight chocolate,
don't care, doesn't matter.
Nine pie, top comment.
Apple pie be the best.
In Kolkata, you get the best at park.
- True.
(laughing)
- That's facts.
- Pop tarts.
Pop-tarts are life.
So when pop-tarts and milk are together,
it was instant heaven.
- It's true.
- Can't eat without milk.
It's a great breakfast.
- I don't like pop-tarts.
- Really?
- I think maybe--
- I think there's like one or two flavors that are okay,
but all in all, that's a food you gotta grow out of
by high school or else you're a permanent child.
- See, if you're like me and you just ate too many of them
for breakfast every day, you just get sick of 'em,
that's what you have to do, I think.
If you're a grown-up though, you can indulge every once in a while in a cinnamon pop tart.
If you get one of these fruity ones or a s'mores pop tart.
Oh, the brown sugar cinnamon pop tarts?
You have something wrong with you if you're eating a fucking confetti strawberry pop tart.
Yeah, the brown cinnamon are the good ones.
The s'mores pop tarts?
Those are the only ones that I would...
Exactly, the s'mores ones are good, but again, those are ones that if you're eating those,
you're older than like 16, you're gonna be shipped away.
Yeah just make a damn s'more you fucking weirdo.
I ate too many s'mores as a kid.
Yeah just sit up.
Come on dude.
Every man gets home from a long day of work at the DEA.
You get home, you fucking pop a swathe.
You see the divorce papers that your wife left on the table for you to sign, you light
them on fire, you cook a nice s'more above them.
Yeah, throw a nice s'more on the grill, pour yourself some scotch.
Come on dude.
Pour the scotch on the grill.
Grow up.
your your shitty little kid around the house with this s'more skewer yeah dude
yeah let him hold your gun yeah okay now we're getting off glue your kids feet to
the floor with melted marshmallow yeah your kid teacher to kid the daddy safe
combo song uh-huh that's right two one one two three eight by your guys the guy
who smokes weed in my alley was back for the old past like few minutes I didn't
to say anything get him on the phone tell you didn't say anything about weed he was
standing over there and he was smoking and then he just started doing this
dude he's bad to Ralph dude yeah he was about to fucking throw up right there and then he just walked away just now
the damn pots hitting him too hard like it wasn't like a normal it was like half
throwing up half some kind of dance it was very weird he hasn't smoked since the
70s do I really even out of what I can these days if you if he if he had been here on 420
I would I would have handed the mic out the window
But you know I live here, and he's here, maybe twice a week, so I don't want to make an enemy
I'm right now. It's a non-fortune. He might be he might be happy to talk about weed
But you know I don't want to start anything
Definitely, and you don't want to deal with some fucking drug addict also there. I'm a waste oid oh my god
It's like junky track marks all over his arm from I wish the Punisher was real
I know dude.
Here, hold on, let me read this thing right here.
Number 18, Twinkies.
There's a comment here.
It says, "Me and my buds call this Twanky Milk."
Twanky Milk.
Kids in high school come up with the most fucked up combination foods.
I knew this dude who would he would put like a handful of after dinner mints in a glass of milk and then he drink
Oh and the after dinner mints would make like a paste at the bottom of the cup and then he'd eat that
Are you serious? I swear to God
We have a similar situation here on number 20
Number 20 is flaming hot Cheetos and the bottom comment is I make milkshakes of this
Call mini chef Ramsey be because I be cooking boo tap my feet
What stop trying to start a catchphrase dude you ain't hamburger Jones yeah boot
Don't come on now. You can't fucking hit me with a boot at my feet. I don't know you catchphrases are just really lame
I'm so ooey-gooey I
Just don't respect most people who'd like try to make something happen that just shouldn't happen yeah
Swag number this is the last one on the list number 51 cotton candy
What?
Dip it in taste, wink emoji.
It was just milk.
That's a prank on someone who likes cotton candy but doesn't know what happens when you
eat it.
Yeah, no seriously, put this cotton candy in the milk.
Put a bunch of water on your cotton candy.
See what happens.
It'll be really funny and delicious.
Have you ever like, when you were a kid, did you ever just take a whole, like you get like
a bag of cotton candy at the fair or whatever.
Just make it a ball?
Yeah, turn it into the ball, like clump it in your, crush it in your hands until like
all the sugars like turn hard.
Yeah, then just throw it away cuz you can't fucking eat it anymore.
Right, well I would eat it. I would eat it.
Turns into fucking Teflon, dude.
Yeah, so bad.
You could stop a train.
Disgusting.
Number 31's hamburger, and the only comment is, "I do this every day."
That is my grandfather, dude.
Oh, fuck.
Milk and a burger.
Milk and a burger, nothing better than that.
Well, that was before they invented fries.
Cola, cheese, yogurt, butter, ramen noodles.
Pear.
What is rusk?
I don't know.
A hard dry biscuit or twice baked bread.
A hard dry biscuit?
This techno shit's gone too far.
It is sometimes used as a teether for babies.
Oh fuck.
Mentos.
Number 50 vanilla wafers.
Holy Jesus Christo, these are good.
flavors. Holy Jesus Christo, these are good. Oh my God. I've put Coca-Cola and milk, not
very good. Yeah? Yeah, don't recommend it. How the fuck would that ever be good? I don't
know, fucking milk and Coca-Cola. You know what? You should put milk in the Freestyle
machines. Yeah. You should, dude. Mix it all up. You should be able to put different flavors
of milk. No, you know what it should be? Okay, here's my invention. We're replacing Freestyle,
or they're putting an update in freestyle machines.
You can choose as many as you want,
like as many different things as you want,
but every additional thing you add,
there's a growing chance that it will just add milk
without telling you.
(laughing)
- He's playing Russian roulette.
- Exactly, yeah.
So if you just want one thing, that's fine.
You don't get any milk.
Two different things mixed together,
there's about a 20% chance there's some milk
getting plopped in there.
- I think you've finally become an inventor, dude.
And we call it the Coca-Cola unfree style.
Oh my God, dude.
- The Coca-Cola battle rap.
- Battle Royale Coca-Cola free machine.
- Yeah, Coca-Cola battle Royale.
- That's pretty good, dude.
All right, I will go pee now.
- Yeah. - All right.
- Bye. - Bye.