You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts are the bomb, lads.
You're a crap monster.
Stop! Not doing a dubstep thing!
No.
No, you guys ruined it already.
You know what?
I'm not-
No, don't mind me.
*Beatboxing*
Now end it, finish it up!
BUM BUM BUM BUM
That was horrible. That was a bad ending.
That's the worst ending I've ever seen.
That is Electric Funeral by Black Sabbath.
So that song has to have an ending at some point, right?
I did a cover.
You have to have some kind of ending for it that you could use.
You need a better ending.
But instead you just hit BOW BOW BOW
You just kind of did the same.
That's how the song ends!
Well they should have written a better ending.
That's one of the top ten Sabbath songs.
It's Iron Man, War Pigs, and they didn't write any other songs to my knowledge.
What about Paranoid?
That was in Guitar Hero.
No, I think that's actually by Justin Bieber.
What the hell?
Paranoid is Justin Bieber, yeah.
No!
Not Justin!
You can't talk about Justin Bieber and Black Sabbath in the same sentence!
Why?
They're two of the greatest guitarists of all time.
No!
Paranoid is a...
What?
Simon was telling me that, like, whatever the guy's name is, he has a funny name.
Tony Iommi?
No, the guy who writes the songs, he has a funny name.
Geezer Butler?
Yeah, Geezer Butler.
he was like writing paranoid he like he the song is about being depressed and he
just forgot what the word for depression was he called it paranoid instead
because the song is all just like I am so crazy cuz I'm frowning all the time
yeah that type of thing. That's so funny. That rules. I love stuff like that and sundry. Yeah. Yeah. And what?
And sundry? Oh sorry I've been playing chivalry too so I like things and sundry. What the fuck are you saying?
my new thing. You don't know about how to talk medieval? No. That's kind of
embarrassing dude. You weren't talking medieval at all. I mostly say stuff like
that in sundry now so. Stop it. It's not medieval. It is medieval. That's just one word. Yeah it's pretty
pretty medieval. You're not saying there's no ye olde or anything. So if I was like so if I was like yeah I'm
gonna go to the store lasers and I think I'm gonna buy like some bread or
something would that be like a futuristic? No because if you were talking
of buying a laser. Okay wait I'm gonna go buy some space bread. Alright. Fairly well. Yeah
me and Patrick have been really into the future lately. So we've been talking sophisticated
like that. Well me I'm more medieval. 001100110011. In our robotic conversations we tend to mention
lot of technology like that so you enjoy the heavens you you you you foul boilers
I will continue to play chivalry to and Sunder three maybe you're playing a
computer game that's not yeah no it is medieval because I don't know how it
works so I'm just I I just medieval guy wouldn't even get to click a button I
mean they weren't many but they were no buttons in the back whenever you're on
one one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one
zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one
one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one
modulation
escapism
You guys you know escapism when they make that like when you're so he's too much
They make you poop so make you poop yourself when they cut open your stomach so a bunch of flies go in
Yeah, I think cam knows camp cam knows a lot more about maybe you know tons of sundry about medieval torture stop stop saying it why
What's wrong? I shall strike you with my claymore Patrick if you don't if you don't simmer down simmer down is medieval, right?
That is pretty bad.
You don't chill, dawg.
Simmer Down is a chariotary on SNL.
No.
Yeah.
You're just making shit up now.
No, I saw a video.
I accidentally watched a video on the podcast YouTube.
Oh, great.
I love checking those recommendations.
I love that.
It is funny, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, you go on there and it's like, "Quentin Tarantino's directorial style at three budgets.
Four hour long video."
I'm like, "Who's watching this?"
this I watched that yeah fuck it's so
interesting it's that guy that drew good
and guy on YouTube you said like I
watched one episode of every SNL season
and this is what they were called yeah
it was like a 30 minute long video I
want nice most of it I mostly get
recommended live news coverage of
tragedies on my person to page yeah I
I got a Challenger explosion on it the other day.
I get like skate videos and then like videos that are like fat guy chugs like Badlands
Chugs but then like Badlands Chugs imitators.
I get a lot of like plumbing community type of things like because I liked it a lot of
it.
I was looking at like the toilet community on YouTube where there was a bunch of drama
where like you know there's this guy who was like these two these two other users were bullying this
youtuber really yeah and it's all videos of them like posting they take a video of the flush of
each toilet they do it in like public toilets too they like stuff them full of toilet paper and then
flush them and go like that was pretty good i watched the challenger thing and i was like
because it was the it was a live cnn coverage and the guy it's gotta be like the worst
Fucking like job ever is like news anchor during like something like that because the guy they're just showing a live feed of the rocket
And then it explodes and then somebody in NASA doesn't realize it's exploding
So you still hear him be like like like the the like radio communications from NASA be like, okay approaching this speed
and they're just all dead and then the guy in the anchor goes like
I'm not sure what has happened
It's like it fucking exploded!
What are you doing?
How do you see that?
You're like, "Oh, hold on, we need to go to the research desk."
That was the fastest rocket I've ever seen!
Wow! It was here one second, gone the next.
These fellas at NASA really know what they're doing.
Yeah.
Man, did you see, uh...
Did you see Jeff Bezos is gonna be in, uh...
the... the space?
Yeah, they're sending him to space?
Jeff Bezos is gonna go to space.
For what reason?
Uh, probably sex stuff.
Probably right?
He's single now?
He's going up to mingle?
You know what, maybe he's only going to space so he can tell women that.
Why'd you say space like that?
What?
Space.
He's uh...
Jeff Bezos is going to spaces.
No.
You could, you know, you could like kill at an open mic with that one dude.
be a you know be an upscale like an open mic that's in a bistro yeah yeah one of
those pay ten bucks yeah yeah so it seems like space fuck Jeff fuck yeah yeah if I
ever do an open mic again you're allowed to just shoot me in the head you're
allowed to like just gun in the head anyway do you under my contract here gun
to my temple you see me at an open mic and you have a gun you can go up to me
You're telling people to bring a gun to a temple? What are you saying?
No! I think you said that dude. I'm saying bring a gun to my temple. You're a big man to poo-do now.
No! I don't want to kill you. If you see me at an open mic, shoot me. Kill me. You should go
to an open mic and d- after you said Bezos like that, I realized that you kind of- your facial
hair is giving me some Nacho Libro vibes. Yeah? Yeah. Nacho Libro. I've talked about this.
- Nacho-ly Nacho.
- Who is it, Lee Lee Nachos?
- I've talked about this before,
I think I've talked about this before,
but when I was in like the third grade,
my Aunt Joanne came over my house
with a newspaper cutout of--
- My Aunt Joanne came over my house.
- That's all I gotta say.
But my Aunt Joanne came over my house
with a newspaper cutout of a picture of like Nacho Libre,
and she was like, "Doesn't this look like Patrick?
"Doesn't this look exactly like Patrick?"
- You were like a skinny little kid.
I was eight!
And she was like, "That looks just like Patrick!"
And I was like, "Why are you saying that to me?"
Why are you saying that to me?
Yeah, she's like, "See?
Told you.
Same guy."
Yeah, that'd be a mean Halloween costume, I think, for you.
Yeah.
Basically any Jack Black role, I think, I could do.
You should do Shallow Hal.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
You should do the Shallow Hal remake, 'cause these days, you want to fuck a fat woman,
and then she looks skinny.
- I wanna see you in full body paint for Kung Fu Panda.
- Okay. - That's right.
- That would actually be,
that would be so fucking funny.
(laughing)
Not wearing a panda costume,
just like painting myself so I look like a panda.
- Wearing just a speedo and--
- And prosthetics. - And painting your entire body.
- Just gonna be like a panda face, dude.
- No, no, no prosthetics, nothing at all.
- Oh, I'm out.
- Just like white face paint.
ears some yeah yeah like just ears just ears yeah I'm like paws maybe you could
have like some no pause your paws no pause yeah you just have to know that
I'm a panda okay you just can't well be pretty obvious once you say skadoosh I
don't know it wouldn't really question much after that yeah not many pandas say
skadoosh yeah well now I'm rethinking this because I don't want to like be the
turtle. I don't want to. Maybe I'll be a panda costume and I'll be I'll be Master
Chief too. It'll probably not be it'll probably not be a good look for me to
only use paint. I mean from the back people are gonna be pretty scared and
confused. Yeah. I hope this he turns around there's some white on that face.
Yeah. And when you turn around people be like oh he's Kung Fu Panda. Yeah. Yeah.
I hope.
Also, you need to be actively doing Kung Fu to avoid the...
I'm looking at Kung Fu Panda right now and he's... the pattern of his fur is that his
arms and legs are black and everything else is white except for the circles around his
eyes.
So I think you might be fine, you know, as long as maybe you don't sweat and the paint
from your armpits goes down and covers your midsection.
That might be a little tough.
Or up to your face.
That would also be...
That would be...
Hanged upside down. Yeah, it's some form of medieval torture. Maybe yeah, or sundry, you know
Or sundry, whichever maybe maybe I go maybe like maybe I go like cropped shirt like cropped long-sleeve
Shirt women love that. No, you that's I mean then just you might as well not be even dress up as a panda
You gotta do like I'm talking like skin tight skin tight under armor cut you talk so much about
your entire body to be Nightcrawler and you know you're bitching out about a
panda he's blue he's a deep blue my friend blue is a dark dark blue not any
yellow eyes which is hard yeah yeah the yellow eyes would be that
also he doesn't know kung-fu or how to Nightcrawler he knows how to teleport
tail though that's not kung-fu teleporting is good it's not kung-fu
It's a type of Kung Fu.
I think he's right.
Teleporting is magic.
Teleporting is like the furthest level of Kung Fu.
I mean, you of all people should at least pretend
to know this, Caleb.
It's a form of sorcery.
But I guess I wouldn't expect you to.
I mean, you don't really know anything about medieval times.
So you obviously don't know anything about this.
There's something called sorcery, all right,
and that comes from magic books.
But then there's also something called chi, okay?
Which is what I'm centering myself with right now
to avoid murdering you with my bare hands.
There's all types of chi too.
There's nacho chi, there's--
So you'd agree that it's a form of magic.
Yeah, this is Nacho Chi.
That's right.
Whose Chi is it?
Nacho's.
Nacho Chi.
But Chi is, I guess, Chi is not really magic though.
Chi is like essence and spiritual power that you can use to teleport.
I don't think that Nightcrawler uses Chi to teleport.
I think he uses magic.
No, he uses Chi in Sunday as well.
He uses oomph to teleport.
Shut up!
What does that even mean?
It's the sound that they make.
It's bamf.
Oh, bamf.
fucking idiot don't even know shit about X-Men dude you guys both don't know
anything and I'm the only smart guy on this podcast all right wait till I say
that's a huge that's very embarrassing for me to not know the Nightcrawler
sound can we restart the whole episode no because I'm now I'm starting to think
about chi and its various uses I think I think nobody would mind if we restarted
the whole thing I'm a high chi individual yeah you're very low chi I have insanely
I'm extremely high chi.
You have very low chi.
You don't know anything, dude.
I've never seen you meditate once.
I'm one of the best meditators.
I've meditated for hours.
No, you're not.
You don't know anything.
Yeah, I have.
You cannot meditate for hours.
I've meditated on a beach and I've lost a sense of myself
'cause I've had so much chi in my body.
That's bad.
That's not a good thing to lose a sense of self.
That's what meditation is about, okay?
No, it's not.
You're talking to the foremost expert on chi
on this podcast.
me. No, you're not talking to yourself. I'm talking to myself. Hey, what's up? Okay, crazy.
I'm hanging out. Oh, you're fucking crazy. Yeah, I mean, I wouldn't expect a lesser mind
to understand, you know, the power of Zen of talking to yourself, but, you know, being
at one with yourself. Here's the truth, my mind is completely turned off. You know, people
who often have dim minds will label others as crazy, whose ideas they can't comprehend.
Okay, okay. Yeah. And sundry, but whatever. I kind of am like the perfect hybrid between
medieval knight and a Chinese monk. Yeah. In sundry with my chi yeah. Yeah.
Yeah because I basically yeah because I mix the spiritual beliefs of
the Far East and the Orient with the bravery and the tactics of a
medieval knight, an officer actually. You know they call me a berserker.
don't call you a berserker. A berserker is not a knight because a berserker follows a code of
chivalry a berserker has no code it's chaos. Well they call me the berserker
knight. They don't call you that. It's a nickname. Who calls you that? A berserker with a code is not a knight.
Yeah I mean a berserker and knight are like opposites. Yeah. They're like opposite
ends of the order and chaos kind of spectrum. Would two white guys know or would the
berserker knight know? I think me. I think I would know. Would two white guys know or would a pink guy
know that's a good question I do look very pink today because I'm so filled
with rage as a berserker you look like you look like Majin Buu I know oh no I
wasn't gonna say Majin Buu but that's pretty good I was gonna say you look
like you look like if mr. bubble already so much worse just say I'm Majin Buu no
Who's Mr. Bubble?
You guys don't know Mr. Bubble?
I look like Mr. Bubble?
Yeah, you look like pink...
I just googled Mr. Bubble and nothing came up.
This is inventing a fucking character, man.
Oh, okay, here we go.
Yeah, Mr. Bubble.
You should not be using this on your body.
This looks like it will kill you.
Why? I use that every day.
Mr. Bubble?
Yeah.
This is not acceptable.
It's a bubble bath. It's colored exactly like...
You take a bubble bath every day?
Yes, I use this in the shower.
Really?
No. What the fuck? Why would I do that?
I don't know.
Because you said that. You said you'd do it.
Oh, now I can't even believe my friends anymore.
You're robbing me of my chi every time you lie to me.
And one day the entire Earth is going to be in grave danger.
I do think you're sure.
And I will have to defend it.
I'm talking about Mr. Bubble now.
Shut up!
No!
Nobody cares about Mr. Bubble!
They want to hear about cheating!
His name isn't even Mr. Bubble.
It says Mr. Bubbles.
No, it's Mr. Bubble.
Here it says Mr. Bubble, but then here it says Mr. Bubbles.
What's the difference?
You're doing the Mario effect to me right now.
Oh, Mr. Bubbles is from Bioshock.
Yeah.
Okay.
It corrected my search.
I searched Mr. Bubble and it said, "You mean Mr. Bubbles?"
No, I mean Mr. Bubble.
Can you guys get off the computer?
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
Just turn off your computers for one second.
No, don't leave.
No, you have to come back.
Guys.
Well, guess who it is.
It's just me.
Just like I wanted.
Just as I planned.
Now, I can teach you all sorts of chi tricks.
Chi, by the way, is short for China, which is where chi comes from.
And I source...
Don't breathe.
Thank you.
Stop!
You look like...
Nobody wants to hear that, dude.
Cam just turned off his camera.
- Whatever man, anyway, the best way to focus your chi
is to, it's a technique, ancient Chinese technique
called edging.
- It's not.
No.
- Yeah, so you basically rub the tip of your--
- I mean, a real monk would not even touch his thing.
- Yeah, you rub the tip of your penis
like a roller deodorant.
- Monks take a vow, the monks sign a thing
that says no Tadra touching.
We don't touch it.
- I touch my little Tadra all the time
and I'm one of the best monks in the world.
- So you just lost your place in the order of the monks.
Explain my baggy clothes if I ain't no monk, huh?
You're a hip-hop.
Shit.
You mean that?
All right, maybe I might be giving up on the monk code, and I might let myself come, and
I might become a rapper now.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What's your rapping name?
Fucking Swag Fucker.
Swag Fucker?
Is it one word or two words?
Three words.
Where's the...
Swag Fucker.
What the hell? Swag fuck her.
Oh man. That's right.
Big word expecting that.
I wasn't expecting that. My chi tricks.
You don't have any chi tricks. I can't emphasize that enough. That wasn't chi.
I'm gonna chi grab something in my room right now.
That's the force. You're thinking of the force. It moved a little bit. It didn't move.
Your webcam moved.
your way watching a round on the on the my webcam with just she
i can see your home or the
all my god it's not a pure energy
she coming out of my hand i would she does all you need a force
she
i'm sick i'm chicken i'm saying he
i'm sick of sundry
i'm still this
then fine what you talk about something
Okay.
Let's- and here's- here you go.
You're not allowed to use Google and just read a website.
You have to talk about something, Pat.
Alright.
Go.
Have you ever seen, um, the movie...
The, uh...
Doctor...
It's either Strange Love or- or...
Strange?
Doctor Strange.
Have you seen Doctor Strange?
No.
So you're saying I have- well, this is back to Chi, man.
I haven't seen-
You fucked it up!
It's not back to Chi.
Is there Chi in Doctor Strange?
Yeah, he gets uh...
Tilda Swinton plays a Chinese man.
An old, old Chinese man.
And gifts him with the power of Chi.
I never saw that movie.
I thought it looked...
It looked a little too trippy for me.
Isn't it in Tibet?
I don't want to step on any...
Oh shit.
China, Tibet, same shit.
No, no, don't, no.
We can't, no.
It's like saying the US and Hawaii.
That's not the same.
Tibet's basically Hawaii.
It's where all the--
Tibet is not a tropical island paradise.
Here, how about this?
Tibet is not part of China.
It's part of the United States.
I don't even know what the situation over there is.
I don't want to say something that'll get us kicked out.
It's probably good, dude.
Get kicked out of what?
We're not in Tibet right now.
What are you talking about?
What if we get kicked off the Chinese market?
I don't think anybody has ever listened to our podcast
in China.
How do you know?
Because we would have statistical information.
We get analytics.
Can we look up the analytics right now?
I'll look at it right now.
Here, I'm logging in.
If we have a single Chinese listener, then I will...
Alright, I'm logging in.
I'm typing in the password.
You saw what John Cena had to do?
He had to learn Chinese.
He didn't have to do that.
He did that because he wanted to.
Did he?
I don't know.
Okay, so...
But yeah, it's a bet.
I mean, have you seen how strong that guy is?
Nobody can make him do anything.
No, no.
You could take down China with one punch.
Let's see.
Yep, nobody in China.
Zero.
Okay, alright, Tibet's Hawaii.
Don't say Tibet's Hawaii!
Tibet is as...
Let's see what the top countries are.
United States, yep.
Canada's next biggest.
So, I mean, I don't know about if I want...
Okay, Canada is basically...
...is like Tibet for the United States.
Then we got the UK coming in after that.
I mean, even less I want them.
this you know here's my hope one day I mean they probably call this podcast
about cues over there yeah it's fucked up nice one day I pray that one day I log
on to pod bean to look at our analytics right I open up that map entire world
red white and blue America that's right every single listeners in America
because the entire world is America is - we have six downloads from Israel whoa
Sounds like a council has downloaded our podcast. Yeah, well um, because
it's because people say free to bet right? What's that all about? I think free
free is Chinese for for very nice. No. Why are you trying so hard to talk about
this when you don't know anything about it and are terrified of it? If it's free.
You can just move on.
If it's free, I'm taking it.
You're not, you can't take Tibet dude, they'll get mad.
China, the owners, will get mad at you.
I don't know if that's right!
They will, dude.
They own Tibet, it's like their pet.
We have 23 downloads from Poland.
I think it was probably one person who just downloaded the same episode 23 times by accident.
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- Fuck them, dude.
We should take down Tibet, I think.
- Three from Serbia. - No!
- Why?
- Can we, dude, we're all across the world.
God damn, dude.
- Anybody in Galactoy? - One from Nepal.
- Yep, it says five trillion in Galactoy.
- Ooh, wow.
That's not bad.
- Should we read our analytics on the show?
- Yeah, it doesn't matter.
Four from Saudi Arabia.
Yo, my cousins!
I'm about to get flown out, fuck.
Three in Hong Kong.
Would you guys do that?
If a Saudi oil prince--
It's funny, it's Hong Kong you, but not China.
Okay.
That's a stance Pabin's taking.
If a Saudi oil prince asked us three
to come out for a lavish vacation for one week
in the United Arab Emirates.
Absolutely, yes.
Yes, right, you know, we know what's happening
What's what's happening? He's gonna fuck our faces and our assholes. He's not gonna do that and he's friendly. They have a they're a friendly country
Yeah, I guess you're right Saudi Arabia. Have you seen like mostly friendly country?
I mean they Steve Harvey goes over there all the time. Yeah, they have they got big Tigers and stuff that they have
It's pets. I just don't even kill anyone
I mean to throw the Tigers to be that friendly the people got to be for I guess you're right
you gotta be really a very empathetic person. I looked up Steve Harvey Dubai
and the people also ask on Google, Google.com says
what is Steve Harvey doing in Dubai? That's a good question. Here's a... It's him searching that.
He's like I can't remember why I'm here. This is why he was in Dubai. Are you on
Are you on the Emirates news agency?
Yeah, Steve Harvey experiences world's coolest winter in the Emirates.
Dubai, 18th December 2020.
American actor and host Steve Harvey will embark on a journey across the Emirates
to experience life as a citizen in an exclusive docuseries to be released this weekend.
We have to get our hands on this docuseries.
Steve Harvey is experiencing life as a citizen of the UAE.
This picture is nuts.
Dude, he looks amazing.
Look at that fucking drip, dude.
God, he's so cool.
I love Steve Harvey's, like...
Is he wearing the...
That guy who's pointing at him, that's Nas Daily.
That guy who used to post all those videos
where he, like, on Facebook and shit
where, like, he got a ton of followers
and he would, like, post things. He was like,
"Here's why I wear a t-shirt that has a loading bar on it.
It represents the days of my life
and I wear a different one every day."
And then he did a bunch of videos that were, like,
of
I'm still looking at pictures of Steve Harvey.
By user Swank.
Swank's most beautiful Pokemon.
Is he doing a version of Family Feud there?
I would hope.
That'd be sick dude.
Oh man.
Name the most sexual part of a woman.
Bing!
Her knees.
What?
You said what?
He's freaking out.
Yeah.
Ahhhh!
Fuck!
Alright, the list, most beautiful Pokemon.
Here's a picture, sorry to, here's a picture of Steve Harvey.
Yeah, go ahead, second time, yeah, let's do pictures this episode, you know what, let's talk about pictures. Go ahead.
This is a picture of Steve Harvey holding a falcon it looks like.
Yeah, I've seen that one.
He has a message.
I haven't seen it, okay.
I thought it was, I like that that's the thing that made you feel bad is that I had seen it before.
I thought I was giving you like a treat.
No.
Let me tell you something, image of Steve Harvey, never a treat.
What?
He's a good looking guy.
What are you talking about?
He's amazing.
He looks like a Chuck E. Cheese animatronic.
No, I love Steve Harvey.
I fucking love him.
He's great.
What was that thing your dad texted you about him?
Oh yeah, what?
He just texted me.
Sometimes, he likes to watch Family Feud, and hey, I do too.
Sometimes he just texts me the things that he saw on Family Feud that night.
Let me see if I can...
You gotta read one, dude.
I'm scrolling your text.
I'm scrolling off to find it.
Oh yeah, dude, the Burger Fest this week?
Oh fuck, I leaked.
Yeah, don't leak Burger Fest.
Oh shit!
I wasn't supposed to talk about that.
I'm so fucking sorry.
We're on the lineup for next year though.
God damn it.
Watching Family Feud.
Question. You're fishing in the ocean and pull up a mermaid.
What are you going to do?
Contestant answers.
And this is all formatted very well.
He's a writer, runs in the fan.
Yeah.
One, see how much money I can get for her.
Two, put her in the cooler.
Three, use her for bait.
And the next text message, Steve Harvey's reactions were hilarious.
Do you think that's like the audio captions for people with vision impairment?
Steve Harvey makes hilarious reactions.
Top 10's most beautiful Pokemon.
This is by user Swank.
Check out Swank.
What does Swank's hold?
Fucking deal.
Pretty much nothing.
Full name and age.
Yep.
I clicked on that too.
All right.
Number one.
Full name, Hillary.
Hillary Swank.
Move to the right a little.
Number one, Gardevoir.
This is the sexy Pokemon.
This is the one that looks like a woman in a dress.
That everyone thinks is beautiful.
Yeah, I mean she's fucking hot.
Wait, this is not-
I'd fuck any Pokemon.
What?
The story, dude.
Okay.
Alright, yeah, the story is name a Pokemon that you wouldn't fuck mr. Mime
Fucking beat the mind your mind jr. What do you think about my junior? I beat it up, dude
Let me Google baby Pokemon really quick. No, don't not a Rita. No, no, my babies. I'm juniors a baby Pokemon you already
All right. Well, no, baby. Here's my rule
Okay, no, baby, too man, man, no, we both told me and I wrote any of them baby. I like your first generation
What about Ella kid Ella kid?
It's got kid in the name. I'm gonna take I have to pass on you already said you fuck every Pokemon
But not that I'm not gonna know there. What do you fuck this Pokemon named Ching?
I would fuck any Pokemon second generation or further along I'd beat it up
Okay, I think I like it is second generation that that that Pokemon is gonna. I'm gonna have to
Allocate is second generation so you're talking more. I'm gonna be walking funny
What about what about man tight right up to the I asked my ass in or have to be have to be regenerated after my shit
that's right the nurse whatever name is
nurse Jackie I'm gonna beat it up on
right you and then it's like you're
gonna be funny she's addicted to pee pee
up or something yeah I'm gonna put my
pee pee up in there I don't know what to
tell you that's gross what you wouldn't
I wouldn't fuck any Pokemon no Gardevoir
What what about there's one that's that's the playboy bunny one which one really look up. Yeah, look up sexy bunny Pokemon
I don't remember what it's named
It's probably that was the one that was the one where they did Gardevoir and they were like
Oh, we saw how many people freaked out about guard or we gotta go even further dude Gardevoir is a psycho type creature
You know, she crazy in the bedroom. See a little bit crazy. Yeah, I need me a Pokemon
that's a little bit crazy and makes you breakfast in the morning.
Rabbit, Pokemon, Lopunny. Look up Lopunny. L-O-P-U-N-N-Y.
I'd rather look up Lola Bunny over here.
I mean, you pretty much are, yeah.
Oh, fuck!
Damn, she's got a bikini on.
Yeah, pretty crazy that they went for that one.
Yeah, that's nuts.
That one's like, Gardevoir at least has some plausible deniability of like,
looks like a wedding dress it's beautiful
below parties you know that's
yet i don't need a plausible deniability because i did not have a tough but that
money
what's the it's a pokey mom
it's not an animal
that's i mean it's still your that's a you're saying that about some ten year
olds best friends basically
successfully what it could be what you
What are you saying here?
That's what Pokemon are.
Are you saying, "I would fuck this kid's pet."
Oh no.
No, it's not a pet.
I told you, it's not an animal.
It's a warrior.
It's definitely a pet.
It's either a pet or a best friend.
Alright, there's a...
Wait, there's gotta...
There's so many comments on here.
Yeah, there are a whole lot, dude.
We can't waste time.
Holy shit.
Wait, I gotta...
The comments are all insanely long, too.
I like her most.
She is really strong.
She has mega form.
She is really beautiful.
She is best in fairy.
be dragon type pokemon easily. Alright, but talk about the ratio here, you know? I don't
care about her abilities. You know? Unless she has a vacuum ability. I mean, you're gonna
care about her abilities. Yeah. Yeah. Um, there's, these are, Gardevoir's my most favorite
pokemon. She was based off of a guardian angel. I can't believe she is treated like crap!
And she will risk her own life to protect her trainer. She can even create a small black
cold just to protect her trainer. It's just sad to see that Gardevoir is treated so badly.
She is beautiful.
Ladies, I really love her design. This Pokemon is really really fabulous. Faf-faf-fabulous.
I also love her shiny style too.
I know Gardevoir can be male, but I usually treat it as female.
What?
There's male Pokemon?
Oh yeah, we should have gone in on that angle with you.
I still beat it up.
(laughs)
- These, yeah, these comments are, are...
It's so graceful, elegant, beautiful, cute, everything.
It deserves more.
And it's so strong, too.
It's better than any dumb Eevee or Pikachu.
And don't go off about all the porn going around.
It's not Gardevoir's fault.
(laughs)
- It's not Gardevoir's, is it Revenge porn?
- Speaking of that, this comment here says,
it's beautiful, but the fan art, no.
not friendly
no more fan art this thing is beautiful strong protective and uh... i don't know
as kentrick lamar said
be humble
wow
this is some serious fan art
someone has a gardevoir with a gaping
asshole looks like it's been opened with some sort of
like vice
uh... what else
what else
this is it
sucking a rhinos penis
the uh... uh... okay you know what you mean a ryan horn
uh... right on i don't know
uh... what else they got here
uh... what is purple nipples uh...
that's so that's interesting owner also the long guard or style penis
i'd just learned
record for is beautiful both on the outside and inside
that's right
Yeah, beautiful on the inside.
Most of the... my problem with like when people take fictional characters that are non-human
and then draw like a sex version, they always just make it a woman with the same colored
hair.
Yeah.
That's lazy, dude.
What are you doing?
It's just lazy.
I mean, I...
I mean I'm not trying to, you know, not all the time look up Gardevoir naked giant pussy,
but when I do, I don't want it to be just some green haired woman.
Right, you want the trainer to be in there too, is what I'm getting from this, right?
This is so messed up.
You want Ash Ketchum messed up as hell.
No!
No, I want, I want the, she should have the dress on, it should be tasteful.
You want to see her come out of the Pokeball so you know she's a Pokemon.
That's right. That is exactly right. Yeah, I need some proof.
Yeah. I agree that Gardevoir's looks are pretty. I think the reason why she's treated as porn
is all because of that chest spike.
Dude, that's chest spike? I didn't even know.
Chest spike.
Wow.
Can we move on from this so Caleb can stop talking about Gardevoir?
Every time I get home from work, I go to my computer and search Gardevoir on Google Images.
Then I grab my lotion and rub it on my wiener.
(laughing)
- Oh fuck, that's awesome.
That kid rules.
- That's not a kid, it's a get home from work.
- That guy rules.
- Number two.
My low tick.
This is a snake.
- Yeah, this one is not doing it for me.
- This is a snake with beautiful hair.
- I'm gonna be real.
Yeah, this is why this list is so funny to me is because it starts off with Gardevoir, which is like okay understandable
I mean, you know I'm not gonna endorse fucking wanting to fuck Pokemon
But yeah, you know Gardevoir like whatever that that one I get the rest of these are all like snakes and dogs
Yeah, this is literally just a
This is snake exact. It's a worm. It's a colorful
Well this this one
Evolves from my lotic evolves from Phoebus. Yeah, which is just like a bonefish. It's like an ugly magic carp. Yeah
Yeah, it's like a rotten magic carp. Oh, yeah Phoebus looks messed up. I just don't like her mustache looking thing
What eyebrows I'm thinking they're talking about her eyebrows
Here's a comment here no offense my lotic fans, but she kind of looks like a slug yeah
But well more of a beautiful one still I think people judge Gardevoir a bit too harshly while Milotic gets all the attention
She's beautiful, but it's Pokemon abuse
Milotic starts as an ugly Phoebus, but transforms into the world's prettiest Pokemon
She looks like the goddess of the sea and even the Pokédex states that she is the most beautiful Pokemon
If you think Gardevoir is the prettiest then you must think poop is beautiful
That's kind of unfair that the Pokédex says uh, yeah, just states it outright
That's kind of um, it's kind of not. Okay. I think I think they should leave it up to I
Agree fans to decide toots looks like a slug in mascara
All right calling a Pokemon
A little more personal than I yeah comfortable with maybe
Great design tomboys won't like her because she's girly
(laughter)
- This person also said,
"I just don't like her mustache and her black spots.
"Other than that, she's pretty."
Is there something we're missing here?
- A mustache?
- I think it's just the eyebrows thing.
- I think it is.
- They're clearly eyebrows though.
- Yeah, what's wrong with these people?
Number three.
- It looks like Chinesse legendary dragon to me.
special personality and simple look
it is beautiful like a chinese legendary dragon
number three
prima rena
this is a seal
this is a seal dog
this is a dog seal dressed like a ballerina this is a good pokemon to have
if it learns uh...
if it learns what?
what patrick spit it out
if it learns moon blast it got me through the it got me through the
I'm going to moon this Pokemon and then I'm going to blast it.
Coming through the finals.
No.
Primarina, in my opinion, is the most beautiful Pokemon and I think she is most beautiful than Melodic.
Her hair are just so pretty, her eyes are blue as ocean and her eyelashes are killer.
She is a mermaid ocean queen.
Obviously the most beautiful starter on par with Milotic.
Don't give me that Serperior.
No question this challenger needs to be in the top 10.
It even has a run at being completely viable.
It's like a goddamn fairy tale.
How the unwanted Popplio becomes something so sought after.
I mean, jeez, it uses a goddamn spirit bomb.
Majestic!
Rule 34, please, you do not want to do this.
(laughing)
- Beautiful, majestic, sweet, caring, kind.
She is just lovely.
- I want her so bad.
(laughter)
- That's what I mean, that's not,
man you can just go look at a mermaid,
you don't have to look at what this dog did.
- I need Primarina so bad, I need that.
- Her eyes stun me.
(laughter)
Oh man.
- She's so beautiful, queen, period.
- Too pretty and powerful.
see this is this is a heavy drop off here
for the uh... so this is what i'm talking about how how they're not more like
sexual look they didn't even put the sexy rabbit in the italy a playboy boy
that's not even the time i received to upset that the sexy rabbit isn't i'm
that i don't know what i don't name is that or that should absolutely be over a
thing this is a dog with multiple tell i'm sorry what about who's making this
list
mhm horny children
uh...
now I don't want to do it. Or maybe you're the one who said that, who's making the list.
Or grown men who want to fuck dogs maybe. Yeah, probably, you know, honestly.
One guy said he winks his wiener when he comes home from work.
Yeah, I guess you're right, he winks it. Number four is nine tails. I guess the appeal of this is like
a whole lot, there's a lot there. Yeah, I mean nine asses? I mean yeah, what kind of a dump truck ass
could possibly support Ninetales.
You know?
- Here's a comment.
Ninetales, so much Ninetales.
People just think Gardevoir is the most beautiful Pokemon
because it's human-like.
Ninetales really takes the cake.
It's powerful, myth-like, and its fur is so shiny.
If you grab one of its beautiful tails,
you will be cursed forever.
- You know, there's a reason that among the Pokeparents memes
Ninetales is the MILF.
- What?
- Ninetales is a MILF, I guess.
Why would you look at like a dog and call it a MILF?
I don't know.
Here's a poem.
Here's a poem I wrote about this beautiful fox.
Nine tails, oh nine tails.
Spellbound eyes so enchanting.
Tails that bring curses for those who grab them.
Wait, so if you grab the tail...
Oh, that's why she's so high, dude.
Cause it's like, it's forbidden fruit.
More so than any other dog.
Nine tails.
(laughing)
- Ninth Tales, enchanting eyes, elegant beauty
that matches no other, fire of a burning passion.
The beauty is unmistakable.
- This is amazing.
- The fire of a burning passion.
- That's so beautiful.
- It's a dog.
(laughing)
- The milfy dog though, I guess.
- I hate that they called it a milf.
- Just relax, Patrick.
You're such a prude.
- I guess I am.
cartoon
just you know i think it almost you're so conservative about this it feels like
you're covering up your desire for the stuff
uh... all mad dog grabbing all nine of its tails we fucking hit it from the
back of the car
uh...
what's wrong with these people all my god
you nasty
i'm not number five we stop talking about the burning passion of this book
and how romantic an evening with it would be.
- Okay, we get it, it has beautiful red eyes
that just cut right through you.
But, I mean, can we stop talking about fucking eating
its nine pussies?
What the hell?
- And a stunning conversation list.
- It has nine tails.
- Yeah, you would know, you've done a lot of research
on the matter, have you?
- I just don't like it when you guys switch it.
- Number five, dragonair.
This is another worm.
- Yeah, this is straight up a worm.
- This is a worm with big ears.
- This is a worm that turns into like--
- This is a worm that turns into a big--
turns into a dragon tails dragon. But it can fly right? Yeah. A flying worm. Suck you upside down.
Suck your shit off upside down dude. I don't know what to tell you.
I need to find, I need to hear from the kind of people that want to fuck this flying worm.
I need to know, like you know the dog, it's like okay I know there's a lot of people online who
want to fuck a dog. I don't think I've ever like ever read anything from somebody who wants to
for two years. Every time I see it I just fall completely silent. That's how beautiful it
is. This should be number one. Google her with safe search off, I dare you. What? It doesn't
have arms or legs or anything. It's a line. Hey, for research purposes, Dragonair nasty
naked. Oh no. Pokemon sex Dragonair porn videos on Pornhub. Hold on. That's just a girl. That's
for
It's way worse though.
Yeah, it's way, way worse.
Oh, here, let's see, this one has a caption.
So this is Dragonair with a, what looks like a dildo that says Impale Lord on the side of
it.
Impale Lord?
Yeah, getting fucked in its cloaca and it says, "Wailord migration is just around the
corner.
Girl, I wanna see your vulva get wrecked by them all.
So keep up the good work."
Oh, that's nice and encouraging, I guess.
Yeah, I guess that's pretty nice.
I guess that's sweet.
I don't here's what okay well this is just not okay this is this one is a
dragonair sucking a digimon's penis and that I won't stand for that.
That's too far. Yeah you can't put a digimon and a pokemon together I won't allow that.
Fuck as many of these fucking rainbow dogs as you want but just don't mix the
the universes please. That's fucked up. It's not okay. Is there any sexual digimon?
Digimon?
Aren't there some Digimon that are just like people?
Yeah, there are many.
There are a lot of sexual Digimon.
Yeah, because a lot of Digimon are just people with like weird, with like power.
There's one Digimon that, from season 3, that the creator has like gone on record of being
like "I hate you people because you can't Google the name of this Digimon anymore without
it just being porn."
Oh yeah, I'm looking this up and one of the Digimon is just a woman in a bikini.
Yeah, there are a lot like that.
There are a lot that are like angels and stuff.
There's one called Renamon that's like an anthropomorphic fox.
And there's a lot of porn of that one.
This one looks way more like a fox than a person.
Yeah, no, that's the thing.
That's why people want to drop porn of it so bad.
If it's just a person, it's not as interesting.
Number six, Glaceon.
This is just a dog.
This is the closest to the dog that we had.
This is just an ice dog.
This is a dog and if you fuck it your dick's gonna be really cold.
Yeah.
It's a very cold dog.
Uh, yeah, now this is, isn't this the same thing as Ninetales or something?
Which, uh, which Eeveelution are you guys?
Oh, so now you get into it.
I wanna know which Eeveelution you are.
Why should you fuck me, you fucking freak?
No.
So you know which one I've, I'm the bikini dog, you still wanna fuck me?
There's no bikini Eeveelution.
I don't know.
There is.
I'm not which one bikini on is that new it's a secret it's brand new it's one of
the other ones they just announced it I didn't know that Pamela Pamela and Iran
is on that it's like though really the hottest version of that dog that's the
facts I think I'm Brianna's cool you were on
on
dog out of it. Yeah, it just looks like a black lab. Yeah.
And Pat's icing us out now. We're a total Glaceon now.
He muted himself.
You fucker. Glaceon reminds me of an angel. She is so pretty. If I was a
Pokemon, I would love to be Glaceon.
She was, here's a comment. She was my guardian when I was born.
She is so pretty, her color, her cry too much.
Oh, her cry too much for me.
Her cry too much though.
She play too much.
She play far too much.
This one, each word is capitalized.
She's not always a girl.
Wow.
That'll blow your mind.
Yeah, that'll be a serious Ace Ventura moment.
Number seven is Ab-Sol.
Ab-Sol is like a...
Again, a dog.
again a dog yeah it's a dog it's got a it's got a scythe for an ear yeah it's a
dog with like an evil Bluetooth headset yeah that's it's a dog dude I mean like
the next four just like dog cat what is wrong with these people dude I mean I
guess it's probably diagnosable what is wrong with them huh could you go to the
doctor be like hey I want to fuck dogs like can you like give me medicine
I'm sure you could go to like a therapist or something. I don't know about the doctor.
I don't know if the doctor usually deals with that kind of stuff.
You go to a doctor and you tell them that. All he'll do is check your blood pressure.
Yep, and be like, "Well, you're in pretty good condition of fucking dogs actually. You
can probably last a long time." Yeah. I was confused in my physical why the doctor checked
my wiener twice, but the second time he brought a dog into the room just to see if there were
any changes. But there's gotta be some like chemical imbalance, right? That you could...
I don't know. I don't know if I want to go on the record with that one.
Yeah. I'm not sure about that. You're right. It's the devil infesting those people.
I'll stick by that. That's probably... that honestly is the safer
opinion to have. Yeah. Well, the devil, it takes these people over. But they do it on purpose still.
Esbion... no, Sylveon. Sylveon's number eight. This is just a pink dog. This is a fairy type dog.
yeah
uh...
israeli disgusting here
lots of long comments again on this one
uh...
there are there's a war between sylveon and espion fans in the comments here
well like a mud war
command
come on
uh... and it's just too long to even see a user not number nine is at alolan nine
tails which is just blue a blue version oh yeah it's the ice tails yeah ice type
nine tails again freeze your cock and balls off and it's not dog too I think
it's a I mean I guess you're right but if you're you know in for a in for a
dime in for a dollar right so it's already been no I think I already been
dogs this whole time man this one is a cold dog you know listen I don't want to
fuck a dog if you do it so you're saying if you if you were on like tinder and he
were swiping through and you were like you saw a dog you're like no I'm swiping
no you saw another dog you swipe no you saw another dog you swipe no and by the
fifth dog you're like you know I guess if it's gonna be all dogs I might as well swipe right up this one
is that what you're saying?
no listen what I'm saying is if I get captured in sort of a saw situation and
jigsaw is like you have to choose
you spent your entire life not fucking dogs
you have to choose are you going to fuck a dog and I'm like what a dog fuck no
And he's like or a cold dog. I'm just gonna fuck the dog. I don't want the cold
Those are the two options in this list of two options that I'm being given started with a woman I
Was one woman
I want to fuck a worm worm is off the table for me. Yeah, I'm not fucking a worm
But yeah, I'm gonna put that on record. I wouldn't fuck any animals either, but if Jigsaw is
If Jigsaw is telling me you have to fuck a dog or a really cold dog, which one?
I listen I'm not just gonna roll over and die, you know, maybe I have some heart or flavor that has some medieval in me.
Yeah, I think the trap is beautiful dogs.
I'm walking out of the room. Yeah, also the doors unlocked.
You can leave whenever you want.
I forgot to lock the door and honestly it's hard for me to get back in this room that I'm in.
I don't know why I told you that. Yeah, beers are messed up. Oh shit.
What do you do with a dog? The door's unlocked.
Jesus Christ. I'm not even, I don't even have any cameras in the room.
I can't even prove you did this. No!
Best did me!
See that's what I would do if I was in a saw situation
Just like if there's like a trap before he even finishes the monologue just jump into it and die
Yeah, cuz I think about the thing about the saw series
Right is that you have to play the tape recorder every time and those movies are very unrealistic
Not because like the traps are crazy or because there's like stupid plot twists
It's cuz like yeah a normal person a saw trap would not
Press play on a tape recorder before they just like try to what like this things was like if you open the door
it shoots you in the face and it's like I don't know that if I see a door I'm just
gonna walk out I'm gonna waste time like no I'm gonna turn on I'm gonna hear a
guy doing a scary voice like yeah I don't have to listen to this yeah well
you can always hope that there's maybe yeah some music in there I mean I've
played video games I'm skipping the cutscenes I don't care yeah exactly I'm
getting right to the game well I got a flamethrower attached to my head I'm not
pressing fucking play on a tape recorder also get what you give me an iPod right
What the hell? Why do you still use a tape recorder?
You know how much?
Are you making no money off these movies?
You have to be making some money.
Are you one of those guys who buys like,
cassettes, like music cassettes?
Is that like, you know, like...
You think it's cooler?
You think it's cool? You think it's trendy?
It's not trendy. It went out of style a really long time ago.
And it's hard. What if the tape jams?
That's the other thing.
Yeah, what if a magnet's near it?
What if you need a magnet for your trap?
And it erases your tape?
This J-Sup character is pretty stupid when you think about it.
I mean he's not a puppet so you might.
He's actually a haunted puppet.
He's a guy.
He's Toby Bell.
No, it's Chucky.
No, you're thinking of Billy the puppet.
His name's Billy.
I thought it was Jigsaw.
He's a puppet who works for Jigsaw.
Some job that is.
He's just an actor like in Iron Man 3?
He's a puppet actually.
More than an actor.
I guess you could say.
An actor is kind of a puppet.
Wow.
- Wow.
- Yeah, that's--
- So the next one, this is a little girl.
- This one's kind of a person, but it is a little girl.
- Yeah.
- So I don't really care what they have to say about it.
- Next one, what is that?
I don't know how to describe that.
- Next one is some kind of four dimensional being.
- It's like a, yeah, it's like a spaceship.
It looks like a spaceship.
- Oh, Meloletta.
- No, we're skipping that one because that's a child.
- I didn't know that.
- But I mean, you can talk about that as much as you want.
for it dude that's all you man I that's where you want to jump in on this
Patrick then hey who might have stopped you here's a no is a comment of
Cresselia please come with me to my dreamland is this Pokemon supposed to be
a banana yeah yeah it looks like it looks like a blue banana it looks fucked
up it doesn't look like a real thing yeah it looks like a damn Pokemon I'm pissed
off at a banana number 12 dog that's a cat that's a cat
on it that's beyond the dog that's a cat there like a half cat look at the ears
nothing about that is dog like number 13 is Ernie s that's a big deer yeah
Zerny ass gonna have a hurdy-ass when I'm done
fucking that thing no I don't want to do that with this others are never a pair
to this pokemon how does a stupid absolute get how does a stupid absol
get on this scale
wait low pony is on this one dude the bunny one is number fifteen
number fourteen is lapras which is like a loch ness monster turtle pokemon
so number fifteen is the playboy bunny
low pony
uh... just look at its cream or its creme colored fur and its rosy pink eyes
aren't they cute and hands are just so damn cute she is a precious beauty and is
the most beautiful in my opinion.
Someone says, "I would prefer Mega Lopunny."
That's how I feel about most women.
Yeah.
Uh, you're nice.
Lopunny looks like a...
Can you become Mega?
Can I use my Mega Stone on you?
Is there a level X version of you?
Maybe you have an older sister or something?
Lopunny looks like a woman, and sometimes women get offended.
[laughter]
Next one, Rapidash.
This is a horse.
This is the most realistic animal, like, the most realistic horse.
This is straight up a horse.
This is a horse that is on fire.
Yeah.
Which again...
Most of the dog Pokemon, they're like, you know, it doesn't look exactly like a dog.
It has maybe some ribbons or like a magic stone in its forehead.
This is a horse.
This is a horse that you couldn't even...
A realistically...
Couldn't even touch it without burning yourself.
Anatomically drawn horse.
And it's got fire on its ass.
Yeah, and someone says her butt is so fat that it makes her look fabulous.
It's a fucking horse.
Number 17.
Another snake.
Yeah.
Sir Piri or superior
It's a snake 18 is frost lass
Kind of a lass maybe bit of it a lass. I mean more of a weird totem pole creature number 19 is a dog
It's sweet coon and then wait number 21 is a ho-oh
Bird again, what's the ho?
Number 22 Zardacoon Oh another bird back-to-back, dude
Number three, Roserade, that's a number 23, the Roserade is a flower.
Yeah. Yep.
R canine.
It's a dog.
That's just like a husky.
That's a big dog.
Meow stick.
Those are two cats.
Two, but they're twins.
They're twin cats.
Number 26, I've never seen this one before.
What is this?
It's a hat.
Oh, Hatterene.
Hatterene?
Hatterene.
Oh, okay.
Oh, all right.
That's Rene.
Hatterene.
I think that's Sun and Moon. Someone says a beautiful vibe check. Somebody else says
it's a blob a pretty blob. Number 27 is Mew. Yeah I don't know about that one.
Baby hamster. Number 33 is Shaymin and Shaymin is just like it's a baby
sheep yeah it's like a it's like a moss dog it's a yeah to fly that's a bug
dragon yeah flower lots of flower chinchilla giant space bat fish baby dog
Pikachu, that's just disrespectful. Jet engine dog, big fat dragon, water dog, bird, sheep with long hair.
Mega Diancie, that one at least has a dress on. Wobbuffet is blind. Sexy bug.
jolteon yep dog dog dog baby jigglypuff
lion number 83 is Gengar number 72 what is ice cream
yep it's ice cream airplane Arceus who's I think God yeah here's a witch Lucario
gang so be this is another child I don't think we can like get to the end of this
list cuz there's like just every we're gonna moth flower some point so there's
a hundred poke every single one gear squirtle come on another child okay it
ends at one line squirrel sexy salamander wait this one is such a dog that in the
photo they're eating puppy chow out of a bowl like number 90 is salazzle which is
like a curvy a curvy lizard yeah mega rikuwa the only comment on salazzle is
beautiful lizard enough said that's a penguin this is a dugong a starfish
drowsy yep another bird space dragon that one's a pig this is a baby worm Oh
Oh, Jinx. Jinx is this far down?
That's crazy!
I mean, uh...
This, whatever it is, is an ugly butthole from the devil.
It is an ugly butthole from the devil.
It is ugly butthole from the devil.
This thing is hideous. It's so beautiful.
Squirtle.
Here's a baby bird. Here's an older bird.
Another bug.
Another rabbit. A ghost.
Beedoof is a beaver.
[laughter]
Number 153 is Metagross.
And Metagross is just rocks.
Like Metagross is like a rock spider.
Here's an Emperor Penguin.
Here's some normal lions.
A normal zebra.
That one's a tree.
Shark dragon.
Another bird.
A plant.
A hamster.
A bird.
A dog.
A squirrel.
Another insect.
A pig.
The bug ones are the funniest to me.
Some piles of trash.
A pile of trash.
a ball
of fish
another penguin
this is this is to you can't
uh... uh...
fuck this summer
what's the last on the last with salamence
yes alamance is a dragon
so leisure bug dog and bird
blizzard bird beaver bird worm
that's that i have been a good day bog worm who knows those fucking sexual
maniacs over a game freak. You guys really did something here. In the trenches developing
new sexual fireflies. What animal should we make sexy? Bug? No we already did bug 5,000
times. Bird? We have two birds. Can you guys draw a leech with a thang? You know draw a
hamster with that thang on him. Yeah, oh man. The game freak office. A muskrat with a thang.
I thought everybody in the conference room...
Yeah, I was thinking we need some, some sort of...
I need, we need a worm with a big ass thang on it.
I was thinking we could make maybe a dung beetle that's got a thang.
Something with a big ass thang on it.
Just a, yeah.
Oh.
Maybe a ferret with a thang.
Let's take a vote.
Y'all, everybody not in favor say nay.
Everybody in favor say oh.
What about a bog frog with a thang on it?
What about a basketball with a pussy on it?
Yeah, oh, and that's a game freak all right. Bye everybody
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]