you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
you're a crap monster
and may the fourth be with you
may the fourth
that's a powerful duster dude
microphone
That thing is- It's gonna be great for anyone who listens for the first time.
That thing is- That- That's just- Yeah, it's just the first time people are gonna be annoyed by that.
Nobody else would be- Yeah, everybody else is used to you being a fucking dumbass.
Uhhh- Dumbass.
Urr- Urr- Urr- Urr- Urr- Dumbass.
Hi, my name is- What?
Oh my god, dude. Real dumbass. Real ass dumbass.
Yup.
Uh, how you feeling, Pat? How's your- How's your leg?
My leg, uh, not great.
SpongeBob reference.
Yeah, can you do the SpongeBob voice?
My leg!
Are you looking at... did you get that high on the computer duster?
No, Joe texted me and said, "Can the microwave bandit please clean it out?"
Are you the microwave bandit, dude?
I don't know if that's me.
Two months in and you already have a nickname at the apartment?
I was gonna say it's gotta be you, but I think about the people you're living with, I don't
think.
Right.
I think that's a 25-25-25-25 situation.
Yeah, those are the microwave brothers.
Well, I think it's 30- I think it's 33 each right now because Joe is claiming there's a microwave bandit.
Okay, but wouldn't that be the best move?
Whoever fucking smelt it dealt it, dude. Easiest trick in the book.
Let's call him right- let's call him right now.
That's what OJ did. Remember that?
What?
He killed his wife and then he's like, "Somebody killed my wife."
He killed his wife and he said "Whoever smelt it, dealt it."
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Whoever, whoever.
The cop found her.
The cop just found her body and the waiter's body fucking beheaded.
And they were like, "Oh, dude, this is not looking good for you, OJ."
He's like, "Ah ha ha.
Whoever smelt it, dealt it."
And they're like, "Ah."
And that's why he's free.
That's actually why he's free.
Yeah.
Robert Kardashian
Defenses they tried the glove didn't work. Yeah. Yeah, I guess whoever smelt it dealt it in the
Christ yeah, you hear the jury go
Anyway has that defense ever worked in a court of law if somebody listens to this in their lawyer and they know of a case
Not just a lawyer a lawyer slash historian. Yeah the lawyer person
A lawyer historian, can you tell us if the whoever smelt it dealt it defense worked?
You know I could probably give you an answer on that right now.
I think probably not.
I think no.
Okay, I didn't realize you were a lawyer historian.
I don't think so.
This is, to use a law term, this is conjecture.
Here's the thing, whoever did the rhyme did the crime.
(laughter)
It's just kind of, when you think about it, kind of a, kind of a, it's kind of paradoxical.
Your Honor, whoever is the judge did the stuff.
(laughter)
Take him away.
Whoever did the kill fits the bill.
(laughter)
Oh, okay.
Introducing a new one.
My defense rests.
Your honor, your honor, whoever is in the jury did something scurry.
(laughter)
(whispering)
Oh, who else is in that damn courtroom?
is in that damn courtroom whoever surely ain't it this guy did not act fly
whoever shall pay this bailiff you're up you're gonna have to pay for this book
should have picked a different job. If your name is Michael... Michael Guilty, you are
guilty. Your Honor, if you... Your Honor, I believe the lawyer gets to go sit in the
foyer now that you've seen all the pieces can we take a recess paid so much they
should have to speak and run absolutely dude what about like a lawyer cipher you
know it's just it's just a battle rap between the defense and the and the
offense yeah it's a good idea oh your honor it seems the witness is the one
who did this see that one that one's too good that one actually might work yeah I
think all these might work I think whoever smelted Delta is gonna be like
like we're gonna see like like Supreme Court smelted be delted mr. Jonathan
Jonathan dealt it please approach the bench the case of the case Hugh smelted
Jonathan dealt it. Hugh smelt it. Hugh ever. Hugh smelt it. Okay. Dude, that just spent
about an entire Red Thunder's worth of energy right there. Yeah. We're about seven minutes
in. Oh man. Yeah, so that's unlucky. How's your leg? You've hurt yourself so badly. Yeah.
I did a skateboard trick that I have not landed since I was 17.
I already talked about this on my appearance on Seeking Derangements yesterday.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, we can't talk about it.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
Do you get paid to do that show or do you get paid to do this fucking show?
No, I don't.
All right, so I fucking...
Spit it out.
I was doing a back boneless.
It's when you go up the quarter pipe.
I'll say you're back boneless.
Kick the board into your hand and then jump back on it.
Doesn't even respond to afraid.
No, I'm not.
I'll put a bone in your back.
not even gonna fucking humor that. I'll put a bone in your back my boner. I was trying
that. I'm gonna go all the way up your spine. I landed on the board. It'll unlock all your
vertebrae like oh man. Yeah you're gonna itch and it hurts so bad with my boner when I put
it in your back. Okay continue. I landed on the board. I'm gonna give you meningitis when
I put my man inside you. That's how far up your spine I'm gonna go dude. I got both feet
all the way to your brain stem. My leg slipped out, ramp was kind of, quarter pipe was kind
of dirty. Kind of got a lot of like, you know, dirt. A quarter of a dirty pipe. A dirty quarter
pipe. Alright, that one was good. But yeah, got dirt on it and I slipped out, uh, fucking.
I won't slip out. I won't slip out.
I fell onto my leg. It went at like a...
I'll fall onto your leg.
Don't, it hurts.
Okay, never mind. That's retracted.
Yeah, it went down and then I...
But I won't retract it.
I heard two pops. I heard two very distinct pops in my leg.
Yeah, I hear two cops that are with me fucking spit roasting you.
What?
Bring a couple cops over.
Why?
Fuck you.
Only guys I know.
All cops.
Yeah, I heard two pops and then I called Caleb.
You didn't hear two bach because I'm moving the plate.
I heard two pops and my leg sat down for a little bit and then I walked away from the
skate park because I didn't want anyone to see me calling my friend to be like, "Hey,
can you come get me?
I got hurt."
The first thing I did when I like fell is like I looked at my leg saw that it was like on
the ground like slanted and I looked up and just went I'm so old!
That's a good kind of keeping your composure thing.
Yeah.
Is that a big thing at the skate park is if you die you have to pretend that you're fine?
Ah.
So I got up.
The more you explain it the better it sounds.
So I got up, I walked a little bit away from the skate park, sat down, called Cale, or no,
I walked to this like, I walked to this like skate spot, so I was sitting by myself at this
like spot that's been in videos, and I was like, okay, no one's gonna see me here, and
then immediately a dude walks by on a skateboard, or dude like holding a skateboard, I'm like,
oh, now this guy's gonna think I hurt myself skating this big spot by myself like a fucking
dumbass, I look even more stupid than fucking up at a skate park. So I left, I walked more
down the, I walked farther down the street than called Caleb and was like, "Hey, come
pick me up." And Caleb's like, "I'm getting a tattoo right now."
Yeah, I was getting, I was in the middle of getting tattooed. And I, and it hurt so bad.
So I'm like the ditch of my arm inside, it was hurting so bad.
Oh yeah, you were in pain, oh.
No, I almost was like, "Hey man, my friend hurt himself, can I leave?"
I was so close to just saying that because it hurt me so bad.
Well, if you did, I wouldn't have had to spend like $40 on Uber rides.
Yeah, I would have just had to spend $40 to get back home. You would have been on the sidewalk
for like two hours. I was in Greenpoint. That's true. Okay.
I didn't know that. I had to go get my car and shit.
Yeah, so I called an Uber and then went to like a urgent care and as I walked into the urgent care,
like I got out, I'm like drenched in fucking sweat and I just walk in, there's a lady putting like a
sign up, like no mask, no entry and then like I go, I open the door, she's like, "Hi, how can I
help you today?" and I just went, "Knee!" Did you think knee was like heart attack where if you say
it they have to take you back immediately well she she immediately understood
because I was limping true I guess that's that you should have just said a heart
attack that's like yeah you should like like walking in with like you have like
a nail in your face just like a heart attack please the thing is there's only
so many opportunities that you get to like walk into like a doctor or a
hospital or something and just say one word like in pain like that like you
can't go in there and be like like ear infection like you really have to just
take those opportunities whenever you can yes I just sat down and took like she
was like okay can I get like your ID and your insurance card and I just went dude
I've been making some insane noises now I'm like it dude I woke up this morning
I was just like trying to I have this like like this thing yeah the poof yeah
Yeah, no, it's the Falcon Heen balloon.
Yeah, it looks like the Falcon Heen balloon.
Speaking of this thing, I watched the Anthony Weiner documentary, and in the first, he has
this same exact thing in his child's bedroom.
That makes sense.
So this is my pillow from Anthony Weiner.
Thank you, Anthony, for helping me in this trying time.
You found that pillow online because you googled "Wiener's child"
No!
Come on, why couldn't you have just given me "Wiener pillow"?
Child wiener.
I was looking up "child wiener" and you hit this.
Comfortable child wiener.
And you hit "shopping" and that was the...
Documentary video.
And then you hit "shopping" and that was the first result.
That was nuts.
And that's how you got it.
morning it's not like I I was trying to like get my leg like at the pillow I
guess I kicked it off the bed in my sleep I didn't know so I was trying to like
get up so I could get the pillow and keep it elevated yeah and I like moved
my leg over to the bed and I moved it in the same direction I fell on it so like
it obviously just fucking hurt and I just like it sounded like I inhaled a
Wilhelm scream it was like yeah like involuntarily just like yelping at
certain point like I'll step on it weird and just go like I this morning I I made
a funny noise cuz it's like got your a in my scene okay all right are you done
are you done I'm gonna take that as a yes I made a funny noise out of your ass
Okay, is that it? Is it over? Can we stop now? Can I finish my story?
I made a funny noise
out of your ass
Never mind. I went
Okay. Yeah, why did you do that?
Cuz I woke up and I hit my arm right on the tattoo on the corner of my couch cuz I just sleep on the couch
I wake
I was like what the fuck?
Otherwise I will goo all over everything because it seeps goo.
It's so cool how it seeps goo.
I've never gotten a tattoo.
I love the goo.
I lie myself out over every surface in my house just to get the goo everywhere.
You give your house a tattoo.
Exactly.
Yeah, get a perfect imprint.
I almost got one of those things, it's like a fucked up wrap that you put on your shit
and then you just don't touch it but then you have to peel it off and people say it's
like peeling your skin off. That sounds awful. Peeling your skin off is the best thing in the world.
Yeah. Dude, you ever do the old glue thing? Like the glue on the hand? Yeah, of course.
And you peel it off? You ever try to get it in one fell swoop? Like try to get like a whole hand imprint thing?
Of glue? I have weird friends. My friends are criminals. You never did the glue thing? I'm done with you two right now.
No, you're not you and first you said something about my ass first of all that's off-limits to you, bud
your ass is on limits for me and
Cam's ass is to be decided
Whether what limit I have on his ass
Find out find out pretty soon. Yeah, I'm gonna take you to your limit. I'll say I'm gonna push your ass
I'm on guys. I'm gonna push it to the limit to Caleb
I'm gonna go Corbin blue on that ass push that shit to the limit right now Corbin blue Corbin blue
Push it to the limit. That's what I'm gonna do with your ass
See you knew that song. Are you fucking kidding me?
I know I was just commenting on how I have not heard of heard about Corbin blue. Yeah in a bit. I
Don't remember asking you what is he up to?
What's Corbin blue if I had to guess executed by military tribunal? Yeah, he saw he saw Hillary Clinton being hanged
in Guantanamo. I feel like the move for all those people is they either do
TikTok now or they own a restaurant. Yeah. Or they're real estate agents.
Who goes real estate? Pro skaters go real estate.
That's not a pro skater. Corbin Bleu is a pro jumper dude. He's a fucking jump rope master.
Yeah but I feel like Disney Channel star and depending on the
Disney Channel star and pro skater. No I think you just like talking about
about
yeah i'm with you there there dude the the reason that the the nickelodeon gack is so
green and vibrant is because it contains the souls of all the children who who are acting
on on those sets dude they suck a bunch of skulls out yeah if you act really close facial
implants like this those that would be that'd be just dis plants you can just make the face
too you don't need the implant if you can show what kind of face you know what i mean
with your big ass head they'd have to use like robert zadar implants you would end up looking
like that. You have a big ass fucking freak chin. I do. Dude if my chin was like huge like
huge like a like a big. You'd get a Thanos chin. Yeah. What would you do with it? I would
fucking I'd be cutting glass. I would be I would be I would be just hitting people on
the street with it. I'd eat pussy with it put the chin in her butt. Yeah. Have you heard
about this? I got my chin all the way up your ass!
It's kind of a cool move right? Maybe that's why Jay Leno skyrocketed to the top of
entertainment. That's why he wears so much denim. Yeah all the women in charge of entertainment in the 70s
he would just he would eat them out put his, what's it called? His chin in their
ass. Forget the word for chin. His chin-do. Yeah and then it felt like she was fucking getting
eaten out on a bicycle which has got to be the dream for anyone. I mean if you
when you got a chin like that you got to wear you got to wear that much denim
yeah when Jay Leno walked into the office wearing bike pedals on
his hips. They knew what the interns were getting into dude. That's in the oral
history of SNL book. Dude I was getting so I went got tattoos for the first time
a long time and I forgot that whenever I enter a tattoo shop it's like I get
super nervous. I feel like a little kid and so I especially because the
guy's tattooing me is this like fucking cool ass Italian guy like from Italy
Italians from Rome and he's like so Italian that he can let he has
like box braids and it looks like normal to me like I was like yeah okay that's
fine yeah and he's a white guy with box braids but he's not white he's like he
looks like he's from he looks like he was like stuck in a statue and then they
like cracked it like an egg and he popped out and he's like my name is
Simone okay it's got that kind of thing and he was tattooing me and I started
drip my hand was sweating so much that I dripped a bunch of sweat all over his
dick because he was like holding my arm and my hand was it was like I just like
juiced a lemon with my hand it was just like dripping onto him and I was like
hey man sorry and he's just like in no problem that's the thing it's always
that to the the the tattooers are always just like the like the the coolest
people in the world like what you would as a teenager you would imagine yeah
that's the coolest guy ever and then you walk in and like they put like they put
like a pain machine into you and then you just have to stand there like just
staring straight ahead like yeah just pretending it doesn't like hurt so I do
this is sick dude thank yeah dude yeah this is a thousand dollars at the end
yeah and I at one point you got a cigarette break like every ten minutes
he was going like rolling his own cigarettes outside and he came back in
and it was not you know he tattoos you on like a hospital bed and on that
lining they put on there I saw there was a giant sweat stain in the shape of my
ass. I just like sweat through my underwear and my cargo pants onto this
table and then I just was like so I was just hoping so badly he wouldn't notice it
that as he walked back I was like hey Simone sorry about this I must have
spilled my water. It's clearly in the shape of my ass cheeks. That's the thing it's the coolest people seeing you with the most
vulnerable it's like for me I can sit well for it like I'm not I won't like
like freak out or anything but the cost of sitting well so I'll just be
completely empty-minded just like staring straight it's vacuous and
they'll be like oh man like that's a cool shirt I saw that band once I was
like it was like having like your your surgeon be like Anton Chigurh where you
you're like I don't want to fuck this up so badly. Yeah, yeah, it's like if you say
you say the wrong thing they're gonna fuck up your tattoo on purpose. Just do a Z.
Just scribble all over it. Yeah, you wanted a swastika right? Oh no. No. But yeah that was that hurt so bad.
So yeah I've always been. Cam, when did you get hurt this week? When did I get hurt this week?
week. I spilled water on my bed covers earlier today. That hurt my mind pretty bad.
Oh fuck you. No, that's pretty bad. Caleb and I are experiencing real pain and you're
just like, "Oh my wah-wah. Oh, I spilled my wah-wah." I was hurt when my friends refused
to respond to my messages. I responded to your messages last night. Caleb was the only
one who didn't respond to you. Yeah, let me just scroll through my entire text history
and we'll see about that.
- I'm gonna turn on read receipts
just to make you feel worse.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm gonna turn those on
so that every time you guys text me,
I don't respond and you guys fucking know.
- No, I know that you're checking your phone every time
and you're just like lying down
and you don't wanna stand up
because you're imagining something really beautiful to you.
- Aw, that's very sweet.
- You're imagining like some female
Crash Bandicoot character or something
so you can't move.
Like I'm gonna lose this fifth boner,
this fifth of a boner that I have if I if I'm right the first time cuz I get five
in a row no problem it's like a fucking slot machine dude five boners and I'm in
five in a row five years in a row good job okay I actually get I actually get
extremely strong boners and once every ten times that I look at my penis I'm
like that's not that bad I think I've hit my penis too many times for me to
like like you're playing knockout you're just fucking again you know you fall down
on it and you know you start you're falling down on your penis my penis is
like almost completely gone during the day this is another another fucking
skateboarding thing but I'll get hit in the penis with my skateboard sometimes
the penis not the balls yeah if I get hit in the penis and not the balls it
doesn't hurt mmm my balls hang like bats and my
Does that happen to you guys?
You'll get hit in the penis or balls very often so I don't really know.
Like I've been hit in the balls before.
I would imagine that getting hit in the dick hurts less than the balls.
Maybe I've just never been hit in the balls hard enough for it to hurt.
That's a problem we can solve.
Well now I'm too scared to try it.
Yeah, Caleb, have you always had that slingshot duct taped to your hand?
Yes, and I'm coming for you.
for you it's gonna be like a follow up. Walking, walking, going over to Patrick's house with like a dress shoe but on the toe of the shoe there's like a boxing glove pointing up
standing behind him on the train and just sticking your foot out between his feet. Yeah. Pressing a little button. Maybe, what if I just don't have, what if I don't have nerves in my penis?
What if you don't have nuts in your penis? Dude that's probably true. You just got an empty bag. You probably have no feeling at all in there and you haven't realized till now.
yeah you have an empty bag admit it I do it's like a scally cap it is yeah I know
trust me I know well if it's it why the fuck can't I just get like a hole in it
like a kangaroo and keep some shit in there you know keep shit's gonna be
there yeah you get like testicular cancer they should be able to like it
you have to take both of them out they should let you like they take your balls
out you should be able to cancer you should be able to get you should be able
to get like a transparent sack like one of those clear back yes yeah or likes
like a zipper on it but it would look the transparent that it should still have
veins like a fish you know sometimes see inside of a fish yeah I want to replace
I would have placed my penis skin with chameleon skin that'd be really cool
have it blend in yeah I could change it to the color of my pants yeah that's not a
bad idea dudes yeah if it falls out no one can tell exactly they go what's that
strange extra pocket on your pants oh nothing oh nothing I just keep two of my
most favorite things in there have you seen that uh that uh speaking of
blending penises. There's the transition. Have you seen that C-3PO tops card from the
70s that looks like he has a giant boner? No. It's just like a porn in a Disney movie
thing. May the force be with you. I can talk about it today. I guess if there was one day
where you could do this. No, you have to get to the list. You wasted it. You spent so long
C-3PO Goldenrod.
And your empty balls.
Look at it.
You're gonna be holding my rod.
No more Star Wars talk.
That's it.
C-3PO Goldenrod.
I will look this up actually.
You can see his thing.
It looks like he's got a giant boner.
I guess it was like a...
Oh man, that's just nasty.
Yeah.
Oh, that's fucked up dude.
No, that's wrong brother.
I don't like that at all.
I guess like a piece fell off of him while they were taking the photo.
Yeah, his damn piece.
yeah i mean look at that dude he's packing yeah it almost touches this it almost touches his elbow
that's he's i mean further proof that c-3po is gay big ass dick if having a big penis makes you gay
100 dude okay i can get behind that girls hate big penises gay guys love them so you big guys
with big penises are like in i would say it's like a 70 30 split gay straight okay the bigger
your penises and then like that is that is something I would never do research
into and would believe yeah and then the straighter you are the smaller your
penises it was like the straightest thing ever is those guys who like fucking have
really small penises and they never use them and they fuck like toy trucks and
shit those and that's a straight was there in the universe well there's like
oh no there's there's like really gay guys with really tiny penises no no
They're faking. Those guys made a choice.
The ones with the big dicks, they had no choice in that.
If you had a small dick and you're gay, you made a hard, hard choice.
Okay. Yeah.
Top 10 best vegetables from the top tens dot com. It's like being a great Jedi.
Yeah, anyway, top 10 best vegetables.
by user Freddy Godzilla whoa pretty cool name.
Freddy Gibbs.
Oh my god Freddy Gibbs.
Wait here's his about page Freddy Godzilla this is the whole thing I live and end well
my favorite sport is football my favorite food is meat lol.
No way the guy whose favorite food is meat makes the top ten best vegetables.
the top 10 best meat list all right well let's let's do that ourselves hamburger
hot dog hot dog egg there we go hamburger in the eggs not meat eggs is not meat
hamburger in the frying pan eggs is dairy our bones meat yeah no then bones
bones aren't meat are you hair or meat bone marrow that's meat then bones are
fucking meat dude no a hot dog is is bone on top you still say that dog is me
to
You guys can tie anything together.
You don't know anything about hot dogs.
What do you think the bun is?
That's the skin from the leg.
The skin is bread.
The skin goes over the bone.
The hot dog bun is bread.
Did you ever take biology?
No.
Why do you think they boil the hot dogs?
Makes them nice and soft.
Exactly.
Boiled bones.
Everyone likes boiled bones.
That's...
Remember that from a full mac?
That's how you make a demi-glace.
Boiled bone.
You guys ever had boiled bones growing up?
No.
I did.
I never touched a boiled bone.
After you strain them in the colander, God.
Have you ever had the bone marrow?
Dude, pasta tastes so good after you strain it in the colander.
Oh my God, that's the best one.
It doesn't have all that nasty water crap on it
and you just get the pasta.
Oh man.
That hits different.
When you strain the red sauce out of the pasta, it hits different.
Sheesh.
Sheesh!
- Here's what's really bussing to me.
Plain white rigatoni, salt pepper.
- Uncooked. - Sheesh!
- I eat it straight out the box.
I put the water in, I pour the water out.
That's all I need, no heat. - Sheesh!
- That's bussing to me.
- My food bussing challenge. - That's bussing, sheesh!
- My food bussing challenge.
- Number one most bussiness potato or vegetable is a potato.
- Five stars for potatoes.
They're the best.
So soft and can be chopped easily in half.
it's just so good i'm gonna explode from that goodness
have you had any of this so that's the job of something easily in half that's
one of the best parts of food that you guys that's really like a lot of us in
work talking about food
because what's rock of love at all
uh... now
uh... man every time every time uh...
brett michaels is like in a situation with a woman
where she's like
all brett you want to go like back to your room haha just kidding
they'll cut to like a talking head of him
like being interviewed and he's like,
I'm just about ready to explode.
(laughing)
- It is, I do wish that those shows
were like Big Brother or something
where you get to see them have sex.
- Yeah, they always cut it out.
- Yeah, just let me see Bret Michaels' penis.
- In that show, I think the trade-off is
you get to hear a lot about Bret Michaels' type 1 diabetes.
- True, that is as intimate also
seeing someone have sex is learning about their diabetes. The first episode of that show or
the first or like the first three episodes within that range they have to practice phone sex with
him because he's going to be on tour a lot. Practice. So he's gonna so yeah he's gonna you
get a you get like a gold star or whatever for doing the best phone sex with him and they uh
he has like a doctor that's just a fat guy in a lab coat and he hooks something up to his penis to
Like, he hooks his penis up to a computer so he can test whether or not he's getting a boner from the phone sex.
Wow. He needs a scientist to tell if he's getting a boner?
Yeah.
Well, how strong of a boner he gets.
But they can't say all that nasty crap on TV, right? It's gotta be a lot of bleeps.
There's a lot of bleeps and there's a lot of... yeah.
Maybe some innuendo?
Uh-huh.
I hate innuendo. I like the normal crap.
I like innuendo.
Yeah, give me that normal endo.
Give me that exoendo!
I don't need no innuendo.
Give me the exoendo.
Shit's weird.
Yeah, potatoes are pretty good though.
Me loves 'em!
They make you fat, but so does McDonald's,
and does anyone give a scruffy turd about that?
This sounds like Smeagol.
What?
Me loves 'em!
That sounded like Smeagol.
So I hereby declare this potato day,
and we shall feast on potatoes until we cannot anymore.
He loves potatoes.
Fuck, that sucked.
I like all the vegetables in the world.
I'm so sorry for you.
If I see any vegetable, I would want it.
Unless it came from the floor or someone's mouth.
I'm a vegetable addict, you see.
That's why I like all of them in the world.
I think vegetables are pretty tight.
They are tasty and contain 0% sugar.
Well, apart from sweet potatoes.
They are a starchy vegetable and you can also use them for beauty benefits.
Cut slices of potatoes and place them in your eyes.
Leave them there for 20 minutes
leave them there for 20 to 30 minutes and see the results place them in your eyes
put under the eyelid have you have you ever done like gotten potato like like a
juice from a potato in your eye it sucks no I knew a friend of mine growing up
his dad had cancer and he started he was like to solve my cancer I will only eat
raw potatoes and they just died like a million times faster.
Oh that sucks.
I love potatoes they're so delicious and you can have them in so many ways.
Chips, hash brown, mashed, boiled with butter and garlic. Isn't that
mashed potatoes? No boiled and and and and pressed with butter and garlic.
Okay. Yeah you press them all until they're like a real creamy
press oh yeah yeah oh no wait yeah no you can have boy I've had boiled potatoes
I'm realizing just now potatoes equals french fries and for you couch potatoes
potato chips oh finally my brothers and sisters are recognized in the light of
the top ten I don't fuck with potatoes dude what this is it I'm uh these are
These are not ketosis.
I'm trying to keep my entire body in ketosis.
Even one single drop of anti-keto matter such as potatoes will throw me out of ketosis and
put me into a just a downward spiral.
So I can't even fucking touch with, I can't fuck with potatoes right now.
I'm off of those, yeah.
You know what's great?
It's because you look at one and you can't eat it because it reminds you of your own head,
right?
Well, that's a little bit a part of it, yeah.
is about eating things that look as far away from you as possible. Yeah. Yeah, so I
eat a lot of crayons a lot. No carbs in a crayon. Is that a, it was just a rumor,
right? That I eat crayons? That my uncle started that if you eat a crayon your, changes your poop
color? Of course it changes your poop color. What, are you stupid? You can't digest a crayon.
Yeah, but it would just come out in crayon chunks. It wouldn't change the
whole poop. Well you wouldn't, have you ever melted a crayon? Yeah. Made a crayon
candle yeah you've never done that I've done it you guys ever you guys ever
melt crayons together into like one big crayon like you take all the crayons you take the
paper and make crayons and you melt them together so you multicolored crayon yeah
you have hot shit in your stomach that'll melt a crayon no problem probably
five or six seconds the dye the dye wouldn't retain in your poop why have
you ever fucking do you think I can't believe you right now you're eating a
beat it'll mean if you eat red broken glass your shit will be red well that's
from the glass yeah exactly we need to make it we need to send you on a on a
you need to eat you're gonna make me eat a crayon yeah I'm gonna send you on an
idiot abroad style adventure where you have a crayon you have to eat glue you're
gonna eat paper and I it's mostly that that's like maybe two minutes of the
show the rest of the show is a deep dive on your shit. I'm gonna get a scientist
he's gonna test it. We're gonna get color experts. We're gonna hook it up to the
same machine from Rock of Love. Yeah and he's gonna let you know if you
pooped or not. Yeah well your poop is looking very sexually excited sir.
Number two is corn. Who doesn't love corn? I was about to vote for potatoes. I found some corn in my number two.
- Those are also super good.
And then I saw corn.
It's served so good on the cob and it's super healthy.
Corn is sweet and delicious
and it's the reason why I like vegetables.
I would probably have 10 cavities in my mouth
if it weren't for corn,
which I learned to love more than Sour Patch Kids.
- Here's what I'm gonna say.
It might be controversial.
Every food would be better on the cob.
- You know what?
No, that's not controversial at all.
I think a lot of people would agree with that.
- Really?
Dude, can you imagine gummy bears on the cob
fucking like hamburger on the cob. Dude it would be also be really great because I
mean everybody with braces would starve and die. Exactly yeah you eliminate the
worst kind of people. These weak people. People who listen to what an
orthodontist tells them. Yeah you are cowardly enough to take advice from a fake dentist.
You look at a guy who's a fucking, he couldn't even be a
dentist. Yeah half dentist half fucking mechanic that's what you are. You're
cucked by the guy trying to make your mouth a robot yeah meanwhile I'm a mad
scientist who's in there trying to put a fucking Apple watch in your mouth I'm
eating popcorn and it's me now and later fucking I'm eating fucking a dentist is
a is a doctor they couldn't fucking cut it in an orthodontist is another rung
lower than that it's pathetic yeah it's like it's like a gym teacher trainer
exactly it's it the assistant to a gym teacher yeah think about all the shit you
can't eat with braces. Tootsie Roll. Tootsie Rolls suck anyway. Well the fruit ones are
good. No, bad candy. You really like Tootsie Rolls? I don't like chocolate Tootsie Rolls
but I like the... You like Tootsie Rolls so. The lime Tootsie Rolls? That's like maybe
one of the worst candies of all time. Yeah I'm with you. The green Tootsie Rolls is pretty
good. Like literally like maybe bottom three. No no no. Chocolate Tootsie Rolls are bad
But like the the fruit flavored ones kind of good. You're pissing me off so much today. I'm about to lose it
I'm about to fucking lose it right now
shut up
With the tootsie rolls shut the fuck up, dude. Hey, let me see that - that's right
No, that was your first example - that was like I'll think about all the great foods. You can't
See what are you talking on the cob?
We're talking about corn on the cob first of all and then you like what you can't eat popcorn - popcorn is way better than
tootsie rolls? Chicken breasts on the cob? It'd be so good! I mean it has if you eat a wing,
a wing is on the cob. Dude, shwarma on the cob? That fucking writes itself. Shwarma straight
off the spit? Yeah! Just eating the fucking shwarma? Yeah, you're on the cob! Yeah. That's
on the cob, dude. Yeah, you know what? I'll take back what I, I'll backpedal, I'll take
back what I said about tootsie rolls. Once I figure out how to put drinks on the cob,
it's over it's over it's over for food I'm only gonna be having drinks yeah
sorry dude drinks are just better I like drinks more it's a lot less work
water on the cob mmm not what okay that's as weird as going to Tutsi Roll first
delicious beer on the cob what no okay so would like a like a like a popsicle is
that no well first of all it's not a no it's not a drink it's solid I would if I
handed you a popsicle and I said this is juice you'd say no it's not a popsicle.
Okay if you said it was juice on the cob. No the water or the beer cob needs to
have some sort of gravity cob. Yeah it's liquid. That has that that's the
important part. It has its own orbit and the beer will orbit the cob. Okay so it and it is
still a corn cob also. Okay so it's a gravity cob. The gravity cob Caleb
invention not a big deal it happens. They come and go. And you hold and you hold a
beer with it. Wait, okay. It would be like a fair food. It'd be like a turkey leg. You
walk around with a beer cob. So, is turkey leg chicken on the cob? No, that's on the
bone! I have a new invention. I wanna... The cob conversation is frustrating me. I don't
care about that. I don't care how frustrated you are. I don't care. My new invention, I'm
moving forward with, I think, Coca-Cola Freestyle Machine still have a lot of potential. Cob
freestyle machine. Oh my god. There's a bunch of different foods. You know I can be like,
oh I want corn and I also want you know beef. Egg. Scrambled egg on the cob. Exactly. And
it has every, it's linked up to Wikipedia so anything in the food category is fair game.
It makes it or it orders it. If you pick something and you don't have it in stock, like if you're
a crazy person, you're like oh I want kangaroo on the cob. Like you're trying to act crazy.
So we'll automatically order it with an Amazon button.
- Cameron, there's an immediate flaw in your problem.
- Yeah, what is it?
- In your Cobb face now. - It's too good.
- No, no, if it's hooked up to Wikipedia,
you have to limit it to the food section.
- That's what I said.
I said anything that's under the food category.
- Yeah, I missed that completely.
- Man, if you were in an investors meeting,
your head would be chopped off by that woman
from Kill Bill Bill.
- Yeah, we'd throw you out of the damn window.
- Mr. Wonderful's wife would fucking
run her boat into you, dude.
I was just thinking of a situation where somebody gets like, I don't know.
Okay, new restaurant.
New restaurant.
Darth Vader on the cob.
Set up like Subway.
Evil guy.
You can choose anything.
Hitler on a cob.
I know what you're saying.
You choose your type of cob.
Cob way.
Oh, Italian herbs and cob.
That might be a pretty good cob.
Different types of cobs you can pick too.
CMT.
Because at the end, at the end, you finish your CMT sandwich, right?
And then you forgot, oh, because here's a problem with bread.
You can't reuse the bread after you eat it.
Well that's one thing, but also you see the bread and it never surprises you.
You never get a flavored bread and you're like, "Oh shit, I just remembered that I got Italian
herbs and cheese."
If you get an Italian herbs and cheese cob, you've sucked all the salami and ham and fucking
lettuce and tomato off that thing.
You get to the bottom, you're like, "Dude, I got cob to suck.
I can suck this cob dry."
You bring the cob back, you get a discount when you reuse the cob.
You can't do that at Subway.
If you get a sub at Subway and you just eat all the meat and veggies out of the bread
and you bring the bread back, they're gonna kick you out.
That's a restaurant that'll have to happen after the COVID-19 pandemic.
If you keep coming up with shit, I'm gonna fucking put you on the Cobb, Pat.
Look, I'm trying, I'm just trying to make sure this shit works.
I have a new Subway spin-off, okay?
Even better.
This is different from the Cobb, okay?
No more Cobb.
I don't like this so far.
I'm already out.
Okay, but you're gonna like this.
Okay.
Even the traditional subway counter, it's reversed.
All the ingredients are facing you.
The cashier is shielded from it.
They're all in--
- It's the cashier.
(laughing)
- That's pretty good.
I'll give you that idea for free.
But no, you don't need bread.
You can eat 'em right there, right out of the trough.
Slop way.
- Okay, because the best--
- Slop way.
- Slop way, 'cause the best thing in the world
is eating a cold cut straight out of the fridge.
- Exactly.
- And even better than that, eating a cold Cobb cut,
crate, like trough.
- A crate of Cobb crud.
- Okay.
- What about a Subway style restaurant
where you are the person making the subs,
but then, and the people who work there on the other side.
- And you get paid for it, and they come and order stuff.
- No, so they're on the other side of a plate glass,
like a zoo, right?
But there's still like the exit part,
but you have to escape, and if you escape, it's free.
If they catch you, you pay for it.
- Okay, here's my idea, all right?
It's like that, it's like you described there,
in like a plate glass zoo.
You make whatever sandwich you want,
and they have to eat it.
- Oh my God, that's really good.
Yeah, ranch dressing and buffalo sauce on a wrap.
Actually, that sounds pretty good.
- You're gonna hate that.
You're gonna hate that so much.
With chicken? - That actually sounds
pretty good. - With chicken?
- Ugh.
I'm realizing there's only good ingredients at Subway, dude.
Olives and mustard, I'll fucking eat that any time.
- Well, here's the thing,
you can bring in your own ingredients, too.
- Ah, the poop cob.
Wait, are cobs still involved?
I may have lost it.
It's kind of like I think maybe we're looking too far. Okay. Okay. What if we look at the CC's pizza model?
What if we get like what if we like pizza?
What if we make a city?
And ever and we just have a bunch of different types of subways and we can use all our different subway type ideas and coke
Freestyle ideas and Cobb. Okay ideas. We can call Cobb City. I
Guess we could I
Don't know. I don't really have it in me to do something that big. I was singing like a single restaurant
maybe we franchise it out later. We were in like New Mexico, Arizona, Texas, California.
Well, have you heard of Celebration Florida?
Every time I go to Florida it's a celebration, bud. I don't know about you.
Well, Celebration Florida is a town owned by Disney.
Hot weather, hot Miami women. What? Disney owns a town?
Yeah, Celebration. It's where a lot of the, it's like some of the employees live there.
First a land, then a world, and now a town?
Yeah.
They're really backwards.
- It's falling off, yeah.
- Come on, dude.
Yeah, Celebration Florida is a--
- Yeah, what's next, the House of Mouse?
- Yeah, it's a census designated--
- What's next, a Mickey Mouse Clubhouse, dude?
This is, they're--
- They fell off.
Yeah, so it was like a, it's a master plan community
located near Disney World.
It's, what else is next?
- A Disney store?
- Civil suit against Celebration Florida.
Alright, so they're not doing very well, I'm guessing.
Yeah.
Has there ever been a murder there?
I really want to know.
Probably not yet.
Yeah.
Number three, broccoli.
Who, what kind of sicko put broccoli this high?
Broccoli's good.
Broccoli, broccoli with like, like the, you know the, ah, shit.
I tried to think of more vegetables and all that came to my mind was different fruit.
I moved the chair too far and my leg got hurt.
You are a whining weiner.
- Dude, this is, here's a comment.
Here's a good comment.
"Mmm, little trees of goodness.
"A perfect fractal, as tasty as it is mathematical."
- It's Neil deGrasse Tyson commenting on this list.
- The, uh, here's a good one.
"I like the stems, but not that weird fluff.
"Like kid, I'm not eating a bush here."
- Fluff. - Who likes the stems?
- The broccoli fluff at the top.
- The comments are wilding out, dude.
put it with Japanese sauce and you are all set.
- Japanese sauce?
- If you don't like broccoli, I will kill you.
(laughing)
Broccoli fans weird AF.
- The broccoli fanship is wildin' today.
- Fanship?
- What's that, like those party plates
that have the broccoli and the cauliflower
with that ranch dip?
- Just a vegetable plate?
- Yeah, the vegetable plates that people get at Walmart.
- Yeah.
And you bring it to--
Those go crazy.
Such an underloved vegetable.
It tastes like heaven when raw.
Fuck.
Ow.
You coming, dude?
Stop hurting somebody.
I just saw some sperms jumping up onto the camera.
You didn't see any sperm.
Hey, you don't pet sperm!
Hey, I'm gonna go in his mouth where I love to go!
Get back in there.
Okay, I'm jumping in your mouth now!
I need to take my-- I need to take some ibuprofen.
You need to take a Prozac and you need to chill.
Yeah.
Number four, carrots.
No wait, wait, there's a comment on broccoli in all caps that says "KEEPS ME REGULAR"
Some kind of Mr. Hyde monster comes out when he doesn't eat broccoli.
Yeah.
Um, carrots.
This is probably my number one, dude.
Carrots are good.
Dude, I used to love eating carrots, and then I'd fuckin' develop this allergy.
And then you took an arrow to the damn knee.
God, dude, carrots was like just eating carrots, like baby carrots on their own.
It was great.
Now I have to take a Zyrtec every time I fucking eat one.
But dude, is it worth it to you?
Yeah.
Come on, it's worth it.
You'd be sleepy for about six hours.
Yeah, and I just pop a fucking Benadryl or a Zyrtec.
Yeah, it's nothing.
Snort a little Benadryl and then down some carrots.
Carrot dinner.
Norton Zyrtec.
You think that'll, you think that's good?
- It's probably not good,
but you also just inhaled computer duster
before we started recording.
- I didn't inhale it.
- You did. - You definitely did.
- You said, "I inhaled it a little bit."
And then you said, "I feel weird, that's really weird."
- And you started laughing a lot.
- Yeah.
- Well, great for my broken eyesight.
And making it into juice or making it in soup
is just amazing.
Have you ever seen like the people who just eat
like only carrots and their skin turns orange?
- Someone says, "What's up, Doc?"
- Hey, yo!
(laughing)
- Yeah, I had a, when I was vegan,
there was like a summer where I ate probably
like six or seven huge carrots a day.
- That's so good.
- They definitely changed the tone of my skin.
- Yeah.
- I was a lot more orange than I am now.
- It's true, I've been looking at you.
- Yeah, I'm not, I have almost no orange in me.
- You're blending in with your wall.
I know I'm I'm seriously white now. I'm seriously white.
Number five is lettuce. Lettuce on a sandwich they're a miracle. Lettuce is
great toss it in a salad. It's one of the things you put in the salad. Yeah well
you can you can have like a potato salad. Shut up! Shut up! I eat lettuce in salad cheeseburgers
and sandwiches and so good so healthy so crunchy and so delicious and then in like
a dialogue format me heart lettuce can't even say the heart number six peas
peeping peepee what now you know this here's a comment from cartoon network fan
1990 and every word is capitalized individually without a doubt my favorite
greens that peas are a legume right oh so you so you let potatoes slide and
and corn slide but you're gonna pull out legume for peas.
Yeah.
You just wanted to show us you knew that word, dude.
I learned it recently.
You're just bragging at this point.
You're just fucking bragging.
I get it, man.
You spend all your time at the library.
Here's a really good comment.
Little circles.
Best green food ever.
I'm not a pea fan.
What about that green ketchup they used to have?
That's my number one green food.
Is that?
- The Shrek ketchup?
- Yeah, the Heinz.
- Oh my god, that shit was crazy.
- What was that called?
- The green and then the purple.
- We totally talked about it before.
I forgot the name of it.
- That shit was to die for.
- Yeah, it's too bad they got rid of it.
- They should bring it back. - No idea why.
They should.
- Oh yeah, what could have been the problem with that food?
- They should have red ketchup.
- Number seven, onions.
Patrick, I want you to read this first comment here.
Onions?
Blimey, they're good!
(laughter)
- Caramelized, fried, roasted, onions are absolutely
the most fantastic vegetables on the planet.
Please vote onions.
Now I need to point out, the potatoes are disgusting
and should be stripped of their gold spot on this list.
- I just wanted you to say blimey, that's all.
- Yep.
- This guy says, "Ogres have layers."
- Yo, this person says, "Annoying ring."
(laughter)
Yo, anoint ring.
Sheesh.
Yo, my anoint ring bussing.
I can't get enough of their zingy taste.
Just can't.
And number eight is cauliflower.
I want to read the two comments in a row here.
Here's one comment.
"It's a very natural veggie full of mib."
and then comment that's further up that says,
"Sorry, full of minerals and vitamins."
(laughing)
- Really good when cooked.
- A nice healthy puff, love the texture.
- It's awful.
- That's one comment.
- Cauliflower, I like cauliflower.
- Cauliflower's good, no that was a comment.
I love cauliflower, that's a good--
- Cauliflower, fried cauliflower.
- Yeah, that's the snacker's delight, dude.
That's a potato chip fan's vegetable.
Fried cauliflower on like a sandwich.
Pretty good.
- You know what's not very good?
Buffalo cauliflower.
- No, that shit sucks.
- Shit is terrible, dude.
- But cauliflower wings, fuck off.
- Get outta here.
- But what was that, that fucking sandwich they had
at that restaurant I worked at?
- The cauliflower restaurant?
- It was called the Chiron, I think.
- What?
- Yeah, it was called the Chiron sandwich.
- And it was bomb?
It had cauliflower on it?
It had like deep fried cauliflower and like the spicy sauce
and they put like fried rice noodles on it.
- Ugh.
- And it had like a lime cilantro cabbage slaw.
- It's getting worse every second, dude.
You gotta taste it. - It's like shit.
I don't. - Maybe you gotta taste it.
I'll take you back there. - Nope.
- See if they have it.
- No, you know what I like?
A sandwich from the deli called the Gobbler.
- You like a sandwich called the Poop Sandwich?
- Nope, called the Gobbler.
- Oh, the Gobbler. - Is that the Thanksgiving
sandwich? - The Gobbler killed me, dude.
- I had the Gobbler twice when I was there.
- The Gobbler will take you down, dude.
It's a turkey sandwich.
That's all it is.
Gobbler.
Turkey sandwich Russian dressing.
I had the Gobbler when I was there.
Do you remember when we were both, when we both were very ill?
Yeah.
The Gobbler did that to me, dude.
The Gobbler destroyed me.
Yep.
That shit will turn you into a noodle, dude.
For real.
If it's called the Gobbler, it's gotta be a Thanksgiving sandwich.
I'm gonna put my foot down.
A turkey?
Turkey is a food.
Slice turkey at the deli constantly.
Yeah, but that's, no, it shouldn't be called the Gobbler.
The Gobbler should be reserved.
You are insane.
You're a devil.
Honestly, you're fucking crazy.
People will back me up on this.
You've lost it.
You've lost your mind.
You've lost your ever-loving, goddamn, white-ass mind.
And stop looking at me like that.
Stop.
Number 9's peppers.
Not interesting.
Number 10's brussel sprouts.
Yes!
Brussel sprouts is pretty good, dude.
Put some...
I do not like the way that this person spelled vinegar down here.
Not a fan of this one.
I have to say.
Uh, which one is that? Is that on Brussels sprouts?
Yeah, they said I love cooked Brussels sprouts, especially with...
and...
They smelled it wrong.
Yep.
Yeah, that's uh, that's gonna...
That's not the way you write that one.
That's a fail blog right there.
Yeah, that person got smart phoned.
Yeah, enjoy your time on fail blog.
Yeah.
Yeah, Brussels sprouts, that is the best vegetable.
Anything in the broccoli family.
I feel like I'm missing something.
Would you guys count mushrooms as a vegetable?
No, mushrooms are a dirt.
That's true, actually.
Mushrooms are a type of dirt.
They are kind of a type of dirt.
Yeah, they're closer to an animal.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Because they're weird. Yeah. Fair. All right. But mushroom is probably number
one if they do count. Yeah. Oh shoot, like a deep fried mushroom? Mushrooms are so good.
Yeah. That's my favorite vegetable. Yeah. Mushrooms are number one. Pulled pork mushroom?
Dude, how dire is the state of the vegetable world right now that number 30 is seaweed?
Dude, we couldn't come up with 30 better vegetables than seaweed?
Seaweed?
Well, I think seaweed's pretty good.
Seaweed's good, but it's also just salt.
It's just pure.
It's just...
It's like the equivalent of cotton candy, but for salt.
It's just like nothing.
It's just like eating worms.
What?
I feel like a damn dirt worm man.
What are you talking about?
Eating worms.
Number 39 is eggplant.
I'm gonna take a hard stance.
Fuck eggplant.
- What?
- Fuck it, I hate it.
- I don't really like eggplant either.
- Y'all have something.
- I bet you want the eggplant, right?
- Yeah.
- You guys have a disgusting part of your brain.
- No, you have an Italian part of your brain
that makes you like eggplant.
- You have a nasty lobe in your brain
that makes you like nasty crap
and hate good stuff like eggplant.
Eggplant should be number five.
- You are fucking stupid.
- No, you are stupid.
- Artichoke's good as hell.
- Oh, artichoke is, yeah dude, I love fucking mayonnaise.
He saved our friendship.
Yeah.
I'm just scrolling through the
vegetable list and whenever I see a vegetable
I like my eyes are just lighting up and I can't process
what else is going on. It's making me so
hungry. Number 45
Bitter Gourd.
That can't be number 45.
Best ever because I like the nutritional
value of that vegetable.
I don't like it. And then the next thing
coming is especially I like the nutrition of
that.
- Number 50 is horse, or 49, horseradish.
That's not a vegetable, is it?
- Yeah, we can't gatekeep this.
- That's a sauce.
- There's so many on these that are not vegetables.
- Horseradish is a, what?
That's a plant?
- Bamboo shoots.
Do I look like damn Jack Black, the Kung Fu Panda over here?
I'm not gonna eat bamboo.
- Tiger nuts, number 75.
- Oh, edamame, dude.
Alright, yeah, this shit'll turn you into a girl, dude.
- Number 94. - One bean gives you tits.
- Yeah, one bean you're--
- One bean, you're a girl.
- Last, the last thing on the list is a yam,
which I think has been covered by sweet potato.
- Yeah. - Mung.
- What?
- Mung beans? - Mung, you like mung, dude?
- I've never seen mung.
- Really? - You've probably had
mung beans, like mung bean sprouts.
- I don't know what mung is.
Mung is a goo-goo-ga-ga troll word.
- What? - Wait, I just read
the comments on ginger.
I only like gingerbread man please.
The nice spice of ginger.
There's one called Salsify.
Sounds like something Bobby Flay would do.
New start up app I'm working on.
Sounds pretty good actually.
Salsify, I'd go there.
Cassava, sea kale, elephant garlic.
Oh, what does that look like?
I'm going to google that right now.
Probably purple.
garlic. Why would you guess purple? Because elephants are... What the fuck is purple?
Damn. It's too easy for me dude. I know my colors. There's only one picture where it's
purple. Oh okay. Oh so it's just big garlic. Makes sense. Big and purple like an elephant.
Elephants are not purple. Yeah they are. They're not purple. What color are they then? Gray.
A purplish gray. No. Yep. Gray is kind of just like purple, light purple. It's chill
purple dude. Grey is like if purple was in like a black and white movie. Yeah exactly
it's old school. Okay I can get behind that. Old school purple. Yeah the last ten vegetables
I have never heard of. The last 100 vegetables. Well it's probably where they're in the last
ten. Samphire, cat's ears, orachi. Freddy Godzilla just sat here and was like I gotta
add green beetroot, anona, lulo, I gotta add these just in case someone wants to vote for
Yeah, what the fuck is this one here?
What?
Sea rocket sounds pretty cool actually
Let me see. I'm not like Sam fire is a zucchini. What's that sears? Am I right? Yeah?
What is this sea rocket is a fucking flower?
Yo, wait, let me look this up. These people are sick. What is this one here fucking?
lemongrass
No
Come this is a flower that grows on the beach. Not just this horrible. Yeah, I know
turtle. You should not eat anything that grows in sand. That's like... I agree.
That's horrible. That's like eating a tumbleweed. All right. Yep. We are done
with the list. We're done. Pat, do you have any other part of your body you want to
complain about? No. I do. Your belly button. Bye. Why? Because I had it in a building.
I'm gonna make it a puddle, dude, when I come to New York. And it'll just stay like
that forever.
Alright, bye.
Bye.