You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Back with my tooth.
- Turn up.
- Back with some food.
Fuck, I love food.
I love to eat.
I have just one feet.
Fuck, I'm hopping around, around the town.
I'm looking brown.
I'm looking, I got a crown 'cause I'm the king.
I do the thing.
I'm about to sing.
- La, ooh.
- God damn.
- Damn dude.
- Fuck.
- That was beautiful.
- That was so crazy.
You got me feeling lazy and outside it looks hazy
and it is so crazy.
How crazy it looks outside it's so crazy.
That hazy clouds outside around.
I'm looking brown.
I'm on the town.
I'm wearing a crown 'cause I'm the king
and I'm gonna sing.
- La, la, la, la.
- Did we?
Oh my God, did we both say that we're looking brown?
Wow.
What an insane rhyme that is.
You know, I mean, when you're freestyling,
everything's on the table.
- Yeah, you just leave.
(laughing)
- Yeah, if it rhymes, it's okay.
- Yeah. - That's the rule.
- I was just at the beach, you know, so I, you know,
I'm, you can see I'm nice and tan.
It was beautiful.
- It was so amazing, like summer ray.
- I was surfing, I was windsurfing, I was swimming,
I was, you know, I was kickboarding.
Yep, I was windsurfing on a, I--
- I was flip sharking.
- Yeah, I was flip sharking.
I was, you know, I was like surfing on a lobster.
Like I was standing on a lobster and it was swimming.
Like a boat. - That's insane.
I'm thinking about this, why are there not more like,
okay, so you guys, you know like storm chasers, right?
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
- Why do people not like do that with like bears
and sharks and like dangerous animals?
- Grizzly man.
- Grizz, oh, I've been owned.
- And sharks can swim, so I mean.
- Yeah, I don't think, - Men can swim.
- Is there a shark grizzly man?
Is there like a, is there a shark man?
- There are people who do like shark cages and shit.
I don't think you can follow a shark around because like--
- Yeah, you can't.
- Well, no, 'cause like humans, like, you know, if you--
- Yeah, I totally could.
- If you go underwater too fast or come up too fast,
you'll just explode, so like--
- No.
- That is funny. - If the shark like, yeah.
- It's funny that like, if you go down stairs
to the bottom of the ocean too fast,
and then you come back up, your blood explodes.
- Exactly, it's one of those things that makes you realize
like maybe God's creation isn't so beautiful after all.
Like maybe he didn't think of anything.
if you swim too fast you explode.
If God loved us he would let us swim fast.
It definitely is like yeah you're not like God if God exists he did not mean to
make humans like the number one because if we swim too far down we turn into a
cube.
He saw what was like pressed into a fucking like perfect cube.
He created us and he was like well these these things aren't gonna be able to fly
okay and then we made planes and he's like well listen up you fuckers are not
going down you may have figured out a way to go up but how much of the ocean isn't
like explored? 100% 100% of the ocean yeah 100% yeah nobody's ever seen
because you because you can't see underwater. We've only explored
0.1% of the ocean 0.0000001% I mean just whatever is on the beach pretty much yeah
yeah mostly like seashells and hermit crabs and all that. Once it once the waves like
when the wave is on the beach, I'll look at that part of the ocean.
You think one day, I mean it's probably not going to be in our lifetime, but one day we're
going to be able to fuck in, we're going to be able to go down deeper in the ocean and
we're not going to like what we see.
That's pretty true.
You think so?
Alright.
And what is it that you think that we will see in the ocean?
Monster.
You think we will see monster?
Sea monster.
Guys, Patrick, place your bet on how much, what percent of the ocean is actually explored.
and charted. 98% like no has been explored so you think 2% yes I'm gonna go also 2%
it's 5% has been explored. Wow that's way more. That's pretty impressive dude. I mean I mean it was
charting the ocean is probably pretty boring because you're just like oh it's
flat down here maybe some rocks right. Now see how much has been explored by a fish.
Google buy a fish.
See if that is a result for that.
Oh yep, it says 100%.
Wow, that's amazing dude.
That's the thing, if you're like, if you're one of these like, like deep sea fish, like
deep deep sea.
One of the ones that they made ugly because they knew nobody would ever see it.
Yeah.
Who's they Caleb?
The god?
The god, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Come on.
What are you talking about you fucker?
Who do you think is making fish Patrick?
Yeah, who do you think, besides god, nobody else is making fish.
I don't know.
The sea man.
The strange conspiracy theory that nobody else has ever heard of.
Yeah, there's a guy at the bottom of the ocean.
He's called the sea man.
A group of...
Well, you were asking about they, so I mean...
Well, I don't want to give them a gender.
Alright, that's fair.
It's pride month.
I'm not giving anyone a gender.
Yeah, we're taking those shits away, dude.
It's damn white pride month if you're Ellie Kemper.
No.
I mean, come on.
how everyone's like she's a Nazi for just being like a girl who was in a talent
show dude honestly bro fuck that she could go fucking who can see her parents
are like fucking she just fucking fall off a cliff I don't know I think I think
the whole situation so fucking also like I mean she's definitely I mean let's not
get ourselves yeah he's got some fucking Thomas Jefferson's in the family
absolutely also no way more than just a talent so like I mean you know respect
everybody who lives in the midwest but like you gotta call a spade a spade man if i see
somebody wearing bird masks and shit like that's not gonna fly that's not okay i didn't look
into this at all you just decided to defend her because you saw everyone saying she was
kkk cuz you're such an office fan yeah i am i'm a huge office fan god you love those erin
episodes of the office yeah no it's just like is that her name yeah it was you fucking oh
Oh, is that her name?
I don't know.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know the name of the characters in The Office.
Who's the boss again?
Who's the boss?
Is it Michael Storch?
Is that his name?
Come on.
I'm kidding.
I've seen the show.
No.
Yeah, honestly, I only saw that it was like-- Michael Storch would be a better name.
I saw that newspaper article because Josiah Photoshopped me into it.
I will say, one thing that people are right about is like, sometimes you will be at a
pool party in the South, right?
you'll be like at a friend's house you'll be sitting on a floaty or whatever and
then you will look down at between your legs and you will see that it is a
Confederate flag floaty that you were sitting on that's a you know that's a
that's it the South thing Patrick I want I'm gonna write us looked up this thing
that there that Ali Kemper was part of and this is what you're now this is what
you're defending okay you're submitting your candidacy for the next beauty
I would love to be in it so it's called the fair say it's called the fair St.
St.
Louis but it was previously known as the veiled profit ball in 2014 the Atlantic
reported that the veiled profit organization you know that's a great
name for an organization first of all you can tell there's nothing wrong going
on there initially initially barred black and Jewish people from joining it's
only for the white elites of Missouri and there's a veiled profit parade that
happens every year where debutantes given the honor of
of the only way to wrap up a little bit of a little started in eighteen seventy
eight by a confederate officer named alonzo slay back
the
i thought he's is very hard to put the slayer i heard that was a very effective
i heard that i was a little bit of a classic that they
you know it's funny and i heard the first syllable of his last name i'd
honestly thought you're gonna say a lot of slavery
Alonzo Slayback is either a confederate officer or like the coolest black guy of all time.
That's a crazy either or name.
Oh man dude his brother's name was Charles E. Slayback.
That's Chuck E. Cheese dude.
Damn.
Charles Entertainment Slayback.
Fuck dude.
Slayback music.
We're not covering everything right now.
We're like Indiana Jones right now.
we're getting to the bottom of this yeah you guys ever know anybody's a Freemason
no I didn't know anyone who's a Freemason but no I mean we went to
school next to a Masonic temple yeah a lot so I probably play in a Mason's lodge
yeah and in high school yeah the same as the Masonic no no no no no no no
hardcore shows at the Elk's Lodge. I'm picky and choosy with who they who they make a like Illuminati
because I knew this my dad has this friend has been a Mason for like 40 years
and he does like linoleum floors.
- Well yeah.
- And when I asked him, I was like, what's it like?
And he was like, oh, it's pretty much
like free barbecue like twice a week.
- You know that-- - That sounds kinda sick.
- The Illuminati is just one of the biggest
MLM schemes of all time.
- Yeah, absolutely dude, yeah.
- It's like 100%, yeah, fuck it, it's just like,
oh yeah, we need you, like one day,
one day you're gonna be up with the big dogs.
One day you're gonna get to drive our big pyramid Cadillac.
- But until then, keep bringing
baked mac and cheese Frank you're yeah that shit is insane yeah we should try to
join the Masons can you just join or do you have to be invited I think you can like try to
join I don't know I mean you can join but it's not the same as being invited yeah I
guess you know cuz when you get invited there's a party and like do you have to
be initiated oh for sure do you get a gun and a badge you don't get a gun all right
They want to take our guns away.
Do you get a cool hat?
Oh yeah, you get a fez.
Woah, no that's the fucking...
the other one.
The Elks Lodge?
No, they're not that one.
The Shriners.
The hospital?
Yeah, they sponsor hospitals and shit.
That's like the hospital for like burned kids.
The Shriners hospital is for burned kids?
is for burned kids. Well at least there was one. Cause they keep fucking barbecuing all
these kids at some fucked up camp. No they come to parades and they drive tiny little
red cars and wear fezes. You never saw them before? You're thinking of clowns. No look
google shriner cars right now. Alright I will. Have you not seen these before? I will get
to the bottom of this. No. Really? Dude you're gonna love these guys. YOOOOOO! What the fuck
that's sick yeah dude and they do like they do like tricks like they weave in
and out of each other and shit these guys look fucking huge whoa honestly if it
wasn't because the steering wheel is dead in the middle shit no they're like little
cars they're like go-karts yeah golf carts these things are fucking insane
little yellow cars they go fast as hell - see that looks fun if the fucking
Illuminati was like that yeah I mean I wouldn't have all these goddamn
To be honest, I didn't know until like this very second that it was like any type of community.
I just thought it was guys who like to ride little cars.
Yeah, no, Shriners are like the, I think that they probably have like a battle with the Masons.
Yeah.
Like good versus evil, you know?
Yeah, the Shriners are like the, like, it's like the rival summer camps.
And the Shriners are like, like the, like the one, I don't know.
like the jobs I never like or keys or meat masons are like fat camp and then
the holders are like oh yeah you're not coming to the pool party dad's gonna be
the writers are not trying to are masons what something listen I take it all
that Reiner's International also commonly known as the Shriners or
formerly known as ancient Arabic order of the nobles of the mystic shrine the
Masonic society established in 1870.
No!
We were just fucking talking these guys up.
Does Masonic mean that they're Freemasons though?
Are the Shriners Freemasons?
Let's see here.
And it's funny, it's like Masonry.
All Shriners are Masons, but not all Masons are Shriners.
A Shriners International is a spin-off from Freemasonry.
Man, you know, you might be a Shriner.
They did a Fast and Furious spin-off of the Freemasons.
You either go pedophile or tiny car is what you're telling me.
You come to a crossroads.
Okay, it's a kid sized car.
It's a kid sized car.
Yeah, you take the kid, I'll take the car.
I'm a shriner.
I want the little car.
And I want it now.
I got a parade to go to.
It's so funny, it's just like Mason, it's just buildings.
You're just making buildings.
Why is that the most evil people on earth?
Because they can make any building they want, dude.
They're playing fucking Starcraft.
You know what?
That is true.
They can fucking build a base at any point.
All these buildings, all these shitty like new modern buildings, we stopped letting the
masons build buildings and now we got all these fucking cubes.
Exactly dude, they understood that a good building needs a gargoyle.
Yeah.
A gargoyle and like just some weird mural in like a fucking, in the middle, made out
of like a mosaic of like a beaver.
That's a good fucking building man.
Guys, what?
The Shriners are committed to community service and have been instrumental in countless public
projects throughout their domain. Shriners host the annual East West Shrine Game, a college
football all-star game.
What? The East West Shrine Bowl?
Many shrine centers also hold a yearly shrine circus as a fundraiser. And then there's an
image in this Wikipedia page of a Shriner Clown.
There's Shriner Clowns?
A Shriner Clown.
I would hate to break down-
He looks fucked up.
Dude, this guy, if I saw this clown, this is the most evil clown I've ever seen.
Shriner clown.
You know when they put like, I'll send this picture, you know when they put like a Halloween,
like a, make a Halloween mask of a clown and it's like, oh you made it too creepy, like
it's not scary?
Yeah.
This is like what an actual scary clown looks like.
I would kill myself if I saw this clown walking up to me.
Yeah, these are like clowns that you've never actually seen in color because they're in
like all the scary black and white movies.
Yeah, this is a horrible clown.
Fuck.
Fuck that clown.
Yeah, I don't fuck with this clown at all.
I would hate to break down in like a town that's like run by the Shriners because you like call
AAA and a tiny tow truck shows up.
Alright, Hitcher, might take a while.
Oh you go to like the mechanic in a Shriner town?
Yeah.
It's just like the fucking...
The ceiling's four feet tall.
The tools are way too small.
You show up in like a fucking suburban.
What kind of damn car you got here?
Where'd you get this?
The Amazon?
Jesus Christ!
Don't you know there's a Shriner town?
mechanic this what the fuck where's the tiny little battery that goes like I
just googled I just googled Shriner clown just to see what came up and
here's the info box that came up shrine clowns are often considered the most
visible ambassadors of the shrine organization headquartered in
Springfield Massachusetts the Melhurst shrine clown unit is very active in
parades charity benefits festivals and corporate outings all shrine clowns
donate their time and resources as unpaid volunteers.
I think these motherfuckers are more evil.
They have a fucking clown task force.
Imagine being-
Yeah, they have a clown team too.
We have a shrine clown task force.
We've been-
Oh, their logo.
Maybe the fucking Shriners were like,
"Oh yeah, no, the Illuminati, yeah, the fucking free-
"The Illuminati's 100%.
"That's the bad guys right there."
No, meanwhile, these fucking clowns are doing all this bullshit.
Shrine clown, I can tell that's a phrase
that will just be stuck in my head for a year.
Shrine Clown.
What the fuck?
Why is that font, why is the font like, it's like Chinese font.
It's like what they put on like a, on a kung fu, it's like, kung fu lessons for kids.
I'm pretty, I'm pretty anti-clown in general, but once you give them guns and walkie talkies
and shit, I'm out.
God, we can't remember if they have a button on their website to request clowns.
Oh, I'll request.
Don't press that button!
All your windows bust open, they're all fucking zip-lined.
The Melha Shrine Clown's greatest contribution to the welfare of mankind is to warm a heart
with a smile.
If you would like to have the Melha Shrine Clowns at your event, please see the requirements
at the link below.
And then they have a clown's prayer too.
Fuck that dude.
They have a clown prince!
What?!
No shot.
The clown prince is a real thing, it's not just something you call the Joker?
I guess.
Shrine or clown prince.
Is he beautiful?
Oh he better be.
Harold Michael bust my dad's a fucking clown name
I'm just like wandering. I just through websites here
And I just got to this Pinterest link of of choo-choo the answer shrine clown and look
Dude I don't I'm done fucking with this dude. We're gonna get killed. Oh my
We keep talking about this
Tell this clown is not wearing any pants
This cloud is like wet and messy on his legs
Shrine guns a gun shrine cloud
- - the gun shrine cloud
All right
Go ahead and say I have nothing against these clowns. I think they're normal
I don't want you guys doing a fucking payday 2 at my house man.
I don't need that shit.
I'd rather fucking bust in with the clown shit.
It's all a joke on the...
It's a comedy podcast, don't try to attack me.
Yeah dude, you're going to look out your window, there's going to be a small white van parked
out front with no windows.
The fuck dude.
With an antenna.
A tiny antenna on top that's shaped like a bow tie that's spinning.
And then it starts driving away going like, "Ha ha ha ha ha ha!"
You're gonna get owned, bro.
We need to start our own secret society.
You come home from work early and you open up the door to your apartment and there's
just a hundred clowns crammed into your kitchen, like, trying to bug it all at the same time.
Just tripping over each other.
We should have gave out membership cards at the live show.
We should have started our own society.
We can still do that.
That would have been a good move.
Speaking of the live show,
a lot of people met my fucking mom.
Yeah, dude, lucky them.
You met my mom.
Yep, lucky me.
A lot of people have formed--
Your mom touched me.
Amazing friendships with my mom.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude, that's why I was like,
don't bring your family, bro.
I know.
Yeah, they also, you know,
meeting somebody's parents is really demystifying
'cause you're like, I know exactly what proportion
of both of these people is in this person I know.
Right.
Yeah, you look at them--
I know why you are the way you are.
- Yeah, you look at them and go to the Fallout VAC system
and you just get every piece of info
you could possibly want about Patrick
when you look at his parents.
So it's not a good situation to be in.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Thank you to everybody for coming out to that, by the way.
- Oh yeah, thank you.
- Hope you had a lot of fun.
- I mean, we did give out the DVDs.
I guess those can count as the membership,
but we didn't give them out to a lot of people.
I think next show, that's what we do.
We get business cards and then we have a thing on it
that says sign your name here, something like that.
We need a mailing list, I think.
Yeah.
So it's like the first step to a cult, unfortunately.
It's like a mailing list or a call list.
Yeah, I mean we have one. Patreon is, I mean, has that.
That's true. I guess we haven't been using our cult resources enough.
We haven't been good about our cult resources.
We do have to start, we have to start, you know, the organization that will defeat the shrine clowns.
Yeah, we do need to have kind of an anti-clown.
What's the opposite of a clown?
A mummy?
Probably a mummy.
- Not a mummy, dude.
- I don't know.
- No, 'cause here's the thing I thought of.
- Here's the litmus test.
- Clowns are the ones that are afraid of mice
and they eat peanuts, right?
- If it shows up at a birthday party and people like it,
it's too close to a clown.
I think a mummy would be big.
- People would not like it if a mummy showed up.
- Are you fucking kidding me, dude?
I'd do everything to that mummy.
- A magician.
- No, a magician is like exactly a clown.
- A magician is like a subtype of clown.
- A magician's a clown, stupid.
- A magician is literally, it's a subtype of clown.
It's like a--
subtype of clown they do tricks. It's the same thing with the Shriners and the Freemasons.
Clowns do tricks too. A magician is just a clown that's too shy to wear bright colors.
Yeah. It's a goth clown. Yeah. Yeah. Who thinks that it needs to do dark magic. I think the
opposite of a clown I guess would be like an insurance agent or something. Yeah. Or like
a hedgehog. Opposite. Or like maybe like a rock. Yeah. I had to think about it. A rock
might be the exact opposite of a clown. I'm looking up, I looked up what is the opposite
of a clown. What do you think you're gonna find? Okay, Killjoy, Bore, Pessimist, Moaner,
Mope, Miserabilist, Party Pooper, Prude, Damper. No, those are descriptors. We could call them
dampers or something like that or miserabilists. I don't want to... Then that makes us sound
like the bad guys. We're trying to fight this fucking clown Al-Qaeda. We gotta have real
people and we need people on our side. Okay? What about the regular guys?
That's yeah okay. Yeah regular what about the normal society? Nobody is Irish.
That's the number one rule. What? Yeah. That's too close to a clown. That's what
the fuck? Red nose. Yeah dude. Big puffy red nose. Big puffy ass red nose. Big red
cheeks. Red hair. True. Yeah inability to walk a straight line. Yeah really stupid.
there's too many of them yep yeah always the hell is going on right now dude
you're fake Irish bro I'm not whenever yeah you open you open the door you open
the door to a car and there's always more of them in there than you hoped
would be yeah clearly Greek by the way I'm not Greek I took you 23 and me I
like a hundred percent like British and I read your chest hair looks like
fucking taco meat dude you're not there's no fucking way you're Irish you
were you were you are the falafel man that's I don't look I don't look that
Mediterranean you are falafel up my friend you do look pretty Greek yeah I
don't look there is no Greek in my fucking bloodline you blow your nose you
be fucking have a Kleenex full of hummus no yeah hummus hummus is Israeli that's
Mediterranean. Fuck. Fucking idiot. I would have preferred if you were going with the
Greek thing I would have preferred you said you're right you're Israeli you're
right yeah yeah you're right you got me you're fucking Israeli. Look I want to
say my bad I'm sorry about all that crap that's happening. Oh that bull crap who
even knows what it is but it's yeah but it's fully Patrick's fault that's all. I
also want to clear up that one time that that we did we didn't have the theme
song in it wasn't because of what's going on over there was because I forgot to
put it in and then Patrick told some people that it was because you know we
didn't want to be attached to Israel and then I put that I didn't know that he
told people that so I put the song back in because I just forgot it one time by
accident it seemed like we were like yeah it's over we support it now so just
so you know you know it's funny for us to draw a line on that like right now
yeah it's like Israel Israel just this year went too far yeah yeah great thing
to bring up that's hilarious
I'm just saying it's like one of the worst things a country could ever do.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, dude.
We uh, but we, you know, I, the thing is, I'm, my opinion is whatever Biden decides.
That's my guy.
I'm sticking with him.
Oh yeah, we're, we're becoming breadtubers.
I don't know if you know, all those like guys online that complain about like, uh, they
say like Chapo is Biden adjacent or whatever.
Uh, no, that's us.
We're the, uh, we're the fucking, we're becoming political.
I mean, if you, yeah, I mean, that's the one thing.
Yeah.
That's right, I'm going to start fucking sitting on bad dragon dildos and shit on cam.
Why is that with that?
Why is there...
And that is all for Joe Biden.
Yeah, I'm doing it for him.
Dude, I'm sending him all the fucking fuck tokens that I get on the fucking campsites.
Why do women want to have sex with a dragon?
Or men, I don't know.
Why is there a dragon penis that sells so many coffees?
I think it's a texture thing.
I think it's a texture thing. So if I was fucking, if I if I looked like the fantastic for the
thing you think I'd get a lot of pussy? I think some people would be interested in
having sex with you. In a gravel penis? Yeah. Alright dude I might have to become a scientist.
Yeah, wait. I don't know that much about the thing. Is his, is it like bit, he got bit by a rock.
He did not get bit by a rock. He did not get bit by a rock. Well no, is it, is it like
He got cosmic rays.
Cobblestone completely or is it like fleshy cobblestone?
I think it's just rocks.
I think he's just like made of rocks.
Yeah, he's just made out of rocks.
I mean I feel like it wouldn't be a very good power if it's like I just look like I'm made
of rocks but I don't, I'm not actually like strong or hard or anything.
I have all the strength of a rock but I can still bleed because it's flesh.
You can still pinch me.
That could just be bad dude.
You just have like a, then he just has a bunch of like butt cracks all over his body.
That's true.
Yeah, is his penis like wrinkly like that?
I would guess so.
gotta be somebody drew that right yeah let me see yeah they used to have the
Marvel swimsuit edition that used to be what they had yeah oh yeah that's uh I
think they had Namor in a in a bikini whoo yeah wait a little hand of love
Namor loves to wear some some titillating swimsuits - and it's little
wings by his ankles - oh yeah those things I like man yeah yeah there's a
reason he's the king of Atlantis or whatever yeah because of the wing little
things no because of his fat dick he has a fat cock do they draw the dick under
the like when they do the I think draw the bulge let me look up they definitely
they drew a lot of they drew a lot of supervillain bulge in like the old when
they
he's fifteen years old you gotta take that out
that's not cool
number three they have namor
and a lady on the cover
uh... hold on let me look up namor
penis namor the submarine namor penis
nude penis
and this is a research i would not let us know that the wings on the side
this is basically a really complicated you know my daughter he has a h_d_ right
now yeah
doing a dissertation right now on a busy as i was the other that is the of
widows peak pubes to i found this website is called rule thirty four
nice
is a good
i mean look at
name rule yet let me see what i was concerned a more but whole really quick
at a song yeah
Well I just, I mean probably any butthole we can imagine what it would look like on him.
Let's just search up man's butthole.
These people, these people drawing these Namor, you know, I might, yeah, 34 things.
They're so uninventive.
I might just, you know, Henry Butthole.
Oh no, that's, okay.
Search that, just see what comes up.
That's a load.
I thought that they gave him a dick ring.
I was excited.
A load?
Yeah, like there's jizz.
He's coming a perfect ring?
It looked like a ring in his, it looked like a Prince Albert.
Or he can control water, right?
Oh, shit!
If Namor can control water, he can probably control cum, right?
So he can shoot it out and make it...
He can at least control the water part of it and just like white dust will keep going.
He can probably fucking bend it like a balloon animal once he pulls it out of his dick.
That'd be pretty impressive.
Here, here's a dog. Put this in your mouth.
A dog?
Yeah, you make a dog with a balloon animal.
Oh, god.
What's wrong with you, Pat?
I thought you said he was putting his cum in a dog.
Well, he could probably do that. He's evil. He could probably do that, too.
Well, he's sometimes evil. Depends.
I'm sorry. I just laughed because I looked at the list again that we have.
I didn't even mean that as a segue. I just opened the tab and laughed immediately because I saw the picture.
We're doing a list from the pick-up lines dot net.
I can tell we'll be back to this website. This is a really good website.
This is hot, the tagline is "Hot Pickup Lines for Girls or Guys at Tinder and Chat"
and this list is "Top 47 Suicide Pickup Lines"
[Laughter]
So there's 47...
Very good. 47 of them is nuts too.
Suicide pickup lines.
I think there's some repeating ones here.
Here, I mean I can come up with one right now.
Hey, if you don't fuck me, I'm gonna kill myself.
[laughs]
That's like perfect, right?
That's on here.
Is it?
I don't know, I haven't read it yet.
How did you know there were repeats?
You just made that up?
Number one and two, I just read.
Oh yeah, those are kind of the same.
So following is our collection of smooth and dirty,
a dirty suicide pickup line,
uh, pickup lines and opening zinnin,
what?
working better than Reddit.
Include killer Omegle conversation starters
starters and useful chat up lines and comebacks for situations when you are
burned guaranteed to work best as tinder openers all right so you've been fucking
trolling around tender for a little bit you finally fucking a match or somebody
she's hot and then you open with this are you my suicidal thoughts because I
can't stop thinking of you opening I just looked this up opening Zenon is
Dutch for pickup lines Dutch in this might be a Dutch website possibly based
- It is a .net.
- There's also not very many,
I mean the grammar's not great here on a lot of these.
- Number two, hey girl, are you suicide?
Because I think about you a lot.
I'd like to do those two back to back
without the girl responding.
- Yeah, no break in between.
- Are you my suicidal thoughts?
Because I can't stop thinking of you.
Hey girl, are you suicide?
Because I think about you a lot.
- Sending all of them back to back to back.
- Yeah.
- All 47.
- Just copy and pasting the entire thing.
Sending them numbered as well.
- Yeah, with the numbers.
- Yeah.
- Number three.
This will work every time. You can't spell suicide without you and I.
Do you say that in the thing? That's also a threat. That's not a pickup line.
That's a "we are going to commit suicide." That's way more about suicide than it is about picking somebody up.
Yeah.
You can't say that to somebody.
Number four, this one's not safe for work.
So don't use these suicide pickup lines. Don't use that one.
Not this number, everybody else,
they're just pretty fair game.
But this one, don't use this on your boss.
- Are you a suicidal turtle?
'Cause you can swallow my straw.
- I don't think they're committing suicide.
I think they think it's a worm.
- I don't know that straw is that flattering either,
I feel like.
- Yeah, here's my straw.
My coffee stirrer.
- Yeah, you a quill 'cause you can touch my needle.
My little tiny needle penis.
Do you wanna see my needle penis?
it's one inch bigger. Yeah, are you an elf? Because you can have my gumdrop. Maybe it would
be one that you could say. Life without you is like coding while GitHub is down. All I
can commit is suicide. What? That's like, there's so many intersections there. What? You have
to have some knowledge of GitHub and probably... So does she! Yeah, that's what I mean. I need
to know that know that commit can also be used in a github context and then they
have to like suicide jokes yeah I'm gonna read I mean this next six through nine
I'm gonna read just in a row because this is how these are meant to be sent I
think this is a similar situation I agree are you suicide because you won't stop
crossing my mind are you suicide cuz you're always on my mind is your name
suicide cuz you're always on my mind are you suicide cuz I think about you a lot
that's the fucking same one also there's nothing hotter than explaining to a
woman at a bar that all you can do is think about suicide yeah no no oh fuck
he's so hot he wants also like yeah maybe a pickup line to a pickup line that
opens with I think about you all the time is also maybe not the way to go right
if you're approaching somebody for the first time I'm so hey I've been
following I've been thinking about you a lot you're kind of like suicide in that
way I'm realizing that suicide pickup line really sounds like a number you call
and I kill yourself doesn't really sound right number 10 are you diving suicides
because you make my heart rate race I don't know what that means there's a
picture here this picture is what made me laugh when what I clicked onto this
dad yeah there's a picture here it's just a guy and it says suicide pickup
line and then it's the turtle one but he looks concerned yeah he looks like
somebody is taking the photo against his will yeah okay so now we get into the
funny suicide pickup line yeah those other ones weren't funny yeah there's
only two of these were serious credible threats yeah there's only two of these
girl you must be suicide because I've been thinking about you all day and are
Are you a suicide bomber because you have blown me away?
Don't say that one in Ireland.
No.
Those are not that funny.
Pretty funny to me.
I think I would laugh.
But there's only two of those.
Then we get into the depressing pick up lines.
Yeah.
Which is pretty good.
The same one, are you a suicide because I think about you every day.
They have to keep putting that in there.
Okay, this one is at least a joke.
This one is, "Are you a toaster?
Because I really want to take a bath with you."
That's good.
Yeah, I mean...
Are you a noose because I really want to hang with you?
It's good.
Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
"Are you a gravestone?
Because I really wish you were on top of me."
You didn't say if you would.
I will hang with you.
Aw, yay!
I will.
Yay!
And I will fuck you.
Is that what you want?
I'm gonna fuck you and suck your penis.
Yay!
I'm gonna finger your butt.
Here's one for your fucker.
Hey girl, is your name suicide?
Cause I can't stop thinking about you.
Oh that's pretty good.
That's actually pretty good.
What about this one?
Hey boy girl, are you suicide?
Because I think about doing you a lot.
That's pretty good man.
Okay so now I'm starting to see how they got 47.
A lot of filler here.
Are you antidepressants?
you every day I'm going to kill myself
this one is a damn girl is your last name suicide and then in asterisks no why
because I think about you every day is your last name suicide and then her
saying no no are you a coffin because I really wish I was inside you right now
These could be zombie or Dracula themed as well.
It's true.
Between the gravestone and the coffin.
Are you a coroner? Because I really want you to inspect my body.
Ugh.
Are you... this one's gross.
Are you an electrical outlet? Because I really want to stick my fingers in you.
[laughing]
That's pretty bold.
I mean like I get like yeah, you wanna I mean like good
Yeah, are you a fish cuz look at my worm or whatever?
But to walk up to a girl at a bar and be like I'm gonna put my fingers in you
Can I put my finger in your mouth I fucked up I fucked up the pickup line, I'm sorry
You see to count my fingers cuz all of them these going in you right now. You better like this. That's a bad pickup line
Not good
Are you traffic because running into you would really make my day
That would not that was confusing I would I would I would if somebody said that to me
I'll be like I think you got it got it wrong. I think you messed it up
Yeah, I think you're thinking of birthday cake. Yeah traffic. You don't want to run into traffic. You'll die
No, you understand
Yeah
Sinking shit because I really like to go down on you
Scroll down and look at this picture not the one right here, but the one look at the picture after it this picture is horrific
Okay
So this is a this will work every time you can't spell suicide without you and I and the photo is kind of a GQ style
like
Shot of a nude man who looks like he's trying to stab his own back. Yeah, he also has some like bizarre
Musculature going on to some yeah, it's shaped body. He's ripped
except then the rest of them are just are just repeats and I just need to read you
this this last paragraph here from this list use only working paropa and phrases
that can tie this for girls and all brace note that dirty phrases are funny but
don't use them in real life in practice saying sexual smooth suicide phrases to
someone you haven't picked up yet is usually just creepy sexual smooth side
races. Wait, I just found one. I just found an insane one too. Yeah, what's yours? This
one is top eight Japanese pickup lines. I have a really good one too. Do the Japanese
ones and then this one's good. Okay, there's only eight of these. This is pretty easy.
Well, the first one makes no sense, but number two, are you Japanese? Because I want to go
full Hiroshima on you. Oh my God. That one is going to destroy, dude. Are you Japanese?
that'll do really well on someone who's Japanese.
- Right.
- Probably love that dude.
They'll be like, "Oh, I know what that is."
Are you Japanese?
Because I want to get into Japantese.
All right.
Maybe the Jamaican accent, that one.
- That one's a thinker.
- Are you Japanese?
Because I want to put my sake in your Nagasaki.
- What?
- That one doesn't make any sense.
Did you know that I'm quite a bit
like the Japanese public transport system?
When I come three seconds too early,
I will apologize profusely.
I just found...
Wait, wait, wait, I'm sorry.
No, I'm next, Patrick.
This one's good.
Are you Japanese?
Because I'll jam my penis inside you.
I mean, I guess that's a bait and switch.
Jam penis.
It's a pun.
Jam my penis.
That's really a stretch, man.
Yeah.
That's a big time stretch.
I'm sorry.
All right, I got one here that I'm just gonna read through all these in a row for you, okay?
top 18 pet insurance pickup lines
All right
No, I'll just go through them. I hope you have pet insurance because I'm about to destroy your pussy
I hope you have pet insurance because I'm about to destroy your pussy
Do you happen to have pet insurance because that pussy is gonna get smashed tonight
Do you have pet insurance because I'm going destroy your pussy. Do you have pet insurance because your pussy's getting smashed tonight
Do you have pet insurance because I want to smash your cat
Do you have pet insurance because I'm gonna destroy that pussy tonight. Hey girl
I hope you have pet insurance because I'm gonna destroy that pussy later
Do you have pet insurance cuz I'm about to destroy your pussy girl
Do you have pet insurance because I'm about to smash that pussy
Do you have a pet insurance cuz that pushy is pussy is going to get smashed tonight
Do you have pet insurance because I'm going to tear that pussy up
I hope you have pet insurance cuz I am destroying that pussy tonight. Do you have pet insurance girl?
No, why me cuz I'm gonna destroy your pussy
to kill that pussy. I hope you have bed insurance because I'm about to destroy your pussy. Do
you have bed insurance because I'm about to smash your pussy.
Oh my god. All of them are the exact same. They went with
18 too. There's only one thing they could think of.
Why go 18 on that one? You could say maybe top 5 and then do the same one 5 times. That's
still fine. Well, okay. This website has a very weird
thing well they'll throw any number and then just put I looked up there's a tag
on this one June I opened up June pickup lines top two June pickup lines this one
also has a girl oh wait the Archduke of Austria on the day of June 28th 1914
because I want to take you out oh like I like the song uh-huh genius the pet
insurance thing as a one of the picture the auto-generated pictures they have and
And it says, "I hope you have pet insurance because I'm about to destroy your pussy."
And then it's a picture of a dog wearing a bandana.
[Laughter]
Here's the second June pickup line.
"Is your birthday in June? Because you are an Alexandrite."
[Laughter]
Top 50 Columbus Day pickup lines.
I have... Okay, so this is top 50 sexual pickup lines.
Okay.
So I'm excited to see what they have here.
I think I said this one in the chat.
Number one, you're so hot even my zipper is falling for you.
Ooh.
That one's not that bad.
I'm flashing you right now, look down.
[laughter]
Hello pretty young lady.
Would you like to have sexual intercourse with me and I treat you to wine and roses?
[laughter]
That is the most Dutch pickup line on this one.
What the fuck?
I was looking around the room thinking about who I'd like to sexually assault and you'd be my first choice.
What the fuck, dude?
My doctor told me- oh no, I know that one.
These are- these are fucking horrible, bro.
Here's one, here's one.
I did not have sexual relations with that woman, but I'll have them with you.
That one only works if you're Bill Clinton.
Yeah.
Did you know women typically reach their sexual prime in their 30s and 40s?
And you are ripened.
Are you big sweaty guy from Bill Nye the Science Guy because I am sexually attracted to you?
Are you a sex worker because I'd pay to have sex with you?
Doom will gladly engage in sexual activities with you doom endures
Here's one I think it's funny, but probably too sexual what do you think?
Accidentally put a comment into the list. Can I buy you a drink? I'm more normal than you think in reality
I have a decent personality and I'm really into same sexuality
Whoa?
That's a rap. He'd be fucking spit bars there. I don't know what to tell you. Oh, here's another dude. Here's another rap
Will you be my date to the folk festival your haircuts asymmetrical girl? I find it sexual
That's stolen that has stolen. Here's I found I was looking around on this website found this one here
Top 35 Genshin Impact pickup lines.
(laughter)
Did you have fun with Genshin Impact?
'Cause I know a game more fun called Smashing Impact.
Liz, imagine going up to someone in the bar and saying this,
"I got a bomb in my testicles and I need to pass it on.
World's most sexual game of hot potato."
Wait, dude, hold on.
This is the top 50 April Fool's Day pickup lines.
So these are not actual pickup lines.
I just sent it. These are in these are so good
Number one. Oh, these are yeah with your blood. Hey, baby want to paint the whole town red. Yeah with your blood
You said the punchline first by accident and then the next laid it off
Insert pickup line want to get laid totally crawl up a chicken's ass and wait. Whoa
Check out number four here.
A, you are attractive.
B, you are the best.
C, you are cute.
D, you are dear to me.
E, you are excellent.
F, you are funny.
G, you are good looking.
H, hee hee hee.
(laughing)
I, I'm J, joking.
- Oh my god.
- The hee hee hee was a nice touch.
Beautiful, intelligent, talented, cute, hilarious.
Are you smiling now?
You are really bitch.
- 'Cause it smells bitch.
- Yeah, it smells bitch.
- It smells like bitch in here.
- You are the most cute persons in the world.
Just a second, don't misunderstand.
Cute means creating useless troubles everywhere.
- Oh, fuck. - Ooh.
- Fuck, boom!
- I want you to be with me in a nice restaurant
to have candlelight dinner
and say those three sweet word to you.
Pay the bill, fool.
(laughing)
- Do you wanna dance?
Yeah, but not with you.
You must have understood me.
I said you look fat in those pants.
Oh, I love you.
I love you.
Hey, don't get excited.
I also love VWXYZ.
Hey, cutie.
Wait, what is it?
How about you and I hitting the hotspot?
Sorry, I don't date outside my species.
That hipster dress is a joke.
Better take it off.
Pretty, pretty good.
I can make your bed rock.
Oh yeah, an earthquake can too.
I can make your bed rock. Oh, yeah an earthquake can - oh
These are torts - yeah, this is that is somebody ever use that on me I know to say hmm
The pay the bill fool one again
That hipster dress is a joke better take it off. I just said that you just said that one. No
I just said that.
I'm sorry.
Hey Patrick, someone misses you, needs you, worries about you, lonely without you.
Guess who?
The monkey in the zoo!
Aww.
I have the spicy pick up lines, where it's stuff like "Girl you're so hot and I'm looking
to snack on something spicy.
I'd love to taste those spicy meatballs of yours."
But then, oh fuck where is this one?
I just had it.
Your taco meat looks spicy, can I stuff your muff?
And then this one, I want to taste your spicy buffalo sauce.
I got the top 50 clash of clans pick up lines.
Can a wall breaker destroy the walls you built around you?
You gotta use that in clash of clans.
My giants will protect you, baby.
God, can't.
There was a Dateline story, there was a Dateline episode that I watched.
And there was a dude who's wife, he was cheating on his wife.
And I forget his name, I think his name was Remy Ramsaran.
No way.
That's like a $2 champagne.
He was cheating on his wife and then he found out she was cheating on him with a guy in Clash of Clans and he killed her.
killed her to him.
Clash of Clans is crazy because it's like I mean it's clearly very popular and successful
but I don't think I have ever once in my life met somebody who has played it.
I don't even know what it is.
That episode's-
It's a game for your phone right?
Yeah.
That episode's fucking crazy too because they like have interviews with the guy before like
he went to jail and the interviewer's talking to him and she's like, "So you were like,
you were like cheating on your wife."
and he goes, "Oh yeah, oh yeah, that was bad."
(laughing)
- Wait, wait, wait, so his wife cheated on him
with someone in Clash of Clans?
Is there like a fuck button in Clash of Clans?
- There's a chat in Clash of Clans, I guess.
I don't think it was Clash of Clans,
I think it's one of those adjacent games,
but he was like, yeah, and then he,
there's like the interview, the interviewer's like,
"Would anyone ever describe you as like quirky or odd?"
And he goes, "Absolutely, including everybody
"that's ever met me, especially my wife, Jen."
(laughing)
- I never got that, dude.
I remember people used to get,
grown women would cheat on their husbands on Second Life.
And the thing is, who cares?
She's fucking Barney.
Why are you fucking stressed out about that shit, dude?
She's fucking, don't kill her, she's weird.
Yeah, they were, ah fuck, have you seen that Second Life documentary?
No.
Oh dude, it's so- I never got it, I wish I had done Second Life.
I played Second Life like in like, in college, like cause nobody played it anymore.
Just, I will say the character creator, the most fun character creator of all time.
Yeah, I feel like it got- Oh, it made your guy really tiny?
Yeah, you could do anything with that dude.
I feel like all those people are on like VR chat now.
Yeah, sure.
That's a new one.
I get those people who they spend like five thousand dollars to get like a full haptic
feedback suit and then they walk around VRChat trying to hug kids.
Yeah.
It's fucking weird man.
That's why Caleb got the headset.
No, I don't have a haptic VR suit and I hate VRChat.
Everybody's mean to me on there.
I have a, I want to, Caleb this is for you.
A Clash of Clans pick up line.
Goblin's favorite target is resources but my fave is you.
online gather so sweet and patrick this one's for you
all i can't wait
history will be written by men who ride hogs
wall
this is uh... top fifty super mario
pickup lines to sell so if you can get a real more from work less of clinton's
really quick
yeah uh...
if i was a goblin i would totally steal your heart
uh...
The only one that this is loading for me makes no sense at all.
It's, uh, "I'd love to have your castle in my princess."
[laughter]
What the f--
It should be the other way around.
No, is that fucking me? Oh, wait, they loaded.
"You give me a one-up." Dot dot dot.
Yeah, in my pants!
[laughter]
Yeah, that's right, my penis has a new life now.
You've given my penis new life!
hey baby want me to show you where to find the magic mushroom yes my damn
balls in my penis you bitch I I'm looking at a the top 11 Tuesday pickup lines uh-
huh number four I spend Tuesdays with Maury
I spent Tuesday that only works for Mitch album I spent Tuesdays with Maury
This is really funny because I went to the top 50 doctor pickup lines and the
first the first four are about being a doctor. Yeah. The rest of them are all
about Doctor Who. I just go that is like what the fuck is going on because
there's one that's are you a cyborg because you take my breath away and
there's a bunch of stuff like this. Alright dude imagine you're at like the
40/40 Club like really really nice shit right you're like the hottest girl in
world you got a red dress on you know what you're Gal Gadot I just decided you
are Gal Gadot at the 40/40 Club right? I walk in it's a club owned by Jay-Z I
walk in dress head to toe in Spencer's Gift and Hot Topic original t-shirts and
pants okay yeah and I have a I'm wearing my Rick and Morty beanie actually I'm
just dressed exactly I was at the live show full Rick and Morty head to toe I
I walk up to you, "Huh, I can see why Bowser wants to kidnap you so badly."
Tell me you're not getting fucking wet as shit right then, dude.
You're like, "I'm Gal Gadot and I'm gonna fuck you in public 'cause I'm so horny, Mr. Mario."
I'm still on the Tuesday pickup lines.
Number eight here, "Did you know it is Titty Tuesday?
It will mean the world to me if I can caress, nibble, and suck on your sexy boobs.
It's Tuesday, show me your tits.
Here's top three wholesome pickup lines.
There's only three?
Yeah, they messed up somewhere along the line.
I'll read these to you.
So the first one is, you know, it's okay.
Number one, you are platinum in a room full of gold.
My friend who was graduating told me this in a Zoom meeting because he had to leave,
and I told him I'd miss him.
it was extremely kind and wholesome wanted to share now here now the other
two they don't think they understood what to put here because number two is for a
girl named pearl mainly wanted to be wholesome smiley face number three is
one for Emanuelle I like a girl named Emanuelle and she is studying computer
science in college she's also a great singer in my opinion I would really
appreciate a wholesome pickup line girl are you really princess peach for real
because I want to find out what you taste like.
- What?
- That's nasty.
- That's not okay to say to somebody.
- You can't really, okay, okay.
Hold on, let's see.
Can't really search this website.
- No.
- Use only working piropos and frases de cantadas
for girls and hombres.
Note that dirty phrases are funny,
but don't use them in real life.
In practice, saying sexual smooth Super Mario phrases
to someone you haven't picked up yet is usually creepy.
- Let me put that at the bottom of every list.
is
I just imagined like she asked you the time you're like it's flirty flirty you
me go oh shit I remember there's a line I'm supposed to say right now I found the
top eight Wednesday pickup lines so this is good you mess it up and you just say
it's 2:30 and she's like what is it's like six o'clock number one ash
Wednesday is coming up is it a sin that you stole my heart hey girl are you
Italian cuz I'd love to see your Naples number two I'm a vampire but only on
alternate Wednesdays what the fuck does that mean top 50 gangster pickup lines
okay this could be good I've never had authentic Italian you should let me eat
your ass hey do you like Italian food would you like some ball sack no okay
Here's the fucking the last three on the top eight Wednesday pickup lines.
Number six, "Happy Woe Wednesday." Number seven, "I need some woes to help me get
through Wednesday." Number eight, "Want to serve soup kitchen with me on Wednesday?"
Alright, so this is the gangster pickup lines. They go godfather for the first
for but the number five is number five yo ho's what's y'all's bitch asses names
lie down with me it's my final offer or you'll be lying with Jimmy Hoffa if you
don't fuck me I'm gonna kill you I'm a gangster yeah there's a they have a
pretty mostly mostly mostly mafia gangster on here girl I can't wait to
extort you on here yeah what do you mean by that this is a funny gangster pickup
line hey baby are you in 1928 Cadillac Town sedan because I would love to ride
you like a mafia hey baby I'd do anything to get with you including stealing your
husband's identity hey baby I know what you did last summer what's gangster
about that dude I must complete the mission at all first sex working
gangster tinder opener I will be watching you I'm digging you like a shovel ma I'm
here to fulfill your fondest wishes now that your husband sleeps with the fishes
somebody somebody went on here just submitted a bunch that rhyme yeah I
I don't think they understood what a pickup line was.
I think this was a jester.
Yeah.
I think a jester might have been behind this.
Yeah, the gangster jester.
Oh, fuck.
From the t-shirts?
Might have been one of the fucking Shriner clowns, dude.
Yeah, dude.
Oh my god.
If this was written by fucking...
Oh, you know what it is?
I'm stupid, dude.
The opposite of a clown is a mime.
No.
Oh!
No, it's a mime.
No, it's absolutely not.
Yeah, dude.
He's the Bizarro World clown.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's like you have a mi- like a clown is chaotic evil and a mime is lawful evil.
They're still on the same end of the- they're still on the same half.
Nah, the mime is the clown's shadow, brother.
No.
Listen to me on this one, brother.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, you're wrong.
The mime- you gotta- you gotta get- That's an insane thing to say.
Nah, the mime is- the mime is the opposite.
Nah, people will back me- people will vindicate me on this.
He ain't got no colors on him!
Yeah, but he's a silent clown.
A mime is- Yeah, which is one of the defining things about a clown.
Is it their loud? It's a French clown. No, clowns don't talk either. Yeah they do, they
go like... what do they say? They don't say anything, they don't talk. But they do make
noise. They honk. They walk up and they make your wife feel really uncomfortable. They
say "I'm loving it." One time a clown gave me a caramel apple at a fair. Yeah. Pretty
much scared me for life. What happened after that? I fell in love with him. Love potion
the my uh no never mind i was gonna talk about i was gonna talk about a family
member who's a clown but i probably oh yeah no that's a bad idea yeah i'm not
gonna do that clowns have is that like a do they have a secret identities
he's a normal guy who is a clown if that's what you mean but like not a clown all the time if
you're a clown like do you do you do you keep your identity secret yeah there was a like there
somebody finds out your name is Bobo when you're working you have to kill yourself.
Yeah exactly.
When I was in when I was in community college in Laconia there was a uh
there was like a clown supply store.
Oh like one of the cop supply stores but for clowns?
Yeah but for clowns it was like a clown.
That's the opposite of a cop.
Maybe.
Yeah maybe but it was a clown supply store it was run by a clown.
No.
Her name I think it was Serendipity the clown.
Female clown.
Honestly high sh*t of all time.
She was dressed up like a clown all the time apparently. I never went in but my
my professor told me that they had to shoot something there and he had a
student who was afraid of clowns. And they had to shoot a clown that got rabid.
They had to shoot a fucking clown.
Dude, I do not
I do not fuck with clowns. I'd like to, I'd like to, yeah, I'd like to publicly come out
with that. I don't, I'm scared of the Shriner's Clowns now. I think we do need to
The Shrine Clowns I think are maybe the most evil clowns I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Because, yeah, you're not only, you couldn't just decide between being like an Illuminati,
a low-ranking Illuminati member, or like a clown that scares children.
You had to be both.
You had to split the difference.
That's pretty fucking evil.
You must be a fucked up individual.
I really like clowns, but I like them because I like imagining them being killed.
I just think it's funny.
That's very funny to me.
It's like Slipknot.
I do I just sit there I mean that's you know that's probably where it what it
would happen to me at a young age but I do spend a good amount of my time I'm not
talking about you guys just talking with you guys just sitting around thinking
about it like a clown in a meat grinder or something going how many clowns are
murdered in the line of duty every year that's a good question yeah the line
sorry the line of goofy my bad yeah what if it's like when one clown dies
is
like a in line with the rainbow
that's you know that's the guy has a sense of the kids and it's like a flag
that's a race
who yeah i don't know that i don't think that the clown flag has not it's not
what i want to do not only does it work for the worst thing i could have said in
this month he fucked everything up and i have it
well everybody
my body
[BLANK_AUDIO]