You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the hopeless.
You're a crap monster.
Now I remember.
Now I remember how to record an episode.
No you don't.
The next hour will prove you don't remember a single fucking thing about it, pal.
What?
Hey, happy 4/20, guys.
Fuck 4/20.
We're recording this on 4/20.
I forgot guys. I'm so high right now. I forgot how to record an episode great and now my god
Great another person. I'm okay. Just I just hotbox my entire house, too
I closed all the windows and the doors and I put a plastic bag over my head and I was smoking weed out of my
Pen with a lighter and god damn I got high. Yeah, dude. Okay 420. Yeah, like we need another junkie holiday
Yeah, I put I put a first Christmas
I put a lithium ion battery on the stove and I was just inhaling the fumes from that.
Dude, I was getting so high, dude.
I ate a whole ass brownie and I left the gas on.
I'm high on ketosis right now.
I don't need any fucking weed.
K2?
Is that what you said?
No, I'm high on a lack of carbohydrates.
I'm so high, I can't hear.
I'm high on K2.
I smoked kush two times.
Ooh, I smoked two joints in the morning.
Alright, that was actually, that's pretty good actually.
I smoked two joints at night.
Are you guys seriously showing up for work high right now?
I'm getting dug with high right now.
I smoked a bong that was a thousand feet tall.
My dad has never smoked weed in his life and he's a huge getting dug with high fan.
He just sits there and laughs his ass off it.
How does he even understand what they're talking about?
I know dude, they're so fucked up.
I will tell you though, I will tell you though, stay up late past midnight, you're going to
understand a little bit about the stoner's mind.
True.
Just from sleep deprivation will drive you a little giggly.
Yeah.
That's true.
If you know, yeah.
A little slap happy.
You would light up after that.
Dude, that's it.
Oh my God.
I mean, TV is going to be the funniest thing to you ever.
Yeah.
I'm crossfading.
You're going to be watching intro-mercials.
Dude, you're going to be sitting there.
And you're going to be going, "Ooooh."
What's your guys' favorite two things to get crossfaded with?
I like sleepiness and adult swim.
Yeah.
Those are my things.
I sit there and I get high on both.
Those are, that's pretty good.
pretzels and hummus and lying down and that gets me that gets me pretty I laugh
pretty hard at Spongebob that's pretty good yeah I like to my cross fading is I
just take a faucet note and I put it under my lip like this and I go and I
breathe in and out like that yeah oh man and then I and then I uh you what you
want to smell it I smell shoo goo you want to take a you want to take a brown
paper lunch bag and yeah that's what I put shoo goo in the bag tell you what
one you put one nug of marijuana in there it's like smoking tell you what
insanely high insanely high putting like one nug of weed and you can leave it on
your neighbor's porch to for a wild ass high fucking swagged out prank you know
what I like to do I like to fucking put some epoxy or gorilla glue into my
penis tip and try to pee. That shit will get you so insanely high dude. Starts fucking
filling up like a balloon. Oh my god dude. And then you tell your girl, you say, "Try
and get that out." Yeah. Yeah with your ass. She has to chomp on it. Or something. You
gotta chomp on the tip. Use your ass to chomp my penis please. I, dude, there's a. Turn
your, turn your b-hole into a chame chomp. I know you got teeth down there. Learned it
in bible school. Show me that asshole. Chomp on my shit. What you gotta do, you go over
to your great uncle's house, you put your mouth on his stoma, you breathe in, you're gonna
get the craziest buzz of your life. He's gonna deflate like a balloon. Go to grandpa's house,
find the kidney stones that he brought back from the urgent care, crush him up and snort
him dude. That'll get you fucking crazy high. I've definitely talked about getting nicotine
poisoning on the podcast before, but have you guys ever?
Nicotine poisoning?
I never got nicotine poisoning.
I definitely thought I almost threw up sometimes.
How dare you talk bad about the holy nicotine flower?
I've thrown up from smoking too many cigarettes so many times.
From the Blessed Tobacco Plant?
Yeah.
Really?
Uh huh.
I don't believe it, dude.
You're a propaganda artist.
It happened.
Nope.
- Definitely, I don't think it's like,
I bet you believe those paintings
on front of the cigarettes too.
- I'm gonna tell you--
- Ever heard of CGI?
It's how they remove all the guy's teeth.
- I don't know if it's like poisoning that I got,
but it's definitely like--
- Did you turn green?
- Yeah, I turned green.
- I wanna let you guys in on a little nicotine secret, okay?
Everybody knows it doesn't get you high like weed, right?
But that's because you're lighting the cigarette on fire.
You get it cold, gets you high.
Nicotine overdose?
- Do you know nicotine is one molecule--
- I'm on WebMD, I'm looking at nicotine poisoning.
- One molecule off of gold?
- Did you know a cigarette-- - On a molecular level?
- You know they invented a cigarette
that was one molecule wide?
- Whoa. - So you can't see it
and you can hide it from your teachers?
- That's actually fucking genius, dude.
- Yeah.
- Son, what are all these damn molecules
in this shoe box under your bed?
(laughing)
Hey, you tell me, genius, huh?
Go ahead and try, fuckin' asshole.
That is, dude, it's actually low-key genius.
Instead of storing your weed under your bed,
you just store the crafting ingredients
you need to craft weed.
True, dirt, seeds, hydroponic structures.
It's so easy.
And magic.
And alchemical table.
What's the thing in Minecraft that you can put
on the seeds and make it grow?
Can we not talk about Minecraft on the weed holiday?
Can we keep these two things fuckin' separate?
I don't want to think about drugs and my favorite game on the same day.
There's a weed mod for Minecraft, did you know that?
I don't even want to know what it's called.
But it's probably called...
It's called weed mod?
My weed.
Mine weed.
No.
It's called dick weed and it's named after you.
Adolf Spliffler's birthday today.
True.
Sheesh.
Adoink Spliffler.
split a yank split flares favorite day is today yeah Hitler like kill yeah he
killed himself yeah and 30th 10 days after his birth how do you think he
killed himself he had a fucking weed molar and mopped it CBD molar he killed
himself yeah CBD he hail hydrate and fucking popped it yeah secret CBD cap
That guy was in a different dimension though.
So I want you guys to watch it.
Yeah, you don't think weed's addictive?
That's what people say.
It's not addictive, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm still on the nicotine poisoning web page.
I bet you are.
Symptoms typically last an hour or two after a mild overdose.
So it's technically like an overdose on nicotine.
Dude, it's not 4th of July, which is the 4/20 for nicotine.
I'm fuckin 420.
Alright?
Yeah, I don't want to hear about nicotine anymore.
Chill.
That's really good.
Okay?
We're talking about-
That's really good.
You can fuckin do this on our Bastille Day episode.
Yeah, come on dude.
We're talking about weed.
That's true.
Yeah, I think that 420 for cigarettes is a lot better for Bastille Day because it's French.
Yeah.
Well anyway, you guys love smoking cigs.
I'm not French.
Yeah, you are.
I'm white.
And I smoke cigs on Fourth of July.
Isn't it weird to you guys that French dressing is orange?
It's not about weed.
I don't care.
Can you just talk about weed?
I'm sorry, I'm having ideas.
I'm having ideas right now.
No you're fucking not, dude.
This is what you should be talking about.
I'm so stoned.
Listen to me.
I'm so high.
This is what you should be saying, okay?
Remember that?
Oh, you can't overdose on weed?
My cousin overdosed on weed.
He smoked a joint too long, he burned his damn fingers.
Okay, that's the kind of thing you should be saying.
My cousin got addicted to weed.
Don't talk about some French dressing shit.
He got stuck in a traveling sex circus, sucking his own dick, trying to pay for a gram of
a strain called Snoop Dogg's ass.
Right?
That's what happened to him.
Yeah.
Yep.
And then he fucking came in his own mouth, got himself pregnant.
Do you think that's funny?
A little bit.
You think, oh, that's fucking funny.
My cousin got himself pregnant by coming in his mouth and had an ass child.
You think that's really funny?
And guess what?
Godfather I shouldn't be making fun. Yeah
Yeah, the bod between godfathers and
God between a god son. That's not what I said bond. I said bond
Why are you so interested in Caleb's godson's no no
- Okay.
- Nothing high about that.
- Yo, anyway.
- That's low.
- Even for you.
- Imagine a damn circus where everyone's smoking weed.
The animals wouldn't even jump through the hoops.
They'd just be laying there like,
damn man, I want some snacks.
- Man, do you imagine at the zoo or the circus?
- Yeah, here we have a gorilla playing Xbox.
- You're at the circus and the animals get high
and then they accidentally find a box of animal crackers.
- Oh no.
- Oh my God, dude.
- Imagine the crisis they would have.
- That's like when I watch Modern Family
I'm like damn dude I'm also part of a modern family.
Damn, damn this kid looks like my dad.
I'm like damn, I'm like damn these two dads they look like tigers.
You ever get high and go to the aquarium?
No.
Back when I was a fucking drug addict I did.
Yeah?
What'd you see?
See I saw everything dude.
I looked at the jellyfish and right as the edible kicked in and I turned to Janet and
said we have to leave right now. We cannot be here. And then I don't know if I
talked about this, I was like I left, it was the first time I had eaten an edible in
like years and I left the aquarium and there was like they had like
animatronic dinosaurs set up in the exit that like screamed at you. One of the worst days
of my entire life dude. I'm not kidding. I've been there. That was like my childhood
like aquarium like I went to it all the time I go there one time high and
there's a traveling exhibition where as you leave the place you finally get out
of the fucking dark evil jellyfish room yeah velociraptor jumps at you and
screams damn you know how to keep a stoner out of your house dude you
put a mirror on the door he'll get confused and scared and run away yeah he's
He's gonna do his fighter fuck response on the mirror.
Exactly.
You put a two-way mirror, and you start screaming.
Two-way mirror?
Uh-huh.
Mirrors are always two-ways.
Yeah, front, yeah.
Yeah, up and down.
Front and back.
It's so fucked up that that can be called a two-way mirror or a one-way mirror, and
it means the same thing, right?
Yeah, I never- That's a high thought that I had before.
There has to be a correct one, right?
God, can you imagine a three-way mirror?
Yo.
I can't stop imagining a three-way mirror.
Ooh!
Oh my God.
Yep, me, you, and your brother.
Yeah, me, me, and another me.
And we're all doing funny things in the mirror.
Yep.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I haven't smoked weed in a very long time.
Me neither.
Not since I threw up on my bed.
Yeah, I have.
I smoke weed pretty much every night.
I don't.
Oh, that's why you're like that, huh?
Dude, I'm high as hell all the time.
I hate you, you fucking druggie.
My brain basically looks like a bong at this point.
- Are you having a very smoky 4/20 today, Cameron?
- Oh, absolutely, dude.
I walked around.
- Dude, smoke weed on camera!
Bro!
- If you're such a fucking pothead,
how about smoke weed on camera?
- No, no.
- Yeah, come on!
It'll be the first.
It'll be the first time anyone's done that.
- Getting Cameron--
- Getting high, uh-huh.
- No.
- Getting Cameron-- - No, I'll start crying.
- Getting-- - Don't make me do it.
- It's funny that all three of us have just--
- Oh, we can't smoke weed.
- I just can't do it, dude.
- I just like, something that was
something I'd rather we think of.
- 13 year olds will smoke weed and then win a million dollars
in a Fortnite tournament.
- Oh yeah.
- And we are three grown men who can't smoke weed
unless it is twilight.
- It's fucking evil.
I can't smoke, I only smoke weed at night
because it gives me the worst psychosis of my life.
And I think that the matrix is real, but it's red.
(laughing)
- It's red, red numbers.
That's terrifying, dude.
- Yeah, oh my God. - It's so scary.
- Evil matrix.
- It's so fucked up. - Evil matrix?
I can't even imagine.
I would try to do it every night because otherwise I'll lie awake and think, "Damn, what if the
Matrix was red?"
And it won't scare me, but it will intrigue me.
It's crazy how many times I smoked.
I used to take Adderall for my ADHD and I would just smoke weed and just have the worst time
of my life.
I was like, "I just don't understand why I can't smoke weed."
Dude, when I was on Adderall, that was the only time I could smoke weed.
Once I stopped taking Adderall, we're opposite.
I can't smoke weed ever.
I don't think, I think there's something in my brain.
I've tried taking Adderall and then smoking weed and then I'm just normal again.
It's like one of the most disappointing things.
Yeah, I can't, I can't smoke weed for shit.
I suck at it.
Yeah, well that's because you're not using the right formulas.
I think I could smoke CBD and get like high from it.
Yeah, yeah, no that's a, I think plenty of people smoke CBD and think they're high.
Yeah.
I was really hoping that that would like work for me just because I'm like such a
Like a lightweight when it comes to any drugs like that
I could just take CBD and like it would put me to sleep or fuck me up or something
I wouldn't like spend money on weed and shit, but it just didn't do anything
And so it's like damn people are so the people who think this stuff works are such a loser
Yeah, I can't believe all these kids cancer lying, dude
They clearly are I know you ain't getting high you fucking st. Jude's ass little pussy
Fucking smokes him real real drug. Yeah, they wouldn't get it. They don't know tell you what'll help cigarettes calm you down a little bit
Yeah, you got cancer now just fucking speed. Yeah. I mean what honestly if you're gonna if you have cancer
Why not smokes it can't make it worse. Well if you it depends on what kind of cancer you have no
It doesn't it doesn't depend like a tumor on your malignant tumor on your leg start smoking cigarettes. Yeah
You look sick. I miss cigarettes so much dude. I miss like dude
I miss taking like my my fucking my Adderall for my ADD and then smoking like three cigarettes by 8 a.m
Yeah, and just like when I first moved in New York
I keep leaving the classroom and I come back just reeking of cigarettes just like yep. Yep
Yeah, that was that sorry. I just took a really insane smelling shit and it just yeah fucking cover
Oh, yeah the body I fell in a toilet and I had to clean it off
I don't miss having like a yellow finger. You got a yellow finger? I smoked so much that my finger changed color.
That I can do it. You get the stains, right? Yeah, the stained finger. That's why I wear motorcycle gloves. It also adds to how cool I look.
That's what, uh... I wear oven mitts, dude, when I'm smoking weed so I don't get green all over my hands.
Step outside the bar, put on my fucking, my oven mitts and my apron, just to not arouse suspicion from the cops.
That's what the guy who played Grand Moff Tarkin would do. He would, on set, he would wear gloves.
That's also what the guy who played Grand Theft Auto would do, that's me.
Uh-huh.
Smoking cigarettes in a basement, playing GTA 3.
Oh my god, dude. How cool can you get?
Oh my god, the best thing ever.
The best fucking thing ever, smoking cigarettes and playing Grand Theft Auto,
pretending I'm smoking in a car.
Yep.
Getting used to smoking, like, shitty cheap cigarettes,
and then somebody hands you two Marlboro Reds,
and then you're on your roof trying to kill yourself.
Yeah, and you're throwing up, 'cause, like, it's too strong.
You're like what the f-- that is not a tobacco in that.
I don't know if it's local to New Hampshire or if it's like Circle K's like brand of like
cheap cigarettes but there's a cigarette company called Traffic Cigarettes which is one of
the most disgusting cigarette names I've ever heard.
Traffic?
I smoked one pack of Marlboro Reds and I was honestly convinced there was like mayonnaise
in them.
Yeah, oh for sure.
You should this is I feel insane right now. Mm-hmm. I used to smoke dude. I smoked camel blue
So much I would go through like a pack a day
Wow, you're gonna die. Oh, I'm yeah, I'm totally gonna get lung cancer or something
I can't I can't believe I can like walk in like oh, no, I get I get winded pretty easy. Don't you skateboard everywhere? Yeah
Yeah, you can't walk
Yeah, dude, that's that's the fat man's wheelchair. Yeah
Yeah
I saw Pat the other day for my birthday were before it wasn't fat which means it either me or cam has to step it up
Mm-hmm get fucking fatty. Yeah. Yeah. What are you gonna do now? I don't know what the show is anymore
Uh-huh. You're gonna have to dig at me really personally
Bringing up old relationships and shit. I'm like, huh you bet you wish you were fat now
Yeah, this is gonna be a big wake up call for the fans.
It's so fucking funny how we just called you fat.
We just called you fat over and over because we thought it was funny to do and you were
like never even that fat to begin with.
And then all the fans are like, "I see a picture of you."
What have they been talking about?
I was I mean I did find a picture of me from like December and I was pretty round.
I'm gonna start doing edits on every photo that you post.
Yeah, you're gonna like put me through the fat filter seven times on FaceApp.
Yeah, fatty.
Yeah.
Fucking fat ass.
That's right.
Wink.
It was really funny like you seeing me on your birthday and you're just like oh you're
so skinny now.
It was sad.
It was honestly it was heartbreaking dude.
It was like seeing somebody burn a pile of money in front of me.
That's what it fucking felt like.
I was like, "Who am I?
What do-- what am I now?"
Yeah.
I'm not-- this sucks, dude.
It's awful.
I'll feel it.
I ruined the whole show.
I know, dude.
You fucking destroyed everything.
Caleb, you have to grow some hair now, dude.
Yeah.
Why?
Yeah, I know.
Caleb, I'm making fun of you for being bald.
Ugh, dude, I don't want that.
You don't want to grow hair?
i'm losing my hair
i'm losing my hair pretty quick
you know what, i don't want to grow any hair
i actually like being bald
dude bald is sick, i'm insanely aerodynamic
i'm a better swimmer than you
if you grow some hair people will stop looking down at the ground
and confusing you with a nickel
*laughter*
dude if you grow some hair back
people are gonna stop thinking you're a nickel
start thinking you're a penny yeah I'm not that small it would be funny to get
Caleb like have you seen those like Instagram videos where like the guys get
like fitted for two pays yeah it's also always a black guy so I just know I
never not no one's we have very different explore pages there are two
all of my that are exactly the same but one is has underscore white at the end
no but I have there's like the the the toupees for white guys suck dude yeah
ones the ones for black guys they've perfected it it's like it's it's
immaculate and it's amazing and you don't and they just stay on forever you
don't even have to take them off oh yeah have you seen like them like pulling like
the you might see me pull up with an afro pretty soon yeah yeah I don't get
somebody why if I get somebody to agree to do it and give me a clown afro you're
rainbow clown afro yeah but then I'm still doing blackface cut it because of
the the zebra for Madagascar come on man what dude it's played by Chris Rock I
thought I was played by a zebra yeah I think you did fucking immersion for me
sorry god damn it you're gonna tell me the fucking penguins aren't spies um no
no I have nothing to tell you actually oh thank God yeah thank God I don't think I
could have actually I will tell you unless you eat 12 doughnuts in front of
me right now yeah you're trying to yourself before and after. You're trying to become a gainer
or yeah trying to make me become a gainer again yeah I'm gonna start making
plans with you and be like yeah there's like an amazing bowl of lard down the street from you.
It's insane dude yeah hey man do you want to do you want to like
sit down all day with me do you want to sit down and not move for a few weeks
All right Pat new day new lobster spot, let's go. Oh fuck dude. You could do bring your bib
Oh my god, if you were buying me lobster every day like baked stuff lobster and like
Patrons the fucking
Just so insanely fat it's been an $80 a day on lobster breakfast
Drinking anymore. You can't even fucking use the cheat code. I know do we got to make up these calories somewhere. Yeah. Yeah, I
Need to get you a job as an ice cream tester
That'll be my next move.
Yeah.
I'm gonna start setting you up on dates with scientists who are trying to create the biggest
fattest man in the world.
Those aren't scientists, those are just like feeders and gainers.
They're called heroes.
It would be so sick if there was like a job like that, like an ice cream tester job where
like it pays really well and you get to eat ice cream all day and everyone's like, "Well,
what's the downside?"
It's like, "Oh, by the end of the year working there, you're gonna be insanely fat."
Can you imagine like if your job was was
Ice cream taste you spend all day tasting ice cream you get home and your wife or husband asked for oral sex
Can you imagine how disgusting that must be?
You've been tasting fucking pecan
cream
Yeah
Rainbow sherbert all day was amazing flavors, and they're just tasting a fucking salty like butthole. Yeah
That's gotta be an awful life just ruin everything for you fuck. Mm-hmm. Yeah, you'd never
Yeah, the ice cream tester
Unless they come with pussy flavored ice
The ice cream tester factory actually just shut down after a disgruntled employee got brain freeze and shut the place up
Yeah, they cut his brain open afterwards and to prove, you know, we always suspected that there was long-term effects of brain freeze
But then Will Smith cut him open and saw that he had
Sure signs of brain freeze. An ice cube stuck in the cerebellum. Yeah, there's an ice cube in his hippocampus
It actually led to him being extremely violent. Mm-hmm
That's why you freaking smoke weed instead of eating ice cream. Yep, no negative effects
But when you smoke weed you want to eat some ice cream
Not me dude. Hey, dude. Yeah. No, I go for pretzels and chips, baby. When I see your salt terrifies me is that I
Know I don't think I've eaten something after smoking weed in years. It's the only way I can get myself to eat anything
I smoked I when I smoked weed I
ate pretzel or peanut M&Ms and
Those are like those are the perfect high food
I I ate too many of them and I thought I could taste the chemicals in the like the dye
Like I was sitting there, and I was like yeah, these are starting to taste like paint
Closing your eyes and being able to tell what color they are
And then spitting into your hand and being like yep, it's brown
It's crazy how stale the peanuts are in peanut M&Ms
No, they're not stay delicious. They're delicious. Oh, no. They're so good because I mean they're covered in like they're perfectly preserved by chocolate
What are you fucking talking about?
They just grow like that.
They grow them and they put a seed into the middle of the M&M and a single peanut grows.
Yeah, it grows out.
Yeah.
Dude, they only recently started removing the shells from the peanut M&Ms.
They used to have shells inside.
Yeah.
It used to be.
How about this?
Candy, chocolate, shell, nut.
How about a pistachio M&M?
That would never work.
You bite into it, fucking, you eat all the chocolate layer, you let the chocolate melt
in your mouth and then you crack open delicious pistachio.
So there should be more foods that you have to eat, take out of your mouth, like manipulate
in some way and then put back in.
Why stop there doing meatball M&M?
Yeah, exactly.
Little mini miniature kind of like Ikea style meatball with gravy and then the chocolate.
I want an egg yolk in there, dude.
I want a hard boiled egg yolk in the middle of my M&M.
Oh, that'd be pretty good.
Nice chalky texture.
That'll just make you appreciate the chocolate even more.
The smell that fills the room when you bite into one.
Oh, it's just gorgeous.
Chocolate and eggs.
Just an absolutely gorgeous smell.
The ultimate stoner snack.
Yeah, dude, protein M&M's with egg yolk inside.
We can get a couple of people on that.
It's a pretty good idea.
Yeah, I believe it.
I'm gonna get my guys on that, my M&M guys.
I know a couple people who work at the M&M factory.
Yeah, which one, M or M?
I know Marshall.
I don't know Mathers.
Yeah.
I know the orange M&M. Yeah. That guy, Jesus Christ. What about him? I mean, you can't
even hang out with him. What's his problem? He has an M&M. You can't even hang out with
him without him freaking the fuck out. What does that mean? Have you met him? No, no,
but I assume you're talking about a real guy right now, so what does it mean he
freaks out every time you know him? The orange M&M? What does that mean he freaks out? God,
that guy I mean he's he's so nervous he's nervous all the time what does he have
to be nervous about he's a millionaire people can do it oh I just I yeah I just
like we're gonna eat I'm on I'm on I'm on chocolate dot fandom calm on the
orange M&M page and I'm reading about him he's actually been through some shit
dude yeah yeah listen to this that was originally a crispy M&M and he was
always used to being and he always used to be scared of being eaten because he
thought he was the tastiest flavor. Orange doesn't really trust anyone, especially when
Red and Yellow licked him in one of his ads. He's always very scared and worried about what
will happen to him.
"He sounds like Drake."
"Yeah. He's a lot like Drake in that they hang out in the same circles."
"Yeah, and he's nervous because he knows he's the best, dude."
"Yeah. People are plotting on his downfall constantly."
"Eventually, Krispy M&M's were wiped out from the USA and he no longer advertised Krispy
I'll look later. However, he met pretzel guy who made things worse for him
This guy's I mean, this is horrific punished Eminem. This is a great wiki
Yeah, recent wiki activity hot fudge
Cadbury mini let's just go through fuck this other list. Let's go through the chocolate wiki. This won't even come on
20 this is a 420 chocolate special. These are all they're all all these pages are made by someone named Luigi fan 100
Oh wow.
What's he doing on the chocolate fandom page?
Here's a category on the chocolate wiki, "annoying characteristic"
and it's only orange M&M and M&M characters are the only two.
He's the annoying orange.
Oh, because it... whoa!
Yeah, do I have to spell it out for you, you fucking idiot?
Hey, fuck off!
You fat... ah, that's it.
Yeah, that's right.
Ah, fuck. You fat... no, that's not...
huge now. No, I do. I'm on the I'm on the page for hot hot chocolate right now. Do
you guys want to you guys worry about hot chocolate? Yes, hot chocolate is a warm
chocolate drink as implied by the name. It is a common beverage in the US. It is
useful to drink it during the winter season. The reason is because it gives
your body heat. You can also drink it during other seasons, but it is usually
it is mostly usually popular in the winter. Juvia went on a date the other
day like to go get coffee with a girl and he ordered a hot chocolate and we're
just talking about how alpha dog that is yeah to roll up and just be like yeah
yeah whatever she wants in me I'll have a hot chocolate. Can I get warm milk please?
Please can I get an apple juice and then whatever the lady will have. Damn.
just a cake pop for me yeah tradition most people drink hot chocolate on cold
snowy days it is traditional to drink on Christmas and then in parentheses Hanukkah
oh no the fireplace just just one pair but it has it as if Hanukkah is another
word for Christmas it is traditional drink on Christmas Hanukkah near the
fireplace. Successfully doing this will help you get warm.
True. Successfully drinking hot chocolate. Did you read the history here?
Just open the hot chocolate page. Did you read the history? No, but I knew this
already. I thought you did too. Let me guess. Somebody at the milk factory, some guy
brought a lunch chocolate sandwich and he dropped it in the milk. No. And then it
It was a hot day. It was in Arizona. It was in Mumbai.
I found a list on the wiki. The two headings that they have at the top of the wiki are
"chocolate" and "events." Under "events," the three different options are "Easter,"
festivals and movies movies and it's a list of movies with chocolate featured
number one Charlie and the Chocolate Factory from 2005 number two Willy Wonka
and the Chocolate Factory from 1971 number three Matilda from 1996 number
four chocolate from 2000 and number five and number five goo cream egg are we
just not gonna talk about dumb and dumber right are we just gonna ignore dumb and
dumber right now dumb and dumber or the chocolate scene in the bathroom?
whichever one it was yeah the Bob Saget box in the bathroom. We're just gonna pretend it didn't happen?
shit yeah is that we're gonna do we're gonna pretend that wasn't a seminal
chocolate movie oh here's a here's a page here Cadbury mini eggs I know Ron
shout out to Ron he was mad at us when we were talking about egg combos we
didn't mention Ron White yeah Ron White our close personal friend was mad we
didn't mention Cadbury mini eggs as an egg combo. I don't even know what a combo is.
We talked about it last episode. I don't remember that. Bacon and eggs. Yeah.
Huevos and rancheros. Uh-huh. I mean may I do I need to go any further? I mean egg M&M we did that.
Egg M&M that's another one. Egg and... Egg and eggs plant. Egg and egg salad. Uh-huh.
Yeah, that's a good one
Yeah, Cadbury
Cadbury mini eggs here. I don't think I've ever had a Cadbury egg. Why would you fucking eat that eat a Cadbury egg, dude?
Yeah, I'm not that's like it's like made for Swedish pedophiles. That's not a that's not for like normal American consumption
Just like it's like the sweetest thing in the world. There's barely any chocolate. It is it's literally a goo
The fucking you know it's good the Kinder eggs the ones with toys inside. Oh, yeah, the ones that are designed to kill kids
Yeah, those are banned in the u.s.. You know they are anymore. They were yeah, they like yeah, they change they well
I think there's like a different change them now though. Yeah, the old kids like eggs are still banned
I think yeah, like there's like they have something else right now
Yeah
The old ones where it was literally just chocolate and then just like a toy that could easily break apart into tiny plastic pieces
Like if you bite it like just like the worst design of all time. Yeah, I remember wonderful stupid
I don't know. The Wonder Ball? No. Is that a kind of ball? It was a ball full of like
I'm wondering where your balls are. It's a chocolate ball full of Smarties. See
that's that's at least two edible things. The Kinder Eggs they put like a
transformer that turns into a razor blade inside of the egg. Exactly dude.
Yeah go ahead go fucking wild dude. Yeah. It's like making a fucking like
like Darth Vader helmet that just has a plastic bag inside yeah they should put
like cigarettes they should have to put photos of kids with toy Tonka trucks
stuck in their throat on the front of the kid like a whole surprise egg.
yeah exactly that that should if they do that then it should be legal everywhere
mm-hmm everybody should be able to get them this should be free too oh damn
yeah the Nestle Nestle's Wonderball and it had Buzz Lightyear on the cover damn
but now they have Wonderball with prize hold up with prize huh what they have
the Mario the Super Mario Wonderball plus prize and it's a token of Bowser jr.
they still put a carton on a cartoon a toy inside of the cereal no I don't
think so do you fucking I talked about it before but they had DVDs and cereal
yeah you have talked about that yeah yeah yeah I did talk about that I got
Muppets take Manhattan on that. That's like I feel like the only reason anybody
would ever buy like like plain checks is because they have like a Girls Gone Wild DVD.
Right? Your dad's at the store is like "and we'll take ten boxes of checks."
Yeah just plain checks. You don't even want the maple maple syrup. Nope.
Just a plain normal checks. And we're gonna get that Grape Nuts box with the Bumfights DVD.
I'll take the greatness.
Guys, I have...
I...
There's a...
Okay, so, the admin of the
chocolate wiki, LuigiFan100,
only admin on this,
only editor.
He has a blog
that's attached to the chocolate wiki.
The most recent post
is from September 11th,
2015,
and the title of the blog post is
On this day
I'd like to read it to you
Hello there everyone. This is one of the first blog posts not about chocolate today marks the day known as 9/11
Today we acknowledge 9/11 a very unfortunate day in history for america
This was the day that the twin towers fell killing
277 innocent people who were taken too soon, then there's a lot of statistics and
Then the last the last paragraph my personal thoughts are with those who are gone and their families and us at the chocolate wiki
Thank you all for your service
Whether you are a paramedic firefighter police officer security guard or a pilot I and chocolate wiki
Thank you for being brave on that day. Oh my god
That's so nice. I
I love the chocolate wiki. There's a comment on that blog post from Fudgy Guy.
It just says "thanks first responders." Fudgy Guy. Oh my god. Here's what I'll say. Everything
happens for a reason. Yep. What do you mean? I don't know. But if I was a news anchor on September
11, 2001, I probably would have said that live on CNN. Why would you say that? And speaking of
Speaking of these horrible attacks, you know, I just like to quell everyone's fears by saying
everything happens for a reason.
And you need to trust God's plan.
That's literally, that's the only, there's two other blog posts and they're both just
like "Hi everybody, welcome to the wiki."
That's the only, that's the only not a horrible one.
Seems like zero of these are about chocolate.
Yeah.
God damn, dude.
Crackle?
Here's, okay, I'm in the article for Crackle, so let me just read this first paragraph for
you.
The fucking, the streaming service?
No, no, not the streaming service.
guy's not a comedians in cars fan? Mm-hmm. Comedians in cars getting chocolate I'd
love to see that. Wow. Dude I want to get strung out. Can we maybe make that
happen? Yeah I would love to make that happen.
Wait this is wait my plan to get Patrick fat again. Hey Pat can you come back for
another episode of the fans just love you on comedians in cars getting
chocolate could you come back today we're going to the lint factory all right
that's you have been uninvited that was my chocolates that was my chocolate
sound oh don't have a chocolate sound oh here's a okay so the crackle crackle
contains crisp rice and is similar to the competing crunch bar made by Nestle
www www www www www www www www www www www www www www www www www
generally also had almond in its formula peanuts were then added in 1939 but both
almonds and peanuts were removed in 1941 now I'm on the I'm on the community page
for the chocolate wiki which is I guess like kind of like a forum a little yeah
Yeah, chocolate form.
And it's very nice.
People say, "Wow, I just found out this wiki exists."
And I have to say, "Wow, I'm literally obsessed with chocolate, so I'm so glad I found this."
Somebody else posted a post titled "Chocolate, not chocolate," where they're holding a piece
of chocolate and there's another picture of them holding a rock.
Damn.
Don't make those up.
I love, yeah.
I love this page.
I love this wiki.
It's so nice.
Introduction.
Hi, I'm new to the new and I'm definitely a chocolate lover 24/7.
I love milk chocolate, semi-sweet chocolate, white chocolate, and dark chocolate.
Okay my most favorite chocolate candies are Hershey's chocolate bars, Lint, Dove
chocolate, M&M's but they wrote manned M's like they wrote M and as one word and
M&M's, Rocha Ferrero, Gilardi chocolate, Nestle Crunch, Butterfingers, Kit Kat and
last but not least York peppermint patties.
Ooh I felt like a York peppermint patty the other day did I tell you about this?
Did you brush your teeth for the first time?
No.
Oh come on.
No I covered myself in tiger balm.
I was really sore. I was going skating and I was really sore and I like forgot how much
it spreads. I put it on my lower back and like my thighs and I like skated to the train so
I started sweating and like it like moved to my asshole and I was just sitting on the
train just like squirming because I just had tiger balm all over my asshole.
You're squirting dude. Don't lie to me.
I want you in my apartment squirming.
Don't.
To Matt.
Yeah.
tonight bring the bomb out on you this is a bad dude all right i'm done with that i'm trying to
tell you about your boy roy one two three dude i'm gonna get all up in your peppermint patty
don't i'm gonna put my mint in your chocolate hole i'm gonna suck your dick with ice there
wait there's one more post from the community page um it's just a ayo chocolate fandom check
so anyways anywhere in the hershey's world
as a a_t_r_ here's a here's a comment here's a comment from your boy roy one
two three
it says these nuts
come on for the come on for
come on roy what i just thought
i will say this is a nice only fell for that one so hard
you literally said i love
you did say he's not sell out
like i you
you not get me
yeah you got you know i was not a you've got a no i'm gonna get any new right now
you're not gonna get you heard of both of these nuts
both of what
this legna
uh... you guys don't you know but what
have you read that new york times article the leg must take my
have you seen that
now have you read that
now do you know what it is
now looking my ass my balls and talking to me
fucking idiot
fat now
and
the
and you guys are to joe mom is these both of us
uh... yeah actually i'm not a little dog with the haha
the aviary of our government so that we certainly have a lot of my job on the
results
have you guys heard of both of my both these joes those mops have you heard of both of my nuts
have you seen my two nuts have you seen both of my nuts trying to do it yeah uh have you seen
both those joes for to be jerbers oh you're not getting me you're not getting me you're like
oh no i'm not listen i know what's happening here and i am not gonna bite you're not getting me
again don't know how long you know me
yeah did when when Ron Paul had his stroke
didn't is like webcam also glitch just
remembering that video that you know he
has a fucking work bathroom to watch that
video
got a jack off oh man that was a stroke
you a stroke oh my god you know you can around Paul do this guy this this kid
loves weed yeah yeah probably why he fucking started stroking out on live
television Ron Paul's Ron Paul love smoking yeah oh I know that boy was too
high mm-hmm oh my god he's on that homegrown sticky
icky it's funny to talk about that like months after it I had that strokey oaky
ooh yeah that smoky strokey that is that's something that should come back
into the public consciousness that was a great video yeah things things go out
too quick yes I mean something's just something's crazy way too slow but yeah
Ron Paul's true that knees like drunk crunk should be our like Carol Baskin
yeah crunk should totally be bad cuz I'm crunk I'm crunk I feel like you guys
might be - dude it once once punk started going crunk that ruined it dude yeah
yeah I mean they went they went crunk like 15 times I just yeah you could say
Yeah, yeah, I just want to be those I just want to crunk back okay, cuz crunk was a good drug-free
Expression
Outlet for you know kids like me. Yeah kids you have a big fat ass
Kids you love jeans big hat huge hoodie mm-hmm
Have you guys I'm just I'm clicking random page a bunch on
On this wiki. I'm on you guys have you guys heard of the candy Maltesers?
Yeah, I have sounds like a slur doesn't it
You may be you may be skinny on the outside
But tell you what I crack you open you got a caramel core big guy
What the fuck hold on I'm linking you this page, okay, uh-huh
This is the page for white chocolate maltesers. I want you to look at the bottom picture here
I'll post a screenshot of this picture with the caption with the episode because the caption for this picture is
giant white maltesers along with the giant milk ones and giant dark ones with the giant woman
what the [ __ ] is that the file name the file name is giantess remix it's there's a tiny guy
photoshopped on her hand who is this woman somebody somebody on the chocolate wiki has
a giantess fetish dude i don't think it goes that deep look at there's a [ __ ] tiny guy
- Well, that's just to show how big they are.
- The file name is giantist-remix.jpg.
- I don't like this at all.
I hate when a woman is taller than me.
I was in Walgreens the other day, I pissed off.
I was like, "Come on, how are you 5'6" right now?"
Their only contribution, I'm looking at their user page,
their only contribution is to Maltesers.
- No, they edited other stuff, I'm looking at it.
They edited hot fudge, oh no wait that's recent wiki activity.
I just took off my pants because I have to pee so bad.
Can I see?
What?
Yeah sure.
Lower the camera.
Woah!
Okay.
You thought I was faking it?
Yeah.
Come on dude, who do you think I am?
I have to pee so bad, it's like Thanksgiving dinner.
You can go pee dude.
There's still 15 minutes left.
And then can we talk about marijuana again?
Yeah sure.
Okay.
Well, we're talking about the food you eat.
We're talking about candy.
Yeah.
Three edits.
Oh, yeah, they did Maltesers and White Chocolate Maltesers.
Yeah, they...
Oh, yeah, the caption on the Maltesers page, it's the same picture, but the caption this time is,
"A giantess version of a woman eating Maltesers. A giant woman was eating her giant Maltesers along with giant white ones and giant dark ones."
What the fuck is that?
It's fucking
That's so weak cuz it's just like a picture of somebody's like friend that they photoshopped yeah
That's
Are these wait are these pictures all on the huh where how can I see what do you look at?
There's a picture of
Thanos on this wiki somewhere, but I can't figure out how to see what page it's on
there's a gif of a
Some I think it's a final fight character. I don't know yeah, see like what's
What is why there's a pepe tomato? Yeah? There's a dr. Phil Eminem
Well that makes sense that makes at least on the on here. Yeah, yeah
Dude, this wiki sick. This is the coolest wiki ever found. I'm gonna become a regular contributor. Oh
Oh, you should.
I found a thing called Jost-Lewis.
A page called Jost-Lewis.
Diet soda fan likes to post pictures of themselves holding the candies.
[Laughter]
Hershey's Air Delight. Oh, have you ever had that?
Hershey's Air Delight?
No, I don't know what that is.
Yeah, it was like in 2010 they had this candy.
- Yeah, it's a discontinued one,
but it's just they put a bunch of air
into the chocolate, into the candy bars.
- So is it like, kind of like a crunch bar-ish?
Or like, let's put a bunch of air in you.
- It's just like, it's not crispy at all.
It was just like airy chocolate.
Like, it was light like air when chewed on,
is what it says.
- Hey, you wanna go for a ride on my bicycle, pump?
- What?
- You wanna go for a ride on my bicycle, pump?
- What are you talking about?
- Do you wanna go on a bike ride?
bike pump ride. What are you saying? What the fuck are you saying? Do you want to sit on
my bicycle pump and I can blow you up like a balloon? Did you hit your head in the bathroom?
Hey Patrick, hey Patrick, I wanna, hey Patrick, can I blow you up like a balloon? What are
you guys, what the fuck is happening right now? Patrick, can I blow you up like a balloon?
So you're bacon? No! You can't blow me up like a balloon. I didn't say whatever, okay,
you know you didn't, first of all. I'm gonna, I'm gonna handcuff you with bacon and make
you eat yourself out or eat your way out oh come on yeah what the fuck is up come
on man are you serious Patrick saying that I didn't say that you say that
you're crazy and fat I'm no I'm not fuck you right all right we have to talk
about weed a little bit here right yeah yeah I mean we did for 20 minutes yeah
but I hand-picked these these lists much like a nugget of weed these
little is picked by a slave the list that you picked are the ones that I'd
looked at and thought weren't good enough.
So what did you just say?
No, but I'm looking at them right now.
What do you mean?
Hand...
What the fuck was that?
There's...
Marijuana is made by slaves.
That's why it's an immoral industry.
You don't know about this?
What?
Handpicked by slaves?
Ed, you know, that's fascinating because smoking marijuana is one of the only ways you can
emancipate yourself from mental slavery.
That sounded way worse than how you think it sounded in your head.
It sounded bad?
Yeah.
There are...
Slaves make your shoes, man.
You gotta stop saying slaves.
What is-- okay. Brave. Happy fellows. Braves. How about now? That's better.
They're brave. All right. Obviously you have some slave in your family that you
haven't disclosed and you don't want to talk about it but okay we'll move on and
we'll talk about weed. Are you happy now? Yeah. Okay. Which one are we doing? We should do
top 10 things marijuana can help you with. Okay. Right. I'm gonna do it fast. All right.
What time is it? Oh shit. Oh my god. Fuck dude. Hey, you know how it is when you're
high dude. You just fucking time flies when you're time high is when you're flying high.
Dude, last night I was smoking weed and lying down in bed. Next thing you know, I was asleep
and it was a morning and I was awake. That's like, oh, you're a, you're a damn time traveler.
Yeah. It's, it's cool. Smoke. When you smoke weed right before you go to bed, it helps you
time travel to when you wake up in the night and hear an airplane and think that your house
is being bombed and you're about to die.
Yep.
And sometimes you just time travel through the first Avengers movie too.
Yeah.
You just fucking don't remember a single scene.
Yep.
Saw it in theaters.
Who knows, man.
Brought a jar of peanut butter with me.
I can't.
Time traveling through this bag of pretzels to my destination is constipation.
That's right.
It's a little rhyme I just came up with.
That's a good rhyme. Thanks. You guys can use it too if you want. I might use that.
Okay. Yeah. Constipation, slave emancipation. No, I can't bring slaves up again.
Pat will get sad. Come on man, you've been talking about them too much. Who's them, huh?
Slaves. He said it! He said slaves. Book 'em boys. Yep, now you have to get fat or
or else we'll send that clip to your employers.
- Yeah, Pat, if you hate slaves so much--
- My employers, myself?
(laughing)
- No hates, come on.
- I mean, sounds like you kinda do.
- It's not true.
(laughing)
- Number one, school.
You know, in my experience, this is a lie.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Does not help you
with school.
- I tried to smoke weed before school once.
I got like, the smallest amount of weed I could
for like five bucks from somebody.
- Yeah.
- And then I smoked it the night before
and then tried to like smoke like the resin
out of like the, like the bubbler I made
out of a two liter soda bottle.
And I just went to school like kind of high.
- I will say I'm remembering a time
that I actually, I smoked weed in high school
and actually it helped me a lot.
But I did--
- It didn't help me at all 'cause I was still on Adderall.
- But I did, this might be important,
I did go to Freddie Wong's video game high school.
(laughter)
- That might have been why it helped me so much.
But I felt like, I mean it was like, it was like nothing.
- I guess that makes sense.
- Yeah.
- It could have been that.
- Dude, when I smoked weed in high school
it helped me so much with Pokemon Go.
- But do people still play Pokemon Go?
- People do.
- I'm sure they do.
That's, dude, that's one thing I miss about,
I haven't been taking like public transportation
'cause I don't gotta fucking work anymore, baby.
But yeah, all you guys who are listening,
you're gonna have to work forever I hate you you're almost like but just like
right it right thing that right in the bus and just like seeing the one person
on the bus who's like playing Pokemon go or writing just be like oh man you that's
the lamest person in the world right now dude I'm thinking 2020 I said I'm gonna
go until like 2018 playing Pokemon go in 2020 on the bus at like 7 a.m. yeah like
I probably I mean I have I have a few I got a few good a few thousand dollars
worth of Pokemon on Pokemon go it's true yeah I have a I was the I have a
squirter I have like a gold star and the on a few places in Boston really gold
star gym leader some fucking I don't remember easily motivated by gold stars
Yes. Why? Makes sense. No reason. None at all. I did go to Montessori school. Number two, cancer. I mean,
is this really... I mean, it doesn't... This is so fucking good to say. I don't think it helps you. It causes cancer. Are we
joking? Are we fucking making this up? Cancer? You think weed helps cancer? No, it doesn't.
No.
Are you living in an upside down world?
Yeah, it's a joke.
This is a joke entry.
I'm not even, I don't even want to, you know, I don't want to give this the time of day.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Insomnia.
True.
Very true.
Yeah, yeah, because it shuts down your thinking brain.
Exactly.
Make you, tell you what, lie down.
You lie down and you start thinking, damn, post offices really be crazy and your brain
is so embarrassed that it just instantly shuts down and you fall asleep.
Yeah, sitting there trying to understand a stamp and then you just fucking fall asleep.
Your brain just shuts down, just fucking breaks.
Wait, stamps are a kind of money?
What?
Whoa.
Just fall asleep.
I had to mail something the other day and I was like, I honestly, I had that thought.
I was like, what is it?
This is like a currency that just-
Dude, post offices are nuts.
They're like wild west shit.
Yeah.
It's so weird.
Dude, that post office in Brighton, you been to that one?
No.
If only there was a fucking one that didn't have to go stand in line at the post office.
Oh.
If only there was some kind of fucking...
Yeah, like stamps.
Like, every single time I need stamps.
Which is pretty much every day.
I have to walk my ass 50 miles down the street to go to the post office.
I have to stand in line.
Takes two or three hours.
God.
If only there was some kind of...
Like a website?
Dot com almost.
Yeah.
And only if there was a coffee that made me shit my pants.
Uh huh.
If only there was a guy who could play guitar.
Yeah, and he has two cats.
Yeah.
Yeah. He loves those cats. Oh well, guess that guy doesn't exist.
Mm-hmm. The perfect man. If he does, he's probably gonna die soon.
He's probably gonna kill himself pretty soon.
Number four, anxiety and depression. In my experience, Mike's weed greatly magnifies
these two things. Yeah, no. It gave me depression, dude. I was the most normal guy of all time until
I started smoking weed. The media's representation of marijuana does not handle the paranoia.
at all. They're in Snoop Dogg's pocket. Weed fucking turned me from like a like a New Balance
Pokemon nerd to Travis Bickle straight up.
They won't tell you about that and Bob Marley did. Dude I started smoking weed
immediately started losing my hair. Decided a mullet was the way to go. I did
I had the same path brother. Dude I was so high I was like you know what fixes balding?
a mullet. I had the same. I had a mullet for like a year. It's so fucking funny. It's so funny that yeah you smoke weed and you're like damn I should start wearing a size bigger of shirts and grow my hair out.
Yeah. That'll be sick dude. Oh my god dude my pants got huge.
Like if you if you introduced weed to an alien civilization that was like completely different from humans they would still start like growing their hair out and wearing like big tie-dye shirts and shit.
I think weed could be like a chemical weapon.
Yeah.
I think it's possible that weed was dropped on us by the USSR, China, some odd years ago,
just to destroy us.
The weed that they're selling at dispensaries now, you don't think like the CIA is like
meddling with it at all?
No, they're too busy fucking protecting us from Islamic terrorist attacks.
You know what, you're right.
I was thinking about that and then I said it and I was like, man, I sound like a fucking
fool right now.
That's right, yeah.
Come on, are you an idiot, dude?
I guess I am in that moment.
There are CIA agents out there right now taking bullets for you and you're accusing them of
having anything to do with the drug trade?
Well they're taking bullets from me so I don't...
You need to stop fucking reading that People's History of the United States book.
Oh man, I fucking...
Stop reading it and re-reading it and re-re-reading it.
It's not good for you.
You can get high on Howard Zinn.
I gotta stop, I mean, Mark Fisher, you gotta get out of my head.
True.
There you go, he's a ghost of my life. Exactly. That's the damn truth
number five weight loss no
Let you know, what are you talking about?
You know, I'm looking this up and there's actually no way to lose weight, yeah, it's actually impossible
There's only way to doctors recommend that you should gain weight. Yeah, it says it. Oh my god
It says under 300 pounds is a horribly underweight
What yeah, is that oh no? I mean it guys I guess we all got a you know
I'm busy in the next couple weeks, but maybe Pat you get like a head start. We do like a gaming competition
You know okay, that's how you hit 300 pounds first. It might be a good idea
Here I'm gonna send you five cases of olive oil, and if okay just finish just replace water
There's water in olive oil, so you should be good right yes
So anytime you would reach for a water bottle or a lemonade maybe drink an olive oil instead
Can I still, can I just like combine the olive oil and the lemonade?
It kind of needs to be pure or else you're not going to get the kind of fat content that
we're looking for.
What about the sugar in the lemonade?
Wouldn't that help you gain?
So you can add a packet of lemon, like a crystal light to the olive oil.
Yeah, yeah.
And it won't float on top of the olive oil?
No, it mixes right in.
Yeah?
Yeah, it completely dissolves.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that might be a good move for you.
Number six, headaches.
Headaches, not true.
Tell you what, you get a headache, find your fucking
find your child or your wife, or your
child wife smoking weed, that'll give you a headache.
Yeah. Whoa.
Hey now. Yeah, it will.
Hey now. Number seven, epilepsy.
Nope.
No, it does the opposite.
Diabetes. What are you fucking talking about?
You fucking
killing a bag of yogurt
pretzels after smoking weed, that'll give you
diabetes. Number 9, they got creativity and they got that Bill Hicks quote, the one from
the Tool song. And the thing about that is like the creativity thing is like, weed doesn't
make you creative. They used to think it did because the weed they were smoking back in
the fucking 70s or whatever, it has the same effect as if you sit down and just imagine
something. Like it's just made of dirt. It's just nothing dude. You get high and you're
You get higher off the fluoride in your water than they got off of fucking weed in the 70s exactly
It's crazy how many things were created on 70s weed - yeah, I know
Do those people were just they were just weird like they were just guys who like to think that yeah
This is like before they did a minimum wage job. Yeah guys were were hailed as geniuses
That's the thing about it though. They would write all these songs that were just euphemisms for weed, and it's just like
Like about like a wizard or something. Yeah, dude, Chocolate Rain.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
One of the biggest drug addict anthems in the world.
It's fucking horrific.
No, like Sweet Leaf by Black Sabbath.
Yeah. It even rhymes. Wheat Leaf.
Oh my god. Yeah.
Bet you never thought about that, dude.
Wow. Ozzy Osbourne.
That's a dark person.
He ate a bat. That guy got the munchies so bad he ate a fucking bat.
Yeah, is this where the damn coronavirus came from?
Is this guy Ozzy Osbourne?
Hey now, hey now, come on.
Yeah, hey, hey, how about you lay off the bats for a couple years, give us some chance to
recover, Ozzy?
How about you fucking tell your daughter to shut up too while you're at it?
Yeah, Kelly?
Fucking stupid bitch.
Remember that clip of her on The View?
Yeah, and hey, can you tell your brother Norman to take off that green costume and stop throwing
fireballs everywhere?
Yeah, that's a very fair point, dude.
Oh my god, I'm so sick of his bro- Ozzy's brother Norman.
So true. I'd be mad too- by the way I'd be mad too if the media started calling me the
Green Goblin.
After I fucking spent millions of dollars building this cool Iron Man suit.
Just call me Iron Man, dude. Call me the Green Iron.
Yeah, Iron Green Man. Green was just the cheapest color of metal.
Mr. Green! Yeah, why do I- I mean, Green doesn't even have to factor- you don't call Spider-Man
red
spider. No. Stupid.
You don't call Captain America red white and blue
Exactly. Keep going. Yeah, keep going. Yeah, you don't call you don't call the whole
Panther now, I'm that's that makes perfect sense. Actually, I don't call the white tie. Ah, fuck. Yeah, you don't call black man -
You don't call
Green air. No, no green land. No. All right. Well
Red red hulk red hulk. No. No, okay. Don't call reverse flash yellow flash true
That's a good one. We finally got another one. Yeah, you know Batman.
Well, Black Man.
You're right. Don't call him that. That's a very good point.
All right, just stay off the pot. Please don't smoke weed.
Please. I know that you're excited because it's your
And I know you stoners, you're gonna be smoking.
You're gonna be, you know, we're recording this today on 4/20,
but I know you're gonna be smoking tomorrow because you love to be late.
Yep, that's right
I'd also like to specify
And I'd like to I'd like to point out that there is such a thing in in
Rehabilitation centers as a lost cause and I think a lot of you might be that so please
Just do yourself a favor smoke yourself to death if you have to just fucking I don't want to deal with you anymore
where you are an absolute leech
on the public healthcare system
and you should be just demolished,
just turned into gravel.
- All right, one live show ticket left up there.
Thanks everybody.
- Oh wait, Thursday, I'm gonna be on Yabba still.
- Oh yeah, go listen to that.
- Yeah.
- Tomorrow. - Bye.
- Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]