You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Wow, dude.
- Wow.
- An original recipe, dude.
It's been way too long.
- Wow.
- Fuck, and I'm recording live
from the danger zone right now.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Which danger zone?
- North Carolina danger zone.
- Is that a danger zone?
- It is for me, dude.
You know why?
Why?
Because every time I walk down the street, I see a place that sells 50 pounds of kratom
for $10.
And I've never done kratom, but I'm getting close to it.
It's putting you in danger.
It's putting me in danger of trying kratom.
Yeah.
Dude, it's just hard.
They're throwing it at you here, dude.
Yeah.
Just like nonstop.
These big baggies of like sawdust that supposedly they're like, it's like heroin, dude.
It's free.
Just take it.
It's fine.
you take it and you've eaten that day, you throw up.
(laughing)
- Dude, it's amazing being in a place
that doesn't have legal weed,
'cause they're selling like that,
and they're selling this shit called Delta 8.
Have you ever heard of that?
- Oh, I've heard of Delta 8.
- Delta 8 is like, it's like not weed or some shit,
but everybody here thinks that
it's the best thing of all time.
- Yeah.
- I just, dude, I gotta get outta here, man.
It's a danger zone, bro.
- They were too lazy to even change the name of it
after it got leaked from a lab.
Yeah, we're not even gonna call this like Grungus or whatever.
Like Turbo Weed or something.
Kratom, Kava, Grungus, Fumble.
It's fucking terrible dude.
Yeah, Roku, 2B, Hulu.
Yeah, Roku, Amazon, Netflix.
On the Netflix pack dude.
But it's just like, I know that if I tried Kratom, you would never see me again.
Absolutely.
I would be like one of the 0.01% of people who just like do Kratom until they die.
Yeah, like fucking sprinkling over I'd be using like Parmesan cheese on like salads and shit. Yeah, it would not mean it's also it's like
That's maybe the the lamest way you could ever take a drug is in a is in powder like that
Yeah, you just like mix in and drink. Yeah, whatever. Yeah, it's not even like like you don't even snort it
Yeah, you don't know exactly. I mean injection. That's cool. Smoke. Yeah, that's cool. There's fire
Dude, kratom is like, you like put it in like orange juice.
Yeah, exactly.
And you're like, it's like fiber.
Yeah, what kind of a bear is that?
This is a supplement, dude.
But supposedly it'll make you really tired, which I guess is what drugs are about.
That's what people like.
Yeah.
But just everybody here is just fucking, dude.
And they're always, it's like the only thing that you overhear people talking about in public
is like Delta 8 and Kratom and Kava and about how it like cured their knee or whatever. I
used to have knee but then I had Kratom and it cured my knee. It's fucking terrible.
Yeah, that's a good Skyrim reference.
Yeah, yeah. You know how I am, dude. I'm a gamer.
Yeah.
But it's been nice in the danger zone. I have as hot as shit. There's the AC in my car is
broken in my Ford Focus. Tell you what, these fellas at Ford should have focused
on making better damn air conditioning unit. I know, that's right. You know what I'm saying? Absolutely. Which is, you know, sad. Ford was a great
company back in the day. But they lost their focus. American company. Ford used to,
Ford struck a chord in the market as far as cores go. But then they gave up.
they leveled down. Started making these dog shit cars. Exactly. No air conditioner and I'm just
out here sweating dude. Sweating. Dodging. Dodging Cratum. Dodging Cratum landmines left and right.
I wish it was Dodge instead of Ford. That's right. That's fucking right. Yep. Dodge and that's a real
American car brand. Absolutely. Ford here's the thing they don't tell you about Ford. All that
- Ram. - Grab that ram, dude.
- Grab the ram. - Grab the horns.
- Yeah.
- Take care of that thing, dude.
The Ford is nonsense, bro. - Ford, yeah.
Ford is like-- - Here's the thing, man.
Like, the first, Ford's like the first car, right?
- Yeah. - There's nothing
where the first one was the best one.
There's not a single thing where the first kind
of that thing was the best one.
- Let me think here.
What about-- - Books, Gutenberg Bible,
that thing sucks.
What about like, um, the Matrix?
What the fuck?
What?
You can't...
What the fuck?
A challenger has just appeared in the call, dude?
We're in the middle of recording the episode.
Not only that, he's...
Dude, ugh.
Are you recording your audio now?
I am right now.
Alright.
That's fine.
Do you guys like my new sunglasses?
No, dude.
I hate this, dude.
I was having...
I had so much planned, dude.
I was gonna...
What do you mean?
I was going to make an entire playboy featuring your whole family and now I can't, dude.
What?
Yeah, man.
I was going to make a sexy playboy about your family.
How far into recording are you guys?
About five minutes.
Oh, my bad.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
You hopped in.
I'm fine with it.
Yeah.
So, what do you think about Dodge and Ford?
So, what we're talking about-
Is that?
Okay.
a
Nord, but Dodge is more like a Mirage.
Is what
Oh, so it's like a rhyming thing?
No, like a Ford if you put it backwards is
"Droaf".
We were just playing around with different words.
We were doing wordplay.
A shavy, a shavy, uh, as good as gravy.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yep.
A ram, drive you can.
Whoa.
Drive you can.
drive you can. Mazda, let's go get some pasta. Yeah, that's right, head to the Olive Garden
in this Mazda, get some pasta. Exactly. Subaru, Olive Garden has some food for you. Toyota,
go to Olive Garden, get some soda. It's that easy, dude. Camry, go into Olive Garden, it's
one of my greatest mammaries.
Camry, I'm at Olive Garden, I'm angry.
I'm looking at these things here, I'm looking at Ford memes online.
Dude, Ford is a dog shit car, man.
Yeah.
Here's one, it's a picture of Forrest Gump.
It says, "Mom always said Fords are for gay men."
- What's the bottom text of it?
- What's the bottom text?
- The bottom text is Fords are for gay men.
- What's the never know what you're gonna get type thing?
Oh, okay, that's it.
So it says, "My mom always said Fords are for gay men."
That's the whole Forrest Gump format they came up with?
- Well, I mean, you have to give Forrest Gump
a little bit of, you know,
I mean, he is a mentally challenged man.
- Well, that's what I would have,
if I was gonna diss Ford with Forrest Gump,
would have said Ford is as mentally challenged as Forrest Gump is. Ford is
Gump. Ford is Gump yeah yeah I wouldn't have tried to you know also why am I
listening to Forrest Gump dude this guy's a moron. Hey come on he's not a
moron don't say moron about him. Why he's stupid. I never saw that movie. You
never saw Forrest Gump? No. I saw I don't think he was even confirmed he was he was mentally
challenge he's a run slightly above mentally challenged in the movie they
say they show like they show a graph they show a graph and then they're like
your son is here and it's like a little bit seen in that movie that is a scene
in that movie I don't think that's true it's true and then Sally Field fucks the
principal so he can go to normal school yeah I remember that not not challenge
school I was pretty cool dude that's it they should make more porn with that
exact scenario yeah with Forrest Gump involved yeah yeah you gotta fuck this
principal to get to Forrest Gump into school yeah yeah I mean that's a good
way to to get get more like non-sexual actors into the porn as you could have
like you know people who you know playing the person who has to get into
school maybe yeah that's a good point who doesn't have to be in the same room
as as the sex or whatever's going on but maybe just like an intro with a
different actor and then we can you know employ more actors who maybe have been
calling on hard times lately. What about a movie so in this same vein what
about like a movie where Rodney Dangerfield has to go back to college?
No he'd be too funny. Yeah? I'd kick him out of my class if I was a damn professor.
Yeah I would too. He'd be in there sweating up a storm getting everybody
wet and also making them laugh too hard. Yeah. Now, but if he was a professor, now that might
be a funny-ass class. It's really fucked up what they...
They teach a class on how to get respect or how to get no respect.
Yeah, it's really fucked up what they did to Rodney Dangerfield back then. Like, if I was
around him, I would have given him respect and then he wouldn't have, hey, wouldn't have
been so sad all the time. Yeah, he wouldn't have killed himself.
Also, what's this guy's, I mean, this guy was on The Tonight Show, like, once a week.
How much respect can one man have? What, do you want to be Mao Tse-Tung? Like, what is
he going for why is he still complaining he's it's weird another thing he looks
weird another thing he's old as dog crap oh yeah kill himself of course he didn't
kill himself do you don't kill yourself when you turn 80 I would you'd kill
yourself the second turn I would I till 80 if I was if it was an old-age thing
I don't know well if I was like 20 years of being old 20 years of just sucking
yeah I would do Rodney Dangerfield when he was good and ready he that was no that
was no man-made crime God committed that one God's and God's God yeah God was
like I'll take you to a place where you can finally get some respect that's
yeah that could bet and it was hell if he died nowadays that some some political
cartoonist would draw that like yeah Rodney Dangerfield holding hands with God
yeah and it and walking into a door that says respect that's heaven for him yeah
just so just respect I mean this guy he didn't get any respect I think it's
weird that Lou Gehrig killed himself did he yeah Lou Gehrig's disease is that
Russian that's so sad dude I never knew that uh-huh yeah that's why I make you
- Yeah, when people say, you know,
oh, he died of Lou Gehrig's disease,
they lost a battle with their mind.
- Yeah, ALS stands for a lonely stoner.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's what happened to him.
It's actually insanely sad what happened to him.
He killed himself with a baseball, tried to eat it.
(laughing)
He knew it'd kill him, but he just tried.
- Is that, is this part of my mustache not growing?
I don't know dude, I can't even barely see you dude.
I see you on a webcam.
Does it look patchy in the sunlight?
I can't see anything now.
Yeah.
No, you look like you're on fire.
Stop putting those sunglasses on man.
I bought these 'cause they were $5 on the site,
on like Canal Street.
Canal.
Oh, beautiful Canal Street.
But yeah, I was on Canal.
Canal, whatever.
(laughing)
These were, I needed sunglasses and these were five bucks
and I just realized how bad I look in them.
- Were they Gucci sunglasses?
- Yes, they are.
- Yeah, if you're on Canal Street,
you gotta get like a fake.
- No, they're not.
They were sold, they were $5, like a guy with like a table.
- They're all a guy with a table.
- Yeah.
- That's like what everything on Canal Street is.
It's a guy with a table and he has some fucking like,
some like Gucci bags that are made out of paper mache
and he sells them to you.
- Yeah, that's your rules.
When Noah's in town, he's got a Fendi belt there.
- Yeah, there was a guy in Austin recently
who was selling a bunch of suitcases and luggage
and purses and stuff off a table,
but then the one thing that wasn't a bag
that he was selling was a giant wooden cutout
of a cow from Ben and Jerry's.
- Did you pick it up?
- No, I wanted to take a picture of it,
but I also didn't want to just like take a picture of this guy.
- Dude, I really--
- 'Cause he was standing in front of it.
- I really want to go to like the flea market
in my hometown.
I wonder if it's opened back up yet.
- Oh, I was just at a flea market in--
- Dude, Hampshire, dude, to the best.
Last time I was at a flea market, I got a--
- At Hollis, I told you about this.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You ignored me 'cause you hate me.
- Well, I hate Hollis.
- Hollis, dude, Hollis is cool.
The thing about a New Hampshire flea market
is that there's, multiple times that day,
I saw somebody cross the street
and say thank you for your service to the crossing guard.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- Dude, the flea markets are the best, dude.
In the south you get like,
like I went to this flea market a couple years ago
and I got a pro El Chapo t-shirt
that said that it called him
the number one Mexican billionaire.
And it was like free El Chapo, he's the man.
And then I got a framed painting of the Last Supper
where Jesus was replaced with Obama.
- Yeah. - Nice.
- Just the sickest shit ever, dude.
- In New Hampshire, you either get,
the flea market's there, you're either buying
a gun or a combat knife, or a widescreen DVD,
a fellowship of the ring that's covered in cum.
Like those are the very possible things
you can leave with.
- The Londonderry flea market's good.
The Londonderry flea market,
they have a big pond in the middle of it,
and there's a dude and they have a,
a boat in the middle of the pond,
and it's like a mannequin that's kind of,
I think he's dressed up like a troop, I don't remember,
but they just have a mannequin fishing in the pond,
and it just kind of like sits there.
- That's the best, dude.
In North Carolina, all the flea markets are either like,
yeah, like the dogs playing poker,
but it's like Obama and Bill Clinton,
or like the most racist toy that anybody's ever imagined.
And then when you're like, oh shit,
this is like old as hell, like where'd you get this?
and they're like, "Man, I bought that 10 years ago."
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Yeah.
I'm a huge handmaid.
- There was a family there at the flea market
where they had a little kid and they found at a table
like a gun holster that was small,
like a child-sized gun holster.
And they were trying to put it on.
They were trying to put it on the kid
and the kid was crying and being like,
"I don't know what I wear."
- Kid sounds like a baby, dude.
- Yeah, dude, that kid sucks.
- Get a cooler kid, man.
Kid can't handle an empty holster.
- Also, there was a free bin,
like where everyone just put the stuff
they just want to give away for free,
and I walked over and it was just a bunch of trash,
and then a baby doll that had multi-colored paint
splattered all over its face.
(laughing)
- Dude, flea markets are the best, dude.
If I ever need a $25 bootleg copy of Olympus Has Fallen,
I'm headed straight to the flea market, dude.
- Flea markets, that's where you get good DVDs, though.
You get like 10 DVDs for like $5.
Dude, I left there, I went yesterday I guess,
I left there with three Transformers Blu-rays, dude.
- Oh my God.
- Dude, my mom used to go to this flea market in Lowell
and she would just buy bootleg DVDs
out of some guy's car, out of his trunk.
And it was like, some of them were like screener quality,
some of them were like fucking--
A lot of them are a guy just filming it in the theater.
Yeah, like half of them, half of them, like the Hobbit,
we had the Hobbit on DVD.
Also by the time they get to the flea market,
they're on DVD.
Right.
But the Hobbit we had on DVD,
that one was a dude filming in his car,
and then like, she had,
what were the other ones?
I don't know, but there were like a bunch of them
where it was like,
some of them had like a little bar at the bottom
that said like, do not distribute,
like this is a screener.
And like shit like that.
Who's the fuck is it who is selling the screeners to the bootleg guy?
Airplane uh companies I think.
I think airplane companies get like the screeners for like the in-flight movie.
They also just send out they send they just send out screeners to like
company like in LA you'll just if you have like.
Do you think we could get a screener?
We probably could if one of us joined SAG.
Right?
Yeah.
Is that all you have to do?
Yeah you'll join SAG.
Yeah I will.
My nuts on your face.
- They're fucking sagging on my face
and I'm licking them up.
- Yep. - No!
- Yeah, that's right. - That's disgusting.
- We do need-- - I don't wanna join that.
- We need to get screeners,
we need to get press passes to pretty much every event.
And Caleb, this is something that you suggested
that I've been thinking about a whole lot.
We need to get on Family Feud.
- Family Feud, if we could launch some kind of--
- Oh my God, we gotta go, we gotta do it.
- But here's the problem, so I looked it up.
I looked up the Family Feud requirements, okay?
'Cause listen, I would love nothing more
than to do family feud with you too.
But you do need five people.
And they say on the website you have to be blood related.
So we would need to forge documents.
- Well, okay, no, because I just saw celebrity family feud
where it was--
- That's celebrity.
- That's celebrity, Dave.
- We're not making it on celebrity family feud.
- I don't think we're quite reaching that threshold yet.
- We're gonna compete against Rob Lowe and his wife.
- Here's the first step, we become mega ultra famous.
- Okay, but my other point still stands here.
if we just get married, we're a family, okay?
It's not like a husband and a wife is blood related.
- That's a good point, but that only works for two of us.
I don't think there's any states
you can get triple married, right?
We can adopt, can you adopt an adult?
- Yeah. - You could.
Well, who's the second oldest?
I'm the oldest, obviously.
Who's the second oldest? - I'm the youngest.
- All right, so me and Patrick have to get married
and adopt you.
I think that's the only way it legally works.
- Can you-- - Okay, you could probably,
one second.
Even then, who's our other two, dude?
What are we getting?
First of all, your uncle.
Kevin Rudolph's little Wayne?
Is that what we have to do?
Whatever, man, I'll do it.
That'd be crazy.
Well, that's the other thing.
Because we're listening to people.
Wait, wait, wait.
What if we got, like, Steve Harvey's kids?
[laughter]
It's just like us showing up.
That he hasn't talked to?
Why do you assume he hasn't talked to his kids?
Because that would be a funnier reveal.
As he turns around to pitch him the question of
what's the best sex you ever had thing and he turns around it's his damn
daughter he starts crying yeah we say and we say talk about a family feud yeah
true yeah he's not very wind by default yeah exactly a feud yeah I think we
would have been better eventually night person I mean eventually they're gonna
run out of celebrities to have that want to be on family feud and then they're
gonna come to us for celebrity family feud I don't know man I was watching it
Sometime in 20 years.
If they're at One Republic, like, I mean, there's an endless level of One Republic level.
No, don't, no, you don't, you see, that means they're getting there.
One Republic?
You might be right, actually.
Who's the people they would do right before us, though?
Uhhhh...
NumaNuma guy?
No.
No?
No, we should get, we should scout him for our team.
Gary Larson?
Gary, no, it's Gary Prolsma.
Gary Bralsma.
No, Gary Larson, I mean, would he be right before us?
He would not go on that.
I think he would be pretty far before us.
But he's hard to get also because he has a secret identity.
Yeah, he had Lou Gehrig's disease, he killed himself.
I think he's alive, right?
No.
Gary Larson's dead?
I think he's alive.
I'm pretty sure he's alive.
I'm Googling it right now.
Oh, I was thinking of...
Yep, he's alive.
I was thinking of Gary Clarson.
Yeah I was thinking of Blary Blarson actually.
Yeah I know him because he famously died in my neighborhood.
Yeah he's a super dead guy.
No I was just thinking of him.
My bad.
Yeah.
No but I think that it'll be many many years.
Also they keep making these new celebrities.
Like we're never going to get on.
We're going to become celebrities.
I think we have to.
First of all.
I got to go freaking all these new celebrities.
I got to know who Mort Sahl is.
I mean come on.
I mean by next year I'm going to be a superstar too.
I don't know if we brought that into account.
I'm just going to get really famous by performing.
Oh, that's really gorgeous.
Superstars tend to do a lot of performance.
There could be some music involved, but I mainly will focus on stardom.
You think you're going to be like Lillian Gish level famous?
You think that you're going to have like a...
I don't know who that is, but I'll be basically superstar level famous, which is I would put
on the level of like BTS if they're one person or like the president. You think
you got a Lon Chaney movie in you? I don't know if you're trying to make fun of me
right now but I will be a superstar. You could be the first guy who's just normal famous for no reason. My only point of reference is just silent film stars. Oh yeah yeah okay
Cameron Mr. Al Jolson over here. Oh yeah this guy thinks he's Buster Keaton. Oh my
Oh my god. Yeah, hey, check out the big balls on fucking T.W. Griffith over here.
I don't know if that's the one you want to be compared to.
That guy was, I think he was naughty.
Yeah, he was a cheeky tad cheeky.
You know, now that you say it, Austin Powers is a good reference point to how famous I'm going to be.
You mean as famous as Austin Powers?
As famous, if not more famous.
he started doing a game show and it's oh yeah yeah dude Tommy scary god what was
the name of the fucking character is like Tommy something it was like the gong
show and Tommy Maitland that disgusted me dude yeah is just like I mean he is look
you're gonna dress up just do Shrek like just do it as Shrek right I think I do
I do respect the thing of Mike Myers creating a fake British guy because he thinks England is funny.
I think his mom was British or some shit.
Oh right, yeah, because he's from Canada.
Which, for some reason, Canadian people will have the most insane hyphenated British last name.
Yeah.
A lot of like McDonald's, like,
McDonald Quarry, something like that.
- I don't think there's a McDonald Quarry.
- If there was a McDonald's in the quarry,
I would go to it. - I might eat it.
I was hungry.
- Yeah.
- Hell, I'd eat McDonald's anywhere, even the Quarry.
- Yeah?
- I'd go underground for McDonald's.
- I would totally, oh my God.
- They should open an underground McDonald's.
I guess that's just like one in like a subway or something.
- I'd drive my-- - But they should put
one in a cave.
- They should, right?
cave mcdonalds? Have it drip? Instead of it dripping water you could put some damn diet
coca cola to drip. Yeah what about like a stalactites and stalagmites? A coke freestyle machine that
has a stalagmite on it? That might be a fucking genius idea dude. And the chairs and tables
could be like rocks. And I'd drive my Chrysler to get some fries there. Yeah? I'd drive right
over there to get some fries in my Chrysler. Yeah absolutely. I mean I'd pull up there in
my
in
You want to mini scoop them.
In your mouth.
No, I just said you wanted to scoop.
It's too easy with this guy.
No, I don't want to eat poop.
I don't want to eat poop at all.
You can scoop poop in your mouth.
Hey, Caleb, I'm going to ride my ATV.
You will be on ATV.
Yeah, because I'll be so famous.
Because you'll be dead.
No.
I will.
You don't just get on TV when you're dead.
Oh, dude, well, this is unrelated, but I was at my grandma's house going through old shit
because she's just so ready to die.
just hawking shit at me all the time and so she was like showing me all like her
like photos and all this shit newspaper clippings and stuff and that my
apparently my mom when she was a kid was on the front page of a Charlotte
newspaper because she on a she was on a playground when she was four and she
went upside down. And there was an entire news story with a bunch of pictures of my mom hanging
upside down on monkey bars and it was like, "This brave little tyke decided to go upside
down?" And I was like, "Dude, what the fuck was the... did the newspaper used to be?" This
is like a real... there's like stuff about the Cold War four pages in and the front page
is like some kid went upside down on the monkey bars more on page six. What do you mean she
fell asleep and went upside down like no she no she fell asleep. What are you talking about?
What the fuck? Where did I? Did you just read the word fell asleep when you were looking
at something else while he was talking? There's just a bunch of and I asked my grandma I was
like why the hell was this in the news? She was like I don't know some guy some news guy
with a camera just started like taking photos of her while she was at the playground.
Oh no.
I'm actually a reporter for a news story.
There's a guy with a hat, like a fedora that just says "Press" on it.
And he's just like taking pictures of children and he's like "Ah, great story today!"
Yeah, and he's like "You don't understand, she's going in the news man, she's upside
down."
God, that's...
But I, yeah, it just amazed me dude.
Is that, like, I feel like I would have been, could have been the most famous guy of all
time in the in the like 70s yeah if that's how you know how you know what I
would have done next week put a story kid hangs right side up on the monkey bars
exactly dude or same been same kid hang caught caught hanging that same down
hanger yeah hanging right side up yeah I mean come on dude switching sides on us
man I'm still looking at pictures at Tommy Maitland I bet you are I'm looking
He wrote like a whole fucking backstory for Tommy Maitland. What does that mean? Like he has like a
Like a whole story
What's the story dude? I don't want to like it. I don't want to read this like Kim Jong-un
I don't want to read this on the pod. You know, it's like it's like a whole it's a whole page
It's a whole Wikipedia page for this. So you're just gonna say it's very interesting, but we're not gonna read it. He was on
game show in England called You Still Got No Proof. That's kind of funny. Yeah.
All right. Yeah, I guess that is just a piece of comedy, a fake guy's story. Yeah.
Yeah, not much there for us, huh? Right. It's just like, what, that show lasted one
season. He was like, I'm going all in. Yeah, Gong Show. Bringing back the Gong
Show, dude. That was brave. Yeah. Who would have thought that would only last one
season man it makes no sense to me did it yeah it might have lasted no that
probably was the most amazing pitch meeting ever just like hey you remember
that show from like the 70s that like everybody loved and probably was like
insanely racist what if we brought it back and had a just an imaginary
claymation guy host it that was played by Austin Powers would that be good oh it
lasted two seasons hey good for that dude yeah good for the gong show yeah I think
think two seasons is the new I'm cutting this off for starting the list we don't
want to hear about this anymore somebody somebody's about to get gonged yeah I
don't know what that means I don't know what show you're talking about I don't
want to go on it so I think you got kicked off the show right I am going to
wronged you you are I am going to become a superstar because I am the best killer
of all time against Caleb are you serious I'm serious I just got that I just got
Please don't kill me.
I hate to say it.
I'm going to kill you like instantly right now.
Alright, today's list is
Top 10 things boys like.
Can you send this to me?
Yeah.
Here, I'll resend it in the chat.
Sorry, somebody started to show up late.
Can you send this to me in private?
No.
I mean, I can send you my personal list later.
Okay.
Hee hee.
(laughter)
- It's just a list of all your favorite Transformers.
Starscream, Starscream Jazz.
- Mine would be, number one, the hat with a B on it.
Number two, a shirt with funny letters on it.
Number three, mustache that maybe is a little patchy
in one place, can't tell in the sunlight, not sure.
Number four wait, this is just Patrick right orange might cover number five
His is named Lawrence
Know that guy Lawrence yeah
Number one on the list is women. That's not true for a lot of the top comment
Number the top comment here is from Aromax777 and is I may not be capable of loving a girl
But let us face it some things can't be resisted and my English teacher said all boys are
Maniacs when it comes to this what a maroon
What is the is he not capable of love or of making love? I don't know not capable of love
That's how I'm choosing to read it. Yeah, I'm choosing to read it that way
Yeah, I mean hard to argue with this one dude get a girl in a day in a bikini
I mean, I'm gonna I'm gonna va va voom. I'm gonna rubber duck my lips
Yeah, I'm gonna make myself go absolutely hogwild going eyes popping out. I don't I
Don't do that. Really? No, dude. Tell me that you don't only for the woman. I love
Tell me that you don't
When you're walking around in Target see one of those fat-ass mannequins
I mean, then you go stupid crazy. I mean I go wild but a man
I've gone into the into
the Target
After Caleb and I've walked around the store and every single mannequin has a piece of paper with his phone number written on it slipped
Into his hands dude. I got to be prepared in case it's a night of museum type situation and they come alive at night
I might be getting a text at 2 in the morning from the Target phone.
Target security line.
From the intercom.
Yeah.
Hey, it's the plus size mannequin.
It says can opener, $5, SKU code.
I don't know man, you got to be prepared.
I mean, you know, seriously, mannequin in a bikini, I'm going to lose my mind, dude.
Netfan001, all men should vote for this except gay men.
It's true.
Trying to look one since I have autism.
[Laughter]
That wasn't Cameron reading, that was just him saying it.
I think it will be cool to have a family of your own.
[Laughter]
Oh, that's so nice.
SausageLover99 comments, "Boys rule, girls drools."
So true.
I am a dude, but do not find girls interesting at all. Am I the only one? Yes. Yes, you are
I'd like to see just a girl in a bikini
Just discover gay people. Yeah, I didn't have - is there a collective of men who I don't know
Would like a relationship with another man?
Someone says you have to admit she is hot
I don't know, woman.
This was, oh shit, I just realized you could click on the pictures.
I'm a boy but I don't like girls.
I hate they.
You click on the pictures and it says, this picture of this woman was added by mood333
on April 8th, 2016.
I mean, she's in a beautiful bikini.
This comment says, I'm reporting this image.
Just says yes, and it's from beetlesfan1964.
This one says, I'm a boy but I don't like girls.
I hate they.
"The reason is, if you jokes, they are angry."
And Boris Rule says, "Kinda sexist, my mate."
- I really do not think that people should be talking
about that stuff in public.
They should only be talking about that as appropriate
for wherever they are, even at home.
- What, I'm a girl, and it's just weird that boys like.
(laughing)
- RC cars, fishing, fixing things, getting chickens.
- Here, let me read this sequence of comments here.
- Sure.
- Good.
- Yup.
- I love girls.
from Ethan Wakeman. It is true. I love girls. True. Sex. So true.
I really do not think that people should be talking about that stuff in public.
They should only be talking about... Oh, my bad.
You fucking idiot.
I'm gonna go to Subaru and get some food for you.
They're hot.
Sex.
Number two is sports.
Yep.
Um, erm...
I don't know. Some of us actually like the written word. Yeah. Thank you. Some of us actually like the theater.
Somebody or some of us guys are actually thespians. Do you ever think for a second
there's some men who just like looking up pictures of the devil online?
Yeah, those are the guys who belong in solitary confinement. But like I don't
you know some guys just don't like sports they just like looking up really
realistic drawings of the devil. So it's kind of an inaccurate item. And screaming and hiding under the bed.
Well, we're just looking at them and being like, "Well, maybe one day."
So you never thought about that?
One day, what?
I don't know, maybe one day.
Just watch your back.
That's all I gotta say.
Guys love football.
If you asked 100 guys if they liked football, 95 out of 100 would say yes, they love football.
Every Sunday, somebody's always talking about football.
Get my point?
Football is always drilled into boys' minds.
True.
Yep.
Yeah, yeah.
drilling each other's minds on the damn on the football field
a lot of these guys have actual head injuries
some called CTE look this up
look up Junior Seyo
I would say drilling football into somebody's head is a very good thing to say
uh... here's a comment here
i'm a ten-year-old girl and i like to skateboard too but i have a brother
named that's thirteen
and he is the one that taught me how to skateboard so most boys like
skateboarding
That's true.
I like swimming.
That's fun.
Sometimes running.
I am not very good at football.
Probably because I am Mexican.
Who doesn't lobe football?
I ran.
What's there not to love about it?
I think it's really cool and I am a girl of seven boy brothers.
I hate sports!
Except for baseball.
I'm a boy.
I wrestle my brother all the time.
So fun.
I love it.
(laughter)
- I'm on the football team.
- Hell yeah, they obsessed.
- Sports is a boy's life, dude.
- That's the truth, man.
- Dude, what would I do without my sports?
- There's a comment on this one that says,
"I don't like women."
(laughter)
- I don't like sport.
I'm not a gamer, really.
I'm not fat.
I hate wrestling.
I don't listen to rap.
Cars are okay, but I'm not a car guy.
And I also don't use a TikTok, so I'm so unique.
- That's me when I meet anybody new.
That's what I, I just rattle off everything right away.
- I don't like cars.
- Yeah, I don't like cars.
- Here's all you need to know about me.
- Yeah.
- And I don't like sports.
I'm not a gamer, really.
I'm not fat.
I hate wrestling.
- A lot of boys like toot ball, so I agree.
(laughter)
- I'm a girl but ball is life.
- Sheesh. - Truth.
Wow.
Much respect, dude.
That's like a, dude, that's insane.
A girl who likes sports?
- Yeah.
- I feel like I'm in fever pitch right now.
- No, no, she doesn't like sports, that's the thing.
- She likes sports at the end though.
- Yeah, she likes, she runs on the field.
- You don't know anything about fever pitch.
- Are you shitting me?
You don't know anything about Fever Pitch with Jimmy Fallon and Drew Barrymore.
I know so much about that.
No.
Yes.
They sing that, they play that song "It's Not Over" and it's like "It's not over" and she's
running on the field and then he names his daughter Karlo Yastremski at the end of the
movie.
You know, personally, because I'm a man, I mostly remember the hits and the home runs
in that one.
You know? I have a cut of that movie that's just the sports stuff.
Yeah?
No reactions, no story at all. I just watch it like a game.
It's called the 2004 World Series.
Yep.
But with different camera angles.
What a great World Series it was.
Every World Series is great to me, dude.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Even when it's bad?
Even when it's fucking terrible, dude.
Yeah?
I don't think I've ever watched a World Series.
I saw the World Series when I was like four on TV.
Yeah.
Three or four, no six.
Five, six.
I just can't care about baseball.
Seven, seven.
To me, baseball is like a restaurant.
Eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen.
Sixteen, there you go, too.
More than a sport.
No.
Seventeen.
I think I was eighteen.
How old?
Nineteen.
You were twenty-three?
I think I saw the World Series when I turned twenty-one.
No, that wasn't it.
Twenty-one.
that was funny. I think no, you know, another thing about it, maybe it was when I was one
to, I think I could be number three is video games. Yep. I mean, I can attest to this dude.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I know boys. Do you know gate like games and there's mostly boys on
Roblox boys really like Roblox I know boys do you I said that I just said that
motherfucker Subaru food for you minecraft is almost as good as lesbian
porn took it from number four to number three this game is very addictive and
the kids will play for five to six hours. Yeah game video games.
I'm a tomboy and I love roblox. I think they do this all the time.
Not all boys are teenage nerds. Oh falls back into the crowd. This one
says your mom noob and then there's a response. It says seriously, dude.
This game is really fun.
Lots of boys love this game.
Assassins?
Why is--
Minecraft takes away your social life,
family, friends, and sense of reality.
There is no other game that can do it as good as this game.
P.S. This is a cheaper alternative to hard drugs
and will get any child hooked within minutes.
Good luck out there.
(laughing)
Like, good luck out there at the end
makes it really sinister.
Good luck out there, bud.
Why is girls on this list?
I hate e-girls, they're mean-sidiously.
Siciously, I believe is what they were going for.
Siciously.
I like how, I like, sorry, I just wanted to say I like how on every single one under women
there is always a comment of someone saying "I hate women."
Regardless of what it is, it has nothing to do with it, they're always like "I just hate
women."
Yeah.
I feel like that's a good indication that women should not be number one.
Number four is one that hits really deeply for me personally and I think maybe you guys
too.
Number four is music.
Music is so powerful to me.
Yeah, it just changes like the way that, you know, it just like, it changes like silence
into song.
Well, I recently read a study and this is true, I recently read a study that scientists
claim that music can actually change your perspective.
Yeah.
Actually I did a study recently where if I listen to Death Core while I'm washing the
dishes I can nod my head with the music.
That's actually really interesting.
My hypothesis was actually scientifically was in the study.
That's cool.
I recently did a study too to see if I could jack off to S&M by Rihanna and we're waiting
on the results.
So you have to grade these things with a curve, they say.
You're doing it now?
Well, we're looking for the results.
Yeah, you know, the results are still on the way.
Did you lose those?
The results are being processed.
How long has the study been going on?
It's been going on for about six years now that I've been trying to get the results from
this.
And so far it's inconclusive, but there's a lot of hope that this could help people in
dire medical situations.
That sounds like a really intensive study.
Like it takes up a lot of time.
Yeah, mostly it takes up a lot of time.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing.
I mean, I'm not sure if it's a good thing.
But there's a lot of hope that this could help people in dire medical situations
That sounds like a really intensive study
Time it takes up tons of time for me
You know, this has become a full-time gig for me is doing this study and I'm gonna be publishing stuff. So watch out
Here's a publish in a lot of stuff. So we better watch out. Here's a comment here the iPod shot it onto the list
I mean music music was probably not gonna be on this list at all, but then the iPod came out
Hello, my people that are crazy. I might get my brother some music for Christmas
Some music for Christmas, it's so nice. I mean, here's it that you it's Christmas morning, right?
You get all these stupid shit gifts from Santa Claus,
you got a Nerf gun, a VR headset,
but then your brother hands you one special box,
you open it up, music.
- There's music in there, it changes your whole perspective.
- And it can actually scientifically
change your entire perspective.
- Yeah, it's a thing to look out for.
- It's part of the study.
- Here's the last comment on music, says,
wrong, I put in what do boys like, not what do guys like.
- True.
Here's a comment, I like Biff music and cricket.
I'm transgender born a girl but moving to be a guy and I love music that's so nice
yeah I like music a lot especially alternative rock and rap I also like
some electronic I don't really care about the others dark boy X
whoa we see dark boy X before we did yeah it is a familiar name what top
comments is most beautiful thing in the world right now so true that's true
because it's hard to find beauty in this damn messed up world right now.
Until they come out with the next thing after music, it's going to be the most beautiful
for a while.
Yeah, they tried it with tunes for a little bit, but it didn't work.
Before it was music, I think it was like flowers maybe was the most beautiful thing in the
world.
Yeah, and then they moved on to symphonies and then they found music quite far after
that.
Yes, I believe so.
Yes, I concur.
Yes.
That was actually part of my study as well that I was doing on the history of beauty
and music and science and history. Yeah I'm working on like a million studies right now.
Yeah I actually was just doing a study about I've been doing this like social experiment study about
like you know if you could like have two friends that like are your best friends and like it's how
that would play out like long term. I'm really into social experiment studies I'm doing one
that's called can you eat a sandwich in the hood and I've been doing that one for a lot of days
recently. How are the results looking on that one?
Uh, kind of nothing so far. I'm kind of waiting for somebody to ask me to leave the hood.
Right. You know, I'm trying to recreate one of those videos where someone does something
crazy and that guy's like, "Can you just please leave the hood if you're going to do this
crap?" Right? Like, we're in the hood right now. Can you not be doing this crap right
now? I actually was conducting a study recently,
um, to see how many times the same guy would come and, uh, pee at the, uh, on the dumpster
outside my window in the same night.
Oh yeah, that guy.
No, it's actually a new different guy and I actually just received the results a few nights
ago and it's two times.
Oh really?
Is the number of times.
Oh.
Within like 20 minutes.
That's amazing results.
The same guy came and peed right outside my window.
I would like to publish those results.
When I was watching TV.
No, I'll be publishing them myself.
I don't think, I mean you have a history of stealing intellectual property.
I think I might steal that next actually.
You're going to steal intellectual property, the concept of it?
Yeah.
Oh, that's actually genius dude.
- That is, oh.
- You're kinda getting everything.
- Steal the idea of copyright.
- Yeah, yeah, you're stealing my intellectual property.
No, buddy, I own intellectual property.
- I invented copyright. - I think I get
all of this crap.
- Yeah.
- So, actually, I stole it.
I stole copyright, I went to the bank where it's held,
and I stole it.
- Went to Fort Knox, and I stole copyright.
- That's true. - Are you jealous?
- Number five is dogs.
Dude, I hate dogs so much.
- Yeah, I like my dog.
But every other dog if it got cut in half I'd say that's pretty funny.
Wouldn't care dude.
Wouldn't care even a little bit.
I cried when my Labrador died and I'm a man.
Ironic?
Not really.
When people post photos of their dogs online I'm just like dude what are you doing man?
Yeah I agree with Beam456 here who says I hate dog.
They are totally disgusting.
I think that's completely right.
Exactly.
People are guessing everything's not true man.
I'd like to I mean yeah my my dog is my man's best friend but I think beyond
that I mean most other dogs your man's best friend yeah you got a mate yeah
yeah it's me no you mean you guys don't have a man cuz your girls and you I'm
talking about my soul bro I have a Rottweiler he's adorable that's a
different breed. Adorable. Yeah, adorables are a completely different breed. That's a
cross between a doberman and a marble. Yeah. DreTop10's comments, "Girls too, underdogs."
Number six, oh my god, you can't make this shit up.
Number six is sex.
Excuse me, sex, what are we doing here?
Kids in general, don't stop talking about sex.
Go to my school and they act like they're a 20 year old or something.
You're 12, you're not a adult.
It makes me laugh, but it's really annoying too.
You know, I'm with them.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, stop talking about this crap, dude.
I'm sick.
Oh my god, it's so disgusting when somebody's like horny.
Yeah, you like it though.
I hate it.
Yeah, I'm gonna put you in a big polka dot bikini.
I hope not.
I'm gonna put you in a little tiny big polka dot bikini.
Don't.
I'm gonna make it as small as possible.
It's gonna barely cover your nipples.
Oh my god.
And then I'm gonna make you do the jumping challenge.
What's the jumping challenge?
I mean you gotta jump a bunch.
The slow motion jumping challenge.
slow-motion bikini Caleb jumping challenge yeah it's a new challenge
actually just created as a study no I mean you will you create it as a challenge
so I did the study version I've been doing this study on bikinis and how
tight they can possibly get for a thousand years now let me read this
comment here yeah damn all these hot chicks around the world are making me
horny that's very close to the conclusions that I've come to yeah that's
my damn all these hot chicks around the world are making me horny you shouldn't
ask someone if they want sex with you online because you're are a stranger and
it is no for everyone here's a comment all the boys in my school don't stop
talking about it though. Don't stop talking about it. Though nowadays, everyone is into
that. True. It seems like nowadays everyone's into sex. Always on their mind 70% of the
time. Yup. I had sex in pre-K, laugh out loud. Oh my. You're in trouble buddy. I am a boy
and I do not like that.
Sex is evil.
Yep.
I don't know, I'm 11, Beatles fan 1964.
(laughter)
There you go, Beatles fans
got the role.
The school that I go to, Black Butte,
the kids do not stop talking about sex.
It is like you're 10 to 12,
not 26, and in a girl
who is 12, and I know what
it feels like with boys talking about sex,
about it sometimes it scares me this one is terrifying I like sex I want to do it
in real life I know how babies are made and I'm just 10 I want to suck
*laughter*
Oh, dude.
*sigh*
I don't remember being like this when I was a kid.
Me neither!
I liked Master Chief.
Yeah.
That was what I was into.
*laughter*
I wanna suck them.
Does it specify what that could possibly be?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Number seven, money.
Yep.
Hey, heard that.
Yes sir.
What's not to like about this crap, right?
God, I love money, dude.
Money is definitely the one to vote for.
These guys at school are totally in the money.
I am a girl and a tomboy.
I think I should know.
No money on food, no money on girls, no money on telly, no money on games.
please put on top of the list.
- I don't trust tomboys, man.
I think tomboys are girl spies.
- I trust tomboys.
- I don't trust tomboys.
- I know so many guys named Tom.
So many boys named Tom.
- I bet you know a lot of boys.
- Tom, Moshe, all of them.
- Money is not everything,
and most people who love money are bratty.
- True.
- That's fact.
- This is the actual order.
- Most boys who love money are batty.
Parents, money, food like chicken, sports, video games, clothes, population like being
popular, games, girls didn't make it to the list because most 99% are annoying, 65% are
ugly.
Did this kid just flip?
It wasn't food like chicken, it's food like chicken.
Did he just flip?
It's chicken that's food like.
Parents at number one, dude?
Yeah, what the hell?
That's a violation, dude.
Yeah, not right.
What the fuck?
This should be number the first because no money no girl, no money no games, no money
no cheese, no money no sex, got it?
Stiles X.
Stop saying anything about sex, my eyes need bleach so much.
One of the worst comments on the site.
Number eight is movies.
Here's a comment from Beatles fan 1964 who said they were 11 so just keep that in mind
with this.
All right.
Particularly the original Star Wars trilogy, Batman movies, and Quentin Tarantino movies.
I'm a dude and I like movies.
Is there a more perfect sentence in the universe?
I'm a dude and even I like movies, man.
Yes sir.
Movies are fun.
They're even more fun if you're sitting next to your crush.
I hate that actually.
I hate my crush.
I hate my crush so much.
Can you stop looking at my fucking weenie and watch the damn movie dude?
Stop cutting a tube out of the popcorn.
Stop cutting a rug in front of me.
Stop shaking your...
The popcorn's falling out of the hole.
You have to...
You're supposed to put the hole in before the popcorn.
This is a disaster.
What?
Did you cut this hole in this popcorn so we could eat it some weird freak way?
Yeah, well I'm not going to put my tongue in that hole if that's what you're trying to
get me to do.
Disgusting.
You seriously want me to eat popcorn like this?
What are you doing dude?
Ugh.
Crushes are so stupid. Number nine is food. Chez for the win. Chez is my Bible. I eat
Chez. I eat tacos. I like tacos lots. Tacos consist of mixture of meat, salsa, lettuce,
tomato, and a whole lot of other stuff. I don't think it's a lot other stuff than
that. Yeah. I think they kind of got all the ingredients. Beatles fan 1964 is here too and
says me and your boyfriend should be best friends my cousin is nicknamed the
conveyor belt he loves food they're built oh my brother likes pickles and so do I
but I'm a girly girl Wow I was eating cheese when I saw this
No, why is this year both genders seem to like cheese a lot
Lots of these things are of iCarly
true very true
Number ten is taking a full circle here. Yeah number ten is cars. I do love cars, man
Here's a comment car toy tiny with a plays son my play son my
It just feels like it's written by a baby, but it's
That was a that was a tiny guy jumping from key to key on the key. Yeah. Yeah, there's a no
They're too hard to get all the way to the backspace car toy tiny with the place
Yes, even even the ons that can't drive not being sexist at all
sexist
See X us yeah
Think they're trying to spell Lexus. Yeah
Nasty ever get a car the boys will come running to you, and they might want to make out oh
Well number 11 other boys. Yeah
What heck yeah takes on coming here top cut yeah, okay?
Go ahead
Sorry takes one to no one and appreciate the male
Similarity and the secret knowledge of the power of the peen is something any boy
The power of the peen well you don't know the secret knowledge you don't know it I'm
Yeah, I know the secret knowledge.
Say the first secret knowledge then.
Ah, you can get a, sometimes you look at the TV, get a strong penis.
Yep, okay, he knows.
He's got it.
That's a first step, right?
Get some strong penis from watching TV too much.
Okay, well when you put too much in there, I'm thinking maybe you're starting to deviate
from what the knowledge is.
I think you might be.
Might have been a lucky guess.
I
don't think mine is small enough to do that. Mine neither. I haven't done that either. I
was trying to fool you into saying that you have instead. Okay. It's true that boys like
other boys, but that is called gayness my people. Just no. No. My friends, yes, says
Beatles fan 1964. Wow. I'm bisexual so I can agree with this. It's true. Okay but now read
a comment. Oh my god, are you guys serious dude? But you really haven't ever tried to
like fold your skin over your wiener to make it look completely disappeared so it looks
like you only have your balls there? I don't know that it's ever been a second belly button
kind of level. Yeah, I don't think like an outie belly button deal but like. Maybe I
I just have a ton of space. I probably just have a ton of space. I tucked it around the back and made it look like I got it.
For yours it's probably just big enough that you can do that.
Yeah, exactly, big enough.
Yeah, I tucked it around the...
You have to have a big enough one to do that.
Exactly, yeah. I tucked it around the back and put it in my butt.
You put it in your butt?
Yeah, you don't do that.
In your butt hole or just your cheeks?
Just to make, like, if you're wearing tight pants, make them fit better.
You're tucking your penis?
Into my butt.
You're tucking your...
Like in the cheeks or the hole?
The hole.
The hole?
That's a...
I've never done that.
I can't...
I don't think I can do that.
I can make it disappear, go other way inside my body.
Yeah?
Yeah, maybe.
It's still going inside.
You just push it until it touches your bone.
And then it's pretty hard to go past that.
Oh, which bone?
The bone that's behind your wiener?
You're touching your bone?
You push your wiener so far into your body that it touches a bone.
Like a hip bone?
Like your pelvis?
I don't know, whatever bones behind your fucking wiener, I don't know.
I'm not a doctor.
Yeah, there's a bone back there, dude.
Feel right now.
There's a bone there.
Dude, I'll push mine in right now.
Look at this, dude.
Don't show it.
It's touching my bone right now.
I can do it under my pants.
I'm like an expert at this at this point, dude.
That's what I would do if somebody, if some sort of villainous monster was like, "I'm
gonna cut off your penis," I would shoot it.
Oh, somebody already got to me.
Yeah, don't make me move my finger, but I don't have one.
And they go, "I'm sorry."
And then they move on to you two, and you guys would be like, "Oh, I wish I could hide
my ginormous penis, 'cause this man's about to cut it off.
I wish that I had listened to Caleb and practiced for years."
And then you will be sorry.
I just noticed Caleb's Zoom name.
yeah my little brother's account I'm on yep whole family's in the house right
now that's why I'm being mighty quiet I could change it I guess I don't want to
mess this shit up though number 22 it's porn Oh everybody did once right I'm 13
and I still masturbate. Still? Number 31 is the color pink and here's the top comment.
Pink was actually a boy's color and blue was for girls. Before Adolf Hitler came
to power, he used pink patches and clothing to label gay and insane men. After the war,
pink was not considered a boy's color and vice versa the feminine blue. Wow. So
they're saying this is like a Republicans freed the slaves type situation. Yeah, exactly.
But pink is actually the boy color.
Yes.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
Uh, boobs is on here.
Number 34 is destroying things.
And I'm gonna, all the comments here are so good.
I think that when you destroy things that you feel like you can conquer the world.
I love to destroying things.
Am I a tomboy?
Yep.
A crushing room would be awesome.
Wait, number 33 is the number 7.
The first comment is "Just plain lucky."
Internet, popularity, fights.
I guess that's true.
I guess guys do like to fight, especially me because I'm amazing at it.
Strip clubs.
It's weird that boys like girls dancing on a pile.
It's mean and very sexist to us girls.
Number 43 is playing, the comment here is "very good and good".
Number 44 is light, lights are very helpful, lights are awesome.
Number 49 is glow in the dark.
Because they are basically with the girl in the dark together.
True.
Oh.
Number 54 is polygamy.
For now!
comment from crazy rabbit squid number 55 is parks and someone says some boys just
love to hang out with their mates in the park and also go down to the local chippy
after number 59 is polygamy I think that's a different thing isn't it
number 60 says toys and someone says I like them a lot to be honest 23 of these
are on my bed. Oh wait polygamy is... Yeah it's a different thing. I thought polygamy was the same
thing. It's or it's polygamy is is a man who has multiple wives and then I think polygamy if I'm
correct is just like have is like either gender like having more than one wife or husband like
polygamy is specifically for having wives. Call it whatever you want you're still going to hell.
That's right.
Yeah.
And jail.
And also Caleb jail, which is my own personal jail that I put freaks into.
It's basically a hole.
Uh, yeah.
And then the last one here is, number 62, swearing.
Fuck no!
Come on, man. Are you serious?
That's how you want to end this fucking thing?
This thing?
Yep.
Is with that crap?
Yeah, you guys better shut your damn mouths.
I push my penis so far back that it touches my ass
say the word as but hold up you that tip of your tongue all right all right bye