You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Oh, I just Scrooged.
- No, the Scroog guy's like this.
- No.
- I'm gonna screw you.
- He goes like this.
- I thought you were doing Scroog.
- Oh man, there's a screw in my chair.
- There's a screw in Caleb's chair.
- I like my version of it.
- I'm gonna screw you.
- Maybe he could be like,
Okay, we can combine it like, "This is my screwing chair!" he could say.
"I'm gonna screw you in that chair!"
Yeah, there's this...
Yeah.
Like, yeah, there's like...
You see that chair? That's where I'm gonna screw you, because I'm the screw guy.
This is my... maybe he could say like, "This is my screwing screw," and he's got a screw.
I don't like when it's like, like people refer to sex as screwing.
I think...
That's so weird.
I think they should do it more. They should do it in like...
It's a gross image I think, because when I think of a screw I think of like, you know,
when you like see a screw and it's got like the fucking threads.
A spiraling screw.
I think they should do it more, like it should be more accepted as like a, like you should
like, when you confront your wife for cheating on you, you should be like, "Did you screw?"
Have you been screwing that one guy?
Which I mean, you know, watch any made for TV, or not made for TV, but like, you know,
edited for TV movie.
Yeah.
And it's like, that's all you're, I miss that.
I haven't had cable in so long.
Haven't seen a Hallmark movie in a while?
a Hallmark movie but like good TV I mean it's it's you can't you don't get the
like the edited version of good movies but if you get like to be or voodoo or
something and just scroll through like the free with ad stuff they have you can
find like the so like yeah perfect like sci-fi channel stuff that's like
forgotten like I found a show that had one episode called legend of the dog man
have we talked about the the TV edit of the departed no where they do like in
the intro they're like they're like yeah Boston it's a town full of weirdos
freaks it's awesome dude first you had the freaks and some real creepy and then
creeps and the Polish it's awesome dude dude I fuckin I'm miss made for TV edits
That was like such a like thing like the early 2000s was like watching just
edited like. Right. I could never. Maybe it's just a nostalgia thing I'm thinking now. I could never do that.
I never, because this is probably very specific to me but like I would be like
well if I watch the edited for TV version I'll just have to watch it again
because I'll like miss stuff so there's no point. Like I wouldn't watch movies on
airplanes either because I was like oh they edit some of those so it's I won't
even be watching the movie because they take out some of the scenes so what's
they take out the boring love scenes between the girl and boy. They take out when they say
certain things or use certain violences against each other. Not on Spike. On Spike
they take out all the girls. Yeah I mean Kill Bill is like two minutes on Spike.
Yeah it's the best two-minute movie of all time yeah. It's just called Bill. Yeah
yeah you should have seen the version of eighth grade they did now they'd
probably double the length of the movie instead yeah probably double the girls
and probably they chopped and screwed it yeah it's all purple yeah yeah or pink
actually because of all the girls are in it yeah yeah
speaking of - I just remembered on to be I used to watch I think it was AMC had
like a show where Gene Simmons and Paul Stanley were trying to reboot arena
football yeah oh yeah they bought a team they bought the team in LA and they
named it the LA kiss this was recently right yeah this is a like 2014 yeah came
out and like the first like I feel like I've talked about this before on the
show but I don't think ah the first like episode is a guy who's like you know
like arena like footballs like my passion but my doctor says if I get one more
concussion I'll go blind and like it's all like the like the training process
and like them like recruiting people for the team and he like has an injury yeah
in the middle of practice which I mean you know get that like do that to like
raise drama in the show make the make a show about Paul Stanley and Gene Simmons
doing business interesting but it's just so funny like imagine losing sight
because you wanted to play football for you know in Simmons yeah I mean like you
know that's like dying for your country though yeah that's like a super and that
country is Israel is real rock and roller he's the man in the world I I was
watching a show on to be because I couldn't find anything to watch and it
was about is like a cryptid show where they like go and like interview people
about like the cryptids that live in their country or whatever and I was
watching one about the Tata Duende which is like a gnome from like Belize or I
think it's Belize but basically it's like this thing where like the Tata Duende
is not like a cryptid it's like a thing that that like parents tell their kids
like oh you better behave or the Tata Duende is gonna come and like attack you
or like take you away at night but it's so funny good it's like doing like a
like a ghost adventures episode about like the tickle monster.
I had one of those as a kid but my mom...
You had a Tata Duende? You had a personal tickle monster? No, no, it was like
the guy. My mom would say like, "Oh, you leave
if you don't clean your room, the guy's gonna come
the guy's gonna come and inspect the house." I think it was probably
just somebody just like... Oh, that's your fucking landlord, what do you mean? I don't know, I don't know if we had a
landlord but if you if you don't if you don't clean up the bathroom the guy's
gonna come in the guy's gonna come and he's gonna take it away like she would
like threaten us like child services nice way basically we used to threaten my
mom with with child with CPS cuz she she knew a lady who worked there and her
name was in the like family like phone book and so if my mom ever did any like
grounded us I'd be like yeah I'm gonna call her tomorrow I'm gonna call her I'm
I'm gonna say that you bit me.
- And she was like, "No!"
- "You serious?"
- I did not just open the room.
- I didn't know how to dial a phone though.
- Yeah, yeah, it was bad.
- Yeah, 'cause you had a rotary phone.
- I didn't have a rotary phone.
- I, you know what, I was thinking about that the other day,
getting like a landline for my apartment.
- You should get one of those ones
where you have a cone here.
- Yeah, dude, my grandmother had a payphone in her apartment
like that you could--
- That's the worst financial decision I've ever heard.
- No, I mean, you don't need to pay for it.
Like it's like unlocked or whatever,
but it's so, it was, I can't believe that,
'cause like I would always be like,
this is the coolest thing ever,
I just wanna put quarters in there.
Like as a kid, so I would just put all my quarters in,
and then we're like, can I get the backers?
She'd be like, no.
(laughing)
- You just willingly put the quarters in?
- Yeah, well sometimes I'd be like,
can I borrow a quarter to put it in?
Just 'cause I thought it was like fun,
'cause you like open up the slot and like put it in,
and you hear it like roll around in there,
and if you put in like a nickel or something,
it like returns it.
- Yeah, you can get the quarter back.
- Did you guys ever know how fun that is?
You absolutely can, but she didn't--
You just have to call the operator and say,
"Please, can I have my money back?"
She had a key to open it to get the quarters out,
but yeah, she just kept the quarters.
Did you guys ever know a fucking kid--
Oh, like in her apartment, not like in the lobby.
Yeah, like, no, in her house.
Oh, okay.
I thought it was in the lobby.
In the lobby?
What lobby?
I said her house.
I thought you said her apartment.
Oh.
I think I said her house if I didn't--
Did you guys ever know a fucking kid
who had a gumball machine in his house?
Oh, when kids had little gumball machines
or like the Lionel coin bank.
- Yeah.
- I was like, man, you just made a money, huh?
- Yeah, like what the fuck, dude?
I remember talking with a kid, I was like,
why'd you like buy a gumball machine?
Why not like buy just gumballs?
And he was like, well, because I have people over.
I spent $25 on this gumball machine.
So if 100 people get one gumball--
- You go to Gary Vee's house?
- Yeah, I did.
(laughing)
I mean, you know, this kid was,
I'm sure he's friends with Gene Simmons,
if that makes any sense.
(laughing)
- He would be good friends with Gene Simmons.
- It's so genius when they have things like,
like a gumball machine that has like a track
for the gumball to roll down,
or one of those things where it's like you donate,
but like you put the quarter in and it like rolls around,
down like a funnel, you ever seen one of those?
- Oh yeah. - 'Cause they're like,
if there's-- - The dinosaur?
- The dinosaur?
- The Chad one, the Children's Hospital,
- I don't know. - It's like a dinosaur,
they would have them out in Walmart,
and you put like the quarter in the dinosaur's mouth,
and you watch it go down its belly.
- Exactly, shit like that, yeah, they had one of those,
they used to have one of those in the um...
Just to get kids to give it money.
They used to have one of those in the Arsenal Mall.
They used to have an arcade in the Arsenal Mall,
and they used to have one of those right outside the arcade,
which is so funny, 'cause it's like,
you know kids are gonna be leaving and just putting the tokens that they didn't use in there?
Like, that's not gonna help kids with cancer.
That's a horrible... Like, it's either I could put my coin in this, like, funnel,
or I could go play skee-ball and, like, win a prize, like...
But what if a kid with cancer's last wish is to play skee-ball?
Exactly, yeah.
Sorry bud, we can't do it. No tokens. We only have quarters.
You can turn a quarter into a token pretty quick.
It's hard. You gotta go to the airport. You gotta go to currency exchange.
Yeah, I never thought about how that was right outside the arcade. That really does seem
like the worst place to put that.
Oh, absolutely.
Like, yeah. There's a very clear choice of what you can do with your quarter there.
Yeah. You can put it in your mouth.
Yeah.
You guys ever swallow a quarter?
I swallowed a quarter.
I swallowed a damn penny.
Yeah, I squeezed it on my butt.
I ate a quarter in the pool.
A quarter?
A quarter is so huge.
I swallowed a quarter too.
I would throw the quarters in the pool and then like jump into the pool and like catch
them before they reach the bottom.
And you always jump into the pool with your mouth wide open?
No I tried to catch it with my mouth because I thought it was funny and then swam back
up and swallowed a quarter.
There was so much, so I'm drinking like chlorine water in a quarter and as soon as I got out
of the pool, like I'm like kind of choking.
I'm just like my mom's like freaking out. I was like I ate a quarter. I ate a quarter.
I feel like it should be a bigger deal, but it seems like it's no one really cares.
It doesn't matter. Yeah. Oh yeah. My little brother ate a penny.
What was I never I never told anybody because I was like somebody's gonna kill me for doing
that. It's gonna I'm gonna die and I don't want them to know that I'm gonna die. Yeah.
Well, no, like I would say either someone's gonna get mad at me or they're gonna say you're
gonna die in a week. Yeah. And either way I don't want that. I'm gonna see Ed, Edd,
and they're gonna fucking cut me open for a damn jawbreaker.
- Yeah.
- Those jawbreakers are too damn big.
- Here's the thing, the jawbreakers, first of all,
that ain't going in my mouth.
That thing's humongous.
You know, second of all,
do these kids eat anything other than candy?
- I don't know.
- Yeah.
- Third of all, that kid, that Ed kid is not 10.
He is 30 years old.
Listen to his voice, dude.
He is 30 years old and he's a girl.
And fourth of all, that plank's not real.
It's just a piece of wood.
It can't talk to the guy.
- Exactly.
- So there's a lot of things about that.
- Why would you take those out?
- Will you give me your hand?
- No!
- Why?
- No.
- What?
Will you close your eyes?
- No, don't put the handcuffs on me.
- Why?
- I don't want to put the handcuffs on.
- Why, 'cause you're scared?
- I'm not scared, I just don't want handcuffs on me.
- Why?
- 'Cause I don't like 'em.
- You're scared of the police.
- I put them on.
- Come on, put 'em on.
- No, I don't put 'em on.
Seriously put them on. This is so embarrassing. Dude, I'm filming you right now. Oh my god. He's resisting arrest
He's literally resisting arrest. Come here. Come here. You have to give me your hand. No, I'm an officer of the court
Get it on him. It's
Those aren't even oh wait, those are like the little kid I could fucking little kid. Yeah, I'll destroy these
No, don't destroy don't try it, please
Don't can you just let me handcuff you to smell something in my house like me
You fucking you
You you're going to jail. Oh
Yeah, I spent $50 on those. No, you did not spend $50 on these
I'm sorry from here. I can see those are at least $50 handcuffs are made out of platinum. That's why they're so easy to break
I'm sorry. I'm acting up. I lost a lot of blood earlier at the doctor.
Yeah, oh yeah, Caleb went to the hospital for the first time in 10 years.
I did, I went to the doctor and dude, dude, it was so, it was crazy. I didn't realize what this, what, that they do this now.
I walked in, I've been having like heart palpitations. I walked in, I was like, yeah, I've been having heart palpitations.
The doctor said, she said, by the third thing that she said, she was offering me SSRIs.
Really?
I swear to God. She was like, she was like, so, like, hi, my name is whatever.
whatever and I was like yeah cool and she was like what are your symptoms and I was like
oh I've been getting like heart palpitations at night and she was like okay so we can do
a couple things one I can send you to a cardiologist or two I can give you SSRIs like right now
and like see you on your way. SSRIs are fucking evil. Dude it's horrible. The worst medicine
of all time. I mean look at the first two letters no disrespect. And then Rhode Island
at the end. This is like the scariest shit I've ever had.
No disrespect to people who like need to take SSRIs for their mood or something,
but you should just be willpower on your way through it.
Yeah. Have you ever tried being normal?
Have you ever just like thought about eating a vegetable?
Just don't jump out the window. You know what you need to do?
Literally that fucking easy. It's called turmeric.
It's called self-control, dude. It's literally called hanging out and
watching TV and eating a sandwich. Yeah, watch The Simpsons. Hey, smile, honey.
Smile more. You should smile more. You look pretty when you smile.
You're taking these damn SSRIs. You fucking bloated ass face.
And also you want to have sex with me because you're on SSRIs.
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of sex, I forget, like, I haven't been to the doctor in a long time.
It is sexual.
Yeah?
The doctor is sexual.
Yeah, and what a way.
That is weird.
That is the most intimate contact that I've had with a woman since I've been with Jana.
She was like touching, like, my face.
Did you get, did you-
She's holding me.
She held me.
Did you get like a full checkup?
She held me dude. She fucking held me close, wouldn't let me go and she was like
she was like I need to check your heartbeat. Started fucking just on my back
had one hand on the front had another hand mm-hmm just just just compressing
me dude making me feel whole again and she was just sitting there. Maybe that's
all you needed. And then she charged me $10. Just really? Yeah. Nice. And where did
you say this was? But yeah they took a bunch of my blood. Yeah. Tried to get me
on SSRIs I said I said hell no and then just gave my blood as a as a peace
offering yeah yeah it's pretty excited I think I might go to the doctor more did
you do they have one of those like temperature scanners when you go in you
know those yeah when I went I was visiting my my grandma and like a her
senior whatever I don't know it's called but like they had a prison yeah but they
had because I know they have here they have the scanners where they like put it
against your forehead and it just like lights up but at that place they had a
scanner that was like an iPad with a camera and you like center your face and
those are crazy because it's like I know you don't need this you know I know you
don't need like a picture of me for my temperature and this just makes me want
to like stand here for 20 minutes like playing with it like a memoji
temperature changes if I open my mouth is like pulling up like a picture of
somebody on my phone and like holding it up to try and scan that like it took all
my willpower not to...
Dude, it was so fucked. I like went in there really hoping like,
"Please be cancer, please be someone really fucking evil."
It's worse when it's just nothing.
Well, she was like, "Okay, so you have, she was like,
you have ideal blood pressure and you have the heart rate of an Olympic athlete."
And I was like...
She was trying to fuck you.
I was like, "Well, you like, like was good, like what's up, what's our next move?"
Oh my God, yeah. She was like, "The rhythm of your heart is actually perfectly in sync with mine."
And we're the same blood type. And we have the same last name. It's beautiful.
They also hooked me up to, they put electrodes on me.
Oh yeah.
Dude, that was fucking freaky.
They shocked you?
Yeah, they shocked me.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
No they didn't.
I'm straight. It was beautiful.
No, they just like, they hooked up like all these little fucking stickers to me and then
they put all these wires on me and they fucking, they found out that I have the heart rate of an
Olympic athlete.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's good.
But she did say it was bad.
I mean, that actually, that sounds bad to have the heart rate.
That's bad?
Yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause you drove there, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you probably shouldn't have the heart rate
of an Olympic athlete.
- Well, no, like people who are in really good shape
have like slightly below normal heart rates.
- Oh, okay.
- And so she was like, you have like a low heart rate,
but you also are not like 1% body fat,
so it's probably bad.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So I just don't, I think my heart
is a little on the slow side.
- The thing about heart problems
is if you just ignore them, they go away.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- But I did-- - I mean, that's most problems.
I don't, you don't have to go
to the fucking doctor for anything.
I remember the last time they took my heart rate at the doctor, they were like, "Oh my
God!"
And I just never went back to the doctor and said, "Fine."
That's the move.
I was like, "I don't think my dad's been to the doctor in 30 years and he's been chewing
tobacco for 30 years."
It doesn't matter if they don't tell you everything's wrong.
Nothing's going to be wrong.
Also, if my dad died tomorrow, I'd be like, "Well, he's close to 60.
That makes sense."
if he had gone to the doctor ten years ago and then we had this ten years of
like oh no dad's gonna die yeah yeah it's way better for him to just be like
I'm out yeah I mean you know you like as somebody is just like an extreme
hypochondriac I still I don't go to the doctor because if they tell me anything
I'm gonna freak out also you know doctor that's the number one place to get sick
that's they have to keep all the diseases there to test true to test
whether you have there and they're spraying those things on their
Also, Brooklyn hospitals are like way...
Like they had me pee, they did a pee sample.
And they drank it?
Well, I peed into a red Solo cup.
Really?
What?
Yeah, I was like, "Fuck you, I swear to God, dude."
I swear to God, she was like, "Just grab one of those cups."
And usually it's like a little thing with a green cap on it for shit like that.
It's just a red Solo cup.
I don't think you went to an actual doctor.
The more I hear about this visit, the less I think you were in the right place.
La Providencia.
Family Medical.
Yeah.
I mean, that would be if you open, like if you have an apartment next to an urgent care,
just put an urgent care sign on your apartment door.
That's free blood, free urine.
Free blood and free urine, yeah.
Well, that's heartbeat.
Free heartbeat.
You can get the tools, too.
Yeah.
up medical tool prices before. Oh yeah we did it's pretty fucking expensive.
We could do, I mean you know we chip in we all get it together. It's literally really
easy to draw blood you just have to cut somebody and take the blood out. That's
true. I mean if you want all the fancy shit they I mean they just that the tube
they have to draw blood that's the same as like a gumball machine with the track.
True. Like that's just to look cool to make you excited about the blood. It's like a silly straw from Crazy Browns.
Right yeah if you want I mean that's also that's why they that's why they it cost
so much to go to the doctor here it's because they're using all these fancy
the tubes and needles exactly a real doctor just cuts you with their canine
tooth and they let it drip out onto a napkin and they ring the napkin out into
their blood machine yeah that's why if you ever look at like if you go to like
urgent care or like the hospital you look at the medical bill silly to tax
yeah most of the of the bill yeah it is I do feel after this visit I do feel
like American health care is so expensive because the doctors have to be
sexual to you. I honestly do. Yeah. She was so in love with me dude. She diagnosed herself
with humongous boobs. I swear to God.
Man, yeah, that's the other thing. Healthcare in this country is so expensive.
It's just so expensive. I'm sure you're clapping at home. The thing about it is it just costs
so much damn money and it's due to the system as well.
Oh, you know what?
Don't get me fucking started on the system.
And Joe damn Biden is one of the guys doing it.
Yeah, well.
It's not about--
He's not allowed to talk about Joe.
It's not about the system, right?
Right.
It's about literally the factors
that influence the system. Absolutely.
Class.
Yeah.
Healthcare.
Healthcare's a huge factor in the system.
The system.
Yeah.
I mean, the system, you know,
you gotta learn the system to teach the system.
different branches of the presidential government. Here's a question you want my
you need my age, you need my weight, you need my height when I go to the doctor.
What are you gonna do build a statue of me? Well that too but also like you don't
care what my favorite color is? It's blue you don't care? You know you thought I
wouldn't notice that you're not asking me my favorite color? Right. And my
favorite time and my favorite number my favorite letter? Oh what about my favorite
food? My favorite song. My favorite song. Can you play my favorite song? It's like the
The nurse comes in, asks me for all this information,
the doctor comes in, asks me the same information again.
- Exactly.
- That is the most annoying part.
- It is, so it's, they are,
it's a conspiracy to make nurses more annoying.
- Yeah, nurse comes in, she's hot, right?
She's big and hot.
Nurse leaves, doctor comes in,
she's like the Russian nesting doll
that that nurse was sitting in before.
Looks the same, bigger, hotter, right?
She comes in, she says, "I'm gonna need 50 cc's of your cum."
50 cc I'm gonna need two double I mean 50 cc's on my two double D's yeah and
unfortunately I also need a stool sample also on my double D's if you don't mind
on my double B's my double butt cheeks I call these my double D's. How about poop on a butt?
No, I don't want to think about poop on anything. How about poop between two butt cheeks?
Unfortunately we're out of those little vials to put the stool
samples in so I'm gonna need you to put it between these two slices of bread.
yeah if you just put what do we have around here I guess we my lunchbox you
can just take you put your stool sample in my lunchbox and remember fill it to
the top this time yeah there's a fill line I just hate going to dr. poopy he
always eats my poop it's like listen buddy yeah if I could get you to put this
if I could get you to put the your urine sample into this glass here there's
already some liquid in there don't worry about it it's just a little bit of tonic
and a little bit of lemon and there's an ice cube in there too and when you're
done could you put a little umbrella and also let you know that it's ready and
also could you take the lemon twist it and rub it around the rim a little bit
that would be great I'm the doctor yeah I after you after you you know fill this
cup with your urine sample I just need you to microwave it and throw in a few
marshmallows for me would you mean would you even be mad if there was like if you
found out that there was like drinking my pee?
Well, yeah, or if you found out there was a guy who sits outside your toilet all day
eating your shit, like I wouldn't care. I just feel like...
If there was a guy eating my shit in the toilet?
If he's just eating it, that's fine.
So you know that hole that goes, the tube that goes from your toilet all the way down
the street? If he just put his mouth on that like he was like a hamster sucking his food
out?
If he was eating it right out of the tube, I'm fine with that. But if he's storing it
in any capacity, that's not okay.
Because he might clone me.
because he might take my DNA. I mean as long as he's not cloning me. Yeah that's a
good yeah that's the other thing is a lot of the a lot of the like a lot of the
doctor questions are very clone heavy. They are. So they can build a profile.
What's something that only you would know but that someone else would know to
ask you that only you would know? Yeah. Are you sexually active? Yeah. Have you ever been
cloned before? No reason. Cloned by your doctor? No reason it just doesn't work twice.
That's a, you can't clone a, are you a clone?
You actually can't clone a clone.
It's just something we have to know.
She also kept trying to make me get STD tests.
She kept being like, which I feel like
it does not reflect well on what I look like.
Like I walked in and she was like,
first SSRIs, second off,
we have to get you an HPV booster shot.
I was like, I think I'm fine, lady.
- Yeah, speaking of HPV,
list top 10 worst sounds the human body makes by Cole 33 number one vomiting I
vomit I don't like the sound of vomit I gotta be honest it doesn't if somebody
faking like making a fake vomit sound does not bother me at all but the actual
sound of vomit well I don't it's the dry heave that bothers me I think it's the
sound of the puke hitting like the like the speed it's the sound of the end of
you coming out of the body to like you there's a difference between so like
because it sounds like a cough that's shooting stuff out, you know?
And it sounds very disgusting.
Speaking of dry heaving, I was cleaning my ears yesterday.
Where is this going?
I don't know, I went too far into the ear.
You went far enough to make yourself gag?
I put the Q-tip in my ear.
Are you kidding, dude?
And I coughed and was like dry heaving.
I don't know.
Don't put Q-tips in your ears.
Why?
It's not good.
If you're going to use a Q-tip, you got to use it like around the very edge of your ear.
I was bored.
I'm going to get you a Tamagotchi.
Why?
What does that have to do with any of this?
Just would give you something to do.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
Good point.
I forgot to set up a report.
But yeah, I don't know how I made myself dry heaved cleaning my ear.
You put it so deep into your ear that it hits your nose.
And it hits your medulla oblongata.
That is not where the medulla oblongata...
Your uvula.
the he pointed to his throat I don't know what I'm a do love part of your brain
it's from the water boy very funny word though yeah here's the top comment from
blue and black midnight rose okay this is gonna be good yeah listening to someone
vomit is absolute torture one time a very long time ago a kid in my class
said he felt sick so he was sent to the bathroom and the thing is the bathroom
was right across the corner from the classroom and you could hear any body
fluid coming from people in those bathrooms I was trying to take a test and
and I heard loud gagging and gooey vomiting through the walls.
I felt so sick and ill I couldn't focus on my test anymore.
- Gooey vomiting.
- Oh, it's so gooey.
- Ooey gooey.
- I think that you--
- Yeah, well, they didn't know that it was gooey
until the vomiting guy left the bathroom
and they heard the janitor go in and go,
"It's so ooey gooey."
- And then heard like the sounds of Scooby Doo eating
or something.
- Yeah, and then heard the janitor walking and going,
(imitates vomiting)
(laughing)
I don't have a fear of vomiting.
I never would.
Oh.
I think the worst time I ever vomited, uh, I was like five years old and I got like a
uh, the Burger King had like a chicken parm.
That's, you were the dumbest five year old of all time.
I know.
It was like a Burger King, like, I don't know if it was a chicken parm, I think, I think
it was.
Chicken parm?
Yeah.
As in parmesan?
Yeah, it was like a chicken sandwich with like tomato sauce.
At Burger King.
At Burger King?
Yeah.
of those and I was like I just immediately I've never I think that's the
first time I've ever had food poisoning really because I remember the next day
just like getting up and I think I just like I had just really bad diarrhea and
then like my mom was like are you sick and I went yep then just fucking just
projectile vomit on the ground but I didn't I didn't have to go to school
which was nice one time I vomited when my dad tried to tell me that my parents
were getting divorced.
We were like, I swear to God, I was like, I was like feeling really sick coming home from
football and he was like, you know, son, we mean, I mean your mom and I'm in the front
of his Suburban.
I'm like, yeah, dad.
Yeah, what's good?
What's good?
Let me know.
He's like, you know, we've been having immediately just vomit all over his dashboard and dude,
he's never been more relieved in his life.
He's like, oh my God, kick that can down the road.
Yeah.
I'm going to skip to number two here.
two's farting. Oh, that's smelly. Come on. Yeah. There are so many variations in
sounds in farts or trumping as my Nan calls it. Whoa. I think it funny,
especially if it's quiet and someone lets out a little squeaky one it sets off
the whole office. That's bad. That's the fact that this person works in an office.
Yes. It's scaring me. I do feel, speaking of doctors, I do feel like if a doctor or
or a nurse or an EMS worker.
- What if a doctor farted?
- No.
- Let's go down that road.
If a doctor smelled one of my farts,
they would like admit me to like cedar sign.
- Yeah, there's some farts you get where it's just like,
oh, there's something wrong with you.
- You maybe don't even need to call a doctor,
you need to call a priest.
Like this is like, there's something like truly
like an ancient evil in me.
- Yeah.
- You know, like that's how I feel.
But I have not--
- Every once in a while I get one of those.
of those. She loved me so much. Yeah. She loved me down. Here's a comment. As I was
writing down this comment, I farted. My mates kicked me out of their stupid Jojo
Siwa gang just because I farted in front of them. For some particular reason, I
always fart. For some particular reason. There's a bunch of kids dressed like, like
looking like, like, was it Lisa Frank? Yeah. Yeah, looking like all dressed in
like Lisa Frank clothes bow tie yeah whatever it's like you can't hang out
with those if you're gonna be right again kid yeah they're wearing like
slings and leather jackets like like white they're like those Disney gang's
yeah yeah other jackets and they're walking around like hey we're gonna go
walk through graffiti on the side of the ball and we should start a gang like
okay we should start a Jojo see what gang we should just start like a tunnel
snakes type gang yeah yeah I mean imagine like a tunnel snakes type thing
but it's just like a picture of Jojo Siwa on the back is...
Yeah.
That's crazy.
You guys, you could just say, I mean, I just moved here and I've already picked up on this,
so I don't know if you guys, you know, if you've had any experience with this, but certain...
So you have to be really careful wearing certain colors.
Like if you wear green in the sewers, the ninja mutant turtles might run up on you.
That's a really good point.
You know, if you wear like a gray blue in the ocean, they might think you're a shark.
Yeah.
You have to be careful wearing your fin.
Your fin hat.
Yeah, your shark fin.
you don't want to wear anything rainbow and Bushwick. Definitely not.
Definitely not, dude.
These guys might think you're a part of this gang in Bushwick.
Also, Leprechaun might run up on you.
You have to be careful, too.
Pretty much anywhere in the city, if you wear transparent clothes,
the police are going to... Yeah, you definitely got to watch
what you wear. If you wear, like, for instance,
a police station, if you wear, like, a suicide vest,
vest yeah that's like a bad you're gonna get you get clapped up yeah it's like
it's real out there yeah my brother farts silently but is so stinky very very
annoying plus it smells like barf my favorite type is the cheese toasty or
the cornhole creeper the cornhole come on man the cheese toasties really bad
yeah toasty that that's like a food cornhole creeper but it's like okay
but refined to a fart as a cheese toasty.
- Why is it-- - Yeah, it's gross.
- It's nasty. - Why is it a cornhole creeper?
I've never seen-- I've seen corn, I've seen a hole, I've never seen--
I've seen corn!
I've seen a hole, I've never seen no damn cornhole creeper!
Why are you in my cornhole?
Call it a cornhole, because corn's the only thing that comes out of it!
Everything else is just a brown sludge! Corn!
Intact!
It's my cornhole!
*laughter*
But like, does the name-
That's my new character, Poop Seinfeld, by the way.
Poop Seinfeld.
I've heard the word cornhole, but I've never like-
Like, cause it's-
Obviously it's-
derived from a thing that's called a
cornhole.
Is it just-
What is a cornhole?
A cornhole is the game, right?
It's the game where you throw the bean bags.
Cornhole is the game where you throw a beanie baggie baby across the world into the hole.
Not work, not work.
You guys know I have a hard time saying stuff sometimes.
You just leave me alone.
Across the fucking Mission BBQ parking lot you throw a fucking bean bag.
And you try to get in there.
Why is it called a bean bag? Is it because it's a bag full of beans?
Is it a bag full of beans? Is it these bags?
Well Jay, I'm hungry, I might have to split one open.
I might have to eat the beans.
I think every toy should have food in it!
And after that, I'm gonna go eat the corn out of the hole!
*laughter*
Jerry, you don't want to do that.
No! Let me see your corn hole! I wanna eat the corn out of it!
I put my hand in the hole!
Let me put my bean bag in your corn hole!
He's a disgusting monster.
Yeah, it's okay. It's a corn hole
where you throw a bean bag?
Yeah. Wait, what?
Excuse you! While you're drinking beer?
*laughter*
What's next, a pizza penis?
What's up with these food metaphors?
What's next am I gonna park my bread car in your soup garage?
What am I gonna do get on the french fry subway?
Why don't I just sit down on my peanut butter chair?
Jerry that is that is an actual peanut butter. I know I'm gonna peanut butter chair. I made it at home
it feels warm it's all feels good it molds my body it's like a temper panic
it's so what's the deal with calling it food and poop Seinfeld now is the new
version what is this you put the poop
put the food in your mouth and it becomes poop
My poop up my butt I'll burp up a cheeseburger. I don't think so
Jerry the left side of your face is
Burning toast Jerry
(laughing)
- Cheeseburger butler.
- Yeah and then like some--
- Jerry that's the greatest idea you've ever had.
- Some like assistant comes in and just like
shoots Botox in his face as normal again.
Like this happens everyday.
Yeah that's just what he does.
He just starts, if you mention emojis
he just starts doing this at some point.
- Texting!
Emoji me no me
This poop is smiling why is he smiling it makes no sense?
Why would poop smile? Thank you. It comes out of my body. I have a smile
If you were happy would you wake up every morning with a smile on your face?
I don't think so
If you poop happy
frowning
They should make a smell so bad. They should make a frowning poop. They should how they not made a frowning
Gonna take me 10 minutes to get out of the voice
Maybe snoggin his voice for a couple minutes. Yeah number three snoring
My aunt Dottie has super loud snoring and I woke up one time when I was sleeping with her on a vacation
And I couldn't go back to sleep because she was snoring so loudly snoring. That's not like that bad a sound
So I even with your on man, what you?
What are you doing baby boy? What is that about man?
She better be warm as hell!
My snoring is pretty bad.
Really?
It's bad but it's not a disgusting...
I mean I talked about this like last episode.
Just how bad it is.
Yeah we already talked about snoring.
Yeah fuck snoring!
But yeah whenever I snore it sounds like I'm dying.
Yeah number four, chewing.
Chewing...
Are you get disturbed when people chew with their mouth open?
I don't give a fuck.
It just depends. If I'm already like stressed out or like if I'm if I'm annoyed already by something
It'll piss me off. If it's someone that annoys me and I can like pick apart like why they're annoying me
Right, and they're like chewing super loud with their mouth open. They just like got food all over their face
I'm just like you just fucking stop. Yeah, but like in general doesn't it doesn't bother me like immediately
Yeah, like maybe if it's like chewing and there's like a few snorts in there
I could never, you know, somebody's eating like an actual pig like that that kind of bothers me
But I mean if they're chewing with their mouth open like talking with food in their mouth
I don't care. You know what I sound
I don't like when people are eating if somebody bites the fork when they're eating but they like pull their teeth on the floor
What are you doing? Why would you do that?
T thing is so just there's no there's no reason that you're not gonna human mouth is one of the most disgusting
Doesn't taste very good
Leave it at that. It doesn't
Don't taste like food
Hey, you'll be able to pop off your teeth eat it like gum
We're just doing time for made of food again now remember that yeah, I felt made of food
What's this a cry gave me my full tooth you only give me a quarter that could be one that could be one yeah
maybe Jerry Seinfeld talking about food is so funny. It's very funny.
Just food though. Just food. Any food Seinfeld is so good to me. Yeah. Because like the
idea that he is confused by like food. Just like the thing that everyone is always
eating and it and makes sense to everyone. What's the deal with the
gingerbread house? It's not a house and it's not made of gingerbread.
(laughing)
- What's a cheese booger?
I've never had a cheese booger.
Everyone's always eating these damn boogers
and cheese boogers.
- Where's the sand on my sandwich?
I don't know how to get the food into my belly.
- I like the--
- I wish I just had a hole in my stomach,
then I can put the food in there.
- That's a very good idea actually.
It's efficient.
That's just--
(laughing)
- Colossomy bag?
- Yeah, colossomy bag.
this kind of fucked up yeah yeah I think maybe I mean worse sound a human body
can make probably a colostomy bag emptying oh yeah yeah that's it that's
not the human body anymore though no that's the worst that we're sleeping on
the realm of I'm gonna hit you with a knowledge bomb right now we're sound a
human body can make your true love saying I hate you it's true I'd probably
say Justin Bieber singing but that's just me maybe you guys are girls I mean
Yeah, number five, screaming.
Hello.
No comments at all on screaming.
I mean, screaming is--
Screaming's a cool sound.
Yeah.
Screaming always makes me laugh.
True.
Really?
Every time.
No matter the context.
OK.
No, but a scream is a very funny sound, I think.
Sometimes it makes me scared.
When I'm doing it, it makes me scared.
Yeah.
Yeah, when I hear myself screaming, that's pretty scary.
But if I'm hanging out with someone, they just scream.
It's like, that's very funny.
When I hear a scream on the subway, I get scared.
Yeah, that's scary.
Like, in the train station.
I was like, do you remember that one time in Boston
when I was fully convinced that there was a mass shooting
on the train tracks or something,
and it was just snow falling off of a train?
But the snow fell off of the train
in this huge, insanely rattling, loud sound.
And then a lady goes, "Ah!"
So everyone just starts, the guy closest starts running,
and then the people that he runs by start running,
and then now it's like that mobile game
that you get ads for where one guy is running
and he picks up all these groups.
And so I just started running and a lady
was like immediately out of breath
and going up like two flights of stairs.
She's like, "What are we running from?"
I was like, "I don't know.
(laughing)
"I don't know."
And then we got up and then we were just like
got our breaths and kind of acknowledge each other.
And then just, we just both just like
we didn't try to call the cops or anything.
Completely convinced there was a mass shooting going on.
Just leave.
- Yeah, just get out of there.
- But screaming in like that in public,
you always are, I always assume I'm like
somebody is being
uh... attacked
and i'm always also immediately surprised because i'm like
i'm not doing anything and i don't know if we are not going to also i feel like
every time i hear a scream and i think someone is being attacked or dying and i
go like look at the window or like like run the look around the corner it's
always just like a kid
like playing with the yeah i was just about to say it was like a kid like
running and playing with his friends
i was at blue park the other day
and like i just started hearing like it was like
you know like
eight o'clock so it's starting to get dark.
And they do it like ten times in a row too.
They were like running down the street and the screaming's getting louder.
And they're saying, "You're killing me!"
Right.
"You're so funny!"
They're like running down the street so the screaming's getting louder.
I was just sitting, I was like covered in sweat just kind of like sitting there trying
to cool off and all I could hear was just like, "Ahh!
Ahh!"
Like, "Oh fuck, someone's getting killed!"
You should not be able to scream on the street unless you have a license for it.
Absolutely.
This is my screamer's license.
I think if you are you have to go take a test to see how funny you are.
It should just be like alcohol you have to be 21 to scream.
I agree.
That would solve the issue.
Because a lot of these kids are screaming way too young.
Exactly.
It messes with their, it stunts their brain growth.
And then also they get to our age they have that fucking tracheotomy box and they scream
too much.
I would love to get one of those.
They have a Darth Vader voice modulator to help them speak.
They're always going "Hooober."
You know how kids be, they be saying "Hoober."
Kiss me on the Darth Vader shit these days.
Yeah, Darth Vader be saying "Hobur".
Yeah.
Number six, burping.
Burping, um...
I think I've like...
I think I actually don't like the sound of burping sometimes.
Really?
Yeah, I mean it's always funny, but like...
Yeah, I mean, shrek.
Shrek.
I don't care about burping really either way at all.
I don't think it makes me happy or sad.
I never realized burps smell.
Dude, I was just about to say that.
say that a burp is worse than a fart, worse than a shit, worse than a piss, worse than
a cum and a spit and a smell and a poop.
I don't think it's that bad.
It's worse than all those.
I just think like, like getting burped in the face, somebody burps in your face.
I think if somebody like, yeah, I think ultimate disrespect, you're walking down the street,
a guy just comes up to you, burps in your face.
I might have to like immediately.
If you don't kill that person on the spot, you're a pussy.
I would punch bone splinters into their brain immediately.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would probably immediately like...
Why are you laughing?
I'd probably do like a finger punch like in Kill Bill.
Just like burst right through their chest, probably pull their heart out.
Yeah.
Probably like give it to a kid who needs it.
A kid who needs a heart transplant immediately.
I might just like...
Copy them off from Temple of Doom.
I might just literally just rip them apart completely and just shred them.
I might do that.
You burp at me, I'm shredding you.
Yeah, absolutely.
You're getting threshed.
Yeah, I might pick them up over my head and run around looking for a woodchipper and it
takes me like an hour and then you're just completely out of breath.
What am I doing this for?
What happened again?
I never learned to burp as a kid.
I couldn't like belch because I didn't drink soda or anything.
I also never ate all that much food.
I never eat a lot of food and you burp so.
I don't think I've ever burped from eating.
I never did eat that much food growing up.
I just wasn't really into it really.
Genuinely that is how I live my life nowadays is that I'm just not that into eating food.
It's just such a funny thing to say.
It's true.
Yeah, I didn't eat that much food growing up.
This wasn't for me. Not even like, "Oh, I was too poor to eat."
It was just like, "I just didn't want it."
I mean, it was all around. I lived it. It was basically Thanksgiving every day.
I mean, the thing is, you put food in your mouth and after one chew, it's like, "I'm done with this. I want this gone."
Oh, do you really?
I want this in my stomach immediately. I want the taste. I do not...
That keeps happening. I keep, like, chewing.
You're, like, I'm getting so old now.
I hate the texture of food so much.
Like, I'll order Chinese food and then, like, three or four bites in, I'll just, like...
Yeah, it's like, "Fuck this, dude."
I'm like, "Ah, I can't fucking finish this at all."
Yeah, like used to be an absolute monster truck dude. Yeah, I was I you could you fucking used to watch me
Just eat just insane shit. You should be fries fries not with the meal, but fries as an extra side order kind of guy
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, I mean I worked at a I mean I worked at restaurants and I'll just get like discounted meals
So just come to like like your apartment because you lived right down the street from that Clover
So I'd get like my discount at Clover and like show up with like, oh, yeah, they got apple fritters there
So I'd show up with like this gigantic sandwich, an order of fries, like a drink that's like
just all sugar and then like apple fritters or like a side salad and I'd just sit there
and just eat all that in your apartment.
It's pretty beautiful times.
Oh dude.
That was, I mean still, if I could have that meal right now, I'd fucking.
Dude, I honestly, the thing is like I'm not sure that like, like being fat sucks in a
lot of ways, but also just like not caring and eating anything you want almost
outweighs the bad things about being fat. Which I still do, but I think I just
like exercise a little bit now. So now it's like I'm fine. I'm trying to get
absolutely ripped right now. I'm eating disgusting things right now. I have that thought that I should get
insanely ripped because it would be funny. It would not be funny. As soon
as I start working out. Everybody who has the thought of
like it would be so funny if I got ripped. It's not that it would be funny, it's you
want to be ripped.
Yeah.
Well, no.
You would be too good looking, I think, if you got ripped.
Really?
Yeah.
Probably.
Yeah, it'd be upsetting.
Yeah.
That's why I don't do it.
Me, it's funny. I look like a Prometheus alien if I get any muscles.
Yeah.
But if you did it, you'd look like a super movie star, Hollywood style, Bollywood style.
Bollywood style?
Wow.
They have beautiful people there.
They do.
Anytime.
I do you know there's like AI like what what celebrity do you look like yeah it's
always like 15 different like Bollywood guys yeah we talked about yeah I just
look like the squirtle of like a David Krumholz blastoise yeah that's what I
look like I would love to get really ripped but I can't even play a video
game that I enjoy for more than like 20 minutes yeah like my brain like not like
I could never do something that I have to do yeah I just would never yeah I
I fuckin' I, Gus gave me like a workout plan and I fuckin'
- Yeah, no, nothing.
- I can't, like I did it for like two days
and I was just like, oh, I'm like,
I just wanna skate, that's it.
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean it's not fun. - I still have that workout
but I might just do that but who knows.
- I've been going to the gym man,
it's the worst shit ever.
- Oh, I fuckin' hate it. - It sucks, dude.
- I hate going to the gym.
You go, you sit, you wait for everything.
Yeah.
So many fucking people there.
The other day I was there, there's just like insanely autistic, like really old guy there,
who was just like walking around, like doing the machines, like rattling and talking to himself.
And then I walked by him, and he said, "Shove it up your ass, you Nazi piece of shit."
[Laughter]
And I was like, "Holy shit, dude."
I was like, "What the, where the fuck is this coming from, dude?"
I'm being persecuted as a bald man.
Yeah.
It's fucked up, dude.
By this fucking guy.
And he was like an old white dude.
You could have cleaned his clock.
I could have.
You should have.
I'm not going to suck his dick, dude.
What are you talking about?
It's fucking weird.
I don't know.
There is a shower there.
There is a shower.
He seemed like the kind of old man who mostly goes there because it's an easier place.
There he can shower around people, so if he falls, someone sees it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not a bad idea.
Oh, I fell.
Oh, someone needs to pick me up.
Oh, I fell in here.
Penis first.
Yeah, that's not a rope.
- Oh, penis first. - Yeah, that's not a rope.
(laughing)
- Oh no, I dropped all of my soaps.
I'm too old to pick it up.
- It's like any communal shower is like prison.
- Yeah. - He's like, oh.
- Things happen to any communal shower.
- Just turns into prison, he's like, it's like prison.
I drop my soap and I get to have sex.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - Number seven is hiccuping.
- Hiccuping is disgusting.
- I hate hiccups. - You think so?
- Really? - I hate getting hiccups.
- I don't like getting them, but I don't care about hearing them.
- Getting hiccups is one of those times when I'm like,
if I had a button that would painlessly end my life,
I would press it right now.
- It's like that, have you ever heard that interview,
like George Clooney, apparently,
he broke his spine or something,
or had some spine thing,
and he was like, "I almost killed myself."
That's how I get, any time I get the hiccups.
It's like, I could seriously end my life right now,
and I would die.
- I'd be content.
- I would die happy.
It would be the only relief I've ever had.
- Exactly.
- Here's a great story.
Hiccup is embarrassing plus very funny. If you don't believe me then guess what?
When it was my birthday and birthday party, everyone came and we put a Bremen cheesecake and a melted chocolate cake. Yum!
Instead of everyone saying happy birthday, everyone told me to sing a solo and everyone else clapped for me.
But something happened, which was when I began to sing, I hiccup again and again,
and everyone thought I was singing so they didn't notice I was actually hiccuping.
So everyone clapped while I was hiccuping. In the end of my hiccup, I told everyone I was hiccuping. Haha.
Laugh out loud!
That's quite the story.
Yeah.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe it happened.
I would never confuse hiccuping for singing.
No.
That is very funny.
I'm a bit of a smart man.
Happy birthday.
I don't know.
I'm going to give myself hiccups.
I'm terrified.
Yeah, I don't want to fucking...
I will say I never have hiccups in the times when I shouldn't have hiccups.
I don't think I've had hiccups in an insanely long time.
I've never had hiccups before like stand up or something.
Something where I had to like talk and could not have hiccups.
I think that would be the end of my life probably.
I mean you know those, do you ever read like in the like Guinness Book of World Records
it always be like there's a woman who hiccuped for five years straight.
That's the best thing in the Guinness Book of World Records is when they have like, it's
like this is the guy who jumps the highest.
Yeah and this is the guy who lives in the most misery.
And this is the ugliest fucker in the world.
Yeah.
The world's ugliest dog.
Yeah here's the world's ugliest woman, she doesn't know we took this picture.
It's so awesome.
I took this photo on the train.
Yeah.
- Imagine submitting your photo
to the Guinness Book of World Records
and being like, I'm applying for the ugliest woman ever record
like at least maybe I can get this.
And they're like, sorry, you're not ugly enough.
You're still like living the worst.
- Come on. - Please, come on.
- You don't mean that.
- Yeah, not ugly enough for ugliest woman ever.
- You actually just won the award for most beautiful.
- You're kidding.
Are you serious?
- Yeah, and then you see that it was your mailman
who was opening your letters and was giving you that award.
- He's signing everything Guinness.
That's his name.
- Yeah.
- And hit me after beer.
- Is it, it's not the Guinness World Records,
it's not like the Michelin thing?
- I don't know.
- The book is made of beer.
- I was just thinking it could be the Michelin thing.
I don't know.
- Yeah, it could be made by Michelin.
- Which like, you know, everyone found out.
- That one freaked me out.
- Yeah, everyone found that out at the same time,
even though it's like, you know, public knowledge forever,
but then it became like a whole Twitter thing
where it's like--
- Yeah, what do they, whoa, like did you know
that it's the Michelin is actually the tires?
- They give these food, the food, the best food
It's also that beer that old ladies always buy too.
Yeah, Michelin beer.
Yeah.
True.
Michelin Extra.
Michelin Ultra.
That would be funny if Michelin just gives it...
Michelob Ultra is a good beer so I wouldn't get it.
The only person I ever saw buy Michelob Ultra in the... when I worked at the liquor store
was a really really old lady with a lot of plastic surgery.
Yeah.
And that is-
Yeah, it's the latest beer.
O'Tools is not the official beer of the PGA.
Yes it is.
The Michelob Ultra is, dude.
No, no, look it up. O'Tools-
Are you fucking disabled?
It's- they don't have- you're not supposed to- there's not-
I'm sorry, that was too far.
What the-
O'Tools- they wouldn't have a non-alcoholic beer.
Yeah, they do.
No, they wouldn't.
It's on the cans.
Remember I was like, drinking O'Tools for a while?
Michelob Ultra!
No!
Official beer, dude!
Dude, O'Doul's, because nobody ever buys them
or looks at the label, they can just say whatever they want.
- Look, O'Doul's can--
- Official non-alcohol, official soda of the PGA maybe.
- The other official, maybe it says the unofficial beer.
Maybe I misread it. - I mean, that was like
the funniest like five months,
where I was just like drinking like O'Doul's and shit.
- It was so fun. - I was like,
"Oh, I'm gonna be like the most sober guy in the world."
- It's also really funny to be like quitting alcohol
and instead of dropping that like, you know, extra calories,
you're drinking 1200 calories of soda that tastes like beer every night.
That is so funny.
Yeah.
I stopped drinking like O'Doul's and shit just after like...
It's terrible.
Oh yeah, no, I switched to just like drinking like Polar's and shit, but like it was so
for like the...
I don't know.
Like I...
Let's not get into this, but...
Number eight, grinding teeth.
I'm sorry I called you disabled, but could you do a jumping jack please?
(laughing)
- Grinding teeth is gross. - Boring.
- Number nine, choking.
- Sometimes I grind my teeth and I hear my teeth crunch.
- Yeah. - It's pretty bad.
- I have so many cracked teeth just 'cause I grind my teeth
so much in my sleep. - All my teeth
are completely flat.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I told you guys I have a bunch of teeth falling out
and dreams about one specific tooth in my mouth.
- You need to encase that thing in gold.
- Yeah, probably.
- That's the only way to save it.
- I'm really afraid that something's gonna happen to it.
I don't know why I keep having dreams about it.
- All right, well I'm gonna tell you right now
because you told me this, I'm gonna do something.
- Don't do anything to my tooth, please.
- I'm gonna do something to it.
- That is like my worst nightmare, that tooth.
- I'm gonna dress up.
- Because I keep having nightmares about it.
- I'm gonna dress up like a tooth fairy ballerina
and I'm gonna sneak into your house.
- Don't do that, seriously don't do that.
But if it's enough money that you're putting
under my pillow, you can do that.
- And if I look like enough of a slutty tooth fairy?
- The tooth fairy's not slutty.
- Are you kidding me?
- She's doing her job.
- That's a Halloween costume I don't think I've ever seen.
tooth fairy tooth fairy well yeah cuz when the rocks on time why would I do a
slutty version of their slutty Santa well Santa hangs out I mean for sexy
Santa gives everyone fucking presents no plus people do plus people do slutty
cats and they hang out with mice all the time which is basically a baby and they
do was it slutty everything is so I'm gonna dress up as slutty Charlie Brown
What is that? I've seen that they have slutty Charlie Brown. Yeah
Words just like I think you know Charlie Brown a slut
He's a kid he's a damn four-year-old you can't have sex he's a baby well, I'm Jerry Seinfeld
Charlie Brown is a slut and he's younger than me.
Do you know how to make me into a cartoon?
Did you ever read his Jerry Seinfeld's Halloween book?
What was it? He wrote a children's book about Halloween.
And I read that shit. I took that out of the library so many times.
Because it took you so long to read it? Yeah.
Reading two pages at a time. I'm going to need to extend my
I spend my borrow on this.
Yeah.
I miss the library, dude.
I do too.
I spent so much time in the library as a kid.
I'm sure you wouldn't be able to guess that, but I loved riding my bike to the library
and just hanging out there, dude.
I myself.
Yeah, and you print out pictures of like Godzilla.
I wouldn't even go on the computers.
That's how fucked.
Whoa.
I would just sit there and read the books, dude.
I was crazy.
I only went to the library to take out CDs as a kid.
Yeah, that's sick that they had CDs.
They have movies there too.
- They had VHS when I was growing up.
- When I found out the library had music and DVDs and shit.
- They did have video games in the library in Watertown.
The one--
- Fucking crazy man.
- Yeah.
- Each library they had Quadrophenia.
- But I wasn't allowed to take them out
and also I didn't own a video game console.
- You should be able to get drugs from the library now.
- You should.
You have to return them though.
- Yeah.
- You should still mark in at the library.
- They should.
- That's actually, you know what, not a--
- That's a great idea actually.
- That's actually not a bad idea.
a bad idea. It's like a genius idea. Yeah, but you still have to return it. Yeah, I know.
I forgot about the return policy. Yeah. Yeah, you have to return it and if you return it
like damaged or used, you get fined $10,000. I think I want to be the first guy to get
addicted to Narcan or to methadone, like one of those like get off of heroin things. I
I think that is...
I think I could do that.
It feels like it has to be pretty good, right?
Yeah.
It's pretty easy to get addicted to anything.
It is.
Yeah.
All you have to do is do it a bunch.
I had coffee today for the first time in weeks.
Oh, really?
I feel amazing.
I drank two Yerbas.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
I've been having...
I've been cutting down all caffeine.
I had...
And then my doctor was like, "Your heart is slow."
So now I have to pump up my caffeine, I feel like.
Your heart's too slow.
Yeah.
today that is a womanly trait tired well that was just what was in the pot and I
didn't want to like make another half cup like that's a male trait yeah being lazy
well that's there's no but why would I make half a cup worth we'll just make
coffee cups worth and then just have one cup and then you invite over three
friends and then they can all have a cup of coffee yeah I should have done that
that
Girls weren't loud and annoying enough.
(laughter)
Fucking queefing all the time.
Are you serious?
First you're going to nag me about the dishes, now you're going to do this?
Collecting phlegm in your mouth is so gross.
I will say.
I mean, as somebody who's sucking it up.
You do that constantly.
I have to. I have too much phlegm.
That's literally, you do that every five minutes.
Take a damn Zyrtec, brother.
Maybe I gotta take Mucinex.
Take a damn Mucinex.
yeah maybe that's it that is it crying is annoying cries yeah crying sucks dude if
I see someone I mean I hate when people wait wait hold on number 23 noise your
back makes when laying on a wooden floor and making your body no you're missing
important word on a wooden floor and making your body go up and down I know
that exact same I do know that sound yeah it's like it's like a it's like an
armpit fart but yeah your whole your whole back that the like arch of your
back uh-huh it's pretty cool number 24 is kissing or the comment is especially
grown-ups repeatedly kissing babies over and over again I yeah I mean people
kissing is not a good sound no yeah so yeah the mouth is the most disgusting
part in the body yeah I mean it's like like yeah I think it might be the the
poopy but people kissing said you know when people like a little mouth touching
a butt that's well that's pretty gross yeah well let's think of gross throw
What's the most disgusting sound with this new knowledge that we have that the human body could feasibly make?
Probably like if you like burped out your fart well and your back was on the ground.
What if every time you popped a pimple it made like a...
Well, it also has to be contextual, right?
What about like this sound?
That's gross.
Like, okay, so like vomiting.
Like you wouldn't know it was vomit hitting the water unless you saw the person vomiting.
So maybe if you watch somebody eat a piece of shit and then afterwards they go, "Yum!"
That might be pretty disgusting.
Yeah, that might be more like twisted or like subversive.
I would go, it would be subversive.
That person would be an artist.
It's a very good point.
It'd be Maria Abramovich.
That should be her new next thing, just eat shit.
And say, "Yum!"
important that's why it's a subversion.
Actually it's they do here's it's
actually critiquing capitalism because
you know she does Red Robin. Yum!
And people would go oh my god yeah she's a
genius. That is artistic.
Okay bye. Bye.