You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're a crap monster.
[LAUGHTER]
[EXPLOSION]
Yeah, we are now.
I'm just imagining you and Pat fucking in a hot tub at a hotel.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah.
Well, it's like one of those pools
where you have to reserve it.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, really?
That place was crazy.
Your room at that place was like--
Yeah.
That fucked me up so bad.
I like went in and I was like, what the hell?
Like the bathroom was so cool.
Like.
- It had a cool bathroom.
- Dude, it was like cool bathroom.
- It made me wanna get a better bathroom in my real life.
- I don't know.
- I wanna like a sex, I wanna sex bathroom.
- So a place where you can have like,
when rich people talk about like having sex in the shower,
you're like, yeah, okay, I get it.
You have like room in your shower.
- Right, yeah.
- My shower, like I would die like an old person.
I'd like fall over and hit my head
and then be in the hospital, I'd be terrible.
- Yeah. - Probably a coma.
- I would never have sex in the shower.
- Yeah. - Dude.
- I bought a bed, like an expensive-ish bed.
- Yeah. - You know what I mean?
- Yeah. (laughs)
It's working.
- And also, the water is orange in my shower.
(all laughing)
I'm not like, "Yo, baby, let's go to the orange,"
you know that orange, you know the fuckin'
like Gatorade that you grab in the shower?
- Say, "So who loves orange soda?"
(all laughing)
- You'd be like, "Yo, come on."
Say oh yeah like the Kool-Aid man, fuck you and the orange juice.
I love it when you remember the 90s.
Mm-hmm.
Just stepping on just shampoo bottles over and over and over, squirting across the bathtub.
I start using like my dandruff shampoo as lube and stuff.
Ow, dude, fuck.
It stings, dude.
Do you have like grimy floors in the shower?
Oh yeah.
I feel like your feet get dirtier.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
I get out of the shower with like black like pig pen feet.
It's really fucked up.
I just had to replace the shower mat pretty recently,
because I shaved my dick and balls in the shower.
Wow.
And there was so much hair in it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I did.
Yeah, we get manscaped ads on our pod, so I get free manscaped.
Oh, shit.
And so I put that shit to use.
And then I got--
I think it was like a night where I was like--
I had like a 7am flight so I was like, "Alright."
I was like, "Addy'd out."
I was like, "Time to put the manscape to work."
I mean, 4am, that's the best thing to do.
And then it was like one of those situations where you finish and you're like, "Oh, it's
too much."
Yeah.
You shave your dick and balls and then you're like, "Oh, wait a second.
I have a child's cock in my hand."
you call you you call the cops on yourself you think that you're holding a
child's dick and balls
yeah you think you got like reverse I'd love to see my bathtub's full of hair I
I would love to see Pat like versus the Manscaped kit like a like a Tyson. Oh
yeah. It's already way too like like even then like doing it in the like
shaving my shit in the shower just like I was like oh this is like this is gonna
take like. Oh well yeah yeah cuz you're like a hairy guy. I'm hairy as shit. I'm kind of like
you wouldn't think like my arms and legs are like pretty hairless. Yeah. But then
And if you like saw me with my shirt off, you'd be like, you shouldn't have that much.
Do you know it's like a weird patch here.
I kind of just, oh, that's nothing I got.
No, but I like this is a sweater.
Oh, you did the whole thing.
I like really.
I really man's guess.
Yeah.
I know somebody whose dad shaves his entire body every single morning.
Well, like,
when his dad shaves his son's
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's a beautiful, I mean I think it's beautiful.
I wish I had that kind of mom with my dad.
- Father and son by Katzke.
- Just like your dad when he turned 13,
he's like, son, come to the bathroom,
I'm gonna teach you how to shave.
You start at your legs,
(laughing)
square into your body, including your penis.
- That's what it's like, even on vacation,
he doesn't give it a break?
- I think seven days a week, dude.
- Every day.
- All the time.
- Getting a beer with your dad when you're like 24,
you're like why didn't you ever shave me? That's what Cats in the Cradle is all about.
I'm gonna shave my son real soon. I shouldn't have put all those skateboards there.
Oh yeah we're in your room. Is this always where you record? Yeah. Well when we're here
I mean. No because the last time like it. When Cam visits New York but he lives here
now. We've recorded here once. Oh yeah I heard you just moved here. I just moved here yesterday.
Yeah, this is yeah, we're in your we're all in your room my tiny little
apartment
On the pod not really. No you're sitting
Cam's on my bed. Yeah
Don't don't say any details about Patrick's room cuz somebody's gonna build a doom wad of it. Yeah
It's gonna lie awake. It's not enough for you Brandon. I love it. No, I love I love
recording a movie
I
Love being here at 22
22 stop Street
That's too much already
Too much no, that's gonna freak me out
How many 22's do you think there are?
in New York City. Stop saying the number! Not even the number! It's not allowed. How old
were you two years ago? Huh? How old were you two years ago? Stop! I just want to know
some facts about my friend. Is that so wrong? God damn. No, that's like, oh fuck. Okay, it's
23. Okay, it's 23. Stop putting the number in! If we say the wrong number now, can we
say the name of the street.
I have all my skateboards next to the camera and one of them is going to fall over.
You have a big pile of, yeah, a bunch of, all of your worldly possessions.
I am so bad at organization.
This is a bad spot for the skateboards, but don't you normally keep them behind your door
so if you open your door more than halfway they all fall
well i'm trying to figure out a new spot to put them
you got a good uh... nice little uh... dvd
oh yeah i have uh...
this is a combat tai chi
oh yeah that is a good one
we had a i think we had a very
uh... similar cultural diet
we we were talking about this last night
was that last night? or two nights ago
fuck it's all put together
oh come on now
Oh, and we all, oh, we were all hanging out.
Yeah.
We went to, oh, what was that fucking, that Russian samovar?
Yeah, yeah.
I was so mad at you.
Oh yeah, I'm so sorry.
Honestly.
Like, I was like, we were hanging out and I was like, oh, Brandon's cool, like, this
is fun.
And then he took me there and I was like, well, this is where, there were a lot of,
that's where, oh, hello.
What's going on?
Yeah, it's fine.
People can fucking read the title.
People have read the title.
That's true.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, we went to, well, I got, I don't know that I'm going to be able to do this,
That was where everybody we'd make you feel like there's so many people.
Did it make you feel like you were in L.A.
because it was full of evil people?
Right. Demonic.
Yeah. Felix was like, yeah, this is it's a bunch of people that are like networking,
but unemployed. Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Like it was all like sort of, yeah, godless hedonists.
Yeah, it was bad.
Dude, there's so many drinks too much.
They were so expensive. I bought me and Brandon.
I got you a tequila soda, a gin and tonic.
and immediately as I turn around,
dude just fucking knocks it out of my hand
and didn't even offer to buy me another one.
- $20 drink. - I was just so fucking mad.
I was like pacing back and forth in that back room.
Like, "What? He didn't even fucking offer a peg!"
- Yeah. - "Here's a couple of..."
"Here's like $20! He didn't even fucking offer!"
A schoolyard bully lunch tray smacks the shit out of your hand.
"What? It was your drink too!"
Which I felt like such an asshole about.
Yeah, but I gave you...
- Oh yeah, you gave me... - ...a 20.
But no, that was like a...
Well, it was like just late it was like late it was late and that was like where people I knew
Yeah, we're like we got there had friends there. Yeah, we got there and there's like a piano there and they were playing
Fuck you can't get what you want by Joe Jackson and like you can just hear that like they're like
I noticed like the dudes like DJing but it's like the DJ equipments on top of this piano
Right like every 10 minutes. He stands up and just tried to play
and he just wasn't like, he was literally like a kid hitting the keyboard.
So it's just like this dude in a suit just like, "No, no, no, no, no!"
Like, over like that song.
It's just kind of like pressing the pedals as well.
And that song, that song's like a really like fast like slap bass like eight like new wave song.
It's just like, I like I was talking, I met with, Clark was there and like I'm talking to Clark and the whole time I'm just like,
"Alright, I can't talk, what the fuck is that guy? What is he doing?"
It's like, "Oh yeah, I guess people sing here too."
Oh yeah, it was like different levels.
Yeah.
Everybody was on the floor.
Almost like hell.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That was, yeah, I didn't mean to lead you astray.
It's okay.
If you-
If all the like marks of like a bad bar were like the bartender is like having way too
good of a time.
Right.
That is a bad, that's a bad sign.
Like if the bartender is like fucked up and dancing, that's going to be a $45 gin and
tonic.
Right.
He's not putting any fucking well gin in there.
No.
the shelves to start at his chest that's it yeah no it's definitely a scene yeah
that was that scary I went I went out onto the roof and I had like asked to
bum a cig from somebody and he just immediately just started making fun of
me and I was just like I forget exactly yeah he started making fun of me for
shit and like I don't know like I recognize somebody there and it's like
talking to them like somebody I've met at like a like a friend's house one time
I was like mm-hmm she was like asking me for like her like like Instagram or
whatever it's like oh do you have like Twitter or whatever and like the guy was
like Oh Patrick likes Twitter and I was like oh what the fuck yeah he wasn't
making fun of you it was nice of him he said it immediately went all right you
know you got me pretty good yeah that's pretty how did why did he say that
Because you asked about a girl's Twitter or what?
Wait, you asked about a girl's Twitter?
You tell people about your...
I don't tell people about my Twitter.
I was just saying like, you know, it's like...
You say when somebody asks if you have Twitter, you go, "No."
I don't know.
There's...
I promise I don't.
I was pretty fucked up.
I really don't remember what I said.
Yeah.
But...
You definitely, at some...
You definitely at some point have been like, "I guess I'm on Twitter."
I know.
Come on now.
I've seen what you've done.
I've done it.
What you forgot is that you went up to that guy to buy him a cigarette and you held up
your phone and went, "Look how many followers I have.
Give me a cigarette now."
That's what you did that you forgot.
I can't explain to people what I do because I have a podcast and I just say stupid shit
online.
Just say you're in the military.
I should start doing that instead.
It's like the easiest, because nobody cares.
Just say something like, say a job that nobody will ever ask about, you know?
Military.
I'm in the Peace Corps.
Author.
Yeah.
Right.
Say that you wrote Brief and Wondrous Life of Oscar Wilde.
Well, that's the thing, like, those, the people that I was talking to on the, that
roof were like, "Oh, I'm a writer," or like, you know, like, just shit like that.
No, that's-
It's like, "Oh, like, I don't, like, I don't know what I do.
I don't do stand-up anymore, so I can't be like, 'Oh, I'm a comedian,' because I'm just
like-"
"I'm an evil murderer."
Yeah.
I'm a monster. I'm the worst person in the world. Which I mean you know if I'm saying
on my Twitter it's not super rough. I'm your worst fucking nightmare. I'm from hell.
Take all of his cigarettes. I think if someone asks you for a cigarette you should be able to be like
yeah fat ass like no problem. You should be able to do that one for each cigarette.
You get one kind of rib.
Yeah, if he gives you one cigarette, he should also be allowed to give you one titty twister?
Yeah, one purple nurple. You should have to smell his shoe.
He should have to take his shoe off.
And you should have to take a deep whiff.
You have to look at his, the circle.
I know what you're doing. I'm not going to look at it, Pat.
No, I'm sorry. You're not going to give me a...
I'm not, you know, just don't worry about it.
What?
Just, I, the thing, you know what you're doing.
Oh, you dropped, um...
You dropped this circle of my finger. Yeah, I got you.
Yeah, Patrick's doing the white power sign.
Oh, I forgot that they changed that. You know why that changed?
Because some nerd, that happened to him too many times. He's like, "You know that's white power!"
And then that guy like saved
so many people from getting dead on him.
Yeah, that was definitely a party where there was a lot of
lot of people there that are like yeah I'm I'm trad calf yeah yeah yeah I mean
yes you know that was that was in Lower East Side or yeah it was a lot of oh god
you know that yeah a lot of you know like Chinatown kids yeah yeah the dime square
as they call it what's what's your problem with these people yeah that's
such a it's such like saying that there were trad calf people at a party to me as
as like as like nonsensical as being like yeah there's a lot of like bloods and
crypts. I feel like that is a very specific to New York. I mean I guess it's just a weird
like niche part of the internet. It's not just New York but it feels
like a very New York thing. Fucking like 22 year olds.
Who are like I love Christ. Yeah like they stopped drinking for like two weeks.
they're like two weeks I was actually saved yeah they're like but then they're
still going to bars and shit right like it's like oh I still want to hang out
but and I feel like right fucking 17 year old yeah the most
trad cat thing at which I guess that tracks a little yeah but yeah no I doubt
isn't I have not been to a single bar like that until until that one we mostly
go to bars that are like like we went to a bar last night there's basically a
Halloween store. Oh yeah.
That sounds nice.
It was very fun. It sounds a little scary.
I swear there was a ghost there.
I swear to god there was a ghost there.
I'm gonna get a drink while he explains it.
I'm sitting there by myself
I'm waiting for Caleb to leave this
eSports thing he was at.
I heard he was at
an eSports event with a bunch of children.
He was screaming at kids.
I was there with him for a couple minutes and it was just like
I don't...
is not for me, but you know, it's cool people there.
- Cool the cool kids, you like the kids?
- No, no, no, the people we were hanging out with were cool.
- Cool people, you like the little kids?
- Just like, I'm just gonna ignore it.
- So I was gonna go to...
- Patrick got there, Patrick got there.
- I'm talking about the ghosts!
- Patrick was walking up to kids and being like,
"Do you guys need a fifth? I don't even know how to play this game,
but I wanna do teamwork with you so bad."
(laughter)
- "I wanna join the team!"
I love teamwork. I love sharing.
Patrick was cornering people saying, "My ultimate's ready."
[Laughter]
But no.
Oh, you're talking about that thing. Okay.
Yeah, like you screaming at the kids.
I realized that the reason I like any sports is because any scream that I can just scream at.
I mean, we were like... So this whole thing was like these two teams on a stage.
And one team, they brought all their friends, and these guys are going insane.
And every time they get a point, they're yelling.
and then the other side was just it was a Valorant tournament.
How did you find out about this? Some guy just asked me on Twitter to go and I was
like sure. A guy you hadn't met? A friend of a friend. Okay. He was like yeah I'm in
town doing this you want to come? I was like sure and the other side of the of
the stage was just this one kid on the team's mom and we were like we're going
to that side and then those kids like destroyed the kids who brought all the
like fucking friends and we were just like that was getting so belligerent and
just scream just like it was like in good fun until we got there we're like
fuck you! Fuck you, you piece of shit!
Every single time that our team got a point and like we started freaking out the kids who we were rooting for.
[Laughter]
We would scream and they'd be like, "Shut up, man."
So while that's going on I was like you know I don't fucking scream at sports shit so I was like this isn't for me I gotta go.
So I went to this bar and I'm sitting there like waiting for him to show up and like there's like a fireplace
like from like where I'm sitting to where like a
Little bit past cam is like right over there. That's like where the fireplace is
Okay
and this candle just like fell off and
rolled onto the floor and just shattered and I was like what the fuck just happened and the guys like
Looking is like did you do that? I was like nine fuck you like what's going on?
I like look up and there's like a statue like staring straight at me and like a taxidermy animal on the wall
I'm just like oh fuck one of these things is haunting me right now
It sucks, and I go to like pick it up and just like cut my finger on the thing
Oh, I start going to cut your finger the ghost ghost tried to snap didn't you didn't knock over a candle
It sounds like a story where you knocked over a candle and then he was on the fireplace
and then you are stupid.
A ghost!
Did you start running through the hallway going indoors
and then outdoors over and over again?
It was crazy, a piece of glass fell to the
ground and a ghost turned it into a thousand pieces
with magic.
Yeah, that was before Caleb
showed up.
I forgot.
I bought a white cloth
at the place next door and the bartender got mad at me.
Yeah, which was a weird move.
yeah and we got mad at you the bartender
the bar real piece of show you know i think it was one of the bartender this
e-sports event for a little bit of that too
there's a lot of news it was like uh... all of the bartenders had like
in the exact same spot in their body the same doctor who tattoo pretty much
java
home we got a bit of a delicate
whatever i think it was the phone booth is that what they call it i think that's
what we're a little robot guys
the other the doll it really sounds like i used to watch that in high school
sounds like you're the biggest guy
what are they called?
the little monster that in season two episode five he fights is that it?
and just like to be funny like who's your favorite doctor
like your favorite episode yeah just for just as a gag like what's
yeah what what's the best generation who uh yeah no i wish i i don't know maybe i
probably would have gotten some joy from you know I never dealt I remember I
remember when like Chris Hardwick used to talk about it all the time I'm like the
Nerdist podcast. Doctor Who is horrible. I mean that like there's other shows like
Star Trek and stuff you can still watch. I'll fuck up with Star Trek still.
No good. I'll fuck with that shit. That shit was fire back in the day.
Honestly and shit. Yo what's your favorite generation though? TNG like what's up?
up. Yeah. What do you think of Odo? He sleeps in a bucket. What do you think about that?
What do you think about Odo sleeping in a bucket? He's like the, like, he's like the
shapeshifter. Like he's like, like the last of like a race of shapeshifters. But then
in season five, yeah, that's deep space. Oh yeah. Oh, I don't like any show with more than
like 15 episodes. Yeah. I'm just never going to, except for the Simpsons. Every season
of the space nine is like twenty six episodes i don't like it the uh... nine
ever i was uh... as if we use our wars kid yet me too i visit
we got over here
given a d_n_a_ uh...
water
uh... i have
well i have this uh... uh... no i don't like their sting of the force unleashed
here
uh... you know i don't know yet you know you have a course you know that we're
going to forget what he was like a
he was like a weird jewish caricature yeah
yeah every other
yeah he was a hulk nose monster
who was very greedy
he was like a slave master to anakin skywalker
oh i forgot that yeah that too
yeah there's like a line it's such a fucking funny line read
where like quaggan jinn is like walking in like telling anakin he's like free
like free and he's just like you're no longer a slave. He's the one who's like "Credits! You can't pay me credits!"
"Your mindshades don't work on me!"
Yeah, he's awesome dude. They should have brought him, they should have done the
Mandalorian with Wadow. Oh man, I wonder what happens to Wadow after
episode 2. He doesn't show up ever again. He should have done baby Wadow.
That thing would look fucked up. Yeah, because he's got wings too.
He just starts stripping the ship of all the metal.
Just like taking it out of the walls.
It'd be awesome. Damn.
Alright, what's the list today? The nasty ripples.
I have told you guys that I'm a listener.
listener. And I do love that all of the lists are, usually, this one is not written by a
child.
No.
No, I feel like it usually is like, I have, I mean, I've probably listened to like, maybe
like 10 to 15 episodes at this point. And it's almost always like, I'm always like,
oh yeah, this list was written by like a 12 year old.
Yeah, it's always a big, it sucks when I'm doing my job and the person we're making fun
of their name is like Chris 2009. I know why it's 2009. You are 12.
But this one I think you said is not a child and it is-
What's the thing? Whenever it's like, you know, like something like this, it's got something
as fucked up as gonna be in this. Like what was that one? Fuckable lesser apes?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, we did one. If someone made a list of monkeys, it would fuck.
Yeah.
The thing about the ones that are written by kids is they're all from the same website,
but we didn't know the website existed
like before we started the podcast.
- Yeah.
- Like we just found that website
and it's like, okay, I guess we have to do this
every single episode.
- It's also easy.
- The only good one.
It's also very easy.
This list was sent to us by Adam Online on Twitter.
So thank you for this.
This is from popxo.com.
"15 Dirty Riddles with Answers.
"Make Him Laugh and Turn On with These Sex Riddles"
by Sharon Alfonso.
(laughing)
- By who?
- I love when I'm about to--
- Wait, Sharon Alfonso.
- Sharon Alfonso.
Oh Sharon Alfonso that is not the name I expected from the
You're about to like eat a woman's pussy and she's like
That's always that turns me on so hard it makes me laugh
For a girl who likes to spice things up in the bedroom
We know a few naughty dirty riddles that will instantly get your man in the mood
They're not only sexy but hilarious at the same time
From subtly getting the hint to tempting him to hop right in bed with you
You must try these dirty sex riddles for your crushed boyfriend husband at least once
This is like a cool thing for like people who like only fuck bridge trolls
Yeah, yeah
This is where this is really good if you're trying to fuck Gollum. Yeah, like
Riddles like that's work to them. Do you think exactly you know when they be like can you just like knock it off bitch for one?
night a
A girl riddler.
Yeah, maybe.
You think that's the next one that they're gonna have?
A rid-less.
A rid-let.
That would be a child riddler, yeah?
No.
Wouldn't that be a...
Oh, Patrick would love that.
Oh, E-T-T-E-R.
Goddamn it.
He's just asking Pat, like, easy math questions that he can't answer.
Yeah, no, one, two, skip a few.
Ask him these seductive, dirty riddles to get him in the mood.
Are you ready to give them a shot?
Awesome.
Here are 15 sex riddles to ask your guy to get him in the mood and make him raffle.
Woo him away with some funny, dirty, and clever riddles, Tigress.
Tigress?
Tigress.
Number one.
What the fuck?
Oh, like go, okay.
Sorry, I just didn't understand the joke there.
Wait, what?
Like, go get 'em, tiger?
They said Tigress?
I don't know.
I don't think that's...
I think this list is for women.
you can read this list. Number one, you play with it at night and it vibrates in your hand.
What is it? Cell phone. You look, you saw the answer. Is it? It's answer, a cell phone. Oh.
What were you thinking, eh? Wait, what? That's not like... You play with it at night. How's
that sexual, like it's, it's like a bait and switch thing. Is that what all these are gonna
be is like, what are you, fuck? You, a cantaloupe. Ice cream. And that's supposed to make, you're
supposed to be like alright let's hop in.
I'm gonna fuck you right now.
I'm gonna be on my phone.
This is like the like I get this
is like a woman like a from like
trying to write from like a woman's perspective.
This is like a pick up artist's idea of like
like getting laid is all about
like doing the right like
the right dialogue branch like in
Mass Effect.
Being just confusing.
Yeah exactly.
Making them feel completely crazy.
What's that thing, like jester maxing or whatever?
I don't think that's real.
You don't?
That's like on the, I don't know, some incel thing where it's like, oh, looks maxing or
jester maxing or whatever.
Maybe like riddles maxing.
Maybe that's a new thing.
It's on some incel forum for losers.
Some forum that, yeah, I don't, I'm just, I'm checking it all.
Some username.
I'm checking it every day.
God, it's so funny to look at every day in the morning before I do anything else.
in the day. Oh my God. Okay, number two. Now guess this time Patrick. Don't. Okay.
You know. Patrick is the one who has to guess all of these. Alright, yeah. I like that. Okay.
Number two. You'll find them in different sizes. If it's chilly outside, it drips.
And if you blow it, it feels like heaven. What is it? Doesn't that sound sexual?
Say it again. You'll find them in different sizes. If it's chilly outside,
outside it drips and if you blow it it feels like heaven what is it so easy to
think about it okay all right think about so the obvious answer would be
because it's a sex or it'll be your cock have you ever been outside when it was
cold and your cock just started dripping all over the place yeah yeah I guess
that's why you're answering what when you blow it it feels is it cigarettes
(laughing)
- We learned that Pat just blows into the room.
I know somebody who I like,
they had been like smoking weed since they were like 15,
and I would watch them and every time they would smoke weed,
they would just like put it in their mouth like a cigar
and then blow it out.
And then I saw them at 22 years old,
it would be hanging out with my brother,
get high for the first time because my brother was like,
you're not even fucking inhaling it.
He was like, "What do you mean?"
He was like, "You have to inhale the weed."
And it like blew his mind.
I don't think he's smoked weed since then.
Damn.
You need the answer, Pat?
When you blow it, it feels amazing.
You got...
When you breathe it outside, it drips.
Do you want to phone a friend?
No, I got this.
You got three guesses for each of these.
Okay, that's your last guess.
You ready for the answer, Pat?
Yeah, I'm at a loss.
Answer.
A nose, you dirty mind.
Well, what is it?
What's the...
you blow your nose and it drips when it's cold.
And it feels like heaven when you blow it.
If it's chilly outside it drips?
Is that about a...
No, you fucking know.
No, obvious yes.
What is the question?
It seems like you were stoned, my friend.
The implication is that it's like
oh, this could be about something.
A nose isn't sexual to you?
That's not a sexy...
If it's chilly outside it drips?
Yeah, a nose.
balls why is it yeah I guess like you're supposed to think it's a cock well
there's also like a woman this is not I don't I wouldn't fuck this is like this
doesn't make me want to have sex yeah you realize that the person you're about
to fuck is just like completely just well no this is you know maybe maybe you
guys don't want to but as a sapiosexual you know be told a riddle.
No.
Who is this woman?
I do love thinking about who is this woman.
That's a good question.
Who is this woman?
Alfonso.
Sharon Alfonso.
Let's take a look at Sharon Alfonso.
Does she have an Instagram?
What else did she write?
Why is it called Good Friday and why do we celebrate it?
Let's find out.
You know, she's thinking about Good Friday.
She was one of the trad cats at that bar.
Can certain types of food...
Yeah, I have a journalism job.
Can certain types of food cause hair fall?
What comes when you suck on it?
A popsicle.
Yeah, lots of articles here by Sharon Alfonso.
Google Sharon Alfonso.
Google Sharon Alfonso nude.
Sharon Alfonso. There's no way that's a real name. No, that's also like a man who's named Alfonso.
It's like, I need a girl pen name. Yeah. Seven genius ways to repurpose makeup products.
No thanks. All right, this is her most exciting article. Okay, Pat, are you ready for number
three? Also, they have gifs in this article too. Really, really sexy gifs.
Number three, unless you spread it, you can't enjoy it. What is it?
It's peanut butter.
I don't know. Close.
Oh, butter.
You got it.
Good one. Answer, if you thought butter, then you're correct. And look at this.
Are you looking for Sharon Alfonso?
Yeah.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, that does have an Instagram?
That's fully, it's fully not a pseudonym.
Dude, he's in love.
Oh, is she beautiful?
This is...
Brandon's in love with Sharon Alfonso.
This is her?
No, no, no.
I mean, that's her.
This can't be her, right?
That's her.
But also, how many women are there named Sharon Alfonso?
Oh, nah.
This is...
If this bitch tried to tell me riddles...
Nah.
Yeah, she would have to be really hot for me to say yes to that, honestly.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, if you said yes to her riddle, you'd be wrong.
Oh, boy.
Nah.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Sharon.
I'm sorry. Sorry, Sharon.
Patrick, do you like this gif here?
Does that get you excited for the next riddle?
It's really sexy.
Oh, dude, you're making me want to bust.
Number four.
Oh, Christ.
This gif is repeating so good.
Oh.
What's long and hard and has the word come in it?
Okay.
Vacuum.
That's a pretty good guess, actually.
But also like my penis doesn't have the word. Yeah, I think they dropped the ball there by saying the word come.
They just said come. Oh, you know this one. Come on. This is easy like c-o-m-e or c-u-m. C-u-m, baby. Yeah, come on
Oh, you got this. Are you literally serious? Are you stupid?
a little bit
Just guess something
Would you well i'm trying to think of words with yeah, just guess something was a good guess. Yeah. Oh, this one's obvious
brother with the book
are you doing here commer
yeah
and the high-tech com
my company comes to it
uh... because comes to their tomorrow
yes karen over there you go
answer a cucumber duh even said uh... well
that's what i think it was like
is like i was like now is no way it's like a food great like it long and hard
She says a cucumber duh and you're like, "You think you're fucking smarter than me?"
Bitch, get out!
Number five. It has two feathery hoops and is used to chain you in bed. What is it?
It's a dreamcatcher.
It's not a dreamcatcher.
What?
What is it? You think a dreamcatcher like magically like binds you to your bed?
You think it's like a fairy circle for your bed?
It's an enchantment.
it catches your dreams yeah so it's kind of good about something yeah I'm like
I'm not getting out of bed till I have a dream if I don't dream every house and
it chains you your buddies also aren't riddles they're just things there's
questions yeah was it a pillow no no a pillow doesn't show us feathers I mean I
will say I don't know many things that chain me to my bed yeah no you know that
also have to fill in and get to know the answers
i can i know the answer their way in your i can reach it
you guys know it
i know it i read it
i genuinely not what is this is really mad about this one here you are
loaded
answer a pair of sexy handcuffs of course
you know
no
fuck you can't talk to you share it out for a pair of sexy handcuffs of course
Yeah, it's switched. You can't fucking bait and switch us like that.
'Cause now I have to- Everyone was expecting it!
Like cucumber? Yeah.
This is fucking bullshit. You guys never do anybody-
Dude, that's the mark of a clever riddle master.
Always keeping you on your toes.
God damn it, I fucking hate riddles, dude.
God, I'm such a rube, I can't do riddles.
What? That is a huge bait and switch.
Yeah. You can just have an answer that's like,
"Well, a hard penis for a wet pussy."
Yeah. Obviously.
- Obviously. - Gigantic boobies.
- What smells like pussy? Answer.
- Pussy. - Yeah.
- Fuck, I got owned. - How about Sharon?
- Yeah. - Uh...
- Sharon... - One of the answers
is Sharon's pussy. - I can't believe...
- Yeah. What tastes
amazing and you're never gonna see it?
- Yeah. - Sharon's pussy.
- Yeah. Are you ready for the next one here? - Yes.
- Number six. What holds your buns
firmly and makes them look round
and pretty?
What?
Hold your-
Alright, this bitch is stupid.
It's underwear.
No.
It's pretty much.
Yeah.
What is it?
Answer. Nope, it's not a hair tie.
It's your old friend, the thong.
Ah.
Your old friend the thong.
So if you didn't-
Bro.
If you have to guess, your old friend the thong or it's not correct.
Yeah.
If you just say the thong, it doesn't count.
You know Cher has some weak pussy for this.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
I absolutely do.
Oh my god.
Oh, this is...
God damn. He's still on her Instagram.
What the fuck? Oh, she's, uh, yeah, she's engaged. Oh no. Oh yeah.
I'm going to send this article to her husband and be like, do you know what she's been writing?
Oh, I mean, get her under control. Oh, but I'm looking at this guy and it's like, I, you know,
he's not he's not neither of them are bringing much to the table I mean this
guy is you come on no yeah no he looks bad I think he looks I think they look
nice together I think they look like shit you should get a divorce honestly
think so yeah I think they should have a kid and get a divorce just so it's
harder. I think that's a really good idea. What the fuck does this mean?
That's so mean to say. This is a selfie where she's like, it's nice.
And it says I'm defending Sharon 2.0.
Sharon did the upgrade. Oh my god.
What's Sharon's next riddle?
Sharon's next riddle is what's the white sticky stuff most girls like but instead of swallows spits out?
I know it's not come because girls
true
You really tipped it tipped it there
Come on dude you got this
Spit it out. Yeah. Yeah, it's not go believe it or no. That's what I would have thought it was
marshmallow I love a fluffernutter sandwich but I hate having to spit it out.
I wish it was edible that's the only problem.
yeah the white sticky stuff is teeth. Fluffernutter sandwiches like I remember the
fattest kid at my school ate them every day for lunch yeah I mean it's like yeah
- Yeah, the thing is, it's good, but like,
if you can eat it and not--
- It's not something you eat every day.
- Well, it's also, it's funny, gummy worms, though.
- I mean, truly, if you can eat it
like more than one day in a row and like feel okay,
there's a, there's a--
- But just imagine like having like a,
like I remember he had like a hot mom.
Imagine being like a, like a, an in shape,
like older woman with a kid with like,
who's like pre-diabetic, and every day waking up early
to make him a fluffernutter sandwich before school.
That's just like, you gotta be,
she might have a feeding thing.
Oh my God.
We can't talk about it.
No, we've already talked about
moms with feeding things on the
podcast last episode.
Oh, yeah.
The fucking diaper thing.
Yeah.
A lot of people are mad at us for
reading that story on the show.
Nobody's mad. Everybody's happy.
They're all wimps.
I say, you know, grow up.
Yeah.
I say y'all need to get some
pussy.
Except if a woman's ever farted in
your face and you've been like,
yeah, sure. Then you, you need to
grow up.
That's called a fluffernutter.
If you've never shat on the ground during sex, you need to grow up.
He's not even just getting up in the middle of it.
He's shitting on the ground and then going back to it.
No, you're like fucking.
Just fucking shitting all over the ground during a handjob.
*laughter*
I'm so sorry, I lost control
Being just as bashful as when a woman squirts
*laughter*
Being like, "Oh, I'm sorry, do you have a towel? I'll clean it up. I'm sorry."
Sorry, this never happens to me.
*laughter*
I creamed.
My bad. Oh, fuck, I'm gonna squirt.
*laughter*
Oh, God.
I'm going to squirt and then actually shitting on the floor that she's like, is that, do
they do that?
You need the answer for this one with the white sticky stuff is you want to know?
Oh yeah.
I forgot.
I never got the answer.
Right.
A toothpaste.
I was going to fucking say it too.
I don't think that's joy.
- Sticky though.
- No one enjoys toothpaste.
- Also it's like most girls.
- Guys do it too.
- Wait, the joke is that like, I don't know.
Is it implied that some people enjoy swallowing toothpaste?
- Some people do, do you?
Some people do.
(laughing)
- Okay, next row here.
- He was like, I gotta go get a drink.
- Big ol' glasses.
yeah i'm like trying to play it off like it's milk
i keep being like this milk's really stiff
what the fuck this milk it like doesn't move
is that weird?
this glass is so weird
this optical illusion where it looks like it's not moving at all
looks like it has little
blue and red stars in it
it's very funny to me that like the
it already would be weird if you walked back with a glass
you know
it already would be insane
i'm trying to play it off like that
just normal
fridge you know there's not milk in there at all. I think it's funny that the
solution to like people swallowing toothpaste was they made toothpaste like
you can swallow it now. Yeah. You know they make adult toothpaste where you can
just tank it dude. Just gulp it down. And what's it called? I might be hungry later. What goes in
hard and comes out wet, squishy, and sticky? Spaghetti. No. Oh that makes sense.
That's actually a great answer. You might be smarter than Sharon Alexander.
So it goes in hard and comes out wet, sticky, squishy and sticky.
Uh, then what else would it be?
What is it? Is it going to be like, "Bucatini, you dummy!"
It's two pieces of spaghetti.
Come on, you got this.
this
fucking
you know it's a little answer
the talk okay so it's a yeah go ahead is that is the most uh... i was like
the
so that we're getting drinks as i guess you may remain you know if he's like
leaving
history with the book
but in our world
there's one of the water
we we talk about it is good to know that the public will be a little bit
instead asking
one of our water
and that
And then he said, "You didn't know?"
And then we were like, "What are you saying, dude?"
And we're like, "What are you saying, dude?"
And he's like, "Oh, I thought you said
"there was mud in our water."
(laughing)
- It must be crazy to be like your roommate
and just hear this all the time.
- Yeah.
- But I thought I was just having a stroke.
Like I was like--
- I was so confused.
- Like what the fuck is going on?
- 'Cause I was holding the Brita filter too.
And he was just going, "Mud in our water?"
(laughing)
- He just put a bunch of mud in there.
I'm just letting you know before I go, I put a bunch of mud in the brine.
I want to see if it gets the dirt out.
Yeah, I made a bunch of mud, but I want the dirt back.
Don't they have that now?
Don't they have like black water with dirt in it that you can drink?
Oh, it's a charcoal water.
It's coffee.
Oh, the coffee.
Yeah, but like that doesn't, it probably tastes weird, right?
I don't know.
Does it make your mouth black?
Yeah, a little bit.
Like when you eat ink?
Did you ever do that? You ever put ink in your mouth?
From a pen?
No, I've never eaten ink. It's pretty funny.
It'll make your mom real mad.
Yeah, I mean it.
Alright, wait, what was the...
It goes in hard, it comes out wet, sticky, and...
Squishy.
I'm just gonna tell you the answer here.
It's a hot dog. It's not a hot dog.
It's bubble gum.
Oh, fuck off.
Come on, bitch. It's not hard.
Bubble gum is not hard.
- You're pushing on the website. - No, no.
- Please, just please.
Can we just please scroll down and for once
not get a Chris Evans gift and then just get like
a hardcore just something going into your vagina.
Please, Sharon.
- Don't, don't ask her, come on.
- Why?
- What? - It's very rude.
- It's a, she's asking me all these fucking questions.
- All right, what's the next riddle?
- Number nine, you can't taste it until you undress it.
What is it?
- Ranch.
yeah taste it probably in a banana it's a banana take it why do you think that's
there I love yeah that's good so it's like a picture of a computer dusting
himself with very buff white man arms. Can you imagine how he walks with his arms?
So it's basically like the way that it's set up is like the keyboard looks like it's dick
and he's just spraying computer juster onto where his penis should be.
Raising his eyebrows and kind of smirking like.
Damn that's cold.
Yeah alright that's fine. Sorry I got distracted.
No, it's important.
I want to do more inhalants.
I think that's the next drug for me.
Yeah.
You hit that duster.
I guess I could.
The thing is, I would need to do some research and find out what the best one is.
I'm in my inhalant era.
Yeah, exactly.
Make the worst music ever.
Just get like poppers.
Yeah, just if like David Bowie got into like inhalants.
Yeah, that'd be fucking sick, dude.
Just make a music.
That should be the next like the next drug to like rappers get into yeah you
know what I mean yeah like we should like NBA Youngboy should start making music on
fucking Duster and Glu. I think that they should be like constantly on
Whippets while they're recording so they have to yeah they have to rap well on
on
it to play with it what is it balloon it answered did you think balloon to same
pinch motherfucker what is it balloon saying it wasn't a balloon no it's a
blow my penis to play with it yeah like it just is you can play with it right
now you have to do anything millions of different play styles that's what makes
It's so incredible.
It's true, yeah.
God damn, she sucks for this.
This list feels like being on an airplane.
Yeah, you know?
Yeah, absolutely.
You're just kind of stuck.
Yeah.
It also feels like you're like, speaking of on an airplane, this would be like one of
the five internet pages you can access for free on an American Airlines flight.
Right.
You join the Wi-Fi and it's like...
Depersonalize it.
Check this out.
Yeah.
What's the next riddle?
Next riddle is, I end with O-R-N and start with P, and I'm a major player in the film industry.
Popcorn.
Oh my god.
It's popcorn.
That one's just lazy.
This is not...
Boring.
Oh my god.
Check this picture out.
It's pretty good, right?
It's a picture of...
Oh god.
Yo, SNL!
Guys, this sucks, right?
My dick is just so hard.
It's like a rock hard cock.
Somehow, yeah, just like a cartoonishly large penis.
The only giant boner you've ever had.
You're knocking things over in the room.
"What's wrong with you, Steel Head?"
I've knocked down all of Patrick's skateboards.
[Laughter]
This isn't funny or sexy!
I'm doubled over laughing.
[Laughter]
It's somehow bugged you, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, we realize one of your legs is just your cock.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
Number 12, I have a stiff shaft, my tip penetrates, I come with a quiver, what am I?
Bow and arrow.
An arrow.
Dude, you are getting so good at this.
Dude, Sharon would seriously suck your cock.
Come on, man.
You mean it?
Do you guys still get boners in the mornings?
Just random boners?
Just crazy boners?
Yeah.
Dude, they've been on the swing recently.
It doesn't stop.
They tell you it stops in middle school, but no, it doesn't stop.
Every time someone talks about they're like yeah, I was crazy when I was 13. I was getting boners like
DMV
Forest dick I've ever had just like fucking like impressive to me on the so rare the plane over here
Play nap got a fucking massive. Yeah waking up with it sucks. Yeah. Well. I woke up from a nap
Yeah on the plane also always sitting next to like a big fat guy whose belly is going over the armrest
and so like if he sees like I'm I'm toast yeah he's gonna be like fuck my belly
button I would just for the story yeah or I'm like watching like pixels with
fucking headrest Josh Josh dad fucks is it is it miss Pat you know it's like one
of the Oh Q Bert Q Bert okay like you were like
what is it it's like a bird oh type thing yeah like become Ashley Benson or
something all right yet some weeks so it's like that
i'm pretty sure
but what if you turn back in the middle of the events in which you remember i
think she's a she's the longer on spring breakers
yeah okay she's the one that's
the a year and a half yeah
i have eyes only for heather graham as far as like women in movies uh... yeah
old we're some ahead of the ran the other day
is so funny that she's like you were
we were you've had a long weekend yeah it's so funny that there was just like
six years it was like we need a woman's boobs in this movie
Heather Graham let's get Heather Graham sleep on the floor in the living room
yep yeah oh the viral tweet yeah the other no it was the second time so he
can I was worse third time it was so fucked up because there was the one
picture you fall on though you were asleep on the floor and then the other
one and I saw it and that somebody posted it and I could tell there was a
picture of your living room. I was like I can't. I can't reply and be like hey man what's going on.
This is your living room. So he had that thing where he fell asleep on a person's floor and then
two nights later we're watching Austin Powers here at his own home. No that's like a week after.
And he gets, no this was like three days later, and then he gets on the floor and falls asleep
five feet outside of this bedroom that we're in right now. He just like couldn't make it.
And he was talking to me while he was falling asleep and he was like, "Yeah, Austin Powers,
Fah-- Patrick." Oh, man. And then he's just gone. Patrick. Yeah. And I think he had one beer that
night. No. I'm pretty sure he had a single beer. Yeah. It was-- it was served to you in a giant
glass boot. Yeah. It was like this stock, like the-- the-- a Christmas story lamp. Yeah, just
getting-- getting pulled over. I was walking around with that, just like, "Oh, I love beer."
Did you dream about Austin Powers that night? No, I just woke up on the floor.
No dream. The rain shut off. Is that just like a... it's like part of your morning routine now?
Like if you don't wake up on the floor, do you get off of your bed, get on the floor,
and then get back up? You're asking me that because I told you I do that.
He was doing the like talk show host thing. Yeah. Like you fed me that line earlier.
There was a pre-interview. I understand that you've been getting on the floor from the
in the mornings. Yeah, you just told me that. If I'm like hungover... Dude, I don't know what it is.
Why do you love that damn floor so much? It's colder down there. You should be a janitor. Yeah,
well you know that's the thing like, um, like when I was in high school, like I had to live
in a hotel for like, like, god, like, might have been... Five days. Might have been two hours,
three hours on this vacation. One night in Myrtle Beach I had to live in a hotel. It was horrible.
Whole month of March till I graduated high school, like my senior year. And I, like,
you know, it's like my family, my fucking family's like a lot of people. There's like no room for
any of us. There's only like two bedrooms there. And I like, by choice would sleep in this bathtub.
In a bathtub you slept? Yeah. I would just sleep in the bathtub just because like,
the couch wasn't comfortable. What? Oh man. Yeah. Damn bro. Well, because you know my brother had
the, my older brother had the air mattress. Yeah. And you know like getting... It'd be funny to be
your mom waking up for school every single morning just looks like Whitney Houston's like
walking in. She's like Mountain Dew bottles and shit. Yeah. I don't know. I just, I,
beds aren't comfortable for me. Yeah, they're not hard. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All men have one.
Some got long, some got small.
The Pope never uses his,
and a man gives it to his wife after getting married.
- Wait, the Pope uses his cock?
He like pisses, right?
- No, he doesn't.
- Really?
- No, that's what the hat's for, it stores it.
- Is his second bladder up there?
- Yeah.
- Is it a ring?
- Why would it be a ring?
- Yeah, that's what it...
- All men have a ring.
- Every man has at least one ring.
- It's either, it's got a spider on it.
- True, that is cool, yeah.
What's your answer?
What does the Pope not use?
His cock.
We do-
No, he-
Jesus Christ.
Oh my God.
He's being so confused by the riddles.
He's losing motor controls.
Oh fuck.
Which way is up?
Oh no.
I don't know.
What?
I give up.
You need an answer?
His last name?
His last name.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
last name. Oh. What do you mean get long? What? Some get small? Some people have long last
names and some have small ones. Yeah, but they don't become smaller over time. Some
got long, some got small. Yeah. I don't know what to tell you, man. Some got long and some
got small. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Fuck this riddle, because it should say some
have them, like, have them long, some have them small. Yeah, man. Sharon's stupid. How
How many fucking times do I have to go over this?
Before Sharon lets you hit, you have to answer 20 really?
And then she sits there grading for two hours.
It's close to Scantron, it makes it a lot easier.
Alright, we're at home stretch here.
Number 14.
What is soft and wet on the inside while being hard and hairy on the outside?
The word begins with C, ends in T, and there's a U and N between them.
one feels too complicated also our vagina is like hard as steel on the outside
it's like a bear trap oh really yeah yeah we're just soft on the inside yeah it's
a carapace nobody's using the word cunt in like a sexual context
fuck my hard cunt that's the funniest part of the departed is that like
they're trying to make Jack Nicholson a tough guy and they're like yeah like a
tough Boston guy what would he say if he like was talking about sex he'd be like
Yeah, I get cunt.
Oh yeah.
I would not say that.
So gross.
Wait, hold on.
The answer is Chewbacca.
Obviously.
It's hairy.
Has
the letters for cunt in it.
Patrick's like adding things.
It smells like Arby's.
Yeah, read it again.
What is soft and wet on the inside
on the inside while being hard and hairy on the outside. The word begins with C, ends
in T, and there's a U and N in between them.
Come on dude, you got this.
This would be the ultimate bait and switch if it's just cunt. That would be so good.
I wish.
Is the answer obvious?
Harded?
I don't think so. There's too much spelling here for it to be obvious.
The spelling is what's throwing me off.
You want the answer?
Yeah, I'm done with this fucking thing.
A coconut.
Wow.
Oh, fuck off.
That's actually pretty good.
Answer, a coconut.
By the way, what popped up in your head?
You know, Shirley.
Alright, alright.
Keith fucking know what you've done.
Alright, last one.
Is that Russell Brand?
I think that's Keegan-Michael Key.
It's not Keegan-Michael Key.
I think that is, let's see, let me look, let me get a little closer, but not too close.
Yeah, it's Keegan-Michael Key.
Yeah.
What is that?
Keegan-Michael Key.
Dressed up as Ozzy Osbourne.
Who is that?
Who is this fucking guy?
Who is this person?
I don't know.
Television show.
That's what it says here.
Keegan-Michael Key was on a television show.
It's only, it's Tru, Tru, I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
Trugerina.
I don't know if that's the name.
I don't know what's going on.
That's a different guy.
There's all, these are all different.
Wait a second.
Yeah.
Oh, and it's all different.
I don't know.
second yeah oh and it's also it's also used in other like weird yeah mysterious
yeah the true Jerry Jerry on a Jerry on a is it true this is him true Jerry tell
me that doesn't look like Keegan-Michael Key
- It does.
- You don't know what you're talking about, dude.
- No, he's right for that.
- I'm just so spot on today.
- Fuck.
- All right, you ready for your last road all pass?
What gets longer if pulled fits snugly between breasts,
slides neatly into a hole, chokes people
when used incorrectly, and works well when jerked.
- What did they say about breasts?
What the hell?
- What are breasts?
- Wait, say it one more time.
- What gets longer if pulled fits snugly
between breasts, slides neatly into a hole, chokes people when used incorrectly, and works
well when jerked.
Oh I know this one.
This one's easy dude.
Come on, you got this.
You can do this.
I believe in you.
Like a pen maybe?
Yeah, everybody else knows the answer except for you.
Yeah, you look so stupid right now.
Sharon's never gonna fuck you.
Why would the fit snugly... I'm now just like confused about the fit snugly in breasts thing.
That's one of the big clues.
So it has something to do with boobs?
No.
No, it fits snugly between breasts.
It doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
Oh, it's chicken.
Is it?
Let's see.
Is it chicken?
No, it's not chicken.
What else could it be other than a seatbelt?
Oh fuck off.
I would like to come out and say to everybody, I thought that it was chicken.
And I was like, Pat, you fucking idiot.
You don't know that it's chicken.
Fuck dude.
Because the jerk thing.
Slides neatly into a hole.
Pulled.
Like these are all kinds of chicken that you can eat.
Slides neatly into a hole.
My mouth!
Yeah.
Yeah, he's demonstrating.
Tell me that doesn't look like a hole.
That's a good chicken hole.
If I was a chicken, I would love to slide in there.
Yeah, I would love to have you.
So, did you find these dirty riddles funny too?
Because we sure did.
Ask him these and have some fun moments
followed by some uncontrolled passion.
Yeah, I'm gonna fuckin' oh.
What fits snugly between breasts?
First, no reason at all.
Do you guys want to all have sex together right now?
[laughter]
horny at all. Okay, we're done here. Brandon, plug your stuff here.
Listen to Yebba Silk. Check out Bernie Mac's show, Brandon Wardell's
come out with a reboot. Gonna be playing Bernie Mac.
I'm excited for that, man. You're gonna kill it. I think you strike that perfect balance
I mean I'm like funny but intellectual right yeah yeah yeah look people people
know yeah I'm a good I'm a good father yeah yeah yeah you look like a father
yeah I've adopted your sister's kids yeah yeah yeah yeah it'd be funny to
like your sister's going through a really hard time and so you like kind of
adopter kids and you just rename all of them.
(laughter)
Beyonce, Drake, Eminem, Justin Bieber.
Cameron Jr., Cameron III.
My sister was going through a hard time so I adopted all of her kids and I made them wear dumb hats.
With their names on them.
Yeah, these are my four kids, they're all named Dunce.
(laughter)
Yeah, I don't know. I don't really have anything to... I guess like I posted... I just like self-released some stand-up stuff on YouTube.
Nice.
So that's, you know, you just go to... people would know where to find me on the computer.
YouTube.com/infowarst
/22
Or you can find him right now at 22.
Stop! Stop!
Thank you, Brandon.