you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
crap monster
recording
back to it dude all three back yeah
back
back back back back and we're back and we're back back back and we are back
and we're back and we are back recording we're back and we are back we just don't
stop that we're back never stop being back back recording back back in the
shack
the shack whoa in my face that would say stack right now stack of microphones
okay back okay but I got the track I got crack I got lack I got smack a back and
back pack a back attack a racket check a big sack of rats I got a I got a bag I
I got a back attack in me, I slacked,
and then I got the crack.
- Okay, go Pat, go, go, go.
- And we're back doing the one time,
in the track, on the three tracks of audio,
me, Cameron, Caleb, three tracks, not two tracks.
Three tracks, not two tracks.
- Sweet tracks.
- Can we do like a slow down my voice,
like three tracks, not two tracks.
- Uh-huh, we could do that.
We have the, yeah, we're like audio people.
All right.
Ack, back, cack, dack, yak, fack, gack, hack.
Do you remember--
I don't know if I should say his name,
but there was a comic in Boston who was also a rapper.
We probably actually talked about it pretty early on
in the show.
There was a comic in Boston who got in trouble for sending--
Shane Hoban?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Did you ever listen to his rap?
We were talking about--
you sent a clip of his rap.
Dude, it was fucking amazing.
There's a part in the song where he's like,
I'm a sex offender! I'm a sex offender!
Yeah, and then it slows down while he's saying that.
Yeah, I'm a sex offender.
Crazy, crazy that they like, I don't know, there's like that whole article about him on like the Turtle Boy thing.
I'm, I, god damn it. I'm giving, I'm giving fucking like, I know it's already online, but like I probably shouldn't say it.
Dude, he's gonna shoot that old-timey, he's gonna shoot that revolver at you with the sniper scope on it.
Oh god, I'm actually, yeah.
be you're about to have that red dot right on your head yeah for context this guy
owns a gun but it is a he sent a photo of it to another comedian it's a it's like a
like a revolver we've definitely posted pictures of the gun yeah we have yeah
best gun picture the funniest gun ever has a giant like scope on it like and he
has like just like he has like yellow shit under all his fingernails - it's
literally a gun that you would make in warzone that would they be like yeah
Like people be like this guns overpowered for one week and then it would get nerfed. It's the exact same look it's so cool
Just have it. You can kill me instead dude. I don't give a fuck that guy's a pussy
Wow, yeah
Fat and he's a and I will battle rap him attack back-to-back
Say his line you got it say his steal. I'm a sex offender. I'm a sex offender. That's all this was leading up to
I got Caleb. I'm actually
I'm a sex defender.
You said it more times.
No.
Yeah, you did.
I'm a sex defender.
I defend women from sex.
Ugh.
What?
Women having sex?
That's disgusting.
Yeah, I'm like a defensive lineman.
Right?
Guy goes in for a kiss, I just fucking check him, dude.
Yeah.
Poof.
Not today.
And then she gets mad and I say, "But what if it had actually gone really bad?"
Yeah.
I'm like a tomb guardian type thing.
to life when I hear that telltale noise.
- What noise? - What's a telltale noise?
- Sex noise.
- Oh, oh, like the sound of the chastity belt
hitting the floor?
(laughing)
- Yeah, the lock, the big padlock on the chastity belt?
- Yep.
- Do you guys ever get like, feel your chastity belt
like rides up a little bit?
- I hate it 'cause like I'll go out and skate, right?
And like I'll sweat and then like,
not even just the cage 'cause I have the belt on
and the cage.
- Yeah.
It's I mean, it's it's just like the metal. Yeah, it up against my sweaty
No, and it's it really sucks - I hate I hate fucking having to put the diaper over it
That's the second worst part. Yeah
Absolutely. It's like just the you know, it's it's so hard to clean. Yeah, you get in the shower. It's gonna get rusty
I don't write right. I put like a big corn husk over it. Oh
Oh, like an empanada.
Yeah, yeah.
That's kind of my--
because also, my private parts are very squishy, like masa.
So I do have to kind of squish it together
much like an empanada.
Is it empanadas that are in--
I'm kind of holding it.
You're thinking of tamales.
Tamale, yeah.
Yeah.
So I was thinking that when you said it,
but I did not want to try and correct you on food.
Also, the chastity belt tan line is
one of the most embarrassing things. It's like a lightning bolt. That's the first thing. That's
the first bad thing about it is the tan line. It's a tan line. Yeah. Because like, and well,
not that anybody knows, because I wouldn't ever take it off, at least not until I'm married, but
right. Not till I'm married the second time. The first marriage I'm staying on. Forever. Right.
I mean, yeah, because like, I know that that was just going to be kind of just nothing to me. Yeah,
hey, it's called the first marriage for a reason. It's the first one. Exactly. I wouldn't call it
your first marriage if you weren't gonna have a second one.
Exactly.
So, with my first wife, I won't even take it.
I won't even let her look at my chastity.
I pretend my chastity belt is my privates and I won't let her look at them.
Yeah.
My things bend metal since I was born.
My things always bend metal.
Really?
I mean, that's the other thing you gotta, you have to, you know, with trends of sex changing,
the way people have sex changing and like you know you got to wear a chastity belt and an
ass to the belt because you never know when your wife's going to come at you from behind
that's fucking true as shit actually yeah that's a really good point an ass to the belt yeah
how about your wife ass titty belt might be a really good spencer's gifts idea yeah
yeah that could be good yeah it's got ass and titties on it yeah and it's a belt yeah do you
Do you remember like in mid 2000s when people were into like belt buckles?
Yeah.
What the fuck was that?
People having belt buckles that spun and shit.
People have like a-
That was sick.
That's cool as fuck dude.
With a studded belt.
Bring that back.
Dude I almost bought a studded belt.
I almost bought a studded belt and then I didn't.
Probably good that I didn't.
Yeah, I don't think a studded belt is, I don't think it'd look very good on you these days.
You know what would look really good?
A karate belt with a big cowboy belt buckle.
I think that could be a really good fashion look.
I think any type of karate items would look amaze-y on Meezy.
They would look amaze-y on Yeezy?
It would look amaze-y on Meezy.
You really think-sies?
Oh, I think-sies it looks amaze-y on Meezy's.
That's good, man.
Yeah, that's what I say.
My brother had one that was like it like spun around and shit.
A karate belt?
Yeah, a karate belt.
No, he didn't have a karate belt.
I was the one who did karate, okay?
What belt level did you get to?
It was because my parents got divorced and they thought that it would be...
I was one under black belt.
Getting...
No, you weren't.
I was.
No, you were not.
No way.
Yeah, in Taekwondo.
It was called a bochudon.
No.
Okay, well, we're not talking about that show.
You said karate also.
But I did Taekwondo.
We're not talking about that show with the little balls come out of the cards.
you what I was not the thing is about Taekwondo is it's just as if you do like
like if you do it for 18 months you are a black belt you don't have to like fight
someone or be good at it you just have to be like good at like saying yes sir
right and then they gave you I hadn't turned 13 yet so they gave me a bochu
dan instead of a black belt once you turn 13 you are like have this like like
it's like a it's like a it's like a like a weapon license like what you can have
the black belt but before that you have to have a provisional black belt. Yeah, exactly.
It's like a learner's permit for being insanely gay every time you fight.
Is it, like if you are a black belt, is it karate that you have to like legally declare
yourself a weapon? You have to register your fist as a deadly weapon. That's not true.
I don't think that's anything. That's nothing. I think you saw like a Steven Seagal movie
where he says that. Yeah. And you're like yeah, that's supposed to be one of the rules of karate.
probably one of the things that happens in karate. Probably one of the five pillars of karate.
I, I, well it's funny you can tell me it's not true I'm still gonna believe it. Okay. Yeah, I mean
why would it matter to declare your hands as a deadly weapon? Does it mean you have to like
conceal carry them or or what? Yeah keep it in your pockets. Hands always in your pockets. That's
why like nerdy homeschooled like karate dorks always walk around with their hands in their
Exactly yeah, yeah, it's cuz they pulled them out in their giant foam or it's like
You're charged with a different crime if you kill somebody and you know karate then yeah, you definitely karate
Yeah, it's no longer manslaughter because it's no way
You're charged a second-degree karate slaughter yeah, the only thing cooler than manslaughter
It's crazy how cool
Manslaughter yeah, yeah, hey our job is
Hearing man's laughter
Hearing
Or making guns laughter
But we do comedy man's oh yeah, yeah, I mean in that that way you would have been charged for that joke for sure
Cuz I guess as some funny now is the man that's some shit
- That's a big right now.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- That, you think you could get away with that in court?
Is like saying like, no,
that you forgot to put a space there.
- Dude, you know what?
That's, I think the next big,
the next big like, you know,
improv theater scam where we can get a lot of money
from people who want to go into the industry is,
you know, a comedy training style school thing
that uses karate type belts.
And you have different belts and you--
- That's so true.
- Like maybe, dude, maybe it's a roast--
- No, but if it was an improv thing--
- Maybe it's the school of roasting
and you go, you have like roasts.
- Oh shit, can you imagine how many of those belts
would be used to like accidentally kill themselves
while trying to jack off with it?
Like literally that would be like a fucking epidemic
in Los Angeles.
- If it's improv though, it would have to be like bow ties.
- Yeah, everyone's just walking around
with like red bands around their neck
where they permanently cut off circulation.
All these freaks who think roasting is like some high art.
Yeah, yeah, that's the best dude people who are like, yeah, like roasting like that's the only real thing
It's gonna be like what's up fat guy. Where'd you get your pants the fat ass pants ass? Fuck you store
Yeah, and it's like what if there was like a whole podcast dedicated to like
people making fun of one person
Yeah, oh could you imagine like people thinking like roasting one guy is funny
- That would be kind of slow.
- I'll say roasting one guy.
- That would be really mean.
- That would be so mean.
- Roasting one guy who plays up his stupidity a little bit is pretty funny if you do it for long enough.
But roasting a bunch of people is kind of messed up.
But just making fun of one single guy I think is probably okay.
- I think it's probably really mean and unjust.
And I think that if anybody knew of anything like that,
they should swarm the person who was roasted to make sure they're okay.
they're okay and make sure that they're in a healthy friendship. They should send a lot
of messages and make a lot of social media posts and just make sure everything's right
between the three or however many guys are doing whatever this thing is.
It's funny, we can't make this joke because I wasn't on the last two episodes so now it
seems like we had a problem. Because my dad texted me and was like, "Why aren't you on
the last two episodes?" Dude, you need to set a fucking boundary with
your parents dude. They should not hear me right now. Yeah, no my dad said that he looks
forward to it every Saturday morning and I was like oh well I can't tell him no. Tell
him to watch football like a fucking real dad. What is he doing dude? I don't know. Get
into a fucking sport, have some, he's gotta have some extra wood laying around, fucking
build something on Saturdays. Why are you listening to your son fucking talking about
shit right yeah ignore it don't pay attention to your son so glad my dad
hates me dude probably listen to the episode with Tom now what are thinking
my dad listened to the episode with that with Tom because of the name so I kind
of I was trying to torture the fan I received my comeuppance for that one
yeah and he loved it that someone asked him what I did and there is a podcast
and they like found it somehow and then they called him and he was like hey I
just listen to your son's podcast with my entire family and my kids in the car I'm
just gonna tell you don't listen to it he was like all right whatever Wow
that's such a crazy somebody who was that person to your dad was that just
his friends oh that was Snoopy Sarah but she's a complete Snoop Snoopy Snoopy
Sarah and her husband knows he did.
But just imagine being like, all right, all right, kids, like
we're going to listen to my friend's son's podcast on this
car ride.
Well, apparently you don't know him.
But it's like, you know, it's like his oldest friend ever.
And so his family's like, oh, let's listen to like, like they
know my dad, but I don't know.
They got it.
And they turned on the radio and they're like, you know what?
No, we should be supporting the Pitts family today.
That boy, that boy has always had something wrong with him.
Yeah, let's find out exactly what.
They thought it was gonna be a movie podcast.
Poopy, poopy boobs.
Yeah.
Apparently they called him and the guy was like, "Don't ever listen to that.
You will not be proud."
And my dad was like, "I fucking already knew that."
Pretty cool.
Yeah.
I mean, it's cool that your parents don't listen to it, but I guess my parents just know
everything that's ever happened to me now.
Yeah, I guess that's pretty tough, huh?
Yeah.
Do you feel like some stuff is off limits?
can't talk about your... Is that why you're so bashful? Maybe. Is that why you're such
a shy bashful soul? That could be it. Because I know you're hiding in your sweater and going
"ohhh" We actually hang out outside of this and let me tell you Patrick's parents, your
son is an absolute dog. Yeah. Something, I actually never hung out with Patrick outside
of recording the podcast. What do you mean I'm an absolute dog? Come on Pat, you're a
You're a dog on the loose, don't lie to me.
You know, yeah, I guess.
Yeah, you can't be chained up.
You're a rabbit.
You're a dog and you like bones.
Yeah, you're hungry for baby rabbits.
You're a dog, you're barking, you like bones,
and you chase cars.
And I love to sleep on the floor.
You love to sleep on the floor, you're an absolute dog.
You sleep in a little pillow on the floor that I bought you.
You sleep in my room, sometimes at the foot of my bed,
but then my wife kicks you off
'cause you're not allowed up there.
Yeah, it's true.
And you like bones.
I throw coins at you to keep you under control.
- Why would you throw coins at a dog?
- It keeps the dog under control.
You know when you shake a can of coins
next to a dog or cat to scare it
so it doesn't do whatever it did?
- It's because they're so stupid
that they can't conceptualize money at all.
- I don't do that, but you've never seen people do that.
- I've never seen somebody throw coins at their pet.
- Not throw, he's saying that's the better idea.
You shake a can with coins in it.
- The normal thing that people do who are weird
is they shake a can of coins next to their pet's head.
- It's like a whistle almost.
- Yeah, it's like a whistle or like when you spray water
or whatever.
- Windex.
- Windex, so you spray Windex into your cat's mouth.
- Yeah, you can spray Windex in the cat's eye.
- Well, the whole thing is like--
- I've heard that, but throwing a coin is too much.
- The Windex thing makes sense 'cause it's like--
- What if it's only a dime?
It's a very small coin, very light too.
- Yeah, I guess dime will work.
- Okay. - Dime is fine.
- Well, let's, I mean, if you're okay with dime,
how about a nickel? - Let's role play
this situation.
- Nickel, no.
- Okay, penny, penny, penny.
- Penny's in the middle, come on.
- Yeah.
- And that's called negotiation.
That's kind of a business,
'cause he was not okay with any coin,
and then we got him up to penny.
- We got him up to a penny,
which is worth one entire cent.
- Yeah, so.
- So it's not only is it a good size of coin
to throw at your pet. - We don't even need
to print pennies anymore.
- But it's worth barely anything,
so if your pet eats it, that's fine.
- I thought with dogs you're supposed to
yank on their tail real hard.
(laughing)
When they do something wrong.
- I thought you're supposed to like,
wrap them up in chains and swing them around your head.
If your dog is being mean to you, you tie up the end of their tail with a rubber band until
the circulation cuts off.
It's like the Yakuza cutting off a pinky.
I thought you were supposed to take a big piece of plywood and drop it on them.
It's not that heavy.
You're supposed to drop a log on them from really high up.
I thought you were supposed to make them run on a log in the middle of a pond and the log
spins as they run and if they fall in the water they're disqualified. I'm thinking
again a dog I can't decide on size though. Right. You should get a you should get
like a bull terrier. You should get a small type of dog that you I think would
be a perfect owner of because you will kind of look like a bull terrier. I think
your bull is scarier. Is there a bald dog? Yeah you. A bull terrier looks like Caleb. No it
Let me look it up.
Let me look up a bull terrier.
Is this like a cool, like, Puerto Rican dog with a mustache?
Oh, this is the inbred, the crazy inbred one.
That I could never remember the name of.
Now I will.
Bull terrier?
I don't look like a fucking bull- I don't have tiny little eyes.
You look like a bull terrier.
Shut up!
No I don't, dude.
You think I'm saying I look like the fucking target dog?
You have the same kind of like, like, like head shape.
You have the same demeanor as one.
What, loyal?
I mean, like, you guys don't- And a little hungry?
You don't look that much like it except you have similar ears.
Yeah. My ears do not make a triangle shape.
Yeah they do.
What about these ears, are they triangular or large?
You better shut up.
I'm on a website right now.
Can we do like a quiz to see what type of dog Caleb should get?
Yeah let's do a quiz.
What type of dog should I get?
Here Caleb, answer these questions.
I'm here for them. I'm ready and I'm willing and I'm ready to help my family.
Okay, quiz.
what dog breed matches your personality from 4paws.com.
What's your activity level?
- I hope I don't get like evil pet a dog.
(laughing)
- What's your activity level?
Pretty low, moderate, high, very high?
- Very high.
- Okay, pretty low.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm running right now.
- Honest to God, if you had a dog,
you would never want to walk the fucking thing.
- Lie.
- No, you would--
- What do you mean?
I walked today.
- All right, point taken.
I walk today right now. I'm fucking yabba-dabba-dooing with my feet as I sit in this far right here. We're not very high
I am it's are you are you are you an introvert or an extrovert or somewhere in the middle somewhere in the middle?
true
Sometimes I'm shy, but sometimes I can low-key be the the the loudest voice in the room
What's your absolute favorite thing to do and here are your options read a good book?
I know it's not that travel to new vacation spots
Biking running and anything athletic camping hiking and anything outdoorsy or hang with friends and family
watch TV
I'll put that under
Is there like a trip?
Is there a watching TV dog that kind of is like really comfortable to sit on like a couch?
I think maybe a golden doodle
You think a golden doodle would be like could just withstand the weight of my ass when I sit on the couch
and I watch the Simpsons. I my parents have a golden doodle and
He watches TV with me all the time
Would you rather try something you never done before or do something you already know you enjoy a dog with a human vagina
So do something you already know you enjoy yes, sir
What's the most important you your relationship self-improvement memorable experiences staying healthier the environment
Okay
(laughing)
- Which describes you best, low maintenance,
up for anything, or family oriented?
- Most evil man who ever lived.
- Up for anything. - So low maintenance.
- Up for anything, yeah.
On a weekend, would you rather explore a new city,
go backpacking in the woods, have a backyard barbecue,
run a 5K, or work on a creative project?
- Run a 5K, I would love to run a 5K.
- There's so many questions on here.
Do you intend to go with the flow, take the lead,
come up with ingenious solutions?
- That one, ingenious solutions!
I don't even want the other one.
Ingenious Solutions, that is me.
- Go with the flow, take the leader,
come up with ingenious solutions.
- Are you chill, a leader,
or just the biggest genius ever?
- Show results.
Athletic Weimeriner.
- Oh, dude, yeah, a Weimeriner?
- Weimeriner.
- Weimeriner!
- How do you spell that?
- Weimariner.
- Oh, dude, this is a complete me of a dog, dude.
yeah it does look a lot like you it's great
i'm great up
this is all from the uh... melanin in my skin that i'm just great
is like a dog from the blue monday video
this is a good dog
there you know
now let's look at it i think i'll look up athletic by speed thirty five miles
per hour
now i could beat him
i think that's the speed limit in all of new york let's see if they're any
available for adoption in New York City? Cost. $700? No. But if you get a top quality dog,
$1,700. It says their energy level is 5, but their affection level is only 3. Their heat
sensitivity is 3. I need the least affectionate, most energetic dog so he can do much worse.
This one is not very affectionate.
Friendliness is only two levels.
It only has a level two friendliness.
I didn't realize dogs had stats.
Who knew either?
But they do on Pet Finder.
It says right here.
Can I change the attributes of the dog and lose a point for one?
It's like a racing game.
You can't really change the stats.
It's just like a different car?
Do I at least get a boost or something?
Can I upgrade it with more experience?
I think you can put a nitrous tank on the back.
That's actually a really good idea.
have to you'll have to have a nitrous tank that's perfect all right anyway
anyway this is not about dogs no yeah keep telling yourself that sorry best
ways to get revenge on younger sisters by anonymous this guy was so his ideas are
so diabolical. He wouldn't dare put his name on this. Anonymous, 115 years old, Iraq, soon
to be New Jersey, Canada. I really hope you realize none of this stuff is true. I also
love this test. http://www.nerdtest.com/mq and then a bunch of numbers. Wait, can we take
the nerd test right now? Yeah, let's check out this test. Dude, we're testing today. Dude,
testing in yeah monkey quiz okay well what was that I thought if you hate
monkeys if you hate monkeys this nerd test is the website which we I think
we've been on this website before a long time ago we should definitely start
doing stuff on here again because they got some good quizzes here for example
top user test this week are you ticklish do you think I'm fat
What level gymnast are you?
Like, do you think I'm fat?
*laughter*
Some kid just posted a bunch of pictures
of himself and his belly
and just has different
Wait, send it to me, I can't find it
*laughter*
Oh, I found it
Oh my god!
Oh no! Oh, that's so sad!
Why would you do that?
*laughter*
Just a bunch of pictures of him, like, holding his
His stomach just saying, "As you can see, I can grab generous handfuls of my stomach.
Do I seem any fatter, skinnier now?"
There's another quiz by a different person.
It's, "Am I getting too fat?"
Uh-oh.
Oh my god, dude.
Oh, that's like a kid.
What the fuck?
This is gonna be a...
Oh, this has to be fetish.
This has to be evil fetish stuff, doesn't it?
Oh no.
This is an evil website.
We can't take this nerd test.
No.
I want out of that website.
I just got like the most horrible feeling in my stomach.
That is a diabolical...
It's funny that we are always like two clicks away from the most fucked up evil thing online.
I don't know how it happens, dude.
Every once in a while I will like stumble on like an evil portal until this is the worst
website ever.
Remember the one about fucking monkeys?
Yeah, fucking monkeys.
That was evil.
There's definitely been shit that we like clicked on before you started recording.
We were like, "Oh no, this is not the movie."
Yeah.
All right, anyway.
Number one, best way to get revenge on Younger Sister.
Steal just one thing from her room per day.
Why not just steal a lot of things?
That's kind of genius.
I mean, what would you start with though?
I would just take the bed first.
Just the whole bed?
Yeah.
And see if she notices?
Exactly.
Because if she doesn't notice that, you've got free reign.
Yeah, younger sisters are so stupid and annoying that she probably wouldn't even notice when
she walked in.
She'd probably sit on her phone to go to sleep.
Mm-hmm.
Hi, guys.
She probably wouldn't even know if there was a pea under her bed.
Yeah.
Hi, guys.
Here's a comment.
It's Angel Dust here, and I have a brother to try all these pranks on, two thanks.
P.S.
If you want to have sex, write it in the comments.
Here's what I would do.
- A good prank would be like,
kind of a similar like, you know,
like incremental change is get like a bowl of your piss,
right?
And then just like go in once a day
and just flick it like holy water all over the room.
'Cause like the first day she probably won't notice,
but by day seven,
that's gonna be a lot of piss all over that room.
- True. - A lot, yeah.
- Just dip your fingers in it.
- But at that point you won't notice it
'cause it's been gradual.
- Exactly, nothing's gonna be wet.
There might be like little dots.
That's the thing, you could just like pee in your hand and just that once you're peeing
and then just carry it.
You don't have to keep your piss.
You know what I mean?
Well you don't keep it, I guess.
I mean you do, you put a little bit in a cup and then you dip your fingers in and then
you, why do you want to hold your piss so bad?
Well I'm trying to just like cut out keeping piss in the equation.
You don't have to like keep, you can dump it out whenever you're done, but like you seem
really kind of obsessed with like holding piss in your hands like a camel? No. Yeah.
I, no, that's not true. Well so, so you're saying you would, you would use a piss and
then so you just keep it in your hands for the rest of the day? No, keep it in
your hands until you bring it to the room. And then where would you put it? In
your mouth I'm guessing is what you would do? No, on the, you flick it on your
sandwiches for flavor. Did you just come up with that? That's good. That's amazing dude. Yeah, it's a punchline I just
thought of that's really really good use that for me i feel like it could use a
different setup but i feel like you could be i feel like you could be even quieter
when you said it too
yeah yeah um here's some comments um i tried but my brothers are twins he used
his other brother shoe
here's one i have a band name pink diamond come see us
this comment is really sinister
*laughter*
How the fuck is good as either?
Pink, dude, you don't wanna go see Pink Diamond?
Pink Diamond sounds good.
They don't have, they don't have the day of the show, they don't have the anywhere to find, they don't have the bandcamp.
You want them to do fucking everything for you?
God damn Pink Diamond.
If you search pink diamond band the only thing that comes up is like wedding bands that are made that have pink diamonds
Right the terrible sir. You know pink diamond. I'm I've become your manager. I'm taking over
They clearly need somebody to take charge
Uh-huh nobody's hearing all this shit the pink diamond review from London an alternative group from London a world where 60s film
soundtracks meet sample a delic acid house
I decided to do three things to my younger sister.
Yeah, that was the one I was gonna read. Very sinister. Very creepy.
That, my friend, I am so going to do it. I'm feeling evil today.
Good opinion. Thank you a lot. I wish I was as smart as you.
This is a good kid. Great, but I just want to be friends with my sister.
Yeah. Oh.
And she went insane.
He read the list just in case she doesn't want to be friends with him.
Yeah, right. She went insane. I took her favorite toy that she calls froggy and she is absolutely embarrassing. I
Share room with her that does complicate it a little bit. Yeah, she walks in your bed is gone
You know subsist notice anything different. Yeah. Oh, I stole I stole your bed. What are you gonna do? Yeah
That's your bed. Hmm. Is it?
Well thought out. We'll give you the last laugh.
This will work miracles on my sis.
This list should be called "How to get in extreme dead meat with your parents."
This- here's a comment here. "This is the same as stealing. You should be ashamed."
Works every time. Smack him on the ass.
Number two.
Wait, I got one- there's one more here.
and the two little sister noises yep number two put lemon juice on her
toothbrush yep have you guys ever done this pranksters grown up I was not a big
prankster I was a little pranker yeah what was your boys your go-to prank
pretty good prank on my I probably talked about it but my my science
teacher in the eighth grade we put like scotch tape over the sensor on his mouse
It doesn't count as a prank.
And he called the IT department and they replaced the mouse for him.
They brought like a whole new mouse.
One time I tried to do the thing, you know where you put shaving cream on someone's hand and tickle their face while they're asleep?
I tried to do that with my little brother and my friend.
And my friend like tickled his face with the feather and my little brother just fully asleep just put his hand on my friend's face.
(laughter)
- Just like smushed it onto his face.
- Yeah, I don't understand why you wouldn't just put
the shaving cream on the sleeping person's face.
- Yeah, like why do they have to pie themselves, you know?
- Yeah.
- Like just fucking, the ender,
why are you making all these steps?
Why do I have to like capture a bird
before I can do this prank?
- Right.
- Here's a comment.
I tried that before with my little sister
and she hated me from October till March 11th.
(laughter)
- This is the best thing ever.
I might even try it on her food.
I'm gonna prank on her sister
by putting lemon juice on her salmon.
- Yeah, I'm gonna put lemon juice on her lobster
in the butter, it's gonna be, she's gonna hate it.
- She's gonna be so mad.
I'm gonna put pepper, I'm gonna grind pepper
onto her salad 'til she says when.
She's gonna be so upset.
- Yeah, my sister has acid on her teeth,
which is really gross anyway,
but I tried this and her teeth were yellow and she stunk.
Thanks.
- My sister killed me.
(laughing)
- Love it.
My sister is yelling at me
'cause I'm playing my instrument.
- Greatest idea ever in known history.
Whoever posted this is greater than Albert Einstein.
- She will totally freak with the lemon taste.
- I like lemon juice.
I don't have any sisters, but on my cousin who is three,
that would be better.
I want to kill her so badly.
What comment here that says, "I don't love Ella"?
(laughter)
- Yes, just stop that.
- Better post it there than say it's a family dinner, right?
- Yeah, that's a good point.
- Oh yeah.
- Get it out of the system.
- Get it out of the top tens.
- Here's a comment.
How do you do the prank?
- Tried it.
Let's just say she broke my Xbox.
- Yeah, let's just say she did a little thing.
- She broke my Xbox.
He broke my Xbox.
This sounds hilarious, but probably not a good idea to be honest.
I like this one.
I put lemon juice on her toothbrush and hot sauce in her refreshments.
Her refreshments!
Yeah, yeah, she was drinking her bloody berries.
Ah, he gadzooks my refreshments!
What a clever, great, pleasant prank.
I am putting salt on her tooth-proof.
Tooth-proof?
T-B-R-U-T-H.
Uh oh.
Um, number three, jump out of a closet.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah.
It's also, you know.
Nothing wrong with this.
Pretty impressive.
Yeah.
Jump out of a closet.
Yeah, your, the biggest prank on your sister is coming out.
Yeah, yeah.
Jumping out.
Yeah.
I'm gay, ah!
(laughter)
- That's jumping out of the closet.
- Here's one.
- Hey mom, dad, I've been wanting to talk to you about something.
I'm gay!
(screaming)
- Here's a comment.
Haven't heard of this prank before,
but I'll give it a whirl.
- I did this to my sister.
She got so scared she ran into the wall.
- I am an only child, but it sounds good to me.
- Just doing it on yourself.
I'm an only child too, and I was adopted from China.
Maybe I'll do it to one of my annoying friends.
This one here, so it says, you know,
title, jump out of the closet,
and then Epic Jake comments and says,
and then scare her.
- I like this one a lot.
Don't, because I'm stuck for sure now.
(laughing)
- I'm stuck for sure.
- Just like the movie Buried,
just like stuck in the closet.
Has he tried this prank?
Yes, I love scaring!
This will work, thanks the top tens.
I love scaring.
Oh my god, I did the same thing when I was in India.
Also, my sister was 11, I was 15, now I'm 16, she's 12.
I climbed into my uncle's closet and then jumped out literally screaming, "It's me, Green
Lantern!"
She literally fainted.
I'm scared of Green Lantern too.
Yeah.
Number four, tell their secrets.
Here's the top comment. What a horrifying thing to do. Even if your younger sibling is annoying, they are still family.
Now your sibling will never trust you.
I mean, it's hard for youngsters to confide their secrets in others. You shouldn't be tossing them around like they're nothing.
Yeah, I found the little sister
commenter on this list.
Oh my fucking God!
Yeah, I don't I don't uh why are boys so obsessed with secrets? What kind of secret can a girl even have?
Pregnancy
Wow, you think so? I don't know. This person says get over it softy. So my older sister told me that I
Had missing walk because I said she couldn't play GTA 5 on me Xbox
So she said okay, then I'm telling mom that you have missing work. Oh
changed that you wouldn't play on it either so her secret is she's acting
like a boy towards girls
Caleb this is this commenter agrees with you here what secrets girls being fat
isn't a secret dirt it's true it funny when you do it to them but when it done
to me I freak more than I told embarrassing secrets because they would
give me an oreo if i did
uh...
yet
easiest ways by music fans
uh...
i can work out a bit here's here's a comment
make a
chilly sandwich
for her
enjoy your own sandwich
Here wait, start number five, I have to get something.
Number five, pretend that you're putting a curse on her and do bad stuff to her after.
Yeah, so this is good, well this is good because you can combine it with any other item on the list.
Yeah.
You first, you say, "I'm putting a curse on you," and then you put lemon juice on her toothbrush.
You know, this is kind of like...
Oh, and then you're cursed to have bad teeth.
Yeah, exactly. So this is kind of like a, this is...
You can add this onto any other prank.
uh... i was like say anderson's i thought there's a new is a government
grab a random hardback book take off the cover if it has one and say a random
spell while looking at the book symbols
then do weird stuff to her
taking out my uh... bible taking off the cover going
he's only by the usual d
and then just like what would be like
or
uh...
we will be more
probably feels like it probably is what it feels like to my flopped on her
stomach it's pretty good I try that yes today on September 2nd 2020 and I said
that they will have bad dream and so on they went and told on me
whoa yes today little sister goes I ran into the wall 300 times and stepped on
your Legos I hate you and I troma lid my Bible I'm gun no go to hell now I will
smiley face that's it you make a child I do it and hide her Chromebook last
comment me likey weird-ass fucking kid all right this one is fucked up yeah
this is not okay to clean the toilet is number yeah I don't think that's a good
I don't think that's okay to do unless the toilet is filled with lemon juice in which case it's pretty good unless
It's like a toothpaste toilet, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like you guys just kind of like go in there or
You just like if it's her if it's her ass toothbrush
That's a yeah, or if it's her toothbrush that she uses to brush her ass with yeah, which everybody I mean, that's like
Did you guys know that white people don't use a toothbrush to brush their hats?
I didn't know that. Isn't that disgusting dude?
I didn't know that. Now that I know it, I'm pissed.
Me too.
I did this once and I even rubbed it in some poop. So it was really gross. I did this to my brother though, not sister.
Oh, okay. Well don't say it then. Yeah, if it's not to your sister, don't say it. Absolutely. Yeah, I agree.
I'd do this, but she'd get sick and she would be at home while you're at school. That's the only thing. Epic Jake.
I did and now her stomach hurts. I am scared that something really bad will happen.
(laughing)
- Just kidding.
- Dude, you know that kid is like freaking the fuck out.
- Yeah. - Oh yeah.
- Like to type that out and post that on this website,
I'm scared that something really bad will happen.
- Yeah, he made his sister eat shit and she just dies.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Remember to leave it in there when you're done.
That's a bad idea, just like,
I'm not gonna use my toothbrush,
I'm not gonna be like, oh fuck, where's my toothbrush?
Oh, it's just in the toilet.
I have this black sharpie and my sister has her own.
She had hers from years ago
and I just bought mine a month ago.
She wanted mine because she lost hers.
I'm like, you have your own.
Then I get mine and see another black sharpie.
I draw lines and see which is better.
She snatched mine.
I shouted, give it back.
Then my parents got involved and I got mine back
and she was winking like a baby.
And then my mom just took mine.
Then she gave it to my sister.
So now it's revenge.
- Oh my God.
- Cruel for idiots.
they could die from a toilet disease
i like that like
like i think at least half of these people just think that what this prank
will do is give them bad breath
like right now is it that you're making the people who puts that other breath
discusses no bad you have stinky green lines coming out of your mouth yeah
uh...
number seven
poor cold water on her while she is in the shower
I've done this. I remember, yeah, I did this to my older brother once and he ran out of
the, he like ran completely naked, like chased me through the house to beat me up. He was
so mad. It was awesome.
When you like flushed the toilet to make it run cold for a minute?
No, we had like ice water.
That never happened.
And dumped it over the thing.
That happened at my house.
Yeah, the toilet thing never worked at my house.
That never happened at my house.
That worked at my house.
It was just too rich. Just like my water was like mad hot all the time and shit.
I have boiling hot toilet water.
- The reason that that happens is because
when you flush the toilet,
all that water goes into the shower.
- Yeah.
- So, and that water's cold.
- That's a good point.
- 'Cause it's been sitting in the toilet all day.
- I do wish that's how it works,
'cause that'd be a great prank.
It goes like Play-Doh, spaghetti your shits
out of the toilet, or the shower head.
That'd be awesome.
- Yeah, pee too.
- Here's a comment.
- Yeah, and even some pee in there too.
Some toilet paper, some nasty,
and maybe if you put a Q-tip in there.
- Here's a comment.
and watch the makeup slide off
or maybe turn off the heater in winter and see if she likes a chill surprise
uh...
this is this idea was awesome my little sister got sick and puked everywhere
from cold water
sounds like a baby
it's still puking
there's already water
You're already getting hit with water and then...
She's probably... it was probably the... like chewing is like shock.
Shocked her system, yeah.
Just instantly vomited everywhere.
I guess that's the best place to puke is in the shower.
Yeah.
What if you see her naked?
That's a very strong point.
Yeah, that is a good point, yeah.
Number eight. Find a balloon and put it in her pillow so when she lays he head back it will pop.
You don't think that they would notice a giant party balloon?
Just like one of those ones that's like shaped like Spider-Man, like the ones that are like
like the big like Spider-Man balloons.
Yeah, the Mylar balloons.
It looks like a giant one.
The ones that like you can't even pop by like, laying there.
Yeah.
I did this and she screamed, ran to mom and said, "My head cracked open.
It was so funny."
She sounds stupid.
Can kids under 18 do this?
(laughing)
- No. - No.
- Yeah.
My mom would kill me, she doesn't like her carpet wet,
but I will put bags in it to rumble around.
- I'm doing 'cause sis took money.
- She started to scream and cry a lot,
then she ran up to my mom, oh yeah.
Might crack my head open, yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Nice job, but no. - I shouldn't have
proofread it.
Alright, and then number nine, this is a, this takes a serious, cruel drop off here.
Did we read this one?
What?
"LOL sometimes I hate boys, they can be so stupid.
P.S.
Spray her least favorite bathroom spray on her chair."
That's a very polite brother.
What is a bathroom spray?
Like, like, Glade.
Yeah, yeah, her least favorite.
This is a very polite-
Oh, I hate cinnamon!
I hate the smell of cinnamon!
You know I don't want my chair to smell like that.
Yeah, bake her her least favorite pastry.
Yeah.
Give her her least favorite money.
Yeah. Number nine.
Number nine.
Post their nude pictures on the web.
Yeah, I don't know about this one.
Listen, to all the brothers out there,
this might seem funny,
but you're gonna go to jail.
Yeah, you're gonna go to kid jail.
go to jail you know it's that one and then number 10 lock them out of the
house like a very serious crime and it's like you don't get to come in and have
pizza yeah yeah yeah fart on her lock him out of the house amazing idea I will do
this to my little blackmail sister what I think this meant blackmail like
my little sister, I said my little black male sister.
(laughing)
- I was confused for a second.
- Doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
- No.
- My older sister drew on my face
and I'm trying to get revenge.
I would lock her out of the house,
but she has anger issues.
That's smart.
You don't want your anger issue sister to attack you.
- I did that to my sis and she was very mad
and I was like, "Mom, no me pegas,
"'cause I don't know Spanish."
I once fell asleep doing this and suddenly they got in from the window.
Did you guys ever get locked out of the house growing up?
Yeah.
Dude, I got so good at just like, I had a wallet for so long that just had like my dad's old
triple A card in it when I was like 12 just so I could whenever my older brother would
lock me out I could just expertly just safe crack my way into the door.
Dude, I was so good at it.
I didn't get locked out like as a prank, I just got locked out by accident.
I didn't know.
- I didn't get locked out as a prank.
- Yeah, I didn't have any brothers, so.
- Dude, brothers are, brothers will--
- Brothers are the ones who will lock you out.
- They teach you a lot.
- I've definitely locked out my sibling
out of rooms and doors before.
That's very fun to do.
That's one of the ultimate brother activities.
- It is very fun.
It's one of the easiest, it's basically a button
that is an instant prank.
- Yeah.
- It's fucking genius the way they have
these doors locked these days.
- It's great to do to a wife or girlfriend, too.
- Absolutely.
had Jana locked out a couple weeks ago on a 104 degree day outside. She's in our
she's in our hallway banging on the door for about 40 minutes. It's very funny.
And I was playing video games with sound cancelling headphones on. I go out there,
she's crying her ass off talking about how she has has to carry all these
groceries and then I get to play it off as a prank. Right. It's pretty good.
Now that it was a prank so like you can't even get mad about it. And then the tears turned to
laughter almost immediately. Yeah. Yeah. It's also it's funny as hell to do to
your older family members like a grandfather or grandmother who are 80
years old or older. Here's a really funny prank that you can pull on a grandmother.
So instead of locking her out, that's a little cruel, basically cover your entire
bathroom in olive oil and then lock her in, right? And then say, "Grandma, I think I
saw a mouse in there." See that wouldn't work because she would never go if there's a
grandmother will never go in a room that has a mouse in it. No, you have the door
locked. She says, "Let me out!" You say, "Okay, Grandma, I'm trying to find the key to the
bathroom, but I want you to know I did see a mouse or a spider in there." Yeah.
Yeah. And also, Grandma, I would love for you to try on those new rollerblades I
got you. Yeah, and Grandma, I'm really hungry. Yeah, I'm so hungry I might push you over.
I need you to come make me food right now. You need to try and get out of that
room. Yeah, you can come make me delicious food. If you want to give her a treat, set up a slip
and slide between her room and the kitchen and say, "Grandma, you know what time it's lunchtime,
I would like my sandwich." A really good classic grandma prank is a pitfall. Yeah. Works every
single time. You put foliage and jungle vegetation in the middle of her linoleum kitchen floor. She
says, "I don't remember these stairs up to the top of this, all these leaves being here."
I say, "Grandma, I really need the jelly toast that you make so well. You make it like nobody else. I need jelly on toast right now."
*laughter*
Yeah.
And then you put friendly spikes in the bottom.
Right.
Yeah. Mario spikes.
Yeah. Make her bounce up and hold her bottom.
Warning! Do not do this prank if your grandma has one or less lives left.
*laughter*
She will not respawn.
Yeah, if there's like-
She will go back to the beginning of the world.
If there's only one little picture of your grandma's face in the bottom left corner of the screen do not do this prank
It's a bad idea
Number 11 hide just one of their best shoes
That's such a great idea because Christmas is coming up, and they will want to wear good shoes
Facts we've been saying this where it's missus coming up in a hundred days when you feel stupid as fuck though
if like your sis like grabbed her one single sketcher,
went to school and like low-key started the next big thing.
- Mismatched shoes.
- One shoe.
- One shoe, mismatched shoes.
- It's 137 days till Christmas.
- So that's amazing you knew that off the top of your head.
- Yeah, that was really impressive.
- Did you just count that?
- Yep, I did one, two, skip a few,
and I got all the way there.
- There's a comment, this is where ferrets come in.
What does that mean?
I don't know. Oh, you put a ferret in their shoe.
That's a- Of course. I don't think a kid can get a ferret.
A kid can get a ferret.
I don't think a kid should be able to get a ferret.
My friend in high school had a ferret and it killed itself.
What?
It jumped out of his hand, uh, and backwards and- and hit its head on the bathroom sink.
Sounds like your friend killed his ferret.
I don't think so.
Yeah. I believe what he told me.
Yep, the Elliot Smith himself, the ferret did.
Yeah, the ferret drove a steak knife through its own heart.
It's pretty amazing. If you guys knew this ferret,
you know the ferret, he was making some comments, and I was like, he was leaving
some... Were there hesitation wounds? He was giving away
some of his most prized possessions to people close to him. Oh really?
He was saying stuff like, "This is the last time I'm ever going to see you
again." And they'd say, "Why?" And he said, "I'm going on vacation."
Ferret sounds not very discreet, if you ask me.
bit on the nose she was a drama queen
yeah obviously he killed himself
uh...
let's skip around here
we got number nineteen shaving cream and feather while sleeping trick
we discussed that already
that's a number
number twenty one be happy when she's in trouble
pretty good
that's a good prank, just smile big whenever she gets in trouble
Delete games on our iPod/iPhone.
That's pretty fucked.
Yeah, that's not, if you, I mean,
it's most games that's okay, but Flappy Bird,
if you delete Flappy Bird, you cannot get it back.
I actually heard that on the news, on CNN.
Number 36, put diarrhea medicine in her food.
(laughing)
And I don't know if that means like,
like anti, like imodium, or like,
or if that means like laxatives.
Yeah, pro-diarrhea or anti-diarrhea?
Yeah, like are you trying to... I gotta say if you're putting like anti-diarrhea medicine in her food,
yeah, that's just a good brother. But if you're putting like laxatives in her food,
that I mean that's a prank. Number 30 is put a hot sauce in her drink and a comment says
"what were you thinking my mom caught me?"
You idiot! Had you not considered that my mom may catch me!
Number 31, put salt in her soap.
He he he he he, the salt will dry her skin out and she will scratch herself.
It will be so funny for her to scratch like an animal in front of her crush.
So funny.
We share soap, my whole family.
[Laughter]
One bar of soap for everything.
And throw it in the dishwasher.
Number uh, 53, tell her Santa is not real.
Oh my god.
There's a prank, there's a prank, and then there is being cruel.
This is cruel, so just stop.
This is so mean and would crush her dreams.
I wouldn't be able to do this.
She's so stupid, she would prove to me he is real by showing me the elf on the shelf we got in 2014.
I told an eight-year-old illegal immigrant who lives in her house,
who was six at the time, that Santa isn't real.
And she said that she actually knows that.
That's a comment from IHatesSchool.
And there's a comment from Popsicles in response to that that says,
"I'm not gonna ask why there's an illegal immigrant living in your house."
This one, I like how straightforward this one is. Number 55, "Eat on her bed."
Number 40 is, "Tell your dad that you heard her say she was a lesbian."
And then someone comments, "I did this and my family is Christian. Works perfectly."
Number 75, "Fart in her mouth while she is asleep."
Have you guys ever had someone do that to you?
What, fart in my mouth?
I think that's the most mad I've ever been is one of my cousins farted in my mouth while
I was asleep and I woke up right as the fart entered my brain and I just was, I mean I
was furious dude.
That is like, that is the ultimate disrespect I think.
Kick her butt.
Just beat the shit out of her.
Message her random stuff.
Um, that would get her pretty good.
Slap her, hit them with a broom.
Pick the lock while she's in the bathroom.
Yeah watch her poop.
That would be funny as fuck.
Tell her how much you love her when at school or in public around friends.
Put bug spray on her food.
Number 91, hit them with a broom.
Rip their homework in half.
Get a scary toy or a toy that she is already scared of and show it to her.
Follow them around everywhere and stare at them non-stop.
Put poop under her bed.
Which one is that?
120 and there's one comment that says, "This crap stinks."
Is that a reaction?
Yeah.
That's what you're going for.
Pour milk in her mouth and she is sleeping and it will make her throw up.
*laughter*
Just pour milk right in her mouth, she's sleeping on her back.
Number 145, pretend she's mentally ill.
*laughter*
Um...
Number 174, tell her that her nightmare is real.
*laughter*
Hey sis, you know your nightmare? That came true.
Alright, gotta go.
Force her to lick a frozen river and tell her it's just like ice cream.
Fart on things she loves, sneeze on her face when she's sleeping.
Message her random stuff, and this is, um, somebody's, this is
XXseveredHumanityXX says, "I texted my friend
random stuff once. What I texted is down below. Pumpkin, man, clown,
ball, playoff boy, bun, butt, shirt, porcupine, skinny jeans, man, clown,
butt, cheek, eye, eye, eye, eye, eye, eye."
Number 238, tell them that there are terrorists or demons and act deathly afraid.
Just like that they exist?
Yeah, and there's one comment here that says, "The terrorists is a bit much."
Frown face emoji.
Demons are okay.
Yeah, demons, but you know, tell them that there's terrorists.
Not cool.
There's so many of these.
I mean that's cause little boys are complete prank factories.
Scare her with her worst fears.
Force her to annoy your pet cat.
If she did that, then the cat will claw her face.
There's like, hold on, let me...
Control F lemon.
Lemon, the word lemon is used 17 times.
Number 50, pour lemon juice on her head when she's in the shower.
Number 95, put lemon juice in her drink.
Number 208. Number 102, put lemon juice in her lipstick.
Number 228. Put Kool-Aid or lemonade powder in the shower
head so the shower will be colorful and sweet. Tell her there is an emergency.
You're gonna have to get under your desk, there is an emergency. But just you, you're
the only one who's in danger right now. I have bad news, there's an emergency.
They just had an emergency in our house, so you're going to have to hide.
How would you guys prank your sisters? If you had sisters, if you had a younger sister,
How would you prank them?
- I would probably do number 265.
- I think poop under her bed is like insanely strong.
- That's a really good prank.
- That's just like-- - 265, throw away her makeup.
- That's mean though, that's like,
poop under her bed I think might be the least damaging,
the perfect balance of like,
like it's gonna piss her off,
but she's not losing anything.
- Right.
- I mean I guess poop, a fart in her mouth is funny too.
- Well, then you gotta clean up poop.
- You don't have to clean it up.
No, she and then when your parents are like when she goes to your parents you
just say yeah she keeps poop on her bed. She's trying to frame me for poop on her bed.
You say what you think my poop looks like that? No way.
Look at that it spells her name. You really think I could spell?
It says C-A and that's crossed out and that says her name.
Yeah. So what I have a lot of poop and it's real thin.
Who cares? It's almost like I put it in the in the the uh
the cake icer that we have in the kitchen and then sprayed it but nope came right out of my ass.
By the way I can't find the cake icer. Yeah, no idea where it is but it's definitely not in the
trash can so there'd be no reason to look in there. It's definitely not still in the drawer
because somebody couldn't find a place to hide it so don't try to use it if it is. And if there
is something if you do find it it has normal icing in it and not poop it's just brown icing.
By the way I'm allergic to cake I can't ever eat cake made in this house again.
And you guys are also allergic to cake except for my sister who actually loves cake with brown icing on it
And she her birthday's tomorrow and you guys forgot it. Yeah, that's it says all of that written in poop
Dipping your your your quill and to poop like it like it well, yeah
And there shall be a cake with the brown icing. Yeah
They find they they like find it in like like the dumb waiter that never gets open in the house some
stroll
Yeah, oh
My house got two dumb waiters. Yeah you and yourself
Yeah, it's too easy all right goodbye beautiful
Bye bye.