you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the mindless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Yay.
- We have somebody very special.
(laughing)
- Long time coming.
We have very important person, Tom.
with us here today.
Hello.
Tom is here.
Tom, last name on here.
On here, in here, inside of all of you.
Yep.
On your phone now.
Tom, all up in this, is with us today.
Very excited. How's it going, man?
Good, good. Thank you for having me.
Been waiting for so long to be invited on.
It only took how many episodes?
That's fine.
No big deal.
We were busy.
Yeah, we were actually like really busy.
We're so busy.
It sucks how busy we get.
There was this thing where Patrick, he had to like
make dinner one night.
That was a whole ordeal.
And I burnt the dinner too.
Oh shit. Dude, I'm so sorry. I had no idea.
Yeah, so now you feel bad.
I feel so bad.
I've been really busy too.
I've been kind of like working on my hustle.
My money. That type of thing.
Which, you know, anyone who knows,
that's a 24/7 type of deal.
Cameron has been auditioning for Stomp this whole time.
I've been auditioning for Stomp. I want to be, I would like to be a guy who gets to do
like the one really cool jump. Like I'm maybe not in the dance for most of
it but then I like jump from like 20 feet in the air and land on a trash can
and it makes a noise you've never heard before when my shins shatter. That's kind
of the role that I'm auditioning for. It's difficult. I've been in and out of
the hospital and the casting directors don't like me, they don't like the
threats I've made, they don't like the pictures I've taken of them.
And they don't like, they don't like, the thing is is that they don't like
something new, they don't like something fresh.
Right, I mean they just want to keep their old ways.
Absolutely, they want to keep the white man down.
Which is, you know, something I've gone on about at great length.
If you read my blog...
[Laughter]
You wanna go more into this one? Yeah, let's lean in. Let's go.
There are a lot of good recipes on that blog too.
Yeah, it's mostly recipes.
Except for the occasional post that's like, "Man, they won't fucking put me in Stomp!"
It's every recipe blog where there's like, you know, a thousand words of like the most banal story in a really good recipe.
Yeah, the story is just, "I have been auditioning for Stomp for ten months.
This is the only thing I'm allowed to eat because of my strict diet or my strict
training regimen. Yeah. Of making my shins as weak as possible so they snap on every jump.
Yeah I'm trying the calcium free diet. It's really been
doing a number on my bones. I can feel them getting crunchy. Yeah. They feel like
the inside of a peanut butter M&M.
I was gonna say if you're at peanut butter M&M,
wait till you get to Butterfinger texture.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's gonna, yeah, your bones are just gonna flake off.
I've been sitting in hot cars all summer trying to melt my bones down just a little bit.
I've been sitting in a hot car and then going into the, sneaking into the walk-in freezer
at McDonald's to try and make my bones more brittle so they break more easily.
- I've been soaking, filling up a bathtub with Coca-Cola
and just dipping my legs in for hours at a time.
(laughing)
- I've been--
- And the acid just kind of burned through.
- I've also been heavy on the microplastics diet.
That has been really good for me.
I'm working on becoming infertile
because that will make it easier for me to retain
and perform better in my auditions.
- Well, actually, if you want to become weaker,
you need to cum as much as possible
because retaining actually makes you really strong.
And that's just a fact. - It's true.
- I don't mean to correct you on your own show, but--
- Well-- - Like, I just, you know,
if we're gonna talk about retaining--
- Okay, let's talk retaining. - Why don't Cameron
just end the recording? - Yeah.
(laughing)
- I need to, I still need to have some strength.
I need to be able to jump.
All right. - No, no, they can drop you.
They could just drop you. - That's true.
- That's true. (laughing)
You know, I might bring that up to the casting directors.
That might make them a little more sympathetic to my cause.
listen guys you can you can just get pull me up there in a harness you don't even
don't worry about a catwalk or anything just let it go
yeah let me go let me do my thing all right nobody get me another just let me
fall it's gonna be good it's gonna be great
and i mean if you if there's another guy inside the trash can that i'm falling
onto that'll make an even crazier noise i mean it's all about
you guys you guys are making the same stomping noises day in day out i want to
do something new okay here's an idea we get an even weaker
guy inside of that trash can. And so when you land on him, he
crushes just in half completely.
Yeah, I imagine it's gonna sound like it's gonna sound like the
green line at the Boylston stop in Boston combined with the
Minecraft fall damage sound and it's gonna be incredible. It is
gonna change the game and just wait until I chop and screw it
because I'm also a DJ.
We're only gonna have one shot at this.
Yeah.
So you better get the camera out, all right?
It's gonna be so sick.
I'm just glad that, you know, Cameron's following his passion.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Absolutely.
I mean, yeah, you know, other podcasts, other podcasters, they sit around, they, you know,
they talk for two hours a week to each other and then they spend the rest of the time,
what, watching movies, playing video games, reading The Silmarillion, going on a walk,
trying to figure out what to do.
No, not me.
I've never done anything like that.
and day out I'm jumping off my couch over and over and I am creating a hairline
fracture in my shin so that those puppies just explode out of my legs when I when I
have to stick any fall that's further than that.
Yeah, you're micro bruising your shins with a hammer by just tapping it over
and over again creating small fractures.
I have a doctor, I have one of those reflex hammers that the doctor they have
at the doctor's office and I'm just hitting my shins over and over again in
different spots and it I can see it's it's really it's really magical. I can see the effects taking
place and I think you're gonna like it. Yeah I think you're gonna really like me in Stomp
whatever the next Stomp is. They have like a whole theater I've seen I think I was walking
somewhere around here in New York. I haven't seen Stomp I've seen a theater that just said Stomp on
it I are you thinking of like a basketball court where you saw saw guys
jumping around I you go oh this is so this is crazy these guys that might be
it might be well it's a stomp no it's on second Ave the East Village theater with
shows ranging from Little Shop of Horrors to stomp but it's called stomp
so it's not called Little Shop of Horrors and stomp well it'll be called
little shop of horrors and Cameron's done.
Hey!
Oh my god.
They are doing Stomp.
I'm looking at it right now. They have resumed
Stomp after COVID-19.
Oh, thank god.
Finally.
I might need to take a trip up to the city.
Yeah. Go to Stomp.
Yeah, go to Stomp. Seven times in a week.
I just want to
see how much tickets cost really quick.
They're probably
so expensive but I am on the merch page and I got merch they got merch dude they
got you can buy stomp drumsticks for $15 just like they use in the show they do
they use drums they wouldn't I thought they just I okay I'm gonna expose myself
here I've never seen stomp and I just assumed they jumped around a bunch that's
so messed up man I've never stopped either I think I've seen like a
commercial or a preview for it on a DVD or something
None of you guys have seen Stomp?
They do percussion with like garbage cans and stuff, right?
I've never seen Stomp.
Is that, that's an element of it?
Yeah, okay.
I'm glad I got that right.
Yeah, well, I don't.
I just assume it's people jumping around, stomping on the ground.
So, but then like, it shouldn't be called Stomp.
It should just be called like, "Noises."
Yeah.
Yeah, "Trash Noises."
Yes.
You're not going to believe this.
We could get two seats to see Stomp tomorrow.
Oh, shit.
for $48 each.
- Ooh. - What?
- They got three tickets available too.
Look at that.
They're all next to each other.
- Oh, look at this.
There's three of us here.
Let's go.
Let's do it. - Whoa.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- Here, if we see Stomp,
I'm only gonna see it in Dayton, Ohio
at the Victoria on October 15th.
(laughing)
I'm putting my foot down.
- All right, I'll meet you there.
- We're gonna get Skyline and we're gonna go to Stomp.
- Oh my God.
That would be a dream. - Beautiful Dayton, Ohio.
Yeah, beautiful, beautiful Dayton.
I love it.
Tropical Dayton, Ohio.
Yeah.
I've been there.
I've been there like when I was 18.
I just turned 18 and that was like my birthday road trip was going to Dayton, Ohio.
I assume you went to the university and like partied or?
No, no.
It was me and my mom.
Okay.
And my friend Alex and my dad, my brother.
Nah, that sounds like a fun trip.
Yeah, we just, it was the first time I've ever eaten raisin canes.
And then I found out that it wasn't a chain that's local to Dayton.
Oh yeah, you can just get that anywhere.
It's like when I went to LA and I had Chick-fil-A for the first time.
I had Chick-fil-A for the first time in LA too.
Oh yeah, I forget they don't have it.
They don't have them around here. I think they have one around here.
They have one in Nashua, New Hampshire.
There is a there's a fake one in Boston. There's one on Google Maps. It claims
there's one but if you go there it's just there's nothing. It's empty and there are
a bunch of reviews on it that say "Do not go here this is a fake Chick-fil-A."
Yeah that was great because I did want to try it in Boston. I never got tricked by it
though. Me and Caleb were like yeah we walked to try and find it and we
just it was like an empty storefront and we talked about like taking a picture in
front of it and then just photoshopping like a Chick-fil-A sign there and just
like rating it five stars. I'm so glad they finally opened. Yeah we never we
never got around to it. That would be a good idea though you know if anyone else
wants to steal that go ahead. That's like that's like when the Taco Bell first
started open up. Oh my god dude yeah that yeah I'm that one I'm so glad that I
don't live downtown that I and I don't go downtown anymore now that the Taco
there because that would be a problem for me.
Yeah.
That would be an issue.
You don't go to downtown Boston anymore?
Not really.
I don't have anything to do there.
Go to Primark.
The Taco Bell.
Yeah, Taco Bell and Primark.
Yeah, well there's a Taco Bell near here too, but it's just far enough away.
Yeah, but it's not downtown.
Yeah, that's true.
It could be downtown.
You could do a...
I could, yeah.
I've been to Boston twice in my life.
Yeah, alright.
Let's see.
What do I remember from Boston?
could help my sibling-in-law move, which is what I did the first time I visited, and then
you could take like that walking tour.
Yeah.
Which we did the second time.
That's something Cameron's never done.
That walking tour with Taco Bell, now that would be a dream.
That would just be very nice.
It's a walking tour to Taco Bell.
And all the stops are just like, "Oh, this is where like..."
Well, I would go to Taco Bell first.
I would like...
It's like getting popcorn at the movies.
I would go first, I would get a huge bag, I would get like 20 items and I would just eat
them insanely loud right next to the tour guide the entire time.
And I would keep offering, I would keep interrupting the tour guide to offer them like a quesadilla
or something and getting really offended when they said no.
But why would they say no?
You're offering like a free...
Exactly, why would they say no?
I don't know, I guess it's kind of messed up.
Yeah, there would be a lot of trouble by the end of the tour.
I would be in a I would I would have gotten myself into in big trouble, but I can't elaborate on
It's a oh you could go to the
The army navy store there
Is there an army maybe so yeah, there is yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's disappointing that they have both like I'm supposed to have a rivalry
Right. Yeah, it's all okay. All along. They're on the same side
This sucks
At least I have wrestling that's still real. Yeah, but the army and the Navy that's fake that's
Yeah, that's ruining my mood
All right
I feel like we can kind of get into this stuff kind of early because most of them are this is I think longer than
Most of the stuff we do
Yeah
So yeah, we got you know
Sweet sweet baby boy Tom with us. Oh, yeah, we figured we'd read some sweet delightful story
That will make nobody mad.
Nobody will get angry at us or tweet at us. Yeah, no one will say "ew". Nobody will be unable to finish this episode.
Well, they're nice stories, and they're nice. They're heartwarming.
Yeah, these are some stories. So basically you just throw this episode on.
You leave this, you play this through your baby monitor at your baby.
When your girlfriend asks, "Hey, what's the deal with this that podcast that's on your phone that you listen to?"
you can show her this one. Yeah, this is the one. This is the first episode you have them
listen to. This is the girlfriend and parent safe episode. Put this on at work. Yep, absolutely.
If you're allowed to play any sort of thing at work, this is fine. Even if you're not,
you know, your co-workers are going to love you. Just put it on. So yeah, this is a, it's
not really a list, but it's a list that, it's a list in that it's a list of stories that
I found. Most of them are on DeviantArt, which I'm going to try and delve more into for this
show because I did not, I kind of thought it like it came in a stroke of genius. There's
I forgot there's like text posts on DeviantArt and there's some crazy stuff on there.
There's a lot of bad stuff on DeviantArt.
There's people that post their food all the time on DeviantArt and it's just the saddest
meals you can imagine.
I love the people who Photoshop themselves to have powers and stuff.
That's really nice looking at those.
Oh yeah, those are the sickest ones.
Well, I like making them and imagining myself as being stronger than Goku.
I don't want to give away yet what this is.
So I'm going to read the title, but not all of the title, and I'm just going to start
reading the story.
And, you know, it's just a nice story.
So I'll just read this to you guys.
Fun with this story is called Fun with Babysitter.
Okay, off to a good start.
So it's going to be a nice story.
A nice story about a nice little evening.
Okay, here we go.
It's Sunday, meaning Max's mom is going out tonight.
Max loved Sunday because it meant he got to see his babysitter, Ashley, who he secretly
had a crush on. Max was playing in his room, patiently waiting for Ashley to arrive.
"Hey Max, we see Ashley pulling in the driveway so we're going to leave now!" Max's mom yells
from the other room. Max quickly jumps up and bursts out of his room. When he gets to
the front door, he sees Ashley standing there. "Hi little guy," Ashley says, opening her
arms for a hug. "Ashley!" Max yells as he runs over to Ashley and gives her a big hug.
"Bye Max, be good, love you!" his mom says as she leaves. "I missed you so much," says
Max, I miss you too, cutie pie.
What do you want to do today?
Hmm, I don't know.
You can't think of anything?
So, so far, this is just really nice so far.
I'm really, I'm--
- Yeah, this is a nice story about an adult child.
(laughing)
An adult with a babysitter.
- Yep, this is a 21 year old with a--
- 21 year old with a babysitter.
Yeah, can't stress it enough.
I fucking hope it's an adult.
- Jesus Christ.
- Well, there is one thing Max starts to blush.
well what it is
max give no on swear
and just let us know that more
you yet
you won't want to do it
what are you talking about you know i would do anything you want to do
but but it's
weird
weird so what there's nothing wrong with being a little weird
there is it
no not at all max i would never make fun of you
actually sweet angle like voice and a pretty big smile on max's face
so editor on here's a good idea
so
what is it you want to do
well i i i am
max starts but again
can i smell your book
it
this is a little bit good to have a good
my blood
actually look confused
on now you think i'm weird
no max not at all i mean if you want a small but i guess there's nothing wrong
with that
so you'll let me
of course
max jump with excitement
So, I guess I'll just lay on my belly, and you can lay your face on my butt and smell it."
*laughter*
Max giggled.
"Okay."
Ashley laid on her stomach, followed by Max burying his nose in her cracks.
*laughter*
She was wearing leggings so Max could really get his nose in.
"Ha ha ha, oh, that tickles," Ashley giggles as Max starts taking big sniffs of her stinky
bum.
"How does it smell?"
Ashley asks.
"Stinky!"
"Well, duh, it's my butt!"
Max cointined to sniff away at Ashley's bum.
Suddenly Ashley felt a rumble a rumble in her tummy.
"Uh oh, I think I have to fart.
You might want to get away, Max."
"You can fart?"
Max says eagerly.
"You want to smell my farts too?"
"Okay, but I'm warning you, they're really, really bad."
"Birds, pfft."
(laughter)
All these stories have the most, the funniest onomatopoeia I've ever seen.
They're really...
They love onomatopoeia so much.
The smell hit Max hard, but he loved it.
He inhaled Ashley's toxic aroma deep into his lungs.
"Ha ha, you really like that, huh?"
Ashley wiggles her butt at Max's face.
"You... oof."
voice was muffled from Ashley Asscheeks. Here, I got some more. Burt. Blarp.
Blarp.
Dude, I know exactly what a blarp fart sounds like. I can hear that in my head.
I know. I mean, it's beautiful.
I'm lost on blarp. I can't imagine a blarp fart.
I mean, what the human mind can create is beautiful.
with joy and farts the smell hit Ashley's nose phew that stinks she covers
her nose with her shirt I gotta say I'm impressed you can thank all the gas my
friends usually have to leave the room when I rip one
*laughter*
Ooh, a silent one.
That one gonna reek.
Oh boy it did.
It stunk like a fresh pile of shit.
*laughter*
What?
This next one, this next word...
*laughter*
bubble blur. Oh my God, I'm so gassy today. It's your lucky day.
Isn't it Max Blorp each part max sucked directly into his nose
enjoy every second of what was happening. Okay Max. I think I
got one more fart in me Ashley grunts and then bo bo bo bo bo
The fart shook Max's head.
He couldn't believe the size of that one.
Ashley laughs.
"Wow, that was a big one, huh Max?"
Max pulls in head away.
"Yeah, it was huge!"
Max giggles.
"Ha ha, I'm glad you like them.
In fact, if I have to fart again later, I'll be sure to do it right on your face."
Max was so happy.
Now he loved Sundays even more.
Well, at least it had a happy ending.
That's what I'm saying, it's nice heartwarming stories.
It would be really funny if that had just like a horrible twist.
It's like, "Oh, and she died from her farts."
And Max had to explain it to the police.
Hey Pat, do you want to read this next one that you found?
No.
You sure?
Man, I hate this one so much.
This one's really bad. This one I think is maybe the worst one of all, and it's second.
This one is called "Mom's Little Boy - Extreme Slob Story" by Kink Chameleon.
And the summary of this one is "Mother spoils obese son."
Oh no!
We can popcorn this if you want.
Maybe we each read a paragraph.
Alright, yeah, that's good.
Three paragraphs.
Which one is this one?
This is the second link here.
Yeah.
Oh, okay, I see it.
I have to click on it.
I don't really want to click on it.
All right, it's not opening.
You have to hit proceed at the top because of how graphic it is.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right, here we go.
God damn it.
All right.
Chapter one, "Moms" and it's in quotes, "little," so that's how you know it's two adults.
Yep.
I hate that there's so many of these.
*laughter*
I hate this so much.
Alright, come on, stop stalling, let's get it.
Shira slowly opened the door to her son's room,
carrying a large, three-tiered chocolate cake.
Immediately, the musky stench she loved so much hit her.
It smelled of piss, shit, and cum.
*laughter*
Her son's giant form was sat in front of the TV,
some mind-numbing game or other he was ginormous over 800 pounds and entirely
naked except for the various stains covering his body ever since he was born
Shira wanted him to have everything he could ever want and with the sizable
inheritance from her rich family she never had to work she could devote every
second of every day to him it's a good character work some good like yeah
lower building here no he would he would never have to work a day in his life or
worry about anything at all. In fact, he'd never even left the house or been educated.
She wanted him all to herself, living a lie of excess, without any of those silly things,
like thought or dreams. Just pleasure.
Ah, that sucks to hear.
It's so bad, man.
Who's going next?
Just pleasure.
Alright, I'll go next.
Her daydreaming was interrupted by a loud whine and a fart from her beloved son.
The poor boy was hungry, and she was just taking in his brilliance instead of feeding him.
She quickly rushed to her son's side, son's side stepping past the wrapper's boxes and
the growing pile of shit behind her boy.
So cute!
As soon as he realized she was there, he released a torrent of drool and said, "Gimme!"
She handed him the plate and he immediately dug into it.
his face in chocolate as he moaned, taking breaks only to take a drink from his massive
extra sugar bottle of coke.
His toes curling in pleasure as he drank it.
As he continued his feast, Sheera knelt down and began massaging her son's massive stomach.
and begins shitting on the floor.
"Such a good boy, yes you are,"
she said, speaking in the same manner
someone would speak to a baby or a pet.
(laughing)
A baby or a pet.
She continues massaging his greasy belly
getting lower and lower as he continued farting,
shitting, and eating.
His moans of pleasure getting even louder.
- Dude, I don't think it's...
(laughing)
- Uh, no.
- I can't even, I can't even, like, no.
- Take this home, Cameron.
*crying*
*clears throat*
As she was tickling her baby's underbelly, she noticed that his cock was hard and immediately got to work massaging the shaft.
Her little boy didn't like to be pent up and she had started taking care of it more and more when he stopped being able to reach it.
She began jacking him off with one hand and kneading his belly with the other, saying things like,
"You're such a good boy" and "You'll be my special little boy forever."
forever. The sounds of shitting only intensified as he interrupted his own moans with loud
belches and food. This continued until finally he came and finished his cake at the same time
to rest of dream.
And then, yeah, a nosedive again, screaming with ecstasy as he ejaculated all over his
mother's hand and his underbelly.
She began kissing him all over his belly and licking up the cum.
When she had laughed it all up, "More!" he shouted, punctuating the demand with a fart.
She would have to clean all that shit up when he was asleep.
Her baby needed more food right now.
She quickly kissed him on the cheek and rushed to the exit of the room.
"Anything you want, baby, you're doing so well."
She went back to the kitchen, her mind filled only with love.
My mom listens to this show.
My mom and dad both listen to this.
Hey, look at it this way, right?
This is not a premium episode, this is a regular episode.
If you're hearing this and you're pissed off, you better subscribe to the Patreon and listen
to something else, alright?
This is your punishment for not subscribing.
I think, I mean, that was nice.
That was a nice little story.
Exactly, it ends with love.
Yeah, it's just a story of family.
One of the tags on this one is burp freeform.
Freeform burp.
Oh, feedy, fat freeform, feedy, handjob, lazy freeform.
Alright.
That was really good.
It was nice, yeah.
And you said Patrick wrote that?
No, I didn't.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, I misheard him.
it.
Oh, okay. Sorry, I misheard him.
This one's in the first person here and there's a lot of dialogue, so I was thinking maybe,
you know, I can read this, somebody can maybe play the part of the sister.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I just saw the title.
Yeah. Well, no, this is another, this seems fine. I'm not going to judge a book by its
cover, right?
Absolutely.
So, when we see this and it's "Sister's Dutch Oven" I think, "No, that's fine.
We'll see."
Maybe it's not so bad.
Yeah, it could just be about getting a birthday present.
Yeah, a cooking dinner.
You know, that's what the actual Dutch oven is.
Getting a Dutch oven for your birthday.
Maybe that's what it's about.
Yeah, okay.
Alright.
And I like the first line here.
I'll be trying to do a simpler style in this story. I mean, I won't go back to my
original 2014 style, but this one will be easier to read than my recent stories.
That's good to know. Yeah. I just had a nightmare, one of those scary ones that
keep you awake for the rest of the night. I also can't sleep because of the
loneliness that haunts me. I'll be waiting until 6 a.m. Then I'll seek
comfort by my older sister, who always knows how to comfort me. It looks like
human life is just a sad condition. Is there any way we could be happy?
happiness is just a distant emotion that will never reach I hope talking with my
sister will help me change my mind and finally be happy that will be the
emotion I was waiting for my entire life I wipe my tears away and wait silently
suffering the darkness isn't helping me 6 o'clock a.m. I knock at my sister's
door I know she's already awake she tells me to enter her room who wants to
the sister I'll play the sister I mean let me get it is yeah what's wrong she asked
me worried she probably knew I was crying the whole night I need a hug I
told her and she immediately hugged me softly I felt a lot better um and I need
another thing too but it's pretty embarrassing to say that I say blushing
you can ask me anything I'll be here for you she said I almost cried you are an
"An angel," I say, almost crying from happiness.
"So what do you need?" she asks.
"Do you remember when we were younger?
You used to trap me under the covers and... fart.
Well I need you to do that again," I said.
"But why?" she asked.
"It will make me feel better," I said.
"That's...
Okay.
I will do it.
Anything for you."
she said.
"Thanks," I said.
She smiled.
"Come here."
warmly inviting me under her covers.
See this is nice, this is a nice family story, cheering each other up.
Nothing wrong with this so far.
I was so happy she was doing this for me.
My sister is truly an angel.
I remember when she used to do that.
I remember her farts were really smelly.
I can't wait to smell them again and be happy.
The nightmare I had tonight was incredibly scary, so I need a bit of fun.
And what is more fun than farts?
you you you can play the part of the fart here she farted a bit loudly after a few
seconds a putrid stench assaults my nostrils and makes my eyes water maybe
her farts are just too smelly for me I move my head to outside the covers
stinky oh yes it stinks a lot can't breathe in there I said smiling uh-uh
"Uh, but you need to breathe the gas to stay better. I can't let you escape."
She said, covering me with the covers again, just like she did when we were younger.
"I'm so happy."
"Don't escape!"
She warned me.
"Alright, Pat, you're up."
The inside of the covers smelled revolting. It was really hard to breathe in that stench.
Does my sister have skunk-like powers?
It smelled like a can of broccoli went really bad.
"Can I breathe fresh air now?" I asked, disgusted by the rotting smell.
"Not yet," she said, giggling.
But I'm glad I asked her to do this.
It really makes me feel better, even though the smell is noxious, pungent, and very strong.
This smell gives me a nostalgia.
The quality of the air inside the covers quickly deteriorated.
I tried to push a shirt over my nose, but it was totally useless.
It smelled much worse than a sewer.
I need to escape from this.
I try to escape, but she prevents me from doing that.
"No," she said.
"Please, I'm dying here," I complain.
"Does it really smell that bad?" she asks, giggling.
"This smell is rancid," I complain.
"That's a good thing to hear.
Things are gonna get even stinkier now," she said, happy.
*farting*
At this point, thinking straight was impossible.
I needed to get out from this eye-watering stench that permeated the inside of the covers.
Every whiff I took made me want to throw up and cry.
I begged for fresh air, but she wanted me to smell her all of her gas.
I was helpless in this vomit-inducing stench that wasn't letting me breathe.
I knew my sister had nasty gas, but I would never have thought farts could be this smelly.
"Time's over! I hope you enjoyed!" she said, letting me escape. I gasped for fresh air.
"Finally!"
"Thirty minutes, I see!" I say.
"Yup! Do you feel better now?" she asks.
"Sure," I said, smiling. Her gas reached her nostrils and she held her nose.
"Oh, man! I wonder how you didn't pass out from the smell. You can't breathe this thing.
It's too stinky!" she said, giggling.
"It was too stinky, trust me!" I told her.
"You have been a good brother. I'll make you breakfast," she said, going to the kitchen. "I'll make you two eggs."
She said, smiling. I smiled back.
"I feel much better now, and the thought of that scary nightmare don't bother me anymore. My sister's stinky farts saved me.
I need another hug," I say. She hugged me again and said, "I love you."
I ate the egg she cooked, said, "Thank you for everything," then went into my room to play video games.
The sun is rising now and a new life for me begins. Hopefully a life full of happiness and joy
I think me and my sister will do this game more often so that I can be happy
I'm looking at the comments here. I didn't know there was comments on these
There's a somebody says love this and she's willing to do almost anything to help out her brother, too
And that's very nice. Yeah
Actually, and then they also say s actually this gave me the idea of Miyoko gassing her younger sister Kiko on like a dare
To see if she can survive her big sister's gas by locking her door, and she can't use her Saiyan powers to escape
Either or she loses I was wondering if you could do that and Kiko loves her big sister adores her actually their bond is massive
And they said I would do that in the next chapter life of coin conestine
World-building
Country yeah, oh man. Oh, yeah the the the the author of that was named chemical vacuum
Sister needed
Chemical vacuum oh
My god is a good
38,000 views
38,000 it is
Yeah, not enough honestly cuz it's beautiful. Hopefully. Yeah, it's good writing. Yeah. Yeah, it's really good writing
Yeah, I guess we should be plugging the names of the people who wrote these, you know, it's
really fair. The first Fun with Babysitter was by XStinkyFartBoyX. So, you know, if you
want to throw him a little money or something.
Oh, Chemical Vacuum is in the comments, it looks like. Oh, yeah, short but amazing.
Yeah. All right. Should we just keep going?
Yeah, what the hell? Why not?
Yeah, let's move on here to Amusement Park by GarbageMan95.
There's several characters in this one, so I don't know, we'll figure it out as we go,
I guess.
Okay.
This story contains fart humor in some detail.
If you do not like it, do not proceed to read.
It's a good warning right off the top.
Yeah.
All right.
Are you ready yet?
Sadie yelled.
"I'm coming, just wait," Ashley replied.
Ashley walked down the stairs, the steps creaking from the force of her weight.
She wore tight blue shorts with a matching blue shirt.
"Let's go already," Kelly said.
The four of them, Kelly, Sally, Sadie, and Ashley, began walking to their local amusement
park.
"I can't wait," Sadie said.
"Just don't get sick on the rides again," Kelly muttered.
They arrived and were greeted with the smell of greasy amusement park food.
"That smells great," Ashley said, sniffing the air.
"Let's eat first."
After waiting on line, and giving a nice view to anyone standing behind them, they couldn't
resist putting that in parenthesis.
"Oh, your whole story is about these ladies farting, but like, that's somehow the creepiest
thing."
"I know, yeah."
They found a table.
Their seats slightly bent as they sat down.
After devouring their food, the four of them searched for a ride.
"That looks like fun," Sally said as she pointed to a roller coaster.
Kelly's stomach rumbled.
"Are you okay?"
Sadie asked.
"Yeah, I'm fine."
As the coaster was making its way to the top slowly, an idea came into Kelly's head.
"Wanna see something funny?"
Kelly said with a smirk.
"What?"
She leaned forward and released a foghorn of a fart.
slightly shook their ride and caused the passengers behind to gag.
The girls erupted in laughter.
"Nice one!
Wait, let me try."
She grunted, and just as the coaster was about to go down, a window-shattering fart blew out of her butt.
A few unlucky passengers had their mouth open. It stunk of rotten cheese.
As they were screaming from the ride, Ashley yelled out,
That was the turbo!
(Laughter)
The turbo!
Soon later, the ride finished and the girls all had smiles on their faces.
"We should keep doing that," Ashley suggested.
"Do what? Fart?" Sadie replied.
"Yeah, it's funny. Let's find another ride."
They looked around until they found the bumper cars.
The four friends looked at each other and smiled.
The light buzzed green and everyone started knocking into each other.
"Brrrterrrr" was heard from Sally's car as she hit somebody.
Ashley drove towards Sadie and turned around so her backside was facing her and grunted
loudly.
This time, a low fart came out.
It stunk twice as worse as her other ones and lingered in the air.
Anyone driving into it would be hit by a wave of stink.
The cars turned off and they all got off from their cars.
Ashley had farted so hard on the bumper car that it still smelled after she got off.
As they walked away, they saw a machine that twirled you around.
Strapped inside, the ride started.
"Woo!"
Kelly screamed.
"Watch this," Sally said.
She then released a terrible silent fart.
It engulfed the ride and hit all the passengers with a wave of rotten eggs.
They all laughed.
"Okay, it's getting late."
"Alright, one more ride.
The grand finale," Sadie smirked.
"So, oh wait, who's saying this?"
"I don't know who that is."
"I think Ashley, maybe?"
"Okay."
So Ferris wheel? I mean yeah this is the kind of thing they got if they ever want
to film adaptation of this they have to clean up the dialogue. Yeah. They have to
make it clear who's saying what because it's just hard it's hard to understand.
We're doing our best. Yeah. But we don't have a lot to work with right now.
After walking there the four girls board the ride. It slowly turned as they reach
the peak of the wheel. Okay ready? All smiled. Yeah. They all lowered their pants.
They all lowered their pants so their bare butts were revealed. They hung their
their cheeks off the rail for all to see.
Come on man!
Three, two, one.
At once, the girls erupted in a gigantic fart.
It sounded as if three truck horns went off at once.
Cheeks vibrating from the farts,
it even caused the Ferris wheel to move faster slightly.
The smell was awful as it drifted downward,
enveloping a portion of the park.
They all laughed at their smelly work.
Guys got any more?
Sadie laughed.
If I push any harder, something other than gas is gonna come out.
They exited the Ferris wheel and went home from a day of stink.
This is at the bottom here, there's a description about this story.
Four gassy girls go to an amusement park.
Request from Codemaster 9999.
Sadie, Sally, Ashley, and Kelly are his OCs.
Sorry it took so long.
I felt it wasn't its best and still do.
Hope you enjoy.
I want to read a really good comment here.
This is a comment from user "That Guy Likes Farts."
I like and hate this story.
Like probably the first story that doesn't end up with someone shitting themselves.
Loves all fart stories.
Hey, they quote, they all lowered their pants so their bare butts were revealed.
They hung their cheeks off the rail for all to see.
I read some pretty nasty shit, but that's just wrong.
That's the worst part. I mean, I like farts as much as the best guy, the next guy, but
bare butts, no thank you.
Yeah, uh-uh. No, you keep the clothes on that thing.
I like that Garbage Man has his copyright there. In case I steal the story, he's going
to sue me. I'm going to get DMCA'd.
That was really good though.
I'm glad I will say to his credit.
They weren't family members and that's been a big step up, you
know, for the last couple ones.
They were just four friends.
Four friends.
Just four friends.
Then nothing.
No other qualities about them really either.
Yeah, just four friends.
And they love to fart and they stoke really bad.
They like to fart and go on the rides.
Who doesn't like to do that?
Yeah.
What are you supposed to do?
Hold the fart till you get off the ride?
No, you're supposed to engulf the ride with a big sticky fart.
You're supposed to hit them with a wave of eggs.
Yeah.
The turbo makes the ride go faster, so it's more fun.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I'm just glad that one of them didn't fart
and it ignited something in the engine of the bumper car,
so a spark from the bumper car made the whole ride explode.
That would have been really bad.
Yeah, and I'm glad they never include the other people
on the ride puking their guts up and being nasty like that,
Yeah, because that would be too much for me.
That would be too long.
I mean, you know, I can handle farts.
I don't think puke...
No, that's disgusting.
Absolutely not.
No, puke, it's just wrong.
There's a comment here...
Yeah.
It's childish as hell.
The comment here from Lone Skunk just says, "What made you write this?"
Well, Lone Skunk obviously didn't read the bottom because it was a request from Codemaster
9999.
Obviously.
Very obvious.
Yeah.
This next one's pretty long, but...
It is long.
It is, I thought that, you know, it's a nice, it's a supernatural twist on the
genre. I think maybe we can switch off paragraphs here. Yeah. Yeah. You know,
and also I would like to say so far, if we're rating these, you know, so far,
five stars, all of them. Yeah. Five out of five. Perfect. Yeah. I just can't maybe
but yeah, I'm going to be on good read.
I'm going to be recommending them to my to my high school English teacher. That's
friend to be on Goodreads. I've already printed out "Mom's Little Boy." I'm putting it in each
of my neighbor's mailboxes. Like, you gotta read this. I'm leaving them in the Little Free Libraries.
I'm putting them all in, like, leather-bound, like, books. It's gonna be great.
A compilation of really good stories. Yeah, and speaking of leather-bound books,
This next one by ubiquitous 101 is a girl's gassy spell book
All right, this was another request this is another request this one's pretty long, but you know, hopefully it's rewarding
Arena Lexington was your typical college sophomore
She was on her way home, but had decided to take a look at some of her college towns older buildings
It was then that she saw the book. It was a strange ancient looking book covered with dust and bizarre writing. This is strange
Why is this book just lying here? She couldn't help but pick it up.
Oh, well, it looks like the owner didn't want it anymore. So Irina decided to take it home with her.
Irina arrived at her house and examined the book. What's this? Looks like a spell book. She took a closer look at the writing.
I wonder...
She just knows it's a spell book.
It just says spell book on the first page.
Chapter 1 Fart Spell. It's like, oh, okay.
Irina couldn't resist the temptation. She tried to say one of the strange incantations.
Irina waited for a few seconds, then laughed. "Nope, just an old book with weird writing."
Irina put down the book and stood up.
It was then that she first felt it. A very slight pressure in her stomach.
A mild, but insistent bloating. "Oh my," Irina exclaimed.
The swelling only continued, stretching against the tight fabric of her shirt.
Her belly felt inflated, churning with growing amounts of gas.
Ireena was also becoming aware of the slight but incessant pressing against her bottom from within.
She realized she needed to fart.
Ireena was definitely uptight about that sort of thing, and she tried her best to hold the gas in.
But her stomach kept swelling and straining and her butt seemed to be
hugely inflating outwards. That's what happens when you're gassy, your butt inflates.
They don't know how humans work. They don't know how the body works.
Okay, this is a spell that she read. That's true. I'm sorry. That's true. It is supernatural.
Yeah. Uh-oh, he froze. Yeah. He froze there for a second. Oh shit. Yeah, we have to give
that the benefit of the doubt that something very magical could be
happening. We shouldn't be applying like real world logic to it. Right. The
turbulent gas churned within her. She now looked nine months pregnant, fertile with
feel flatulence. And Irina was still getting bigger and rounder. Her belly was
extraordinary taut, as if it were about to burst. Irina couldn't hold it in any
longer. The pressure was too much. An intense direct blast of gas seemed to
cause her butt to double in size before exploding out of her with such force
that her ass vibrated briefly.
Irina blushed, but sighed in relief.
Another fart slipped out, brief but considerably louder than the first.
Then two smaller explosions, one after the other.
In spite of her letting loose, however, her belly had swollen beyond anything humanly
possible.
It was inflated to the size of a large beach ball.
What was even stranger was that even though the farts were quite potent in smell, she could
breathe them in as easily as air.
Irina lost her balance and fell to the ground.
Her enormous belly forced her legs apart.
Irina groaned in visible discomfort.
"Too.
Much.
Gas."
A loud, long, wet, and extremely strong-smelling fart erupted out of her behind, causing the
floorboards to vibrate noisily.
Irina smiled in embarrassment.
Yet again, to her surprise, she could breathe in the dense air freely without discomfort.
"Dude, I hate when I'm trying to sleep and my upstairs neighbor won't stop farting against
the floorboards and vibrating them."
When she keeps casting the fart spell on herself and shaking the whole apartment, it sucks.
So she cut loose and started blasting away.
The room was soon flooded with Irina's flatulence and filled with the rumbling reverberations
of bombs going off.
Irina farted so many times in the next couple of minutes, she lost count immediately.
Once she was finished, the air was ripe with her innermost secret and private scent.
For the longest time, Irina sat in silence.
She had fun cutting loose.
But finally, she got an idea.
Why not try this out on her friends, just for fun?
Yeah, of course.
That would be my next thought too.
So she invited two of her best friends, Christine and Angela, over.
When they arrived, she made conversation with them for a while.
And then Irina cast a spell on both her friends.
At first, neither Christine nor Angela noticed the sudden change in pressure.
suppressed her desire to giggle mischievously at the sight of her
friend's belly slowly bloating outwards with gas. Angela's stomach rumbled
noisily and Angela blushed. "Oh, seems I'm a little filled right now."
Christine started to laugh but an even louder gurgle from her own belly cut it
short. Angela's face was visibly red. "I guess that meal I had disagreed with me
more than I thought." Angela's stomach rapidly swelled up to the size of a
volleyball. "You know if you guys can get your hands on that book you got a
got a good live show you could do.
- That's true, yeah. - It's true.
- The blonde haired woman was struggling
to contain the growing gas within her,
but her fart needed freedom.
With a soft but very long and powerful hiss,
Angela's divine wind broke free of its confinement
and blessed the air with its presence.
Christine looked surprised.
Wow, Angela, you really needed to go, didn't you?
Angela chuckled nervously.
I guess I did.
Christine relaxed and her own aroma
violently erupted from her body
to join with the dense gas of Angela's already in the air.
The two scents mixed and complemented one another, one fragrance balancing out the other to form
one perfect feminine perfume.
It's like that scene in Ratatouille when he eats strawberries and cheese and he gets a
different colors and tastes like combining.
Christine was mortified, but at the same time was relieved.
She looked at Angela.
I needed that.
With a loud rumble, both women's bellies swelled outward yet again.
"This is impossible!" exclaimed Angela as her stomach grew to the size of a large beach
volleyball, causing her to fall to the ground.
Christine followed shortly.
Now the gas was really being passed.
And both women noisily expelled enormous amounts of feminine flatulence into the air.
Their bellies only grew and grew.
Their shirts rode up on them, exposing the taut skin of their tanned, hugely swollen
stomachs. Angela and Christine needed relief from the incessant pressure and the farts
flowed freely and loudly in spite of whatever embarrassment they felt. Their faces contorted
and grimaced as they struggled to expel out all of that flatulence.
All the while, Irina looked on with barely contained amusement. The two women's stomachs
briefly swelled up to twice the size of a big beach ball and they gasped loudly as the
sheer amount of gas buildup became apparent. And with two twin cries of exertion, Angela
Christine released the ripest deepest longest loudest and most powerful chain
farts the extremely strong smell immediately gave away the fact that the
gas had come from the most inner part of the women's systems the blasts were so
powerful that they ripped twin holes clean through both layers of the girls
clothing and they both blush fiercely as the extent of the gases power became
apparent. This is, yeah, this is...
It's taken a turn.
Irina couldn't stop laughing for quite a while. Angela looked annoyed.
"What's so funny?" Irina tried to stop laughing. "I'm sorry, it's just... I'm the
cause of you two letting those farts rip." "It was so funny watching you try not to
fart." Angela looked incredulous. "What do you mean, caused us to fart?" So Irina
explained to them what she had done. Then Christine had an idea. "Hey, why don't we
We all try these spells out on each other.
It'll be fun.
After all, Arena, turnabout is fair play."
Arena smiled slightly.
"Okay, that sounds interesting.
Let's try it.
See what happens."
So Arena got the spell book out.
The first incantation caused extreme bloating in Angela, but no supernatural swelling.
Christine and Arena had to coax the gas out of her by manipulating Angela's swollen belly
with their hands.
Gradually they managed to get it all out of her.
Christine and Irina also had that spell cast on them one after the other.
This is so fucked up dude.
This is so unsafe.
They didn't draw a summoning circle or anything.
Who knows what kind of enmities they could lose in their house.
Well no enmity is going to be able to survive the smells in this house.
The next incantation caused their farts to actually be visible as brilliant colored clouds
of turbulent gas.
Afterwards, they got into swimming gear and went into the pool
and tried out the very first spell Christine had discovered.
They had spent their time floating on the water's surface, expelling huge bubbles
and using their fart to create bubble baths.
The latter experiment was particularly effective when all three of them were close together,
creating one enormous mass of gigantic gas bubbles.
The real fun was when they tried out the next spell, and the last one they would try out
for the day.
They tested it out when they were inside and dried off.
I can't wait to find out what the last spell is.
Me too.
Almost as soon as the spell was cast, their stomachs began to swell out.
At first it seemed like nothing new, but the swelling didn't stop.
In fact, the rest of their body started to inflate with gas as well, and their flatulence
became uncontrollable, both in terms of frequency and power.
All three of them grew rounder, larger, and more inflated by the minute.
They wondered when it would stop.
When it did, they looked like gigantic, round, human balloons.
Then they began to feel very light, and soon they were floating upwards until they hit
the ceiling.
For about a minute, they didn't know what to do.
"Alright, take us home."
But as it turned out, their farts had become so powerful that they could literally propel
themselves around the room.
That quickly turned into an opportunity for various games like Bumper Girls and Aerial
Tag and they played those games for hours.
By the time they were done, the room was so filled with gas they couldn't be able to,
they wouldn't be able to smell anything else for a couple hours.
But they didn't mind.
They were having fun.
And when it was over, they resolved to use the spell book whenever they wanted to play
these kind of games again.
I mean, this is, this story I think is a great, a perfect example of the, the female mind
is incapable of hustle, you know, because if I had found a spell book like this, I would
be using it to rob banks, I would be street performing, I would be making so much money,
but they, all they want to do is play bumper girls all day.
They don't want to monetize it at all.
Like you could, people could pay to play Bumper Girls and Aerial Tag in your house.
Exactly.
They're just like, "Oh, let's go swim in the pool."
No, dude.
I would be online.
I would be selling this, I would be selling the gas as fuel, okay, to the government.
I would be, I would be becoming a military contractor using this spell book.
I would talk to NASA.
I found a completely energy-free use, free way to go to space.
All right?
Yeah, we could just use all this methane and just fucking, you know, I mean, it probably
get up there, do a number on the ozone layer, but we'll figure something out.
This was made in 2006 and Jamal in 2012 wrote, please make a sequel.
This is my request.
And then 11 days later, oh, wow, it looks like I'm six years late, huh?
Well, the sequel would still be nice.
There's also a comment here from Major Tom 2000 that says, oh, Major Tom.
No, hold on, not me.
Hold up.
But wait, if they couldn't smell anything for two hours, that doesn't make sense, because
earlier you said they could breathe it like air.
It's a different spell, Major Tom.
It was very clearly a different spell.
True.
There's a comment here from Nick09y3, and they say, "I can only describe Hat in two
words, sheer brilliance.
Here's a comment from great five and this is an asterisk, jumps up and down,
awesome.
Can you draw it as a picture?
This is a reply to asking for a request.
Definitely should be a pretty anime girl who gets squeezed and goes,
it's up to you who squeezes her.
Non-fat please, that's about it.
No wait, one more thing, if you write a story about a beautiful non-fat
anime girl who gets a hissing fart squeezed out of her, then have the
squeezer repeatedly squeeze her midsection sort of pumping it causing the
gas to come out in spurts that'd be super smexy please write the story if you want
but definitely draw the picture if you draw both I'll do a commissioned art
piece for you if anything you want
they're bargaining in the replies
playful Absol says could you do something like this except with a dragon instead
and the author said if I had the time perhaps but I can't make any promises
Hey listen I'm very busy. Hey I got so many fucking fart stories I gotta write.
Add it to the fucking list dude. Throw it on the pile. Yeah all right this this next
one will I think can be our last one. Okay. This one's nice. This one's sweet. Which one is this?
A girlfriend's fart goes straight to the heart. Oh okay. By the spazzer. It's very nice.
there's this is another dialogue one Pat do you want to play my girlfriend I guess
real life okay oh and you're sure you want to do this yes I always have haha
well all right but if you want to back out I don't think I possibly can I
giggle as I hold my girlfriend close to me her thighs leaning over and
overlapping my leg.
Just know it's my first time doing something like it too.
She slides over completely and fully sits in my lap.
Oh, I thought that was your line.
I can't tell if it is.
It doesn't have any names here.
I know.
That's the worst part about these is, you know, you never can tell.
You're right.
That's the worst part about these.
It's shoddy, right?
Yeah.
You're right, Patrick.
Yeah, I just wish that I could, like, there was more detail about what was going on.
That's my main concern.
It's so hard to follow the fucking story.
This is a comment from Patrick 2000. Hey, did you make sure to write who's saying
what yeah yeah doing like script coverage on these like like you have you have
tons of third act problems in this yeah absolutely yeah I mean try to we need to
know why we care about the characters way faster you know we yeah she slides
over completely and fully sits in my lap I can feel her back pockets touch my
crotch and I do a silent sigh of arousal and nuzzle her with my head on the back
of hers. I know, just make sure you get comfy though. Is that... I don't know.
We'll just split the call. Who is who? Doesn't matter anymore. I think both of you are
everything. Yeah. Nuzzling, I also, nuzzle her with my head on the back of hers
doesn't seem like a very good, like just sticking your face into the back of her
head. I can feel her body seem to calm into me and her butt got more into my
crotch. Well yeah, if I wasn't comfy I don't think I would be doing this hun. I
go lower with my head and now my face is fully in her hair smelling the shampoo
and conditioner she uses in the morning. It'll probably be the last good thing I
smell. I like that this one is like it's like a classic like burr purr purr purr
kind of situation that ends with tort. Yeah but then there's a BRB right in the
middle. That was when that the girlfriend took a break from farting. So the Zordash guy
I arrived, I had to go pick up the order.
I admittedly jolt a little as she lets out a long and bubbly fart point black against
my crotch.
Point black.
Clothed, but it feels like the blast goes right through the cloth and into my skin.
I can feel her body relax and get less tense after the fart ends, and she can't help but
sigh after.
God, that felt so much better than it should have.
How about you?
Oh, you have no...
a process first the blast then the heat then the smell it rises from my lap and
up to my nose smelling like the definition of meaty with a smack of
vegetables packed in I can't believe that my girlfriend someone I find so
attractive someone I love and have a connection to doesn't mind and even
thinks it's cute that I'm into her gas this is the first time she's farted in
front of me and the first time a girl has farted on me.
Hun, I must have been in a trance.
I blink a little and put my arms around her.
You have no idea how great it really is.
So yeah, the confusing dialogue here, you know, there's no, it doesn't say who's saying
what.
Well.
Maybe, maybe this is a fight club situation.
Oh my God.
Well, but I hate to do this, but you know, Pat didn't really sell me with that last line.
Yeah, I just I can tell his heart wasn't into it.
So I gotta say I can read this again.
I need you to re-read that.
You have no idea how great it really is.
That's oh man, now I'm in it.
Now I'm into this story.
Yeah.
Her body warms up even more from emotion and she leans back going lower on my chest and
looks up at me.
I think this is a you line Patrick and I want to really hear your I want to hear just your
love.
It's just a fart you goof.
There will be more.
I go down and smooch her forehead, even chucking to myself.
Let's hope so.
I just like, I guess she leaned back.
I'm just trying to, I'm confused by like the bodily proportions.
There's so much going on in this story.
I mean, I think this is our first one star out of five.
Yeah.
Well, okay, but here's something here at the bottom.
"Hey, another scene story this time. I had to write it down and make a story of it,
even if it is short. I really hope you enjoy. I love scenes like this.
I also tried to make it gender neutral so either gender can enjoy."
Oh.
I think maybe that's why they didn't say who's saying what,
but that doesn't really make any sense.
It doesn't because they still use like gendered pronouns, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, they do.
I guess maybe you don't, maybe, yeah.
Maybe it's so if you can read it, if you have the kind of fart fetish where you
like to fart on people or if you like to be farted on.
Yeah. Either one. Maybe that's what they mean. But yeah, you know, I'm gonna have
to hit this with a two stars out of five because, you know, I really like the
emotion on display. It's just kind of difficult to read. I
appreciate it. It is short and it is sweet and it is a loving, it kind of
displays a loving relationship, but it is very hard to reenact this with
my partner because we both keep getting confused at what line
we're supposed to read. So if you could work on that for me,
thank you.
A comment from boyo3. If this is a true story, then goddamn man,
you got a wife on your hands. A reply from fart slave. I had a
similar situation. It lasted one year and two months. I think
that she doesn't even know what she wants.
Oh, this one's fucked up. This guy wrote, I wish I could have a
girlfriend like that. Then again, I'm a teen still in high
school maybe one day I'll find the one and one heart stinky girls replies yeah
same man we can only hope oh man are you a teen or are you just saying you hope
you can find a girl that won't fart on you. Alright well yeah I would say I'm sorry for this episode but I'm not.
That was really good. Yeah you have to listen to this. You know yeah. Turn the volume all the way up.
You put this on a beats pill you put on the subway.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You will not get in trouble for listening to it.
You are allowed to play it over the loudspeaker at like a Target or a Walmart.
You can take the phone.
I think if it's like you hit the star button, you can broadcast it.
You know what else you should listen to over the loudspeaker at the store is Chapo FYM
streams.
That's right.
Yeah.
You want to plug that, Tom?
You have anything else too or just...
twitch.tv/chappotraphouse or patreon.com/chappoFYM where we watch videos that are very similar to this.
Both these boys have been on our lovely stream.
We love it.
Yep.
Yeah.
And we, we, anytime you got a fart video, call us in.
No particular reason.
Yes, absolutely.
Yeah.
I've got, we watch, I watch just fat guys eating a disgusting amount of food all day,
so they fart a lot.
So don't worry, I will be calling you.
All right.
All right, well, thank you so much for coming on.
Yeah, thanks for having me on.
Bye!
Bye.