You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Welcome to the Monster Conf Lists.
[Music]
You're a crap monster.
[Explosion]
And now we're at it.
Yeah.
But yeah, dude, this bed is, this bed is, I have a bunch of old shit, dude.
Well, let's start, let's not get back into that.
Let's not do that.
Why?
It's already brought up too much pain for you.
That is true, man.
It does hurt me when you guys make fun of my cool old shit.
We have a very special guest today.
CJ! Hey buddy, how are you?
Hey guys, thanks for having me on.
We finally turned CJ into our food slave.
Oh my god.
What's up with that? Why are you guys always threatening to enslave me and shit?
Not enslave you, you would sign a contract.
Yeah, right.
But like, you would be a food slave for me after.
You would become a slave, but we wouldn't enslave you.
Like, the verb enslave is not in play here.
here. Maybe if you don't want to be a food slave, stop making so much fucking food, man.
Okay. There's an idea. Yeah, no, I mean when you say it like that, I never realized that
was an option. I could just stop making food. Just take a break from making all of this
delicious... McDonald's is down the street. Yeah. Just knock it off. Yeah, like I don't...
You keep showing me all this fucking amazing stuff with truffles in it and shit. Buddy,
I'm gonna find you and make you my slave. See, there it is right there. Make me... You
said make or make you agree to be my slave okay I'm I'm not saying it's like a
hard no I'm just saying like right now you're not pitching it very well okay
come back to you the better offer like right well this is for yeah I might be I
might be grinding you down on this whole making my food slave thing I might be
getting you pretty close to you come on look at that giggle okay do you have one
of those those fucking beds for me to sleep in too?
*laughter*
Yeah, that is the type of bed that only comes with a hundred of them side by side.
You cannot get that bed alone.
*laughter*
Yeah, it's a horrible bed, I'm gonna be honest with you guys, man.
It's not, I don't like this bed.
I want one of these fucking, I want like an IKEA bed made out of fucking, like, cardboard that I can replace every year.
I don't want this fucking shit.
I heard little orphan Annie actually did sleep on that exact bed frame in the movie.
So...
No, you didn't hear... who would you hear that from?
That doesn't make any fucking sense.
I heard that from Carol Burnett in an interview.
You are so stupid about my bed, dude.
No. And CJ, if you came to... if... you know...
By the way, I'd fly you out to be my slave.
So, that's on me.
Okay. Alright. Looking better, yeah.
Food is gonna be on you.
Wait, hold on. Visit the coach.
What is it?
Business or coach flight?
Um, slave.
Slave.
So, you're selling the cargo hold.
Yeah, whatever the furthest back cheapest option is.
I mean, come on.
I get you a business card.
It's a one way ticket though, dog.
You can't, okay, whatever, fine.
Cargo hold, got it.
It's on spirit.
Yeah, it's going to be on spirit, of course.
That's all the seats are.
Yeah, and you will be able to stay.
You're going to be able to stay for a couple of days.
hold got it. It's our spirit. Yeah it's all the seats are. Yeah and you will be able to
stay well you can't well you can't leave the kitchen that's a big part of this
late thing. Yeah. Do you have a bed in the kitchen then? Are you in your kitchen right now?
We can get you one. Can you move your camera around and shit? No there's there's no kitchen here I'm
sorry yeah and you're not allowed to look at me while you're here so get that in
now as well. Okay, done. So it sounds pretty good, right? You could sleep in the oven too,
maybe would be an option if you know you couldn't fit a bed in the kitchen. A cold neck would
be nice. All right, you know what? Let me move first because I'm going to move pretty soon
and we'll see if we have room for a slave quarters. Yeah. We're looking for a one bedroom,
one bedroom, and one food slave quarters. And here are the slave quarters. Have you guys been
thinking about slaves
no
yeah
i would never but it's i mean just you know the option
her parents are bugging us about it though they keep asking us when are you going to have slaves
i don't know how long have you been together you don't even have one slave just because you had slaves when you were twenty
doesn't mean i have to you know you ruined your entire life
fuck you man
But yeah, we're happy to have CJ here. Yeah, what do you guys been doing today, man? What is this is I'm so I'm this is a
Hot yeah, I was I was in situ it baby. I was I was walking out on that's in that's a little
Beach town and with some very rich people and some big houses
So I was you know kind of making money moves out on at the water. That's you
Exactly thinking of which boats I might like to purchase when I you know become very rich when you hit it big time. Yeah
Yeah, I mean you're on the path to superstardom. I'm
Yeah, I'm on the the I would say I'm like and the teleporter
It's kind of becoming famous for getting it's going pretty fast. It's definitely heating up for you Kim
Yeah, I mean my fans are just they're ravenous
That's all would you say that you do it for them?
I would say I do everything for them, but more importantly I do everything for me. It's like
Famous ass answer dude, you are a star already. Mm-hmm. Jesus Christ, dude. CJ. Have you ever thought about maybe coming famous? I
Thought about yeah
I thought about once but I you have to be like good at something or like you also have to be kind of psycho and
I'm not either one of those yet
I might I might be so I might become psycho from not being good at anything like what about enough to get famous
- That might work for me, what?
- What about singing?
- I feel like you got pipes on you, dude.
You look like one of those little white guys
who comes out on American Idol
and sings the most amazing R&B song you've ever heard.
(laughing)
Right?
He has the voice of a black worship leader
who's like 400 pounds. - No, it's crazy.
I can sing an amazing R&B song,
where the problem is I never make it past the first round
because I'm always like,
"Here's an old negro spiritual I learned."
(laughing)
And then I get cut off like two seconds later.
Yeah, they definitely draw a line with that.
[LAUGHTER]
Do you ever know anybody who's on like American Idol or one
of those competition shows?
I think we went to college with a few.
True, yeah.
I guess we did.
We went to the American Idol reject college.
That makes perfect sense.
We went to X Factor University.
I knew people who just like it's funny that they like just completely like you
can make it pretty far and never be on TV you can make it like top a hundred and
you're just never on TV you weren't like you weren't weird enough yeah they
could have you like Sanjay or whatever like who's Sanjay you don't remember
Sanjay no oh he was like that little Indian kid from like seasoned whatever
and he like hit a weird haircut and like Howard Stern like rigged the votes so
so that he kept winning.
- What?
- Yeah, there was like a thing.
- I didn't know about that.
- Howard Stern rigged the votes
so that a little boy would win?
- Let me look up.
- How did he do, do you just mean he told people
to vote for him?
- Yeah, he was like--
- He has a lot of pull.
- Yeah, here's a votefortheworst.com,
support the season's underdogs.
This is an archive on mtv.com from 2007.
- Nice.
- So I didn't just make that up.
Wait, what show was that?
That was American Idol.
Sanjay is in like a disaster movie I think.
I think they parody him in disaster movie.
Oh, that must be cutting.
I don't know.
They probably take him down.
This guy is psychic.
Neither of you fucking remembered?
Yeah.
I have a strong...
Now it's funny because you would watch that
just like not remembering who that guy is at all
and it's probably just like the most racist shit of all time.
And you have no idea what it's referencing.
You're like, "Aw, dude, these movies rule, bro."
Those things are sick, dude.
Whatever fucking Bizarro White Wayans Brothers have made all those fucking parody movies,
they're the best.
It's Meet the Spartan Sanjayazin.
So it's like one, it's a different, it's like a rung below disaster movie.
One more removed from when they started parodying specific movies.
Yeah.
I really wish they still made those.
Me too, man.
On a large scale.
I agree. They were hits, man. I remember being really scared of the Alvin and the Chipmunk
part of Disaster movie.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I remember being like, "I have to stop watching this movie, man."
I've never seen that movie. What happened to Alvin?
They just get really big teeth in the movie.
That's one of the biggest disasters of all time, I would say.
Yeah, I was like, "We have to pause."
The chipmunks get big teeth.
It was a fucking disaster for me man. I had to go hide from the movie. Well, the rest of my friends watch it, bro
That was a social disaster for me, man. Yeah, 2020 was a rough year for us all
All right, she's booming me about my bed and now I'm a little kid now dude, okay, but you're also trying to enslave me like
here in my defense on the one hand I'm giving you some shit I'm not like trying
to I'm trying to spit game at you about this whole slave shit try maybe convince
you you know the pick up artists for slaves
Isn't that the language they use in Pickup Artistry too?
Yeah, they do.
I got mad slave last night.
Dude, the thing is CJ, I just can't feed myself very well.
Today I ate a half pound of Greek yogurt and a bunch of hard boiled eggs.
about it. And to me, I hope you know this, I don't know many chefs, so in my brain you
could be one of the greatest in the world or ever. You could be like really far up there.
So I just need some excuse to, I just need somebody to make my meals for me, man.
Yeah, well, that's really nice of you to say. I wouldn't really put myself like, I'm not
like a celebrity chef yet but I think I'm like one DUI away from becoming a
celebrity chef. Or like one domestic incident away from becoming one.
I feel like you you see my potential. Yeah I do. See that's how all those guys
started as food slaves you know that right? I would like to you know hire
you as a slave I think is how you would say it. But you know not to make me food
but maybe just take pictures of the food that I make. Like I think I you know I
I made like a mean peanut butter and jelly sandwich today
that I think would have really benefited from maybe having like, you know,
some of the ingredients on the side, like of the plate,
and like, you know, maybe it was like cut in a cool way.
I think that that could be a service that you could provide for me
completely without me paying you.
PB&J and cilantro.
When you sprinkle it, it's garnish.
Yeah, that's right.
Shit looks great. It looks amazing.
Look at that, see, you know all your time.
I'm learning so much already.
Can you imagine if we were full time?
Yeah, I'm thinking about it, I'm thinking about it, but now I got Cameron's offer.
Cameron, I'll give you one for free.
If you would take in that sandwich and knock on into like a bathroom that you just showered in,
completely dark, and then turn the flash on on your phone and take in a photo.
All those things. Cut those out of your next photography session, dog.
You gotta get rid of that shit. You gotta go like out, you know.
Natural light, that kind of thing.
Right. His feet should be nowhere near the food, right?
Like that's not...
So what if it's pouring rain outside
and I go outside barefoot and I put the sandwich on the ground,
I take a picture of it like that.
And then he sends you that.
Is this all right, CJ?
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry my stomach hurt after I ate it.
I think I'm allergic to rain.
Oh.
What filter should I put on this?
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, I guess that would be better.
It'd be better lit, but it'd be more wet.
So it's kind of a wash, right?
No pun intended.
- Fucking trade-offs, dude.
That's what cooking's all about, right?
- Yeah, that's what cooking's all about, is trade-offs.
- I think I need a, I've been,
a lot of people I know have recently gotten gigs
as like line cooks.
I think I need something like that, dude.
I think it would help me in everything.
I think I need a job.
- Yeah, I think everybody,
I think like if you're ever feeling like you're kind of stuck
getting a job where you work like 12 hours,
you do cocaine at 8 a.m.
and go and hang out with all your gremlin,
psycho fucking line cook friends.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- It'll get you, it'll put you in the right state of mind.
- A friend of mine was just working a line cook job
where they had like a new chef come in
and he was like, he was like,
listen, I'm a very serious guy,
no cocaine during the shifts
and like eight people quit immediately.
(laughing)
I was like, I am in the wrong business.
That's the sickest shit of all time.
- When I worked at Cracker Barrel,
I've probably talked about this before, but there was a--
(laughing)
There was some fucking country cooking old lady railing lines in the back of a cracker
barrel.
I worked at a cracker barrel.
I was the dishwasher at a cracker barrel for like a month and then I quit because I wanted
to kill myself because I was a dishwasher at a cracker barrel.
And there was a dude who was telling me that he would take Percocet and Adderall so he
could like not feel pain when he touched hot pans and work really fast.
It makes sense, right?
Yeah.
I guess that works, yeah.
I mean, I would have...
And plus, you vibe super hard too while you're doing it.
Oh yeah.
Absolutely, yeah.
He was definitely trying to just buy my Adderall off of me.
Did you advertise that you had Adderall in the kitchen?
I think I told him I have ADHD.
Oh yeah.
Yep, there we go.
Do you tell everybody you meet that you have ADHD?
I think I forgot something.
Of course you did.
And I was like, "Sorry, man.
I have ADHD."
Oh, man, I thought you were opening up to us when you told us that.
I thought you were sharing something special.
You tell everybody at the Cracker Barrel.
Whatever meeting I have to go in at Cracker Barrel where we like salute the flag or whatever the fuck and I'm just like,
"Before we say anything, before we say grace, I just want to say I'm neurodivergent and it affects how I work."
Baby, before we take this thing any further, we've been going steady for a while now. You should know something about me.
I do have ADHD.
very serious I could have an attack at any point in time.
Oh man.
Do you want to watch Rush Hour?
I wish I had ADHD dude I'm too good at focusing on things.
No you didn't it's a curse.
It's not a curse dude.
It's horrible.
Albert Einstein had ADHD.
Do you have ADHD too?
Yeah dude it's terrible.
I'm like the only normal one here.
I have to look at my phone once every ten minutes during a movie or else I'll die.
It's like it's basically like living with cancer yeah.
Yeah, no, I know. It's worse than cancer, dude.
At least it's lungless.
At least cancer you die.
Yeah, you die.
You can't like, just ride it out and like wait for the end.
Exactly. It's not treatable either.
They can't like zap me with a laser beam.
They can't fry your brain from the age of six with methamphetamine.
It doesn't work.
It is funny that that became the solution at some point.
It's so fucked up, dude.
It's really fucking horrible.
Giving a six-year-old fucking like speed just so they don't like they don't tell you that they like this dragon they saw
Like parents have such a low limit for like how willing they are to be annoyed before they just like sit down their kid
It's so sick, dude
I can't believe the industry that prescribed housewives like Xanax and fucking speed constantly thought this is the way to treat
responsible than that. Oh man. There's gotta be some heroes in there. That's all I'm saying.
Who should have been thinking dude? I don't know. I was, I didn't, they tried to put me
on Adderall at school and then they were like you should go try to get prescribed something
and then my mom was like that is gonna, my mom thought everything caused autism when
I was a kid. Like more than just vaccines. She was like any one thing that you take every
day will give you autism. She thought that like this kid that we knew. Well then yeah
Yeah, because I mean you look at like a medication chart where you have to check it off every
day that starts to look like a spreadsheet, you know, one thing leads to another.
Yeah.
You're going to start making bar graphs of how often you take your medication.
Yeah, you're a finance guy.
You develop an interest in autism more than anything like that.
But yeah, I never, I evaded all that shit, man.
I had, we just had to wholly anoint everything in my house instead.
That kind of kept us safe from ADHD and the like.
prayed the gay away and no pray it away no yeah it was very unsuccessful now I
didn't I don't think I don't think I knew anybody who went to one of those like
camp things the conversion camp yeah I don't think either I think by the time I
was like a teenager that was kind of that was out of vogue to elect it's kind
of weird yeah yeah they did they just had like if anybody in my hometown that
Christian be like came out as gay they would just make it would make the gay
kid talk like six hours a week to a guy who used to be gay they were just like
put them in both in a room and just be like you guys just hash all this weird
come back later and I don't think it ever worked if you guys can believe that
Yeah, I know somebody who who got like hypnosis in their therapy which is like I
didn't know that they did that at all like what I thought like no I didn't I
didn't think that was a joke yeah exactly I did like that's not even like
electroshock where I thought like oh that was like an old thing they used to do
like I just didn't know that that ever was a thing that's just like we're gonna
cast a magic spell on you well you're gonna for cigarettes - dude I'm hypnotized
that a cigarette. I've convinced myself like I can't be hypnotized but
then I like I know that if I watch like Now You See Me and there's a hypnosis
scene I'm gonna be like fully hypnotized by a movie. Like I just can feel it
coming. I have such a weak mind. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah I mean like I I don't know
that I believe in hypnosis. I feel like hypnosis is like... You play like a lot of
hours of video games though, right? Yes, yes you do. And you do the Bitcoin casino too,
you like the flashing lights and colors and that. They're beautiful, what do you mean?
The spinning shapes. Yeah, and the beautiful fruit. And you click again and again, more and more.
That's not hypnosis though, that's just having a good time. Yeah, that's just being addicted to
something. Hypnosis is supposed to be for like, so you stop doing something bad. This is just,
you know. Exactly, yeah. Yeah. But I mean, you can be hypnotized into, you know,
like clucking like a chicken. Yeah or like spinning around or something. Yeah.
Yeah. So both of those sound fucking fine like fine like I'll just do that like you don't have to
you don't have to hypnotize me. Yeah it doesn't have to be like a whole production around it.
Yeah like you don't have to fucking uh dangle a stopwatch. Well yeah so if I was if I was going
to be like a hypnotist or a mentalist or whatever and like have like rich people hire me for their
like their parties I would what I would do is I would like single out a really weak-willed looking
person before my act and I would go up to them and I whisper in their ear, "If you don't
do what I say during the hypnosis, I will kill myself." And then...
Yeah, just let them know it's a very actionable threat.
Yeah.
But like, what do you, like, how do they know if somebody's susceptible to hypnosis? Do
they just pick like the shortest guy in the room?
It's the person with the swirliest eyes.
Did they bring a hypnotist to your high school? Or is that like a just another fucking...
- No, they did that for me too,
they did like when you graduated from high school,
there was like the sober alternative thing,
like we have a hypnotist,
they might trick you into seeing something crazy.
It's like, I think I'd rather go throw up
in someone's backyard, but that sounds--
- Oh, actually, no, wait,
they did have a hypnotist and I didn't go.
Yeah, okay, I think I do remember that.
It was $5, it was like a student council fundraiser,
and I went and just the whole time
I was just telling everyone, you're faking it.
(laughing)
just in the like the top of the bleachers just like you're faking that it's not
real dude i've always that hypnotist did not cry in his car after the show
i've always wanted to go to like one of those like uh comedy hypnotist shows i
feel like they got a [ __ ] rule dude yeah like i'm sure i mean what do you
like to see do you just like make people say fart or something like
I don't really understand.
Well the hypnotist is the host and he before when he's bringing the people on stage he
goes and I now hypnotize you to say some funny jokes.
And then they open their eyes.
Maybe what if he hypnotizes himself into thinking he's Robin Williams.
That might work right?
Or something like that.
I feel like that's like the only way that a comedy hypnotist would make any sense.
Maybe he could turn somebody else into Robin Williams.
he could turn somebody into a newt yeah that'd be funny yeah that might be more
of a witch or a warlock fuck you're right dude they should have
a warlock comedy show comedy with a warlock hey we brought this warlock to
your school that's yeah one of these kids into a fucking slug and that's
that's gonna keep you off the drugs.
And every single--
You're faking it!
Yeah.
It's not!
You brought that noob from home!
It's not real!
It's so irritating when you go to the Warlock comedy show and then every single comic that
comes up at the top of their act, they try to do a quick joke about the smell of brimstone
lingering in the air and it's like, come on, the guy right before you already mentioned
that.
Oh, fuck.
All right, we have a long ass list today.
I feel like we could hop into it.
Yeah, it's long as shit, dude.
Ooh.
Ooh!
And it's on, I mean, it's on CJ. I mean, what, think about it. What's the one thing we know about CJ?
He's a Twitch streamer.
Fo-
Yeah, that's a-
Food.
It's okay, you got two.
I bet you guys can get up to three if you really try.
Uh, food.
Uh, no.
He's wearing headphones.
Chef.
There we go. Look at that.
Chef. Oh, that's a new-
Okay.
Alright.
Yeah.
For having ADHD, you sure are sharp. You just immediately grab it. You weren't, you weren't like-
Laser focus on that one.
Yeah. This is top 10 worst foods. This is from user Bob Tech on the top tens. Bob
Tech, not a lot going on his profile. No. He likes keeping it low-key, which I respect.
The number one worst food is cow tongue, according to this. I disagree. I've had
cow tongue before. It's pretty good. I've had cow tongue too. Yeah, it's just like, you
know, all meat, I mean, I'm stupid. Like, all meat is the same to me. Yeah. There's
There's chicken and there's beef, and those are the only two kinds of meat that I can taste.
And there's different types, there's subclasses of chicken and there's subclasses of meat.
No, no, no.
That's it.
Pork is a type of chicken.
Pork tastes like chicken.
Alligator tastes like chicken.
Yeah, alligator's chicken.
As far as beef goes, shrimp is beef.
Shrimp is 100%.
No, shrimp is chicken.
No, shrimp, no.
Listen, okay.
It's the other white meat.
Shrimp is chicken.
Shrimp is chicken, popcorn shrimp is beef.
All right, you know what he said?
Popcorn shrimp is popcorn.
Popcorn.
Fuck, dude.
All right, so there's chicken, there's beef, and there's popcorn.
Popcorn shrimp is popcorn, but popcorn is chicken.
There's so many different types of popcorn, dude.
There is a lot of popcorn, dude.
There's a lot of popcorn.
I can't even...
Well, scallops is caramel corn.
I might have backed myself into writing a book right now.
Scallops is caramel corn?
Nah, dude.
Scallops is chicken, bro.
Yeah, scallops is chicken.
this
It scares me that it's circular.
I've had, I had a thing of frozen scallops
when I was moving into my sister's house
in like 2016. I found them in the back of the fridge
and I was like, "Oh, are you guys going to use these?"
That sounds good.
It sounds delicious.
And I got the worst food poisoning I've ever had
in my entire life.
I ate a whole thing of scallops wrapped in bacon by myself
and just shit and puking for two days.
two days. Hell yeah, dude. Awesome. That rocks, man. You see a bag of frozen scallops in the
back of the fridge and not one red flag goes up. In a box, yes. It's even worse, man. That
is worse. Yeah, that's some Trader Joe's shit. Well, you know, at the time, they tasted amazing.
It was honestly... They are great. Yeah. It was good to eat a whole thing of scallops
wrapped in bacon by yourself. What happened after, I wouldn't recommend. When you say a
whole thing how many we talking probably like thing yeah maybe like a big things
a things worth yeah probably it might have been like a 20 to 25 count what the
fuck you gave yourself like you didn't know you boys didn't like three wasn't
yourself you like you ate like a Roman King and then you eat 25 fucking
scallops when I was on a girl I eat whatever I wanted when you're on Adderall
you don't eat that's the thing with Adderall. I know that was my one meal that day. How do you manage to eat 20 to 25 like you can't eat a slice of bread on fucking Adderall.
That's the thing that it does you have no appetite. The scallops like hockey puck sized right?
No these were kind of small I mean you know how do you fit 25 in a box. Yeah well it's a big box I don't know most stuff comes in a box Pat.
No.
Something's got to be working.
What even is this?
Is this a scallop like a snake?
Yeah.
No, it's a clam.
No, it's chicken.
No, wait.
Oh.
Yeah, we talked about this.
It's chicken.
That's why it's in a circle.
I'm not mad.
Here's a comment on this.
This is a comment and a reply.
The comment is on Cow Tongue is, "I would kill anyone who ate my country's holy cow."
And then the reply is from Sammy Spore and says, "Well then, that's disturbing."
I'm not mad.
from Sammy's Spore and says, "Well then, that's disturbing."
There's a good comment under that one that says, "Don't judge a meat by what it is. Conch,
for example." Someone says, "Why would they invent something
like this?" Damn, it was the psycho that came up with
this. Fuck, invented cow tongue.
That's just wrong. That's, yeah.
the fuck I hiss when I see the word get that word away from me I want to go
cow-tipping by the way I have no idea what the heck that's a food it's like
licking a cow's tongue yes true but is it cow tongues like good right it's some
sort of delicacy no no they serve it in like Mexican restaurants and shit yeah
it's like a taco if it's served there it's not a delicacy
You could buy it for like $4 at a taco, it's not a delicacy.
But there's only one per cow.
I feel like that should be more,
that should be expensive.
There's only one meat per cow too.
There's a shit load of cows though.
There's an insane,
there's more cows than people on the earth, I'm pretty sure.
I haven't done the math on that, but yeah.
Mexicans eat this, bruh.
Best thing ever.
Here's a comment.
Pass me the bleach.
Well, yeah, that's just a seasoning.
Yeah.
For the cow tongue.
Why the hell would you have oral sex with a goddamn cow?
That's a good question.
That's a, you know, not even on this list.
That's a really strong question, I guess.
Yeah.
Would you?
No, today I broke the story of Mr. Hands to Jana.
Oh, really?
She had never--
That's a big step.
Dude, this is like what girls had to deal with
growing up, okay?
I was like, she was like, "What is Mr. Hands?"
And I was like, "Oh, you know, like two girls, one cup,
like like shock sites and she was like oh like Charlie the unicorn I was like no you
fucking idiot no that's a cartoon it's supposed to be funny no I'm talking about like
videos of people kill each other and I she just like she was like horrified when
I told her what it was I was like I don't even that doesn't bother me at all
anymore I guess. Yeah I think it was a big realization for her about like what
like my growing up was like. Number two is Brussels sprouts. That's fucked up.
That's a fucked up thing. I love a Brussels sprout. Dude, they're good. I'm not off to a good start bro. I figured like he keeps a low
key in his bio he wants to let the post speak for itself but so far his list is
dog shit. Dude sometimes when I'm fucking hungry to eat some pussy I just leave
some brussel sprouts out at room temperature for about 30 minutes bro.
It's like the exact same smell dude. It's fucking beautiful.
Just walk around, I'm wafting it. It looks pretty much the same too.
Yeah, cut in half, put it through a color filter. That is an aphrodisiac dude.
For sure. Man, I eat it one leaf at a time.
First day ordering brussel sprouts and mashed potatoes, just fucking eating out of brussel sprouts in front of us.
So all i'm gonna leave it at this, you know, what's up?
Hey, can y'all when y'all cook the brussel sprouts, can you leave the stems at the top, you know those little ass stems?
Yeah, i'm about to do work on that
Uh, could you also make the stem like look like it's kind of hard to find but like i'll find it easily
Maybe hide it a little bit.
Could you like hide the stem in there somewhere?
I fucking know this stem's in here somewhere.
Fucking god damn it.
They smell like feet from an old lady who has never showered in her life.
I don't know about that dude.
That's not true.
I like brussel sprouts.
Roasted brussel sprouts, they're like maple syrup.
Like a little bit of like bacon and shit.
Yeah, like maple butter.
Dude, putting like sugar and bacon on a food doesn't mean it's like a good food.
You don't even have to put the bacon on it, like brussel sprouts with like a...
Yeah, they're just good.
Yeah, you just like throw some, like just squeeze a lemon over it or something.
Yeah.
Easy.
Salt and pepper.
Deep fry them with za'atar?
Yeah, for sure.
What the fuck is za'atar?
Is that like genie dust?
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
It's basically, it's basically like all the shit that falls out of like your spice bottles
in the back of the cabinet.
You just kind of take them all out and then you swipe that into like a drawer thing and
then you just roll your meat in it.
Yeah, you're like, "Yeah, this is the star."
Oh my god, that's beautiful, dude.
Cumin and brown sugar and Monterey chicken.
Yeah, all spices.
And just some black.
Spider eggs.
One whole clove.
Yeah, it's great.
That's beautiful.
I think my spice cabinet is about ready to make some za'atar, dude.
I opened it the other day and it like blew spice at me.
Like all in my eyes and face.
It was fucking horrible.
It's a defense mechanism.
It's evolving, dude.
I know, dude.
It's fighting back.
Here's a comment.
comment. Oh, don't even get me started on how much I hate these little green
devils, laughing emoji.
[Laughter]
No, not my radish.
It makes me fart.
Here's a comment that's just in all capitals. Nasty, and that's from Stoner69.
Whoa. Fuck, yeah.
He likes a different green sprout if you know what I'm talking about.
That's right, dude.
I don't really like this, but at least it's not as bad as cow tongue, lamb heart, bull
or buffalo penis, and a buffalo penis smoothie.
Oh, well there's a spoiler for the fucking list, Caleb.
Great job.
Is a buffalo penis on here?
Maybe.
Could be.
Yeah, we don't know.
Number three.
There's got to be at least like five penises on here, I feel like.
Different animal penises.
Yeah, I'm looking at three right now.
Oh, oh.
Come on man, put your pants back on.
[Laughter]
Sorry, I'm having trouble with my audio, but just for Patrick, I'm not going to be able to respond to anything he says.
That's right, ice him out.
Damn dude, when the in-laws come over for dinner, you're going to be like the best slave ever dude, just fucking taking care of them dude.
Making them feel like shit.
Yeah, that's what I like.
Turning off your microphone in front of them.
Yeah, because you have a microphone like a drive-thru.
Yeah, you see, he threw an intercom.
Number three is Rocky Mountain Oysters, aka Bull Testicles.
Damn, they don't make fear factor shit now.
Yeah.
Is this, do you guys have a defense for this one?
No, I've never had them.
It's actually really good.
There's no way this is good, dude.
I mean, I guess there's no reason it wouldn't be good, because like, it's not like there's
like pee in them.
It's, you know, 100% if it's gonna be bad it's because of texture.
Because that's every bad part of like beef is like beef tendon.
It's because it's fucking disgusting and chewy and weird in your mouth.
Yeah.
I mean, I gotta imagine.
Yeah, so what's the texture of a testicle like in your mouth?
Yeah, I mean one of you guys has to be able to answer this, right?
I mean, yeah.
What's it like when you're really going to town chewing on it?
I haven't reached them yet.
Yeah, mine haven't dropped yet, so I can't reach them either.
[laughter]
Uh, it's like-
This is like- yeah, are we about to read the same thing?
I was gonna say, it's like neutering your dog and then eating it.
This should be outlawed.
Wow. Oh, look at us.
I mean, yeah, I see dog. I gravitate to that pretty fast on one of these lists.
Yeah, you know, when you take your dog in to get neutered, it's sitting in the front seat, next thing you just look at it,
you're like, "I'm gonna eat your fucking nuts after I take him out."
[laughter]
You better- last time, you better say goodbye to him, he's gonna be in my stomach pretty soon.
Are dog testicles like fucking wisdom teeth where you're gonna have to keep them?
Do you think they get that?
I need you to neuter this dog before dinner time and I want to keep them.
I got a stew pot going, I'm gonna put these in when I get home.
And this is just what they need.
Listen, I have the nose thing from Ratatouille, I know what every dish needs at all times.
This one needs dog testicles.
Here's a comment.
Or should I say rubbish from a nasty animal part.
Wow.
That's pretty polite.
There's a comment below that.
It says, "I already eat a human testicle."
Alright.
Next minute, if my girlfriend ate it, she will have a minotaur.
That's how it works.
You eat food, it grows in you like a baby.
In total drama, the contestants had to eat them.
Yuck.
Isn't that a cartoon?
Yeah.
Why are you like grunting stuff?
It's a cartoon.
Oh, God, I would hate to be on this show, man.
It's disgusting to eating a bull's bits.
You're not a British person, bro.
Gross.
What?
It has sperm in it?
Oh my gosh, so disgusting.
Vomiting emoji.
Oh, this is sperm in it nasty.
I would be so pissed off if they forgot to remove the sperm out of the testicle.
Yeah, no, that's the hardest part about getting these oysters is you have to jack the bull
off.
You have to jack the bull off so hard that it shoots its balls out.
Yeah.
Okay, who the heck eats the privates of a bull?
That's a good question.
That is just wrong.
People in the Rocky Mountains, apparently.
Get this out of my face.
Sorry, this is something I wouldn't try.
I'm not going to eat a bull private part.
[Laughter]
Fair. Drawing the line on that one.
Number four is lamb heart.
I've never eaten hearts. I know that they sell like...
I've eaten chicken hearts before.
Something about, like my local grocery store has,
the poultry section is like
ten chicken breast packages and then only chicken heads and hearts.
Yeah.
Like what is it?
What do people think of it?
I mean that's how you gain either the intelligence or the courage.
I only go into Halloween though.
That might be the problem.
That's like a skill tree type thing where whichever one you buy you either class it
into intelligence, like mana or HP.
What's like the nastiest, like on paper nastiest part of an animal you've eaten?
Probably all the poop and the butt and the wiener.
That's pretty gross, man.
And the throw up too.
And all its boogers too.
And the cat's armpit hair.
Pretty gross.
And all its earwax.
That was nasty. I don't even know why I ate that.
That was cow-pubes nasty.
I was on one that day for real though.
I was on fire though.
I'm eating chicken gizzard which you I I think it's uh I don't usually trust a
double Z in a food but it was it's pretty fine what about pizza you fucking
moron lizard either one of those I don't I can't eat pizza because that's gluten
in it now what are other double Z's that you don't trust
Wazzah!
The answer to finding a hit with that dude, you're in trouble bro, you might be in a scary
movie.
You might be Scream on the other end.
Yeah, it's true.
But I've never eaten a heart.
Yeah.
I don't like blood tastes.
Like anything that has blood in it is freaky to me.
I don't think they have the blood still in the heart when you eat it.
But there used to be some blood in there.
Well, there used to be blood in there.
If you're eating meat, there's blood in there.
I'm pretty sure it's in there somewhere.
Yeah, hearts gotta have tons of blood in it, dude.
[laughter]
You can't get blood out of a heart.
Yeah, when you kill the animal, all the blood, it's like how a spider's legs retract when you kill it.
All the blood goes directly in the heart.
Yeah, I don't want that shit, man.
That's nasty.
That's why you got so many veins.
I don't have that many. I'm not that veiny.
I have a big one in my head that people point out all the time,
on the train and then that's like the only one though so it's fine. I have a big big anime like
like three things that whenever I get stressed out. I love this it tastes like normal meat but it
sounds gross. I guess it would probably taste kind of normal. Yeah you know I would I would try
lamb heart before I tried bull testicles I will say. Yeah yeah for sure. Nah dude because if you eat
bull testicles like that's like a that's either like a really funny story or you just won like
like a million dollars. Yeah. That's like a pretty good, I feel like you're always in a
pretty good situation. I'm sure you can get them for two dollars. Well you live in Colorado
and you're just one of those fucking freaks that's just like, "Yeah, I love this." It's
like, "Do you actually love this?" Because they're all fucking potheads, man. Yeah. They
get the munchies, they'll fucking... "Oh, I'm so hungry. Oh, my pantry doesn't have any
chips in it. I guess I'll eat my fucking bull's testicles." That was the first guy that came
up with that. Yeah. You know one comment just says vomits. That's short. That's to the point.
Someone says sounds disgusting shrimpies. Number five is frog's legs. Frog legs I guess taste
like chicken. So I guess frog is another type of chicken. Alright we got another win for
chicken right now. But it's because they fry it like chicken. It's like if you eat them
without, it's like because they're dressed up like fried chicken. So your brain goes oh
- Yeah, it's chicken, but it's like,
yeah, nevermind.
I was gonna say, the only other,
usually most people, the only other time
you run into a dead frog is either
on the side of the road or when you have to dissect it.
It smells like shit 'cause it's full of formaldehyde.
Nobody really knows what a frog tastes like.
It's like, oh, it's battered and fried and salted.
Everything tastes the same when you do that.
- I know what a toad tastes like, but not a frog.
(laughing)
But yeah, I guess that makes sense.
it's like your brain's tricking you into thinking it's chicken.
I guess it's the same thing for gator tail too,
'cause I've had fried gator tail and it's just like,
"Oh yeah, it's chicken."
I had gator that was like, it was cooked like in the oven.
And it just had like dry rub on it and shit.
It was solid, man.
Gator is an underrated meat.
The problem to me is that it is much easier to kill a chicken than an alligator.
Yeah.
Maybe you do.
But I think a gator is more of a reward when you kill it,
'cause it's like you killed a dinosaur.
We should be eating more reptiles in general, I think.
I think that's, uh...
What is your opinion on eating bugs?
Who?
Uh...
Just the panel.
Oh yeah, haven't people been eating cicadas and shit lately?
'Cause they're everywhere?
I mean, if it's around, you know.
Yeah, might as well eat it.
I will say, if I see one crawling up my wall, I'm gonna grab it.
It's easier than getting up to find a Clif Bar in the pantry.
[laughter]
Last night, I fought a fly that was like...
Not because I'm super small.
And I didn't use it too thick as a spear.
No.
I didn't do that.
No, I'm not really small.
Are you sailing in your sink on a bottle cap?
No, dude.
Why would I square up to a fly?
No, I was in fly combat.
I was chasing it all night, dude.
Like the Breaking Bad episode.
You were chasing it across your kitchen counter.
No, I was not.
I did not capture him and say, "Oh, we will feast for a week on this fly."
You know, you're far away from us.
I was chasing it all night, dude.
Like the Breaking Bad episode.
You were chasing it across your kitchen counter.
No, I was not.
I did not capture him and say, "Oh, we will feast for a week on this fly."
I did not capture him and say, "Ah, we will feast for a week on this fly."
Dude, did you do a really cool move where you swung on your window shades cord across and
you did like a Pirates of the Caribbean thing and you stabbed the fly with a toothpick?
Or a thumbtack, actually?
I don't even want to tell my fly story anymore, actually.
I want to hear your fly story.
Caleb, let's hear your fly story.
I just saw a big fly.
I think you're a regular sized man.
That's a regular sized bed behind you and a normal sized bed.
That's right.
Yeah, what about my bedroom?
room looks like I'm in a dollhouse right now. Almost nothing, right? I fought a fly and I
just looked at it and I was like I think if I ate you you'd fill me up about as
much as a grape. I hit him out of the sky and because I'm so big that it's the sky
at the top of my apartment I hit him out of the sky and he flew into my sink and
I was like you know I'm gonna do the dishes tomorrow I'll pick the fly out of
that thing later but this fucking fly had so much fucking gumption and gusto that
he I found him today next to my TV he crawled all the way out of the sink what
if that's a different fly I was gonna say the same thing unmistakably large fly
yeah Caleb small enough he could see the flies haircut he could tell the
difference are you fucking serious right now keep it going me being really really
little all right I'm not little dude I don't fight dust bunnies it's not true
you don't you ride them
your oscillating fan is blowing them across the room and you go and you tie a
piece of floss to them and you get dragged behind. If you even insinuate for a second
that I have to jump on a light switch with my entire weight of my body to make
it go on or off. No of course not you could never reach to the light switch.
What if I had a bunch of dental floss that I climbed up like a cable? Did you
even fucking consider that dude? No. And no I don't use a post-it note as a
paraglider. What is wrong with you people dude? I'm fucking done talking about this shit
dude any good comments on fried legs frogs legs legs top one here is frogs are
natural for me but try to eat it it's tasty if you are an adult you surely get
beat by a kid because my cousins only eight and nine but they already eat
frogs oh and my first time eating this is what I am 11 years old
If you are an adult, you're gonna be beat by a kid.
You'll surely get beat by a kid.
So stupid.
There's a comment here also that says, "This is actually considered a delicacy in some countries."
Which I like that they went to that much effort just to not to write France.
They just didn't want that dirty name.
Yeah, they didn't want to pay it the respect of naming it.
Good for them.
number six is sure strumming
of the sort of running fish that is the uh... yes it is a
sounds canadian back
is this a yet this is a look at everybody everybody is getting the eat some
fucking food is gotten all with a slash through it and we're like white slurry
it's the uh... but the every will not be held
the reason i do that they are from the you know
the first i would bet it's getting a view of food he wandered into like a uh...
toxic waste dumping ground and he saw the big the big circle with the line through
it like do not go here and he was like oh this must be food and that's why that
owes everything now.
Yeah that's uh what is this exactly? It's like rotting fish. Yeah in a can.
Rotting fish? I remember there was a there was a point where like a bunch of
people on YouTube would like like be like I tried to eat this and it would just be
them opening the can and then immediately vomiting because of how it
smelled or something like that.
Lightly salted fermented Baltic sea herring traditional.
Yeah.
Swedish.
Of course it's Swedish.
Fuck.
They love that kind of disgusting shit.
And then they, they eat a disgusting can of fish and then they go on vacation for
four months.
It's like, yeah, I have to go swimming for four months.
I guess I would want to vacation every, you know, every month of work.
If I had to eat that shit all the time.
I mean, it's super sick.
If like, that's all you had to do to like get out of work for that long.
Yeah.
You eat that shit.
You eat a box of scallops and some fried chicken for two days.
You eat surstromming, you get so sick, you get like, it opens up your third eye and you
invent like Legos.
Like, that's like.
Yeah, exactly.
That's how it works over there.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
It's the fumes.
You eat like a can of like gross fish and then you elect a bisexual as president of your country.
That's how much your third eye gets opened.
Yeah.
Or it drives you so insane that you kill somebody and then go to prison for 30 days.
In what perfect country, dude?
Yeah, you knock someone's head off with a flail.
"Um, 30 days?"
"Probably about 30."
"I have to go to defensive driving class."
"Probably around 30 days."
"Wiz Game Cube!"
Oh, yeah, you have Luigi's Mansion, yeah, we give you...
We give you much!
You get 30 hours of community service of cleaning up Luigi's Mansion.
Yeah, what a perfect country, dude.
Yeah, they got it all figured out there.
Number 7's hard-boiled eggs.
Dude, I ate fucking tons of these today.
I'm not a big fan of hard-boiled eggs.
hard boiled eggs.
Are you serious right now?
That's like, I'm not, I try not to be a super opinionated food guy because I think that shit's
annoying but that's like the one food I just can't, like super hard boiled eggs, it just
tastes like fireworks to me.
It's like sulfur.
Fireworks?
No, I'm with CJ on this.
I think a hard boiled egg on its own.
People usually act like I'm crazy when I say that.
You are crazy.
See, see, see?
You better get used to making hard boiled eggs but I'll tell you that much.
It is nice that it's like a food that just smells horrible.
Just a terrible, terrible smelling food.
It's just nice to have a food that smells like that.
Because most foods just, you know, they don't smell like that bad.
It's one of those foods that people for some reason when they make it, like all food safety
ideas they would have with anything else just go out of the window.
Where someone will keep a hard boiled egg in a bag for four days in a backpack and then
you'll be like, "Oh, it's fucking fine, dude.
"I'll eat this right now."
- There was a restaurant I worked at
that had a hard-boiled egg and eggplant sandwich,
and I thought that was one of the grossest
combinations of foods.
- That's fucking disgusting.
That's so gross.
- Yeah, eggplant sucks.
I hate eggplant.
I hate hard-boiled eggs.
- I like them. - Put it together.
Nah.
- I just find it hard to believe that
this is the one animal product
that doesn't get improved when you boil it.
It's crazy.
Everything else is like, you boil a steak
and it comes out so good.
Yeah, perfect.
Boiled steak, boiled.
It doesn't have all that annoying crust it gets in your guts and shit.
Yeah, oh man.
What if I hurt myself?
And then all the blood from the steak goes into the water.
Keep that, you gotta fucking eat it raw.
Makes a nice gray foam on the top of the pot.
That's basically beer.
Yeah.
True.
Number eight is casu marzu.
That looks like a fucking bread bowl.
Yeah, that's cheese.
I don't know what this is.
It translates to rotten cheese.
It's even illegal.
Italian friend ate this and he said it was disgusting.
That's the top comment.
You know, we all got that one Italian friend who eats...
He's always eating rotten cheese.
Of course, like,
Italians got so addicted
to such a, like, disgusting food
they had to make it illegal.
Like, this is a threat.
It contains live maggots.
Oh. Oh, wait, I've seen
this shit! Yeah.
This was on the Andrew Zimmer
show.
He ate that shit.
It is freaking infected in maggots. What the heck Italy?
He said it looked pretty good actually and it tasted alright too.
Hey Italy, you gotta knock it off with the maggot food and you gotta knock it off with converting to fascism alright?
The more of that shit. Knock it off.
I think this might be why.
Yeah they eat so much bad cheese they're like, "Hmm what if we gave like a weird bald guy power?"
What do the maggots do for the cheese dude?
dude they eat the cheese it's like a scope it's a scope just it's like a scope
it's like a you know like you know the kombucha you know it's you know like
when you go to like you go out and the hibachi chef does some crazy shit with
your food that's basically what the maggots are doing yeah they're doing like
they're just like playing around in there doing flips and stuff to you
cashew Martz who is considered by Sardinian aficionados to be unsafe to
eat when the maggots and the cheese have died.
It's only when they're alive.
What the fuck dude?
I'm looking at pictures of it, there's maggots like straight up in it.
Dude this is fucked.
Yeah, I feel like this is one of the few where it's just right on the money.
I mean, I can see that hard boiled eggs it's like, well it's just not for me, but this
is, apparently this is for, it's not for me and it's not for anybody who lives in Italy.
by
a whole wheel of cheese and just be like, "Yeah, I have to leave this in your car for like three
weeks."
Yeah, nice try, but I don't have a car, so that's not going to work.
Okay.
Well, maybe you can spring for a slave car, right?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, fine.
It's a sidecar and a lime scooter.
Yeah.
Number nine, this made me laugh when I found this list, number nine is just salmon.
(laughter)
- Which is very funny after all those.
- Yeah, salmon.
- You know, salmon's all right.
I like white fish more than salmon, honestly.
I know that it makes me poor,
but I like catfish and tilapia and shit way more.
- I do, tilapia was my favorite fish growing up.
- I ate tilapia almost every day.
- Yeah, I ate that so much.
- I adored it.
- It's a lie, you're a liar about that.
- No, any time I make dinner, I'm making tilapia
and fucking something that makes my pee stink so bad.
When I was a boy, I'd run home from the wharf and I would say, "Mama, we need tilapia for dinner."
And she said, "No, no, no, we have no money for tilapia. Not yet. Go, sell a goat in town. Buy a pound of tilapia."
But yeah, I'm a big tilapia fan. Salmon is just like, I don't know, it's pink.
Salmon poached in like a white wine sauce with like lemon and asparagus.
Oh, white wine.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm, okay.
Damn.
Alright.
Yeah.
Salmon, like, cooked real good and really tasty.
Could be really good.
The best salmon in the world would be amazing.
The best salmon in the world could be amazing if done right.
I hate that you guys got me there.
Fuck.
That would actually be so delicious.
Human dead body's better than salmon.
Here's another one.
Salmon is fabulous and it's good for you too.
Oh, this is the worst fish.
It is so weird and smelly.
Gross, I prefer cod.
Hey, we're not talking about video games here, bud.
Come on now.
So gooey.
Gooey?
What?
Gooey salmon?
Yeah.
I think you need to send that back, dude.
I think my favorite one on here is "I love salmon, S-A-M-O-N, take it off by Elmo World
rocks. That is good. Number 10 is century eggs. There's only one comment on it. What the fuck
is that? Century eggs are fucked up. It's an egg that's cooked for one century. That's
not true. It's not good. Century eggs, there's one comment here from the Bruh Boy 0098. It
and says, "Is this a insult to China?
I have porridge with this egg
and there's nothing wrong with it."
So I guess, I guess you put it in porridge.
- I can't figure out what the century egg is,
but it says that when they're making it,
they have to wear gloves to protect against chemical burns.
- But you know what?
Let's put it in my mouth right now.
- Yeah, I think that this is kind of like,
if you don't like hard boiled eggs, try the century egg.
maybe that'll do it for you.
- This might be the one.
- Yeah, this might be the thing that,
like maybe the problem that Patrick and I have
is that it hasn't been fucked up enough
to the point where it's black and gray.
- I want it to kill me.
Look, I eat scallops, I have to pack the freezer.
I'll fucking, I'll eat anything that kills me once.
- It's like when you have a gray steak, you know,
it's like not raw, but it's not cooked enough.
Like you just haven't taken it far enough.
- You just gotta take it to the limit, dude.
- Yeah, take it to the limit.
- A century egg looks crazy.
Like it looks like where they find the DNA.
like a DNA in Jurassic Park. Yeah it's like it does look like it's suspended in
amber. Yeah it's like it's like a mystical gem. Hey can you give me can you
give me some shit that like the big white buff guy from Prometheus would eat
and then fall into a river after?
Just give me that yeah whatever it is. Even the name Century Egg that is that's a Ridley Scott
name right there yeah. Honestly dude I'd eat this shit. Yeah you would?
I like old stuff. I like old shit. I like old shit with chemicals in it.
Caleb and I are gonna go find a place that has century eggs. I'm gonna make him watch me eat it.
I mean I'll say I would probably eat anything on this list. You know if I did if
You would eat the fucked up cheese?
I would you know maybe not the fuck that's maybe the only thing.
That's a little too far.
You would eat this before you ate the cheese?
Yeah it's an egg.
Dude, I'd eat it. I could fucking pick maggots out of my shit.
I'm not fucking eating a black egg.
If you pick out the maggots, it's not the... it's just cheese.
You don't eat the maggots, do you?
I don't think so.
You could, maybe they taste good.
I think you eat the maggots.
It's like a miscall worm.
Maggots kind of get in everything.
It's not like, "Oh, we'll just scrape this layer off."
They're like, they've already done their shit.
They're like, I don't know.
I could be wrong.
Me, dude, give me some fucking chopsticks in 30 seconds.
These maggots are gonna...
You'll have cheese and maggots.
Those will be the two things that we have.
Yeah.
Number, oh no, this is a newcomer.
Yeah, the new, this is an insult to my culture.
This is good that this is not actually on the list.
Shepherd's pie, what a beautiful dish, dude.
Oh man, shepherd's pie.
What the fuck?
Fucking so gorgeous.
So good.
That's probably like top 10 food for me.
I fucking love shepherd's pie.
Okay, all right, but he said like,
I just had this and I liked it at first bite,
but then I took a big bite and it had this weird,
gooey, unsatisfying texture.
This is, this man has never had mashed potatoes before.
(laughter)
- You said there was gonna be potatoes in this,
I thought it was gonna be like raw.
- There's some fucking creamy, salty, buttery bullshit
in this dude, this sucks.
- This brown shit and orange shit, so weird.
- Well actually, number 14 is mashed potatoes.
(laughter)
- Come on man.
- There's two comments that says, "Why are these here?"
and the other one says, "It tastes like crap, that's why."
- I also, I wanna just jump around here
so we get to some of the good ones. Number 12 is mayonnaise, which the comments on
here, the top comment is, "Every single time I eat this, I get sick. When I refuse to
eat a sandwich with mayo on it, my friend forced me to eat it. I ended up throwing
it away. Bleh." Which is it? Did your friend, were you forced to eat it or did you throw it away?
Exactly. This is a liar here. There's also a comment here that says, "Tastes bad when
mixed with cheese in a sandwich and grilled together.
Oh, I hate it. I hate that.
Oh, when you put mayonnaise on the outside of the bread and you
fucking fry it. It tastes horrible in a sandwich with lettuce and bacon and tomato.
Oh my god. I will say a lot of people from the south don't like mayonnaise
because they grew up eating something called mayonnaise sandwiches, which is just
mayonnaise and like white bread. And it just made me, I'm a fucking freak
for mayonnaise. I'll do anything for it. I love mayo.
It's very, it's mayonnaise is great, but yeah, it is very, it's easy to understand
why someone would be grossed out by it, I think.
I think like oil. I mean, yeah.
I was going to say, I think like people get grossed out by it because they don't know
actually like, it's like three things you can just make like immediately.
Yeah. Well, I think it's just like the experience
of like, like putting it, like dipping a knife into like a Hellman's jar. Like it's just
a gross looking thing, you know?
People see it and they're like,
"Oh, this doesn't taste like pudding like it look like."
(laughing)
They get mad.
- I'll concede this, mayonnaise should be vanilla.
Just based on how it looks.
There should be a vanilla flavor, but there is not.
15 anchovies, I don't fuck with anchovies, man.
- Never really, I don't think I've really had 'em.
- Really?
You're not, don't fuck with anchovies.
- That's just, I don't, they smell funny.
- I mean, I don't eat 'em like out of the tin or whatever.
They fucking rock to add to shit.
I just said I don't.
You'd love him out of the ten, dude.
If I'm gonna be enslaved by you, you have to listen to me.
There has to be a two-way, there has to be a dialogue.
Yeah, there has to be good communication there.
The only time you're gonna listen to me is when you make something really good
and I say, "Mm, my compliments to the slave."
[laughter]
That. That'll be it, dude.
Number 29's chicken liver. Here's the top comment.
"I tasted a little piece of liver one day.
It had a rubbery, powdery, grainy texture
and a bloody, metallic, heavy aftertaste.
taste I felt sleepy in an instant that I needed mom and dad to massage me and I
ate everything else on my plate afterward it felt like snow white biting into that
poisoned apple and it smells like the vapor of blood and pee. This sounds like
those guys that like post about colognes and shit. Jeremy Fragrance? I had to get
massaged by mom and dad is Vegemite in breaks and break comments do not insult
the heaven of a Aussie. I don't like that shit dude. Vegemite and Marmite.
Vegemite's fucked up. It's crazy to me that your like whole like cultural identity
revolves around around this thing that like looks like just shit on toilet
paper when you do not fucking talk about that is heaven for a Aussie yeah turtle
soup that sounds fine jelly deals mmm jelly that's just a British thing
grits do grits feel like the most fucking incredible thing in the world
You're from the south, you can't...
Dude, it's amazing.
We got charred meat.
I put, dude...
I worked at a cracker barrel. I can't eat grits ever.
I'll make you some damn grits.
I fuckin', I saw, I had to scoop ketchup and grits out of bowls and throw them into a trash can.
I can never eat that shit.
That ain't my problem.
It's a meat, yeah, it's a meat problem, just sayin'.
Bread, pepperoni, pickles...
Cow brain...
Barbecue sauce...
And then bacon.
What?
Cheeseburgers. Number 108 cheeseburgers.
Oh, fuck that shit.
Oh, fucking cheeseburgers, dude.
That shit is disgusting.
Um, caviar. I had caviar for like the first time recently. It was terrible.
Oh, yeah, me too.
It was fucking awful.
Well, it was probably because it was warm.
I mean, I don't...
Was it warm?
We were eating it at a public park.
Some guy just like brought it to a park, and he was like, "Taste this."
this and I was like fuck you dude this is horrible and also really weird move man
I was gonna bring my thermos of caviar to the park and offer it to strangers hey
what's up number number 135 and don't get mad with me for saying this bat soup
it caused the coronavirus oh my god ding ding ding ding there you go
Dude, how could you resist it? It looks so delicious.
It's true.
Alright, that's pretty much it for this, yeah?
Yeah.
Number 189 is cod sperm.
This is from Japan. Japan is a really cool place.
Except for this food.
That's just sad.
The last one is number 192.
The Japanese are really fucking up over there.
The last one is "fuh".
And the only comment is,
"What is dat garbage?"
All right, thank you CJ for coming on man.
Thank you so much CJ.
Yeah, that was a lot of fun.
Where should people find you?
What's the deal?
Where should people look for you?
Plug your shit.
Oh yeah, hey, if you want to watch three men in their 30s watch reality TV shows, men for
women in their late teens and 20s, then feel free to go to Eat Chain, twitch.tv/eatchain
and you can watch.
We love Eat Chain.
Oh man.
Oh yeah, we've got to have you guys on.
90 day streams.
Oh yeah, I'd love to come back on. I can't find the good episodes. No, you know what it is,
is the first time I ever watched it, I watched it with you and then I tried to watch it alone
and it wasn't the same. It's really bad. Yeah, I haven't watched it since we all watched it
together. Yeah, it's fucked up. We're watching that one where it's about those two blonde,
those pumpkin-headed twins, Darcy and Stacy, but it's a whole show about them. So normally they're
only on there for like eight minutes, but now it's a whole 40-minute episode and it's so fucking
and bad. It's the worst shit in the world. I hate it. I'm not gonna make you guys do it.
No, it sounded like, "Oh, this can't be that bad." And it's so horrible. It's like I regret
doing it. Damn. I think all reality TV is good. Yeah. It's beautiful. Yeah, normally
they're really entertaining and cool and well produced. This one's bad. All right, so I-Chen,
check it out. Bye, everybody. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.