You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
Crap monster.
Where is the lamb who was slain?
Isn't awesome God he lambs.
We need a rest of the boat.
Okay, yeah, right away.
Yeah.
First things first.
Okay, so let's think of the elements of a worship song.
of a song first of all I need a melody so we can just use twinkle twinkle little
star for that that's that works that's a love you I love God I am so in love with
God I'm married to God God is my husband or my wife nuns aren't allowed to make
worship song my song is about my love with God no all of the evangelical songs
have to be about like how big God is. God so big. God is the biggest man I've ever seen.
Yeah like God. Yeah God you're the tallest guy. God is bigger than the Empire State Building.
He's bigger than a car and he's bigger than a hippo. I was writing my own melody. I was writing
a appeal to like kids nowadays so we could have a rap verse where it's like "yo my God is immense
in size when I saw him I couldn't believe my eyes I went to heaven he was so tall
standing next to him I felt so small I got his love I felt his power I was only
in heaven for one hour I came back to life on the operating table and that is
the story and the moral of my fable that could be a good yeah that's good God is
big as as King Kong God he chose me to write the song God is bigger than the
Titanic if I didn't make the song then God would panic I had to go to the God
store to now I always go to the store and all my freestyle I'm like I think I
think I maybe lost my touch with rapping dude I might get kicked out of the
cipher soon I think you might I think you know what dude there's nothing more
embarrassing than getting kicked out of the cipher where they the head of the
Cypher walks up to you and he turns your hat back forwards and he says, "You're out."
Yeah, he uncrooked your hat.
Yeah, and you say, "Play a what?"
Yeah, and you know what? I'm gonna be 100% with you.
You keep it 100% with me?
I'm gonna keep it 300% with you.
You honestly have not been rapping as much as you should.
And then the guy comes up to you to try and kick you out of the Cypher
and he turns your hat back around and everything and you're panicking and you're like
"No I wanna stay in the cypher, you look like you have a dirty diaper, by the way I'm gonna
go to the store" and then you know it's...
It's all yeah.
You know you've been, you have been going to the store so much that you have store fixation
with
You've turned your back on hip hop.
The store can be hip hop.
Oh really?
Supreme store.
Really?
I had to go to the Supreme store, get some clothes for my whore, and then she was a bore,
so I went back to the store, and I got more.
So I went to a shrink, he analyzed my dreams, he said it's lack of sex that's bringing me
down.
Yeah, yeah, and then he went to a whore, said my life's a bore, so quit your whining or
your God is awesomely large.
Sometimes I give myself the faith, sometimes God puts me in my place.
It all keeps adding up.
I think Christ is coming up.
Out of the ground.
Out of the cave.
Am I here to praise the Lord or am I...
Fuck.
masturbations lust is fun you should find the Lord that could be maybe a
different you know that maybe do a full bite bite my lip and close my eyes think
of Christ tonight no I mean no you know it's a same pray to Christ and close my
eyes pray to God pray to Christ for paradise I haven't been beautiful
paradise about pray to Christ and close my eyes pray for Christ I and paradise
Pray to take me to paradise. I've been sleeping in my dad and wife
I had a dream last night
That I was with you guys and we were trying to buy Green Day t-shirts
I straight up you just remind me. I did have a dream last night about a rap battle. That was on the beach
Oh my god, this is like some this is very little but Caleb was there, but he is not so yet
We're all we're all talking about our dream. I wasn't battling wait what I think I remember
I don't realize that means that you're like subconscious mind and shit doesn't see me as a battle rapper
I the I remember it was it was people at the beach
And then there was like a like a kid who was trying to start a rap battle like it was a young kid who was trying
to like
Yeah, just a one kid. You just want a one-man rap battle. Well. I know that's why that's why that was kind of the crux
Of the dream that's why it was like what is this? Yeah?
Because you were promised a rap battle that didn't happen.
No, we were just like at the beach and then a kid came up and he was you know trying to
start a rap battle.
You spit heat?
Yeah.
And was everybody just like, "No dude, I can't battle you."
I don't remember.
I'm at the beach.
I think I woke up going, "Ahh!" at that point, covered in sweat.
"There was nobody to battle that little boy!"
That's the worst.
Dude, I've been, this is my first week.
We should start a charity for kids who won't.
It's a Big Brothers Big Sisters program.
No battler left behind, dude.
Yeah.
You get assigned a cipher partner.
Oh my god, dude, if I seriously get M&M, I'm gonna lose.
Oh, no.
That's the worst part about it is, obviously, they're older than you, so they know way more about magic.
So they have more knowledge of the-- more street knowledge.
Maybe they assign, like, really young orphans that are younger than the kids who have no opponents, so that the kids can easily defeat them.
Yeah, so it's like big brothers, big sisters, but you're the big brother.
So the kid's like, like comes in and is like, "Hey little orphan, I'm gonna battle you.
You're so ugly and that's why I'm mad at you."
And then the orphan, you know, tries to do a verse and he's like, "I'm so hungry!
I'm so hungry!
It's cold!
I want more food!
I need food!
May I have some more, sir?"
Oh my god, he flopped.
Yo, he flopped hard.
What the fuck?
Dude, I've been having the most insane dreams.
This is my first week ever taking melatonin.
Yeah, yeah, and it's giving me the most the fucking craziest dreams
I had last they're like like I'll wake up and like see the real world and then my brain is like you're not done yet
Buddy, and it'll put I feel hands just pulling me back down into a dream like my dad is a lot of
Dreams. Yeah, it's fucking horrifying. I don't like that
I had there was this one time me and my ex-girlfriend like both took melatonin and you trips together
We both
Around each other
It's like it's like the like every acid yeah movies you on the other side
I dude I like we both woke up from having like like a night terror like we both woke up at the same time like
And like I just remember like like at the same time just like we we can never take
Dude, I had a really scary dream the night before last. I've had two. I had two. I don't remember my dreams that often
But I had two in a row. The one from
The night before last night was I had this dream that I was in like this dorm thing where everyone was like packing up to
Leave and and I was like outside and it started like blizzarding all of a sudden and I was like trying to walk back to the dorm
But it was like it's hard to walk in the snow
And then there were these like big like just like
Stick figure creature things that were just like peeking around corners and trying to follow me back
And I finally got inside and I took the elevator up and I got to my dorm room and I like went around the corner and
The door was already open and I was like in the gym
I was like, oh that means something's waiting for me in there and then I woke up it was
And then I went on my phone I checked Instagram and then I looked at my Twitter notifications
And then I got up and I had a bowl of cereal and I made some coffee
and I went on my laptop. It's funny when someone tells you about a dream like
nobody cares about your dream but the person who had the dream but it's funny
pretend you're like insanely interested you're like please continue please no
no don't end it now. Who else showed up? What did your father look like? Yeah no I'm
fine. I'll never talk about a dream again it's okay. I don't know that I've ever had a
good dream. Yeah. Yeah. All my dreams are about like, like, it's like, just, it might as
well be a memory of like me going to like middle school and like forgetting that to
pack a lunch and that's like the entire dream. I mostly have stress dreams like that.
Have you ever had a night terror? Yeah, dude, I think I've talked about it before. What's the difference between a night terror and a nightmare?
Couldn't tell you, that's why I'm asking. Or I think it was sleep paralysis is what I had.
That's not a night terror, dude. Well, you wake up fucking terror, you feel like
you're glued to the bed. I saw a scary movie at night that could be a night terror.
That is a kind of night terror. I saw it. I probably talked about it before but I was
watching on because I used to have that like CRTV CRT TV with like the the VCR
DVD combo thing. Oh yeah. I would watch like I had just a shit ton of VHS tapes
and I just watched those before bed and I was watching the first Star Trek movie
and I like went to bed and then like at the end of that like tape was just like
a gray screen I remember looking at the gray screen falling asleep my light was
on and then I like felt like I woke up I was in my bed in complete darkness and
I was like oh there's somebody like right at the foot of my bed huh there's
somebody like right there and he's like gonna kill me yeah I remember like I
getting up like like I remember like like I have to lunge forward or something
like if I get up he'll go away and I like got up and then like I woke up in my bed
in the same position and like the light all that happened was like the lights turned on.
It was funny. Yeah I've had I've only had sleep paralysis a few times so one of the times I did
was when I was at school and I was like a like a standardized test day and like it was like oh
when you finish your test you can't leave so you can just like sleep at your desk or like read or
something and I fell asleep on my desk yeah and then I got sleep paralysis and I like couldn't
move with my head on my desk and I like thought there was somebody just like
standing over me it was so fucked up.
Dude I like uh I've had sleep paralysis a couple times but I never really noticed
that I can't move because like if somebody was in my room
I just yeah I wouldn't move anyway. I don't want to like have to like I'd
rather die than like have to fight a monster dude.
Like fuck that dude. Yeah dreams suck also because it's like I feel like
people talk about dreams like it's like a free like virtual reality
But like, it's not. No, every dream is like you're in church and then you look down at your feet and
you realize you're a bug. Yeah. It's like, that's not like fun. It's kind of nothing to me.
All my dreams are like either stress related or anxiety related. And it's just like...
It's also, it's funny to me like to like be really into lucid dreaming when like,
like, like when you're asleep is like the one time and you don't have to think about everything,
anything at all. And you just be like, I have to control this and I have to create stories
every night. Dude, I used to be a big time fucking lucid dreaming brain hacker.
I've had weird dreams where it's like I know it's a dream and then I'm like, well,
I could just do this right now and they're all skateboarding related.
So like, I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna land that trick that I thought of.
Just like shit like that. Like I landed a varial heel flip in a dream and I was like,
I'm gonna do that tomorrow. You're in a dream and you're doing like a real trick. Like why not have
like a like a right jump I just like I feel like I'm not gonna lose man every
time I've like realized I was in a dream I didn't like control anything I just be
like damn this is a dream that's crazy it just keeps like everything just keeps
going yeah yeah yeah no nothing I tried to I tried to astral project when I was
in high school cuz I was - yeah I never a lot of drugs and also I heard sin bad
talk about it yeah Sinbad really into astral projection he claimed that he
went to China in the astral world that's not the same as lucid dreaming right
because I guess astral projection is people believe that you leave your
body and I never really believed it but I was like I mean might as well try
like whatever. Sinbad's doing it. Sinbad's like a normal guy right he wouldn't believe something crazy so I
like would just sit and I would just like sit up in my bed and try to fall
asleep while like sitting up and then like right before you fall asleep you
try to like grab something in front of you and he claimed that yeah he did that
one time and he put a rock on his bed and he like reached out grabbed the rock and
he was in like an astral world and then he's like I'm going to China and he flew
to China. Damn I know Ray Romano is really into lucid dreaming because of an
interview. That makes sense, he changes his voice to be normal in the dream. It's an interview on the Pete Holmes show that I saw in high
school.
Awesome dude.
Yeah.
He's like, "I love lucid dreaming."
So cool.
"I love getting away from my nagging wife."
I'm a bit of a psychonaut.
Yeah, I do like a lot of acid.
I do a lot of...
Is this the guy from Bob's Burgers?
This isn't even Ray Romano.
That's all Ray Romano dude.
That's true.
That counts.
Just hold your nose.
It's Ray Romano.
Squidward is Ray Romano.
Hey Spongebob, you gotta flip the burgers.
Come on.
Bob you got it flip the burgers come on come on Spongebob have you guys seen
that show men of a certain age with Ray Romano I thought that was Tony Shalhoub
nope suck my cock it's Ray Romano nah dude you don't you don't talk shit about
the lube I love the lube are you fucking me I've seen every episode of monk Tony
the Tony the little you know my funny mannerisms I just completely ripped off
From Monk.
Yeah.
From Monk, yeah.
Yeah, a lot of this show is very Monk inspired.
Yeah, we do a lot of Monk shit.
Yeah.
You know, I'm always smelling my hands and shit.
Oh, it's raining now.
Just a quick update for my friends.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
I really appreciate that.
Cool.
It's an update for Caleb.
Caleb, I'm supposed to deliver a shirt to you that John gave me.
And you're gonna not do it 'cause it's raining.
Yeah, I'm not doing it 'cause it's raining.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
I don't expect you to do that.
I have the shirt right here.
I believe you.
You can tell me this at any time.
Yeah, this is not...
We were just on a phone call before this, and you're still showing me my future FUBU shirt.
It is cool.
Yeah.
It is really, really cool, and I'll look good in it.
Check right here, NBA logo on the sleeve.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Aren't you excited now?
I mean, I've been excited.
I just don't know that this is the platform to talk about the shirt that you're giving
me.
Well, I'm trying to...
For John.
how good of friends we are.
- You know, I was probably gonna post a photo
in that shirt at some point.
- Yeah, well now people are gonna get excited for sure.
- They've already gotten a spoiler about it
and you've kinda fucked up my entire plan.
- I didn't fuck up anything.
I made, I drew up hype.
- Dude, the other day I bought like a pack of white t-shirts
and a pack of black t-shirts 'cause I was like,
I like looked in the mirror and I had on like a,
this like El Chapo shirt I got from a fucking like
flea market about like the drug dealer
and I was wearing like big ass shorts
and my like camel cigarettes, like windbreaker.
And I was like, I dress like a fucking cartoon character, dude.
I need to get like just some normal clothes.
- I dress like that.
- I'm like a grown man, I'm dressing like I'm a baby.
So now it's all gonna be white tees and black tees for me.
- I did that in high school.
I did the exact opposite. - And a propeller hat.
- When I got older, I started wearing more goofy shit.
This morning I was out to breakfast at a diner.
I was sitting at the counter and this old lady came in
and was sitting next to me, me and my girlfriend.
And she, near the end of our meal,
she turned to me and she asked what it said
on the back of my shirt,
'cause I'm wearing my cemetery shirt,
which says, "Come with me to hell"
in gothic letters, old English.
- Yeah. - You know?
And I was like, "Oh, it says, 'Come with me to hell.'
"It's the name of a song."
and she's like, she just like didn't care what it said.
And was just like, oh, see, that's interesting.
You know, I grew up in Switzerland
and I had to learn to read Gothic letters
when I was growing up.
(laughing)
I was like, oh really?
And she was like, yep, but not in school.
And I was like, okay.
And then she said, I bet COVID's really bad for bands.
Do you play instruments?
And I said, nope, I'm just wearing a band shirt.
And then she stopped talking to me.
I hate old ladies with a past, dude.
I don't give a fuck, dude.
I don't give a fuck that you used to fucking eat canned fucking piss in the depression.
Shut up, dude.
You grew up in Switzerland?
Well, you're in Watertown now, so fuck you.
Yeah, that's a true town.
The town, baby!
The town from the town!
That's right, Watertown Strong, baby.
Yeah!
Suck my balls, you old bitch.
I don't give a fuck about where you're from.
It's about what block you're from in Watertown.
How about you start spitting that cross address, because I'm going to fucking kill you.
Old people, I mean we've talked about, let's not get back into this.
I mean let's do it, why not?
We've talked about how much I don't like old people.
No, you know what?
They haven't had enough.
Listen up you old pieces of shit.
Hey, old people.
Nobody can't, listen, World War I and II, I don't think either of them happened, and
I think you're lying.
Yeah, I'm happy when you get senile because it means I don't have to listen to your dumb
stories anymore you just walk around going "blah blah blah"
I get to take stuff from your purse now. You don't get to hide that candy from me.
Huh? I'm taking, you know what? I'm taking two Werther's Originals.
Here's what I do. I go to the Dollar Tree, I buy every single bag of Werther's they have
just to fucking make poor old people, their life a little bit worse.
And then I scatter them on the ground outside the senior center so that they trip and slip
around. I melt them all down, I make a sculpture of
a middle finger and I put it in the middle of the old people's home and I flip off all
those old people with my big Werther's Originals middle finger.
Old people are scary man.
The last time I saw my great grandpa, it was before he died, he was like staying at a nursing
home and he just like wouldn't say anything, he was just like completely catatonic and
we were like, "How you doing there, Papa?"
And he was just like, "Get me out of here."
That was the last thing he ever said to me.
oh my god it was like me and my brothers trying to like come visit like cheer him
up we knew he's sick and we were all like oh oh pop funny yeah yeah yeah yeah
and then like going back to my mom she's like what did he say he's loving it
He said I get his car. He said take me to McDonald's please and I'll come right
back cuz I love it. He said this bed is so comfortable. He said they don't hit me
with socks filled with oranges. Yeah there was a yeah and I think he also said I'm
in jail. Yeah no it was a bad day. Yeah. He was one of those guys who like the last
three years of his life he just ate every day at the same Chinese restaurant.
and if he could like days that he couldn't eat there he was like
noticeably like depressed yeah and also he would go and he would just get he
would get like plain chicken and white rice nice so cool dude yeah he's a
fucking man dude yeah do the white rice at the Chinese restaurant don't you
don't you dare say that it's delicious don't you dare say that it's like a
- Don't.
- Oh man, the white rice, best thing at the Chinese restaurant.
- I wish they'd lay off the spice a little bit though.
- Yeah, I wish restaurants stopped using seasoning.
- Yeah.
- I really do.
- I know, it's like they're slathering on the salt on there
and it's like I'm gonna have to rinse my mouth out
after I eat this, it's so spicy.
- Just white, all white rice, plain chicken.
- Yep, white bread, ice cubes.
tin foil, no nothing like salmon, raw spaghetti.
Even if there is any kind of fish, no salmon.
Yup.
Yeah, I will say--
Just the bones, just the fish bones.
I do agree that every time I go to the Chinese restaurant,
it low-key feels like I'm doing the white rice challenge.
Yeah.
Dude, I keep ordering from this one Indian place
and I keep forgetting that, like the meal that I will order.
Like I'm like trying new things on the menu.
I tried chicken dildo last night.
Yeah, I bet you did.
It was really good.
Chick-a-dilder in your ass.
Chicken dilder.
It's...
Chicken...
I hope that's how it's pronounced.
Chicken dilder.
Oh, it...
Well, okay, hold on.
It'd be funny if you Googled "chicken dilder" and it was like zero results.
Yeah, every time I look up "chicken dilder" it just says "chicken and pineapple curry,"
so I guess maybe I could have just called it that.
I hate when they be putting that pineapple in that shit.
Oh, dude, it was so good.
Dude, I don't want no hot pineapple.
It was good.
You just ate the desert?
It was really good, but I keep forgetting that it comes with white rice.
So for the first two weeks I was living here, me and Joe would both order from it and then
also forget.
And for the first two weeks I was here, our fridge was just full of boxes of white rice.
When you get to takeout, they hit you with the big-ass fucking white rice.
Yeah.
Big boxes of white, like, we had no room
on the top shelf of the fridge for two weeks
'cause it was all white rice.
- Yeah, here's what they should do.
Chinese places, if you're listening.
Stop giving me that white rice, fill up that takeout box
with more fortune cookies, bro.
- Oh man, do fortune-- - I'm fuckin--
- Fortune cookies are so, like, so good.
- It's one of the best cookies in the universe
and I don't know-- - What is the flavor of it?
- It's paper, that's the thing that you like about it.
- Maybe that's the thing that makes it so good,
is the paper. No, it tastes like destiny dude. You don't know. It's so beautiful. It's not
too sweet. What do you mean I don't know? You think I didn't try a fortune cookie before?
You've never had one dude. You're not adventurous like me. I'm trying all sorts of ethnic foods
like fortune cookies almost every single day. I'm going around doing like a Andrew Zimmer.
I'm ordering fortune cookies from Indian restaurants. I'm ordering them from...
A kind of bizarre foods world tour where I try fortune cookies. I tried cookies from
every culture. This one tastes really, this one tastes slightly of lemon and
actually has a very neat fortune in it. I am trying the Chips Ahoy from
every continent. Did they do, did they do the lottery numbers in other countries
fortune cookies? I don't think, I don't know. That's a very
funny thing to put in a fortune cookie. Yeah. Yeah, I like that. I like that they
do that. What, what is the, what's the flavor that
makes fortune cookies taste like fortune? It's lemon dude. Is it lemon? Hint of
lemon. I don't know. Let me look up. It's lime dude. It's a hint. It's actually a hint of lime.
Oh, it's a sugar. It's tahini. It's the tahini and the other stuff that they're pouring on top
of the fortune cookie. Also, who are these beautiful women who fold these things? I want to see them so
bad. Yeah. These are hand folded. A machine couldn't do that. That's a craftsmanship. My high school...
- Vanilla and sesame oil.
- My high school, the Chinese class,
the Chinese language class,
they would take a field trip every year
to a Chinese restaurant and make fortune cookies.
- Oh.
- But I did not take Chinese, so I did not get some.
- You ever have to make so incredible.
- Yeah, from what I heard, it was pretty stressful,
'cause it's kinda like--
- Also, you gotta come up with a fortune, dude.
- Yeah, like making food in a restaurant.
- Right.
- It's like maybe not the best field trip.
- Yeah, free labor, yeah, it sucks.
We're going on a field trip to my restaurant
and you will work there doing math with the food.
That was my math class in eighth grade.
Did I ever tell you about this?
I probably have.
In the eighth grade, I got put into a math class
of four kids 'cause we all had ADHD.
That means you're either the smartest
or the stupidest in the entire school.
It was 'cause we were the stupidest
and all we would do was cook and it would be like,
okay, well, you could put this many teaspoons
or whatever into this.
It was like, every Friday, we would make food
with the Home Ec teacher.
- They're teaching you how to use a measuring cup?
That was an entire math class?
- Pretty much, 'cause they were like,
oh, they're all just gonna be line cooks in the future.
Like, just shit like that.
- That's fucking incredible, dude.
- Oh, dude, it was the best math class I was ever in.
- Yeah, we had very different--
- We made the worst, the worst thing we ever made
in that class was the teacher was like,
okay, we're gonna make this recipe.
It's a tortilla and you spray it with Pam cooking oil and you put cinnamon sugar on it.
[Laughter]
I forget what it was!
That that was supposed to be... I think it was supposed to be churros. I don't know!
[Laughter]
We literally like spent a whole class spraying tortillas with like Pam and like putting brown shit like just cinnamon sugar on it.
It was like one of the best fucking days in that math class. It was just like, "Ah, this is sick."
My math class at my like right-wing homeschool thing was like, it was all like libertarian
like economics like we never did like real math so we had like a three-week chunk just
on the national debt and we all had to like come up with ways to get rid of the national
debt and one kid was like cut everything except the military that the United States spends
its budget on.
I was like dude that kid's a fucking genius.
Yeah, smart.
It would work.
He's got it dialed.
also had a debate class where we had to do we had to debate for and against
slavery what we the proslavery team won and I was the leader we weren't able to
choose what side we were on we're supposed to be doing the Lincoln
Douglas debates which usually people in class in like high school do that format
but they don't do the actual Lincoln Douglas debate we did the same topic
except more narrow and just on slavery. Me and my friend were in the
same English class where we had like a we did like a debate style thing like
that or maybe it was like a social studies class I don't know it was like
it but the debate was something about was something about like like just racial
discrimination or slavery or something and me and my friend would do this thing
where we would just like sit on other other opposite sides of the room for
each other and just really loudly argue like during the debate just to like try
like just to like be loud and annoying like this yell back and forth but then it would like make
other people's in the rooms energy like rise too and like we were doing it one time and this girl
was like this girl like we were like you know like yelling at each other and this girl was like
well you know i can actually kind of see like why why um people might have been discriminating
against black people back then we're like what the fuck jesus christ yeah we never did it again
Yeah, the worst part about our slavery debate was that it was judged by like five parents from the like homeschool thing. Oh, no
And it was unanimous that the that the pro-slavery
Team won and when they were like giving their decision they were like they just made better points. There's no way around it. They were more logical
That's fucking crazy, dude. I wish I had gotten into debate team, dude
Yeah, i'm glad I didn't I wish I'd gotten on like a fucking debate team's a very funny thing to get into because it doesn't
It's not going to help you with an argument in real life.
Like it's going to lose you an argument in real life.
That is the most sociopathic thing you can get into in high school.
That's why like there is a like you're like that somebody wants to be like a politician
or something like if you're like a teenager and you want to be a politician or like your
dream is like I want to be the president it's like you are a fucking psycho fuck you.
That is a psycho thing.
You should luck into the presidency.
No I'm going to become the president pretty soon.
You can decide that at 23, 24.
Yeah, but if you're like 15 and you're like, "I'm gonna be the president," that's...
If you're 15 and your goal is power...
There's an age window.
If you're in elementary school or middle school, it's okay to want to be the president.
But once you're in high school...
That's a big dream.
Once you're in high school, yeah, you can't...
That's the cutoff for the sociopath.
The 17-year-old who wants to be a president is like, "Well, I have a plan.
I'm gonna work my way up to selectman."
That kid is gonna kill someone.
That's a fucking murderer.
Okay, the thing is though that I will debate either of you right now on any topic
And what about the top 10 most common lies people tell you can give me any position and I will win
You choose go ahead. Okay. What about number one the top 10 most common lie. I'm fine
What do you?
Before before we get into the list actually do you want to debate Caleb on something?
No, I would like to debate Caleb on whether or not he is as tiny as a bug
I would like Caleb to argue that he is that tiny.
You can go first.
I'd like you to speak for about five minutes on this
and then I may or may not provide a rebuttal.
- Of course.
So basically I'm obviously as small as a bug
due to my tiny size.
You can see it on the camera right now.
I'm as small as maybe an ant or maybe an ant's child even
because I'm even smaller than an ant.
I think that a toothpick is a flagpole
and I think that a gumdrop is a house to me
because of how large it appears in stature
to my tiny body. I'm less than an inch tall. I smell really bad and because I was hiding
in a man's ass, which I can do because of my smallness, or it was actually a girl's ass.
I changed my mind. And then also I have to fight different bugs in my house. We've been over that.
And I'm really one inch tall or smaller. I yield my time to my opponent.
Yes, I concede the debate and request a copy of the recording of the debate.
The copy has actually been destroyed.
That's not true.
And the original.
Okay, well, you look at it, there's no evidence that you won the debate then.
Well, I guess I'll...
Okay, I guess I'll do it again.
So basically to me, a piece of gum is like a surfboard because of how small I am, and
I like to ride it around in the sink.
The bathtub to me is bigger than the entire ocean combined, and I live in a tiny hole
in my wall.
Okay.
I'd like to ask Caleb some questions about borrowing.
Yes, go ahead.
Do you borrow things from the house that you live in?
Yes.
No further questions.
Sometimes I'll borrow like a grain of rice, but it's too big for me to eat, so I drive
it like a car because of how small I am.
And you might be asking yourself, how do you drive a grain of rice or a car that doesn't
have any wheels?
Well, the wheels that I use are actually nerds, the candy, and I put those on there and I drive
around.
Okay.
Guilty, I sentence you to one year in Lego jail.
We can do this now.
Lego jail?
Oh, fuck.
All right, so number one, the most common lie is I'm fine, but shit, that's so real.
That is real.
lowkey that's true.
Well I mean not that you guys would know anything about this because you're not dark and demented
like me and have-
What are you talking- I have the most pain out of anyone here.
Um.
Ow!
Oh!
No, no I have-
I have pain!
I have mental pain that you could-
Oh my head is hurting with all my thoughts!
If you guys could see a list of my mental pains your draw would drop.
I think that there's three people besides me in this call right now because I'm so crazy.
It's not about crazy, it's about mental pain.
What and it hurts to think about.
You're crazy that means you don't feel pain.
Yeah.
Look, I have mental pain, ask me a math question.
Okay.
Yeah.
How many people are in this call right now?
Oh, my head already.
That's not mental, it's physical.
Oh, I'm so anguished mentally and emotionally too, but I'm fine.
I suffer, I'm a sucker for pain.
I'm a suffer for pain.
That's like double worse.
Here's a comment here.
Honestly this is true most of the time people say I'm fine when they really
aren't I've actually told this lie before when I broke my foot in PE it hurt a lot
so I was hobbling around all day repeating I'll be fine to everyone that
asked nobody believed me I always say I'm fine when I'm sad or something I try not
to show weakness to not cry to accomplish this I cover my face just in
case I do then pinch myself or something getting an obvious like physical injury
yeah and then they're like oh my god you need to go the hospital I'm fine yeah
Seriously, don't look at me, I'm fine.
That's how I was like a month ago when I hurt my leg.
You were not, you were not.
You love talking about that shit.
You did not say you were fine once.
I said I was fine to the guy.
To the guy that I was like, can you help me land this trick?
I said like, I'm fine, whatever.
And then you set off on a months long campaign of not being fine.
To tell the entire world about your weird leg.
Yeah.
Well yeah, I mean that was the most pain I was in for a pretty long while.
No matter how many people ask me if I'm okay, the answer will always be I'm fine, even though
I might be depressed as hell.
But it's better than people thinking pity of me, depressed teenager.
Damn, that's from a depressed teenager.
They signed it depressed teenager.
Even when I'm hurt, angry, sad, etc.
I still say I'm perfectly fine.
From XXDarkStorm_PhoenixMothXX.
That's such a good username.
Yeah.
Sloth XX.
That's such a good username.
Yeah.
There's a comment here, we haven't read any of the stories on this list, but there's a
comment from Sloth21 that says, "The stories on this list are horrible."
It's da truth.
Rachel did it to me today.
Rachel?
Dude.
When I think about Rachel, it low-key breaks my heart.
Rachel, you gotta talk to people, Rachel.
Rachel, you need someone to talk to.
Your issues are mad piling up.
We got a hotline for you.
It's called the...
1-800-HOTLINE-BLING.
You gotta call that.
Drake wrote a song about it.
No.
Really powerful song.
Do you think he's going to...
There's a way...
Sorry, I just read an insane comment.
Say what you'd say.
Yeah, wait, can I read this?
Yeah.
Find that same one.
Recently, my parents got divorced.
My dad killed my brothers and I have to live with my friend.
I have only two more days here, then I'm on the streets.
I have two friends and one that tries to make me feel okay.
I have tried taking my life four times before and I'm only twelve.
I feel hopeless.
I just want to end it, but how do I without upsetting my only true friend?
She actually cares about me.
I have a knife that looks like it would do the job of finishing me, but I'm not one of
your friend's friends, so if I go, she will too.
That's horrible.
I think it's cool, it's mad cool to be depressed.
Here's a comment I found from user Lucky's that says Bart Simpson.
That's true, Bart Simpson always do behind the scene with a smile.
He was low key depressed as hell.
Yeah.
Kind of like me too.
V-Lone Bart.
Yeah.
I try to, you know, I don't know man, I'm just, I get down, you know.
Yeah, I get down.
I just need a bad bitch by my side though.
True.
a bad bitch to stick by me when I'm depressing. Sit in my car in hot box my armpits melt.
If you really want to know how I feel you gotta listen to Depression and Anxiety by the boy
boy west coast. Yeah. You have to listen to the song Caleb's Mental Anguish by B-Lack.
He's lowkey fire though. He's waiting to get signed. Yeah he's the only thing keeping me
alive right now. His music is like fire. This guy B-Lack whose raps are off the chain. I
I don't know, do you like rap? Do you like store corps? He's like the most insane store corps rapper right now.
He'd be rapping about the store all the time and shit.
And also he's mad depressed, Loki.
Yeah, V-Lack's the most depressed rapper I've ever heard of.
He truly is. He's so depressed.
He sampled the sound of his tears hitting the linoleum at the grocery store.
He said, "Clean up." He has this song, "Clean Up On Aisle My Heart."
It's so sad.
It's insanely sad.
It tells a story too. That's the thing about him.
He's a storyteller at heart.
You know, it's none of this stuff about
about jewelry or guns.
I mean besides "I'm so sad
I don't have jewelry or guns"
[laughter]
But you know, other than that
it's lyrical content.
It's about stories and poetry mostly.
He like low-key changed my entire
life. Too bad he got assassinated when he was
years old. It's one of the saddest stories in all of rap. Yeah. Is that he was the
most depressed eight-year-old in the world and then and that's why they killed
him low-key. He was about to make a documentary about depression and they
killed his ass. Yeah. They couldn't let the truth come out. Yeah and he was he was also
yeah he was in this big beef with Happy Guy the Rapper. Yeah. And if you listen to
if you listen happy guy the rapper's track smiling all the time you know there's a lot of subliminals
in there yeah i mean and i mean i don't even know why he never got convicted or anything
from that song i'm so happy i just killed a little boy named b-black
it's really fun it's one of the most [ __ ] up stories yeah and there's no lyrics either he's
just you can be like i'm smiling on the microphone but it would just make
B-Lack Stip. B-Lack Stip. B-Lack Stip was like low-key. He was real though. He was twisted,
he was tortured, he spoke to the soul of the people, you know. Yeah, the heartbeat of the
streets I would say too. Yep, and he was addicted to perfume and that was a big part of it too
actually. He was so addicted to drinking perfume that it would, I mean it's like low-key like he
He got sober right before he died and his raps absolutely fell off.
It was like, it was like maybe this.
It's chilling too because some of his lyrics you'll hear, I mean there's that one in that
and that one song I'm so sad where he says damn this perfume might kill me.
Yeah.
And it's like damn he could kind of see the future in a way.
It's damn this perfume might kill me, fuck it one more spritz.
Yeah and then yeah there's that other song where he says fuck it I'm not even gonna make
it to nine and it's like damn like that's real shit.
Yeah, it's real shit.
He kinda knew it was coming.
Yeah, and remember that one line where he's like,
he's like, "Yo, past the Vogue,
"I'm flippin' to the cardboard page, I'm goin' rogue."
Remember that one?
Yeah, that line where he says,
"I hide all my pain behind my mask.
"Every night I drink a bottle of Axe."
Yeah.
That was deep. That went crazy, dude.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
That boy was on another level.
Rest in peace.
And I do mean boy, he was eight years old again.
I would like to clarify. He's one of the most tortured eight-year-olds.
V-Lack Stip.
Yeah, they ran up on him while he was in a Maybach that was powered by a battery and it
was about eight pounds. He was riding it in his backyard.
Are we even doing the list anymore?
You guys remember his merch drop where he released a handkerchief that was labeled "For
My Tears"?
That was insane dude. That was fucking crazy to me bro.
Yeah. Anyway, on that note, number two lie, common lie people tell is I have read and agreed to the
above terms and conditions. I do that shit. Yeah, I mean, if I see one of those I click no,
I don't agree because I'm not reading that shit. I never agree. I never agree to your terms and
and conditions. I just won't use iTunes. I don't even care.
They should seriously do a South Park about this.
True. True.
I don't have all day to read 15 pages in size 8 font for nothing.
What about your future, bud?
My mom forces me to read these, even if they're over 10 pages long.
Your mom forcing you to read the terms and conditions.
and it's two pages long, I actually read this.
Dude, I wouldn't read it if it was a sentence long
and it said, "I'll kill you."
I wouldn't fucking, there's no way I'm reading that shit.
- You signed, "If you agree to this term and condition,
"I'll kill you."
- Yeah.
- Hey, fuck it, dude.
- You guys ever, did you guys ever,
I remember somebody in like elementary school or something,
like when I was first like,
when I was first like getting music
and so I like downloaded iTunes and stuff
and you have to like read the terms and conditions.
I think one of my friends told me like,
"You know like, if you actually read it,
there's a part in there that like they can use your computer to launch a nuclear missile
if you agree to it.
That's true actually.
It actually is in there.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
You didn't read, well I read the iTunes one.
Yeah.
You know, you gotta read that one.
True, that's true, yeah.
The iTunes one is the most important one to read because you get a voucher for one free
song.
One free listen.
Is that true?
Dude, what the fuck, I'm getting iTunes now.
Yeah.
Number three, I don't lie.
True.
Wait, wait, that's low key blowing my mind though because it's a list of lies and it's
on it and it actually says I don't lie.
So it's like, which is it?
Yeah, so messed up.
Top comment here is the most popular lies in our everyday lives.
If you say this, then you're being dishonest to yourself first.
All of us have lied at least once in our lives, mostly for good, sometimes even overtaken by
our evil side.
Yes, all of us have lied, admit it.
That's from that's from madman38.
Yeah, we've all given it to our madman side.
True yeah, I mean the madman knows the bad man knows evil.
Now and this
madman38, if you click on his profile, it just says Slim Shady 13.
Everybody has an evil side you know. It's true. I think that's the truth.
I hear this all the time, but you know and they know that they're lying about that the bad part
Grandma says that but she just lied so
True my grandpa said this then he lied he told my mom that we didn't eat junk food the whole weekend when he bought me a
Bag of potato chips on Saturday and a chocolate bar on the Sunday
Damn, I hate it when grandparents lie. They low-key be lying about sweets all the time and shit. Yeah
Number four I will be there in five minutes
True yeah, I use this one all the time. You do use this one a lot. Yeah, yeah
Maybe add another 25 onto that though depends on the traffic. You know he he he he parents going to the grocery store true
True that's from ocean breeze the awesome warrior. This is this is maybe what this is maybe one of my favorite usernames
I've seen on this website five minutes more like five hours, and that's from the user breakfast beast 2005
That's a good thing to like recognize about yourself
Like beast out I'm gonna fucking breakfast dude, I think I turned to a savage for breakfast only
Goes to pick up friend for school friend. I'll be out in five minutes 20 minutes later me you're on your own bitch
True, that's a little strong. I don't know about that. I think it's true. I think that's fucked up, dude
Number five Wow you look great in that dress
Yeah, I say that to Caleb all the time no, I don't wear a dress okay, okay, you want me to pull up the proof
I don't wear one often you want me to pull up the proof, but
XX dark storm underscore Phoenix moth XX is coming in with a zinger here in response. Okay, so
Great. Oh my I think I need to clean my ears
my ears. I must have misheard the phrase worse than a clown as
great
baby. Do I look good in this dress?
Now you look worse than a clown.
Yeah,
you know, not even as good as a clown, which looks like shit by
the way.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, did you say great?
I thought you said worse than a clown
and then Madman 38 says even though your inner heart says
hell no you look like a clown my wife's always fucking coming out of the
dressing room that target look like a damn clown my 200 wives all piling out
of the dress yeah and all in like it like in droning with each other saying
How do we look, babe?
Honestly, you look like 200 clowns to me right now.
[Laughter]
Number six, sorry I forgot.
True.
I don't...
But you actually don't forget.
Most of the time, yes, though I am very forgetful.
I got ADHD. I forget
so much crap.
Yeah? Like your own name?
I wish you'd forget you had ADHD.
Yeah? Why?
'Cause then you wouldn't have it anymore.
You want me to forget my pain?
Yeah, that's good.
That's so beautiful, Cameron.
I know.
Oh my god, Cameron, that's such a beautiful thing to say.
Can I tell you a poem to you about you?
You're so beautiful, you look like a rose.
You're so beautiful, the smell from you comes to my nose.
It smells so good, it smells so nice.
You're as beautiful as a sculpture made from out of ice.
I will go ice skating together on a rink.
That will be quite fun I think.
I would like to end the poem.
If there was a good line to end it, I don't know it.
Oh my fucking god dude.
You're making him cry.
You're actually making him cry.
Okay take it back.
You're such a baby dude.
You don't stop crying all the time.
You lowkey should have collabed with B-Lack when he was still alive.
Do a Watch the Throne type shit.
yeah you know i actually i i i asked him i mailed it i sent him a letter in the
mail to ask to do a collab he sent me a letter a postcard back
no writing on it just tear stains remember that line where he's like
he's like uh will ferrell anchorman i know that shit funny
funny uh posted on the couch surround sound
sipping armani remember that yeah
Remember that shit about watching Anchorman?
Yeah, yeah more rappers like him should rap about shit that I care about, you know, exactly. Yeah
Like there's a serious gap in the market in the hip-hop market right now
The market yeah with all this kind of
Cool shit that i'm into you know
You guys you remember when he was like I went to the restaurant and I ate some shawarma
My brain's so fucked up about the world and big pharma
Damn, because he was low-key conscious and shit.
Yeah, he was like a society-based rapper.
Yeah.
I just remember, yeah, there was lots of stuff like that.
You know, "My house is so awesome because I am the resident.
I hate this stupid imperialist president."
Was that the word you used?
Yeah, and it was like, damn, for there to be a rapper that could actually know about imperialism
and shit, that's like low-key insane.
And do you remember the name of the song was "This song could be about any of the presidents."
Whoa, yeah, that was insane. Yeah, he said that one line that was like I'm eight years old. No lies
I can tell I only drink perfume because of the smell. Yeah, it was insane. Yeah, he went that was from his song
My name is be like where he explained this whole deal. Yeah, that was like the first, you know, yeah
I was like when he came out on the scene
Yeah, that was like the opening bars of that song too, which were so hard when he was like I am so sad
I feel so bad
Yeah, I was like
Second of all, I feel that, like I feel that in my bones,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
And I remember going to Target the next day
and there was just like,
there wasn't like a single bottle of Chanel blue
on the shelf 'cause it was like,
he low-key had like blown up the entire industry.
And people were drinking,
people were going to Marshalls
and taking those curves samplers
and drinking all the curves perfume.
Yeah, it was insane, dude.
(laughing)
It was insane as hell, dude.
It was insane.
Yeah, remember all the people,
all those like those fake B-Lack fans that were drinking bod body spray.
Yeah it's like that's body spray low-key that's not perfume.
I mean some of them and some people were even like they were drinking shampoo.
Yeah it's like how's that anything to do with what he's doing?
When B-Lack got that Axe sponsorship I mean like a lot of people did like tell him he
sold out which is probably one of the reasons that you know he kind of you know maybe that
led maybe that led to some darker stuff. Yeah.
There's the eight-year-old rapper. Remember that line where it was like, "Take the adidas,
mix it with the Sprite, I'll be home soon. No matter how much Sprite I put in the cup,
it still tastes like perfume." I heard that and I was like, "He low-key doesn't even care how
bad it tastes because he's so addicted to that shit and he's insane on it."
And that was when I really started to think about addiction more clearly.
He's the reason I got sober as a gopher.
Yeah, for sure, yeah.
That was, he was crazy.
Number seven, don't worry, it will be okay.
Like I hate to bring this back to beelike and shit, but like...
That's a good point.
But like that's word for word, word for word, the words from his song.
Word? Yeah.
I mean, do you guys remember his lyric where he was like,
"Rollin' so deep, fucked up off this perfume,
I have a feeling that it might be my doom.
Yeah, and I was like, oh dude, remember that one that was like,
I've got perfume on my heart, you know it's never hate.
I do think I will be murdered before I turn eight.
That was like, it was like, this guy, kid,
can actually like almost tell the future and shit.
Yeah.
It's fucking insane to me.
Do you remember when he was like,
when he had that chain?
Do you remember his chain with the,
he had a Peppa Pig chain?
Thought that was really stylish.
- That was nuts, dude.
- I mean, it really changed the game.
- Remember when he ate a crayon?
- Yeah, he would eat a crayon.
Yeah, and I remember he was like one of the first,
like, not only about depression,
but he was one of the first rappers to come out
and really be honest about wetting the bed and shit.
- Yeah.
- And he was like, yeah, low-key,
like I sleep with a liner on my bed.
But you know I'm an all-timer off the head because he was such an insane freestyle rapper.
Yeah, he would only freestyle in every interview.
He wouldn't talk.
He was like, you remember when he was like, "This perfume might be the end of me.
It's like venom from a viper.
When I go to bed, I have to wear a damn diaper."
Yeah, that was insane.
And nobody could tell if it was because he was sad or because he was eight years old
or what.
line where he's like like you know you know this perfume is what my cup gonna
be full up every night I wet my damn pull up yep remember when he was like he was
like um like I'm the star player these other rappers bench guys hit the
restaurant order the smiley face French fries.
And he was like, "Whoa, he actually knows about sports."
When he was like, "When I'm feeling sad, I just cry the pain away.
I will die at age 8, 26, June, Friday."
It was impressive, dude.
Number eight, "I am sick."
Another another be like
Another one he's like he's like when he was like damn all this perfume is making me so sick at least I can stay home from
third grade and watch click
You know what a funny thing about click the first movie I ever cried yeah
Yeah, dude when he's like walking through the rain, and he's crying and he's like falling over and he's got cancer and shit
I was like, "Wait, I know people with cancer.
What the hell?"
I'm gonna cry.
I was at Chicken Pox.
I saw a click last day of third grade and my brother hit somebody's car next to us and
they freaked, like he opened the door and dinged it and then she came in and like started
crying.
I don't remember why, but she was like telling us it was like a show car and she like knew
like yeah and you tried to rewind her yeah I wish I had the remote to rewind that
damn story if you had the click remote what would you do in your life I would
fucking rewind time so that I could go back in time and save be lack from
getting hit by that stray bullet I would low-key change the channel to Fox and
just watch the Simpsons cuz I get to be in their world and they would might think
I'm pretty cool since I look different from them they might like me or they
might you know sacrifice me or something yeah different I see if I had the click
remote I would rewind time all the way back so that I go watch the first
episode of SNL live a hundred percent cuz I'm such a comedy fan that's what I
would have done and then I would have fast-forwarded and been like I've seen
it I saw it live I saw it live I saw the Muppet show I saw the Coosbane sketch
I probably would fast-forward you guys a lot yeah really yeah I just skip around
a little bit just see who dies first I would press if I had the click remote I
would press the open disk tray button just to see what happens it's in the
middle of the ocean just like yeah dude it's a giant DVD that would be so cool
It's like the biggest DVD and it just says like something jackass to you
Something I was obsessed with like a few weeks ago
It's just imagining that like like archaeologists like just find like an a thousand year old DVD
They find out that like cavemen like had DVDs back then they just didn't have like DVD players
But that would be even cooler if it was like a giant did they like we're digging in a cave and they like unearthed
It's like a huge like a hundred foot DVD. Yeah
They find like a caveman stand-up DVD called a no-collar comedy tour
And he holds a rock in his hand
Yeah, yeah, there's like there's like a Gallagher type guy who's trying to smash a rock with another
Well, yeah, I mean you guys heard what happened at Louis BC, right
*laughter*
Yeah, he accidentally dropped his loincloth.
Oh...
Yeah...
Oh my god, man.
Naaaaaah!
No, that didn't happen back then.
There were no DVDs in caveman times.
No, that's nasty.
You don't even know what you're talking about, man.
Oh my god. Number 10, I love you.
Whoa.
Damn, that's some true shit.
I mean, yeah, I mean, and that honestly just takes it back in full circle to, you know,
B-Lack's wife.
Yeah, true. B-Lack did have that adult wife. He was mad problematic. He had an adult wife and
shit. It was just like, what are you doing, bro? And a lot of people were trying to like
cancel him and shit. And it's like, I get it, but like, listen to his music first.
when he got famous and then he like left her for Mila Kunis. Yeah that was like entirely
fucked up dude. Yeah. And she's still out there and she like still like has him in her heart and
she's still posting pictures of him on Instagram every day. She actually wears it. It kind of
looks like it's her son or something. Yeah she actually wears a fragment of his skull around
her neck on a chain. She actually like had his blood turned into perfume so she could wear it.
Yeah.
I mean, talk about poetic, you know, not justice necessarily, but it's just a poetic thing that
he was kind of turned into perfume after his death.
A hundred percent, dude.
Right.
Yeah.
Number 11, LOL. Admit it.
Who actually laughs every time they send LOL? Me.
I do, yeah.
Yeah.
Me too.
I go, "So what?"
I like to laugh, okay? I put a smile on my face because somebody sent me a very funny photo.
Yeah.
Is that so fucking... I'm not lying, dude.
Also, I dare you to prove it.
Yeah.
Um, number 12, I understand.
Number 13, it's no problem.
Number 19, I don't have a crush.
Whoa.
Number 22 is a bit of a turn.
Animals were humanely slaughtered to become my burger.
Yes, ma'am.
And the only comment is, "Yes, ma'am, I did my homework."
Um, number 29, I finished all of my homework.
so true number 27 hold on number 27 is I am part Native American number 35 is no
homo yeah they're usually being so homo when they say that shit yeah this tastes
good number 47 Columbus discovered America
Shit.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Number 49, God exists.
Come on, man.
Holy fuck.
Are you serious?
That's so crazy.
Someone says, "It was science that created us, not God or any religious figure."
Yeah, true.
It was science.
It was Ya-cube.
That's what they mean.
You can't prove God isn't real.
You'll know when you die.
True.
That's facts, Kenny Williams.
Number 50, I can't hear you.
Yeah.
when people just say that when I'm talking to them.
What?
Excuse me, I can't hear you.
I can't hear you, Caleb.
Number 52, the Easter Bunny is real.
That's like one of the main lies that this white supremacist society has been built upon
actually, Loki.
True, yeah.
Facts.
Easter Bunny is real.
It's like, can we just at least stop spreading, I don't know, misinformation?
Yeah, I hate misinformation.
You know?
Oh God, I hate it so much.
And the number 54, I mean, you can't make this up.
My dog ate my homework.
- So true.
- Yeah. - So true.
- I never had that excuse. - So true, but that's false.
- What was your go-to excuse if you didn't have a homework?
I could never come up with a good one, so I just--
- Yeah, I didn't tell you.
You just don't do, yeah, I just say I didn't do it.
- Yeah, I'm just stupid. - Yeah, I hate you.
Yeah, I'm dumb.
- I didn't want to do it.
I'm too gifted.
- Yeah, sorry, I-- - I'm too smart that this,
it's like pain to bring my brain down to this level.
It hurts me to do that.
Pardon me, I was actually spending that time creating a theory, so maybe I'm an idiot now.
Trying to pull up the like, yeah, it's actually, I'm way too smart for this, but you see,
I started writing my name with the top of the paper and spelled it wrong and gave up.
Yeah.
Just build a beelag.
All right, yeah, I mean, Ghoststream, Beelag, the story of my tears.
Yeah, yeah.
As a posthumous release.
Joe Strain, yeah, B-Lag, My Thoughts Are Knives, My Heart Is a Cold Sweater.
Playing on the Playground at Recess.
The Beast from the East.
Sweeter Than Candy, Softer Than a Fry.
Night of the Living Dummy.
Prince of the Playground.
Yeah, Attack of the Egg Monsters from Mars was a Sugar Plum Fairy dream.
Yeah, that was insane. Best Buy Commercial, that's like an amazing
album yeah camp camp jelly jam was good uh calling all creeps you know um yeah the concept album
uh uh fucked up at the school um i mean and his cover of every rose has its thorn
it's so gorgeous he did have a low-key great singing voice all right bye everybody