You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- [Woman] Welcome to the podcast.
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(thunder)
- Hola.
- What's up?
- Yeah, hola.
- Hola.
We're going with hola today.
Oh, are you looking down at your Duolingo?
Is that what you're gonna do?
- No, I actually don't do Duolingo.
I'm doing immersive learning for Spanish right now.
- You're doing immersive learning?
What do you, yeah.
- What does that mean?
- So here, so just ask me.
- That's when you break into a person's house
you listen to them. You sit there for a little bit. Yeah, well you talk to them back. Yeah.
Just ask them to change the TV and stuff. So ask me, ask me what app I'm about to open
on my phone. Just ask me. Duolingo. Are you opening Duolingo? No, just ask me what app.
What app? Clima. What is it? Clima. Clima. Clima. Clima. What is Clima? No. Clima. Okay,
- Climb on these hills. - Okay, fine.
You know what, I'll open up Notas.
- Notas?
- Yeah, or photos.
- Oh, I see.
- It's called immersion learning, okay?
- Oh, so you're putting your whole phone in Spanish.
- My whole shit's in Spanish right now, dude.
If I wanna change the configuracion, I might have to.
If I want to open Camara, is that Camara?
(laughing)
If I need to know what time it is,
Perhaps I'll open Reloj.
Reloj.
Reloj?
Oh.
Perhaps if I'm hungry I will go to 7-Eleven.
I don't think it changed that one.
I think that one stayed.
Siete.
Siete-Eleven.
Onze.
Siete.
Siete-Onze.
I don't speak Spanish.
Onze.
ABCD.
AFJ.
HITKLM.
Perhaps I will open Yara.
Yara.
- Yo, band.
- Yaraj band and make a reggaeton song.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- I mean, I am liable to, now that I've been fully immersed.
- It's true, you could.
- God damn, I'm so yo immersed-o'd.
- Yeah.
- I got, hold on, I gotta.
- What?
You gotta change shirts again?
- Yeah, I gotta change my, I'm in front of my AC
and I was wearing this, I put a crop top on as a joke.
- Yeah, big joke.
- Yeah, it was just for me, really.
I'm the only one in the room
and you can't even see it on the camera.
- You got up and showed it to us,
and I gotta say, you should be wearing one, dude.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, dude, here's what you should do.
Once you start skating again, grab your skateboard.
Actually, start riding a penny board,
and head on down.
- Yeah, ride a penny board, wear a crop top,
wear short shorts, wear tiny little shoes
that don't fit on your feet,
just wear a bunch of clothes that are too small for you.
- I was gonna make a joke about how--
- It looks like you were a gnome
and you got struck by lightning and grew three feet.
I was gonna make a joke about how I shouldn't wear this, but now you guys are telling me
I should.
Dude, apparently all these girls want you to wear short shorts.
The other day I walked outside in a bathing suit.
I was wearing a bathing suit because it was hot and it's a very short bathing suit and
I was like, "Oh fuck, I want an energy drink."
So I walked down the street to the deli to grab one and I made it about 30 feet before
an old Dominican dude called me the F-slur.
Yeah?
Yep, just instantly.
And I was like, "Yeah man, I can't be mad at you.
I shouldn't be wearing this.
I look ridiculous."
i don't think i just want to know what's like an hour and a half to say that
that's true to the copies are well he's wearing his head for the city as a
shortcut
the head for the court now that but now you know he's going through the shirt
but you are in a pickle he was just talking at it for a second turn to
figure out what happened i guess that the
yet to do
there you go
okay i can't hear
what they're saying i hope
patrick stupid things
patrick stone
I hope they're being nice about me.
Nice hat, dumbass. Stupid ass bitch. Fuck you.
Green shirt, what are you? Grass?
Yeah, what are you? A bunch of grass?
What do you think you are? An army man?
Yeah, are you a football field, you grass ass, green ass bitch?
You fucker, what's up? Hey Pat, love you bud.
[Laughter]
I don't know what he said.
I just was saying how nice you looked.
We were admiring the different colors you were wearing.
Yeah, I really like your different, you know.
Yeah, we were worshipping you.
You dress like Skittles today.
I'm not I'm wearing a blue hat and a green shirt. Yeah, it's not skittles. Is there a blue skittle?
You know what? I don't and is there a green? I mean skittle
Anyway, the thing about the though, you know, the men's short shorts thing like the five inch inseam like to you guys
That's basketball shorts, but to me that's like a speedo. You know, I'm yeah, I that I can't do that
I'm sorry, like it just like that work. Not possible. That's about that's about four inches from my cock just slipping out
Yeah, exactly dude. That's dangerous. You know, if somebody rolled up my shorts four inches without
asking me, the tip of my penis might just show a little tiny bit. It's true. So I got to be very
careful with an inseam that small. I got these, I think my legs are pretty short. I think I can go
about wearing those. You what? I can go about wearing those. My legs are short. I got short
legs you have five inch legs I do I got five inch legs so I think that the the
shorts would just kind of look like pants kind of like baggy yeah they'll
be like that's why they call them Patagonia baggies just cuz they look
like JNCOs on you mm-hmm Pat's gonia
dude we should you know what this summer everybody should be wearing groin old
bags I have to say that's true that's the look no me gusta no me gusta you don't
like a groin bag no me gusta te llamo te llamo dinner and lunch and breakfast
Yeah, I am Caleb.
And I like breakfast and dinner.
You are a fucking bitch.
No, you are a fucking bastard.
No.
Yes.
You are a big...
No, no, no, no!
Big bitch.
No, you are a...
I wish I could understand what you guys are saying.
It sounds like a really friendly conversation.
I wish I could get in on this.
I wish I knew what you were saying.
No.
You're...
Tu eres azul.
Tu eres azul y blanco.
Yo soy azul.
De a partir de a batall.
(laughing)
(singing in foreign language)
That's a beautiful song, dude.
Yeah, oh man, maybe that should be our goal.
That's a reggaeton song.
That, when you translate into Spanish,
that reveals the true meaning,
'cause they'll start going,
(singing in foreign language)
and you're like, oh, it did say
he's in need of a guy in there,
'cause you hear hombre, you know?
Also, for all we know,
(singing in foreign language)
could be Spanish for something.
Yeah, I think Dabba Dee Dabba Die is actually, uh, 'cause where are the, where is Eiffel 65 from?
They were from, uh...
I'm gonna say Germany.
Eiffel, so that's Paris.
Oh, it could be Paris.
Well, they could be Belgian, those fucking freaks.
Uh...
65 could be, um, America, the 65th country.
Eiffel 65 is an Italian music group, so I think Dabba Dee Dabba Die is probably just Italian.
What do you think it's Italian for?
Uh, pizza pie.
I don't think so.
Yeah?
Nope.
It's Italian for pizza and spaghetti and cannolis.
No, you are... we don't speak Italian.
You are white.
No.
You are big, white, whore.
No, I am pink.
No debate there, dude.
I think we should start moving to the Latin market.
market. It seems to be growing year after year. We're losing out on money. I'm sorry, pesos.
And every year we're losing out on more and more pesos. So I think that we need to start
changing our content to kind of, I don't know, to appeal to a different audience.
We could do what The Office did. Start kind of a remake, you know?
Oh, yes!
We could do a Spanish remake for the podcast.
That's such a good idea.
Who, okay, who do we want in our Mexican remake?
Salma Hayek.
Uh huh.
Who do we put?
Cameron.
Uh, I will play myself.
No, no you won't.
And Pablo Sobre La Lista.
Yo hablamos espanol.
That's what we'll call it.
It's Pablo Sobre La Lista.
Uh huh.
No.
Who plays Patrick though?
Dolph Lundgren.
I don't think he...
I think Dolph Lundgren will learn Spanish and play Patrick.
I think he's Obama's Espanola.
I do look a lot like him in most ways.
Yeah, well it's like partly like the iron jaw and the height.
I would say those are the two main kind of factors you guys have in common.
Yeah, that's true.
But why stop at Latin America also?
Right, we could get German...
We could get a German thing going.
Yeah, German...
Uh-huh.
Uh, Australian.
Podcast Auf...
Listen.
I mean, why not just do just one for every country?
And then we just hit everything, you know?
- That's a pretty good idea too.
- Yeah, I guess the big thing here would be
we don't have any money.
- Right, yeah, we're completely poor
and we're living in the street right now.
- Okay, so it's podcast Uber Liste.
- Ooh!
- Podcast Uber Liste.
- That's pretty cool, yeah.
- I haven't taken, my German sucks so bad.
My German is so rusty. It used to be so good though.
I used to be speaking perfect German all the time.
Ich sammle Briefmarken.
What's that mean?
I collect stamps.
Why'd you learn that?
I don't remember.
Does German have its own...
We had to write a thing on the board every day.
We had to write a sentence every day.
And I would write the same thing every day.
I would write, "Ich laufe Skateboard."
I collect stamps every day
Mm-hmm, and I didn't learn any other fucking German. I could have used that to like learn other German phrases, but no
Right like you could have said like my name is stamps or like yeah, my favorite color is skateboard me me
I'm okay on it
Yeah, does German have its own version of like how in Spanish class you just learn like this like it has its own version of?
me amo
See you know
It's ish heiser
Shice yeah, you shite suffice. I gotta suffice a
You should I studied French in high school. Yeah, really go that's that's nothing that's useless that nobody speak. Hey, that makes sense
Why oh no reason because I'm cultured my knowledge something like that. Yeah, my naman is to slip slim shady
Is that on the that was one of the assignments?
You have to translate all of the real sub shady. Uh-huh, I'd be good. Yeah, I took Latin in high school
yeah, I was kind of a thinker kind of a philosopher kind of a
Latin is Latin is the slacker language because you'll never have to speak to another person in it besides the teacher
That is you there's no way that somebody can tell you don't I I do remember in high school being like mom
"Mom, why the fuck am I taking Latin?
"Why do I have to take Latin?"
She was like, "What if you wanna become a doctor?"
- Oh, what?
- I was like, "What?"
- Yeah, you're gonna become a doctor.
- What is that?
Doctors don't use Latin all the time.
- Right. - Yeah.
- Well, I mean, if they say the Hippocratic Oath,
they probably have to learn Latin.
- Hippocratic, it's not like you're Miranda rights.
You don't have to read it in Latin
every time you're about to operate on somebody.
- Why are these fucking guys taking a bunch of oaths
to be a bunch of hypocrites?
That's the thing that pisses me off the most.
- That's a good point.
- Yeah, let's say hypocritical.
- If you're gonna be a hypocrite.
- I can do surgery on you, but you can't do it on me.
Tee hee, tee hee.
- I mean, that's true about doctors too.
It's one of the fucked up things.
- Yeah, they're all hypocrites.
- About the industry.
Yeah, is you can't do surgery on them.
- Yeah.
I'm looking, I'm trying to local, I'm trying to,
I just started throwing lines from My Name Is
to Google Translate.
- Yeah.
- The first line of the song,
"Hi kids, do you like violence?"
so german that the hello can the master default
i'm not being there
how hello can there is not sound good
no no no i don't know how i i i i i can't determine a minute
jim and i would have been thrown in jail this immediately yeah i mean i think
that's a good that's all i'd be happy to see the movie m
no i haven't even just know it's about a german to them in a m
yeah actually you know what it could be about eminem
could be short
yet at the end is short for him and watch it
what it's fucked somebody told that the alex told me about it
so you know what
and is that the is that fritz lang yeah fritz lang uh...
uh... with the serial killer praise on children
no
there you may know
yeah
I need to get more into world cinema.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Dude, I watched it.
Let me tell you, it is, it's liberating.
It's so beautiful to see other people's movies.
I watched...
I don't understand it all.
I watched Come and See on Sunday and I got, that took me out, dude.
I got so depressed.
You watched Come and Pee in the Toilet.
I wish, I wish I watched that instead.
I wish I watched the video...
You watched it swirl around and you tie-dyed your shirt in it.
I wish I did.
I wish I did that movie very hard watch
Not for me. It's pretty easy. Yeah, I I watch I laugh
You can't say that you can't say that with your your head
You can't say that with you didn't finish the movie because you were too upset that the Nazis were being shown as evil
I want no I should not laugh like Santa Claus talking about Patrick you laugh you laugh at all the
Atrocities Patrick Pat. No, I laugh at that little kids funny face
turn it off before the scene where they they shoot at Hitler a bunch of times
the end of the movie basically Hitler's in this giant movie theater and then the
kid and then the kid waves it to everybody in the town he's like come and
see Hitler's in a giant man he's destroying the entire town it's so cool
yeah the kids powers activate and he starts swinging up like I wish the green
Goblin's there too played by Willem Dafoe yeah and and that kid uses special power
of being really dirty all the time to destroy Mecca Hitler I wish I'd finished
the movie then well that's the part that's what I'm saying it's a funny
movie you laugh it in a jolly Santa Claus way in the end yeah and everything works
out and in the end Hitler Hitler decides to be good like the Grinch his heart
grows three sizes yeah and then there's a post-credit scene where Thanos calls
Hitler and it's like oh this could be something big what up yeah he's like
come work for me I would hate it if those if those two linked up I would
hate it so much we should make a movie called come and see and it's about me
and I got a really huge big nice new TV yeah I'm trying to get a little over
see my TV come see yeah hey come see my 60-inch come and see yeah come at the
end it's all of us staring into the camera like oh yeah come and see this I
got Dolby I got Dolby 7.1 I gotta look at this I got a receiver yeah it's us we're
trying we're walking over to Caleb's house to see the TV but we're like
waist-deep in mud and there's all these people around us and there's bombs in
this guy and it's like man I just want to see my friends I just want to come and
see that TV god damn it dude I hear it's got 3d he's got a 3d TV and I want to
come and see the 3D TV and he's got a ps3 and he's got Batman Arkham City and I
want to come and see Arkham City on a 3d TV ps3 3ds 3 3d TV on an Xbox 360 no
there's only on ps3 that they had the 3d he and I can watch for free he he he
alright we should start writing this movie okay intro intro interior interior
Caleb's apartment. Two Best Buy delivery men, two Best Buy Geek Squad delivery men deliver a
Samsung 4k 3d extra sharp, a Shang Tsung from Mortal Kombat.
Okay yeah a Shang Tsung 4k 3d current TV. Yeah this is a movie for geeks. And places it on the
the TV stand in his apartment. Cut to Caleb opening up his phone. Exterior
Belarus. Yeah exterior Belarus. Cameron and Patrick get a phone call. Cameron and Patrick dig up a
gun from the sand. And get a phone call on the gun. They answer it by pressing down on
the trigger. And Caleb picks up. And a big antenna comes out of the barrel. Yeah they
say guten morgen Caleb says hola hola hola me amo yo soy Caleb te amo
giant TVO come and see it yeah and they say je m'appelle Cameron mm-hmm and
Patrick and Patrick says I collect stamps and then you guys and then he oh
wait what's that in the sky is that a hot air balloon oh I believe it is and
who's driving it, Jackie Chan,
and you guys have to go around the world in 80 days
to come and see my TV.
And you have to do all the Jackie Chan movies
between here and the end of the world.
So you have to do Drunken Master,
you have to do Rush Hour,
you have to do--
- We have to do the cartoon.
- You have to Shanghai Noon once you get to California.
And then everybody meets at my house,
you two, Jackie Chan,
- Steve Coogan, Owen Wilson.
all those guys from those Jackie Chan movies.
- Yeah, Big Ben is there.
- The Medallion from The Medallion is there.
- Yeah, Chris Tucker is there.
You gotta do Rush Hour.
- There are some other martial arts stars.
Jean-Claude Van Damme is there.
- Jet Li is there.
- Bruce Lee is there, Jet Li is there.
- Brandon Lee is there.
- Brandon Lee is there, and he's still dead.
I mean, he's there.
- It's a different guy named Brandon Lee.
- It's a different guy named Brandon Lee,
but he's also dead.
- Yeah, he's still--
- He died the same way.
but he looks different.
(laughing)
So it's not disrespectful.
- And then here's the twist of the movie, right?
You guys get into my house,
I have a giant L-shaped couch that I got from Ikea.
- And there's not enough room.
- No, there's plenty of room.
I say, "You guys ready to watch the movie?"
You say, "Yeah."
I press play, the movie starts over again.
It's an endless loop.
- Okay, yeah, but it's on the screen this time.
- But it slowly pans into the screen
and then the movie starts again.
I mean tell me there's ever been a more genius movie than that and then plus
this becomes world cinema because we've spoken so many different languages plus
Jackie Chan is there. And get this too the DVD of the movie looks like a
donut like the Simpsons movie yeah but it's a different color donut it's a
different color donut it's purple instead of pink it's purple instead of
pink and it's got jelly beans on it it's like the Easter it's got jelly donuts
Easter donut if I like Jackie Chan movies am I a world cinema fan?
Yes you are. Really? That's yeah. That's fucking sick dude.
I just get away with saying like yeah I love world cinema. I love cinema nouveau
and then I'm a Jackie Chan fan. See I don't even know what that means. I think I've
heard that before. Cinema nouveau. Isn't a nouveau that thing women put in their hole?
That's French. Okay then I love it. You love new cinema?
I'm a cinema new cinema fan. Yeah. Cinema nouveau
Cinema, new line cinema.
New line cinema fan.
(speaking in foreign language)
Are you doing French?
Yeah.
That's how you speak French.
French I thought you were doing Spanish for some reason I think I put your finger
in your ass while you were talking that is how you speak French those you just
you need to know just a few for you need to know the phrases that are how do you
say and like something and what and then you got that and go like in in the
middle of it it's a lot that's what I've learned by by trying to learn Spanish as
well when I talk to my phone is I have to go like "ee" and "eh" a lot.
Yeah it's like most languages have like a version of "um" that they use
way more than I say "um." Yeah yeah and French they say they go "euh"
"euh" "euh" "euh"
What a horrible language.
Why is that?
Can you guys explain why they're called the romance languages?
"Mackelpenis"
And also why do the romance countries have the highest population of pedophiles over any other countries?
I mean, I think you just said it right there, unfortunately
Yeah, the pedophiles are hopeless romantics always have
Can't say that on homeless
You see that we're on a video call yeah, we're on TV right now
This is being live streamed to millions of Americans. Yeah, whoever
There were you know back in the in the olden days
There were the people who'd like rolled around in a hog stable to do it
And they're the people who'd set a nice table, and you know you know unfortunately
Table work, but it's nothing romantic to me about France. I don't know I need to go
Romantic to me if I'm gonna make a statement. I don't give a shit about the Eiffel Tower
You fuck that thing dude. I've seen bigger shit. Yeah, they got the Empire State Building here
I mean like the Tower of Pisa, then we'll talk yeah
Tell you what's a tower a more impressive tower the Citadel from Half-Life
Uh-huh, yeah, why don't they just try to I mean make something that big I'd fuck dare you oh yeah
Make it make City 17 a real place, and then I'll go there. Yeah, you know stop pussyfooting around with all this
Why did they build it was an accident it was so it's like a magnet for snails
It's a big
It's a big magnet for snails. That's how they get all the snails to come to France for the escargot
So you just walk over and they just scrape them off the side like barnacles. Yeah. Yeah, it's like a lightning rod kind of
Well, what I did now has to be struck by lightning pretty often, right? I think it was
Very lucky. Yeah
There's no protective measures if it does so they were just across their fingers and it's lasted this long
Man, it would be funny if they only had the Eiffel Tower in France
It's just so that it like it's just the world's biggest lightning rod
That's it. It looks you know what it looks I'm gonna say it
This is gonna offend a lot of our French listeners. It looks unfinished finish that damn thing
It looks like scaffolding. What's wrong put a damn wall on this thing. What god damn put some money
How do you go to the bathroom there if you work there?
Right!
Everyone's gonna see!
Yeah, what if your office is up there?
Yeah, too many holes in it.
Exactly.
Hey, hey!
Why don't you take your lunch break?
Hey, Eiffel, here's a fucking novel idea.
What if it gets cold?
Uh-huh.
Fucking dumbass stupid French guy.
And look, there's like a huge, there's a huge, it's shaped like an A, you know?
It's like there's a huge gap, you know what you could put-
Finish the word!
Yeah, you know what you could put inside of that A, that tower? You could put a big hammock.
I just had an idea for art. I just had an idea for art.
Are they armresters?
Yeah, I mean we've been basically getting them in the art game recently.
Eiffel Tower, Eiffel Tower.
Yep.
Circle around it.
Okay.
Because it's shaped like an A. Circle around an A.
Wow.
Anarchy.
Whoa.
How about this? Eiffel Tower, Eiffel Tower, big ol' S.
As.
Spelled it wrong.
Oh, okay, Eiffel Tower, two S's.
Yeah.
Ass.
There you go.
Yeah.
Well, there were two S's in France in 1940, but I don't want to bring that up.
Oh.
Those people are still healing, dude.
I know.
Come on.
That's my bad.
You fucker.
I think, well, I'm just saying, I think the French people would not like it if you put two S's...
If you brought two S's back to France.
Yeah.
It's honestly so beast to have never been invaded by anybody.
Mm-hmm.
We just, like, we just...
Except for aliens.
Well, maybe. But we've just never... we're like undefeated with like...
What's going on with that? There's aliens or some shit?
Like...
They're supposed to drop the intel. I mean, I'm like way up on all this stuff,
obviously, because I'm smart.
Yeah, I mean, like you and Tom DeLonge have been...
We've been working together, you know, but the thing is... the hard thing is you get me
and Tom DeLonge in a room. I just call him Tom. It's hard for us to be around each other
without making a song.
Yeah, without making a song, without making just like kind of like a funny little like...
a funny little song yeah yeah it's like you guys are getting together fuck my poop that was the
right recent one we did you know and that looks really good i i i remember you sending me over
the file for that the uh you sent me the the the what's it called the roots is that the
stems the stems you sent me the stems over for that because you guys wanted me to play bass on it
because yeah you know and and tom to launch but uh i also alien invasion so i've been we've been
trying to kind of stay focused and talk more about aliens and apparently they've
heard our songs. Really? Wow. Have they heard "Aliens Exist" by Blink-182?
I think that's their favorite song and the thing is they keep getting really
close to "Invading Earth" and then Tom DeLonge will drop one of these alien
classics and then they get it you know that because all radio waves just keep
going forever into the space so they keep getting them and being like ah
maybe we should hold off they seem to be pretty big fans of us. They could make a sequel to this song.
Yeah, yeah, so they recently got aliens exist and they decided to stop the invasion. Yeah. Mm-hmm
Something I mean the segue here something else paranormal that I wanted to share with you guys. Oh, yeah that I found online
This is just you know, just you know aliens
Ghosts pretty much the same thing I would say and many ways to me. What is this?
This is a little web page. I didn't really I just thought it was very funny
I just wanted to to share it on the on the podcast because I think we do
So this is a web page I found for about a haunted subway in Wisconsin in Dodgeville, Wisconsin.
1400 State Road 23.
If you want to visit it, they got a picture of it here.
Incredibly normal looking subway.
I mean, I can't lie.
It looks like a subway to me.
They even put that they have specific directions here on how to get to it.
So if you live in Wisconsin, from Highway 151 coming from the east, take a right onto Highway
18 into Dodgeville, take a right on Highway 23, North Beckett Street.
The subway will be on the left-hand side at the corner of Highway 23 and Highway YZ, King
Street.
Don't go to the other subway on the right-hand side.
Right, yeah.
That one's even worse.
So here's the background of this spot, okay?
Of this paranormal activity hotbed.
prior to being a subway restaurant a Harley-Davidson shop owned by a man named
Eugene Forbes sat at this location. So you can tell that's going to be very haunted already.
Here's the type of haunting that's going on. Here's the paranormal activity that's taking
place in this subway. Items being knocked off their shelves both on the main floor and
in the basement. Subway has a basement? That's already scary enough. That is one of the scariest
places you've ever been to. Also is this a subway where they have like a, there's like
book shelves everywhere.
There are books flying off.
What is there besides like chips?
Subway library.
Yeah.
Foul odors that seem to fill the restaurant with no known source.
Hey, I can tell you, I know where that source is.
It's the god damn food.
Yeah, it's all the food at Subway.
I'm gonna say quick,
quickly, uh, fuck Subway.
Why?
Horrible establishment.
You're a dumbass, dude. Subway rules.
It's fucking are you stupid dude subway fucking rocks.
Jimmy John's way better and their CEO kills elephants.
It's so cool.
Dude, Jimmy John's you get less sandwich though.
It's too skinny.
Yeah, but free smells.
Yeah, free.
Exactly.
They have free smells here.
See foul odors that seem to fill the restaurant with no known source.
It's true.
The apparition of a woman is seen standing behind the cash register.
See below.
That's scary.
Nothing is scarier than a woman behind the cash register.
It was the most terrifying thought I've ever had.
Door buzzers to let employees know that someone has entered the building go off without any
reason.
That's very scary.
One of the scariest things you can hear when you're working at Subway is "Ding dong!"
Yeah, a guy just walked in.
A customer coming in.
And they're like, "Who was that?
What is that?"
He's like, "Guys, I'm...
Who is this?
Show yourself!"
You smell!
You smell for no reason!
I guess I'll just leave.
Employees hear their name called when nobody is there.
I mean, whatever.
Now this is this last bullet point.
This is the one that made me decide to share this with you guys.
This is making me laugh a lot when I found this.
Employees preparing sandwiches have turned their backs only for a moment, only to notice
that their sandwiches have already been cut for them.
Seems to me less like a haunting, more like a Casper situation.
who's a bit friendly. Yeah, a ghost that cuts sandwiches for people. Yeah, dude. Saving
so many seconds. Yeah. Why is it haunted? Why, this is a whole story about the Harley Davidson
store that used to be there and then, here we go. Subway employees, oh what is it? Both
Eugene and Shirley were killed in the crash as was Pindell and his two passengers, also
young men in their early 20s. Alan Forbes, Eugene's son, inherited the Harley Davidson
shop and eventually sold the land to the Subway franchise. The years passed by and all seemed
calm. Then, in 2000, things changed. Subway employees began reporting strange occurrences
taking place in the restaurant. Items were being knocked off their shelves, employees
hearing their name called when no one else was around. Even more disturbing was when
some employees began seeing the vision of a woman standing behind the cash register.
Described as being about 50 years old, skinny, and wearing a dress, the woman is said to
give a dirty look at the employees and when confronted, she simply disappears before the
the
I think this might be a Karen.
Dude, I hate Karens so much.
You guys want to see my impression of a Karen?
Yeah.
Alright, ready?
Watch this.
I'm ready.
Hey, yeah, I'll have a million dollars for free.
What?
You can't order that.
Oh my god.
Oh, I can't order that?
Well then I'm going to sexually assault you.
I'm a Karen, by the way.
I don't know about that one.
That's not what they say.
I don't think Karens say that.
I think Karens do.
I think you're going to say...
They say I'm going to speak to the manager.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I'm gonna, okay, all right, let me try again.
If you don't give me a million dollars,
I'm gonna sexually assault your manager.
- No. - No, stop saying that.
- What is that? - Don't say that.
- Stop saying that. - That's what Karens do.
- No, they don't.
- No, you know that they don't say that.
Stop saying that.
- I'm gonna--
- Don't, no.
- Speak. - Speak.
- Say, say it with me. - I'm gonna speak to the manager.
I'm gonna use my hands and I'm gonna use my love language to speak to your manager.
No! Don't say that!
Oh, so somebody's on the Karen side.
I'm not on the Karen-
So then why are you defending the Karen that I invented?
Don't say you're gonna sexually assault somebody on the podcast.
I'm not! The Karen is!
What the fuck?
You guys are so pro-Karen it's disgusting me right now.
Just don't say that.
You fucker.
Uh, top ten ways to tell someone is a psycho.
I got one way.
What way?
They fucking ruin the podcast by saying shit like that.
How is that, that was, everybody thought that was helpful, informative, maybe even a little
bit funny.
God damn it, this fucking show.
Yeah, 150th episode and you, this is what you do.
I'm about to go Karen on you guys.
You go Karen on us every day.
Now it means something else.
Why does it mean something else?
Because you made it mean something else.
No. You don't know what you're talking about.
You're being a Karen right now and I'm scared of you.
Ways to tell if someone is a psycho from the top 10s by Preach and Preach.
Ever notice someone do really weird things?
Ever notice someone being crazy?
Let us know what to look out for.
I have to say I don't think I've ever noticed that.
Yeah.
Personally.
Number one.
They keep posting nasty comment about artists and their fans.
Okay, you know what?
Psycho move, dude.
Definitely a psycho move.
That is the number one psycho move.
I think that's on the, I think that's in the DSM.
I do, yeah.
I mean, when I see people talking shit on my stand list, I send it to my besties.
And they take them down.
And besties take them down, dude.
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
Who is on your stan list?
My stan list?
Let me think.
Number one, mom and dad.
Jimmy Fallon.
Number two, Fallon.
Number three, God and his son, Jesus.
Walter White.
I mean, this guy's got to be stan-able
more than anybody else.
Jake Paul, not
Logan Paul.
Logan Paul is not stan-able.
Not stan-able, no.
I'll say it, I stand Malcolm X.
Okay.
Yep, me too.
He's my, he's, I stand that guy.
Yep.
Ummmm.
I guess I stand Martin Luther King.
Robert Pattinson.
Whoever invented chocolate.
Yeah.
Not sure who, but that guy, gotta stand him.
I think it was Montezuma.
Mr. Jif.
Montezuma.
From the Adabutter Company.
Yep.
Bruce, Bruce Lee.
Bruce Bruce Lee as well as Lee the whole time the whole as well as Rosa Parks
come and see yeah yep John Bon Jovi Keith Richards uh-huh JFK
Dwayne Wade. That's a good that's a good Stan to have. Roger Moore. JFK Jr. he's still
doing good work. I used to Stan Chester Bennington but he messed that up. Yeah he
himself yeah Pete fumbled John John Stewart double-oh-seven yeah Mel Gibson
no Mel Gibson I wouldn't stand Mel Gibson well that's a bad Stan you can't tell me
if it's a bit I'm gonna you know I'm gonna report you to my besties right now
and you're not gonna like what they do to you all right seems like you're a
a psycho.
You're the psycho, you left hating comments on my stand.
I did not.
That's true, yeah.
No, somebody says on this item, "Always jellious with every person."
True.
I hate when people get jellious of me.
Number two, "They keep starting all kind of worst lists and cannot stop hating."
Yep.
YoshiDude says, "I do this, but I'm not a psycho."
Sounds like you might be a psycho, YoshiDude.
This is one of the ways to tell, so I think you are so psychopathic that you're actually
a stupid idiot.
Uh-huh, yeah, this is normal to you because you're a psycho.
There's a number of, there's another comment on this list here, it says, "Their eyes are
full of hatred."
I mean, that's also, that's a pretty easy way to tell if somebody's a psycho.
If someone's eyes are full of hatred.
Iry eyes full of hatred.
Yeah.
That's got to be like a clear telltale sign.
They have like Sith eyes with yellow pupils.
Yeah, if their face is veiny and white and they have what look like horns popping out of the front of their head
Oh, yes, they could be a psycho. Yeah, and also when you go to inspect their character model, they're there
All the way in the red and they have a red smoke behind them. Yeah. Yeah, it's like there
yeah, you know that that thing the like Japanese thing where like if you're if they
They had this called like senpaku eyes
I
to
of a psychopathic killer these eyes want to gain power of you. Senpaku eyes. They're just
high hooded eyelids. Yeah here. No it's about like the what the your iris like where your how much
space there is around your iris like what directions. Look at this picture I found uh that's the
first result when you look up Senpaku eyes. It's a picture of so it's just describing Senpaku eyes
then it has six pictures and the six people on it the first one left to right Charles Manson,
James Holmes, uh, the, the Heaven's Gate guy, Adam Lanza, Casey Anthony, and Jimmy Savile.
All right, I see Billie Eilish is on here too. I see AOC here as an example of someone with Senpaku eyes.
So Billie Eilish has Senpaku eyes, is that, so people are just like mad at her now? No,
No she's evil.
So she, okay.
Well, she did, I mean, surprise, surprise, she did say that she was the bad guy.
So it's like, why, why are you freaking out?
Exactly, if she would have said duh.
Which is rude, on top of being bad.
Oh my gosh, first she's evil, then she's rude?
It's like, can't this be funny?
Okay, if you're evil, that's one thing.
If you're evil and sarcastic, you're getting kicked out of school.
Number three, they don't understand great jokes, but laugh at silly things.
furniture shampoo and clocks someone says my family's Asian whenever the grown-ups
talk about random stuff about their lives they laugh so hard and they even
look at us kids like we're expected to know what's funny what are you guys even
laughing about anyway we don't get what's so funny about whatever you're
talking about. Why do you... why do you... why do you mention that you're Asian? I don't get that.
Here's another comment. I don't laugh when the rest of my family or friends
laugh but I laughed so hard I couldn't breathe when my mom put a black sock in
the white washing load and they all got annoyed when everything turned gray.
Makes me laugh even when I'm just thinking about it. That's a psycho. Yeah
that is a psycho. That's a dorky twisted psycho. This is totally me. I seem to not understand a joke
everyone is dying laughing over and yet I'm laughing to the point of crying when
I look at a microwave oven. The author of that comment is named Rock Fashionista.
Number four they start acting like Britney Spears. What like a slut? Hey. Like
a fucking slutty woman. Come on now. Here's a comment. She's an amazing woman.
start start to start to acting like Simon Cowell yep yep true
I mean I hated Britney Spears Simon Cowell when she was on that show he was
one of the biggest psychos on TV sure you want to talk about some Paco eyes I
think he has him now maybe didn't he ten years ago he's got him now dude
those fucking pictures of him now he's got so much he just doesn't look real
he looks like an animal yeah he does not look like a human anymore he looks like
Like
He does look really messed up.
People have been saying he looks like a GTA 5 NPC.
And that's yeah, for 100%.
Oh my god!
Wait, he was in an accident.
He was in an accident?
He had a back injury.
That should make your face look like that.
That makes Simon Cowell break his back falling off of an electric bike in California.
How do you...
He got caught in the spokes.
He was going around and around.
yeah no this guy's a fucked-up fucking fallout 4 character somebody just
deleted his lips he was one of the most handsome men in the world at one point I
mean he was up there for sure I mean for a British smashed his spine to pieces by
falling off an electric bike oh I get yeah he's old I get mine's already in
pieces can we can we hold vertebrae can we edit this out because I'm gonna try
out for American Idol in two weeks. Oh, I had no idea. Yeah, I don't know. I know he's not
a judge anymore, but he might still be like an executive producer or something. I feel
like just as your friend I should be able to like give you some advice or something. So
could you like show me what you're auditioning with? Yeah. What are you doing? Like a bridge
Bridge over troubled water
I'm gonna be honest with you, dog. You're going to Hollywood, dog.
Yeah?
Yeah, G.
You mean it?
I mean it, G.
No.
Number five, they keep insulting people.
I'm sorry. I'm still stuck on Simon Cowell falling off of an electric bike.
I found this article and it's...
The article is called "Simon Cowell did not fall off an e-bike"
and that's not my italy's there is a difference between a bike and a
motorcycle
and it's a whole article about how it he fell off his technically a book
recycle i was thinking maybe this is a kind of like like uh... fake paul
mccartney thing with a look at it and i have a suicide if he died so they were
there
are eight hundred and ninety comments arguing about whether it's a biker
motorcycle only shot website
and what's the difference
I'll stick with the new two-stroke dirt bikes. At least then I won't have to eat granola and wear my hair in a bun.
True.
True!
That's what happens when you have a spine injury.
Yeah.
The only thing you can take is granola.
As soon as you break your spine, the first thing you do, go out and buy a dang Prius.
Well, they put you on an all-crunchy diet.
Yeah.
Because it's easier to eat.
Right, it's all crunchy because your spine got crunchy.
Yeah.
LOL, not a motorcycle, not an e-bike. This is just a new iteration of the moped.
Oh yeah, good point.
Number five, they keep insulting people.
I'm gonna issue a psycho watch on one Jeffrey Ross Roastmaster General because this guy seems
to like insulting people more than almost anybody alive.
So if this is a psycho-
And he's the general.
He's also the general.
So if this is a psycho attribute, I think that he might be public psycho number one.
And he should be dishonorably discharged for being a psychopath.
I mean have you ever seen Doctor Strangelove?
You see what a psycho general can do?
Discharge Geoffrey Ross, replace him with Hannah Gadsby.
Or maybe just like if they don't want to do a whole thing of like discharging them they
could have like maybe the people close to him influence him into committing suicide
or something.
Might be a good idea.
I mean the CIA listens to this and I know that they'll take that to heart.
I mean and honestly it doesn't even have to be the CIA it just could be whoever.
I mean it could be like three guys.
He's also listening to it.
Maybe we can do it.
Or like maybe set up a situation where like you know, he, you're like for example maybe
you put him in a giant frying pan or something and he wants to get out of the frying pan
because his flesh is like sizzling and melting but like if he jumps out there's spikes underneath
so then technically he is killing himself and you're not liable for it because he's
the one who threw himself out of the frying pan.
Well what if it's like, it's a cast iron pan you put in the oven to roast him.
Yeah.
poetic isn't it? Uh-huh. Yeah. That's true. No judge will convict you for a poetic crime.
Yeah. Ah, I would convict you for this murder but its irony was too beautiful.
Yeah. It's ironic. It was too poignant. Yeah. And that judge, the Honorable Alanis Morissette.
I'm pleading guilty. I'm pleading guilty with a point. Yeah, with a moral. Yeah,
with a "Bah, but have I not created a new moral tale? One that you may, you may tell
to your children before bedtime? Yeah, a guy reading a bedtime story to a kid
and it's like, "And that's why you never put a man in a giant cast-iron pan and put him
in the oven." And it's thanks to Caleb Pitts that we have that moral today.
You know what, I'm a veritable brother Grimm. Yeah.
Number seven, the voices in your head communicate with the voices in yours.
You skipped number six. Oh.
Number six, they come up to you at scream in your face.
important yeah I believe you tried you tried to skip that because you do that
and you didn't want anyone to know you're no I don't come up and at scream
in your face you absolutely do I've come to the conclusion that almost anyone
could be defined as psycho and that's another comment from rock fashionista
rock fashionista has a point yeah moose for life 19 says um that's pretty crazy
yeah and imagine somebody coming up to your face and screaming um that's pretty
crazy in it yeah I don't want to I don't want to stick on this thing of like
maybe all comedians are psychos but maybe ever heard of a little guy named Bobcat
Goldthwait? Oh yeah. This is one of the loudest dudes who's ever lived. Okay. Yeah.
He's broken sound barriers and he's short as well. Yeah. And he uh he made a movie
about Bigfoot. He directed World's Greatest Dad. That's true he did World's Greatest Dad.
You know he made a... Which was about Bigfoot. I mean only a psycho could have come up with his Bigfoot.
only a psycho could have come up with the idea to make a found footage Bigfoot
movie but then not show Bigfoot at the end and show a naked old lady instead
yeah that is pretty diabolical yeah yeah only the craziest mind would make
Junie Cortez true Robin Williams child number seven the voices in their head
communicate with the voices in yours this seems to have come it this just
This seems to have more to do with like ESP or some kind of mental communication than being
a psychopath.
Yeah, maybe they thought it was psychic.
Also, this means that you both have voices in your head.
And here's the top comment here.
Don't judge us, but my friends and I do this a lot and I for sure am not giving them up
because I think it's cool and since some of my friends are boys, they have said that guys
I think are cute, they don't know that, actually have crushes on me.
One even said he had feelings for me.
Oops, got off track.
Wow. You got off track.
Yeah. I mean, you revealed the existence of telepathy.
Yeah. Maybe they're psycho and that's why they're saying that.
True. I also got the same experience since from 13 years old.
I have hundreds of voices in my head.
And as far as I'm concerned, they've never communicated with any real person before.
Rock fashionista. That's also from rock fashionista.
Number eight, they are having a conversation and no one and no cell phone is part of it.
Whoa. This is the truth because for psychopaths are
people who want the feeling of importance so they do this.
So they just have a conversation? Mm-hmm.
What if they're the Long Island medium? Oh my God.
Yeah, what if they're speaking to...
By the way, there can't be a group of more fucking annoying ghosts
than the ones on Long Island, dude.
I would rather fuck it...
Go anywhere else but Long Island if you're gonna be a medium.
That is a bad, bad move, dude.
You know how much, like, racist shit you're gonna hear?
You can't help where you're from.
And I think that, you know,
she was born with those powers.
And I think the people of Long Island,
maybe this could help them.
I don't think anything can help those poor souls. They should be put out of their misery.
If I was a medium, I would live in a zoo and I would walk around, I would talk to the animal ghosts.
Yeah, well that one's an easy one.
I'd make that, yeah, because I would go like...
Tell us, what is the monkey saying?
And he's going...
Yeah.
And then he says...
And then I would just be walking around, they would like...
You know, at first they'd be like, "Oh, there's that weird guy."
He's walking around going like...
And then it's like, "Oh, he's talking to the dead lion that died because it had to get
tranquil way too much and and do you want a banana right now somebody says you
would like a banana right now okay I walk around Dunstan Dunstan did you any of
you know what does it have you checked in yeah I'd walk I'd walk I'd walk up to a
like a family that it was that one of the you know and I'd be like and I'd be
like a spirit has a message for you and I'd stand there for a while and they'd
be like "well" and I'd be like "well I already said it was from the giraffe"
teehee! teehee! teehee!
and I'd run away and say teehee
I'd be a prank medium
Goddamn that medium!
I think that's the most important thing about being a medium is probably having fun
mm-hmm pranking
I mean you hear the cries of the dead all day it's like hey can you tell me like at least one or two
I'll tell you some jokes. Yeah, exactly. I would like to be the
The comedy store medium. Yeah, right where I'm in there and I'm like, hi, Richard Pryor saying he wants to have sex with a mannequin
I'd be a medium and I'd I'd be walking I'd be walking around that I'd accidentally walk through like
Like walk past like a skydiving class and just go
(laughing)
- It's over and over.
- Yeah.
Sorry, I'm picking up, I'm sorry,
I was picking up a voice.
- Yeah, I'm sorry, I was picking up the 10 people
who were here this morning.
(laughing)
- He's a bad instructor!
Don't go to his class!
Sorry, sorry, that was, ugh, that was,
I'm hearing John, I'm hearing John.
That's the funniest thing about the,
Just ruining every business, just walking into a restaurant and being like
"I WAS POISONED! I WAS POISONED BY THE CHEF!"
Yeah, just doing that in every store you go to.
"The security guard is evil! He killed me! I'm a ghost!"
"Unless they give the medium a gift card and then nothing happened, and it was all fine."
Yeah, I mean if you were like a famous medium, I'm sure you could just be like, "Oh, I'm
hearing that my appetizer is 50% off."
I'm hearing that from the ghost of the manager.
The medium says it's true.
What's the, oh fuck, wait, Gary Spivey.
Yeah, Gary Spivey is the-
Oh, the guy that everybody had as their profile picture in 2009.
Because he has that big white afro?
Yes.
Sylvia Brown Sylvia Brown was on the Montel Williams show all the time cool
growing they wouldn't my mom would watch that all the fucking time and I hated
Sylvia Brown I thought she a medium yeah she was a medium it's crock of shit yeah
such that her job you don't believe in mediums I believe in every medium but
Sylvia Brown Sylvia Brown I'm challenging I'm right now I'm doing a psychic attack
on you. I'm sending brainwaves, I'm sending you the souls of so many people.
If you don't think that she has some sort of defense mechanism, iron shield for psychic energy.
Oh my god, no! I'm being attacked by her ghost, she's been dead since 2013!
I can see it on your face right now.
It's flying around you.
Number 9, they bitch complain, and this is something that maybe Caleb would know a thing or two about.
They bitch, complain, cry, and cause a scene no matter where they are.
I don't think I know anything about that, 'cause I haven't cried in 15 years.
Are you complaining right now?
No, I'm just making an observation.
What are you whining about?
Oh, I'm not-- Oh, am I whining?
You're crying.
Oh, does it appear that I'm crying? I wasn't here--
I can hear it in your voice.
Oh, did you think I'm crying?
Okay.
I know a person whose daughter is studying with us.
One day, she complained to her parent that she is not happy with the class.
The parent was at a yoga class from where he started shouting.
He stated calling bad words and making a bad scene without even knowing...
even without knowing what the matter is.
Okay.
So just yelling and screaming seems to be a big part of the of the psycho's repertoire.
My husband is a psycho.
He loves to criticize, doesn't know how to enjoy life,
loves to take stress and pressure all time,
saddest, rude, has two personalities,
the world believe he is good, which in reality he isn't.
I went to a party and met this guy named Richard and he seemed nice, but he is a real pain
He has scared seven of my friends off. They don't talk to me. He is a stalker
He went up to my old job and threatened the people for my phone number and he is really crazy
I try to get right off him. I don't know go in town
I got a job far away and I need to do something about this. He scream and follow me. He shows up at night
He's psycho person. I don't try to talk or see him
Richard sounds really bad. Oh my god. He's scream and follow
You show up
That's horrifying dude. That is horrible. He's a stalker
Stocker number 10 they walk out the door naked
Yeah, well, that's pretty yeah, I hate that psycho Lana Rhodes. She is such a psycho. Okay, I definitely
Definitely wouldn't do that. That's from Yoshi, dude, Sylvia Brown and I have made up by the way, really? Oh, what does that entail?
Come on be honest with me play. Oh man. I can't say it on here
number a mo
number 11
They stare at you and smile. I
Do it especially creepily just to disturb the crap out of my friends or people spreading rumors of me
I hold scissors to accompany the psycho effect works awesomely
You know something is wrong is they give you that mischievous smile that says I'm up to something
Let's see here
Number 15 they start preaching about the giant flying spaghetti monster. Oh hell no that's facts. Yeah, I'm a psycho because of this
Oh hell no not the spaghetti number 16. They misunderestimate you
Number 20 they have chili in their shoes
That is a is psychotic every time they walk into a room the psycho shower scene music plays
That's a pretty that would be pretty pissed if I as a psycho they kept blowing my cover with that
Number 25 they become interested in death and the top comment is they are interested in death more than life and hence
They become psychos a psycho is a person who is very interested in the opposite face of reality
Number number 31 they live in a world of their own
Number 28 I can't tell the difference between the real world and my imaginary world
world rock rock rock actually has a mental number 28 their favorite movie is psycho and they
want to reenact it 34 have an attraction to preteens at the age of 38 they are determined
to have sex with every young woman they meet.
Number 35, they know what you are thinking.
Again there seems to be some kind of disconnect here.
Number 51, they joined the KKK.
And there's one comment from jasmine21064 that says, "Duh."
Number 48, continuing the thread, if someone is about 15+ years older than you and they
want to become close friends with you.
Total psycho dude. Something's going on.
Oh no, this is a bad one.
Number 66, they live in downtown New York, New York.
That's true.
Yeah. Yeah, there's tons of psychos down there.
Number 70, they like pony porn.
Number 54, they try to kill all the time.
Never a break for these psychos.
Happy death, sad death, death all the time.
Number 71, they laugh crazily.
So true.
Oh, even more proof.
There's a comment on it. I know one who laughs like
"Kia ha ha" in an evil voice.
Can you do that? Can you do that in a more
evil voice? "Kia ha ha!"
Number 55 is
"They cut themselves." And there's two comments.
One is, "I actually do this myself
for several and understandable reasons.
Some that people don't care about."
And then the comment under that is
"Girl in my class bites herself."
[laughter]
Number 56, they are obsessed with you and stalk you and the two comments say, "I happen to do this often" and then YoshiDude says, "I did this twice!"
Number 57, they think music is getting better. Here's a comment by Rock Fashionista, "I'm practically psycho and the only music I ever listen to besides rock and metal is 80's music."
Damn, that's so true.
They laugh crazily.
Number 59 they eat salami with marmalade. Yeah
That's a chart that's a charcuterie board, yeah, dude, that's how I'm so good you're telling me
Charcuterie is psycho. Hell no number 69. They're obsessed with serial killers only comment serial killers are 100% psychos
I'm not all of them. There has to be a serial killer who killed who did it for a good reason. Yeah Dexter. Oh
My fucking god. Mm-hmm. I think you just cracked the psycho code
Here's it. Here's what we should do. Honestly
psychos, we should get rid of the
Of it being like a social faux pas to be a psychopath and we should hire these people if Dexter is any indication
We should hire these people as police officers
Because they are so effective at stopping crime according to this TV show Dexter
That on Showtime that I think that we would actually see a much better and more effective police force
Yeah, and they probably would I mean it would be cool to maybe
We can make a TV show out of it - out of it's a really good point. There could be like a psycho
Division of every police priest. Yeah, where these are the guys that that when they're like, all right
We give up on everything else and we're just gonna try and kill this guy
think that already exists I thought of a now mm-hmm and we could make a TV show
about it and we could call it Hannibal maybe okay no cuz Hannibal is already a
guy we need we don't be called okay then Dexter Dexter is actually a really good
name for a show like this yeah extras laboratory cuz he's works in the crime
lab where he does psycho shit and his a character's name
Hannibal Lecter. Oh. Let's go with Dracula. Okay. Yeah. Dracula I think is a perfect name for a
psycho. What about Dracula Frankenstein? Could be. That'd be pretty... what about Dracula Frankenstein
the ghost? Okay. But he's just a guy. Officer Dracula Frankenstein the ghost. What's your name
and badge number? Officer Frankenstein Dracula the ghost badge number 666. Because they wouldn't be
be scared to give it away because they don't have any fear of repercussion.
Badge number 1031.
1999.
What if the K-9 unit has Officer Werewolf?
There's no such thing as werewolves.
Can we end the episode?
Yeah.
What?
No such thing as werewolves.
Bye.
I saw one.