you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
you're a crap monster
did you get it? did you get it? I know it goes fast
that wasn't as fast as I was uh... thinking
I went as fast as I could on the countdown I was going
I mean that was fast
yeah I mean I could hear you that I could hear you mouthing Mississippi in
between the numbers just the smack of his lips and his saliva yeah it was right
here what was recorded
yeah counting all the milliseconds very softly yeah I hate that yeah I do hate
when people say moist because it means that I'm always into myself by accident
again I hate when people say the n-word that's probably that's yeah that
definitely yeah there's a I would say there's like five to ten words that when
people say that my shoulders kind of go up.
You know?
Yeah.
And I can like picture it.
I can like picture it when they say it.
My shoulders don't go up like I'm curious or like I don't care.
They go up like I'm scared.
Yeah, yeah, like you're protecting your neck.
Right, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, my hair's stand on end because I'm trying to make myself appear larger.
Poop is another one of those.
Yeah, I hold my hands up in the air and make scary motions with them.
Yeah, I wear a windbreaker.
[laughter]
And I make it really windy too.
Start blowing into it.
I use a bear horn.
We're in a situation with a bear.
I don't remember, are you supposed to make yourself very small or very big?
And it's important for me to know.
Very big?
There's very few animals where you're supposed to make yourself very small.
[laughter]
See, I would go the other way.
the bear like doesn't think I exist I would like that I think that's a better
one right cuz like a bear I'm never gonna make myself bigger than a bear that's
right the reality I've looked at my body and I've thought about this and I said
you can be kind of loud and you can you can but I could I could become so small
that a bear might forget about me like there's like to eat berries and stuff
though that's right they have they have a taste and a knack for really small
things like honey and fruit and and little bees yeah yeah don't eat bees you
guys are very see fucking stupid no they don't eat why do they always show them in
cartoons next to bees then cuz they're trying to get honey do it's like what a
monkey is next to a banana yeah but it's a banana if a bear can get one B that's
unlimited honey that's true that's true yeah I guess well that's it no yeah I
guess why don't bears start like bears are smart right like they know how to
fish maybe raising a good point it is very cool to see the bear do the like
the ninja trick with the stick that yeah that all day that's a great one they
learned how to stand it seems the last like three years yeah they kind of have
hands they basically houses a little bit they know you have to go in a cave you
can't just sleep on the ground like which is what we were doing for like too long
so they're doing pretty well I would say we kind of copied them there we I think
maybe they also invented like laying around all day yeah true yeah I guess
they did life hack yeah but I just feel like they should they like I don't know
I I don't think I can make a noise loud enough that a bear would be scared of me
the
bear with my car but that like otherwise I'm trying to make myself how high
completely disappear um higher than you would think honestly all right I would
say you should if you jump high over and over again that's also a good way to add
some size do you have this have like like their brains like process images
really slowly so maybe I think it's that they only see me on the frames when I'm
really high yeah there's only have six frames per day like a time-lapse all
hibernating creatures have a time-lapse vision yeah yeah so much of their time
yeah they interpolate it so if you jump up really high it's gonna look like
you're like a snake type thing that's very oh that's actually that's somebody's
new bears they come with motion smoothing on though yeah and yeah I
guess you have to reach behind the bears head and flick the little switch behind
its ear yeah I mean that is what I would do if I got attacked by a bear is I
would just remove his teeth and his claws so that he's no longer yeah also I I
I would I would accidentally kill him during like emergency surgery probably
I would I know I would maybe I would make some parts of my body really big
But not all of them like I might make my hands really big and then I could pick up the bears throw it
I'd become I'd become a homunculus
To kill the bears that can be as tiny as a spaghetti
Or I guess like another way to do do it is like look like like bears like to fuck right sure everyone
Everyone knows that. Except panda bears. Panda bears notoriously don't want to fuck. They don't want to fuck really?
That's why yeah, I mean they you
People show videos of pandas fucking to pandas and then they change the channel. They say what else is on
They can change the channel? Wow
I feel like you just look like a really like
unfuckable bear, you know, because like a bear if you look like a really good-looking bear, it's gonna want to fuck you and if you
look like a
Like a bear that it would want to fight, you know
But if you're trying to if you do like a really bad job seducing it
It's not gonna like try to look like the bear that a bear thinks of when it doesn't want to come too quick. Exactly
Yeah, yeah, you try to look like their grandma bear
I might I might try to look like I might try to look like the devil because I think they might have an instinct about
That to kind of avoid
Or a demon they might they might see a demon and think that's you know
That's might be evil for that is exactly how like a matador came into being as a profession is like what if what if a?
Bull was scared of the Christian devil
Good show on our I
Guess that's true. Yeah, do they still do mad at bullfighting is that still legal?
I think so I think I don't know which one is which but people ride the bulls - still
There was a I saw a page something like like some week some guy holds the title for most gourd matador
That's sick dude. He has been gourd. Well. That's the thing about a matter about a
Bull is it like it's really just it does not gonna bite you you know
Like it's like it only has like the horns and like its head
I guess like it's not gonna like all the feet are what fuck you up like like bear fighting is like way cooler and more
dangerous to me the feet what a
Bull if a bull steps on you it's gonna break all your bones is it in stilettos. I can take
If it had stilettos that would be serious stepped on you would crack you up
It'd be you'd be like a glove his elk that'd be like you're trying to kill me with your damn feet pussy
Yeah, it would suck if a bull had like the mouth of a hippo cuz then it could write you and it can gore you
Yeah, maybe like high-heel shoes. Yeah, the arms of a gun could be dangerous, too
Yeah of a big-ass gun
Hippos scare me because anytime I see a video of a hippo,
they don't look real to me, like at all.
They look like the shark from like the Jaws ride at Universal.
They're like animatronic.
They do look animatronic.
They're like the Arnold Schwarzenegger of animals
because at any time they could be replaced with like a polyurethane version of themselves.
They're inhuman in a way.
Yeah.
And they love watermelons.
Oh, they love them.
And my head is about as big as a watermelon these days.
I think they just like to crunch. I think it's the watermelons. That's the other thing is you
watch those videos none of that's getting in their mouth. They just like squish it and it just
falls out and you're like of course you have to feed them like 50 of these because like
of the rind is actually going down their hole. They're like cookie monster.
Yeah yeah yeah. They eat exactly like cookie monster. Yeah yeah.
But they should do more, I don't know, I feel like we're past the bull thing.
Like, make it, like I think people, I think animals should be, we should be able to kill
any animal at any time for no reason.
You know what I mean?
I think you pretty much can.
No, but like, okay, so like my brother, like maybe I should say this, my brother will-
Don't say it, I don't want to have to edit it out.
No, no, it's not, he's not in trouble.
but my brother sometimes will like bet on like chicken fights that are happening in Mexico
and then watch them on Facebook Live. So, and like that to me is like fine. Like two chickens,
like if two chickens have a blood feud, who am I to get in the way?
Yeah, that's between them.
Yeah.
That's between the chickens. I think that we should get past this issue of like,
you know it being inhumane to do to do bullfights are like to wrestle
alligators or whatever
by i think they should be breeding new animals just for it
human combat
just just yet breed new animals that would be satisfying to best in combat
exactly like a xenomorph to a style thing that's but it's a little different
something something that like represents exactly something that is a young
negative on the world and the ecosystem just combine all the invasive species in
the world
and then yeah and keep them in like a like a really poorly secured area
somewhere
right like a city yeah yeah you know
I feel like that's a good idea yeah and some size enhancement
ooze could maybe be developed in here to them as well
yeah and they should be bred to have like a glowing red weak spot so that
yeah it's multiple health bars to you
he said it up they should you should have to defeat them in stages
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, we're like maybe charging up now now he has a shield at first
It's a bull and then mate perhaps it becomes a bull with a large head after you kill it
What this is what like the ancient Greeks do used to do all day. It's just
the scariest
They would think about it and be like, yeah, that's probably true
day now that i'm thinking about like a giant monster i think that that's
actually real i think that happened my brother who was a god
it's funny too that like they were kind of they were kind of on point for some
of it but then it's like because like you know they had the
chimera and it's like okay like the wings of a dragon which first of all
that's cheating you can't use a dragon in there
but that's terrifying right and then like yeah and uh and a lion and a snake
you know what else
a goat
that's also
that's how we make the scariest animal
we add a goat head
that's a whole head that you could be using for like
like i don't know a bear even a bear is better than a goat
yeah another snake
you use two snakes instead of one goat and a snake
exactly a goat that's just wasted
that's wasted real estate
that was also like the best kind of like religion because it was like
They would be like, with Christianity, you'll be like,
so where is God and stuff?
They'll be like, oh, he's all around you,
or he's in heaven, whatever,
like you'll never, you won't see it 'til you die.
And then with all that shit, they'd be like,
where are the gods?
And they'd be like, they're over there.
- Right there.
(laughing)
- You see that hill?
They're--
- Yeah, they live there.
- They're up there.
Can I go up there?
- I think I hear them fucking right now.
- Oh my God, and it's going really bad.
yeah they're fucking oh i think another monster might be coming
and then yeah they all huddle into a circle and they're like okay 100 heads
yeah yeah exactly yeah it's like the first lesson a baby
learns is i think i hear sex and a monster over there and the baby's like
i don't even know colors yet
yeah i like they they did also they had the guts to go to do half gods too
like not to you know like that and they're half gods it wasn't like it
wasn't like a jesus thing where it's like okay yeah like he's half god but he's
also just the same thing as god so you'll never see him or anything
but they were like yeah there was a guy he had this crazy spear and he was real
and he lived in this town with us yeah yeah um yeah because the coolest guy in
the whole town fucked some animal and then made him
yeah um i was thinking like do you think that there was like
Medusa eventually became just a woman with a head full of snakes, or do you think it started out as like she's disgusting
She's got one snake one worm one centipede
Yeah, it takes too long
Yeah, like did they like
Sit around like a windowless office like throwing a hacky sack like
big table with index cards like pinned up. Lion with a donkey dick. No that's not
good. They also have like 500 gods like they would just like they would
just be like oh yeah there's this guy oh they were just like oh shit fuck we need
a guy for a welcome mat we need a god that does welcome mats. That doesn't fit into anything.
God for boogers yeah yeah no we're not doing the booger God I told you I keep
telling you we don't need a the booger God is categorized under fire he's part
of the fire God yeah yeah does fire and boogers fine whatever what the fuck ever
yeah that all yeah all the gods have like some some like like RPG like like
specialization combo yeah he's proficient in in in flame warfare and streets it's
been he's the god of dessert - it's very funny - that that they had they had a
goddess of love but then they also had another god of love that was a baby
they're like yeah there's two love gods one of them's a beautiful woman the
There's a naked baby that flies around and it's
It attacks you with the bow and arrow yeah, yeah when he shoots you with a bow and arrow you want to fuck him
Yeah, you don't want to be a baby fucker you have to dodge the arrows
Yeah, that's the scariest part they could come out of anywhere
Yeah, that was like trials and the law and order was like your honor. I got shot by the baby who makes you want to fuck him with his magic arrows
It's fucked up that that's the one that we got for Valentine's Day
We didn't get to go with Aphrodite like the beautiful love woman god
It's the naked baby
that attacks you and makes you fall in love
Because he also loves candy he's also the god of candy
he's the god of candy and school getting cards at school
he's the god of snow days
uh... and uh... i should get back into greek gods i think
i feel like every little boy was obsessed with it at some point
and maybe it's worth taking another look at as an adult
were you into like norse gods at all
no
i thought those ones were cool
No, there was this Indian kid who became a Nazi who loved Norse gods.
Yeah, he's a weird person, but he became a real Nazi.
He sounds kind of problematic.
Yeah, he's a bit odd.
But he was into Norse gods, and I was like, "This kid's a freak.
I don't want anything to do with that."
He's one of those kids that metal actually turned him racist.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
you have to be careful about that near metal is a that's it
it's a little bit slow there's a dark triad for now yeah i mean you can add on
or scott's
and then uh...
yet all i mean lord of the rings i think is the the third thing they're probably
metal
nor the rings for turning racist
r_u_k_ and what is it so that those things are all related to the lord of
the rings is based
what rings is actually based on norse mythology and many metal bands and
their iconography from Lord of the Rings so I just thought it would make a good try at.
Many Nazis latch onto the imagery.
Many Nazis.
It's true.
I don't think it's true dude.
Lord of the Rings is like, no, it's just, Lord of the Rings isn't as racist as any fantasy
thing.
No, I don't think it's racist, but racist people think it is because they see like, oh, Gandalf
the white is destroying goblins and they're like oh I know what the goblins
are supposed to be and then they do that whole thing I know but they're just
stupid he made this for me yeah he wasn't yeah he's just an old guy who's
like I like to come up with words and language
Yeah, and this guy was named Borbalorbaloth and he was a wizard.
That's how it, that's how I always like...
He read, he read like Grimm's fairy tales and he was like, "I'm gonna make this into history."
Yeah, it's funny how no Nazis ever take like Star Wars as one of their foundational texts.
Yeah.
Even though it's like the exact same thing.
Yeah, no one's like...
That's why I always like, like, C.S. Lewis more 'cause he's like so on the nose about like what it's actually supposed to mean.
Like there's zero room for interpretation.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, just like there's this lion and he died on a cross no died in a different way
But he died for your sin. I know we've talked about the whole Narnia thing before on here
But it yeah, it's so sick like there's I did in one of the books
They have like they have like a like a multi armed pagan god that ever that's like all the followers are evil
It's like yeah, and they have a tiny rat. Yeah. Yeah, like yeah, really like it's like whoa
a lion yeah wow so cool dude yeah and then I got into like like I loved those
books as a kid so I was like I'm gonna check out this guy's other shit and like
he has like a book that's like it's called like the screw tape letters and
it's about like the devil writing like notes to like a deal and he's like
what's up you have you made anybody do some evil recently he's like eyes yeah
you know same old same old I'm the devil it's pretty cool dude that is good
yeah is that like a required reading you had for your home school or that yeah
yes Lewis was was that was that was heavy dude we were coming heavy with the CS
Lewis yeah I learned so much it was it was a it was beautiful it was like CS
Lewis until you were 13 and then it was like Ayn Rand like kind of the opposite
person but like they really pushed it on you they were like she doesn't believe
in
book and shit it and then closed it. Oh my god. I can smell it through my microphone too.
It's like there's some kind of like update that lets me smell this. At least fucking wipe
your ass. No, not with your own face. It's so, one of the most disgusting parts is how
silent this poop is. I mean I can see it coming out, it's just not making a sound. That's
how smooth it's flowing. It keeps coming out. Oh my god, it just changed colors from like
a dark brown to a deep black halfway through. It looks like a magician's scarf coming out
Oh my god. It keeps changing colors.
Oh what is this? Green? That's unhealthy man.
Oh fuck.
Oh he just framed a piece of it and it squished all over the frame.
Oh he's back now.
[laughter]
Okay.
How was that?
Something got squished?
Oh yeah. Yeah, something got squished.
For sure.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
The head of my peepee by my index finger and thumb when I was squeezing the peepee out got squished.
You don't squeeze the peepee out.
Sure you do. Yeah.
What?
Yeah, you drain, because the tip of your head, the head of the penis is like a sponge and
then it fills up with pee and then you have to strain it.
That's not true.
That's not how it happens.
No, you don't have to pizza roll your penis to get the pee out.
It's not like an icing bag either.
Yeah, like a tube of toothpaste.
So don't say that.
No, I just said it's not like an icing bag or a tube of toothpaste or, it's not anything
like that.
And it's not, there's not a lever either that drops the payload.
So don't try and use that excuse.
Okay.
then what were you guys talking about? Just you shit all over the place.
For that you do have to need your colon like it's a... I mean that is
actually true yeah I kind of like I when I take a shit I like go into the fetal
position I have to like rock back and forth and my my the shit is like yeah it
it like has to like somehow kind of like one of those ball maze puzzles like fall
finally to the end through my I do like a type of like you watch pot doesn't never
boils type of thing so I don't try to like make too much of an effort I just
kind of sit down there and go you know whatever happens here happens either way
and I just wait something that you learn in adulthood is that you don't have to
push so hard you can just you just give it a dull roar and then you kind of have
to not care. And you kind of just say out loud, like, I don't even care, you know, whatever,
whichever thing happens right now is fine with me. You got to do reverse psychology to your
butt every time you go to the bathroom. Yeah. You just kind of have to say, like, I'm feeling
normal about this either way. It's just, hey, I'll be happy if I do or I don't. It doesn't
matter. I don't give a shit. I don't take a shit. If I just have a long fart here, that's
fine I'll still tell everybody I pooped that's better yeah yeah flush the toilet
- yeah I'm gonna like I came in here and jerked off or something so I'm just
gonna sit here as far because if you did jerk off you would also leave it on the
bath mat yeah we just leave the toilet you leave it on the belly button dude I
I don't want to clog everything up leave it on the belly button and he just yeah, it dries dude
Guys
Some guy on the street just spit directly into my belly button.
Isn't this weird?
It's the weirdest spit I've ever seen.
Oh my god, he was like gargling salt water beforehand or something so the consistency
is just bizarre.
Ugh, it's so weird.
Ugh, and it won't wash off.
It keeps getting stuck.
This guy's got the weird spit.
I actually forgot to tell you but I did shower and it kind of like cooked like it was egg
whites.
Why does cum hate hot water so much? It's like fucking crazy dude. Like why is it like
yeah every time I like have cum on my body which is not often but when I do I forget
and I'll wash it off with hot water all of a sudden I have like a like a patch of like
tachyderm like stuck to my fucking to my it's so you can use it to seal stuff up if you
need to.
that's how you use canning back in the day.
- Yeah. - Right.
- It's the body's mayonnaise,
it holds the whole sandwich together.
- They used to, cavemen used to seal the doors
to their caves like that,
so that no creatures could come in in the night.
- Oh. - Yeah.
They would all play the cookie game
at the entrance of the cave.
- Right, yeah. (laughing)
- Well, yeah, they had the cookie game.
- Yeah, with the big round door.
- Yeah, it was originally a big round slab of stone
that they would roll into place.
- Yeah, it was called the Rocky Game.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And then once cookies were invented,
were like oh this is actually a lot easier let's just do this this is a lot
better than rolling around yeah cuz you can't you can't have like eight people
sit around a square. It doesn't make any sense. It has to be a circle.
Someone's going to get the corner. It's going to be really uncomfortable.
Yeah, it needed to be a circle.
Yeah. Hey, speaking of inventions.
Hey. Dude, you're a master. Yeah, pretty easy for me. You're a fucking master.
Today's list is from the top 10's.
Top 10 most wanted inventions.
make life easier or more interesting. As simple as possible in a complex world.
What do you guys need?
What's the hole in your life that you need to fill with an invention right now?
Hmm...
I guess, like, I wish I had the equivalent of a cyanide capsule, but it was just a
like a snack, like an internet snack. That's a really good idea.
Yeah, like a cyanide tooth, but it's like a... it pops a Jolly Rancher into your mouth.
Yeah. It could be nice to have something like that's soft
to be in between me and the floor when I'm sleeping.
Could be a nice invention that I would enjoy.
I might need. The Jolly Rancher thing would be good too because like if you
were ever in a situation where someone was going to kill you
you'd be like you act real smug and be like "huh yeah sure"
and you they see you like pop the tooth in your mouth and then you go like
yeah
"how did you do that I can't kill you now" I was
I was thinking about this like a probably a few weeks ago just like a like I just
I was just imagining a guy walking around like licking a blue lollipop a bunch and
then it's going blah and his tongue is just like a disgusting brown.
It's half on.
It's like a horrible like this gray brown color.
Have you heard of black hairy tongue?
No, what's that?
Black hairy tongue is a disorder you get when you don't wash your tongue enough
and it literally just becomes black and hairy.
What? Wait, what?
Black hairy tongue.
I thought that was gonna be like a food item.
No, it's called black hairy tongue.
What the fuck?
That's just hair.
Holy shit, dude.
What?
And it's called black hairy tongue.
it's not
what you know that i'm going on
fighting like the most fucked up guy here it is not like three t_v_ he's always
sticking his tongue out at you can see like that away i think that we are
different neighborhood might actually be a medical mystery
woman diagnosed with a very black tongue after car crash
falling from a car crash
uh... no
maybe if you like
I don't know. If you hit like an animal. If you crash into a porcupine or something.
If you had like a rat in your mouth before you crashed and when you crashed it like jolted
all the hair off. It like road rashed on your tongue and took
all the hair off. That's gross. There's a guy in my neighborhood
who's like a shopping cart guy who has like a volcano on his hand and it's pretty cool.
And he like licks it like I'll be like walking in the subway. I'll be like you like look at it scratch it
They go yeah, that is his little Jolly Rancher a capsule
Infinite snack
Yeah, it's just pus and salt
Good for him. I gotta wean myself off
I'm a hit this too hard
One is teleportation device
There's a comment here
I guess that's a good idea
But then humans can get into way more trouble this way and cops won't be able to find any criminal since they can just teleport to
Africa or something. I think it's a bad idea, but it's my opinion
I'm gonna go to Africa where everything is legal because I'm a criminal
Yeah
Too big to find anyone that's true. Yeah, you can hide forever
This type of invention/machine is needed by us for a long time.
It will turn the human lifestyle.
Some of our scientists are working on this project.
"Human lifestyle" all caps.
That's a lab manager there.
Yeah, working on that.
And "Human Lifestyle" is all first letter capital.
Yeah, and it's going to be turned.
Teleportation would be awesome.
You could get from the kitchen to the bathroom in half a second.
That happens to this guy every day.
Kitchen the bathrooms the funniest combination of room
Microwave cheese, it's in a bowl of water
Taking the last bite and then just staring down like
Take me an hour to get to the bathroom
Ain't gonna happen to forever
teleportation would be... go ahead.
teleport back home after school/work
this guy hates taking the bus but he also loves going to school and work
this will be absolutely awesome when it comes out
Dallas cheerleaders beamed into my living room
yeah you can teleport on whoever you want
anywhere you'd like
at any point in time
teleportation would be so cool and then that emoji with the heart eyes
if i could teleport it would be even go ahead it would be going either away from
danger or to a relatives for a holiday
that again kidnappers could step in take a kid and step out with the kid
also nobody would walk again just teleport with a very comfortable chair
to every place and could easily brought a store or bank
i love it no one ever says the limits of teleportation they just talk about
how it's completely unlimited technology and you can do the worst thing that i can
come up with. It's so funny to me, if i could teleport i'd either go on vacation or
teleport away from danger.
That's my top thing is
i would be able to escape from danger if i could do that.
This comment says you could go anywhere you want with a thumbs up emoji.
And then right below it, yes i want teleport all caps.
So they're imagining a scenario where there's no like, like, uh, cinder and receiver.
You can just, you kind of, you're like, you're like, you're like, everyone's going everywhere.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Control.
That would be cooler.
I want to move through this list quick because I want to get to the stuff that's like past the top
10 here.
Okay.
Number two.
You're actually all really good inventors.
Yeah, they're just very clever inventions.
Number two, time machine.
I mean, I wouldn't have ever come up with this is the thing.
I wouldn't have been able to think of this.
[Laughter]
He says, "What happens if you kill your grandfather then? Wouldn't it be a paradox?"
Yeah man, I mean, I guess.
[Laughter]
If I had a time machine, I would go...
I would kill Hitler and stop Abraham Lincoln from dying and give cavemen iPads.
I would also try to change the world by giving Indians machine guns.
guns and i would give missiles and food to dinosaurs so they would still be alive today
wait you say missiles for dinosaurs? missiles and food so they can defend themselves
yeah i guess that's fair yeah i would see my grandma
it is really funny that like the paradox of time travel is like you can't like kill a family member
Like that's like as if that's like whatever was gonna go. Yeah, you can't do the most horrible thing
Something you wouldn't really want to do
Okay, so if you go back in time and fuck yourself as a little baby like why what would happen
I'd used it to go to where back when a doof Hitler
To art school and force the school to enter just so World War two would not happen
I would go to my grandparents' teenager days, and I'm going to talk to them.
Number three, the cure for deadly diseases.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah, someone should invent that.
Yeah, that'd be a really great, really strong invention.
That'd get a lot of likes on Shark Tale.
Number one top disease that has claimed more lives is heart disease, also called cardiovascular disease.
A way to less likely have this disease or getting rid of it works with the person eating a specific vegetable,
vegetable even though it might not have a pleasant taste at all but could be
reduced with a mixture of fruit or put into capsules. Awesome. That guy's a genius.
These diseases are deadly we need to stop them.
Number four, animal communicator.
Okay, this is like a sci-fi gadget that translates.
yeah I guess is it gonna how do we make this because I am planning to make this
for my invention I am in seventh grade so I hope this isn't that hard for me to
make so if someone knows how to make this or like a website that would be perfect
oh that would be perfect if anyone has a website if anyone has a website might be
a long shot but maybe one of you has a website that teaches you how to make an
I'm a communicator because I am in seventh grade.
Yeah, and I'm planning to invent this.
Hi fishy fishy.
Destroy it!
He's at once.
Hi fishy fishy. Don't let him talk back.
Destroy it.
Can you imagine like how
how would a fish react if you could just
make yourself understood to it just for like
just like two
seconds like it would have just
a new reaction because like when a fish gets
it wouldn't get scared right it would know
willfully swimming around issues can only swim
yeah i think that's like i think it would be actually get up to anything is
swimming or died i think it would do something new that we haven't seen
before i think that's the key to getting a fish to do something other than swim
might be to say hi fishy fishy
i think i think she did see in my fish
blinked
uh...
what
yeah not know yet i lives but he did blank
This one's good, this comment, "We would understand our pets."
I mean, you does not want to do that.
[laughter]
Uh, number five, "Instant learning. Download knowledge directly to brain."
Hmm, that's pretty good.
It is, yeah.
This way we wouldn't have to go to no dumb school.
True.
That would be called cheating in school, but still awesome.
As would a brain internet chip, so one can see the internet before their very eyes, via the chip.
I am 10 years old but I know how to do it
genius children on this website if this were to happen because they think that
these are the only adults that are worth impressing is the adults yeah if this
were to happen it would add at least 12 years to a person's life to live
is
a ton of movies probably.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Watch it with my eyes closed.
Yeah.
Oh, I would bookmark addicting games.
Yes, yeah, I'd be on E-Bomb's World and I would play Frank's Adventure and I would skip
to the part where you see Barney Rubble's wife's boobs.
Yeah, I would just download all the victory screens of all the math games and I wouldn't
even have to play them.
Damn.
Instead of like seeing a really fucked up crazy guy, you would just see a guy and automatically
know that he has salad fingers on there.
You would know, okay, he's watching salad fingers.
fingers. Yeah, you have been deranged by salad fingers. Yeah. Number six, a device to record
your dreams. Um, no. Here's a comment. I don't care for that. I don't really. Here's a comment
though. Dick in my booty. Okay. Okay. And what's the comment, Kim? Oh, shit. If I had
I would I would show all my friends my dreams all the time
Yeah
It'd be funny to show your friend like be like okay like just have a bunch of like like
Sex dreams and stuff and then be like oh finally
I had just like a funny dream that I could show my friends and showing them and they're like they're really
You forgot that like in the background
Tanya says top
True, okay, very cool
It would be cool imagine recording a dream about having se star
Yes, oh, yes
I'm seven pretty fucked up sex dreams when I was in middle school
Yeah, I remember
Yeah
Just like the the weird kid in school the kid who was always like pretending he was turning into the Hulk when he didn't get
A math question right yeah dream that you know he came on my face
that one
The whole kid? The whole kid.
The first time I ever lucid dreamed it was like my cousin like
got a new girlfriend and I like
felt I took a nap and I like started lucid dreaming and I was like, oh my god, I can do anything.
So I imagined myself getting a blowjob from her.
That was the entire dream and then I woke up and I was kind of like hmm.
Oh hey you two.
Is everything still okay with you guys?
Yeah, I remember having like what was basically a lucid dream like I was about to sort of seal the deal with a
With a pretty girl from my high school
And then I guess at a certain point like right when I was about to happen she was like I can't do this
I'm a lesbian
And then she goes and hangs out with the girl and I I remember waking up right after that and I was like I knew
I was dreaming. Why did I make that happen?
Because I thought it would be a good story because I thought it would be a funny twist
That's the only thing like hotter than having sex with a girl I guess is like being like
one second from having sex and she's like I'm a lesbian.
That is awesome.
That's seriously fucking cool.
I'm gonna go have a dream about this now.
Number seven, saltwater desalinator.
I don't care.
I don't think I care either.
I don't care at all. Also everyone in the comments are saying this already exists. I know how to make one
I can make this in an hour
Does it exist? I think it does I don't think to make something exists that is worth
Yeah, it's not going to make it but I'm going to make it cheap and fast
Okay. Well, it sounds like sounds like these people have got it locked down. Just nobody thought to do it yet
number eight invisibility cloak less of an invention and more of a
magical relic well yeah like once you make it a
Now I'm a true ghost
It's a comment I'll purely be the phantom of the night
Yeah, no, that's not a good if they said invisibility device that's the right a device is an invention a cloak is is a magical
Yeah, that's an artifact. Yeah, I don't like that.
Number nine, a device for remembering everything. Yeah. Yeah. Why not? I mean, I'll take it, I guess.
I think this device will be great for students to remember their lessons, even older people,
to not forget or lost something. But on the other hand, it may be a bad invention for some people by
remembering bad memories that will cause them to have depression. Yes. That's a good point.
Santa has that
This one this is like a Bill Maher voice comment, maybe which is there is something called a diary I
I imagine Bill Maher doing the Santa one too.
Yeah.
Santa has that.
Here's one, here's another one for him.
So annoying for me.
It's very weird if this device exists in this world.
Ah ha ha, colon D.
It's already been invented.
Yeah, it's called the to-do list.
I need this very...
And Santa has it.
(laughter)
And Santa already has it.
It's called the naughty nice list.
I need this very urgent
and I forget everything
even mostly on where I place things at.
(laughter)
Bill Maher's like the biggest atheist in the world
but he believes in Santa.
(laughter)
He's talking about some fucking Republican
built Republicans trying to
filibuster the healthcare bill
this week. Enjoy the
naughty list from Santa.
[laughter]
Okay, so I guess there's an
infinite being who judges
you. Yeah, I think that we already
have a name for him.
He's Santa and he's real.
[laughter]
He has a device for remembering everything.
And he has tons of different
devices.
He's basically
a device collector.
He invented a big bag
that reindeer carry.
Have I ever seen him? No, but uh... I do have
the power of belief on my side.
Number ten is hoverboard.
Okay.
Santa does have that actually. This has already been invented are being sold
widespread as of 11/13/2016.
This shit's not a fucking hoverboard, dude.
It's a wheel. It's on wheels, man.
Yeah.
Stupid-ass bitch.
I hate it!
I hate it.
I hate that thing!
I don't care if Santa has it. I hate it and I don't want one.
Mm-mm.
And if he puts it in my stocking, I'm gonna freak out because I heard those things effing explode.
They do explode. I forgot about that.
I heard they effing explode, so maybe I don't leave a bomb in my stocking.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Let me just ask for a bomb for Christmas. Let's skip all the bullshit.
it
bad idea
They get good. They're stepping it up here. They step it up a little bit. Awesome.
Um, just skip around here. Number 12 is Mind Reader.
Um, cool. Tropical J- Tropical J says, "Bad idea. The human brain is fickle."
It's unreadable. Everyone would end up destroying each other.
I don't want this. Mine should be Privet. Espe- Especially mine.
(laughing)
- Number 13, flying car.
- Yup.
- Possible and could revolutionize the oil crisis.
- Shut up.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
- I wanna revolutionize a crisis.
- Santa literally does already have this too.
- Flying car.
- He straight up has a flying car.
That's what a sleigh is.
- Yeah, exactly.
- That's literally all it is.
- 14, battery with long life.
not to not into this life i'm too lazy to charge my battery
uh...
true they want us to recharge our batteries but if you can find a way to
charge the normal batteries are changing batteries in the long life ones are at
least make it a longer time before it has to be recharged you can have the
patent and make it suitably for the kids
straight idea to make money
number seventeen aids detector
I wish they had it. I wish they had it. I think they can tell if somebody has AIDS already.
I don't think they're just guessing. Yeah, but you have to go to the hospital. You want
to know if the guy next to you on the bus has it. Oh, yeah, like a metal detector. Yeah.
Okay, or an EMF reader. You just walk around just embarrassing people. And Santa has that.
And Santa does have that. That's how he decides if naughty or nice list. I really like this
It's like next run in a row from 19 to 22. I just want to read all these in a row
because okay so but number 19 bioengineered meal fruit that provides
100% of nutritional needs and can be grown in home garden number 20 batteries
that work forever number 21 a machine that can communicate directly with your
minds number 22 is glow in the dark trees
from amber star 120 is no more terrified kids screaming through your window at
night. Ah, these dark trees! I can't see the trees. I can't see these trees. Can you help me in there?
Yelling into somebody's window. Open the window! Open the window, the trees are so dark out here.
Do these trees look dark to you? Wow. All the kids in the neighborhood. Vehicles that can transform
into planes or boats.
Robot Woman/Man.
Either one is fine.
Whichever they invent first.
Cosmetically appealing.
No intelligence required.
I wonder what they want.
I wonder if they want a man or a woman robot.
Number 27's wireless electricity.
28 is a nutritional biscuit that has one sixth of minimum complete daily nutrition for a pregnant
woman per biscuit.
And the comment here that says "would be great for geeks too."
Yeah, nerd, what are you eating?
A nutritional biscuit that has one sixth of minimum complete daily nutrition for a pregnant
woman per biscuit?
Let me correct you on that, pregnant woman or geek.
Okay, so you are a nerd.
This is a good one-two punch.
Number 30, a light-speed spacecraft.
Number 31, a fast elevator.
(laughing)
- That would be actually dangerous
because of the extreme G-forces
and it would crush our bones.
- I need a very deep imagination for this.
(laughing)
- Automatic roller skates.
- Yup, color-changing clothing.
- Okay, glasses that automatically adjust
for perfect vision.
- That could be pretty nice.
So that means they don't do anything if you already have perfect vision.
Yeah, they don't do anything.
Good for the old people, as somebody says.
But are people's prescription needs changing so rapidly that you would need...
Oh, mine change every day.
It's just that the manufacturers can just make one lens.
Oh, so they don't have to make any...
Okay, they just have to make a computer lens that changes the glass all the time.
Right.
Glasses could just be computer screens that show you things instead of this.
You don't have glasses, Pierce?
Mm-mm.
I thought you had glasses.
I do seem like the type of kid who would try and sit too close to the TV every night to
try and make yourself-- Just to get myself?
Yeah, just to get glasses.
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes for Christmas I ask for non-prescription transition glasses, which is-- it is truly
the most autistic thing you can own.
Yeah.
It's just an announcement that you have nothing going on socially.
Yeah, I've gotten glasses twice and the first time I was like I really wanted glasses and
I was like a kid so I just like completely like through the vision test like I just said
all the wrong letters and numbers and stuff and I never thought of like getting just non-prescription
glasses so I just had these glasses that just made everything just invisible just like it
like it's like the highest prescription and my mom's like I didn't know you had
such terrible eyes and then they give you tiny eyes yeah no they give me big ass
eyes okay I can picture you wearing glasses that give you tiny little eyes. You can't picture that.
Yeah I can picture it too. I yeah no I would no you look like a little goober I'm
closing my eyes and picturing right now. Stop. Number 41 is a way to grow
any wings you like.
This would be mutation.
Not a good idea if you ask me.
I'd have bird wings that are feathery and white and black tips.
I'd have flame wings.
#39.
An easy way to come up with an invention.
That would be nice.
That would actually be really nice.
I've written more than 13 idea books.
I am interested in printing them as an idea generator.
Once they are published, the inventions and ideas contained within each shall be given
freely to anyone that reads the books or is interested.
I'm giving all rights to the invention away.
Be blessed and stay safe.
Mitchell S. Lankford.
Wait, can we search that name?
I did, he has a magnetic mind master class.
We have to get this guy's books.
Can we order those books and read them on the show?
Oh, I guess it's magnetic mind master class, but I thought it was magnetic mind master.
michael s langford angel investor
yo
more than thirteen
why is this guy on the top tens? he's in a suit
maybe it's somebody impersonating him
could be i guess
i'm gonna search magnetic mind masterclass
um...
number forty four, gun gloves
gun gloves is awesome
that is cool
bath with built in storage
vegetables that taste like fruit
that's good advice that automatically plays songs according to one's emotions
time remote control
with any of you
number sixty one is
auto identity system for police
haha
fascist cuban
uh...
of the union you control with your mind
the
they have that
it's like a pretty good
lands
with
Yesterday lens.
Do they not explain it?
No, they just say yes.
Everyone in the comments seems to know what it is.
Vibrating condom.
That's actually a pretty good idea.
Life prolonger.
Yeah, instead of a reservoir tip, it's just a little battery.
Yeah, exactly.
50 gigabyte memory cell phone.
Economical dynamic wall pictures.
I am working on this in Arizona.
I like I like that there there's like a small percentage of these people who are
just inventors that are working on an invention and coming in to see whether
their invention is on this list. Inventing and this guy's just inventing a TV.
I'm already inventing this. I'm actually working on this.
A silent suction cup. Here I just posted a screenshot of this guy who does the magnetic
mind master class. Number 86 is a silent suction strong enough to pick up fleas
from pet dogs or cats.
The suction cup should be able to be flushed down the toilet for quick disposal.
I don't like to use harsh chemicals on my pets.
One of them tries to bite me when I do the curry comb to hunt and kill the fleas.
The fleas are very resilient to being pinched.
Toilet overflow tray.
What if you had a tray under your toilet that would catch any leaks or overflows?
And a sewer backup protector.
How much would such a product be?
A toilet moat.
What would that be, a million dollars for something like that?
How much would that fetch?
71 is life prolonger.
A mirror that takes pictures.
Device to transfer sleep.
Some people like to sleep and could sell their sleep, others don't like to sleep and would
purchase it in order to stay awake.
Someone who did life prolonger also did stamina prolonger.
People became tired but this is the invention that will guarantee that you will prolong everything
you do, work, sex, performance, sports, etc.
Nano paint that can be programmed to only paint what you want.
Thanks, I'll try to invent.
Super virus protector.
"Inventor"
Thanks, I'll try to invent.
"Chemical, microorganisms, salt, sugar, etc. filter"
Uh...
"Walking ships"
"Ships that are able to walk on land"
This is a bra moment.
"Another way of reading that's quicker"
"Spray"
Spray that will make your shoelaces stand up straight for 24 hours.
Anti-sun explosion device.
The sun will explode after millions of years, and this device will stop it.
Device to transfer sleep. Some people like to sleep and can sell their sleep.
Others don't like to sleep and would purchase it in order to stay awake.
I need this.
A built-in microwave for your...
This is... These are... This is... These are both the same thing.
A built-in microwave for your lunchbox.
A zapper that automatically zaps your teeth straight to replace braces.
Weather controls.
Tornado creation.
Bracelet that tells you how long you have to live.
I also like tablet with infinite power storage and an unbreakable screen.
Edible everlasting cups.
Ultra image converter.
Ancient time clock.
We need to invent an ancient thing.
Size gun.
Freeze microwave.
The concept is similar to a microwave.
Freezes food faster than a freezer.
Number 117 is lightsaber and the comment is "The force is strong with this one."
switch edible tape useful for certain foods such as burgers burritos and
delicate foods artificial black holes overpowered but okay Oh silent microwave
microwave that operates silently do you have a device device that could end all
life typically on a planet 181 is bladeless helicopters and the
and says helicopters without police
perpetual mobile
the uh...
seeking bullets
invention machine
these are all by i have pra
he's commenting what they are
all of these are the same guy
he's just explaining what it is not something i just are are just something
but silent
that's the last time i was on the leaf blower
uh... silent jet engine
silent microwave force field he threw out here
young
nanotech clothing multi-purpose i wear
device records the past advice is capable of recording through both imagery and
audio in the past time while in present time sounds impossible but the concept
is interesting to go
uh... freeze microwave
yeah uh...
uh... here is a billion uh... disaster creation artificial creation of
disasters of any kind
very last what is machine that can bring fictional characters to life
is that also a pro
so that when is that the only one that's from someone else not
i have is a good name
is also a fucking genius inventor this guy
yeah
uh... we have to do we need to fucking getting contact with this mitchell
Lankford and find out about his magnetic mind master stuff.
I have a tab open, I'm saving this, I'll order one of the books or something and we'll come
back.
Oh my god, wait, never mind.
I'll talk about it after.
A 12 month program that teaches you how to implement our revolutionary super conscious
creation process and create what you love.
And the pictures of someone meditating with like a dodecahedron behind them.
And he works at the Conscious Education Company.
Yes.
Wow.
I'm joining LinkedIn to connect with him.
Oh, it says sponsor running out.
Reserve yours by Thursday, July 8th, but that's today.
Fuck!
Shit.
I wonder if you go on tomorrow if it will say Friday, July 9th.
Alright, I am gonna sign up.
I'm gonna sign up.
Alright.
Me too.
Okay.
Bye.
Wait, Pierce.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, is that the end?
Yeah.
It is kind of the end, because I have to pee so bad.
Sorry.
nothing at all?
no
not even one little thing?
no, I'm stopping recording right now
alright fine