You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Having a chicken attack.
- You're having a chicken attack.
- I'm having a chicken attack.
I ate two tacos.
They tasted so good yesterday
and then they reached a threshold
and they tasted like trash.
- Oh, they were day old tacos.
- No, 'cause you got fish tacos.
No, these were these were these were tacos that I made in the slow cooker.
I mean, dude, I put this chicken in the slow cooker.
How many tacos did you eat yesterday?
Three.
Three? No, because you got tacos at dinner last night.
Yeah, that three tacos.
I just ate these tacos like 15 minutes ago and made them.
I ate the chicken cold.
You made the chicken yesterday.
I made the chicken five days ago now.
Oh, OK. Dude.
And I was like, five days, you know, that's like right on the edge.
I mean, five days, if it were a slice of bread, it would be fine.
So I don't see the issue.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what I was thinking.
If the chicken was a bar of chocolate, I wouldn't have any issue eating this.
Yeah.
Weeks after.
If it was like a can of baked beans, I wouldn't care.
So why would it be any different for it to be a chicken?
It's not like it still has feathers.
Turns out it tastes like lemons after five days.
And it hurts your stomach really bad.
Dude, if it tasted acidic at all, that's--
Also, it makes your nose burn like you ate a jalapeno.
It makes your nose bleed.
Yeah, it makes your nose bleed, pops a blood vessel in your eye.
Yeah.
It makes your penis really long.
Also, I can, I can, you can also see into your stomach through your belly button now.
You were not supposed to eat that.
I know I wasn't supposed to eat that, dude.
I feel like I fucking, I feel like I played flag football.
I did eat the whole thing.
I'm hungry.
Did you eat the whole thing?
Hungry.
Hungry, I was hungry.
It was out of food, dude.
Dude, I've been eating, listen, I found out.
Have you ever had a stomachache?
I have.
I found out that I-- - If you open your fridge
and the only thing in there was a worm, would you eat it?
Raw? - If hungry.
- Raw worm? - Yeah, if hungry.
- No seasoning neither?
- You know I can't take that seasoning crap.
- He can't.
- The worm's too spicy for this guy.
- God damn it, I'm so tired, I'm so tired.
I didn't grab a Red Bull or anything before recording.
This sucks. - Yeah.
You need to grab life by the bull.
- No, dude, I fucking-- - That's right.
- Last night-- - Or the bull
by the horns.
- Last night, so two nights ago--
Three nights ago.
So five nights ago, I made this chicken.
[Laughter]
And then it went really bad.
I went to that, I went to the Brandon show,
hung out after, went to a bar.
Well, also, I want to, this is, this is going to come out,
this is, this is, this is the first, okay,
so Patrick just revealed what we were hiding,
which is that these are all backlogged.
Yeah.
We didn't mention that at all,
which it wasn't on purpose that we didn't mention it,
but yeah, just so you guys know, I guess now,
that none of this has been current.
So I guess if, if one,
If something horrible happened and we didn't comment on it, that's why.
Yeah, you just ruined like so many alibis for all three of us.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Um, nothing is happening in Cuba yet.
Let me just say, nothing's happening in Cuba right now.
So you went to some bar.
Yeah, I went to the bar, um, left my card there because it started like pouring rain
and I was like, "Oh, I need to go home immediately."
So I called like a, 'cause it was in Gowanus,
or I think that's what, Perks Slope, I don't-
- Gowanus!
- Gowanus.
- Yeah.
- And I left my card there,
and then we were meeting up with our friends.
So I was like, "Well, fuck it.
Why don't we like go back to the same bar
and just get drinks there?"
'Cause I'll, you know, it was a pretty good bar.
- Yeah, I mean, also I would like to say,
in an effort to get his card,
Patrick made all of us travel at least one hour to go to this bar.
That is so far away.
I didn't know I didn't know how far away they were.
And then what happened after we went to a restaurant across the
street.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and I left my backpack at the bar.
So you had to go back to the bar.
last night I got home with Caleb at like a 10 50 something like that and then he
called me I called him because I I wanted to know what's he crying the lift he
called me and he was crying I wasn't crying
if I was it was about swing him back and forth out of his nose while he cried
I could... *sniff sniff*
It's my manic bag in your hand!
Do you have a tissue?
That's what he said when you picked up.
Okay, I was... I will say...
I was very stressed out last night.
And Caleb said like...
"Don't forget your shoes at the bar."
And I just like bitch-buttoned him.
Just like completely.
Yeah, and immediately I was like,
"Patrick's kind of a pussy, dude."
*laughter*
You know I've been...
There's a lot going on in my life right now.
You know I'm stressed out.
And tell me, did you leave your shoes at the bar, you fucking clown?
I wore flip-flops.
So that I wore flip-flops, did you?
I wore my Tevas so that I wouldn't forget.
The most easy to lose shoe in the world, by the way.
It's the easiest shoe to forget.
Because I love my Tevas.
Yeah.
Don't let your backpack hear that.
It's going to be mad at you.
You just keep showing up to the bar with one less article of clothing.
Be like, I think I left my pants here.
Can you guys help me?
I mean, that sucked, 'cause then I took the train home
'cause I took two lifts that night,
and it was like 50 bucks.
I was like, "Jesus fucking Christ,
"I'm not spending that much money."
If I were that bartender, I'd be pretty scared of you.
Really? Yeah.
Why? 'Cause two nights in a row,
you have some excuse to come back.
Well, I'm never going there again.
I'm never going to that bar again.
You better, I don't know, yeah.
If I keep fucking losing shit there,
that means it's a sign.
That means it's a sign from Christ.
Maybe they have a giant magnet there.
Who he.
Stop kissing your chain.
You don't care about God.
Stop.
You hate Christ.
It's a sign from Christ that I should go there ever again.
Don't touch Christ.
Stop.
I don't like how Italian you're trying to look recently.
Yeah.
I don't like that, dude.
I'm not trying to look Italian.
Because you're not Italian.
You're trying.
You're trying very hard.
You're clearly trying to look Italian, dude.
Don't ask me what I had for lunch today.
What'd you have for lunch today?
I said, don't ask.
And I'm telling you, I'm asking you, what'd you have?
Chicken Parmesan.
Okay.
All right.
No, I don't approve.
Oh yeah.
Whatever you do.
Don't ask me what I had for lunch today.
What'd you have?
Leaf bar.
I had all the chicken, very old chicken taco.
You might still be
my stomach hurt.
My stomach.
I need to stop eating old food, but I'm trying to save money.
And so I will make a bunch of food.
That is the easiest way to do it.
Yes. And it'll just it'll just sit in my fridge.
And like the thing is, I saw this.
I still have maybe two more tacos worth of this chicken.
So I might eat it again after we're done recording.
I'll do that.
But like, what else am I supposed to?
I can't throw it away.
You can throw it away. Throw it away.
Oh, I can't throw it away. You're right.
You're right, I can't just throw it away.
I mean leftovers are like, you know.
I guess I don't have to eat trash, do I?
Depending on what the leftovers are,
like any kind of meat,
you keep it in the fridge 2-3 days.
Oh, I love to keep my leftovers an hour after and I throw them away.
Even if I don't eat them.
You like fresh stuff.
I would say there are certain things that keep a lot better.
Mashed potatoes last about 90 minutes in the fridge
before they need to be thrown in the trash.
No, you can reheat mashed potatoes.
No, you can't.
In the oven.
Oh, also, I don't have a fucking microwave.
So you know what you can do with old mashed potatoes is make a shepherd's pie.
Put that on top.
Wait, you don't have a microwave.
I don't.
And it depends on how creamy the mashed potatoes.
So I eat the chicken cold.
You're eating the chicken tacos cold?
Just cold as ice, dude.
There's like little bits of like fat.
I don't care about shepherd's pie right now.
I need to get to the bottom of this.
There's little bits of like congealed fat in the taco.
What else was in the talk?
But poop I took and what else?
There was rice in there.
Who puts rice in a taco?
I don't know. I'm asking what's in there.
Oh, it was just it was Greek yogurt.
Pandemic is Greek yogurt, lime hot sauce.
Very old chicken.
Nothing else.
No. OK.
Chicken's a star.
You should have tasted this chicken four days ago.
Incredible.
It just got bad.
It just spoiled.
It was the texture of the tortilla like
Corny, chewy, delicious, perfectly warm.
I actually heated that up on the oven.
Shit, I should really make a shepherd's pie soon.
Shut up about the shepherd's pie.
You don't know how to make a shepherd's pie.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
That's the one thing.
A shepherd's pie is when an Irish guy takes a-
You don't know how to fucking crack on the ground.
I know how to make a shepherd's pie really good.
And I'm gonna make it for Caleb.
I'm gonna make it for Caleb.
And you wouldn't dare make me a shepherd's pie
and give it to me.
I haven't made a shepherd's pie in like 20 years.
I should, oh, I should make that, right?
I'm going to this is the Shepherds Pie challenge on the show.
I'm going to make Caleb a Shepherds Pie.
He's going to eat it and he's going to tell me if it's good.
Why not?
Because I don't eat things.
I don't eat square stuff.
You eat square stuff.
I never eat anything that can be served in a square.
You know what I don't put?
You know what I don't do?
I don't put cheese on the mashed potatoes.
Why?
Because that's not traditional Shepherds Pie.
You should be killed.
I shouldn't.
You should be fucking killed.
I shouldn't be killed.
You're trying to make it like the tradition of the worst cuisine in the world.
It's Gordon Ramsay's recipe.
You don't make Gordon Ramsay's recipe.
I don't.
I make Patrick's recipe.
You take a British man's word for shepherd's pie, dude?
Yeah.
That's fucked.
Who am I supposed to be trusting?
That's very fucked up.
Irish guy.
Oh, an Irish guy?
Yeah, what are you talking about?
You're taking a fucking-
He's Scottish!
No, he's not.
Yeah, he's Scottish.
He's a monkey from Mars.
Look at his face.
Yeah.
It's true.
What are you talking about, dude?
He literally like-
Gordon Ramsay is Scottish.
No, dude.
He was fucking-
He was grown like Little Shop of Horrors and then he fucking popped out.
What?
Yeah.
He was grown?
He's not Scottish.
He was born in Johnstone, Scotland.
Oh, raised in Stratford-upon-Avon, England.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
That's right, dude.
And you're trusting that, man?
That's the guy, yeah.
That's the guy who's...
Maybe you are Italian, dude.
Recipe, you're not Irish now.
No way.
No, shut up.
You just lost your Irish card.
I just got it.
No, this is my...
I got this for...
Christ.
Well, I got a missed call from my mom.
She's calling you to tell you that you're really not Irish.
She just found out.
She's got the results back.
No.
Yep. She just felt the hairs raise up on the back of her neck when you said that you you follow
Gordon Ramsay's recipe for shepherd's pie and she's like I have to call him right now. Well I'm like
I'm I looked at my 23andMe results I'm like British enough. You're adopted. So okay if you're I mean
I'm okay you can say you're British enough that's fine but now that you you're a you're an
you're an Irish LARPer dude. You either claim it or you reject it. Okay.
there's more Irish than there is British. You think that it's good to be both Irish?
You think that Irish people should also be British is what you're saying right now, I think.
That's pretty much the argument you're making to me. I'll say this, British and Irish people are
the same. They're the same. They're not the same. They're the same. I've also been thinking about
this. So if I was a president, I would probably nuke every other country in the world immediately
Because then I could just like watch TV.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's yeah, not a bad plan.
I feel like that's an amazing plan, right?
I mean, you're going to be the one who survives, right?
Like that much this fucking week of people been talking about, like,
oh, Cuba this and there's and there's a ship at China and there's and there's soccer in Europe.
And it's like, shut up, dude.
Can I just fucking watch TV?
That's right.
Fucking annoying me, dude.
Yeah, it's like I'm just done with it.
Like I don't I'm done caring about any other country.
Yeah.
Like I'm just I live here and I'm like,
when that when that Cuba shit's happening.
I'm not going to care.
I don't I don't care when when that did or when it on.
Yeah, the mixing up when it when it happens.
Yep.
Because we did.
We're not backlogging this.
Yeah.
Or when that happened.
Today is.
It's October.
When when when?
How are you guys?
What's your plan to dodge the draft when we invade Cuba?
Um, I won't. Probably.
You won't? I'm gonna be in there.
I'm gonna be cracking skulls, dude. Really?
Yep. The thing is, I- Are you kidding me?
Vacation in Havana? No, you don't vacation.
You have to kill kids. Oh, not if you just tell them you don't want to.
Yeah. Not if you don't.
You say, "Oh, I just wanted to join so I could get, like, the sun and the beach or whatever."
I'm here to tan. I'm in the tanning force.
I'm here with my big reflective piece of metal.
Oh no, I know. I'm one of the guys they sent over just to put more brands into the grocery
store. I don't do the killing stuff.
There's a talking jiff in the Cuban grocery store. Ah, much better. All right, we're done.
Yeah. Dude, I will join the military if I could join the eSports team, I think. Because
they got to have a serious lack of talent.
Oh yeah.
And I would be...
Oh dude, I don't know, they have drone operators.
Those guys are like...
That's not impressive to me.
Those things are heat seeking.
Nobody in the Navy or Air Force has the aim that I have.
We should buy a drone to see how...
We should buy a drone to see inside the girls locker room.
It's so loud.
it's
And you're like, "Oh, that's a fly."
It's a weapon's drone too, like it's a military.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, what's that noise in the air vent above?
Yeah, it just keeps, you said this heat's heating.
It's just Obama's voice.
It just keeps targeting, it just keeps targeting your hot penis.
Oh my God, wait, my recording just stopped.
Oh, are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding you.
You mother fucker.
I'm starting again right now.
It doesn't matter what you say right now or not.
Can we do a clap or something?
No, don't do a clap.
13.59
13.59, let me write that down.
Alright, and I'm not cutting this part out either.
Really? Fuck em.
I was at McDonald's last night.
I was getting McChicken.
Ooooo.
Yeah, and a guy, there were two guys waiting for their orders in front of me.
in front of me. One of them was an Uber Eats driver. And they started having this conversation.
And this one guy was clearly very fucked up on something. And he asked the Uber Eats driver,
"So what are you doing here?" And the guy was like, "Oh, I'm Uber Eats." And then the guy was like,
"I'm Uber Eats?" Uber Eats driver was like, "What?" And then there's a long pause. The guy was like,
No, man, I'm sorry. I just know a guy named Uber.
How do you think honestly, how do you think that's spelled?
He's telling the truth.
Their kid Uber Eats.
I know it might be like Uber Eats or something.
Yeah, my guess is like O-B-E-R-I-Z-E.
Yeah, it's got to be something like that, but it was making me laugh so hard, dude.
I'm so glad I was wearing a mask because, yeah, because it was immediately laughing.
with this crazy virus. As soon as he said, "I'm Upris." That was already, that already hit me,
Guy. I realized today that I've become one of those people who's just like talking all the
time on the street to like anybody who walks by them. Like it shifted like today. Yeah, I did,
like, it's just like, I used to be my like, when you, when, like, when you walk past them,
you can see them kind of like talking to themselves. No, no, it's not even that. It's
like, I will just address everything that happens on the street as I walk by it out loud.
Hey, that's pretty crazy, huh?
Yeah, I got around. Yeah, exactly.
It was like he's like ever since I moved to New York, I've just always been
just like, look at my shoes, like walk around, be quiet.
But today I walked by like two ladies who had their dog
they had their dog leash all spun up.
I did not. I.
Now they did not do giant T-bones covered in barbecue sauce.
But I did. I was I saw that they had their dog leashes all mixed up
between the two dogs.
And I said, Oh, no, they all tangled up now.
And they just looked at me as they're like struggling
to like make their dogs out, bite each other.
Like, what?
They all tangled up now.
You know, they tangled now.
Imagine that the people.
Wow. Well, that's strange.
Hey, everybody, come look at this.
Hey, open up your window.
Look down. There's two dogs tangled up.
I was trying to be friendly, man.
And they just fucking they just give me the icy eyes.
You were being rude.
Man, y'all stupid as hell tangling your dogs up.
[laughs]
You do that voice too?
Yeah, I did.
I hope you were doing that voice.
I was trying to be loud, you know?
That's as soon as I get above a certain kind of decibel level.
Right, let's do a test.
Okay, just start quiet.
Start saying something.
Oh man, they are all tangled up now.
Okay, get a little louder.
They're all tangled up now.
Okay, a little louder.
They all tangled up now!
[laughs]
Okay, what happens if you go,
Oh, what happens if you go loud in that?
Oh, no, they all got tangled up now.
They got tangled now.
If you don't just tangle.
Yeah, my GPS does that, too.
If you turn it up.
Oh, no, you miss.
Oh, you miss.
Oh, come on.
Oh, oh, just does that before every instruction.
Oh, no, no, you got to take a left here, man.
Oh, nah, man.
Man, I've been really stressed out lately
and just kind of like going through situations in my head.
Studied for the SIT.
Yeah, oh man, I can't wait.
PSAT.
I can't wait to go to college again.
But I realized the other day,
I was like just like trying to like figure something out
and realized I was like just like thinking with my hands
and like looked up and saw somebody
And I was just like doing like, just like, okay.
Just like.
- Just going Sherlock Holmes, mind telling.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Like moving equations with your fear.
- As I'm walking, as I'm walking.
So I just look like insanely great.
Like I look insane.
Like I'm like just.
- You kinda look cool, man.
- Just the guy, just like, like you saw me yesterday.
I was wearing like a fucking, like a button down shirt
and like my chain is like hanging out.
And I was like, I just looked so Italian.
- People probably thought I was crazy too.
I was blasting heavy metal music on my headphones to get this.
I wasn't looking where I was walking.
I was playing crosswords on my phone.
Wow.
They probably thought I was like homeless or something.
I was dressed up like a one man band.
Yeah.
Walking around like it was like Dick Van Dyke and I was, yeah, I was in my monster
costume and I was chasing people.
They probably thought I was crazy as hell.
I was walking up to people like, hello, Mary Poppins.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim.
I does what I like.
It's so fucking funny that he was supposed to be British.
I've talked to me. I just thought he was me, man.
I just thought he was mentally impaired.
I didn't think that was supposed to be a British man in that movie.
And then what they had Lin-Manuel Miranda in the in the remake.
Yeah, made that movie.
Because now it was a remake.
I think my mom watched that movie.
Was it like a remake?
Or was it like a making like what was that?
Oh, it was a sequel. It was a sequel of something. It was something weird.
It was like a sequel that was like in the real world or something. I don't remember.
Mary Poppins Returns. What's it called? Mary Poppins Returns? Yeah. Dick Van Dyke was in it.
Really? But Lin-Manuel played that same role?
Lin-Manuel played Jack, a cockney lamplighter. Oh no.
Oh, Jesus Christ. An apprentice of Bert.
I've got the soot on my face, governor.
I've got soot on my face. I love this place.
is
That's right. Yeah. Yeah
Just give me an upskirt scene
Cuz she got that long-ass dress. What you see? Yeah, she floats down on the umbrella - like she comes
Yeah, like it's like be so fucking easy
You know just make him look up once just once. Oh, I'm saying did you show me your thingy?
You know, I don't what I don't want to see Mary Poppins thing. Sorry. Never mind. You're not Italian. I
I changed my mind. You don't want to go up her chimney?
I don't want to see her chimney. You don't want to go chim-chim-ree in her
fucking... I don't want to lift up her... You don't want to do what you like?
I don't want her skirt to lift up and a bunch of soot to come out of the chimney.
I think you do. Just that actually. That's a fucking crazy image.
Just like a bunch of soot hitting somebody's face. Like somebody trying to uproot somebody.
A bunch of shit soot. It just flies out.
Blasting off like a rocket, black smoke all over you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, man.
It's a it's how you prevent it.
It's like when they put the that like red dye all over the money when you steal it.
You know? Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Or or on on like T-shirts at like department stores.
They'll put that like little ink bomb.
Oh, yeah. On the shirt.
You know how to get those off like the the tags is
because I have a bunch of that's just so much clothes.
They're the ones like the circular ones.
You just have to burn the top and the pin comes out.
Yeah. I heard.
And also if you kill the store manager.
Yeah. And I'll put him in the back and then wear his clothes.
Oh, yeah. Kind of magic.
Well, that's the trick. Yeah.
None of the clothes that the that the store workers are wearing
have any have that stuff on them. Yeah.
She thinks they just have to close it to them.
That's the exactly the employees security device. Yeah.
But they're pretty they're easy to remove.
Yeah. Yeah. You just tickle them and they'll leave.
Yeah, then they get they get normal.
They get normal.
I don't know what I'm going to go to a mall recently.
Oh, do you guys want to take a trip to the mall?
Let's go to the mall.
Like, can we just go to the mall?
We got to know I've been saving all this money eating fucking old tacos.
We should go.
I've earned myself a little shopping spree at the mall.
And we go to that mall near the where the Nets play.
The Brooklyn Mall.
Is that what it's called?
I don't know.
The Berkeley Center, the Berkeley.
You guys want to go to the mall and just go to all the kiosks and those stores?
I went to... So I was going to the mall.
Phone cases?
It was my brother's wedding four months ago. And I think, I don't fucking know.
Yeah.
My brother's wedding.
Yeah, this will come out in January.
Okay. So it was my brother's wedding six years ago. And I was trying to... I was like buying shoes.
I was just kind of like walking around because my mom was like shopping. And I got...
there's like a group of kids sitting on a kiosk, like where like a kiosk was.
Yeah.
Like where like a bigger kiosk should have been, but they were all sitting on it.
And I thought they were just hanging out, but like one of them came up to me and was like,
"Yo, yo, yo, yo, what's your name?" I'm like, "Patrick, why?"
They was like, "Yo, I got something for your phasos, dude. Come over here."
And I was like, "No, I'm all set." And I left, then walked back the other way.
And the guy came up to me, same kid comes up to me, he's like,
"Hey man, real quick, let me talk to you." And I was like, "You already fucking tried this."
He was there, it was like these kids. He was chasing you?
He didn't recognize me. He didn't recognize me because he just really, I think I was wearing a
hat actually, you know what? So I did buy a Red Sox fitted at Lids. Why the fuck would he recognize
you? Why would he know who you were? I mean, come on. He's a million people a day, works at a mall,
the most popular place in the world.
It wasn't pop, it wasn't, it wasn't popping then.
It was also sad now, man, you walk through a mall and it's like,
there's, it's like an elephant graveyard.
There's just like, like elephant skeletons everywhere.
There's big bones everywhere.
Hyenas constantly laughing at you.
That one with the crazy eyes and tongue.
Yeah, he weird as hell.
Oh my God.
There's a toucan.
Yeah, that kid.
I, he was trying to sell me like, like, you know, that stuff that you put,
like it was like a shoe restoration kiosk and they were like restoring like like anybody
was wearing Air Force Ones they had like antique shoes on I was walking around in clogs I got
a real good deal on a pair of like curly Victorian elf shoes.
Jing Jing Jing Jing Jing Jing.
Hey you let me clean those shoes up.
Let me lace you up come on.
You got the Air Force 1901s.
[Laughter]
It's just like a
the buckle on the Air Force one
is like an actual, you know, like that little like metal thing
Like Santa's buckle.
It's like a big brass buckle.
I want to go to the mall and I want to go to one of those
toy kiosks where they have like
they have you know something set up where all the toys
are jumping around and they're like
you know they have like a ball toy
that rolls around and stuff. I want to buy out the whole
thing. I want to buy
everything that's on the cart. I want to have a sample smorgasbord.
Yeah. I want to walk up there and I want to say, give me everything.
One of everything on the menu. Yeah. As a sample though,
as a sample I'll be returning. I'll have to pick which one I want.
So I'll be returning all but one later today. Yeah, dude.
I'll up the samples, man. Every time I go, dude, I'm getting full on samples.
I'm not even ordering anything from Chick-fil-A.
We had some Kung Pao chicken.
They don't have samples at the mall now because of COVID.
I don't care.
I'm going to...
They're coming back.
If you...
Maybe you could request.
Oh, maybe you have to...
Yeah, you have to sign a sheet of paper before you get a sample.
Yeah.
It'd still be worth it, dude.
That's a free food.
Proof of vaccination.
I'm trying to save money, dude.
I'm in money saving mode, man.
Yeah.
If you just go to a bunch of different malls...
I'm not even washing my clothes anymore.
...and just get samples every day.
I'm not showering.
You don't have to...
anymore ever again. And you can save up for that guitar at Guitar Center in the mall.
And you can walk in, you could be like, "Can I get a sample of like maybe two eggs
raw? And could I get a sample of some salt and some pepper?"
Yeah, and a fry pan.
"Can I get a sample of a little tiny bit of milk?"
And...
"Can I get a sample of Big Mac sauce? And can I get a sample of hamburger meat?"
Is he doing your grocery shopping?
If you guys want a money move, try going to the bank and asking for a sample.
Yeah.
They have to give it to you.
Oh my god.
Can I get a sample of $1,000?
Like a sample of the millionaire package?
Yeah, like I'm gonna buy a million dollars pretty soon, but I'd like to get a sample of a thousand.
Can I test it out?
Just to test it out, make sure that it's good.
Yeah.
And they'd go, "Yeah, sure."
They handed you a thousand dollars on a toothpick.
I'd love a sample of a cashier's check from that guy's account over there,
wearing the nice suit.
Come on, it's just a sample.
Like I'm gonna...
Yeah.
I'm gonna actually...
I just want to look at the check.
I'm not gonna deposit it.
I just want to make sure that it's a good looking check.
I'm gonna get one myself.
Okay, I'm just gonna go look at this outside for a minute.
Good evening!
I'd like to...
*laughter*
Hello!
A bank?
I had no idea there was one here.
Do you have samples, perchance?
I'd like to cash this cashier's check I just found.
Oh my god.
All right, we have two lists today.
Yeah, we might not get through them.
We might not get through them, but hey, we're taking it.
I mean, whatever the wind takes us today, man.
That's right.
You and Cameron are the wind beneath my wings.
You're a fart.
You're a sweetie.
I'm a fart.
that's wind so I guess
you're saying you're saying you're not really in the forest
ok
yo!
this is the most
yeah
look out for these people
to
It's been laughed out of every scientific community.
- Basically, what is the UN, what's your theory?
- You can make ice at home
by putting a cup of water in the freezer.
- Yeah, I actually have a few formulas
that people haven't really been accepting of.
(coughing)
I had this one formula that was--
- I'm so sick, 'cause you guys aren't laughing at me.
It's this formula called 1 McChicken 219, 2 McChicken 3.
It's equals.
Sounds pretty good.
Yeah, there's equals signs in there too, but I didn't want to give the whole thing away.
I've had this theory that you can age taco chicken like beer, and it will slowly get
better and alcoholic, but it actually just gives you a stomachache and diarrhea when
you're trying to work.
I got to get a glass of water.
That Jool hit really took me out.
You just swallowed a chicken bone.
I think I might have.
I think something's going wrong with me. Maybe I got the Delta variant. Maybe that's why.
That's serious. Yeah.
Do you guys know the Delta variant? You can't even get it if you're vaccinated.
You know that the COVID has been fake this entire time?
It's fucking, it's so stupid dude. Every website is being like, the Delta variant is going
to kill us all. It's like, no, it's just going to kill a ton of people.
I've been faking being vaccinated.
I do like that it now stuff is open
enough in New York that if you weren't
vaccinated, it just doesn't matter.
Like the people at the bar will be like,
hey, are you vaccinated?
You're like, oh, you should have seen
me the day after my shot.
Oh my goodness.
I was, uh, I had, uh, uh, uh, oh my God.
I got a special, the special bed.
They made me lie on to get vaccinated.
Right?
Yeah.
I think they put your beer on the...
It was so sticky.
Watching their reaction to fishing.
I mean the special chair,
the special nurse thing.
They put your drink on the bar
and you try to pick it up.
You're like, "Oh, I can't even pick it up with my arm.
It's so sore still from that damn shot.
I'll have to use my left arm.
Oh, wait, that's where I got the second shot.
Oh my God."
You have a huge straw.
Yeah, man.
My blood was so green the next day.
I just, you know,
right now I just need to sit down at the bar
And the only cure for my COVID vaccine withdrawal is one.
I'm having a withdrawal.
That's how much I got the vaccine.
I mean, I just I need I need two shots, one shot of Jameson
and a third shot, my damn arm.
That's right. Right.
Yeah, I got the vaccine 600 times.
Yeah, I didn't. I didn't just say that you're someone else.
I did my name the first time, and then I said my name was Ricardo Gomez.
599 times. I'm just walking in. Yeah, no, I'm a different Ricardo Gomez from the guy that
you had yesterday. It sucks that I changed my name the week after I got my first shot.
Yeah. Number one, doctor I know what's best. We all know a doctor like that. I would say
most doctors probably think that they know what's best as compared to someone like me
who has never done anything doctor like. It's true. Right. I mean, I'm sick of doctors trying
to tell me what to do. Yeah, stop putting your hand on the stove.
Yeah, I came in here. I came in here to check how hot it gets.
I came in here to draw on the paper that's on the seat. I don't I don't really care about
what you have to say to me. Just shut up. Just shut up and give me my
fucking ibuprofen, you asshole. Yeah, I hand. I touch the stove again. I need
ibuprofen. Just give me the ibuprofen, dude. Yeah, I
know. I want it through my insurance. It's $100 a bottle. Please just fucking give it
to me. They don't sell 200 milligram ibuprofen at the store. You're lying.
They don't sell that there. I asked. Doctors are so bossy.
Yeah. It's like if you, if you put that,
that thermometer thing in my ear one more time,
I'm literally going to kill you. Yeah, I'm going to kill you.
I have a gun in my car. I'm going to kill you.
It would be a fun prank is a, put it like a big piece of like a,
like red wax or something in your ear while the doc,
before the doctor puts that
that little thing in your ear.
Dude, I had the I had the best prank ever.
I said gum.
I swallowed a big a big tumor
and I went and I went,
oh, I think I have stomach cancer.
They totally fell for it.
They're so stupid.
Yeah, so fucking stupid.
I fucking I hate doctors, man.
I dude, I was I was standing.
I was standing.
I was standing right in front
of the microwave dick level.
I went and I said, I think I'm sterile.
They fell for it.
Dude, hook, line and sinker.
Yeah, I mean, I can't have kids now,
But what's that fucking what's that?
What's that little thing around their their their neck?
Are they trying to rob a bank over here?
Why? Yeah, you look like you're about to rob a bank.
Yeah. Hey, your iPod's just a little circle.
Don't think. Yeah, that's got to be the worst iPod ever.
Maybe. Yeah.
It's not going to play any music.
You let me sing into it.
Let me flick it twice, please.
Come on.
I got a miracle.
You know, when you see a doctor on the train on the way to work
and he's humming into his stethoscope
as he forgot his iPod at home.
He's going to do do do do do do do do do.
I got I can tell.
Yeah, this the fidelity of this stethoscope.
Wow. Wow.
The the mids in this are amazing.
Yeah, this really sounds amazing.
Yeah. They always use Tom's Diner by Suzanne Fagan.
Yeah, that is. It's a good benchmark.
Well, it's I would say Tom's Diner is a perfect song
for a human to try to sing by themselves.
That's without any instruments.
It's the only actual acapella song.
Yeah, that's the one that they tested.
That's how they made MP3 was that song.
That's how I made MP3. Yeah.
Yeah. It's fun fact.
I don't know what that means.
I knew I knew Cameron got it.
I knew Cameron got the joke, but I didn't get the joke.
I was just saying that because I didn't know what you're talking about.
I was repeating what you said.
What do you mean they made MP3 with that song?
That song, they couldn't get vocals for MP3 files like they had everything
pretty much set. And then that song is the one that they use to test whether or not the
vocals would work for MP3. Is that true? Yeah, I watched a Vox video about this. Oh, yeah,
I don't watch Vox. I wouldn't know that. That's I watched that one. And then the one it's nice.
Something that's nice about like about like, tick tock and like and like, and like just
all these like YouTube explainer stuff taking off is there some facts that people can tell
you that you instantly know you never have to listen to anything else they say.
Yeah.
Because you know that it's a fact that it's only on TikTok or something.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
I mean, not that that one's one of the pet.
This is an unrelated thing.
Yeah, like, dude, the people are like, "You know we're running out of helium?"
It's like, "Fuck you, dude.
Go home and watch fucking Veritasium, you fucking loser."
Why are you bothering me?
Did you know that we're running out of helium?
No, I had no idea.
Okay, go to the store and get some more, bitch.
What's up?
*laughter*
I fucking love this stuff!
I'm addicted to helium!
Yeah, that's probably just a misinformation campaign.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, that's probably-
Homeless guy on the street who comes up to you and he's like,
"Hey man, can I have five dollars?"
And your dad's like, "Don't give it to him. He's just gonna use it for fucking helium."
He's gonna go to the grocery store and buy balloons.
He's gonna buy some damn balloons, junkie.
Yeah.
lips are like bright purple getting mugged for your iron man balloon that
you're bringing your kids all right sucker
I do love doing that though yeah oh man the high voice on a balloon yeah you
have to like pay back a friend and they're like all right like where's the
I swear, I just, I needed to pay rent.
It's like an intervention.
See, I wish it like, like...
Donald, we know you've been using again.
Shut the f*** up, b***h! What are you talking about?
Yeah, you come home late at night, your dad's like, "Where have you been?"
Nowhere! I haven't been!
I was in the library, I was studying!
Yeah!
Did you go to another damn birthday party?
No!
Somehow have a high burp
Donald yeah, or like I knew you had a problem. I knew you had a problem when you went to my mother's my mother's birthday
Getting you in the garage and you were sucking down
the the middle part of a spider-man
blow up a spider-man
Balloon you in I don't fucking know getting
You suck the six and it looked like she was turning eight
She's not eight!
Getting sold, getting sold your first uh, your first like helium by, by your slacker friend in high school
and like, and like doing it in front of him being like,
"Yeah man, I feel it's totally working. I can feel it. Oh my god."
"My eye is hella right now."
"My eye is hella up there. Damn, I can totally tell it's affecting my voice."
Have you seen that spider man, that like, that spider man balloon where it's like him like
doing like a web crawl and then there's like in the middle it looks like his penis.
He has his wiener out? Yeah.
Yeah, I was trying to talk about that spider-man balloon. I'm so
Times I'm so tired today. I'm ruining the episode. I'm sorry
I'm straight up gonna kill you. I'm ruining. I'm ruining it. I'm ruining all the stuff
Dude, you look so cute when you ruin the episode. Oh god
Did you fucking to keep I'm gonna I'm gonna go throw up now. I'm gonna go don't throw up for no reason
Oh my God, I think I'm gonna puke.
Oh no, God.
Number two type of people in the scientific community.
Number two is Professor Awkward.
Now we didn't read the comment on the Positron Wildhog
writes long blurbs about these ones.
I want to just at least read the first sentence here about Professor Awkward.
Okay.
Which is, "Now here's a character who was photoshopped into our world by a drunk ape."
Facts.
That's true, yeah.
Yeah, so true. I hate Professor Awkward dude. I'm not a fan of Professor Awkward. Yeah.
Professor Awkward. Don't you hate it when Professor Awkward leans over and he farts
in front of the whole friggin' scientific community. And he gets up and he goes "Umm,
up and he goes, Oh, it wasn't me.
Yeah.
And then, yeah.
And the guy next to you turns and says, didn't you used to do
experiments with that guy?
And you say, no, I swear.
No, I don't know who that is.
No, no, I promise.
Um, number three is those excited by boring things.
Yup.
That's a lot of those scientific can tell you a science.
If you're excited by science, you're probably one of these people.
Cause that's boring.
Here's a comment and I think we can maybe, you know, we can talk about this comment,
but my grade seven Polish science teacher.
The way she jumps up and down because she's excited by science.
She's great.
Polish science.
Polish lady.
So she's not jumping up and down because she's excited by science.
She's trying to change the light bulb.
And a reason like jumping up and down because the light bulb finally got
turned on.
Yeah, pull it.
Yeah,
The Polish science class and all the kids are just trying to make a potato battery to power
one light bulb.
Yeah, they're making a potato battery to power the other potato battery.
The top.
Dude, yeah, they have they have like a they have a science lab.
They all put on on like safety goggles and like lab coats and like protective gear, gloves
and stuff.
just trying to pour a glass of water out of a pitcher and it just keeps dribbling down
the side every time.
Put on a full hazmat suit to like take a test.
Yeah.
Alright, today we're going to be installing a screen door on a boat.
Dude, everyone, everyone failed the first two questions on the Polish science test, name
and date.
It was a tough one.
Oh boy.
before the clutts
Oh, the klutzy scientist, the klutz.
That has to have been some like 90s SNL sketch, right?
That's the nutty professor.
Yeah, I guess it was the nutty professor, huh?
But he wasn't clumsy, was he?
He's just goofy.
I he he was definitely nutty.
I mean, he'll a beaker, though.
He took that cool potion.
And that professor.
Yeah.
Well, isn't it funny that that's like a whole like plot point and family matters?
Yeah, it is. It's you know, it's kind of funny that they always that they're always like on TV and movies and stuff. Scientists are always making potions. The potions are magic. They should be making chemicals.
It's true. I agree. Yeah, it's I mean, if you want to make a cool potion, you should have a wizard character in your movie. That's making a yeah, some formula some some just because a potion is in a beaker doesn't make it not a potion.
as far as I can.
Exactly, yeah.
It should be an equation or maybe a model.
Yeah, maybe an equation that makes you fall in love.
Yeah, or a computer program.
Yeah, that would work too.
That would be much more scientific than a potion.
Maybe like a laser?
A laser might work too.
I mean yeah, Flubber would just be a lot better if they were robots instead of Flubbers.
They could call the movie iRobot too.
That would have been cool.
That would be a cool name for a robot.
Yeah, that is a cool name for a robot.
Number five is the idiot, which is, I guess like, yeah, if you had a scientist who was
just like a village idiot style, like eyes going the wrong way, like tongue sticking
out all the time.
Maybe kind of a nutty professor type.
Stop trying to make everything about the fucking nutty professor, dude.
Yeah, he wasn't even that nutty, too.
He's barely nutty.
Are you kidding me?
He was barely even nutty.
Did you see him?
He was going, "Lady!"
it's not very nutty. The nutty professor? He was a lady! I thought that what Eddie
Murphy didn't say that shit. No Jerry Lewis. I'm thinking of Eddie Murphy man.
Eddie Murphy's funny as hell though. I know, hey. Eddie Murphy's funny as fuck. There's a different, that
nutty professor he was just fat. Yeah that's true.
They should have called him the buddy professor because his butt was too big.
I mean, honestly, the fatty fucking shit professor.
The fat, stupid, fat-ass, fucking, overweight, fatty.
He's too fat, he can't do science.
Um, honestly, this list I think we just skip ahead here to number 9.
This is just the, this is.
Number 9 is Dr. Horny.
Oh.
Whoa.
Okay, Dr. Horny.
That's right.
What makes them, what makes them differ from other horny individuals is that they think
they have coined the perfect algorithm for meeting and talking to the opposite sex, often
by outlining that they have fancy-sounding degrees in obscure-sounding areas of research
and often with cheesy lines that relate to such. It just ends with more and more injuries
to the face for them."
"Injuries."
"They're getting hit in the face with a beaker. Because you go over to a lady and you say,
you know, 'I want to get a...'"
"I'm a heliomologist. I'm studying... Did you know that we're rapidly losing helium?"
limited resource. Did you know that I'm rapidly we're rapidly
losing helium?
Yeah. Yeah. And then you like do you work at a grocery store or
a party? So did you know that there have been a series of
break-ins to science labs recently to steal helium? You
should be careful and she's like completely spin for you and
then you get back to to her place. Yeah. It's actually like
yeah. Oh, this is great. Thank you so much for having me over.
Yeah, what the fuck you're lying you're you said you were
Number 10 is a comedian. I think a funny doctor would be funny to me. Yeah, no funny doc
the thing about funny doctors is they're
They're always they're the funny doctors are always just weird
They're not you know, I feel like every every doctor
I've had every comedian doctor I've had is very like I went to the urgent care for a
for a sinus infection and they gave me they gave me Sudafed and the you know
the the lady there was like you know that's that's the stuff that they make
meth with and it's like that's not hmm you should have gone loudly hmm it feels
like that's the that feels like a trap cuz that's like the that's just what
they're setting you up I think I actually have 15 sinus infections all my
friends at home have sinus infections - it's spread around everybody in my
My family has a sinus infection actually.
Yeah, I think I'm going to need that.
I'm going to need that.
15 of my family members, but that is, I mean, that feels like to me.
That's what the funny doctor is always just the doctor who's like, you're not going to
sell this to your friends, are you?
Yeah, it's like their job.
The only actual funny doctor shut up.
The only actual funny doctors are like really, really old doctors who are like refusing to
stop working.
And they're like 90 years old.
I had one and he was like my grandma's friend and he was my family doctor growing up and
he was like completely blind and he did like a physical on me for football.
Yeah.
And he was like, listen, I know your parents.
I don't want to have to touch your balls, but we're going to have to do it.
Yeah.
I think, hey, at least you weren't like excited about it.
Right.
That's kind of funny.
I went to the same.
I think you have demonic humors in your veins.
I'm going to have to bloodlet you.
I went to the same pediatrician until I was like 20 years old.
You went to a pediatrician?
Yeah, I went to the same doctor until I was 20.
And I was like, I can't keep going to a pediatrician.
I'll just never go to the doctor again.
Yeah, I haven't been to the doctor in so long.
Yeah, me neither.
There's no reason to.
I don't think I've been to the doctor since that guy quit because he got too blind.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it's like, what am I going to do?
I'll go if I have a broken leg, maybe.
No, I will go to the hospital.
I don't care, I don't need to go to the doctor.
As somebody who's like as much of a hypochondriac as I am, I'm glad I don't know a doctor right
now.
Exactly dude, that's the thing.
I'd be blowing up their line all the time.
I'd be like, "Yeah, hey I think my brain just exploded."
I think I swallowed a balloon.
I think I'm too high.
I need to I don't know what I did, but I think I'm way too high.
It's a mystery.
Go in there like, yeah, do you smoke?
Do you drink any helium usage?
No.
Yeah, that was always the worst is like until you turn 18,
like your parent is in the room and they'll be like,
so have you ever done anything naughty?
Yeah. You're like, no, never.
No. Good, good, because we actually have a naughty detector here.
Yeah, yeah.
If if it says you did something
naughty, it will give you cancer.
Yeah. And you just you walk through it
like a metal detector and it lights up
and it says like still pokeybomb cards
at age 50.
Yeah. Any any cigarettes, alcohol use
you ever masturbate?
Well, you're probably in the
kitchen. Have you ever masturbated in
their bedroom?
You ever forget to clean it up?
You ever watch Skinamax at night
after your parents go to bed?
On Mr. Skin dot com.
Yeah, have you ever, uh...
Been on mrskin.com, look up...
I'm gonna need you to go down this...
...look up "Judy Professor"
...this list of porn sites and just...
...give me a quick check mark next to them, if you've ever...
Just let me know if you've seen them or not.
...thought about looking at them, um...
And I'll put a star if you use your parents' computer.
You ever watch Family Guy porn on your parents' computer?
We just need to know.
Yeah. You watched South Park before you were 13?
Yeah.
Uh, have you ever seen an R-rated movie? Um...
Have you ever put your mouth on the water bubbler?
Don't call it a bubbler, dude.
It's what it's called, not called a bubble.
It's called the bubbler.
You know, you can't call it the bubbler, dude.
You you didn't fucking grow up here.
The rest of the world.
Everyone in me, I grew up.
No, you didn't want to New Hampshire.
Yeah. Everyone called it the bubbler there.
Yeah. Because there are a bunch of fakers, dude.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, with the bubbler.
Yeah, everyone did.
They are you guys are all just fucking wish you were here dude so bad.
I do.
So bad.
I'm so sick of all the trains here dude.
I know and the money.
Oh I wish I had no money.
Oh my god I wish I was I wish I was I wish I was on Stanhope street.
Me too.
That's right I look at it every day I go huh.
I wish I was on I wish I was on Bromfield street at the Payless Shoes.
That's right.
Is that still no that got turned into one gig.
Let him, uh, let him know.
Uh, second list.
Top 10 silliest things I have a crush on.
I mean, this is like the complete opposite.
Yeah, did you get this one from the
Discord? Yeah, I don't know
who sent it. You gotta figure that, we gotta say
that, man. Yeah. They're gonna sue us.
Fuck them!
That's true, you are, you're our pigs.
Fuck you and shut up.
Yeah, if you sent this, we're gonna ban you.
If you sent this to us, I'm gonna kick you out of the Discord.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
a
who says I don't care obviously you'd have a crush on a boy or a girl for
example I have a crush on a boy named Cal never mind I am a girl why is this
list it's a joke right it doesn't say Cal dude it's just CIL and then there's
two dashes like it's cut off hey Pat
don't chew fucking gum into the microphone dude no keep doing you look
cute. You look so cute. I have to go. Okay, where you going?
Um you want to pick me up later? I have to go to someone's
house in Ridgewood. That's me. Uh Positron Wild Hawk is on this
list too. Oh there he is. While he's in the middle, while he's
in his lab, he's on uh this computer. He says, I cherish my
crush with all of my hearth. I promise to cushion her falls and
wouldn't give her up for the world.
It's a magical IKEA.
What are you doing a bit of a
come there positron you?
You're not only a scientist with science,
you're also a word scientist.
It seems number two number
two a glass of milk.
When I was a toddler,
I loved my bottles low key.
I fucked with milk.
Yo, yo, y'all remember?
Y'all remember as a kid?
Y'all remember playtime and mill?
Real no no.
I didn't have none of that shit, I just had milk.
Uh, number three, a rock.
Why would you do this?
Misfire says, "I have a crush on my pet rock named We Will Rock You."
Hmm, maybe I should name him Rocky Raccoon instead.
What do you think?
I think you should totally change that name.
Yeah, I think you should stop having a crush on your pet.
Just make it lose like a handsome anime guy.
Just 'cause a pet is a rock doesn't mean you're allowed to have a crush on it.
You can't have a crush on a pet.
That's not, that's no bueno.
is
demologically.
Maybe.
Number four, a book.
Yeah, what if it's a pop
up, though?
Yeah, that doesn't count.
Yeah, that's also like, I mean,
there's like sports illustrated
fucking swimsuit edition.
That's a book. I have a crush on a
book. It's a magazine.
That's a book.
It's a magazine.
Some pages.
No, there's no pages.
There's pages on the book.
There's no girls all.
OK, but it has no you
You can't keep it on the shelf though.
So how about this Cameron?
A dictionary of hot swimsuit girls.
That might be a book.
That might be more than a book to me.
That might be a lifestyle.
Let me tell you about the B section.
*whistles*
Seriously some boobs on that.
*laughs*
It's not like names or anything?
No, it's different parts of the girl.
There's bras too.
the
is a stack section brain, beard, brain, yeah. Mm-hmm. No, yeah, A is great too. Belly. Ass,
Adam's apple. Yeah. Actually, her boobs. Yep. A one, A big boob, A small boob. Yeah. A, A hole.
Yeah. A, A, A finger, another finger. A finger in her thing.
Let's see, C is good too. Crap. Crap? No. Crap hole.
Chest. Cummer. That's what we call her thing. Corneas.
Her corns. She's got corns on her feet. Her shoot, maybe? Her shoot H.
or C H U T E
clavicle
cra-
cranny
her cranny
oh my god
her her
her ker-
her gina
that crazy pussy
her
that's under T, Caleb, that's under T
creepy
that's under T
that's under D
started the T section
creepy zone
the D and the T section are very similar
cause the D section
a lot of that is that
yeah
that thang
That thing.
That boobs.
Da pussy.
Yeah, no, and A and D are also similar.
A and D are also.
Oh man, yeah, I mean that dictionary.
I would get a box set.
It's only 50 pages.
Yeah, they sell it at the, I got it at this Scholastic book fair.
It was the most expensive book they had.
It cost 500 tickets.
it's
and there could be a mouth on the other side.
*laughter*
Very good point.
Yeah, you like walk up to a glory hole and you put your dick in
and you get a sug, and you're like, "This fucking wall
is so amazing!"
"I want to marry this wall!"
"What kind of wall is this?"
Also, putting a glory hole
on a door and then somebody just opens it
and just slams you into the wall.
*laughter*
Shouldn't be on a door.
You're flattened on the wall adjacent to the door and your dick is hanging out of the door.
They'll think your dick is the doorknob.
Yeah, that's true.
They'll yank it right off.
Twist it around.
They'll try to put a key in your thing hole.
Number six, a bar of soap.
I've had a fair amount of soap on my penis.
You put a hole in a bar of soap and put your thing through it, huh?
I mean, I wouldn't be like opposed to that, I guess.
I mean, yeah, I feel like that's like a probably feel pretty good, right?
I don't know.
Plus, you can clean your penis with it.
That's true.
They do.
They do have at Spencer's gifts.
They have the weenie cleaning, which is a ring of soap.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Do you guys what would you guys do if you if if you worked at like Dunkin Donuts or
something a really creepy guy came in and said, "Can I get the warmest, slipperiest donut
that you have?"
And what's the bathroom code?
Yeah.
Can I get a Boston cream?
Only put a little bit of cream.
And microwave the cream.
Yeah, and microwave the dough.
Could you pour orange juice on a croissant and then heat it up for a little bit and then
give it to me?
No, I don't need a bag.
I'll just put it in my hands.
Thanks.
Yeah.
donut where there's a hole and there's a special part above the hole that's really extra special
and like a big sprinkle on the top of the donut and but make it a little hard to find and I'm
and could you guys not look at that corner for a minute yeah I'm only gonna need two
minutes I mean well to eat the donut two minutes average yeah number seven a box well the top
if they're not me anything box can actually mean quite a few things yeah
the comment is the sexy box number eight a fictional character yeah so here's a
comment from Patrick but I've pretty much only ever liked fictional
characters since I was three years old right now I have a crush on Luke
Skywalker if that's so silly I must be quirky. Wow, Patrick, that's a great comment.
You're really good at typing you're getting a lot better. Here's another comment.
Here's another one for Patrick. That's both bestiality and pedophilia because Elmo is a
three-year-old monster. Not replying to anything. No one said anything about Elmo. Here's a comment
here from Caden Young that just says what? I had a thought about Elmo today. I was thinking about
I was thinking about calling him because I'm like best friends with that guy.
You're not best friends with Elmo.
But if you are, can you ask him what he looks like if you shave all his hair off?
Yeah, I want to know.
I could ask him.
What does he look like?
Does he look like a dog?
Probably like, probably red, but with no hair.
He might look like a bird under there.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't think so.
I mean, if you shave off Elmo, you'll see his bones.
True, yeah.
He might just be bones underneath.
He's got bones and fur, yeah.
Skeleton, those guys.
He's all bones under the fur.
(laughter)
Number 9 is DIRT
DIRT?
Minecrafter1212
says "haha I don't know why this is
so funny to me" Probably cause of Minecraft
That's a Minecraft ass comment my friend
Dude there's so many on here we gotta go
lightning round. Alright lightning round
Pop singer
Picture of Justin Bieber
Mud. Loaf of bread. Yourself.
An ironing board. A celebrity's butt
Here we go. Top comment
Anaconda don't want none.
Your reflection, a skeleton, a toy, broken condom.
A parody music artist, a gorilla.
Probably should have just done this list.
Now, a broken condom.
You already said that one.
There's number 47 here.
Number 47 is a baby.
And the comment is only pedophiles would have a crush on a baby.
Number 67 is a dictator.
And it's a picture of Hitler.
Oh my God, my friend literally has a crush on Joseph Stalin.
Not kidding.
A cat number 72 a video game.
I have a crush on Mario Kart 8 because it's so amazing and I
love it.
A smartphone one of your comments posted online is over
73 year but oh that's that's not right.
Bye bye.