Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
[Music]
Crap monster.
[Explosion]
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
We have a big discovery here.
Our sommelier here, sommelier Duran.
Yes.
Who's, who's, I think he's, what are you going to be training him?
I've acquired, I've acquired two.
Monkha?
Huh?
What is that?
Monster.
And what's next on the tasting menu, Ossemelier?
Well, hold on, let me just...
Un Lois?
Le Biste?
Oh, you said...
I thought you were saying what's next as in the other drink I have here.
No, what's next on the tasting menu?
Well, here we have a 2015 Monster Energy.
Oh, that's lovely.
And where was it grown?
This was grown in South Africa in 2015.
Oh, they have beautiful monsters there.
Have you been to Monster Valley in South Africa?
It's so arid. It gives so many... and could you have a sip for us?
You gotta...
That's right. And how is it? Is it earthy?
It's... it tastes like I'm gonna throw up.
And what are the notes?
Notes of expired.
Okay, and the tannins?
in
layer. There's no way I am not going to get... Do you mind if I try, if I partake? You can
have some. Let's see. Yeah. I mean it tastes like regular Monster. It tastes like they're
hiding something. Yeah. I would say. It's very syrupy. Yeah. No, it's definitely, I can tell
that I got one of the sips at the bottom, I can tell that's where a lot of the flavor is condensed.
Yeah. And this...
Wait, listen to how thick it is.
Sure, let's hear.
It has a very syrupy kind of attribute.
To be clear, this is...
I think maybe I'm going to stop drinking this.
Yeah, this is actually a 2015 Monster from South Africa that Patrick found in the bodega.
Yeah, I picked it up and I was like, "This can feels a little bit taller."
And the tab didn't have any logo on it.
No marking on it.
No markings on it. No texture on the can.
Luckily, you did yourself a big favor.
I did myself a big favor because I thought that this was a normal can and I thought it
would be funny if we did a taste test.
Yeah.
Well, what happened with the monster though is you went into the bodega and you were like,
can I see your South African room?
And they took you to the back and there was a room with paintings on the wall.
They walked into a cellar.
Like a mural on the wall, like a forest.
They pulled one off the rack.
He held it on his forearm like this, the can.
He said, here we have a beautiful 2015 invention.
There's a huge painting, Nelson Mandela in that basement.
But I thought this would be great for the show if we review...
Let's take a picture of this can here.
This is Raptor.
I believe it's Raptor.
Raptor.
Raptor Energy.
Sparkling energy drink.
And does that, correct me if I'm wrong, does that say that this can costs $99?
This can costs actually 99 cents.
- No way. - This has got to be
the steal of the century.
- Oh my goodness. - Sorry, oh my God.
South African monsters attack.
- You're in trouble.
- Yeah, that's not, that would not come up good.
- No, I saw, I've never seen you burp like that.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Oh man. - That was like
when your mouth wiggled like in a cartoon burp.
- Yeah, you can see the air rippling
like a screaming superpower.
- Let me read the ingredients of Raptor here.
Carbonated water, sugar, taurine, citric acid,
maltodextrin. - It has esterate in it.
natural and artificial flavors, caffeine,
D-glucoronusnate,
inositol,
sodium citrate,
caramel color,
niacin,
- Hey, that's like an apple.
That's pretty close to an apple.
- Pyridoxine, hydrochloride,
calcium, okay, vitamin, okay,
it says next to their names,
it's the vitamins that they are.
So vitamin B5, sodium benzoate.
It's a healthy one.
Yeah, it's got vitamins in it.
Cyanide.
Cyanocobalamin.
I know, all right, I know that you're not supposed to eat many things that start with
cyan.
Cyanocobalamin.
Yeah.
That's probably fine though.
That's vitamin B12.
Oh.
Yeah, it's not cyanide, it's cyanara powder.
Which makes you say cyanara.
Each serving of Raptor contains 1,419 milligrams of taurine and 141 milligrams of caffeine.
So and can you tell me what is there any kind of symbol on this that indicates how safe it
is?
There is a triangle with an exclamation point in it.
And that usually, so I drive a lot.
I know you guys don't drive but basically that's like, you know there's a stop sign?
That's like the go sign.
That's like exciting.
Yeah.
That's like, that means here we go.
That means you can go really fast, very safely.
Yeah, yeah.
It says that it is a product of Guatemala.
Guatemala?
Oh!
They have great raptor plants there.
Alright, now we need to get a taste here. Taste test it for me.
I'm not kidding, that tastes like sweet tarts.
Give me a fucking sip of this.
It tastes exactly like sweet tarts.
Let's try this thing out.
All right.
I would like to...
It's the exact color of piss and pee.
Yeah.
Piss and pee.
That's crazy.
That tastes exactly like a sweet tart.
Honestly, it's not too sweet.
Damn good energy drink.
I'm not going to lie about Raptor.
Honestly, I had my doubts going into this.
I was like, "Oh, this has an emergency label on it."
It's sour.
It's a little sour.
It's got a Raptor on it.
also says on it says serve chilled with Tori yeah yeah you put a little
closer to you yeah I'm sure those are supposed to be separate things yeah
there's supposed to be an extra tour in the fucking thing there's so much
touring in this what the fuck is touring what is to know why do we let that why
do we let that be in every drink now but nobody knows what it is I think touring
is like...
Siri, what's taurine?
It's easier than Google.
That's why Red Bull is called Red Bull.
It's an organic compound that is widely distributed in animal tissues.
That's great, thank you Siri.
They're putting fucking meat glue in the shit now?
Is it...
What? I don't know.
Is it meat glue?
I don't know.
Sounds like meat glue.
Damn.
That means that like...
It's not vegetarian.
What's it supposed to do for me though?
Right.
Like caffeine makes me go...
Oh, it must be from the raptor.
Oh, it must be the blood of the raptor.
Yeah.
I mean for 99 cents.
Caffeine?
With that much taurine for 99 cents?
Ginseng gives you boners, caffeine makes you shit.
What is taurine doing for me though?
Taurine I think is the energy.
Yeah, the strength and agility of a monster or a raptor.
Really? It turns you into a new beast?
Yeah.
The second sip was not as good as the first.
Really? It's one of those?
It coats your tongue once?
Uh-huh.
Let's see.
Oh, by God.
What's going on in the bottom of the can there?
Can you tilt that back slightly again?
Energy drink.
What is that?
That is a dent.
There's a huge dent.
Okay.
It looked like a bulge when I saw it at first.
I was like, "Oh, you guys are going to die."
See bottom of can for lot number and expiration date.
All right.
When did this expire?
Check the EXP.
EXP, BBD.
It's not a day.
24.
The year 24
Makes way more. Oh, yeah, it's for fucking cavemen. Yeah back when dinosaurs are alive in the year 24
My teeth do not feel good right now. Yeah. No, I feel brush my teeth so hard after this
I feel like you know that guy who pitched a no-hitter on LSD. Yeah, we're about to do that
Yeah, this might be the best episode ever be no jokes. We're gonna be completely just like yeah, it's gonna be revelation
See I'm already fucking myself up man.
Revelation.
Revolutionary.
It won't be a revolution but it's going to be a revelation.
It's a sparkling energy drink.
Yeah.
What is it though?
That first sip I will say, that was good.
Yeah, if they could replicate that first sip for like 60 more sips, it might be a pretty
alright energy drink.
Stop burping dude.
I'm going to call 911 if you keep burping for the monster.
It also says, I'm going to start floating.
It says refrigerate after opening.
Immediately after opening.
It says refrigerator after opening.
Do not microwave.
Oh, that's what the exclamation point is.
Yeah.
Man, it's always good when it has like a...
Do not introduce bacteria into this.
That's like, have you seen the Arizona energy drinks?
The other ones that are also a dollar.
The ones that say RX on them, like they're medicine?
And they have, but they have medicine, the RX medicine thing,
Rx medicine thing but then the label is like the fucking like red and or the
yellow and black stripes like yeah yeah yeah that's all I like that as the new
that's the energy drink drink branding is like this is dangerous this will kill
you yeah gonna fucking Red Bulls the only one that is classy look yeah red bull
tries to class it up I'm reading the the nutrition facts on rap tour what do you
got um well it's got for a daily daily values wise this is a hundred and six
percent of your daily value for sugar.
Oh, but what's making me laugh here is that it's vitamin B6.
It's 420%
That's a funny things about the energy drinks because I'm getting
so many vitamin B and shit is like insanely cheap.
So they just dump like a crazy amount like it should it's
probably like a toxic amount of vitamins.
Yeah, like it always will be like a thousand percent of your
vitamin D for the day.
Yeah.
Oh, but here's a good thing if you have like an allergy.
If you're deficient on...
Zero vitamin D.
Oh.
Yeah.
If you're deficient on taurine, this is one of the best drinks you can get.
Or if you're anemic, it has zero iron in it.
Nice.
Yeah, they take care of that with a can.
Oh, if you're anemic, you eat the can when you're done.
Yeah.
Well, no.
It's a cast iron can.
You can swallow the tab.
Yeah, it's like a pill.
or just you know the the liquid in the can is corroding the the can it's
you know you're getting this done we're like if you cook in it you're supposed
to get what gives you iron so weird that we need to eat a metal I don't think
that's true about cast iron I think that is true that's like one of the things
about it is it likes put some iron in your food I don't think that is true I
think it's true like it's good I think so I feel like whoever I feel like
whoever's right I could say I was on their side well okay so like with with
like a pie with Teflon pans like a nonstick pan yeah that shit's that makes
you proof yeah so it's the same thing with cast-iron third sip not bad let me
try the third hold on we got a real we're rethinking this as we you know we're
about evolutions here that's true well I'll be damned yeah you waited longer
yeah yeah that's true I think maybe there's gases being expunged from the
can yeah this is it I can there's something in the air in this apartment
since you open that can yeah give it a really strong is the spirit of the
Raptor the Raptor gave its life yeah it's very Native American style drink
I'm saying Raptor a bunch it what it is Raptor it's Nate what are you talking
about you stupid Native Americans yeah that's he runs with rock oh come on dude
I forgot it really is called rap tour because there's a line break between rap and tour and the like the little trademark symbols after rap
Oh, yeah, it is two words. Yeah, that's rap tour
Man, it's not rap. You're good
No, that makes sense
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna revolutionize the world with the rap tour episode. Yeah, I think I think I gotta pour these out
Don't waste the the ambrosia. Just go refrigerate it. Waste the ambrosia. Ambrosia is nectar of the gods.
Well, I drank two energy drinks back-to-back now. Why?
Hey, it's okay. Coffee. You need to drink coffee?
Yeah, can you make me some coffee? No, that's not tasty. I don't have any coffee. I'm sorry.
That's great for me right now. Some coffee. A third drink.
Yeah, some green tea. A third drink to put in my body. I have a five-hour energy you could chug. Really? No.
That one I think is most diabolical one. Yeah. Yeah, it's all the same shit, but they they mini-meet it
They made it and made it stronger somehow like mini-me exactly strong package small package
Yeah
Think about five hour energy to me is it looks like you know those those tiny little like party popper things you pull the string
And I like shoots out confetti and like yeah, it kind of look the container kind of looks like that to me
So I feel like that's how it should be
It also looks like poppers.
You should pull a string and it should shoot the drink into your mouth.
That's a good idea.
You should be able to load it into a gun and put it in your mouth and pull the trigger.
Because that's really what you want to do.
Anytime you buy a 5-hour energy.
If you have to buy 5-hour energy, you've got to get your life.
I feel like you've got to turn your life around at some point.
Monster would genuinely make a killing if they made tiny containers of monster.
They're shaped exactly like bullets.
Definitely.
would be more of a I would say that would be like a bang kind of product.
You've seen like you see a monster monster does the the army themed one.
Oh yeah.
And then that's like yeah monster assault and it's like this is not political.
Yeah.
We don't we don't have any opinions about war or soldiers.
The entire thing is Israel themed.
Yeah yeah.
Like no it's not political at all.
It's actually meh.
Yeah.
That's cool.
We just think it's awesome.
Do you guys ever know anybody took caffeine pills?
No but I've been thinking about it.
do it dude. Why would you do that? You're so bad. I've been thinking about it. Dude, I want to go full
Jesse Spanos. I want to get like, take a bunch of caffeine pills. You guys come over my house,
I'm in my living room just like singing. Well somebody's cord is fucking... Mine? Freaking
out again. I don't know. I have the good cord I think. Oh, I guess I just have to watch the
recorder until someone messes up again. Alright, I'm not going to mess up, I promise you. I knew
some like like a trucker guy who would take caffeine pills that seems to be the
main thing that they sell them for yeah yeah have you seen that episode of save
by the bell? That's also what like diet pills are right? For truckers? No.
It's just caffeine right isn't it? Yeah. It's just like stimulants and shit.
Yeah. I gotta drive fucking six hours tomorrow but I'll be damned if I didn't
take my hydroxycut. People wonder how I do it. I think it's Caleb who's
Who's fucking, who's cord is fucked up?
Maybe it's your mic, whatever.
Not much we can do.
- Well, fuck you everyone.
- Wait, did you get rid of the bad cord?
- No, it's right there.
- You're probably using it.
- No, 'cause this is the rigid one.
I know that this is the good one.
- All right, whatever.
- I mean, we can switch 'em.
- Nah, it doesn't matter.
- This guy don't give a fuck.
If it does it again, we'll switch 'em, try 'em out.
- Okay.
- Have you seen the, you haven't seen
the Saved by the Bell episode?
- Why have you watched Saved by the Bell?
- I watch Saved by the Bell every morning
23 year old man. I was like eight. What? Yeah. It was on TBS. They played two episodes of Saved by
the Bell. I would finish my breakfast and then watch Saved by the Bell. In the morning before
school? That's a dangerous before school show. Any school show, put you in the wrong headspace.
That's right. You go to school, you think that you can talk to the camera. Yeah. You're sitting
there in class, just like. Or on flipping over people's lunch trays. You know? Yeah,
Yeah, you think you can freeze time like Zack Morris?
Exactly, yeah, no.
Now, with that episode, Jesse starts taking caffeine pills so she can study for like the
SATs or some bullshit, but she also has a big concert at the Max.
No.
And so she gets addicted to caffeine pills and she passes out and Zack goes to her house
and is like, "Oh, Jesse, where were you?
You missed the big concert."
like no I oh no I need more pills and it's supposed to like it was the episode
that was supposed to tackle addiction but she's addicted to fucking caffeine pills
she's in her bedroom just like there's like a really funny scene where she's
like screaming scream singing yeah you're right they should have done that
episode with heroin instead there was a couple of shows like that like yeah like
see like ABC family shows about where like the middle schooler comes home and
like yeah out of his backpack like a heroin needle drops out yeah it's
pretty like are you serious man yeah yeah it's like that's how you would react
there was a that's not cool yeah no yeah this ends today yeah there was that's
are all gonna think you're lame that's like you have to stop with reverse
psychology yeah your friends are gonna make funny because you're so skinny now
do they so none of your friends know what the velvet underground is I think
that's cool at all. There's an episode of... man, they don't have those anymore.
PSA episodes? Yeah. Like that was a big Reagan era. They still do. They do.
No, they still do. They just don't watch the shows that have them anymore.
I think like... What, all of them now are like PSAs for like parents who don't
understand like what a transgendered person is? Yeah, yeah. You're right. Yeah,
it's always like, it's like way like weirder issues now than like...
- Well the thing, the thing, the thing.
- Like the yells are like transgender issues.
- You said that, not me.
- No, no, you said it.
- You said it.
- The PSA episodes I've seen are ones on like Netflix shows
where it'll be like somebody wants to commit suicide
in the episode and then at the end of the episode,
it'll be like, it'll be like,
if you or someone you know is contemplating suicide,
please go to netflix.com/suicide
for resources to help you.
(laughing)
It's like so fucked.
- Yeah.
- It's all, yeah.
- It's, it is, it does feel like the PSAs used to be like,
like uh... yeah this is that this is the order is it smoking correct no they're
way we're it's like but but in a different way it was like this kid is
smoking crack in his parents
uh... don't know what to do or whatever
like this kid wants to kill himself
and now there will be like a netflix cartoon like made for babies and then
there at the end of the more will be like
sometimes it's okay to be grumpy
yeah
sometimes you know anybody anything you can be grumpy sometimes
you know that you're most it's not okay to be grumpy though
You don't have to be your best self all the time.
And also, meditation is very valid.
- Therapy is good.
- Yeah, it's like, "Shut up, you pussy."
- Yeah, "Grow up."
- "Make the kid smoke crack again."
- Dude, I missed that.
- I want the Amazing World of Gumball kid,
whose name is, I think, Amazing World,
to smoke crack in the show.
(laughing)
- Man, there's a different Strokes episode
my mom's friend used to talk about
where like
encounter a pedophile
that's
yeah i mean that's crazy that is crazy but i think that like back in the seventies
like they just had like a
but they put pedophiles on t_v_ now you know i was happy again some work though
fuck you
what you play think i was in the i was in a row in the seventies yeah yeah
yeah yeah you were you are
You were a pedophile.
No.
You didn't know that you were on the show.
I mean, you know, I just thank God that they had, you know, back then they had people like,
you know, Jimmy Savile on TV to like pick up the slack, to, you know, tell people that
those things aren't real.
I mean, the thing about the 70s is back then they couldn't, they had to teach like anti-pedophile
rhetoric on TV shows because like they only hired pedophiles to be teachers.
like they would just they would just omit it from the curriculum yeah they would
just be like I don't feel like teaching this do you think someone like Jimmy
Savile like saw that different strokes episode and was like I was saying oh
wow this is bullcrap did he sound like that yeah he's British I don't think he
sounded like that though yeah what's always seen I was I don't think he did
that it's crazy that that guy looked that scary and people were like what
"Jimmy Savile's a pedophile? No!"
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, "What are you fucking... that guy looks like he kidnapped kids."
Not Slimer from Ghostbusters.
You're telling me he's bad?
You're telling me that he's going around the city scaring people?
Wait, Slimer's sliming people?
No.
Are you fucking kidding me, dude?
That can't be true.
Yeah, he just eats hot dogs.
Yeah, I thought he was just, I don't know, green?
I guess that's more of a hindsight thing.
Yeah, and then they do all the... and then Bill Murray comes out and says, "Slimer
slimed me on the set of Ghostbusters." I was actually slimed. The director didn't
stop us. It was directed by Vincent Gallo. He actually let him slime him. He was
really fucked up. Yeah. I was talking to Cam about this earlier, so like Emily
Radajowski said that that guy Robin Thicke like groped her on the set of
Blurred Lines, right? That's the music video. You remember that song?
Yeah.
So I read that story and I was like, "Oh my God, that's fucking awful." I read that this
morning and I was walking around doing the dishes the entire morning like, "I hate that
Blurred Lines." It's such a good song.
I mean, you know.
It's like the best song ever, dude.
Pharrell is an amazing producer.
Dude, it's so fucked up.
He knows how to write a fucking hit.
Dude, it's the same thing with R. Kelly. We're like, "Anytime anybody brings up R. Kelly,"
and they're like, "Oh, it's horrible."
It's like, "Oh, fuck him."
I'm at dinner talking about, "Oh, God, what a horrible story."
Go to the bathroom, "Is that Reema doing this?"
I mean, fucking, what was that other R. Kelly song?
I remember, dude, in college we had a class where we just watched the R. Kelly documentary.
Yeah, trapped in the closet?
That's so funny.
That's so funny. We watched the R. Kelly documentary and then like immediately after we watched
like 15 R. Kelly music videos in a row. And then that was like where we started the discussion
was like okay you saw one side now you see the other. Now let's watch double up. Let's
watch same girl. Yeah. I mean pretty you know. Dude that fucking that video of him I think
he's in uh... e_c_o_p_ ur somewhere at lake
he's doing a concert where he's like
who wants to go home with robert
iso for the money will that is one of the funniest looking videos like it's
like
the band behind us on like
and this is a
who wants to
do you have your passport
so it's a little more people to use
you use
uses uses grooming people
in the crowd public the other side of them
I wish none of those missionaries were fucking
kinda jumping from his penis like a bullet.
All the missionaries in the R. Kelly show?
You know?
They're singing like fucking
bump and grind.
Yeah dude, it's Ethiopia dude.
Ethiopia's like half missionaries at this point.
They're pumping them out of fucking Georgia.
Just sending them to Ethiopia.
Yeah.
These dudes are just going down there.
They're all trying to make the
big money on 90 Day Fiance.
Yeah, they go to like a normal
Trent Lee Brampton's going down to Ethiopia with a Bible in his hand.
They will go to Ethiopia and raise all this money and be like, "We're gonna go to
Ethiopia and build a well, a water well." And they'll go to like the middle of a
city and then just put like a well in the street. In the middle of traffic.
Like a very like big city. Yeah, huge city.
Running water. Every single house. Just put a well in the middle of a park.
We did something great here today.
Yeah, or they'll buy a family a goat
in the middle of like fucking Mozambique or something.
Right.
It's like a family that lives in like an apartment.
Yeah, exactly.
They're like, "Great, now we have a fucking goat. Thanks a lot. Cool."
"You don't even have a fucking room to put..."
"This is a two bedroom."
"Thanks a lot. Yeah, no, I'm gonna pray to God now. Thanks for the goat, you fucking asshole."
"Thank you Christ for giving me this fucking goat. It's gonna eat all my shit."
"Yeah, he takes shit the size of an Xbox. Thank you very much."
Oh great, the goat got into the pantry and ate a whole can of beans.
Cool, yeah, the goat ate my kid's hat.
And his hair.
Thank you so much, this is an awesome gift.
Sick, yeah, oh yeah, he just kicked the TV.
Great.
They need to be sending, missionaries should be sent to like, like Mars and Jupiter.
They gotta go to Antarctica in case the thing, we gotta teach the thing about Christ.
If we got the thing on Christ's side, that might be a huge weapon against the enemies.
you know? Yeah. All of Christ's enemies. Did you guys, no one ever tried to trick you into going
on a missions trip growing up? I mean, not yet. No? No. They tried to ship me out. I'm sure somebody
was like... They tried to ship me out to China, bro. I'm sure if somebody was like, you know,
just very nice to me and they did something for me, I'm pretty sure they could trick me into going
going on a missionary trip?
- They tried to send me to China.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
They said, "Caleb, you're one of the best agents we have.
"We're gonna send you on an extremely dangerous mission."
- Yeah. - And I said,
"And where am I going?
"Am I going to Syria?" - Yeah, there's this guy
named Jack Ma.
- They said, well, no, they said that they wanted me
to go convert Jackie Chan.
- Wow. - They wanted me
to do the honors.
They said, "You're almost, if we could get Jackie Chan
"on our side, the devil, no weapon forged
"against Jackie Chan shall prosper."
That's true.
I mean, think about it.
Jesus Christ, Jackie Chan, two Jaycees.
Jaycee.
Two Jaycees?
It's over, dude.
You have two Jaycees on your side?
I think we've already seen the second coming.
Every Jaycee is one of the greatest men of all time.
Jesus Christ, Jackie Chan, Jamal Crawford, Los Angeles Clippers, John Carpenter, Jadov
Chitler.
That's not J.
No, Jadov Chitler.
You don't know him?
Jadov Chitler.
Adolf Hitler yeah
It rhymes with that asshole that piece of shit fucker Adolf Hitler, but I didn't even think about that no I
People think I'm saying that when I talk about him Jadolf Chitler Jadolf Chitler remember
Time did remember that time he bought us all that beer near underage. Oh, he was so awesome
He was I mean his you know his jet ski was so cool. He was is so beautiful, dude
I probably should not have made that joke. He had a bonus room, remember?
J-Dolph? He had a bonus room in his house. Yeah.
Had a foosball table, big-ass flat screen TV, surround sound.
Oh my god. 7.1.
Yeah. Yeah.
Real nice German fella.
It was not German.
Oh really?
The opposite of German.
What's the opposite of German?
Austrian.
(laughter)
- Strong point.
- Yeah, that is a good point.
- He was Austrian, I forgot about that.
(laughter)
- Oh no.
- Okay.
- Fucker.
- So speaking of Adolf Hitler, which we weren't, but--
- No, you're talking about Adolf Chitler?
- Top 10 grossest things on the top tens.
dog poo vomit i've personally taken the liberty to delve into these gross
abominations just to give you the necessary info
that's very kind
this guy's an undercover brother
number one... that's not the term
I gotta re-watch that movie undercover brother? it's so good. I want to join the
CIA as an undercover brother
I'm gonna go to Langley, I'm gonna turn in my resume. I'd like to become an undercover brother please
you're just neil patrick eris' character in that movie. I would like to become an
undercover brother right now, thank you.
Yeah, when he has the watch that squirts hot sauce into the mayonnaise.
It's pretty fucking cool. Says that is the funniest fucking thing. It's a good movie.
I haven't seen it, I don't even know what it is at all.
It's about a little brother
who goes to high school, pretending to be a high schooler so he can
hang out with his big brother it's one of the sweetest movies of all time it's
called undercover brother. That's not it. It sounds awesome. Yeah it is. No you're thinking
of Big Brother Little Brother. Oh. No, Undercover Brother is when it's like a
Wayans Brothers movie where one of them is a like a little person criminal. Oh
yeah. Yeah and he pretends to be a baby. Yeah he's undercover as a baby. Wait I forgot about that.
movie? Little Man? Remember there's a movie where he like, where he tries, where he gets
a girl to breastfeed him? Yeah. The part where he's like, this lady's like, oh, he wants
to breastfeed, here, you can use my huge tits. And he's like, he's like a grown man. It's
a fucking crazy movie, dude. That sounds sick. Yeah. We gotta do a Little Man rewatch. Do
you know what Little Man, you've never seen that? No. No. Look up the poster for Little
man right now. I'm gonna love this. Really good poster. Yeah. My fucking space bar is broken.
Oh your space bar is broken? How did that happen? It just happens all the time. That's like
the crown jewel of the keyboard. It always gets stuck all the time. Oh this is a cool
poster. Man. From the guys who brought you White Chicks. That would be... Little Man.
That would be such... Loaded with extra crap edition. Woah! Oh come on man I love extra
crap. I would order a poster to get on it on DVD PSP and Blu-ray.
We get an office dude little man little man poster right in the
original one. We're gonna get it signed. Oh we get this one poster
little man cave. We need a space where we can spread out as guys.
You want to give us an you gotta get this as opposed to a little
man white chicks double feature double feature. Holy **** with
the DVD logo. Imagine watching those two back to back. I mean
it's crazy how good white chicks is and then how terrible
little man is. Well because white chicks is a perfect comedy, like perfect idea for
comedy right? Yeah. Is Wayne's guys pretending to be white women. White women.
So funny. And then little man is just like... Did you kind of think they were a
little hot growing up? Who? The white chicks? Shit. But I mean I don't know
there's something fundamentally missing from little man. I think it may be there's
no white there's no white chicks aren't in it. No. That could be it. I think it's
turning a grown man into a baby. It freaked me out. White chicks if the white chicks
showed up at like if I was seeing like a fucking like turnstile right the only
thing cooler than like like just seeing like a band that you really like is
seeing a band you really like and they're like we have a very special guest.
So white chicks come out and start dancing.
That would be the sickest shit ever dude.
That would be cool.
You'd be like, you'd be losing your mind.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Is that the white chick?
Yeah, one of the white chicks is playing bass.
Yeah dude, yeah.
Oh man.
Yeah.
He's so cool.
He's so bassist.
They're beatboxing?
Yeah.
How are those white chicks doing that?
I don't think you're allowed to do that.
I don't think a white chick can beatbox.
He's got no rhythm.
Yeah, that I've identified the problem with a little man is my my fear of adult babies. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, true. Yeah, I guess we have done a lot of a BDL shit. Yeah, it must have been a
Fear into you. I've always been afraid of adult babies. You've been afraid. Yeah, my mom's scared about like a fucking guy
I was yeah, I was terrified of that guy
You're scared of adult babies. Yes, you're scared
It was I mean if I showed you my diaper right now, would you get freaked I would I think I know what we're doing for
Patrick's birthday next year. We're hiring an entertainer. We're gonna walk in with a big cake and it smells like shit
Big ass fake cake smells like shit
Baby biscuits on the side of it. Yeah, it's a boy
No, go ahead. There's nobody in that definitely
I think seeing like an adult in a diaper and sucking on a binky is a very weird thing.
I'm going to make sure you see that every day of your life.
We're setting you up.
We're going to hire one to follow you around.
I should exposure therapy.
I'm getting rid of your phobia.
This is like the thing where they put Bam Margera in the snake tank.
Oh yeah, and he actually freaks out.
That is like a heartbreaking part of that movie where you're like, "Oh no, these guys are
like really hurting their friend."
Yeah.
Well, number one, dirty public toilets.
Dirty public toilets.
So I was just walking into my local Target bathroom.
I was with my mom, and we walk in and we nearly scream due to the nastiness.
There is a baby coughing, a woman with her kids running around, can I speak to the manager?
Period pads and blood are everywhere, a bloody tissue, poop marks on the seat, pee on the
floor ice. I don't know why and just more crap a few stalls away. I hear my mom
shaking and cringe. Then I realized when I get up from the seat. I was sitting
right next to some sticky poop stuck to the ball. I scream but quietly we were
going to meet up with my cousin at the store. So when we walk out, she says I
have to pee. We look at her and just say hey look, it's that makeup you were
looking for. Thank goodness. You didn't go in there are times when I go into a
public toilet and I you see something so just like something that just doesn't
make any sense to your brain, right? And so I wish that I could do like Curse of the
Obra Dinn, just like relive that person's shit, to like know what happened.
The other day I was eating dinner out with my girlfriend. We were at
like some like vegetarian place that was like nice, and it had like
paintings on the wall and like music playing. It was like a nice place, and I
had to go to the bathroom. I got up and they literally had like a dive bars
bathroom in the back. It was like the craziest. I was like, "This, what is going
out like what are you doing world what did this place like used to be like how why
do they have this and they ran out of money remodeling yeah they just couldn't
get all keep the bathrooms the same it was so bizarre into a bathroom in a gas
station once where someone had just completely missed the toilet and shit on
the toilet seat I was like you're so was it that wasn't a miss you're right that's
actually pinpoint accurate yeah yeah but I was like what is it what are you doing
here. So somebody runs in and sits on the shit. As if you're gonna run in so fast
you don't notice a huge brown shit. That's true. On the toilet seat. I went to, you know what, I went to a
I went to a. I think I took a photo of it somewhere. Yeah. I have a photo, oh no I used to, I don't anymore. I had a
photo of, I went to a Buffalo Wild Wings in a mall. Mm-hmm.
I forget which mall, I think it was in, I don't know, it doesn't matter. Went into a Buffalo
Wild Wings bathroom in a mall, open up the stall door, blood on the seat. Oh my
God, dude.
Blood on the seat and in the water.
I was like, "Man."
Blood on the seat.
I should have said that.
That guy did the six-minute wing challenge, and he lost.
Yeah.
He lost.
He lost for sure.
It is funny, every time you open a bathroom stall in a men's bathroom, you really brace
yourself for the worst one.
Oh, yeah.
You go to any bar.
You open it, you're just like, "I'm prepared."
You have to be ready, because if it catches you off guard, you're going to upchuck.
Yeah, absolutely.
Or you're going to fucking eat it up.
Oh, God.
- We went to, when I was in Seattle, we went to a bar
and somebody, I forget the name, oh, the chieftain.
Went to the chieftain and we went into the bathroom
and someone was like, "Yo, someone pissed in the sink."
We're all like, "What?"
And then we all went in and it was not piss, but puke.
- Oh, that guy trolled you.
- I know. - Wow.
- Yeah.
- The toilet might have AIDS on it, yo.
Never know, I mean, God, yo could die.
That's a PSA episode waiting to happen.
Yeah.
Don't sit on a toilet.
It could have AIDS on it.
7th Heaven, like the priest dad's like, "I've contracted AIDS from a toilet."
The home improvement.
Yeah.
One of the kids gets an AIDS.
Dad?
Dad, I remember the other day when we were at CVS and I used the bathroom.
Well, yeah, son.
Of course I remember that.
i have aids
from the toilet who blew up
the
what i tell you that's in on a
on aids
are are pretty smart once at the mall i saw some poop on the floor
the reason why i hate this is because chinese toilets that have no flushes no
doors and no toilet paper and once i saw a turd just lying in the floor and
didn't got to the toilet in a week until i got back home i almost threw up fat
your score is going crazy i press possible switch
okay
number two fat people in skimpy clothes
the hell no
but i should not have uh... fucking somewhere sleeping bag
policy all that
it's not
my mom is over two hundred pounds
and then to think it's attractive to walk around a sports bra with a massive
gut hanging over pants
when i ask you to put a shirt on she yells that she's pretty and smiles at my
my dad with her double chin. He says "ooh mama" and I literally want to puke my guts out.
My mom is such a fat piece of shit and guess what?
And my dad loves her!
She fucks my dad, dude. It's so gross.
Ugh.
Do you think she wouldn't do that?
Nasty.
Look, if you're going to be fat, at least get a license first and then consult your
fashion stylist. You've got to be aware of your current body state. Also, please refrain
from McDonald's or Burger King. Wendy's is also not acceptable.
Wendy's is the healthier option.
Uh, yeah.
Wendy's has a salad that has mandarin oranges in it.
Pretty fucking good salad too.
But they have a salad with strawberries in it, right?
They got like literally five salads on the menu, bro.
Damn, and they got chili too?
It's a healthy option.
Do they still have chili at Wendy's?
It's a damn good chili.
After that woman pretended to put her thumb in it or something?
What?
Or who cut off their finger and put it in a Chili's?
Or a Wendy's Chili?
I don't know. Someone cut off their finger and then placed it in a Wendy's Chili. I don't think so.
Yeah, I've never heard about that.
What?
Yeah.
Are their toe or something?
Or a band-aid or something?
A band-aid?
Downgraded to a band-aid?
I remember there was some body part in Wendy's Chili.
A band-aid's not a body part.
Band-aid is a body part when you put it on, but when you take it off it no longer is.
So, checkmate.
He just said checkmate. I think he won.
I think I think the Raptors is controlling his brain dude. Yeah
Dude he's been acting so much like a raptor since he had the Raptors
Arms just shrank. Oh, yeah, he's so much. He's so fast. No Raptors have tiny arms. No
Rex no
Not that's
Big toes they have the bigger bigger legs and arms, which I don't have hmm. What are you talking about?
Yes, you do. No, my arms are way bigger my legs. No, they're not
I walk around on my arms.
Hold your arm out.
Hold your arms out to your side right now.
See, if I do this it looks like it's bending.
You can't even measure.
Look at this.
Alright, look at this.
Ready?
Abracadabra.
Whoa.
It looks like your arm is moving up and down.
I know.
But he's holding it still.
How do you do that?
It's magic.
I learned it at school.
What school?
Magic school.
School for the giftedly magic.
School for the clinically magic.
Yeah.
magic.
Go for the clinically magic.
Yeah.
Uh, number three, vomit.
P-U.
I think vomit's funny.
It doesn't really gross me out that much.
Yeah.
Except like, that's a lie.
Wendy's chili finger lady comes clean.
It was a lady put her finger in a chili.
I put my finger in chili before.
Yeah, it's how else you eat it.
True.
Eat it one finger at a time.
Well, no, she cut off her finger and put it in chili.
that over and over again. Yeah puke is funny sometimes. There's some types of puke that
are funny and sometimes a puke is really disgusting. A chunky puke is going to put me in the dust.
But a fucking, if someone pukes out like a white puke, and as long as they don't make
a crazy noise, I'm golden. I'm fine. I'm not going to freak out that much. If somebody
pukes like vile, not for me. A puke that shoots out is one of the funniest things in the world.
A dribbling puke is disgusting.
Horrible.
A shooting fire hose puke.
A fountain or like a magic missile puke.
That is really funny.
Yeah, a shit-seeking.
If you have like a puke after a Thanksgiving meal, funny as hell.
Yeah.
A puke after like...
That video I sent you where a guy takes one drag of a cigarette and then pukes all over his entire body.
It's not weed.
He's lying on his back and he goes like, "Bleah!" and it shoots out like a fountain.
Immediately.
It's all over him.
He pukes like up into the air.
It's so fucking good.
Oh, Jerry Hits the Bong and Spews, that's a good, that's a classic video.
Never seen it?
Yeah, you have.
It's that fat British guy.
Oh yeah, okay.
He's sitting on his couch, he hits a bong and spews.
I've seen it, he hits a bong and spews.
And then it's like now in slow-mo and then it puts it in like the rainbow like Windows
Movie Maker.
What's his name?
LA Beast Crystal Pepsi Puke?
Yep.
Funny.
Oh yeah.
That is a perfect puke.
LA Beast One Month Old Milk Puke?
Funny.
LA Beast has perfect pukes.
puke is the faded family modelo chug. That is like the best puke of all time. I think
those videos are offline. No, Will got someone to like upload a backup. Oh sick. I'll find
it for you guys. I guess that's pretty tough to get a job if you search your name and you
get faded family and it's you drinking modelos till you vomit. Puking literally like more
modelo than you drink. 32 ounce modelo challenge. I said $32. That'd be a big ass modelo. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, hell I could drink. No, I have one right now though. Yeah
Yeah, I love to number four is people not flushing the toilet. This is nasty again. That is pretty nasty
This is the same one
I feel like I mean but if you if you're like sitting down to pee and you forget because you're on your phone and you're playing
like
No playing that I think people who forget to flush the toilet should be like executed. That's like I agree
yeah, that's like if it's literally you should be like in like a
special program. If you forget to flush the toilet. That's one of the most
pathetic and disgusting things you could possibly do in this world.
I forget to flush when I pee all the time.
When you pee it's not that bad when it's pee.
But in general if you forget that's like the come on. Flush it's not hard to do.
You know what else is fucked up now? Those like top flusher toilets.
If you don't push that thing hard enough.
Yeah. I do hate going to someone's house and they have like every toilet has a different
like handle that you have to hold down a different amount of time or else it won't flush.
When someone has a fancy handle...
The two button ones, those ones are the worst because you think you can just press the button
once but no, it's not all going down. So it's going to come back up. You got to hold that
thing down till you see it go down.
Yeah. There's a technique to it.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Don't fucking... don't put a technique into your flush thing.
No, it should be like... it should be the perfect flusher, handle in a public restroom.
Those fucking...
Super flusher.
Those ones now that are like, that have like pressure in them, and it shoots like a gun,
those ones are perfect. Gets everything gone.
Strong toilet.
Here's a comment.
Those top button ones, fuck that shit.
Disgusting.
It's annoying and plus don't want to look at somebody's poop. I mean really people?
Some people who I know who does it. Xander, Gladath, and the worst, Sarkanda.
Really Sarkanda? Really?
Sarkanda, you fucker.
Fucking Gladath never flushes the toilet.
My boy Gladath and Sarkander, they be fuckin'
going in one after the other for getting a flush in the toilet.
And Voldemort too, he's always doing that shit.
Don't even get me started on fuckin'
My boy Bowser, this guy tears it up when he comes over.
Dry bones.
Dry bones, he...
Dry bones is the worst 'cause it's all dust.
Yeah, what's that in the toilet? I ain't never seen a shit like that.
I ain't never seen a shit like that.
You gotta send that boy to the... Stop trying to get me to use Seinfeld.
Stop, dude.
He poops, and it's dust!
I didn't know poop had a bone in it!
Stop.
Stop trying to make me do...
He wouldn't eat bones.
He wouldn't...
He is bones.
Yeah, but what does he eat?
He shits.
He eats bones too.
He eats dust, yeah, but he wouldn't eat a bone.
He literally eats bones.
He wouldn't be a bone in his poop.
He wouldn't eat bones.
You wouldn't eat like an arm.
I'd eat meat.
I eat meat every day.
Checkmate.
I also checkmated you.
Oh my god.
You've been checkmated twice in one episode.
No.
I'm made out of meat, I eat meat.
But you're not just made out of meat.
He's just made out of bones.
- Wings are not just made out of meat,
they're made out of bones and meat, checkmate.
- But he wouldn't eat an arm, that's, come on.
- Literally what a wing is.
- Wings is a bone, checkmate.
- Dude, you are getting fucking destroyed.
- You don't eat the bone.
- Oh my God, dude, he's--
- I eat bones.
- What about bone marrow, you can eat bones from bone marrow?
- Dude, you're getting taken down and he's getting mad.
- I'm not getting mad.
- He's getting so checkmated.
- You guys sound stupid right now.
- You're just mad, you're literally--
- You're just mad that you're eating an arm.
- You're literally eating an arm.
- I've eaten tons of arms.
- You don't eat an arm.
- Chicken wing.
- No, you don't eat the bone there.
- Chicken leg.
- I've eaten a bone.
- You don't eat the bone.
- I've eaten a bone hole.
- I ate the bone.
- You don't eat a bone hole.
That's not true.
That's false.
You guys are lying to try and make me look stupid.
- If you get a microwave,
you can eat the bone.
- You guys are sounding stupider and stupider
by the second.
- I agree.
- You can chew on that bone.
- Yeah, you can eat the bone.
- You can chew the marrow out of the bone
and put it in the microwave.
- But it wouldn't go in your poop.
poop. No it wouldn't. Let's eat a bone right now. Go eat a bone right now. Yep you can inspect
my poop. Okay go do it. No it's not a checkmate until you eat the bone. Hey how about a dog
eats meat and a bone. Yep. Not together. A dog also doesn't eat the bone. Dogs eat the
bone. No they don't. Yes they do. No they don't. You've never been around pit bulls.
I've been checkmated. You've not been checkmated. Stand your ground. Alright yeah. You know what?
a bitch. Double checkmate. Double checkmate, well how? He'd eat the bones! He'd get the
bones out! It's too easy. But a dog wouldn't eat a dog leg. A dog would probably eat another
dog. Have you ever been to a dog fight? No. They eat the other dog. Have you been to a
dog fight? Yeah. Okay, checkmate dude, you're going to jail. No. Looks like we're in a Mexican
Checkmate here this the statute of limitations checkmate. What's the statute of limitations on going to a dogfight? I?
Don't know like ten minutes, right? Yeah
Gone so there's no evidence. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hmm. Where's the dog? Yeah, these two dogs weren't fighting one of them
See if the cops pull up to if the cops pull up to your dog fight if you're having a dog fight
Yeah, all you have to do is just say hey officer
Maybe there's something that we can work out and then you point to the dogs and just start doing like a gun
Yeah
Cops love to shoot dogs. They do you owned them take that cops number
Some of those that work forces are the same some of those that walk dogs is are the same that
Fuck, what would the fuck dog dogs is I don't like that. I don't like it either. Here's number five is Justin Bieber
We went from poop and pee to Justin B. This guy is monstrously disgusting
Here's a just a little here's a comment from a Justin Bieber fan. I think you should put dirty water on your mom's head
Shit, oh man
Justin Bieber dry hair and clean it yeah
Yeah, want to see pictures of the back of him with no clothes on and covering his private parts, lol
Nakey pic of Justin Bieber like yesterday didn't he shows cock and something
It's funny that like if you're famous for more than you
He peed into a bucket and said "Fuck Bill Clinton."
If you're famous for more than like five years, people will see your cock.
Yeah.
That's true.
It's kind of inevitable.
Someone's going to iCloud hack you.
Someone's going to like fucking...
If you're like super famous, your cock is going public.
Yep.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe we can do something about that.
Yeah?
What would we do?
Like maybe some kind of cyber security thing we could invent.
Why would we do that?
- Like a cock destroyer?
- A cock lock.
- Cock lock?
- It's like an encryption.
- Yeah.
- So you just destroy their cocks.
- It's an app, right?
- That encrypts your cock?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- So every photo--
- So it's just like a matrix,
one's a zero outline of your cock?
- Okay, so you know those AI things
where you take a, you upload a photo of yourself
and then it describes your face.
It says like, this is what the AI thinks of you.
It says like, a lot of them said like,
you're a buck or whatever.
- Oh, I do remember the description that Caleb got
when he put his face into that. What was it? I don't remember.
Oh, it was like predator. It was worse than that.
Oh, right.
I don't remember what it was. Oh, well, yeah, never mind. What did you think I was? You have to tell me.
You don't remember? I don't remember. It said "rapist".
Oh, that is funny.
Yeah, the AI said that. Okay, so it's that. Everyone's posting their face of their thing, their screenshot
the AI thing online, it was like, "It said I'm a cowboy!"
[Laughter]
"It said I'm an IT worker!"
Yeah, no, that was definitely...
The thing is, yeah, I mean...
It's so funny, they put that into their, like, their AI knowledge bag.
And also, they uploaded, they were like, "Hmm, should we disable this one for the website?"
Nah, nah, we'll use that one.
People love that one.
Yeah, nah, that was a dark day.
Mine said "Young Buck" every time.
I don't remember what mine said, to be honest.
- Okay, so that one.
So we use that same technology, right?
And then we use that AI thing
to write detailed descriptions of penises.
- Uh-huh. - Okay.
- And then if a celebrity takes a,
they take a photo in the app,
and then the photo, the penis is removed from the photo.
- Okay. - Content-aware fill style.
- Soft nub. - Ken doll.
- Ken doll, soft nub.
- Okay. - And then at the bottom,
just has a very vivid description of what the penis would look like.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Yeah, that is actually clever.
So anytime a celebrity takes a cock pic, they do it with this app.
Yes.
Send it to whatever, like...
Send it to Selena Gomez.
Yeah, send it to Selena Gomez and then she can imagine it, right?
And then there's no...
And she's getting 99% of the experience of cock photo.
Because women like words, too.
Yeah, exactly.
And it'll get people to read again.
That's a big thing.
None of these kids are reading.
They're all too busy looking at cocks.
And here's the thing.
It doesn't get sent over your phone.
It gets sent in a book.
- Yeah, it's like a pamphlet and then you have to read it.
- And the app is celebrities only.
- Yeah. - Like Raya.
- Yeah, it's like Raya.
And then also, it would need to be,
so we'd work on this, right?
So probably it's gonna be grueling hours
of us looking at cots and writing the descriptions.
And probably getting really good at it too.
By the end we might be able to--
- We'll be the Joyce Carol Oates of--
- Well, here's the end game.
Then once a bunch of celebrities join,
they don't realize what they accepted
in the terms of service.
we turn all of them into a coffee table book.
- Ah. - And we sell that.
- 'Cause they can't-- - Celebrity Penises.
- Yeah, Celebrity Penises. (laughs)
- Celebrity Penises-- - Time Life Presents.
- Description, Celebrity Penises.
- It's all like, it's like an art book
where it's like Celebrity Penises
and it has like essays on them.
- Yeah, they describe what they actually look like.
But then it's mostly, most people get it--
- A soft nub. - So that they can see.
Most people, surprisingly short,
like most people get it so that they can see
like the background of a celebrity home.
Yeah, you know we can actually make a lot of money making a celebrity penises coffee table book and just putting like just random other penises
Oh, yeah, it's celebrity. Yeah, we get sued really bad for that
Pictures, yeah, no, no, probably not. I mean you do like at so you spell the names in leet
Yeah, you spell you just change one letter at all their names. Yeah
broad pit yeah
Bradley goopers
Christopher Lloyd with one L and Lloyd
That's horrible I thought he was in that
Yeah, probably
He was in that that that um that movie with Bob Odenkirk the John wick movie. Oh, yeah, it's like fucking shit
It's insane that he's still in fucking 80. Yeah, I know it's nuts that he's still like alive. It was like 45 on taxi
It's crazy. I mean he he how old is he now? He's gotta be 100 years old. He's gotta be late 80s
No, I would say he's 88. Yeah, 188 88 or 89
No, let's see. There's no ways like he's probably not always pushing a hundred. He's 82. Whoa, did I fucking know?
Yes, just looked old forever. That's what I'm saying. Yeah, he's old when he was like, yeah 50
I mean he had he had at least gray not white hair in taxi and a little bit more of it
You know he looks like the devil now. He looked very young when he was fester. He looked young and and yeah and
Maybe you should just do it all the time now if that's the case. It's really it's the hair yeah
Oh, yeah, cuz in in one flew over the cuckoo's nest he looks like you know
He does not really look that young as uncle fester, but he looks he look he has he has life force
Mm-hmm. He looks like like yeah like there dude. He's looking rough man. Yeah. Oh, God. He's got vigor
Hmm as uncle Fester. He kinda looks like my grandpa.
Yeah? Yeah, he kinda looks like my grandpa. Your grandpa's loitered up? I think yeah.
My grandpa looks like a fucking like a like an eight ball. Yeah? Yeah. He's black? Big and round and brown.
Oh. Brown? Guess he's like a seven ball then.
Yeah, my grandpa's like insanely brown.
Okay. Yeah, and he just like rolls around. Yeah? He's awesome, dude. Yeah? Yeah, he's a man.
I can't wait to see him.
You have Grandpa Roly?
Seen him in a couple weeks.
Roly Poly.
Can't wait to see him.
As soon as I get to his house every single time, he's like, I haven't seen him in like
a year or something, he's like, "Oh, great to see you.
Can you move 400 boxes from my garage to my bedroom?"
And I go, "Yeah, yeah, Grandad, no problem."
Then he makes me the worst food ever.
Yeah.
He's an absolute pimp.
My grandpa, when my grandpa lived with me, he would make his own food, but he would make
it too hot.
Grandpa food is--
Or too spicy.
you make it to some of the worst food of all time
we would hear him eating it in the other room and he'd just be like
my grandpa made uh... he would make this thing called it was egg mcpits
oh god that doesn't sound good at all
my last name is pits
so it's like an egg mcmuffin but it's egg mcpits
and it's all the ingredients of an egg mcmuffin
but he chops them all up and puts them in a bowl
he makes like eggs, bacon,
cheese, an english muffin and he just chops it all up
It's horrible.
Why does he chop up the egg?
It makes no sense.
Why does he chop up the bread?
He has all the ingredients, he's making egg sandwich, chops everything up, puts it in
a bowl, calls it an Egg McPitz.
That's a horrible name too.
I mean, wouldn't it be like an Egg Pitz Muffin?
Well, he uses his last name when he makes it for himself, but when he makes it for me.
But I'm saying-
Egg Pitz Muffin makes a lot more sense.
Yeah, but it's like McPitz.
You see what I'm saying?
No.
Because it's McDonald's.
Yeah, oh yeah.
It's a McMuffin, so it would be like-
No, he's not smart.
It should be like a Pitz Muffin.
Yeah, no, he thinks that the guy's name is Donald and it's like
Like MC is like some kind of like like old Donald like it's like
McDonald Ronald
Mick Donald it's he thinks it's a name. He thinks his name is Ronald middle name Mick last name Donald
Yeah, MC Donald Ronald Donald. Yeah, he's made a lot of fucked up food
He used to make a thing where he would just make he would just boil olive oil and then put and then pour it over pasta
Like a soup.
Soup?
What the fuck?
You wouldn't put any seasoning in it?
I mean like salt.
That's it?
Yeah, he individually salts.
You put cracked red pepper and garlic in it.
And parsley, that's pasta di gillo.
That's from Chef.
Listen to this.
We go to a Mexican restaurant, they serve chips beforehand.
Individually salts every single chip that goes into his mouth.
Sits there, just salts them.
salt some. Not even the good flaky salt they already have on them. Nah dude he's putting
table salt on them. This is called an egg Mcchip. It's a chip Mcme. It's really good, it's the
best thing ever. He also goes to Mexican restaurants, he's a hamburger at the Mexican restaurant
guy. Oh yeah. Always, and when I was a kid he used to bring, we didn't have milk at our
house, he would come over for dinner, he'd bring a gallon of milk, just pour, he'd drink
a half gallon of milk at dinner. He's alive. Incredible. How old is he? He's like 78 maybe?
Nice. 79? Something like that. Very nice. Number, what is this, 5? Yeah, we've got to
go pretty fast here. Oh yeah, we've done a lot of, I think the Raptor. The Raptor. The
Raptor has taken a lot out of this episode. Let's see, I mean we'll just read through the
rest of it. People spitting on you when they're talking to you. Yup, that's pretty bad. Two
girls one cup video it's not that bad
uh... snotty nose little kids like like patrick might disagree with this one
what uh... number nine is but they may be snotty nose little kids like we don't
have to we don't have to get it we have to get into a bad idea that they may be
not going to visually describe what these kids look like to you were as
little as one of your son he knows i think like aroo decade
you don't like rude kids you're like you got what polite ones that act we have
like submissive kids
i'm trying to number nine i don't want to keep talking about this
never know if we also should maybe bring up in front patrick make it hungry
that's true
you poop just grosses me out like i don't think it should be seen at all i
hate changing pampers although i can handle it i'd feel like the sick emoji
green and i feel as if i am going to pass out but i live this is just
ridiculous anytime i like see it somewhere i just want to die i can never
change a diaper
you never change a diaper no no never have never could
never let me let's the kids you have it after you have
fuck you
if you have a kid
you won't change the diaper
if i have a kid
i will not change the diaper no
you being a dad would be so funny
yeah it would be horrible for everyone involved
no the kid would have a very you would see you would you would uh... i mean i'd rather
adopt a kid at like you might be able to raise honestly you might be able to raise
next like Bob Dylan a kid with like just the most fucked up life it just becomes a
genius because he's like you my daddy fucking yeah slipped on banana peels
over my dad was going yeah writing all these songs about you man banana peel
Why are you on the floor?
My head keeps asking me who's on first. Yeah
Dead but throwing a dead parrot the parent teacher conference on the fucking death trying to return it
Yeah, yeah, you might honestly raise like an amazing artist
Raising like one of the most great the greatest musicians of all time just because your dad
Just because you as a father cannot stop doing three stooges bits.
Like you can't.
There's a song called...
And my dad's a shimp.
He calls you by your first name instead of dad.
He calls you booger lips.
The last one here, number 10, dog poo on the sidewalk.
Here's the last comment I'll read.
For those who say dog poop is not gross, I've had it on my shoe before, and that my friend, is not pretty.
Dog poo on the sidewalk sounds like a cool, like, like, Houston hip-hop slang.
Dog poo on the sidewalk, like a Zero song.
Yeah.
Alright.
I eat so many poops I got dog poop poisoning.
(laughing)
- Okay. - Page time.
- Oh man.
- Thank you for listening. - Bye everyone.
- Subscribe to the Patreon for a lot of beautiful things.
The 100th premium episode is coming out this week.
- You're kidding. - This Saturday.
We recorded something great for it.
You're not gonna wanna miss it.
- Also, subscribe to the Twitch.
We have to make Jubio quit his job.
- Yeah, Jubio needs money.
We've got him in a lot of trouble financially.
- Yes. - Yep.
We have the police, the American police are after him. We have him in a really tight spot. Interpol is
searching for him. And we need your help. Send Jubio your credit card number,
the special number's on the back, billing, zip code. Yep, he needs it. Yep. Thank you everybody.
Bye. Bye.