Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Okay, now recording.
- You know when you've been--
- Smells like Yoda's yurt right now.
- You know when you've been really gassy
and you've been sitting in your room like all day long?
- Yeah.
- And then you go to the kitchen and you get some water.
- And you go back in.
- And you come back and you just smell--
- Stink wave.
- Yeah, you haven't even farted in like an hour.
- Yeah.
- And you're in your room.
- It's just still in there.
- I just bought these two--
- It smells so bad.
You know those like gel like the things like the glade like gel things?
Yeah, the volcanoes?
Yeah, about two of those and then like these two things that like you stick
onto like the wall.
You went hard.
That says last like 60 days.
Yeah, because my room smelled like farts.
So I like left and then just like brought a bunch of like air fresheners to make it not smell.
That's so dominating though when you bring somebody over to your house and you've been gone all day.
Why does it smell good?
And it still smells like farts.
Oh, I thought you were saying like, why does it smell good?
It's so dominating, have a nice smelling room.
Well, this smells too good. It smells too good, like what's the reason?
Yeah, it's clear that you're covering something up.
You know what the best, if it smells just like laundry, then it's like, okay.
This guy's never farted.
I'm gonna start boiling a fabuloso.
If I get a pair of pants clean, they smell like laundry for about 90 seconds when they're on my body.
on my body. And then I'll take them off. They're immediately dirty because of my stink and
my stench.
Me too.
Yeah, and my smells are there too.
Oh, I told you about I didn't do laundry for like a month.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, and then, you know, I mean, my clothes smell good now, but there was like probably
like a week where I was just, you know, coming to hang out and just smelling like...
What's your limit on a shirt and a pair of pants?
i mean uh... pair of pants all rewire it's harder 'cause like
if i sweat in them when i was skating
parents like
ten months honestly and uh... six months maybe a bit
asserted her bidding the uh... i've heard like like
if i'm if i'm being really lazy and disgusting play like three days on a
shirt from the city of white shirt one day
well depends if you get a lot of pain and also at like you that's true yeah i
And if I'm wearing a shirt multiple days, it's because I'm literally just sitting in one place
for three days.
I mean, I do a lot of laundry because I, like, I don't know, I go out and skate too much.
But I didn't do...
You just told us you didn't do any laundry.
Yeah, and I also never fart, too.
I never fart.
I mean, I have a bunch of clothes is what I mean.
You do have a lot of clothes.
Yeah, I have two.
I just bought, like, I realized I only had two jackets, so then I went out and bought
four jackets.
Yeah, you remind me of a store.
Yeah, you are kind of like a store.
You're always getting new items and selling other items.
Yeah.
And like there's customers too.
A cash register.
You always got mad, now I think about it, you always got mad customers in your crib.
And your open and close sign, it always be changing.
True.
I guess that's true.
I guess you're right.
What the fuck's that about?
Yeah.
I guess that's right.
That's right.
You do kind of strike me as a guy who's going to turn 50 and open up a shop.
You do kind of strike me as a store.
A little bit.
You kind of, you're kind of like a...
I've always thought of you as a store.
There's something about you.
Maybe it's like, oh, I'm a little bit like a...
you maybe it's like oh wait oh it's my big red circle it's your big red circle yeah yeah
yeah it might be the automatic doors and so yeah it might be the things uh in the windows
of you right the pro my man yeah the mannequins in the windows of you yeah really reminded
me of a store and you know they're nude come on and you know i got no clothes speaking
of things in the window i got an update on wally the alligator okay somebody me and uh
Juvia were streaming last night. Someone comes in the stream says, "I live in that
town. I've seen that fucking alligator like 50 times." Yeah. And I was like, "Tell me
more." He says, "Apparently, the guy who owns Wally also owns like a little shop
where they just sell dildos, bongs, and Donald Trump flags, and Wally sits like a
mannequin in the window of the shop to get people to come in. He just like sits
there all day. Wow. So now I have a pilgrimage. Yeah. Yeah. Now I have like, I
think, I think I have to, right? Like Islam dude, I think I have to do, I have to do my...
What? Islam. What? Say it like that. Islam dude. That's what it's called. What do you guys say?
Why did you say it like it's long? Islam. You're saying it like it's long. Islam.
Islam is long. Islam. Islam. Why are you saying it so long? Islam. Islam. That's a cube, you
gotta go there. It just makes sense. You gotta see the cube. You gotta kneel in front of
the cube. You gotta say hi to the cube. Do you kneel in front of the cube? Huh? Do you
kneel in front of the cube? I think you probably kneel when you pray. I think you glee to the
I think the thing is it's cool about Islam is that the cube you don't get
lead off like a card where they check to see if you're actually Muslim right you
go see the cube yeah you just gotta wear the white stuff you know that you know
they have a meteor inside there yeah they climb there's a meteor I did I just
want like that's like like literally the coolest thing in any religion ever a
cube with a meteor inside there you have to go visit that's why does it so we had
the closest thing that we had okay honestly was like like when I was
growing up the Statue of Liberty that was like the cool the cool like Christian
thing is relics like like old see like a saint dog Saints bones and stuff that
stuff's cool that's the cool part of but like that's that's a Catholic like yeah
like Protestantism hasn't it's too new yeah doesn't have anything cool there's
nothing ancient about it you know there's like Jesus shit but I don't share with
all the other fucking religion my grandma's hatred your grandma's I did go
see your grandma quite a few times I'm kicking you out of Islam yeah yeah
you're banned for don't say good I'm already a beautiful religion with them
I'm a I'm a pasta farian because I think all religion is hocus-pocus
I've been flip-flopping between becoming Reddit atheist and very TradCath. I don't know which
one is more annoying. You're gonna become TradCath? I'm gonna be very annoying. Are you gonna
become TradCath at Dimesquare? You fucking idiot. Between Reddit atheism and TradCath?
I'm gonna do Reddit atheism. I honestly hope a trucker kills you. I swear to fucking God.
I hope you get completely just meat-grinded by the front end of a Peterbilt.
No you don't.
I do.
That'd be so...
Yeah, and you're sitting there, you're smoking a fucking camel blue, talking about being Trad
Catholic Dimesquare, and some guy just turns you into mush.
Anyway, I think I'm going to become traditionally Catholic.
Now that'd be pretty cool.
I'm going to become Trad Muslim, dude.
Yeah.
I'm going to get real into it.
Which one's more annoying?
I just finished reading Dune and I feel like I'm ready to become Muslim.
White Muslim or a traditional Catholic guy?
No white Muslim is cool as hell.
White Muslim is so sick dude.
It's awesome.
If I became white Muslim as a bald guy.
That's literally what Dune is about.
Really?
Yeah.
So cool man.
Dude it's so sick.
It's about he becomes white Muslim and Hitler.
That's the story arc.
That's what they're doing to Timmy Chalamet.
Literally yeah.
you're gonna be a white muslim hitler
so they can make him white muslim hitler
i thought he was a good guy
no no no he's very evil
no paul trees is not a good guy
come on
so who's the good guy in dune
the worm?
what? really?
no the worm is baron harkonen
yeah baron harkonen
patrick likes what he does to kids in the book
oh fuck i forgot about that
god damn it
And I forgot that they just made the villain of Dune just like a gay floating pedophile.
Yeah. So everybody's bad in the movie? There's not a good guy?
There's no good guy in Dune except the worm.
The worm sounded pretty cool. The worm is cool.
They should make a movie about him called Worm. Yeah.
Yeah. They should be mostly worm.
No. No.
Do they ride the worms? They do.
Yeah. Dude, I gotta fucking read this book.
Dude, it's so good. You've never seen the original, the lynch
dune no well it took me three times to try and finish it it's kind of here it's
terrible I didn't watch this shit well you should read the book the books I
watched half of the Jodorowsky dune the documentary oh yeah yeah and that guy's
cool as fuck he's cool he's like the movie was going to be so good everyone's
like he's a genius he's a fucking genius that thing where he was like for the um
What is it the ankle and call the history like comic like he was doing this thing recently
He's like I'm gonna announce the director soon like it's gonna blow your mind. Who's directing this and it was taiko with TT. Yeah
so cool, so funny to tease that for like a
Period of time like not just that's something you just have to come out and say yeah. Yeah, you can't get people hi
That's yeah, you gotta say like I mean who?
Who even is a director that would have been worth the hype? I mean him. I guess he's like a hundred years old
old. He's I think he's like ninety seven. Yeah. Yeah. It is funny that
Taika Waititi was first like I'm going to adapt Akira and then he's like no
you know what like people get mad if I do that. I'll do it.
Jodorowsky instead. The coolest thing about that Jodorowsky guy is his like
most famous movie. It's just like him and his son who's completely naked just
like hanging out for an hour and a half. Yeah. Yeah. He's a cowboy. His son is a
naked little boy who was a wiener out the entire movie and they just walk around.
Yeah.
He's like, "My soft penis was very funny in the movie."
Very cool.
I want to become an eclectic, I think.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to become eclectic.
Eclectic?
I think I'm going to become.
Eccentric or eclectic?
I think I might be both.
Okay.
But that's also one of my eclectic and eccentric quirks is not knowing the difference.
Yeah.
I think I might become.
I thought I've been doing that.
just a mental disorder. Yeah, which disorder? ADHD. That's not eccentric. No. Or a disorder.
You need to be, to be eccentric you need to really hurt people's feelings. Yeah. I think
I'm gonna start flipping people off more. I'm like basically the most eccentric guy
like in the city. No, I'm becoming a white Muslim. I'm pretty. Oh, deep go go go go go
go. That's my language. Oh yeah, be eh. Is this like, is there any like classes to become
languages. Yeah, UCB. Oh, that's right. Yeah. That'll make you so weird. Yeah, you'll walk
out of there. Hey, keep New York weird. That's what I always say. You'll walk out of there.
You'll be at the pizza place. You'll be like, what do you want to order? You're coming right
out of an improv class. And you'll say, I don't know, a huge poop. A chocolate pizza.
I shot the pizza with Hershey kisses on it. Yeah, we actually have that it's
called the cookie pizza. Okay, that's weird. I'm gonna drive my car.
Hello.
Hello. Oh no, this is just a banana.
I'm the banana phone guy. So now I'd like my free pizza because I just paid
you performance here is a coupon you have to take yeah yeah here's my real money
just like okay here's 1 million dollar sir they're like yeah we can't take that
like oh okay yeah great scene partner yeah cool yeah cool yeah yes remember
that video I'm writing a call-out post about you they're never gonna work in
this pizza shop ever again you guys remember that video that it's like the
improv performers and like the other one one of them calls the other guy 9/11
beard and the guy freaks out so hard that he leaves the room the guys that
somebody freaks in like improv and shit and you see like in every improv class
there's always like one guy who every time he's in a scene with like a female
like a female person he's sitting there and they're like okay start the scene
and he goes I mean he's like uh hi I'm a professional pussy eater and I'm here to
eat your pussy and then everybody goes don't stop doing that and then he just
keeps doing it every year. So cool. There's always someone who like
literally can't yeah like there's a mental block that they can't not do
stuff like that. The episode of The Office where Michael Scott keeps
having the gun, that guy doesn't exist but the guy who his gun is that he's a
sexual predator is in every single class. Yeah. It's so cool. Yeah. What a
beautiful art that is. Yeah. As a white Muslim I'm like that's like I think
think one of the big pillars right now is improv is evil.
I thought you were going to say one of the big pillars of Islam is improv.
It's improv, graffiti, knowledge.
That's big.
Improv, graffiti, knowledge, where to get the best curtains for your apartment.
And basically just chilling.
And a square hat.
Yeah, that's the uniform. That doesn't like go into the pillars. I want that square hat so bad.
Yeah, it's so cool. It fixes any head shape. Yeah, yeah. I would like to join a
religion where I can wear a knight's helmet every day. You can be a Templar.
I would love to be a Templar. You should become a Templar. In my religion,
Pasipharianism, you can wear a colander on your head. Yeah, my
jousting lance shall strike thy head from thine shoulders. So, and I'm gonna
pray to I'm gonna pray to Muhammad to shoot you with a laser yeah yeah he's
got a laser I know that it's got everything dude he's practically God
jr. you're not allowed to see what he looks like cuz he was he was he was an
awesome creature he's a what he was a creature I don't know if we can continue
you this bit. And he looked like this. Can we just reverse this whole... You can't draw him, but you can say what he looked like.
You can't say... I don't think you can say what he looks like. He had a cherubic face.
And he had a corn pop. He looked exactly... He had a corn cob pipe in a button nose.
He looked exactly like the puppet from Saw. That's what he looked like.
I don't think this is a good move for us.
He looked like Cheesosaurus Rex.
He did.
I don't think this is...
And he would skate on cheese all through the Middle East.
And everybody's like, "What the fuck? That guy's like God's junior right now."
Is there going to be a fartwa on us?
There's going to be a fartwa on you pretty soon when I fart on your mouth.
This is not good.
I'm declaring a fartwa on Patrick.
If you see him, you have to fart on him.
No, don't do that because someone will really do it.
That's why I'm hoping somebody if someone comes okay
If you don't have the self-respect if a stranger to fart that farts on you like if you don't have the self-respect to punch them in
The face that's on you. There's not um that is on you if you see Patrick. Please go if you're crazy, please fart on
Please come up to him while he's skating. He bends over to pick up his board. You just fart his face
I will fucking hit them with my trucks. Thank good. That's a big
I've always wanted to do that.
- Hit someone, you've never--
- You psycho! - Never done a truck smack
someone? - What's wrong with you?
- I've always wanted to truck smack somebody.
Dude, it's so-- - Now I'm instituting
a gun law on you, where somebody has to use their gun on you.
- Like, it's so sick, like I've seen it in a movie.
- Truck smacking, is that what they call it?
- Yeah, you grab it by the other truck
and you just kinda like swing it.
- I gotta say, that would hurt.
- Yeah. - Yeah, that'd be bad.
- Yeah, it's metal and wood, the two types of bats
combined into one. - True, oh my god,
it's a super bat. - And a wheel.
Yeah, and polyurethane.
Yeah, that's a serious bat.
Yeah.
It's true.
Probably one of the scariest bats of all time.
Besides, hey, Dracula in his bat form.
You think that's the scariest one, but which one do you see more often?
Dracula in his bat form.
Really?
Yeah, he's in my window most nights.
Ah, damn. I'm sorry, man.
Yeah, it's kind of annoying.
Yeah.
He's always asking to hang out.
He's always tapping on the window. He says, "Hey, can I come in?"
I say, "Like, maybe tomorrow, man, because I don't want to be, like, rude."
rude. I mean you can't just be like no. Yeah he has a dark board. Yeah it's like every few
hours. Tap tap tap tap tap. Where did the thing that Dracula can only be in, he has to be invited
in, where did that come from? He's like really awkward low key. Yeah. Like he doesn't, he's
the kind of guy who like he doesn't get invited to stuff and he sits around and he's like
man like I feel like I don't have any friends but if he reached out to people they'd be
like come on come out but he just kind of like you know. He just like doesn't make that
extra effort to actually be social.
Yeah, he doesn't really put himself out there.
I do like to think that maybe that rule was like Dracula was trying to go into someone's
house and he was like, "No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't come in here unless I invite you."
Yeah, it was maybe somebody's house rule that he thought was a rule about hair.
Yeah, and he was like, "Ah, shit.
This is a rule for...
I just turned into a damn Dracula.
I don't know.
I don't know any of these goddamn rules."
Well, what happened was he saw like a cheeky, sarcastic welcome mat that was like, "You're
not welcome in here and he's like oh my god yeah words have a sort of power back
then true that's what I said the penis might ear than the sword mm-hmm it's
true yeah I'm seriously just getting that mm-hmm the power of words whoa I
love wordplay so much yeah yeah it's this abracadabra which is oh my god what
you do you take away all this word that's what I always got their words you can
speak anymore
all the old real alakazam
what the fuck is a big ever could have a good normal again
I'm actually think I feel like I do
how much do you guys believe in magic uh not that I says before I don't think
bad I think energy
it's a little energy do you think we can maybe like try to harness it sometime
i think we could i think we should get i think we could read a spell book
all i got all i got rid of my
all of the subject of the handbook of america still have a we need to create
one hundred and i don't know our own type of like chaos magic thing yeah i
think we could develop a decision making
huh sigils yeah we can make sigils to be part of it
is that a crystal
now uh... those are the symbols that that the draw
there'll be a little bit of sigil to dispel nightmares
stuff like that smiley face
smiley face that's good to know that it'll spread happiness
to get idea
uh... and
media monkey
yeah i keep a s
maybe
that could be a situation so we have to do for all the ultimate bananas
yeah forgetting
tons of an is in your own
the
a dollar sign to be a good sigil yeah keep all
polio
for its usual for ultimate randomness yep
you know the uh...
the big l
you know that's your city
the digital for a little bit about
civil to become a little big l
was in new york for
now keep
the key to keep
that keep note that you look
now people are going to be on the evening in t_c_o_d_ writing she's or
[BeaconNigga and Cheesy talking over each other]
Come on, Ock.
Let me get a...
Let me get a BeaconNigga and Cheese.
Do you want a roll?
You already know the vibes.
Salt, pepper, ketchup, mayo.
Gotta get the beer!
Gotta cop the Yari!
Gotta cop the beer!
You already know what it is.
You got Lucy's!
Come on, Ock.
Can I?
Ock!
hey oh hey can I'm a hero it's your white horse can I be heroic your white sauce
I would love to be the New Zealand arc the New Zealand ox are just guys like us
yeah American dudes yeah there just chopping it up chip in a chip and chip
it up it is yeah I'm chipping it up in the baby ship
I'm at the baby ship.
Sheepin' it up.
We're in the baby ship asking who's the baby ship.
Who's your top five?
Who's your goat?
You get.
You get it.
You already know the vibes.
If it's in New Zealand, wouldn't it be the sheep?
What?
Who's the sheep?
Who's your sheep of all time?
I only in Oakland oh whoa that's where they come from that's where art comes
from that's what they say the guy from New Zealand goes into a bodega asks for
something the Aki way he gets at the Aki way he goes no this isn't what I aced
for yeah I wanted it the Auckland way that's pretty good mm-hmm yeah yeah New
New Zealand guy in New York is pretty funny to me.
Yeah, imagine if that happened.
Imagine if two New Zealand guys lived in New York and they sang songs.
I mean like, you know, like cool New Zealand.
Imagine how crazy their fan would be too.
Yeah, oh my god.
And they would have a crazy manager who works at the fruit stand being rude to them.
But then it turns out many years later that he was actually the reason for a few women.
I think I love their song about robots as well.
Yeah, I think I might love all their songs.
Yeah.
And I think I might often get them confused with Bo Burnham if they did that.
That was my favorite show when I was a little kid.
Really?
Yeah.
You must have been so annoying.
Yes, I was.
That's cool.
You know what my favorite show was?
You don't think I'm annoying now?
No.
No, you're my good friend.
I would never call you annoying.
You know what my favorite show was?
You don't think that's continued on into my adult life?
Fuck no.
Come on, dude.
I'm just trying to get people to fart on you.
I don't dislike you. I just want to see you smell.
I don't dislike you. I just want to see you in pain.
I'm preying on your smell fall.
Your downy fall.
Because you're going to have to wash your damn clothes.
You know what?
Have you guys ever seriously considered getting one of those pads that makes your fart smell good?
Yes.
Me too.
Every day.
I've honestly been like, maybe this morning.
Especially.
It's like a fucking pad that a woman wears for her vagina.
Oh, come on.
What?
it looks like that
will say that
so it's a good
for thingy
okay and thank you for when it goes weird
and uh... it sits on your butthole and it's like a filter
and it's like a hit the filter but it like returns your parts of the like a
good smell
uh... there's like a fragrance yeah but i did like i don't know what the for the
actually put on backwards and yes well even worse
to be a point where you get a hemorrhoid minute
you can get blood on it then I think it's doing its job hmm yeah yeah I've been so
I have one right now I've been so scared of like farting blood like a snot bubble
yeah you serious like a big emerald right now you're worried about farting
out a blood bubble yeah that floats out of my like back
it's a little rascal
it just pops up out of your pants
it pops out like
it flies, you watch it
it goes out the window and floats down
and like pops on like a grandmother
it floats down 5th avenue and just hits Imrata in the face
like a big bubble gum
just pops, he's covered in red
oh sorry, that's my hemorrhoid fart
whose hemorrhoid blood bubble fart was that?
that? Not me! She just goes like, "It was you!" And he's more like hemorrhoid-a.
Oh my god. But if you had that pad the bubble would be clear and beautiful and
when it popped on Emrata she'd marry you. Yeah she'd say, "Who was that? It was you!"
And then you'd probably suck your dick. It smelled so good when it popped all over me.
is that your bubble that bubble that bubble smelled so good it's like a
clear bubble but you can see like green gas inside it floating floating around
and it pops in her face yeah it looks like the remember all from a Harry
Harry Potter, she becomes
like it's like the Palantir, Lord of the
Saron's eye.
It's like a like like a roiling fog with like a burning red eye and it's seeking
out amrata down the street.
It's like swerving around a homeless women. She's running
whatever he'll break. She's back
(laughter)
It just swallows her whole?
Yeah.
And then she falls in love with you and you get to swallow her whole.
I'm worried that that's going to happen with, because I have a hemorrhoid.
That exact situation is going to happen.
Is it that Emorada falls in love with you and becomes your fart slave?
She's not going to become my fart slave.
What the hell are you fucking talking about?
If she likes it, she will.
I would never have a fart slave.
Why not?
You know why.
I've seen your fart gear.
You might already have one.
You might have a... I saw your butt to face tube. I would have a fart employee.
Alright. You'd pay them? You'd get paid in farts. That's what a fart slave is. You pay them in farts, they love it.
Yeah. They're a voluntary slave. I saw your butt straw in your room. I know what you're up to. My butt straw?
Yeah. I saw your butt snorkel mask.
Where they put the tube right in your butt and then they just... I saw your stink amplifier.
It's a box of Cheetos.
(laughter)
I saw it in your closet.
You have a giant box like when
they buy dog food in bulk, like a huge
just like tank and it says
"Fart Food" on it.
It has that lid that pops like this
in a little circle. On my floor
there's just like a crock pot cooking pot roast.
(laughter)
And then there's another crock pot that you fart into
and cover and cook it.
Just like tons of jars of the water
from chickpea cans you keep that shit you can make aqua faba yeah aqua Farta mm-hmm
Florida is nor from Queens what are you better put in your mouth is that what is
You know what HALS stands for?
Honey and Lemons.
Woah!
Well there's two L's.
Honey and Lemons.
And there's a second L that's the one you just took.
Trying to name that shit.
Bitch, what's up?
Dude, you're on a heater right now.
Keep going.
You did the aquafaba thing.
You did the HALS thing.
What's your next one?
I'm just gonna make disgusting hard candy noises into the mic.
Where did I put...
Oh, okay.
I put my AirPods over here.
This guy loves talking about the fact that he has AirPods.
Oh, my AirPods. I'm wondering where my AirPods are in this room.
Those are my headphones that I get because I'm a working man and they're $15 and I buy
them.
Those two broke for me.
Broke boy.
Yeah, I'm the broke boy.
Broke boy never rich again.
There's a third one. I knew a third one was coming. Third banger from Patrick. Broke boy
never rich again.
I'll be my name.
What about old boy never young again?
boy never talked to my daughter again yeah there's different boys you could be
mm-hmm Nintendo boy Nintendo boy mm-hmm never tried to get that username and
never bored again people already had Nintendo boy never bored again
well it's so fun to play and if I had Nintendo game boy never bored again oh
Oh my god.
You just changed my life.
That's like a...
Wow.
You just put me on a different path my friend.
Oh my god.
Oh my god that felt so good.
You guys think I could be...
iCarly?
What is that?
That's just the guy with the big sword and he walks down the street.
He just carries it down the street.
Yeah he just drags it down the street.
His pyramid head.
He just chases somebody.
Yeah.
Very slowly though.
You guys think I could become like a Nintendo YouTuber?
Probably pretty easily.
Yeah, I think there's a few people who are we know who just you just do it. Yeah. Yeah, you can just do it, dude
Yeah, just do it. You think I could I could be like what's up gamers?
Yeah, you can always tell so fucking easily. I was telling Caleb about this on like Pluto TV. They have like a
Gaming like section where they just play like let's plays
I was just like flipping through everything on Pluto TV and they have a roblox channel
Whoa, and I think you could be one of those guys if you wanted to yeah
Literally I like I turned it
It's like it was like it felt like a magic spell to make me die when I was watching it
It was the worst things I've ever seen feels me on there. They'd call it Poodo TV
They would cuz all the pootsie. Yeah, no
Cuz you're a little I'm not very well
No, but it was literally it was just a guy like playing roblox and it's being just like yeah talking like what's up guys?
Okay, this is crazy
but it is like every other word you just like put an effect on his voice and like this face would like change like change colors
And like it like just like literally like it just felt like a shit sick dude. It's so it's crazy. What like I
I'm I live in fear of what yeah, it's like when I was watching let's plays in middle school
I settled for this a guy talking in a monotone voice
for an hour with nothing.
I mean that shit was boring as fuck though.
I hated watching it. I watched like episode
one of every let's play and then I was just like
yeah I don't even care. I shut it off halfway
through like I don't give a shit. Yeah I always think like
I would always think like oh I can't like
play this game so I'll watch someone else play it and then I'd try
to watch it and be like this isn't worth it.
I'll just pretend the game doesn't exist.
I don't want it anymore. I can't watch Pluto TV anymore.
Yeah? Yeah. I changed
a channel to this one channel and it
was just a camera of the back of my head watching
I just gave up on it. That's how it's free though. That's true. That's how they pay for it. Yeah.
I look back there's nothing behind me. Yeah. It's a very scary experience. You know what,
on Pluto TV Fail Army, they sometimes they'll play the ones where it's like dads hurting
their kids by accident. Yeah. Those dads should be put to death. I agree. They just play the
Daddy of Five videos. That segment makes me so mad. Careless dads hitting their kids in
the face because they're trying to do a fortnite dance.
Dude, that shit does not fly as well.
I literally, I want to kill them.
Do you remember that shit, Daddyof5?
The YouTube guy that just like, abused
his kids and was like,
"This is funny as shit, this is good
content." No. No.
Damn, that was a crazy saga. What did he did?
He like,
did this, it was this thing called
the invisible ink prank where him and his wife just
put a bunch of like,
disappearing ink on their carpet
and like call their kids into the room and just like screaming at them like
"What the fuck did you do?" and the kids like crying
and he's like "It's just a prank!" like he like made the kids like cry like so hard.
He did hood pranks with his own children.
Uh-huh.
Holy shit.
And then he would make the kids fight each other but one of them like two of
them were like his kids from a previous marriage.
And he was married to like a WWE superstar.
It was like a little nerdy kid and then he would have like the oldest son just like it's like oh go into his room
And throw this at him and just like that just like making his kids like well each other up for content. That's sick
Yeah, it's tight. Did they take his kids they did
Kids yeah, the kids are getting bullied the most I think he broke the kids Xbox once
And that's I mean you have to do that. Yeah
Everybody had at least like my I had a friend who his like his mom threw away
his computer so many times. Yeah. Once a year she would just throw his
laptop in the trash. Yeah. And because she gets so mad that he like didn't do the
dishes or something. Yeah. It's pretty sick dude. I'll just get it taken away.
Yeah. Yeah but then I would always like just go get it again like probably
within the hour. I always kept my mom always forgot I had anything. Yeah. So
she'd be like, when I was like, you know, 15,
she'd be like, you can't leave your room
for the rest of the day.
And I'd be like, swag.
- Yeah.
- Like I don't own a book, you fucking idiot.
Like it's all just, I have DVDs in my room.
What are you gonna do?
- Do your parents ever try to implement the like,
it's like, oh, you can only play video games
for X amount of hours or whatever?
- Yeah.
- Fuck no.
- That shit was the worst.
Yeah, I think they gave up on that in middle school and I discovered like...
They tried that every two weeks and then gave up on it within the hour because we would
just fight each other?
Yeah.
Well, for me it was just that like, yeah, that was all I did.
So you couldn't...
Yeah.
Right, me too.
My mom would try to get me off the computer and it was just like, this is all I do.
Yeah.
put a they tried to put a like a a fucking web like watcher on my computer
yeah like blocked me from shit and they didn't realize you could just close the
app yeah yeah so I just oh yeah that was yeah
all day you my uncle my uncle Paul I think I talked about this before but my
uncle Paul like tried to put like a he put like a alien you put right put a bug
in my computer no he tried to put like a it was like a thing that every time you
went to a new web page you would have to type in a password and only my mom knew
the password so I just kept going to like a website that would just keep having
like pop-up windows and then eventually my mom got so annoyed by it that he made
her him like shut it off she's just like look I don't know I just I guess my kids
are gonna see bad shit on the internet yeah and one of the things one of his
examples was like oh look at these watching fucking porky pigs swearing
Porky Pig shouldn't be swearing.
Do you guys remember the first like naughty thing you saw?
Like the first bad flash video?
I saw the first...
The raunchy flash video.
I tried to go to...
I thought askjeeves.com before it was just ask.com.
I went to askjeeves.com, got a pop-up that said like "Find your dream girl" and it was
a nude woman and I got so scared that my parents were going to see that that I closed the laptop
and I ran to my room.
I mine was it was this video that was it was like a like a newgrounds video and it
was like a like a kid's cartoon of a guy saying like singing the ABCs and then at
the end he was like he's like next time what won't you suck my dick fuck you
I just wanted to know why he sees. No. It was awesome dude. He's like, fuck you suck my
dick. Fuck you. I think, do you know that that one, uh, this, this is different, but
you know that one weird Al song that's about like, like Santa killing everybody. Oh yeah.
We printed out the, the, the lyrics to that. I had that like in elementary school. Yeah.
That one. I think that was probably, I don't know. There's probably something I don't remember
though. There was a big one. The flash video of him killing all the elves and shit, that
was cool. Happy Tree Friends was up there too. Happy Tree Friends like scared me too much
I think. Me too, I like to watch it. I like watched one and I was like oh my god. That
follow up video. Honestly, when you're a kid it's as bad as an ISIS beheading video. Yeah,
it's so scary. Dude that follow up video, follow up boy video, Carpal Tunnel of Love
is a Happy Tree Friends like collab and I saw that and I was like why are they doing this?
like these sweet animals yeah why are they doing I just didn't understand like
with it it could be like funny or like I was just like what like I thought it
yeah that's like yeah that's like oh like this is that's like the equivalent
of like a dark web video yeah when you're when you're a kid yeah exactly
like why does this not as if you're watching this is yeah two guys want it
should be arrested for making somebody needs to arrest these these branches and
things that the squirrels are falling on to.
Alright, this list here.
Top 10 best letters in the English alphabet.
If you're wondering why we went long on the non-list stuff today,
it's because they don't like this list, but I think it's a great list.
Number one is A. What do you guys think of the letter A?
I think the letter A is doing too much.
Yeah? Here's the top comment here.
Such a revolutionary yet grotesquely beautiful letter.
Words can't describe how linearly three of those lines form
with graceful angles making such a perfectly shaped triangle of such sheer
beauty bound within those strong lines there's some words right there bitch with
the letter a you have the power to save even the worst world problems currently
existing in this planet called earth but not many people understand this letter
is the way and the true meaning that unlocks the essence of life what was that
I got supper yeah junkyard dudes without a earth is just earth that's so true
A is the angelic letter and represents the number one. A is awesome in all ways. Say
it with grades or with always coming at first. Even in alphabates, it represents the first
letter. Awesome! Wow. I think this letter sucks. I'm not a fan of A either. I think
A is for assholes and asshats. Yup. Yeah. Fuck it. Easy A? Yeah, more like fuck you
A. Talking about that movie? Yeah. With the fucking Emma Stone. Stupid ass bitch. I don't
I don't remember her name.
I respect her as an actress.
I'd like to kick some dirt under her shins.
No!
Disrespect her shoes a little.
She needs to go to the dentist.
She's good in Superbad.
She needs to get a paddle.
She needs to be paddled by the principal.
What other movie is she in?
Easy A.
She was in Easy A.
She was also in Superbad and Easy A.
And then I think back in 2008 she was in Superbad.
I remember Easy A, the whole thing with that movie.
And then I think back in like 2008, she was in Superbad.
Yeah.
I remember Easy A, the whole thing with that movie was like,
what if she might show her nipples in this?
And she didn't. It was like, this movie's fucking stupid, bro.
It's about the Scarlet Letter and then we had to read the Scarlet Letter in school,
so they'd be like, oh, well, this is like, oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's just like Easy A.
Can you guys just draw like literally a big circle and then a small circle on the board?
I feel like a bunch of like English teachers probably paid the director of that movie to
to make it yeah yeah can you can you can you as you know teachers control
Hollywood yeah that's literally true they yeah they literally did yeah that's why
there's so many facts and movies oh yeah I mean ever heard of documentaries ever
have you ever thought about the fact that almost every movie has a lesson oh
damn the Fox colony that's Hollywood calling to silence us for does the
teachers union yeah calling right now dude oh my god there's a red sniper dot
on your floor yeah oh my god oh my god it's pointing to all the information on
your head oh my god they're putting more information in there I got it's
definitely a teacher no he's pointing at the at the relevant parts of your face
no here's another comment I like this letter five out of ten because I don't
really like the three sticks hmm that was my comment I made that the three sticks
I posted that Allah start from a so I am proud my name start from a I am very
lucky I think that might be a really good guy that might be my new kind of
guy yeah the name you changed it my crush's name starts with this letter I'm
I'm gonna change my name to Allah when I become a white Muslim.
Just like not understanding at all.
It's like everyone at your new church is mad at you.
Yeah.
What? My name's Allah?
What the hell?
That's like our number one guy, you fucking idiot.
Look, I learned about this shit last week.
Number two.
Now I'm the fourth right scholar on it.
So y'all like Vinnie Pass?
What's up?
Jerimon, heavenly divine, steadily shining 99.
(laughing)
- Do you think he like crushes at his mosque?
- Probably.
- Do you think like he let his mosque like him?
- Oh yeah.
- You think so?
- He's famous, right?
So.
- Yeah, well kinda, yeah.
- He probably gives back.
- But he's famous also for like talking about like
shooting the Pope in the head.
And he shows up at the mosque.
- Well, the Muslims would like that.
- I guess, I don't know.
- Yeah, right?
That's what they want, right?
- That's the whole thing.
- You know all the religions have like a big like,
like anchorman style battle at the end of the year.
Yeah, they'll meet in a parking lot.
It's Vinnie Paz, it's...
Vinnie Paz, Chris Pratt, Woody Allen.
Who's a Catholic in the Pope?
This is just the Pope.
Did I say, oh, Chris Pratt?
Chris Pratt I thought is a normal Christian.
Oh, well he's Hollywood Christian so it doesn't really matter.
Yeah, so he's not Catholic.
he's not actually yeah what are the other religions Oh the guy plays Dwight mm-hmm
oh yeah behind yeah it's just only him yeah there's no crew behind him yeah
blah blah church or something Richard Richard Dawkins for the pasta for oh
yeah oh I think Stephen Fry for the pasta far ends and Richard Dawkins for
the atheists.
Yeah.
Then, Tey Zonday, I don't know, he's there singing music.
Well, they have to have a soundtrack.
Yeah, he's over in the corner playing piano like an old saloon.
He stops playing when he first sees them, then the fight starts and he starts playing
again.
Nick Kroll with the caveman's?
Uh-huh.
Nick Kroll with the caveman religion.
I think maybe uh...
what other
well are you gonna do you so it's like for the catholics is it each branch of
catholics like is it like the irish catholics and the roman catholics? no catholics all one
fucking thing
yeah
they all follow one guy
uh...
alright so i think it's maybe the pope is not there
he's like the most famous guy he's off getting his dick sucked
the fuck? no he's not he doesn't get his dick sucked dude
No.
That guy's horny as fuck.
No he isn't.
Yes he is.
No.
Nah, he's, you know.
Don't say that.
He's like, every-
He's definitely horny.
Every picture of him, you ever seen him?
He's got like, both hands and his tongue's out and he's like, looking at ass.
You know, the Pope.
Yeah.
He's always like, "Ahh!"
Oh, I forgot about that.
Yeah.
I forgot about that picture.
You haven't heard his song, "I Love to Eat Ass"?
I forgot about that song.
Yeah.
That was a good song, too.
It was like, really good.
It's like, "Back that thing up, let me smell it!"
Yeah.
if you do know that we're a god i'ma tell it
if you don't you will go to
helix
really bad very bad there
and how it's so that
yes it's not a good
he's like an image doom
where it is a lot of wordplay but it is a lot of s play to the guy does a lot of
turd play a
that
uh...
damn
number two favorite letters s and i want one of you to read this time twister and
the top comment on the show she says i think that's not what it says we got on
the got the image got this
which one
but i came with a tongue twister that involves a letter to super sally
sirens wing some inside and sons of sirens and some inside and so sorry
someone silly salt so silly salt some insulted soup so super salty should
share seats to eat the soup
Wow dude try saying that five times.
I know right.
That's tough.
Yeah it's a good one.
I love this letter because it is so commonly used and it's the first letter of my last
name in the last letter of the middle name.
So true.
My name starts with an S. I'm not going to tell my name because my name is Chinese.
It starts with C idiot.
Wait what?
My name is Chinese.
I am Chinese.
Instant plural creator.
Here's a comment from Borat.
It's a very sweet ladder.
Damn, it's crazy they got Borat on here.
How did they get Borat for this?
I know, right?
Amazon doing promo for Borat 2.
Too good a letter and just too cool.
Facts.
Because my sister loves it.
Tell me more about Keteress.
My country names start with this letter, so I love it.
My name starts with S, and that's from Sean.
Someone had all three, I saw in an earlier comment, all three names start with an S.
Whoa.
It seems a bit of a snake-ish human to me.
Yes, it is for the best courtoon, SpongeBob.
Sis, sis, ultimately say superest sensational setter.
Now that's a good one.
The thing is like, what are some...
I can only think of bad things when I think of the letter S.
I think of bad words.
Yeah, put two of those together, it's the worst thing in the world.
Sinister.
Snake, Sinister, SJW.
Yep.
Yeah.
Okay.
Socialism.
Sisterhood.
Hate that shit.
Yeah.
Some guy named Adolf Hitler.
Yuck.
Yeah.
Sucking off Adolf Hitler.
Oh!
Seeing Adolf Hitler in your bathroom.
Smoking with Adolf Hitler when you see him in your bathroom.
all this is bad did
you know summoning adolf hitler with a ritual in the floor
not gonna do the running circle meant to some in a dollar filler
summoning it's a summoning materials for a couple of summer in ritual
some of the stuff i'm using with my two friends will record a podcast to some in
a dollar for
subtraction
subtracting one friend as a sacrifice for a dollar
so that's why i don't like that word
yeah shooting my friend because he didn't turn in a little filler when the
summoning circle was done some blood on the ground
super happy when it'll finally appears
and watches some t_v_ with me
i don't think i would have a little bit of a home with no dinner because he
misbehaved
and he you know he always do that
sending a dollar a christmas card on accident
he's not going to like that
it's a big about it very hated christmas super embarrassed when i say
merry christmas instead of happy holidays to a dollar filler
so sad when it all that he is so sad when it all fit where is my airbnb host in
argentina
such ugly decoration
in a bill that was there to be a peak
stupid dog named blondie
and i think that
so crazy he that this happened to be in argentina
in september
Sumptuous paella created by Adolf Hitler, my Airbnb host.
Scrumptious dinner.
Scrumptious...
Schnitzel and sausages.
Made by my Airbnb host, Adolf Hitler.
So old, my 100 year old.
Shit, food poisoning.
So terrible experience at Adolf Hitler Airbnb.
So long, Adolf Hitler.
Super clogged toilet at Airbnb, hosted by Adolf Hitler.
Sitting next to me on the flight home, Adolf Hitler?
*laughter*
So why are you going to New York, I ask Adolf Hitler.
Sneaking around the plane in disguise.
Some plans, he says.
Super long mustache now.
*laughter*
Super thin but long mustache.
Oh dude, like an Adolf Hitler Fu Manchu, just come on, single.
*laughter*
I don't know.
What if he did like some kung fu I learned?
Staying with me?
Adolf Hitler is?
Say I.
Oh no you don't.
Stupid ass.
Seeing him hail a cab is funny.
Yeah, but the letter s is pretty yeah pretty good third letter e e
Yeah
Fuck my BFF Ellie is awesome. She is energetic and everything you can possibly be that's so true. Here's
My name is Emmett Martin
That's all it says.
It's twice in a row.
Oh cool, now we're doxing people in the podcast.
English starts with L.
Here's my name is Emmett Martin, it begins with E. Another comment.
I'm Emmett Martin, best letter.
There's gotta be more, right?
Let's see.
Oh no, the last comment's just yes.
Alright, fourth best letter, Z.
Z?
I feel like Z is maybe number one, dude.
Z is pretty good.
is the rarest letter. It's one of the most exclusive letters. You ever play the uh Scrabble? The
alphabet game in the car? You try to find all the letters? Dude, Z, J, and Q. Those are some
rare letters. Yeah. J you'd think you'd see more often because of how many people are
named Jim. Yeah but people don't usually, that's like gone out of vogue to put your
first name as a vanity plate on the back of your car. I remember there was years, everybody
had a fucking just their name I'm a shit ton of vanity plates Doug hmm
zoo Hitler bought in New York this is bad news zebras that I wonder what it's like
with SS stripes I wonder what it's like to be a cop when you're like you like
calling in like a pursuit on a guy with a vanity plate yeah yeah yeah
Red Lamborghini, license plate says Tweety Bird
TWTYBRD
License plate says Hitler
I saw, I don't know if I can say it
because it's like an antiquated slur
but I saw a license plate in Boston that had
ok then they did it on purpose yeah and it had a big bald eagle on the back of the truck
That's cool. What did it say?
Can I... Hold on.
Can we pause it?
I'll pause it.
Alright, my bad. It was a different word.
It was mulatta.
Yeah, he said it. You know what Pat says?
If it's good enough for Huck Finn, it's good enough for him.
[laughter]
You said I could say it.
No, I didn't.
We said not to say it.
That kid in overalls holding a frog behind you.
Check this one. I found Link and Park.
Link and Park is so good.
I have a lot of license plates.
I had a folder on my old phone of all the license plates.
I really wish I got a picture of Mayhem.
That's my favorite one I've seen.
Check this one out.
I found Agony.
Agony is way better than Mayhem.
It was on a poor focus.
New Hampshire plate that just says Estrogen.
That's good.
My favorite is still the one I saw in LA that just said Da World.
New Hampshire plate.
Evil Dead.
around it that says I love my Siberian Husky.
Yeah. This is a good, this is the best one I ever saw. Oh I did, I did. This was, this was
it, so there was a dentist that when I lived in Laconia and I went to community
college there I would ride my bike past a dentist's office and one of the
dentists had Killary as his license plate. That is the sickest shit I've ever seen. Yeah. I did see, I saw, I saw, I saw DC Joker with a
the bumper sticker that said I don't play well with others on it and I saw a
sports car with black Goku as a license plate that's so this is a handicapped
New Hampshire plate it says meme that's good and then the main one that says
L'chaim cool with a lobster on it you should be able to get you know you can
get the handicap like the guy in the wheelchair on the back you should be
able to get anything there I think yeah I should be able to get bad luck Brian on
my on my that'd be good. Here's one. Yiffin. Okay. You know, like furry sex. I
don't know anything about that. I know a lot about it. This one. Groot. Groot is
good. New Hampshire. Dude, New Hampshire vanity plates are so good. Yeah, it's
freedom. Yeah, it's about freedom there. Yeah, this one nihilist. Oh, sick. I saw
that in the parking lot of I'm pissed off. I'll never think of a better one
and then agony.
I feel like that's like the funniest one to me.
This is a crazy one I saw in New York.
What is that guy's?
E1 patron.
Yo!
That was in New York?
Yeah.
E1 patron?
I guess someone who's a big fan.
It says E1 patron and there's a picture of Scooby Doo and Shaggy on the back.
I wonder what that actually means.
I think that's Branson's car.
That might be Branson's car.
Not a bad idea.
Yeah, if it fit I would love to get one that was like suffering on like the worst car ever.
This one, Black and Tan.
Nice.
I'm flipping that car off when I see it.
That's sick dude.
I flipped that shit off.
You don't like black and tans?
Oh well you already said the mulatta thing so.
No.
That's not what that means.
I heard that.
This is one I keep seeing in my neighborhood.
Eurekan and this guy, it's a van with truck nuts.
That's sick dude.
That's tight.
Van nuts.
And then hi, you mad?
I saw that one yesterday.
yesterday. That's a really good. You mad that is good. That's so good dude. I
can't find the mulatto. Where did that go? You should get a cool out of here's
a here's a
I feel like a good one. Be like screaming. Yeah, yeah, that'd be good
whaling yeah beefing i beefed my fart my fart my gas yeah oh here it is my smell
that with it with a giant fucking with your eyes that's on the on the wrap the rope eagle eye vinyl
on the back of the i want a truck that i could just i mean like you dress it up like a barbie
doll when you have a truck like that yeah i want one of those so bad dude yeah do you see this though
That's pretty cool. Number five is B. Where?
You didn't scare me.
Dude, I'm so skittish.
You got so fucking scared.
I'm so skittish. You guys have seen me whenever like a truck honks a horn and I go like, "Ahh!"
True.
But then I realized that it's, I was like with my mom, I visited my mom a couple weeks ago,
or a week ago and she does the same thing.
Just like runs in my family. We're like all like very like loud noises freak us
all out really.
"Ahh! Stop! See I told you!"
It's like a completely... the reaction I can't control.
It's like you're hitting the top of my kneecap.
I just instinctively go like "Ahh! Don't do it again!"
Alright this guy's got the right idea. Beer, boobs, butt, babes, bacon, great job.
*Janna screams*
*laughter*
Stop!
It's not funny!
It scares me! I knew you were gonna do it too!
You leaned over, I knew that you were gonna do that!
And it still got me!
*laughter*
Dude, every time I get out of the shower, Janna...
*Janna screams* Stop!
Stop!
It's not funny!
Every time I get out of the shower, Janna stands
Right out so this isn't gonna get me this one won't give me I can see how close you're getting
You talking so Jana gets it stop
Listening to you Jana stands outside of the shower and I get out and she screams at me and I gets really it really scares
Me yeah, but let her be let's go back to let me
See
Just lean in and read the cover.
AHHHHH!
NO!
*laughter*
He's done. What's the next letter? I'm white as a sheet. No, you're as red as a red sheet.
Next letter, number six is X. Yeah, shout out to Xavier. That's our boy. Letters that start
with Z sound cool. Change that Z to an X and now it looks cool. True. Symmetrical and underused.
Plus you know it's all about...
AHHHHH! Stop!
Alright, I'm serious. We have to stop.
It's going to be too loud.
People won't like it. It's not very fun.
It's not fun to get...
It's not fun.
I'm serious.
You have to do a sound.
I have sensitive ears.
I love X.
I used to put XXX a lot.
Whoa, hold up.
What do you mean by that?
Nobody uses this thing.
I use it.
It's in my fucking search bar.
Number seven is M.
That one, oh that's just a list of words.
Yep.
It makes such an appealing, comforting sound and starts some of my favorite words, which I appreciate for the way they sound or how it feels to say them.
Melody, music, moxie, marvelous, m-
(yells)
- God damn it, dude.
- No, I'm controlling it now.
You've done it too much, I told you.
- You overdid it.
- And you leaned in and I knew you were gonna do it.
- I'm desensitized.
- I'm going back and editing them all out.
- You soured it.
- I thought I had one more in me.
- No, it's because there's no situation normally
where you would try to read a list of words this long.
- You would literally be--
- It was way too out of character.
You started the first word and I was like, really?
- Yeah, I was like, wait,
Pat really wants to like read the list.
- Hmm.
- What?
- Look, I--
- He's not like eating a chip.
See, that wasn't loud enough.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, although the hand kind of got, it almost got me.
- Yeah, he outstretched his hand like a 3D movie.
But Pat kind of ruined everything.
- Yeah, I think I got fucked up.
- He scared me enough.
I think I'm over my fear of loud noises.
- Yeah, we did CBT. - And sudden.
- Congratulations.
- I'm over my-- - We did CBT on Caleb.
- I used to have a real fear of--
- Yeah, I have a fear of immersion therapy.
- Okay, I'll say that. - Caleb Pits.
guys, I'd like to thank you both. I used to have a real fear of sudden things,
but now I've gotten over that fear and now sudden suddenly doesn't ever scare
me anymore. Suddenly the number eight is C. Well, that's scary. It starts with
suddenly. That's true. That's C. I love C.
It's my favorite letter because I'm Caden with the C and I'm the biggest
Ryan C. Crest
Ryan Seacrest.
Siri says, with a C, says, "Take a guess while I voted for this one."
True.
Damn.
Number 9 is L, Caleb's favorite letter.
Number 10 is J, Patrick's favorite letter.
Yeah, because it's backwards L.
Because he smoked a damn J.
Joking with my guest.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Who does not care for the letter J.
Bye.