You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Man.
- Oh, okay.
- Hey.
- We're back on the computer this episode.
- It's 'cause we're calling in a man.
Oh man, he's on his private jet.
He couldn't be tied down tonight.
- He's in his private submarine.
- Yeah.
what's up with some similar
you're swimming right now
my son was a submarine swims
yes it doesn't look at the rise he doesn't have to be doesn't have to know
what a separate car walk you idiot
no one's
who
that's it
though i did not mean to move to the smallest monologue people are that's why
you're so
richard you have a submarine
uh...
jimmy is with us this week because he
is going to be taking over the for the most part the twitch channel and uh wanted to get
the word out we're doing the classic thing of just having hiring a mexican guy to do something
we don't want to do
it's just like one of the best moves honestly yeah works every time that we got to the point
that we were able to do that it's true i mean i never thought the goal in life right never
thought we'd make it but you know here we are. I was like this is maybe this
isn't a great idea and then I remembered my dad's back deck is like immaculate
yeah and he kind of did the same thing. It's really advanced stuff so I'm hoping
I'll be streaming building decks. No don't do that no that's not what I mean. Okay yeah. Don't do racist shit
That's gonna get us in trouble.
- I'll be sure to walk into Taco Bell.
- No, you--
- In Queens.
- They don't even, oh, please move to New York City.
- What do I have to do?
- Move to New York and you work at the Taco Bell
and we get free Taco Bell?
- That would be so incredible.
I mean, it also would work with any other
fast food restaurant, but it should be Taco Bell.
- Yeah.
Why should it be Taco Bell, Cameron?
- 'Cause he just, you know,
there's just something about the Taco Bell.
- What do you mean?
- There's just something delicious about Taco Bell food
and the people that make it.
- What kind of people make Taco Bell food?
- Just like these crazy people.
(laughing)
Just these crazy weird people.
- I actually brought, I brought Julio to the Taco Bell
for the first time in his life and he hated it.
It was like so upsetting.
I honestly thought he was gonna be like,
"This is beast, this is exactly what Mexican food is like."
This is like--
- I said it was fine.
I liked it.
- I don't think you even finished your fucking burrito, dude.
- Yes I did!
Now I was like still hungry. I was like...
Wait, you...
You threw something away.
I did not.
You did.
Such a liar.
No, I had a Crunchwrap, whatever it's called.
Whoa, okay.
You didn't remember Crunchwrap and forget Supreme.
Yeah, that one.
I had a quesadilla and the soda.
The green soda. I had the green thing.
Baja Blast.
I went in there, I can have the green thing, and they gave me a big, big, big bottle of green stuff.
I don't think they'll give you a bottle.
They don't give you a bottle, dude.
You have to admit Baja Blast is really fucking good.
That should be a Mexican food staple, I think.
It's just like Jarritos.
Jarritos?
It's pretty good.
I'm Colombian now.
Last night I learned a man came up to me at a bar last night,
pointed at me and said,
"You're Colombian."
and then for like 20 minutes just kept trying to talk to me about being
Colombian mm-hmm yeah and I think Caleb probably remembers more than I do but
yeah I sat there for like about Colombian being Colombian for a minute
and then he turned to me and started saying many Pacquiao number number one
many no no no he wasn't saying he was saying many Pacquiao basura what many
Pacquiao Basura. What does that mean? That Manny Pacquiao's trash. Yeah. What? Really? Yeah.
I know Basura. I don't know any other Spanish. I don't know a lot of Spanish. And then he tried to box me. Oh yeah, he was trying to box you at the bar.
What do you say this? Did he look at Caleb and was like, this guy's a Filipino and I hate my abacado. I think he maybe thought that Pat was Colombian and I'm Filipino.
He thought, no, he thought I was Colombian and just kept in, he was adamant that I was
Colombian and was only speaking to me in Spanish and I kept saying like "Hey, no
hablo, no hablo, I'm Irish, I'm 100% Irish."
"Yo soy Irish."
Yeah, "Yo soy Irish, no hablo, no hablo," and he just would not stop. He just was just
could just like did not accept that I wasn't Colombian. He looked at my
He looked at my roommate Alex pointed up and said Venezuelan and then
Real life they live glasses
He knows that I'm secretly Filipino, yeah, yeah. Yeah. What do you miss the most of it with the Philippines the chocolate?
Okay, then the the
the sandwiches the you know, you know
The Cuba has the Cuban and every other you every country has to have a sandwich is just named after the country
So I like the Philippines
It's one sandwich, it's the Philippine the Philips exit the Philippines
It's a it's a pizza that has it's got spaghetti
Yeah, and fried chicken. It's a sandwich with spaghetti and I only know skittles on it
Yeah, it is funny that somebody like somebody who is inventing all the food in the Philippines watched elf with
Will Ferrell and was like yeah, we're gonna make all that
Although like maple syrup spaghetti shit, that's gonna be like our whole thing. I think that Filipino food is the best
At the best fry you're telling me you're telling me that that will ferrell ripped off the look I said, I don't think so
I don't think so as a Colombian
The Philippines exists. I've been what Columbia is nowhere near fucking the Philippines as a Colombian
I'm not stupid
What do you think I'm stupid just cuz I'm Colombian now. No, you're not Colombian. I'm Colombian
I'm full Colombian now the most popular Filipino foods the most
roast pig candy canes candy corns
Pin am I right? Okay. This looks good. What is what is pin a pig?
For like a pig type deal. No, it's like rice
You are getting into the list - - yeah, you know, I went to the video
I went to that dim sum place that we went when you were in town. Oh, you went to China
I went to China because there's a part of Queens that is just it's literally China like it's
not like Chinatown and you're in a whole different world it rules and I went to this place called
Asian Jewels and I was so good when Juvia was in town we went and I went today and do
you remember they you ordered off like a menu when we went yeah yeah so this time I walked
in they sat us down and immediately like a lady came by with like a cart like I was on
a train and handed just handed me I had no choice you just started putting like
giant like shrimp meatballs all over the table that's how does some works they
ask you what you want and you they didn't ask me what I wanted at all no
that's how I did say no cuz she was just piling the same shrimp meatball over and
over and over again like she thought it was my favorite food in the world and I
like we ordered like fucking 12 of these I guess and like they were Filipino
That's a classic Filipino dish.
Well, yeah, it must be that.
But once it was on the table, I can't be like, "Hey, will you put this back in the cart?
I don't want to eat 50 shrimp meatballs."
So I just felt like shit all day.
I just had shrimp in my stomach all day long.
Dude, I had a shrimp incident too.
I don't know.
Do you tell?
Same situation?
Yeah, I had a shrimp incident.
I went to the grocery store and they had like a thing of ceviche in a plastic like one of
those like the grab and go fridge.
I bought ceviche from the grab and go and then ate it and the shrimp was just like mealy
and like it dissolved in my mouth and I was like I can't eat that.
And I spent like five dollars on it and like had to throw it out.
- The shrimp was pretty fucked up.
These meatballs looked like,
it looked like it was like a creature.
One of them still had a tail poking out of the top.
- Well that's a garnish.
The tail is a garnish.
- No, no, it was like stuck,
it was like a full shrimp that didn't get mashed up
in the meatball.
- Oh, okay. - It was sticking out.
I think there was a big eye on one side as well.
(laughing)
- A shrimp eye?
- No, a human eye.
- A human eye.
- Yeah.
A shrimp with a human eye was poking out of your meatball?
Yeah, pretty much.
It was very scary.
And there were a hundred of them on your table?
There was a hundred to a hundred thousand.
And they each had an eye and a tail?
Yeah, they each had an eye and they looked at me and they were talking to me the entire
time.
And I ate so much of it.
Why do you keep eating it?
Because I was like, I'm going to fucking, okay, here's the fucked up part.
I was like, oh my God, dude, they put so much food on this table.
Like, I have to eat it all because this has got to be like $200 worth of food.
You ate it?
I ate like as much as I could.
I stuffed myself with these disgusting cold shrimp meatballs and then I get to the front
and I hand the guy my ticket and he like does some math, hands it back.
The entire thing was $28.
Whoa.
I gotta fucking, I gotta go to this place.
We didn't eat like half of these fucking shrimp.
No, don't go there.
I'm saying do not go there.
It's good. It's good. It was fucking evil today. They did something and also it was
it was so it was suspicious because they at some point this is what was
suspicious about it at one point you know we're sitting there eating our
shrimp meatballs and then I look up and I noticed that everybody else is eating
like delicious noodles like nobody else has anything even remotely close to what
we had they didn't give us a like everybody everything else had a menu
that they were looking at so we walked in sat down and then they just like dumped
the like bad shrimp you might have said the bad food table I must have had it
like a shrimp it's like the shrimp themed table or something like the
shrimp lovers delight that would be a good they should have that like it like
I mean a hell yeah like if you should like walk into McDonald's and you sit at
a table it's like oh if you sit at this table they bring you like five McChickens
That's like a chicken table you could sit it that way I never have to look at the menu or go order you sit where you
Want the food from you just get McChickens just and then you just keep coming
You could get up your flow and something different
Don't you think that those other people are table eating? You know noodles maybe ask for those noodles?
Option I was
To the server like I couldn't I couldn't I was buried in shrimp. Yeah, I literally they couldn't hear me if I yelled
I was struck. They needed to call the fire department. I was covered in shrimp. I swear to God
It was a fucking nightmare
And then there was like one thing that didn't have shrimp in it and we all just like fought over it like it was like a
Big point of contention at the lunch. Oh wait you like you didn't get anything, but shrimp is what you're saying
It was literally all shrimp actually the one thing that I said I'd be in heaven it was it was sharp
- Shumai, which is like--
- Is it shumai shrimp?
- Shumai has shrimp in it.
- Yeah.
- Shumai is shrimp.
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
It was pork with like a little less shrimp on it
than most of the other shit.
But it was still shrimpy and it just felt,
dude, I like walked around smelling my own burps
and wanting to vomit all day.
- Dude, I fucking, I love eating,
like shrimp is my favorite food.
- Shrimp is like--
- Put you through the shrimp gauntlet.
- Shrimp is one of those fucking, yeah,
I will take you there and put you
the $30 shrimp gauntlet. I'll fucking, I'll pass with flying colors. You will not defeat the boss.
I will defeat the boss level of shrimp. No, no, no, no. I do feel like if I had eaten the entire thing
like they would have brought out like a, like a, like a bigger shrimp. Yeah, like the shrimp from
like the like Bubba Gump logo. Oh my god, I did that thing in a heartbeat. Are you kidding me?
To defeat and fight. I'd fucking, I'd destroy that thing. Patrick, you wanna go to Bubba Gump with me
in Cancun? Yes. Okay, I'm going to go to Cancun. Oh my god, I went to, so I think I've talked about
this before, but I went to a Bubba Gump in Universal Studios Orlando with my ex-girlfriend
and it was just like me and her and then like this Australian family. The way that Bubba Gump works
is they put you in a different like section like quadrant section things like there's like
different spots in a bubblegum. They put you in different quadrant sections. So it's like
the shrimp zone it's the same system from the dim sum place where you sit that's where they
what they bring. It's one of those well no it's just like a weird thing where they put us in this
like room and it was just me and this me my ex-girlfriend at a table and then an Australian
at Bubba Gump in China.
(laughter)
This is the worst dim sum ever.
It was us at this
fucking Bubba Gump and we're in this room
and the
you know at Bubba Gump it's a
Forrest Gump themed restaurant
so like
Do people think you work there?
Yes. No, they uh
the waiter comes out and
starts like, he's like alright well
You know, while you wait, um, you know, they're playing like Forrest Gump on every TV, we're like watching it.
While you wait, we can do some Forrest Gump trivia, and he starts like doing trivia.
The fucking Australian family has never seen Forrest Gump.
So, it's me, and it's just my table and this family who has never seen Forrest Gump.
I find out then
She's also never seen Forrest Gump, so I had to just do Forrest Gump trivia by myself
Until I got my food. So you did work there. Yeah, how dare they you don't get to go there
I feel like if you didn't want to do the trivia you could have just stayed silent
I don't think you had to do trivia
Until your food got there
You know I felt bad
I felt bad this dude came into the room
Yeah I could have fucking done that
You could have been like I don't want to do trivia
that's a requirement for their job like
yes I have to do this. If somebody walks in and is doing
fucking trivia at you like yeah they
have to fucking do that. I feel like he
would have gotten in trouble if I like
nobody wanted the trivia. I'm sure that's what was going through your head when you when you were
spouting off your favorite Forrest Gump facts
for 15 minutes straight with no
interruption. Look you know what? The guy wasn't even doing trivia.
He came in to take your order and you just
immediately started rattling off facts about Forrest Gump.
what though I fucking I aced that quiz that's that's one of the first quizzes
I've ever gotten an A on. You aced the Forrest Gump quiz? I did. You know I guess all the
questions are like what is Forrest Gump's girlfriend's name? Yeah it's a quiz
that like Forrest Gump could answer and you yeah that's great. Pat walking into the
Bubba Gump shrimp company is like is like walking into like a Best Buy in a
blue polo shirt. He just feels like he fits in so perfectly. Yeah, that's how I felt at
Margaritaville last night. Oh yeah, Margaritaville. Oh wait, just speaking of like fucked up food,
I ate at a British restaurant and like a couple days ago, not really a restaurant, it was like
a bar but it had food, and I ordered something called bubble and squeak. It was a pub, I believe
That's what they call it. I ordered something off of the menu that was called Bubble and
Squeak and it was one of the worst things I've ever eaten.
What is it?
It's cabbage and potatoes.
Yeah, it's like a quiche.
And some mystery...
No, it's nothing like quiche. It was literally cabbage, potatoes, and a disgusting third
root vegetable that just like...
They usually put an egg on top of it. Did you get an egg?
I didn't get any eggs, dude. It tasted like shit.
That's the squeak.
The squeak is the cabbage.
Because the chicken squeaks.
This chicken doesn't fucking squeak, especially not an egg.
An egg squeaks too.
Yeah, an egg can squeak.
If you like, polish an egg, it can make a squeaking noise while you're rubbing it.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Checkmate, bitch.
Checkmate.
That's not checkmate. You put yourself in checkmate.
Cameron got you.
Yeah, I checkmated you.
You checked out your mate because she's your boyfriend.
And a potato looks like a bubble.
That is true. That's, I believe the potato is the bubble.
The bubble is the boiling water that you put the potatoes in.
Well, they don't serve it with the boiling water, so it's that a potato looks like a bubble.
Okay, good point. I've been chest-mated.
What's the squeak, though? It's the cabbage, right?
The squeak is the cabbage.
Okay. Anyway, that's fucking terrible. Talk about Margaritaville, though. I do want to hear about those.
So, I went to Margaritaville with Ben and Jacques from Seeking Derangements,
and Clark from group project and a couple other people.
- Which podcast were they from?
- I don't know.
I don't even know if they had podcasts.
- Can you not shout them out?
I think Jack's hating them.
- I wanted to give them shout outs
'cause they're my friends.
- No, he hates me.
- Oh yeah.
- Who?
- Jack.
- Oh, Jack.
- Oh yeah, Jack Kashubia, yeah.
- Good point.
- I kept replying to their--
- All right, so let's censor out their name.
- Wait, how did you get Block?
- So Ben and Boop from--
So when they were like, I think it was you guys turning out the promo for the live show.
I think I kept replying like, "No thanks" in an angry emoji.
And then I went to check the account and I was blocked.
And I was like, "Damn, I was joking."
But yeah, I was hanging out with them.
And you know, Margaritaville is a fucked up place.
The restaurant or the real place?
Both.
Uh, we tried to go, like, up the stairs and, uh, we got yelled at.
And then me and Clark were like the- Clark was wearing, like, a wig the whole time.
What was the wig?
It was like a gray wig to make him look like an old man.
We went there with the intention- so Clark found out that there's a synagogue in Margaritaville
because the place where the Margaritaville resort was put in Times Square had a synagogue
in it and I think like legally it has to have a synagogue. So there is a Margaritaville synagogue
and Clark wanted to go there to go to the Rosh Hashanah services the next day and we ended up
like we were pretty much asked to leave. We were like about to go and then like somebody
did you do to the synagogue?
what did you do to the synagogue?
what?
did you wipe it off the face of the planet?
the synagogue is not built yet
the synagogue does not exist yet
yeah, because you wiped it off the face of the earth
you completely
desecrated the synagogue
with a weapon
of mass destruction
you completely destroyed it
yeah, why did you do that?
don't know what kind of answer is that? I was bored. It was a full synagogue. I said I was
bored. That's not good enough for me. Alright, well, I'll figure out a better excuse later.
But Clark insists that we were kicked out because somebody came up to us and said "have a good
night everybody" and then like three security guards popped up behind them. So I think we
were asked to leave sounds like you guys are scared. How do you know there's no security
guards? You're already, I mean it's already a costume night, one of you is wearing a wig.
It could be three, it could be just three men in business suits going to the Margaritaville
resort. Yeah, maybe they just got off their job as security for, I don't know, the best
band in the world and then they just want to go to Margaritaville and enjoy themselves.
the best one in the world. Red Hot Chili Peppers.
Had a lot of fun with that group. Yeah. Would love to get kicked out
of Margaritaville again with them. I'm sure you would if you went back. This
time if we go back we have to wear more disguises. You know like
Clark was in the wig. I think maybe we switch it up. We all wear wigs. Wait, why are you guys
wearing disguises. What do you guys think?
Is it so you can get into the synagogue?
Yeah.
Why do you...
You already did enough damage.
What disguise would I wear to get in there?
I feel like visually, like, I don't know that it matters to wear a disguise to get in,
but I'm curious to know what your plans are to like, you know...
You know, as a...
How would you hide your facial features?
Like any prosthetics on your face that you're thinking of using?
As somebody who just learned that they were Colombian,
I think maybe just like a Colombian flag yarmulke.
That's good. I think maybe that's my only disguise.
Because I'm not ashamed to be a Jewish Columbian man.
Look, regardless of
what time my
my grandfather moved to Columbia,
you know, my grandfather, it doesn't matter what
time in the 40s that he moved
there you know that in nineteen forty five uh...
the unanimous is a hitler
yeah
patricia
it also has been a girl
yes that's right what you're you're cut your beautiful columbian girl like the
mall on the other hand
you're fucking going all over you now pat and you won't be able to you know you
have been three c_o_ patricio
their guard
Oh my god. Can I put you in a little dress?
That name just made me squirt a bit.
[Laughter]
Fuck, I'm squirting.
I don't know. Oh my god.
I think you have such a tight butt.
Me? I bet I could bounce my penis off your ass.
Oh my god. What?
My butt or my butthole?
Which one is loose?
The butthole. Why is your butthole loose?
Because I keep coins in there.
[Laughter]
Is that what you're in disguise? You're breaking into the Margaritaville reserve?
Wait, that's your way to get into the synagogue is put a bunch of coins up your ass?
Come on, bro.
That's not what I said. I didn't say that was my disguise.
They say, "Hey, we kicked you out last week." You say, "Uh-uh-uh."
How about that?
And I just jump up. I do jumping jacks.
Sit all over the floor
You do a reverse Mario you jump up and a coin a big coin
Like I shit I shit on the floor and then like I'm like, oh my god. I'm so sorry. Oh, oh, I'm so sorry
I'm gonna throw up and then just a bunch of coins jump out of my mouth like fucking like Sonic getting hit
fucking rings in his mouth.
It's true.
Yeah, I guess asked and answered.
In his pocket.
He doesn't have a pocket.
He's naked, you fucking idiot.
He has a mouth and he has, he might have something in the back, who knows.
Don't search Sonic Pocket.
I'm searching Sonic Pocket.
I see you searching Sonic Pocket right now.
Sonic doesn't have a pocket and if it was his pocket, he wouldn't be big enough to keep
all his damn rings.
It would be too small to fit even one ring, let alone a thousand.
Those rings are as big as his fucking body.
Which is how many I would score.
They're big rings.
You would never score a thousand.
over a thousand rings and I saw him put them in his mouth when I scored them
because I got the special version of the game that shows you where they go.
Hang on I got it. Really? Where'd you get that? It shows an x-ray of Sonic's stomach while you're
playing so you can see all the rings in there. Are you serious dude? I'm serious. I got the
Sonic Pocket. Rule 34.us. Okay yeah. That's nice. Damn that is crazy. Oh okay. This is where he's
hiding the rings. This is humongous ass. Oh and he's playing uh what is that Sonic
Shadow the Hedgehog?
Alright, here's the tags.
So Sonic is playing, it says Pocket Mania, he's back.
Here, let's listen to the tags.
Ass. So I'm gonna give you guys a hint.
Sonic is way far down on the tags.
Ass, Big Butt, Bubble Gum, Bulge, Candy, Clothing, Dessert,
Ellipo-typhian.
That's Ethiopian.
I'm not picking that.
gum shit hedgehog huge but hyper hyper but male mammal panties solo sonic pocket
adventure
more and i think it's just the only thing that this is the only side pocket
he's done wrote their new history
i've never played this game of the switch out of the hedgehog
no uh... that they were there to some
sonic pocket of the world we would have a white cock
what the fuck i a m well my yeah i i i
This is girl, this is girl tales.
This is what I never understand about like, like drawn pornography.
Why is there always...
I mean look at this, hold on, look at this foot. That is the most fucked up foot I've ever seen.
Dude, well, okay, the most, the most...
This is honestly, like, you know, there's a lot of tags on here that are like, you know, big balls, uh, humanoid feet, etc.
But the, the tag that's really skeeving me out here is that there's a tag that's just looking at another, looking at another.
There's also one just called "inside".
Yeah, and above inside it's "Imminent Sex"
*laughter*
"Imminent Sex"
What does that mean?
Oh my god, veiny penis
Humanoid penis, I don't see why-
Imminent sex has at least-
Dipstick tail
That is like 20- over 20,000 tags
It must have sucked so much to be like a caveman who wanted to see this so bad
Yeah, yeah, caveman who was like like, oh, I wish I could see sonic fuck. Yeah
Well, he's no just like a caveman looking at like a rock and he was like, oh someone should draw that with like a really
Wet penis, but yeah, I don't have a ship put up, but they should put a bulge on it. Yeah. Yeah
Gum is also a bad hashtag on there gum. Yeah, I can't figure out
What about this rule 34 sonic thing is gum? Oh, he's blowing
I was so distracted by the humongous blue ass. I didn't realize he's blowing bubbles.
I was watching the first, looking at the first one.
How do you butt?
Hyper butt?
Oh this is, don't click on hyper butt. Do not click on...
What?
This is not good dude.
Oh wow.
This is crazy.
Oh my god.
And this is all for free?
There's like...
There's like Pokemon?
I don't have to pay for this?
This is one, some fucked up Pokemon or something has eaten every Pokemon and is shitting out
their bones in this one.
Out of their huge butt.
I'm gonna send this to you guys.
I just found...
What do y'all think of that?
Who's this?
Which Pokemon is this?
I have no idea.
That is not a Pokemon.
What is it?
It's shitting out bones.
What the fuck?
Yeah, what is it?
Wait, there's more.
Why did you assume this was a Pokemon?
Because it was, there's outlines of all the Pokemon in her stomach.
That's not, those are bones.
What Pokemon do you see?
What Pokemon bones do you see?
Yeah, I don't see any Pokemon in here.
No, in her stomach, look, Gengar.
Where?
In her stomach, not in, in her ass.
Oh, yeah, okay, I see that.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I just assumed, and then there's another one with no outlines.
Oh, yeah.
It's a smoother version of the same photo.
Yeah, I think, I think over here is, uh, what's his name?
Uh, well I can totally see Dratini over here.
Oh, this butt has hair all over it.
where?
oh and *laughs*
wait there's a video
oh god
this is so good
wait send it
send it in the chat
use audio i just sent it
please keep your audio on
oh my god
what the fuck is this
*laughs*
oh no
she farts on you
It's a giant evil woman with a hairy ass who farts on you and then crushes your head with
her hyper ass.
It's a pretty good deal, honestly.
Yeah.
She's an elf too.
That's your thing.
I mean, these people make so much money off this shit.
It's insane.
Do they make money or are they doing this for the love of the game?
There's a ton of like Patreons and shit just for people who make this.
Oh yeah.
I did I actually have met somebody who does this really yeah, Cameron. Yeah, I don't do this
I wish I did me too. I'd be rich. Yeah, are you kidding?
I mean if I could figure out you know 3d if I you know I try I was gonna be a VFX artist if I could
you know
Yeah, I could do that for money those folks at corridor digital should react to some of this mm-hmm
Think that'd be a good a good video my idea with a huge ass sitting on you
Yeah.
Did you just see that?
What?
Minecraft Steve's huge ass.
No, that's a...
Oh, I do want to search Minecraft Steve, though.
That's quarter to you's newest video.
Minecraft Steve in real life with giant evil ass that farts and shits on you?
Minecraft Steve.
No, there's really not that much Minecraft Steve.
Here's him getting fucked in the ass by a zombie.
Okay.
Here's him fucking a
Some white thing in the ass. Yeah Cameron. Here's a version. Yeah
Here's something else that's not even his cock you out you looked at that and you were immediately like
Yeah, I'll show you what I saw
You know a sentence in the chat. You're skipping for you. So yeah, you're I don't want to make you guys fucking yeah
Oh, he's got minecraft Steve has a cube penis and
Two square balls that are hanging independently a lot a lot of really hold on not square come
yeah, and completely just like just like like
Some clam chowder one of the worst things I've found
What is this one?
Is this the dog one? Oh?
Yep, it is the dog one. What is this? No you saw it. That's from Larry and Steve
I think Larry and Steve was Seth MacFarlane's project that he had on like the, it was like
some Hanna-Barbera thing, and he had that on there before Family Guy.
And that was basically the basis for Family Guy.
So somebody was so into Larry and Steve, they drew Bordo.
There's only two things with Larry and Steve, and the other one is him.
Yes, it's Larry fucking Brian.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Hey, at least it's two dogs, right?
At least it's not a dog and a person.
Oh, here's one here. This is a Lois Lewis Griffin getting
fucked by the yellow M&M
Peaches castle from Super Mario. I mean they're like so here. Here's here's uh
This is oh this one's crazy. This is oh my god. This one's animated. Holy shit
This is that you know this being fucked this one is making me think
How easy how easy it is to animate family guy if you can just animate like
Santa fucking
Does this make you cry this photo of the Mexican flag this is a
Again, did I oh sorry I just I'm still looking at that one
This photo this is this is Dan Smith dressed up like Santa, okay, no no I sent you the right one this is
Isn't it working
the same thing over and over again.
Oh, what the hell? It's like a love letter.
Oh man, the same thing that makes me cry is this Minecraft Steve again.
Here, okay.
It's the Mexican flag,
with his eyes crossed and his tongue
out, and he has
he's holding like a rosary
and he's getting just completely destroyed
by a red guy.
I don't like that. Who's the red guy?
I don't know, I'm trying to figure, probably the Chinese flag, right?
It says Russia on the left.
Oh, okay. Oh, so it's, okay.
Oh no dude, I searched Santa Claus and there's one of a girl sucking Santa's dick and then a dog fucking her
Rendered in 3d it's really oh no
Happy holidays
Wait, I can you send this?
This one. I want to see this. Okay, dude. I
I think this list is great.
Good job guys.
Wow that is horrible.
Oh my god.
That is like
Daz 3D. That is like
fucking like
early Daz 3D 2.
Maybe I talked about this before. I got this
porn game that me and Juvia played
and we just started making
people we knew in it.
She will punish them.
We made Rex in it
And just gave him humongous tits and then just took a bunch of like screenshots of him. Yo lingerie. Oh wait
I'm really Rex say Rick. Oh, yeah. Well yesterday is Rex's birthday. So no what's today?
What are you so so fuck that shit? I'm not saying happy birthday, but I will say happy birthday today
But when this comes out when this comes out he said
No, sir. All right
Yeah, are we starting with the Justin Bieber one
We can. I'll do. I also found one. This might be more. This one is about gaming. If you guys
want to do a game. Yeah. Okay. I like gaming. So we're on this website called VIX.com, which
is basically the biggest news network for the Spanish speaking world as far as I'm aware.
It's pretty much, as far as Jubio has told us, it's basically like CNN, MSNBC, Fox, and
CBS like wrapped into one.
Yeah.
And like it's basically where everyone gets every single piece of news from, right?
Including like, uh, here for example, like I'm, this is like a huge story in Mexico right
now.
A woman can breastfeed her baby through the armpit.
It affects 10% of women.
Yeah.
This is like huge, right?
Can you send me that link?
Yeah, no problem.
I mean, here's another really big story.
Queen Elizabeth epically trolled some tourists who did not recognize her.
We have the story.
Whoa.
This website is all in Spanish so we're using Google Translate to look at it.
Yeah, because I can't speak Spanish.
I can, I just don't want to embarrass Cameron and Pat since I can't.
Here's one.
I appreciate that.
Here's a, I don't want to spoil this, but click this link here.
What are we clicking here?
How to make paper boats.
Yeah, I mean that's like one of the biggest things in Mexico right now.
It's a huge story that I noticed on this website that's going on right now is top 10 blue drinks
has been really big.
Yeah, that's like...
Wait, I want to see the one.
I want to see the top 10 blue drinks.
Yeah, I bet you are.
That's why it's selling so well in Mexico.
Yeah, let's look at this one.
Let's look at this one first then.
They know exactly what you want.
The top 10 blue drinks.
Okay, here, let me send this link over to you guys.
Number one's got to be water.
That's not true.
No, no, no, no, no.
Agua.
In the world of drinks, there are thousands of delicious varieties.
We always talk about the best drinks for this or that occasion, or the drinks to accompany
such a dish, etc.
But we rarely refer to the immensity of drinks that can be made with just one color, blue.
Check out this top 10 blue drinks that you are sure to love.
I would really like to just completely skip this list except for number one on this list.
Number one is Smurf.
Yup.
What is Smurf?
No way, it is.
I have no idea.
Smurf?
Smurf cocktail is served in a tall glass decorated with a lemon wedge and made with strawberry
vodka, blue carousel, lemon juice and lemon lime soda.
That sounds really good.
I want to try that.
Sounds amazing.
I want to drink the Smurf.
I think this list is just cheating because everything here is a cocktail made out of
like blue carousel.
Yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
How about where the soda's at?
What's a blue soda?
Blue soda is like the one that they had at Friendly's.
Yeah, like a blue raspberry soda.
The blue soda at Friendly's is probably one of the best sodas in the world.
Blue Mountain Dew.
There's a blue mountain dew.
Wait, fuck you.
Blue Mountain Dew.
Voltage.
So you want to suck my cock now, don't you?
There's also blue game fuel.
This is one of the smartest things I've ever seen.
we get into the main list. This is three alcoholic beverages that leave the least
hangover. And so number three is wine, number two is white drinks, and number
one, best drink for no hangover, drinks with a lot of ice.
So genius. Oh here's one, here's, wait, hold on, we saw that, we saw the blue drinks.
Here's a list of red drinks here.
This is breaking news.
You hear someone speaking Spanish on the street, you can go up to them and say, "Have you ever
heard of what's going on with the drinks Rojo?"
They'll know exactly what you're talking about.
Yo baby Rojo.
This doesn't really have a lot of...
Yeah, anyway, this list here.
There's only three drinks and there's one drink called Red Liquid.
That's the number one drink is called Red Liquid.
It's two ounces of tequila, one ounce of natural strawberry juice, one ounce of pink grapefruit juice.
I don't care about what goes into Red Liquid.
Yeah, can you just shut up?
Here, so this is the list.
You know what, I'm screenshotting this page.
I'm gonna make red liquid. I'm not bad it's lag six situations that only real
gamers understand this is again this is huge news. This is all me. Yeah this is
2008. TV shows are being interrupted yeah for a breaking news
bulletin from a guy who looks exactly like Juvio. I don't look like that.
Since 2008 August 29th was marked as gamers day by specialized magazines that wanted to
celebrate the gaming community around the world. Video games are becoming more
popular and accepted. It has even become a career for some people. It says some
people on that. Not this fucker. It says some people. That is not why they cease to be
enjoyable casually and that is why we bring six situations that only gamers
understand. The first one here, B.O.G. O.G. is part of the English slang that stands for
original gangster and is used to refer to people who have been followers of
something in particular for a long time. The term evolved and can now also be
translated as old school, old school, or has its adaptation to video games as old
gamer or original gamer. I'm an OG. What's your first game Cameron?
I probably have to be like tag, hide and seek, one of those. Probably like Jacks.
yeah Jack's was good online Jack's yeah yep yeah I was really into online jump
rope you know you know that that that thing where it looks like a lawnmower
for a baby and you push around and it pops I was really into that online that
was a good one yeah wait wait online online rock-paper-scissors
you remember online pretend was really good you guys ever play you guys ever
play ball in a cup online? Oh my god, dude. I was pretty much high score on it. Yeah. We
didn't have that one down here. What's this about? Really? You didn't have ball in a cup
online? No, we didn't. It's pretty much, I mean, it's just like a cool game. I guess
you're not like an OG like me though, but it's just fine. I started gaming on the Nintendo
64, so I guess I'm not a real gamer. Yeah, you're right. I started on the Nintendo 1.
I didn't even have graphics or games when I was gaming. It was like literally like...
personal video. When I started gaming I wasn't even alive yet. That's how early I was gaming.
I was poop when I started gaming. I was just shit in my dad's ball sack. A pile of poop
outside. That they forgot about. That's what I was for so long. I was like a bug in the
dirt back before I was born. Then I crawled up somewhere I shouldn't have gone. I was
a stinky pocket of air and then I was gaming. I was basically this like
brown ball of slime that was just flying around everywhere trying to get
into people's houses and stuff. Yeah, I was like a piece of hair on a fly
like that was like all I was
and I got bored. I was just kind of this spec that was like just kind of
a spec of dirt. There was nothing just lying around kind of just a
chill and then I was more. I was like a game. I was like a piece of ice
a fridge. Yes I'm pretty much an original gamer. Number two, F in chat. What does that mean?
I've seen Jubio drop some F's in chat. I've seen Jubio. Everybody go and drop some F's
in the chat for Jubio right now. Twitch.tv/pod about list. Podcast about list. Podcast about
Yes, make sure to give them all the Fs you got.
In recent years, with the popularization of video game streaming, F became a meme used
by gamers and non-gamers for different situations of failure or shame.
However, only true OGs know the origin of the F, which was a command used in Call of
Duty Advanced Warfare that was pushed to show respect at the funerals of fallen soldiers.
F for those who thought it meant fail.
Is it really that recent?
Yep.
Yeah.
Call of Duty Advanced Warfare?
I think that's not a very recent game, Caleb.
I think it's like almost 10 years ago.
Really?
Advanced Warfare was uh...
That came out in 2020.
Yeah.
No.
Yeah, it came out in 2020.
That's when FNChat started.
Really?
It came out in 2014.
2020 actually.
2022.
That still is not...
That's 2014.
Not recent enough.
2014 it came out.
I know dude, I- Modern Warfare, the like first Modern Warfare came out in like 2007 or some fucked up shit.
Oh, it's a Kevin Spacey call, did he?
Oh, that's the one?
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, they should like, they should release all the assets for that game so that you can just do whatever you want to his body.
Yeah, you can just put- you can get a Kevin Spacey 3D model from that guy.
I'm sure, I'm sure there's like data miners or whatever who have figured out how to get it.
it, but I think maybe we should like, you remember like Interactive Buddy on Newgrounds?
They should do that with the Kevin Spacey model.
They should release a remaster and they have no Russian, but the airport is just Kevin Spacey.
Filled with Kevin Spaceys?
Yeah.
That would be a good way to show respect.
That would be good, yeah.
Yeah, just a million clones of Kevin Spacey in an airport asking each other how old they
are and you walk in with a machine gun.
Yeah.
I'm not bad, it's lag. If you are beaten in the game, it is unforgivable to accept the
opponent is better than you, so lag or internet delay is to blame for losing. That is why there
is the saying, "Video games don't make gamers violent, but lag does." I hate lag.
I actually do. GBO can attest that I get so mad.
Kaelthas lived in New York for 10 years now, and he didn't think of getting a better ISP
until yesterday.
And then I yeah, and I didn't even get a better ISP because Fios won't fucking they think like I think my there must be like
A ton of lead in the walls here because they don't want to like replace anything or install Fios in my my apartment
I got I got Fios. Yeah
Fucking stupid and fat and yeah, they even have Fios in fucking Mexico. Oh you can use
These
These EOS guys would rather go from New York down to Mexico to install it at Juvio's house
Then go fucking like one mile down the street and put it in my fucking they wanted a vacation
They wanted to see the sights of Mexico. That's the thing. That's the thing. It's like beautiful down there
What I've seen in Breaking Bad it is beautiful and yellow and it's so yellow. It's golden. It's the most golden. Oh my god
It is very yellow.
It's the golden state in America.
Did you, have you ever met the evil brothers from Breaking Bad?
Do those guys live around you?
Yeah, the twins.
Do you know Gus Fring?
Yeah.
I went to school with him.
Do you know Tuco?
Dude, Tuco, that guy's crazy.
I would love to, if you, dude, if you know him, I'd love to hang out with him sometime.
Can you get me in with Tuco?
Do you know La Tortuga?
You know Hustle Tortuga?
I don't know any of these guys actually.
I was lying.
Well, I know Hustle Tortuga.
No, you don't.
I do.
Why?
Because I made him up.
Okay, next one.
Can't pause online.
How many times are we going to have to explain to parents that Nintendo cannot be paused if
we are playing online?
The child from China you are playing against is not going to wait for you to return from
the tortillas to continue the game.
Okay, okay.
This is one of those things that actually happens to me all the time.
I guess I do have to go purchase some tortillas from the store.
You have to go return from the tortillas.
Yeah, well...
Return from the tortillas?
What is the...
What the fuck does return from the tortillas mean?
You know, where they make the tortillas.
There's like tortillas stores?
Only real OGs go buy fresh tortillas.
Oh, I've been doing that.
If I could...
Actually, I could probably buy fresh tortillas somewhere around here.
They don't make them over there.
They don't have tortillas in America.
It's only, it's a secret recipe.
It's corn!
And it's only in Mexico.
It's pretty smart.
The child from China, I mean this kid is just lapping.
Huge.
I hate that guy.
Yeah, they're, just eat your tortillas later man.
Finish the damn game.
This Chinese kid is waiting on you.
It's a child actually.
of smash brothers. Deceptions. What? The translation says the disappointments.
Yeah I'm going with Google Translate I think. Yeah I don't really I mean I don't
know yeah. You're not like like you want a billion results when I tell you. Here
show me pictures of a naked woman right now. Yeah. A billion results right now.
Yeah I got it right here. Wow this is a long Google search. This is taking way longer
than Google. That's a car! That's not a naked woman, that's a car!
Smash Bros is characterized by adding characters from different franchises to
the game's catalog of fighters which has led fans to make requests and
predictions of their favorites. Sometimes the franchise... that's my own self. Don't...
I'm not naked, I'm not that naked. Damn, I look bowlegged. My ass... you can see it from the front.
(laughter)
You look so scary!
I have a lot of scary photos of myself.
Sometimes a franchise is surprised with important additions, but at other times it has been
downright disappointing.
How long are we going to have to wait to have Crash in Smash, Nintendo?
They can't have him in there because people will get confused.
They'll be like, "Is the game called Crash or is the character Smash?"
I would get confused if he was Star Fox.
Right, yeah.
Right?
Maybe I would think like he was like Lucas or Ness or something. Yeah
I was might like that though. He's moving really fast and I just saw the pants. I might think it was like Lucas or Ness
Hmm, or I might see like I don't know
I might think he was like the piranha plant if I saw I just saw the inside of his mouth
It could be the piranha plant. What's that?
What's that show that they would play on Telemundo and it's all the adults and they're dressed up like little kids. Oh
Oh, El Chavo?
Yeah, El Chavo.
I think if I, I think uh, I think Ness probably looks like that if you saw Ness in real life he'd look like El Chavo.
You think he looks like a homeless Mexican kid?
Yes.
Yes, I think that's exactly what he would look like.
This is a great show. I used to watch this a lot when I was a kid.
El Chavo?
Yeah.
I would watch El Chavo. I would watch El Chavo by accident and it always scared me.
How would you watch El Chavo? I would put it like 3 a.m. I'd be like channel surfing and
then I would like see that and it's like why like I don't understand the language
why are these grown-ups acting like little kids. So it was a horror show like
a scary show? It was like it was like accidentally seeing the Twilight Zone as
a kid. You thought it was like that David Lynch Rabbits thing? It's like Candle Cove dude.
You're like what the fuck is this? It's like one of the most beloved like Spanish speaking
shows of all time and just my stupid like American ass is just like "OH GOD WHAT THE FUCK IS
THAT?" It's like Candle Cove that like creepypasta thing where like you're like freaking out about
it and then the next morning you find out you were just watching static the whole time.
It does look like they are reusing the first season SNL set on this fucking thing.
It's true.
Yeah, no, it does look, it looks a lot like...
So they played homeless children.
I didn't know, the homeless aspect of that I had no idea.
So they live in like this, this like neighborhood, and El Chavo is the one homeless kid living
in like a little, like a barrel in the middle of the neighborhood.
to close the show
uh... distros run him and his
various adventures in his friends
and the people of the neighborhood like three times
world and there's the one guy is el chavo el chavo is the one that uh...
he's got like huge like cheeks or whatever
you know it was it was a very good at a child's cheeks
no child's huge bouncing cheeks you know i look at the bottom of the government
look it up but none of that it's not a good and he's going to make it a class
he
it's because
keiko has the the big cheeks yeah
and it's that just that what he looks like as i'm looking at like photos as a
young man that's is uh... his rich friend
also he's he's rich so he was a pinwheel hats yes pretty much is that how it
works down there
it yet that's why don't worry about it
uh... and live in by living a barrel
uh... well you know what
we are going to get you a opinion that
which
i can't do it like a young you should get a pinwheel yamaka
all-mass you should wear that to the synagogue next time you go
uh... i'd like to go the next list but i will say there is a great
that is a lot of the bottom of this is a ninja turtle yeah the ninja turtle
poster
and it says less tortugas ninja
well which is pretty funny to me
as i don't know what that means
but i have a guess the next one
uh... let's do
let's do uh...
eleven valid reasons to hate justin bieber blamelessly in front of his fans
if he still has to. okay can i read the name of this list really quick
nine movies that a cooking lover must see that will make you the best little chef
number one chef
yes. is chef on here? ratatouille is on here.
chef isn't on there?
you're not going to learn shit from ratatouille
You're not going to learn literally a single thing from Ratatouille.
You're going to learn a lot.
And chef, you're going to learn how to have knife skills, you're going to learn how to
make a Cubano, you're going to learn how to make a...
They have knife skills.
You're going to learn how to repair your relationship with your beautiful Colombian wife.
Yeah, you're going to learn how to fuck a million hot girls in a row every single day
at the same time.
And you'll learn how to befriend John Leguizamo.
Exactly.
And who doesn't need a funny John Leguizamo type friend?
If you don't want to be friends with the pest, you gotta go to the mental hospital.
No cap.
If you don't want to be friends with Luigi Mario, you disabled mentally.
I can't lie to you.
That's just how it is.
That's the truth.
Alright, 11 valid reasons to hate Justin Bieber blamelessly in front of his fans if he still
has them.
Number eleven, he has bad manners in his everyday life.
Using toilets to relieve ourselves is something natural for everyone, but less
so for the adolescent.
Justin not only did not use the bathroom in a restaurant, but he also recorded
himself while doing his things to later make his video public.
Where would the funny part of all this be?
In the toilet.
I don't remember that. Justin Bieber taking shit in a restaurant?
He took a piss into like the mop
and bucket at a restaurant and uh...
and looked at the camera and said,
"Hey yo, fuck Bill Clinton!"
'Cause he was on some odd future shit in 2013.
That kinda- he sounds great, dude.
Yeah, that's like, kinda sick.
Um...
And on more than one occasion he was disrespectful.
"Just as it is not advisable to tease and spit on your fans,
it is not good to take advantage of them.
Do you remember an unusual fact that he wanted to be hidden by his henchmen,
but could not be left behind due to photographs taken at the exact moment?
moment no one believed that the singer did not want to cut touch the girls
bodice we are not stupid come on what the fuck it I don't know what this is but
this means at all I think it's different like a bra yeah oh
Julia what's a bodice it's like a bra for girls like a girl's bra I thought you
know what genuinely thought there was a Spanish I think it's part of a dress I
looked it up as part of a dress it's like a what about a bow vice instead of a
What about Bo Dice?
Yeah, a bovine.
A Bo Bice?
Remember Bo Bice from American Idol?
No.
Bo Bice?
Bo Bice.
There was the same year as Bo Bice and Constantine?
This guy's fucked up.
Constantine whatever?
What does Bo Bice look like now?
He's got short hair.
He's got sh- what?
No.
Yeah, shaved his head down.
And choose this title yourselves.
He already had his bad reputation in Argentina, but after his concert in the Latin American
country he earned, he ended up earning the complete hatred of each of them and with much
much reason.
Sweep the ground with the flag of that country?
Disrespectful and ridiculous.
Which number was that?
That was number four, I'm just skipping around here.
Number three, heartbroken.
If you didn't know about this lousy Bieber gesture, it's about time you knew about it.
An attitude of contempt that he had with a child with cancer, who after meeting him only
managed to be disappointed.
Despite the fact that this helped him get money for his foundation, the star did not reach
even five minutes with the little one."
I guess that is like a hard part about being like a famous celebrity, is that people with
cancer just have to spend time with you.
Yeah.
That's also, I think that it's funny because that is the last person I would want around
a little kid who's about to die.
Is like a celebrity.
a celebrity. Yeah, exactly. And also, like, if I was about to die, I would not be like,
I need to spend my remaining moments with, like, John Cena. Like, that's crazy. I would
try and kill the celebrity to leave my mark on the world, I think. Oh, that's actually
a good idea, Juvia. If you just have, like, go tell, like, the WWE, like, listen, I'm
nine years old, I have cancer, I'm going to die in, like, three weeks. What if you guys
just like pulled me out of the audience like a like a like a folding chair in the
middle of one of the matches and just beat the shit out of me until I fucking
died. That would be so sick. That would be how if I was 11 with with like bone
cancer that's exactly how I'd want to go out. Oh yeah. It's just like me completely
beaten to death in the ring. I want Chris Jericho to throw me off a bridge.
Yeah, yeah, bring me to the top of the fucking the the the cage match cage and
toss me off like you're the Undertaker. If I get a terminal disease I
would love to like be the mocap actor for Megatron getting his head ripped off in
the next Transformers movie. Yeah, exactly. Like they put a big tennis ball on my head and then and then like
the Rock or whoever just you know twist my head off. Leave a lasting legacy you
know? Yeah. Like I just let those wrestlers get so fake at throwing
so sick of throwing fake punches just let them land a couple of fucking crushing
blows on my soft spot. Plus the bones are probably softer. Yeah way softer I'm gonna be
pliable as fuck you could like do the backbreaker to me over and over and over again.
Yeah and like I'm already fucking I might as well already be dead right I have
like would I rather just waste away for the next three weeks in the hospital
yeah and if you're worried it's like too much of a heel turn to like you know
just start beating me up I can dress like Hitler and like walk out. Yeah dress me up like Hitler I
already have cancer I'm gonna die it doesn't matter what my fucking. Exactly and you can like swing me
around by the feet and throw me into the audience. What if you survive and then like there's just
footage of you dressed up like Hitler and like they're throwing you from the top of the cage.
Come back the next day you're gonna die one of these times. Yeah. What is the craziest thing
- And they can just ask the Make-A-Wish Foundation guys.
Like, he'll be like, "Oh yeah, I wanna do like 9/11 again."
(laughing)
- Like, come on, come on, just let me do it.
- Look, look, I'll get the Pentagon for real this time.
Like, I'll like, it'll be gone.
- Yeah, that was the 9/11 commission.
They didn't look into it,
but that was what happened the first time.
(laughing)
It was five young boys from Saudi Arabia.
(laughter)
Well, we can't really say anything.
They had cancer.
What are we supposed to do? They had cancer.
We paid for flight school.
I froze.
Oh, Patrick froze.
How's that Fios treating you, you asshole?
Fuck you.
Well, I don't feel... We should end this so I don't have to
re-sync it. It's over.
It's done.
I said, you want me to yell, "I had a kid with cancer."
I don't care.
Yeah, it would have already showed up because when you freeze you're still recording on audacity.
UGH!
You are so brainless.
So stupid.
Get him!
Twitch.tv/podcastswithoutlist.
Jubio's gonna be live 24/7, every single day, every single moment.
He's going and he's gonna be naked.
You can give bits to move to Ankit.
You can do virtual buddy with his body on Twitch, I swear to God.
You give different bits and he'll smell literally anything for four bits.
It's four cents.
In Mexico it's a fortune.
Look, he'll even smell his finger.
He'll smell his finger and you know where that's been.
We're going to do shows in the weekends where we kill bats all this money away and rope
it.
I will also be doing that.
I will be at the digital casino and everybody's invited.
Alright.
Is that allowed?
Yeah.
Bye.
Digital casino and Twitch?
Alright, bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]