come back and make a bet
and we see a black
crap monster
the
this year the listener
it's true it's how we can hear the listening i think we use scared the
listener to my own
uh... did
we have a special guest today
Caleb Pitts is with us in the room.
Hey, what's up?
I'm Caleb Pitts.
I like to eat butts.
I smell like poop all the time, every day of my life.
I'm glad you finally admitted it.
That's my name.
This is what Caleb says often.
We have our beautiful friend Alex here with us.
My roommate.
Because Caleb got very sick from eating butts and he smelled his own poop smell too much.
Caleb smelled his finger and he like, you know when a cat smells like a pickle?
No, you're seeing those videos
For like a cat like a cat was smelling your pickle in a video. There's like a video if you ever see those videos I make
They're really good. You have my computer
there's like videos are like people giving their cats and their dogs like pickles and then like the hands will be like
Caleb did and it yeah, you know how I can in like
Colonial times or whatever they believed like that you would get sick if you're like your humors were in balance like there
you know, you had like black bile and yellow bile and like and blood and snot or whatever the last
one was. And well, Caleb had like a really bad imbalance of his poop humor. Like it was like
way out of whack. He's actually one of the only people that has a fifth humor that's like,
because he just has like poop in his body. It's disgusting. He's got poop in his blood.
He would be probably like burnt at the stake. Yeah. In the back in the olden times.
I mean back then fire was precious. They probably wouldn't even waste it on him.
Yeah.
Yeah. That was back before fire was everywhere.
Used to.
It was so precious.
It was very rare.
I used to have to walk up to...
They used to use it as currency.
I used to have two...
We don't have any precious things anymore.
No, there's so much of everything.
It's fucked up.
Yeah.
I was going to say.
Yeah, shut up.
I mean yeah, it's like back in the middle ages, Bitcoin used to be, you'd find like one Bitcoin
your whole life. But nowadays there's like millions of them just like flying through the air every
second. Yeah, I caught a ride on one earlier today. Bitcoin was something that a bartender
at a saloon used to do. That's right. What's up? Yeah, what's up? Come on, come on. I'll give it
up for that. Okay, okay. Let's go, let's go. Yeah, back then they had freaking Bit Treasure.
used to bite into a doubloon and now I've got doubloon the amount of Bitcoin that I
used to have because it inflated it inflate and inflated back then all the
only thing they didn't play was a balloon yeah now they've now we are my doubloon
now you go you go up on that you go on the computer you look up Lois Griffin
inflated you get a million results mm-hmm back then Lois Griffin was a
a mythical creature true yeah now I wish I could meet a strong woman what it's
enough to make a man go crazy yeah make me do something crazy
uh-huh yeah no low low is Griffin those Griffin if you're listening we're
kidding leave you got a Peter you gotta get with a real man oh I wonder if like
the the Griffin family would have been able to survive in the Middle Ages
definitely Stewie yeah yeah Stewie he's like resourceful and clever he would have
used his inventions probably yeah he probably would have been a prince oh
hell yeah yeah oh hell yeah yeah I think I think Meg oh oh no yeah shut up Meg
that's what I would get in on it like all the peasants would be saying like
shut up Meg yeah I'm like Stewie would be Goku. Back in the day yes Stewie was Goku.
Man like kids nowadays don't know but like when we were growing up like Stewie was Goku and like
Peter Griffin was Batman. Chris Griffin was Robin Hood and Lois Griffin she was perfect.
Yeah, she's so busted now. She's so old. Kids these days don't know. She's all saggy and
weird looking now on TV. Like, dude, take me back to when I was three years old. I do
not understand Generation Z. No. They're all twisted backwards, man. They don't understand
like what it was like growing up back in like the 1400s. We had good Lois Griffins. Yep.
Yeah, Lois Griffin used to used to be deflated then now she's inflated. Yeah, and you can also
Look up Lois Griffin in real life
You can look that up too you can look up
Look at the lowest Griffin like in the phone book in real life like where Google
Google images they got so much shit on there
They have they have so much shit on Google images now
It's like you just get you can scroll forever doesn't you?
Yeah, remember when you used to have to click next page?
Doesn't happen anymore. No, you can just continuously scroll. Yeah kids nowadays. They never click next page anymore
It's like back in the day bet like like kids nowadays. They'll they'll go to a library. They'll read a book
They'll get to the bottom of the page. They'll say why is the next one loading?
It's like, "Hey, you got to click next page on the book."
True.
Yeah.
We know stuff like that.
They don't.
It's almost like websites or books.
It's almost like books are like...
In the new era.
Yeah, it's almost like books became like what movies were for like back when we were kids,
but then like video games are kind of like more like websites now.
True.
Wow.
Yeah.
You guys are so smart.
I'm learning so much.
I'm glad we like we huffed all that paint before we started recording.
in my living room there's been a gas leak in here. There is a pretty much a gas leak that
has followed me to every room. Yeah, to your ass. Yeah, the past month. I feel like every
time I get in a room with either Patrick or Caleb, something happens to my brain.
Well, you said the air smelled weird in our apartment. It did. There was a difference in
the air. I think it's the scented candle. Yeah, I bought that candle a while ago.
Yeah. So you know it's good. It's gone bad.
I think it's stale. That candle expired. It tastes so weird when I try to eat it.
Is that? God, that candle's expired as fuck right now. It is so crazy. It does look, it's
like black slime. Yeah. There's like a layer, it's like when you see like one of those videos,
it's like this is what happens to your lungs when you smoke a cigarette and there's like
a like black tar. That's what the candle looks like right now. Let's say you know it's working.
There's also this weird like bright flickering orange thing on top of the wax. It's dancing.
It's beautiful, I want to touch it.
It's hypnotic.
Hypnotic, tectonic.
Yesterday when I was walking to Caleb's, I forgot to mention this to you guys, I saw
two guys in military uniforms walking down the street, but not like camo, like fatigues,
some kind of like, I don't know if it was like Navy or what, but they had like, they
were in some kind of uniform.
And they were walking down the street, they weren't talking or anything, and then one
One of them walked by a mannequin and he just reached out and grabbed its boob.
That was so funny.
That was the FBI.
That was the Federal Booby Inspectors.
Hell yeah.
You saw them.
Damn.
Dude, it's like seeing a G-Man or a man in black.
You saw the Federal Booby Inspector.
Damn.
Dude, I should have taken a video.
Were they armed?
I don't know.
They were armed and dangerous.
Not that I could see.
He had an arm for two boobs.
That's right yeah I for two boobs they keep us safe yeah yeah I saw a big
pulsating imprint of a gun in his pocket.
His gun got way bigger.
He had a long straight gun.
It was scary and it smelled really bad.
It shot at me.
It got in my mouth.
It shot conditioner out.
It must have been some kind of conditioner gun.
Yeah, yeah, because he did also say you're going to taste my conditioner
gun. I thought that was really weird. Yeah, yeah, this is the Alberto V05 gun.
The what? The what? The Alberto V05. The what? It's like a shampoo that costs
like a dollar. Alberta, what is it? Alberto. Alberto. V05. V05. V05. Unless
Those are two different.
Alberto V05.
Check this stuff out.
Whoa.
Okay.
It comes in different colors.
Y'all never fucked with Alberto V05?
No, I have.
I just never knew that that was actually called that.
Just looking at that is very...
There's one, I think it's the strawberry one right there.
Click on the strawberry.
That's like a classic.
Yeah, that one, dude.
Ooh, that one's good enough to eat.
Strawberries and cream.
Oh, man.
That one...
It's good enough to eat, to drink.
That one is like...
Yeah.
I mean, this looks like it would...
It smells like toxically strawberry.
looks like it would smell nice but I'd rather it not be strawberries and just be cream
via five cream there was so many creams
I've had I've used it so much growing up that like looking at the bottles is like giving me like
like I can smell it yeah it's one of those yeah Patrick's nose is bleeding right yeah oh oh what
- Oh, what is that? - Oh, look, they have normal.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Why is it like-- - I love normal scent.
- Why is it poop color? (laughing)
- Yeah, I know, it's like-- - Normal is like brown.
- Yeah, what else do we have?
- Oh, that's nice.
- Oh, dude. - Ocean refresh.
- Ocean refresh, yeah.
- I wanna drink all these.
- Dude, describe that one. - They look really delicious.
- It looks like, like it smelled like you could drink it.
Like it smelled like a very like,
it looks like the, have you ever had the pink Sobe?
- No. - Sobe Energy?
- No. - Oh, wait, yeah, I have.
Dude, it's my favorite. It looked like that if you put a bunch of water in it and then
It smelled like this is the pink one. Yeah
It smelled like a fucking remember like strawberry shortcake like you could like smell like her hair
Who?
The toy like your sisters didn't have a strawberry shortcake. Uh, no. Oh, I know the the popsicle though
Like the strawberry shortcake popsicle that you yeah, that was good. That was some good eating. I like that one
You didn't like that one?
No, if it's like a popsicle, I like a sour, like a Crybaby.
That one's good.
A Crybaby?
Or like a 2 Ball Screwball.
You ever get Spongebob though?
Mmmhmm.
Ooo, Spongebob.
I was about to ask you the same thing.
What was the one, it was like the ice cream trucks that have the one and it's like in
a snow cone thing, but it's like tiny little like sour balls.
Oh, the lemon lime ones?
Yeah.
Those ones are so good.
I liked those a lot. Yeah, I liked those a lot. I like pizza. Yeah, pizza was pretty good from the ice cream truck.
There should be a pizza ice cream truck.
That sells ice cream and pizza from a truck.
And the song that it plays. Yeah, what's the song?
That song from the Portivolo.
the
it was that's all it is a good thing to do it
was like a solid the plate funeral
the
that's what it was taps
You always think there's like a military funeral going on?
It's just like, "Oh no, that's just the pizza and ice cream, man."
I mean, you know what?
He never stops.
Yeah.
You know, if like a, because everyone like knows the ice cream truck song now.
You know, it's everyone.
The Entertainer by Scott Joplin.
Yeah.
And so I feel like-
Like Janis Joplin?
I feel like now they have to like-
There's also The Sting.
There's got to be like some kind of ice cream truck like startup that needs to like disrupt
it and like draw more people.
here's my idea okay is a an ice cream truck it doesn't play any music but
every once in a while it plays like an insanely loud noise of just a car crash
then like even the parents everyone's running outside to see what's happening
and then they go they're so excited that nobody died that you know they'll buy
ice cream yeah but that's the thing that's the thing about the pizza and
ice cream truck have you ever been to a funeral and heard an ice cream truck no I
Have I wish I had that sounds so fun. That's like it would cheer me right up
No, cuz you're at the funeral and like out of nowhere you hear the ice cream truck you're like damn
I wish I could leave this boring. Yeah, right now true go get an ice cream. You know what I saw
I don't know if I'm gonna sleep like yeah, let me get in there with you
Kill me I don't even get to put a cigarette in his mouth. I'm so bored kill me. I want to die
They have a they have an ice cream truck in Boston
That's like it's run entirely by police, and I think it's called like to protect and serve ice cream or something
I forget it has some weird do cop run businesses are so fucking funny cuz it's like
like
It's just PR for cops
It's like in a paddy wagon - god damn dude
It's so like like how do we really?
Work, how do we rehabilitate the Boston cops image? Yeah, what's he cups?
Dude, so sick
There's a there's a skate shop in South Carolina called five. Oh
And it's like run by like a former cop
it's like
The same shit is like like a cop making an ice cream truck is just like trying to get like kids to trust cops
cops. Yeah, I scream press. What is that? Fucking say his shit that kid shirt says
coaches secret weapon. I let it said Corrin secret. This kid shirt says beach
and surf. Yeah, that is a 40 look. All those kids are getting guns. Yeah, time
they have gun shaped ice cream and then they keep giving the kids gun shaped ice
Well they probably like, you know what they probably do is they probably like have like
a trash can to throw away the like the popsicle sticks and they just like like pull all the
DNA off it.
They're planting DNA of like children.
Well that's isn't that what they don't they have like a truck that like the police have
like a truck where you can play like video games for free and then they just like pull
you I don't know if I don't know if it's true if they pull your fingerprints or not but like
I feel I have heard of that I think you told me about that.
Yeah they're definitely there is a truck where you can play video games for free and it's
it's like so fun and the cops are really nice when you do it. All right, I'm pro
cop.
All right, it's all working on you. You convinced me. Yeah,
cops are awesome. This is from food and wine magazine. Whoa, people are
pulling
people over to give them free ice cream. Officers in Boston bought an eighty
nine thousand dollar
free ice cream to their community.
God damn do rocks dude. If a cop pulled me over and gave me ice cream,
just be pissed off dude i would like i
would i would i would kill him yeah i
commit so many crimes
oh now i'm going to article for later
it's so awesome dude we should start a
cop ice cream truck
yeah like we should wait no no we should
wait here's why is there's a police man
that just is it and turns it into a
police damn that's so fucked
that's awesome
we should start like
like the bank robber ice cream
that's a terrible idea you know what all these cops
and then get this we get cops to staff it the cops pull up see a truck that says
that says
bank robbers they arrest the cops who are running it uh... puts cops in jail
okay
yeah some of those workforces are the same that sell ice cream
That's what Rage Against the Machine was saying.
That's what it's all about.
Mm-hmm.
Cops, ice cream, crime.
My three favorite things.
The three Cs.
Cops, cream.
Cops, cream, and crime.
Ooh.
I got blasted full of cop cream.
Get out of the speeding ticket.
Suddenly, suddenly I can't stand up.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've been blasted full of cop cream.
Man, yeah, the cops are really cool.
They blast me full of cream.
Yeah, no, I'm I'm like I like I like cops cream, but like I'm kind of like a leftist.
So like when a cop pulls me over and I like let him fuck me to get out of the ticket like
I don't let him come.
Yeah, like I yeah, I run I run away from him.
The total cock punishment.
I'm a total officer. I'm going to punish your car. I'm a total come here. I'm a
total police cock blocker. I get in there. I start fucking them, but I like
jump up and I put a cage on that shit.
I lock it up. I say no chance you sir are not serving your community. So I will
not serve your cock. I'm doing the citizens arrest on your penis. That's
right, you will never squirt again.
You've blasted your last slime, my friend. This is reform. Yep. Yeah, I'm
going to defund your balls, officer.
So yeah, I'm going to handcuff your balls to your wiener. See how you
like that.
Yeah, I'm a hero. Yeah, yeah, you're you're handcuffed like it's like
handcuffed around the balls in the wiener like a cock ring, but you're handcuffed to the handcuffs
and it's like what's that is it 48 hours where they wear the handcuffs like a handcuff to
the cop.
What are you chewing on?
That's just something I found on the floor.
What is it?
It's like a leg piece.
It looks like part of a urinal.
Yeah.
Do you want it?
I'm not eating that.
No, it's just in your mouth.
I did almost.
Come on.
I did almost do it for a split second.
Yeah, you did.
Best split second of my life.
Yeah.
Ouch.
Whenever a cop pulls me over, right before they walk up to my window, I turn off the
porn that I was watching on my GPS screen so that they can't enjoy it.
Can you do that in a Tesla?
Isn't that like what the big-
Well, the police do that in their damn police cars.
They're riding around with a laptop.
How many cops do you think pull their shit while they're driving?
All of them.
constantly talking. Yeah, they you know their uniform has a yeah. They have a
special tugging machine that goes in the pants.
That's why they're so angry whenever they get out because you interrupted
them. Yeah, if you interrupted their tug, yeah, I have to arrest you. That's
why it's why they wear sunglasses a lot too because you'll see like their
eyes are like super bloodshot because they just been like drained of all
moisture.
They've just been like squirting out all the liquid in their body all day
Cops do like an IV drip of like semen.
Yeah they do, a lot of them have to.
Because it's like, I mean it's just so punishing to like just be like, just like coming and
blasting and squirting and dripping all the time.
I need 10 cc's of junk.
I mean that's why, that's why like, that's why it's tough for like when they get defunded
it's like you know.
It affects all of us.
They have to start stealing their magazines.
It's like, it's tough you know.
It's like millions of dollars of magazine budget of dirty mags.
Yeah, so yeah, we have we've ascertained that the at our offices stumbled upon 40
40 40 copies of ass magazine. I don't know where I was going with that.
- I can't do the voice.
- You're crazy.
- Dude, oh, speaking of crime,
dude, me and Caleb did the best crime of all time.
- What'd you do?
- You were there.
No, you weren't there, you were there.
- Alex was there.
- Oh, yeah, I know.
- Yeah, we, if, yeah.
- You guys went to Six Flags, I didn't go.
- Yeah, I don't wanna talk about that.
(laughing)
But there was, on the way back from Six Flags,
there was a vending machine,
I don't want to reveal the location because I think we'll be going back and
using this trick several more times.
But we were trying to get water and it was all sold out of water,
but I was putting in dollar coins to try and like, like,
like get by the water and there was was sold out.
So I pressed the coin return and what comes out but $2 coins plus four quarters.
Yup. That's right. I found a real life infinite money hack.
And we did that for about 30 minutes.
You guys went, Caleb really went fucking crazy.
Caleb went nuts.
Caleb got like an old Susan B. Anthony dollar that was worth like $8.
I'd never seen that like look in Caleb's eyes before.
It was just like 10 minutes of him.
I feel like he was like so excited.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah, I would have too.
It was cool.
Yeah, it's like when you teach like a rat that it can like pull a lever to get a treat.
Yeah, yeah.
He just like...
Get cheese.
Yeah.
That's like a rat eating cheese was watching him.
Watching Caleb.
Yeah, most of the time watching him just like watching a rat.
But that time it was more like watching a rat eating cheese.
Yeah, that's crazy, because he's like not he doesn't eat. She doesn't have cheese with
them. Yeah, that day specifically was like a rat with his cheese. Yeah, it's totally
like a rat like with eating his cheap bit of a bit of a doctor do a little type. You
talk to you talk to animals pretty much. Yeah, most days wait. We're talking to a dog right
now telepathically. Yeah, you should give me a beer. Whoa, really run along. Okay, I'll
I'll go get it.
Go go.
I'll get it.
What's the dog's name?
Uh, Fido.
Fido.
Ah.
That sounds like a very generic dog name.
But you're too, it's telepathic.
Yeah.
It's not, you don't like, you don't bark or anything.
No, I don't need to.
I am in my head.
You guys wouldn't get it, humans.
I don't know why you're laughing at me.
Why are you making fun of me right now?
You guys are my nemesi.
I'm not.
You guys have any nemesi in the rotation?
I don't.
in the rotation currently. How many nemesis is? Probably my boss. Yeah. Yeah I don't like
your boss either. Your baby cousin? My baby cousin Steven. What did he do? Yeah what did
your baby cousin do? He hit me and he beat me and he strangled me within an inch of my life.
He was grabbing your finger really tight? Yeah. Yeah. And he almost died. He hasn't been born
yet this is gonna happen this is gonna happen in the future this is all mental
I can look into the future yeah I took a lot of spice yeah I have to say one of
my writings in June yet don't spoil it well one of my cousin Stephen is in it
he's everywhere damn you kind of look like him right now I'm gonna kill you
shit one of my greatest nemesis nowadays it have to be like the devil and like
the evil see and flicks on our world I think the devil and his demons yeah he
has a lot of demons true and endless supply he has I mean more than endless
sometimes it feels like cuz I mean I feel like he does pretty much all the
bad shit in the world - with his demons I think my nemesis is probably myself
every day. That is deep shit. Me and Alex also, I know I don't. That is hilarious.
Hell yeah! Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo! Me and Alex did run into one of the devil's demons
also after we committed our, on the train there was a. Oh my god. I blocked that out
of my mind. No that was crazy. There's just like a crazy guy who just started yelling
at me when we're on the what do you say he was like five full. He was just
like he was like spitting like like spitting while he yelled and he was
saying he was going to like cut off all our faces and stuff and he like he
like finished his rant to actually turn to me and he was like do you know what
inflation is and I was like I was like I don't know and he was like it's when
it's when like supply Griffin. No he literally was like it was like it's like
the supply is greater than demand or like whatever and I was like oh cool and
he's like now. I taught you something now you learn something and I was like
thank you and then he like left. He just walked out of the car, damn he was
yelling about like five minutes telling you for such a long time. He's going to
like kill me and then we went past the side. He's like yeah, this one my
lawyer in this oh yeah, john golly
john golly
I did a sound like a fucking can do a character. Did he like Mr Member John
got he was I think so yeah, we're what train were you guys on you were going
like canal street. He was like canal street. This is where my lawyer lives
John Golly
and then he said he's a Jew.
I don't that doesn't sound like it's honestly the best night of my life.
really cool. Yeah. That's crazy. I fucking yelled at you. He was he was going off
to you. He said he was talking about jail too. It was like you're going to go to
jail a thousand hard dicks in your ass.
He was on one crazy New York baby. Yeah. I've not had that was I think the
craziest the craziest person who yeah it was like the only time i've ever had
someone like yell on my face. I think I am pretty new to the city.
True. Yeah so I did there was a crazy guy on the subway one time who was
walking up and down the car like giving a speech and at one point he was like
you were like did you guys see the little guys on tv in that commercial
i'll get back to that later
the little like the like i have no idea like the toy story aliens. Yeah i was
I was picturing like minions or something.
Yeah.
You see these little guys?
That was pretty much it.
They follow groups.
He was just giving a speech about like an app or something.
Like he was talking about like some website and then in the middle of it he just said
that.
Pretty cool.
Oh wait, maybe it's the Geico Gecko.
Could be the Geico Gecko.
There's only one of the Geico Gecko.
Hello mate, I'm a Geico Gecko.
That was so good.
Dude, thank you.
That was amazing.
Holy crap.
holy crap
hello my name is Alex Forrest
I am auditioning for the Geico Gecko
ok
hello mate
I'm the Geico Gecko
laughing
that was beautiful
that was really good
could you do like flow from progressive now
hello mate
I'm the Geico Gecko
That's all I say for the rest of the podcast.
This is a protest.
I'm protesting your show while I'm on it.
I'm protesting the apartheid.
Yeah.
That's what the Geico Gecko caused.
The Geico Gecko caused apartheid in South Africa.
Yeah, he did do a bunch of fucked up stuff.
I don't like him.
The first time I got suspended from Twitter was because I told him to kill himself.
That's not funny.
Back then you could say whatever you wanted back then too.
That was an outlier.
Isn't it crazy that like, why the fuck is the Geico, like Geico's insurance, why the
fuck is it a gecko?
Well geckos are, they love...
The fastest animal on earth.
And the best thing about insurance is how fast it is.
Yeah, how fast you get your money.
The only commercials that make sense in my head is like Allstate.
But like why do they have insurance commercials in the first place?
Because insurance is so boring.
Yeah you need an exciting character.
You need someone like J.K. Simmons, Flo, the cavemen, people you can trust.
Yeah.
To give them their money.
Remember when Flo first dropped?
Oh yeah.
We all know who we were.
The streets were on fire. Oh man, you could not you could not it's like the OJ verdict. Yeah flow dropping
I think that happened on the same day actually
That's what people were crazy about. Yeah
That's the thing about oh, Jason's a people like crazy
I don't know how to feel about this fucking OJ verdict, but I mean have you seen flow? Yeah, goddamn dude
That's a keeper. They're gonna keep her around for like 10. It's been like 10 years since it's been a long time
Yeah, it's crazy. She's good. She has a good job. Yeah, she has a good job. You know what fuck you guys
She has a good job
She's probably so rich. She probably is like net worth. You know, that's her name
She played I think she played
Tom's wife
Yeah, what's her name Stephanie Courtney Stephanie? Sounds like I made it up
It's like oh yeah
Brittany Ashley, that's her from the from the Geico Gecko. That's the woman. That's the
Geico Gecko, that's the woman who does the Gecko? Yeah model. She's like the does the mocap. Yeah mocap for the Gecko
Yeah, cuz she has a tail so
Only woman with a tail only women with a tail can mocap for the Gecko true
The only woman can mocap for the gecko too because of his contract demands.
He has a slender body.
And his slender body.
His beautiful slender body.
He's slim thick.
He is.
He is slim thick.
I'd love to see the Geico Gecko with a BBL.
Damn.
I'd love to see.
I'd love.
Oh man.
Suddenly I gotta put this pillow on my lap.
Suddenly I can't stand up.
The Geico Gecko with a big ass.
You should draw that.
You draw that picture.
it to me. I'm sure it already. I think it's so funny in like movies or just I don't know
maybe in real life but when people are horny and they're like "Oh mommy!" Dude big in the
80s like people do that all the time. Yeah. Oh mommy. The thing it's it makes me laugh
every time to like to like see like a hot girl or something and go oh my god that
gets me like literally every time just it's always funny like pretending you
have like a stomachache cuz yeah just like yeah like saying like like it like
you're in pain oh no my stomach hurts cuz I saw her you just do like the Tom
scream from Tom and Jerry. I'm gonna drink some water my throat has been killing me
lately. Yeah I mean you don't have to tell us you're gonna drink water you can just
do it. Look at what I'm doing right now. While he's drinking that if anyone wants
to buy a guitar for $200 I'm selling my guitar. You're selling your guitar? I
don't play my SG enough to like I have another guitar. Message Patrick if you want to
If you live in Bushwick or anywhere in New York and you want to buy a Gibson SG for $200 or an Epiphone SG for $200
I don't know. I don't want to over sell it. It's a 2010 Epiphone SG. Can I have it? Do you have 200 bucks?
No, I
Want it for free
Yeah, all right
My Stratocaster that's kind of broken but the SG was a an impulse purchase that I can't justify
justify my anyone if any other listeners are wanting to buy something.
I have my Rodney copper bottom that I am willing to sell.
I have my madam gasket.
I'm also willing to sell.
I will not be selling my big well.
Okay, so you can just come to our apartment and buy some stuff.
Yeah, I am serious about the guitar though.
I can't justify owning it.
Yeah.
Anyway, here's the list.
I'm also selling some shirts that I own.
What is this?
You can just post about this on Twitter.
I'm selling a t-shirt that I own.
I'm not selling anything.
I like everything I own.
Nothing will be sold by me.
Some people have all the answers.
Maybe I've got to get into Depop as a side hustle.
You do really well on Depop, I think.
Yeah, I've got some shit.
I bought a lot of quasi skateboards crew neck.
like green velour and I put it on and I was like man I look so fat in this.
All you have to do is order like a Jurassic Park t-shirt from Amazon and then just list
it as like retro logo tee and you can sell it for $80.
Are you serious?
I'm completely serious.
Oh who's this?
Someone just ran past our closet?
No it's somebody, no it's not somebody coming in here.
I thought it was someone knocking.
yeah i thought like joe got home
now i don't know when he comes home
i think he died
no he died and went to heaven he's in universal studios
yeah he's in the harry potter world the wizarding world of harry potter
joe's exact location my roommate joe
his exact location
california
at the butterbeer stand
at the butterbeer restaurant yeah but dude i don't know if he's there is he
there for horror nights
uh... not maybe i don't know if he is on the lucky son of a bitch he's just
hanging out on if if that's why he's there on the sleep in his bed tonight
because
but a freak he can't should be kind of everything nice i'm gonna fordnick
deal
ford's bed
joe if you listen to this shit
sniffing if maybe welcome to your nightmare and i say the real world and
is what i'm going to do in your room
alright which one should i do policy that there
this one
other one other one okay this is today's list this is top 10 ways to annoy your
dentist by positron wild hog do this i don't think we did this no we didn't do
yeah we didn't do this we did not you say that every episode before you start
a little pretty much yeah uh the description of this list is at least be
kind to some dentists they too have feelings
all day and that's a good point that's a good point right there
well i get it feeling like a lot of the other students are you going to
but i am not only stole that from my from my drake parody song in my feelings
well just to themed you were not for so long to get it's not finish it i got
about one line
yeah is good though many cry the for the other one
kiki do you love me
well about as far as i got the next line will look at his point but i haven't got
there yet to get on the uh... number one
bite down suddenly the moment his finger is furthest down your mouth.
It's funny to me how your dentist is sticking his finger like so far down your mouth.
That's just like trying, that's how to help you if your dentist is like trying to do something
to you.
When the dentist puts the finger in the mouth, it's like man, don't you, can't you make a
tool to do this?
Yeah, use a tool.
Like I'd rather they use like a...
My dentist doesn't really put his hand in my mouth.
Mine does.
Really?
They just use their tools.
I mean if they're gonna put their finger in my mouth, I'd rather they make like a
Like a silicone finger that they put in my mouth. Yeah, yeah
I just their actual they should you know, like when you get a magic kit and yeah
Like a fake finger job that you can have to wear one of those
Yeah, so I can buy you like maybe like like a latex like
Fake finger for all five fingers and it's blue. Well, no it
It should be like that like to be a dentist
You should have to like chop off one of your fingers as like the dentist oath or whatever
Yeah, and then you put on like a fake finger every day that the patient is allowed to try like bite off sure if they want
To sure cuz like me how fucked up are your guys teeth? I do that really good
Yeah, mine are like not great. But I mean you all know my teeth stories. You don't know what's going on
You just ask cuz you wanted to tell your teeth stories again and you guys all know y'all know my teeth stories are wild as fuck
Dude yeah Pat at parties telling his teeth stories like the whole room. Yeah
There was like two nights ago. I we were at that like that show and somebody was talking to me about like
Dental insurance or something and I did like just like, you know, you know how I like Trent like trail off until like ADHD stories
I like go nowhere. I just like told them about like my cracked tooth
I was like, I realized like after like I stopped saying it, I was like, yeah, that was like,
that went fucking nowhere. Like that was you were doing it to strangers. There was, yeah,
somebody like I met is a long story. Kind of dude. I was just like punishing somebody
about my tooth. It sucks. It sucks that I do that. I hate it so much. But if you get
a text and it's like, Hey, can we hang out and talk more about your tooth? Hey, you're
You're the tooth guy, right?
Yeah.
Whoa.
You're the weird teeth guy.
I wanted to hear the end of the story.
Like what happened?
This guy came into my job the other day and he was like, "Man, I really want to buy a
soda but I really hurt my tooth.
I got a hole in it.
Look.
Ah."
And he's like, "You can see it in the back.
That, dude, yeah.
Whoa.
For like a year.
For like a year, I like, while we were, I think like a day we were recording like the
first couple episodes I cracked my tooth eating candy. I cracked my back molar eating candy
and I didn't get it like fixed until like. I cracked that tooth and I cracked the bottom
tooth I'm doing it again. I'm doing the same fucking story. Here's a top comment. I did
this they got upset because it hurt her finger. It's a good point. But it says his finger.
this one says her finger. Well I think you could only do this if you have a boy dentist.
I've always wanted to do this, says cat lover 2004. I did that once before, she screamed
super loud. I never went to that dentist ever again. It's crazy that you can just change
your dentist up. Yeah. Damn. I do, I'm no loyalty to your dentist, fuck you. That's
right, I hate going to my dentist. Folks, do you hate going to the dentist? Yes. Well
teeth.com you can get new teeth delivered straight to your door. Use promo code
Marin20. Marin20. Marin20. I don't know why I'm giving him this voice. I'm Mark
Marin and I hate going to the dentist. Yeah. Fuck. I just was trying to put this on your head.
Oh my god. You want to play my little games? Fine.
Number two. Oh you guys are making fun of me all the time.
Number two. Paint the words dentistry is for tit heads on your teeth before your appointment. That's
actually pretty clever. That sounds like it's a more harder for you because you have paint on
on your teeth. Yeah. So, let's say the dentist has to clean it off. I hate this
fucking list. Yeah. God damn it. Well, that's what happens. This doesn't fit.
This wouldn't fit on your teeth. So, you start writing it and then you end up
just painting the words dentistry on your teeth. And they go in and they're
like, you know, you don't have to do that. Is that 26? Yeah, they'll do it like that.
They'd be like, oh. Is that 26 letters? Let's count together. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five.
You do count, I mean you need a space.
Yeah, but your teeth have spaces, at least mine do.
My teeth really have, this guy right here.
Look at this, I have a tooth right here, it's rather sharp.
It's called my canine tooth.
That guy at work was just me.
I just had a...
Yeah, you were in the mirror.
Did you guys know I had two sharp teeth in my top teeth?
Because my past life I was a dog named Werewolf.
Really?
Yeah.
That was you?
I used to have a dog named Werewolf.
Oh!
Boy?
That's it.
Maybe it would be a baby.
A baby?
Yeah.
Just like old times.
Yeah, I was this mistreated dog in my past life.
my owner used to like do all these crazy things to me shut up shut up you liked
it the top comment is was going to vote this for the first one but this was
going to vote the first one but this genius one will do nicely haha true does
anyone does one have that many teeth though good point dude I gotta wear my
my glasses that's like too far for me to read yeah martingales says
got Donald Duck yeah
do that Donald Duck last sometimes this weird martingales
says
so he will love that, but it's true. I mean that I mean well that thing is
He will love that that's Glenn Martin DDS. Yeah
Well dentistry is for tit heads. It's like a tit head is like a fan of tits, right?
There's like tit heads and ass heads or is it a head? That's a big tit. Yeah, I mean either way either way
I'm sure on that thing's face
Sucking on your dentist face, huh?
So you can get a mouth profile
He puts his mouth on my mouth. Yeah, he sucks it in and then it's like Kirby
He knows like when I go to the dentist
They put the lead blanket on me the whole time because my boners like so
Try to weigh it down
You're just like I'm sorry
They like leave the room for a second they come back and I'm lying like like belly down like
pumping the air. You're completely naked. Oh, I didn't know you were coming back.
Yeah, where did the water jet go? Where is that? There's like a huge puddle
like pouring. Get out! I rented this space today. I'm trying to take dick pics
with the x-ray.
They're like, "All right, we need to take a picture of your teeth," and they leave the
room to take the x-ray.
I take my pants off and stand up.
I'm so glad I've never had a tailbone injury or something like that where they have to
take an x-ray where my dick is visible.
Where they have to put that thing in your butt in order to heal you.
I don't want my doctor knowing how small my thing is.
No way.
Oh my God.
Could you imagine?
and they're like, oh yeah, they're trying to they're trying to rub it off.
They're roasting like there's like a like there's a smudge on it, but now
it's just my thing. Yeah, they'd be like, can you try and make your thing
bigger before we take the x ray? Just like it's so that you don't get
embarrassed. Yeah, that nurse kind of likes you.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with your tailbone like
Doug. Yeah, I don't know. Like put this on and go talk to her. And it's like that
like robe with like the butt exposed.
Yo, she wants to see your butt so bad through the robe.
It's like a 95 year old man.
Yeah. I'm not even your doctor. I'm just like helping you out, dude. I'm just
trying to wingman you here.
Yo, Pops.
That's what they call me in this doctor's office. They call me Pops. They only keep
me here for vibes.
True.
I'm kind of like bez and the happy mondays. I'm just here to dance. I treat
I treat the dentist office like a barber shop crazy. I go in there. I'm like
y'all seen this. Yeah, it's a little seen this shit. Yeah. What do y'all
yeah, arms broken number three fill him up with all the anesthetic. I got a
munch as since I keep breaking my own arms. I could talk to the doctor fill
him up with all the anesthetic until he feels nothing at all. Then amputate his
arm when he's looking away.
Martin Clitz says, "I think this won't just annoy him."
Good point, Martin.
Yeah.
That's a very good point.
It's a bad idea.
Don't do that to your dentist.
You'll get arrested.
That's just a crime.
Yup.
Most of these are crimes.
And crimes aren't annoying.
They're cool.
Crime is the coolest thing you can do.
I respect criminals.
Unless it's to me.
Unless you mug me or steal my shit.
Never do a crime to me.
Then it's lame.
Then it's embarrassing for you.
I straight up I don't like when crime happens to me.
Facts.
Yup.
Deadass.
For my family or my chosen family.
Or anybody.
Homies is family too.
Homies is my like chosen family.
I'll drink to that.
Is that the ICP song?
My homies blood is like thicker than my family's blood.
It's like a saying.
Yup.
What's the lyrics to that ICP song?
Homies.
I know the chorus is like, Homies, homies.
Yeah.
I heard that in fourth grade.
That song is all about homies.
Did I ever tell you about the ADHD forums I was on in fourth grade?
No.
It's called sparktop.org.
I told you about it for sure.
It was on sparktop.org.
I found out about, I looked up if other kids on there were talking about CKY and there
were, there were a lot of kids talking about CKY on there.
And they got, one of them got me into ICP.
They told me to look up "Piggy Pie."
And then through that, I found "Homies,"
and I thought that was a beautiful song.
- Yeah.
I don't care about the "Homies" song.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I don't like that one very much.
- It's not a good one.
It's not their best.
- It's not a good one, no.
- 'Cause it's not about anything scary or clown-related.
- No, the good ones are, yeah,
are all the-- - Yeah.
- The good ones are-- - The good ICP songs
are all about either killing people,
being a clown, or being a Christian.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
water air fire and earth fucking magnets how do they know it's it's water air
fire and dirt Oh dirt yeah I was earth you ever you ever realize you've like
miss heard a song lyric your whole life but like still like you you correct it
you look up the lyric and what it really is I always thought it was happy
happy birthday.
Why are we singing this?
Shouldn't it be happy birthday?
It's his birthday.
You guys are so stupid.
His birthday was last week.
Number four, throw up violently the moment he starts examining you.
Can the dentist sue you for this?
There's one comment that just says, "Oh God!"
If I saw someone do that, I'd say that.
Oh God.
I'd say oh brother. That's what I'd say. I'd say oh mommy. Yeah. Like you're like insanely horny.
Mommy! Mama! We can just cut that part out. What movie is that there's like one specific...
There's an Austin Powers. That's what it was. That's why I was thinking about it. He's like
mommy. Yeah then he's like falls into lava. Thinking about his mom. Oh man. That Austin.
I mean that piece of work those that crowd that he hangs with yeah Austin their sketch uh-huh
man gold gold member loves gold but he did I mean he loves his faja too I think he loves it or he
hated his faja I can't I know Dr. Evil hated his faja I know Beyonce Knowles is in that movie oh
remember when he kisses Nathan Lane that's a funny scene oh yeah Nathan Lane Nathan Lane is doing
Beyonce's voice. Oh yeah yeah yeah. That's a perfect movie. All three of them. Yeah. One
mega movie. I'm a huge AP fan. AP and Dune are my favorite movies right now. Hey I still
haven't seen it so you better not drop any spoilers. It's so good. This would be horrible
but you probably wouldn't get sued since throwing up isn't your fault even if you did it on
purpose how would they know. True. I can't throw up on purpose. Me neither. I stick my
finger down my throat everywhere. I'm sorry. I'm really sick. I ate some time.
I have to go home. Can you take me to the nurse? Yeah, I don't want to. I don't want
to get a dentist appointment today. So can you just send me home? I'm so sick. I can't
when you guys go to the dentist. You just kind of smell like latex for the rest of the day.
A little bit. I feel like that's whenever I go to the dentist. I think I talked about it before,
but there's like a like a latex mask thing that they would put on like they had like scented
latex masks that they would put on at this one dentist office I went to for
like the laughing gas. And my little brother did that. He's like
insanely allergic to latex and like that's how they found out was like they
put one of those on. He was like I want the grape scented one and then like they put it on
and he like couldn't breathe. And he died. Rip. Yeah my little brother is dead.
do we know happy halloween
number five pin him down with his tools and start pulling his teeth out without
anesthetic. I would so do this to my former childhood dentist. He did that to
me, so i would love to do it to him as well, so he could see how that feels. Who
made this? Did jigsaw make this list? No, it was positron wild talk. Oh yeah, you
you know hello dr. harry i'ma for years you pulled out my teeth for years you
told me to floss but now you will have to floss or else you'll die that's the
thing about dentists they don't do any of the shit they tell you to do no way
huge hypocrites yeah you smell the dentist's breath disgusting it's
horrible yeah they just eat candy all day - yeah it's like they since their
dentists like they don't have to get yelled at by any dentist so they know
they can do whatever they want up they get candy all of themselves because no
- No one else is eating it.
- Exactly, all to themselves.
So, you know, if you see a dentist
come to your house on Halloween,
don't give him any candy, they've had enough already.
- I went to a dentist a year ago,
saw a Reese's cup in his pocket.
- What?
- Back pocket.
- What a hypocrite.
- And it melted.
- I think he might have pooped his pants.
- Nah, dude.
- And it smelled weird.
- 'Cause it did smell like peanut butter, but also shit.
- You know what I had the other day?
- I think he made a Reese's at home.
- I think he had a feces cup.
(laughing)
bit into a Reese's cup and it was one of the Reese's cups with the Reese's pieces inside.
Whoa. It was really delicious. They got one now that's two Reese's with a pretzel in it.
Really? Yeah. I saw that somewhere. I don't believe you. I saw it at the store. Which
store? Now do you believe me? Which store? Candy store. I love the candy store. You buy
yourself five minutes. I will be back with questions. Number six, ask for a toffee filling.
Actually, that's like if you could get fillings made out of food. Yeah. That'd be great. You
you could just taste it all the time.
- I would get a Cool Ranch filling.
- Yeah.
- What's the food that you'd want to taste like 24/7?
- Not Cool Ranch, actually.
It would probably be Brussels sprouts or steak,
or steak and Brussels sprouts.
(laughing)
- Yeah, probably.
- I might.
- Or with mashed potatoes on the side.
- I mean, if we're going practical,
maybe like mint, like just have mint in your mouth all the
time.
- 'Cause then other people could taste it if you kiss them.
- Exactly, or if you like tried to,
if you were like, open your mouth really wide
and like licked all over their face.
- You know what would suck though?
If you're like, you're a big fan of Big Red
and then you're like, oh yeah, I want the Big Red filling
and then you like, later just like, man.
- Why did I choose that?
- Yeah, or like if you chose like the poop
or like the sewage filling and it's like,
well, like this was fun for like an hour,
but now it's the rest of my life.
- That's the, here's the thing about that.
Can you shut the flavor off?
- No, it's a film.
- Yeah, I mean, you could take it out.
- So, I think--
I think maybe it'd have to be something that can go with every food.
Yeah, because if it's like the water filling, the water filling would be pretty good.
That would be perfect.
Yeah.
Maybe like a cheese whiz, sparkling water filling.
I get pop rocks filling.
I get the YouTube filling.
I'd have Charlie the Unicorn in my mouth all the time.
I get the Charlie Brown feeling.
I get to open my mouth and hear it go, say, "Leo Plerodon."
When does the Charlie Brown show come on?
Charlie Brown Pumpkin.
Usually around Halloween or Christmas.
It's soon though, right?
Isn't tomorrow Halloween?
Valentine's Day, Arbor Day, my birthday.
Now I know where that fucking plastic thing came from.
It's from the goggles you're wearing.
Oh yeah?
It fell off.
Alex has been putting on and taking off goggles this entire time.
I don't know why.
It's because I'm smart.
- You're looking at this like it's a science experiment for you.
- Yeah, everything is an experiment for me.
- The only guest who fidgets more than Patrick.
(laughing)
- I got a lot going on.
- He's like chewing on your goggles.
(laughing)
- I'm hungry.
- I've honestly, since he's been here,
I've not fidgeted that much.
- He's doing it all for you.
- Yeah, I know.
(laughing)
- He's dancing.
- Help me!
(laughing)
Number seven, hide a tiny paintball gun in your gums,
which you can operate with your tongue.
(laughing)
Just make sure you--
- What kind of fantasy world do you live in, Positron?
- Well, listen to this, just make sure you practice
and perfect this skill before the big day.
Yeah, I mean, obviously you couldn't do it with no practice.
- Yeah, you'd have to practice so hard.
- Yeah, number eight is speak as if you're already
on anesthetic when you walk in, and the only comment is,
would love to be a fly on the wall if anyone did this.
- That is actually a perfect comedy sketch
when you think about it.
- Yeah, it is.
I could see that on SNL or Ellen's show.
Also, this is kind of similar, but you know people are always like, if you could have dinner
with anyone living or dead, who would it be?
I would probably choose my dentist because he could tell me which food I should eat and
which I shouldn't.
At dinner.
Yeah, at dinner.
If I could have dinner with someone living or dead, I would prefer to choose living because
I think it would smell pretty bad.
yeah. I want to come to the food, though dead. I do not like live animals.
They're loud
okay,
number
nine. Keep a live snake in your mouth and wait for him to discover it by
surprise. Whatever number ten is really good. It is really good. Eat his tools.
That is clever. Yeah. He wouldn't expect that. He would be fucked. That's like a lot of money.
Yeah, I try to swallow the like water thing, but like you know it has like the whole, the
like the pipe that goes like it's like a, it's like a tube. Oh yeah. I love it when
they do that. I try to swallow it. That feels so good when they do that. I swallow the entire
chair eventually. Oh yeah? Yeah. That probably set, could cost him, send back a few hundo.
(laughing)
- He's probably--
- Didn't we look up--
- Apple Creek without a paddle.
(laughing)
- Didn't we look that up one time,
like how much dentist tools cost?
Or we looked up medical tool,
'cause we found that Amazon thing where it was like--
- You can buy medical tools on Amazon
for like thousands of dollars.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - But what?
- We should get, for the apartment,
we should get like an ultrasound machine.
- Yeah.
- A dentist chair. - We have so many tummy aches
and we don't know why.
- Okay, we get an ultrasound machine, right?
we have friends over we were like okay eat this coin we're gonna see if we can
see the coin yeah yeah bad news you're pregnant with four babies we find out
one of our roommates is pregnant yeah I'm not looking forward to that day yeah
I'm not pregnant all right let's see number 11 chug a two liter of coke in
front of him before your appointment yeah you know what I did I went to
I went to, because I had that weird like lymph node thing,
I went to the, like I went to urgent care
to get it checked out.
And I did get prescribed candy.
- Ooh. - That's so sick, dude.
- The dentist, or the dentist, the doctor said
that like I take antibiotics,
but also I should eat a lot of sour things,
like Warheads and Sour Patch Kids.
- Damn, dude, that's the dream.
- I was like, whoa. - That's insane.
- That's so sick. - Wow.
- Oh man, I yesterday had--
- That's what I get for going to Dr. Wonka.
- It'd be funny if like, if you,
You got prescribed that and then you like, you go, you like, you get like a $10,000 bill
because the candy isn't covered by your insurance.
You were not supposed to eat that.
Yeah.
Yesterday at that mic I saw like a, there's a plate of candy at this open mic and it was,
I thought it was like a gobstopper, like something to suck on, but it was a gumball.
I felt violated.
You just suck on a gumball for like an hour.
Wait, you could have grabbed the candy?
Yeah, you didn't see that?
They had a big tray.
asked the guy to throw me a piece of candy. He said no? No, he said no. I'm sorry man.
Damn. Then they spelled my name wrong. Did you see? I did. Yeah, I went, I'm doing stand up again.
I went to a mic. My handwriting is so bad that they wrote Patrick Domav.
It was like projected on the screen behind him when he was going. Patrick Domav. Patrick Domav.
yeah, I don't know like the Irish rush. Yeah,
the Irish, the Irish Russian could be all my jokes are done and yeah,
yak off smirnoff thing, but yeah, the Irish in in troubles, Ireland car bomb you yeah,
hey, sorry to all the I'm sorry to all my my people yeah for that joke yeah, it's you're
you're the Irish Russian comedian. You just get on stage and immediately pass out from alcohol
all poisoning because I'm drinking whiskey and vodka.
Yeah.
All right.
What's the last one on the last one on the list?
Number twelve say you've never flossed in your life.
There's one comment on it that just says oh God.
Yeah.
Just imagining the dentist reaction and just like would flip out.
Yeah I might actually do that the next.
That's the only one on this one that you on this list that you can do.
Just telling your dentist like yeah I'm never going to floss again.
I never floss nothing you can say will make me floss.
I hate you.
All right.
Is that the episode?
Alex, plug your shit.
Oh yeah.
Home Planet on Twitter.
Yeah.
Me and our other roommate Joe, we make videos and movies and crap.
They're great.
Check it out.
Home_planet.
Yes sir.
I've been in two of them now.
Patrick's been in a couple.
Yeah.
And just keep your eyes out because you never know.
You never know who might pop up.
There could be more.
There could be other people in them.
All right.
And $200 for an Epiphone SG2010.
True.
We have a super exciting Halloween episode coming out Saturday that you don't want to miss.
Not going to spoil what it is, but subscribe because it's going to be really good.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
There is a demon.
Bye.