You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
- Keep going.
(singing)
- I have something important to say.
- Okay, let's hear it.
- If everyone listening could please,
please go to patreon.com/podcastsaboutlists.
I am ruined.
We all are.
Oh, Cameron's not.
No, dude, cash out Cam.
Cash out Cameron's not.
We went to Atlantic City this weekend.
Atlantic City has broken me.
I'm a different man.
I'm worse.
I'm a worse man.
I'm a bad man.
I rose from the ashes like a phoenix, but I didn't even need any ashes.
I was fine.
You mean you rose from the dead like Christ.
I rose from myself.
I rose from life.
How many times on the podcast did I say I was afraid of gambling because of how much I would lose?
Probably a million. You don't know didn't pain and then you didn't even lose the most though. You lost the least I did not
Lease and you put in the least money if you had kept going you would have made money
No, I would have lost no you also you you have the worst energy going on
I my strategy at the slots as you play until you get five dollars and then you can buy any drink you want
- Dude, you had the absolute worst strategy.
- The Doran system works every time.
- Imagine--
- You get a vodka cranberry whenever you want.
- Think about a soccer game, right?
- I've never watched it.
- There's a guy kicking penalty kicks, right?
- Yeah.
- If he walked up to it every single time like,
"Oh, I'm gonna miss.
"Oh, I'm gonna miss right now."
He would miss every single time.
- That's not the attitude I went--
- This is the Doran strategy in the soccer metaphor,
is if the guy walking up for the penalty kick,
if he kicked it 100 times in 10 seconds,
missed them all, and then walked off the field
like Charlie Brown looking at his feet.
(laughing)
- Dude, you just, you have to--
- That's the Doran system.
- You have to approach a slot--
- Look, the Patty Jackpot system--
- Listen, okay, I'm gonna let you in on a little knowledge,
and I shouldn't do this, because this is a free episode,
and I shouldn't be giving away these money tips.
- I'm not kidding, please, please.
There's over 100 hours of content on that Patreon, okay?
And $5 gets you, that's, come on.
- Come on, and also, if you wanna just send just me money,
you could do that, you could too.
- No, you gotta send it to me and Caleb.
- If you wanna just send me like a, just a bunch of money.
- And me too.
- And Cameron.
- Okay, fine, all the--
- And Patches.
- Okay, just do the Patreon then.
- Listen, here's the system, here's what you wanna do, okay?
- Okay.
- You're going in there,
you're putting your money into the machine,
you spend maximum three times, you are going to win money,
you're gonna be up 40 cents a dollar, it doesn't matter.
The second you're up, you cash out.
You shake your receipt around,
you shake the voucher back and forth, okay?
- Yeah. - Yeah, we gotta close
this window, dude. - Oh, fuck.
- That's okay.
- You guys gotta shut up out there with your motorcycles.
- You're shaking the voucher around, okay?
'Cause that's like aerating wine, okay?
That gets-- - Yeah, yeah.
It's like a decanter.
- Exactly. - Yeah, that's a good point.
- You're walking around and you're letting,
It's not your heart, okay?
It's not your heart that's pulling you to the next machine.
It's your spirit.
It's your soul.
Your soul is going to tell you where to go.
It's like a compass.
You walk over to the next machine.
One spin, you're going to win $17, okay?
You're up $17.40.
Next machine, down $40.
Doesn't matter, okay?
Next machine, down $20 more.
Doesn't matter.
Next machine, you're going to be up $47,000.
That's right.
That's the system.
And it works.
Because they've got little cameras in the casino.
They're watching.
They're saying, "Who's shaking the voucher the most?"
That's the hustler.
that's the person that's gonna win the jackpot. We want to give that man all we can.
Right, who's the guy who hasn't ordered a single drink this whole time except for
one bottled water at the very end? I'm gonna dress up, next time we go I'm gonna
dress up like an Afghan veteran right? I'm gonna like, I'm gonna duct tape one
of my, one of my arms behind my back. That's a good idea. I'm gonna dress in full
fatigues, keep looking at all the cameras, saluting them and then sitting down.
See if they don't fucking, see if they don't treat me right. I'm gonna do
the opposite. I'm gonna go in, dress up like a Taliban soldier and I'm gonna
chase you around the casino.
Well that'll be even better for me, that might sell it even more.
Right, see but then whatever money you make, we split the profits.
No, I'm not going to split my money with a Taliban damn dirty low down son of a bitch
dog.
Here's another tip, and I really, I should not be giving away these tips, but I will
because I love the fans so much.
What you want to do, you want to go in there, put five dollars into the worst machine, the
most terrible slot, the one you can tell is not going to pay.
You put five minutes in there, five dollars in there,
five minutes at the machine,
you're gonna get down to 12 cents, okay?
You might start crying, you might think,
"I'm ruined."
No, this is what you do.
You take your voucher for 12 cents,
you look for the richest guy in the casino,
you walk over, you say, "Here man,
"let me just give this to you, I'm not gonna use this."
You give them the 12 cents, they add it to their slots,
you are entitled to half of whatever they win.
- That's true. - That's how it works.
- 'Cause you don't know which money
they're making their money off of.
- Exactly, exactly.
You don't know if they just made money off of your 12 cents.
You don't know what the proportion is,
so you just assume it's gotta be 99%.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, so you know what, I'll settle for half of the money.
- You tell 'em, if I hadn't put that 12 cents in,
you wouldn't be winning.
- Yeah.
- Gambling is so beautiful, dude.
I'm still, every time I close my eyes,
I'm just seeing cash, cash, cash.
- I honestly, I love Atlantic City.
I hate the gambling.
I love the free concerts.
- You sound like a mom.
- I love the atmosphere, I love the restaurants.
You love the atmosphere of Atlantic City?
You didn't even like the view.
You looked out at the marshes and you said, "Those are disgusting.
It looks like Final Fantasy VII."
It looks like Final Fantasy VII.
You know what Final Fantasy VII Advent Children looks like?
I do know what that looks like.
And you said it was disgusting.
It's a beautiful movie.
I never said it was disgusting.
You did.
You said it looked horrible.
No.
I said it looks beautiful.
I did not say that.
I said it looks like Final Fantasy VII.
I said look at the sun reflecting off the water.
No.
Yeah, that's what I said.
And you said, "This looks like a poop and a dirt combined."
I never said it looked like poop and dirt.
You did.
No, you just did.
all I call that dupe and I said what are you talking about that doesn't make any
sense you said this looks like dupe I said that's not a thing stop saying that
you said it's poop and dirt combined. Dupe is a thing though. Dupe is not a thing. I said it's it is a
thing it's called pert and he said no it's dupe and we got in a big fight yeah
pert's a shampoo dupe is not a thing. Dupe is a thing. Where? Gwyneth Paltrow has it.
That's goop and that's what she puts. No dupe is dupe is dude goop. Dude goop?
- Dude goop.
- It's dude goop that you eat.
- Dude goop, it's goop for dudes.
- It's dude goop dirt poop.
- They should, dude.
You should sign up for goop that should come
like Hello Fresh.
- Yeah, I got it.
- It's like, dude, doop is like,
it's a yoni egg that you put through your urethra.
- Yeah.
- Through your butt.
Why not your butt?
- No, no, it's your urethra.
Come on.
- Can you use those on your butt or is that dangerous?
- You can use a yoni egg on your butt, but be careful.
- That's probably a really good move like for self defense.
- Yeah.
shoot it out like a burrito. Yeah, exactly. Shoot it out like a burrito. Using a yoni egg on your butt is like when you
know like you see those posts that are like oh an inexperienced witch tried to
take on a law and got put in the hospital like you're not ready for the power.
Like there's too much shocker energy. That's why you put it in your penis first because it's both going
it's going to the same place it's going to the pee stot. Yeah, it's true. It's both
going there. How you gonna put an egg in the tip of your fucking thing? It's really
small. It's a tiny egg. Yeah it's the size of a grain of dirt. That would hurt. No it
wouldn't. It's really soft. It has fur on it. Look, if you don't subscribe to
dupe, if you don't go to dupe.com you won't you you won't understand it. I
don't think there is a dupe.com. There is a dupe. I'm going on incognito for dupe.com.
dude go
here in on the baby
uh...
on the real website it's a it's a splash page
uh... it's a splash of you soon to return to the system to be consumed for an
upcoming i'm guessing you might be right that maybe i said or info this does look
like it would dislike is i think an upcoming
the other brand here
yeah yeah
Maybe, maybe that's our sponsor this week.
Dudegoop.com.
Yeah, that's right.
We have an announcement to make.
It's officially, you know, before true fans of the podcast will remember, we had Next
Gear, okay?
We had Ultimate Gear.
We're entering a new era of the podcast.
We're entering a brand new gear.
That's right.
We are in money rock star, lots of millions of dollars gear.
Atlantic City changed me and now I would like to make,
I would honestly like to become a millionaire.
- Yep. - It's truly--
- And not because I wanna buy a fancy car,
I would just like to be able to sit at the slots
a little bit longer than I was able to.
You know, and lose a little more money.
- Yeah, when you're sitting at the slot
and you got $20 worth of credit in there,
you look at the guy next to you, he's got $350.
- You know that he wouldn't--
- That is the best guy in the world.
- Exactly, yeah.
- You know what it is, you have to keep putting money in
to keep winning.
I mean, yeah, the feeling when you, I mean, even when you have the $20 in there, you look
over and you see the guy next to you has $3 left, you are the most powerful man in the
world right now.
Exactly.
It doesn't matter how much he put in.
As long as he got more money.
Money is power.
Power is beauty.
Especially if you spend that money on Rise of Ra MegaWays.
Oh my God, Super Rise of Ra.
Super Rise of Ra.
I didn't play Rise of Ra, but I did play Money Frog.
Money Frog.
I played Buffalo Soldier bonus game.
Oh, Hip Hop Clinko.
Hip Hop Clinko.
I got a time.
Clinko was crazy.
Myths and legend, when that dragon breathes the fire onto the slots, you know you're about
to win big.
Oh, dude.
Press the pustule.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
I forget what I was playing.
Which one did I cashed out $6.66?
Oh my God.
Yeah, Monster Slots, Monster Frankenstein.
I went there after I cashed out, but it was a...
Oh, Clinko Hip Hop Pump Up the Club bonus.
Yeah.
That might have been it.
And again, y'all. Had a great song. Oh my god, yeah. The Squirting Sprayer, that's one of the best.
Dude. Yeah. Funky... Funk? Funky Funk. Yeah. Yeah. There was a lot of different like combos.
The Dagwood. The Dagwood. Mighty Monkey Massacre. That was... Oh, that was so good. Yeah, when you
get the monkey decapitation bonus, oh my god. Gringo's Revenge. Gringo's Revenge is great.
The Skunk of the Day is a great one.
The Slug of Siam was a good machine.
The Slug of Science is also good.
Yeah, they put those two together. It's like Klinko and hip-hop Klinko.
There was also... Did you guys play Oriental Patrick?
Oh, that one was really good.
Oriental Patrick, Kung Fu Patrick. There was African Patrick.
Yeah, Patrick's Fortune.
Yeah, Patrick's Fortune. Yeah, there was a lot of good ones.
there and you know I didn't sign off on any of them.
Aztec chief Patrick.
Patrick the bone doctor.
Yup.
The witch doctor Patrick.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of pictures of my face photoshopped into those things.
In a different, pretty offensive scenario.
Yeah.
Which is, you know, that's why I didn't like the machines.
That's why I like to go into the ice cream store and the, what was that place, Destinations?
The convenience store.
Destinations, the convenience store with the $8 soda.
They should, there should be more convenience stores called stuff like Destinations.
I agree. I agree. That's a really good idea.
What was the...
Ah, fuck.
There was another...
another thing.
Oh, Guy's Sandwich Joint.
Oh, we did hit Guy Fieri.
I finally ate at a Guy Fieri restaurant.
That's been a lifelong dream of mine.
And it was the sandwich joint.
Yeah, just a roast beef sandwich. It's pretty normal.
We live in New York. We could go to Times Square and go to
Guy Fieri's restaurant.
What kind of food does he make?
he make? He makes like... It's just a TGI Fridays, right? Yeah, it's just TGI Fridays, but you know,
it's got that, it's got guys, a seal of approval. Yeah, which is like a Michelin star. Yeah, yeah.
It's like a Michelin star, but the Michelin tire is on like a smash mouth, like hot rod.
It's on like a, it's on like a model T that has flames on the side. One of those.
That shit is sick, man. Yeah. Yeah. But I think we need to, I think I've decided like...
We also, we did also eat at Cosby's Crepes.
It's true.
We did, yeah.
Cosby's Crepes, I mean.
Cosby's Crepatorium.
Save it what you will about that guy, but those crepes, oh my god.
Those are some of the best crepes I've ever had.
Oh my god, Cosby's Crepe Crypt, that was just, that was a culinary delight.
Yeah.
Cosby's Crepes.
It's a bad name.
Yeah.
I know, it's just one letter off from what he did.
- Yeah, be a creep, right?
- Yeah, creep.
- That's what we're talking about, right?
- Exactly, yeah.
- But I think I'm gonna get into political organizing,
but just for like trying to get gambling legalized
in every state.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I think it like is a--
- Everybody deserves it.
- I think everybody deserves to gamble and should gamble.
And also I think we should lower the age of gambling.
- Yeah.
- Like way, way, way lower.
- 16.
Like if you can drive to the casino, you should be able to put a dollar in.
Did you see all those signs on the casino floor that said like don't leave children unattended?
No.
There's like a picture just like a really sad kid.
Dude, a kid in a casino, that kid would not be sad. That is like a paradise.
Also, you can just walk into a casino and use the thing.
You don't have to be, as long as you don't order a drink, they're never gonna card you for the casino.
Yeah, the whole thing you could can be done just with a I'm really this is a good piece of advice for any young people
We were listening. Yeah, just if just go to the casino. Yeah, start putting money
They're not gonna stop you as long as you avoid, you know, like poker or like anything with a dealer. You're fine
Yeah, exactly. Nothing with if you go to Crystal Cove, you can smoke as many cigarettes as you want. I'm in
Cove was a smoking section. Yeah, it's not Crystal. Where's Crystal Cove?
Crystal Cove is probably in the Middle East and it's probably magical but Diamond Cove is a room. It's not even a room
It's a half wall. Yeah, which is great for keeping smoking
Really really good. Yeah, you're not a little smoke on the on the regular floor
But like, you know once you go through that half wall that half wall keeps the smoke in. Yeah
Yeah, that's always the best dude. Like I miss smoking section
so I remember Golden Corral used to have a smoking section and it was literally a it was a
Like a like a velvet rope. Yeah, and I and that was how I could still know well the velvet absorbs the smoke
It's like a sponge for smoke.
Also, smoke is disrespectful and low class.
If you put something fancy like velvet, it can't pass through that.
Right.
Yeah, it can't go past.
It's like drawing salt around a ghost.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It works really well.
It does.
Man, I do, I mean, smoking at a casino, pretty fun.
Smoking at a slot machine, that was awesome.
Pretty fun, yeah.
Yeah.
That was sick.
at the Tropicana, there was like that whole section
of just like the oldest, leatheriest people.
- You used to get the worst people there.
- Yeah, oh my God.
- Just smoking just like, like misty 100s.
- Yeah.
- So many people, like multiple people,
like old people just like passed out at the slot
with the hand of the spin button so badly,
wanted to just go over and do like a stealth,
like Indiana Jones switch and switch out our voucher,
like cash them out and put my 10 cent voucher in.
You would have lost nine cents if you did that.
Yeah, does a guy just pass that next to like a
Smucker's cigarettes somehow?
Like some cigarettes that just like,
like a hundred year old brand of cigarettes.
- These are unbrushable cigarettes.
- Yeah, it's like a cigarette with like a leather pouch
that they come in.
- But they didn't roll their own, they're just that old.
They just stocked up in 1920.
- I remember sitting down next to a--
- They're made of parchment.
I sat down next to a dude who like clearly was smoking before I got there and I saw him
like slam the machine like he was mad at it.
And I asked him if he had a light and he looked at me and just went, "No!"
Just like, "Let's go."
My man, dude.
Yeah.
The best part of going to the casino and seeing like everyone like being like, "Oh, these
people are weird.
Like this guy's like, this guy's swiping the screen on the slot to try and get to win.
Like this guy like is like has a special, he hits the button to try and win and like,
these people are so ridiculous and by the end of the first day I'm trying to like
cast spells to make it. My new thing was, it has worked one time so I started drawing an
infinity sign with my finger on the screen. And that never worked again. On the Dracula machine?
Yeah on Dracula. Oh yeah. What a machine that was. One of the best bonus games.
They also they had amazing Dracula characters I'd never heard of. Yeah well
you know you you never read the book dude you don't understand. What's that guy's name?
Renfield. Renfield's cool dude. He's an insane, he's insane.
Lucretia. He's great as long as he's a second best.
Lucretia's not a Dracula character okay. If you're gonna fucking try and be a...
Latoya. Shamiqua. Shamiqua? Kiki. What?
Titi. These are the girls. You're thinking of a different Dracula.
You're thinking of Mina Harker. The Dracula girl. Oh my god the Dracula girl.
Oh God. What's hotter than a girl? Oh my God, the bats and wolves.
With a girl. What's hotter than a girl? Let's be real. A Dracula girl? That's right.
Yeah. It's a damn good answer. She got the fangs. But we really want to design a podcast
with a list slot so bad. Yeah. I think that's the next logical step. I have a slot concept that I'd
like to pitch to you guys. It's, you know, when you walk around the casino, there's some that are,
you know, like Dracula themed or like Game of Thrones themed or whatever. But the
most prevalent thing is you'll see different ethnic themed slots. Like
there's the Chinese slots, there's a Native American slots, there's the
African slots. And it's always great when you are sitting right next to somebody
who is of that ethnicity while you're at that slot. Exactly. So here's my pitch,
is a slot that matches them all up. So one of the symbols is, you know, it's
It's the slots are, the reels have the different slot machines on them.
Oh, okay.
So you see, you see like you get like five oriental mysteries in a row or whatever, you
know?
That's a pretty good idea.
I think that's a good idea for a slot.
I would say it would be tricky.
I don't think there are enough meta slots.
It would also be tricky because the way that slots work is that there's different symbols
that are ranked best to worst.
Right.
So that would be a pretty tricky thing.
Yeah.
- So you end up with like, you know,
like one of them scoring like the least
and it's like, well why does that one score the least?
- Okay, here's, okay.
- Well, because.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that would not be a good conversation after that.
- Okay, here's my solution.
- Okay.
- It's, and get ready, this is gonna blow your mind, okay?
You win the more different symbols you get.
- Wow.
- If you get a line with one of each,
that's the biggest win you can get.
- That's beautiful. - That's a jackpot.
There might be a line for this slot.
Yeah, this is a slot that will make a lot of people happy.
This might be the new Wheel of Fortune cash link.
It might be.
The RTP on this is gonna be amazing.
I have a slot concept.
Yeah, let's hear it.
My thing in your slot.
Come on, dude.
That's just nasty.
Ooh!
I won't pay out.
I had a slot concept that was basically just like,
if you won, the slot just turned into a TV for 30 minutes
and you got to like earn TV.
TV time. Yeah. You get to watch a scene from a movie or the TV show that the slot is based on.
And then if you guess what scene the movie's from, then you get money.
How about...
The slot itself is like the Gilligan Island slot.
I had another idea which is that you put in money and then it's like a food themed slot.
And if you get a full line of a kind of food, it pops out.
You get that food.
Yeah.
Here's a slot idea for you.
That is a really good idea.
Here's my idea.
it's the slot is a massage chair and you win to turn on different parts of the
massage chair and there can be an adult version
that's a sibyan
that's a really there should be a slot in women's stomachs
that you can play
when you're looking at them. And with your babies in it?
yeah yeah right and you can gamble to see if it's a boy or a girl
yeah yeah or to make them a boy or a girl. Oh no jackpot I just won five thousand babies
I have to take care of these now. This sucks. This is the only slot you don't want a jackpot on
It's true. Which I mean, most slots I don't want a jackpot on. I just want the free drink.
That is a diabolical thing that they have, which is that you...
If you play for five bucks... If you just keep moving machines, if you just keep moving around...
You can get a free drink every ten minutes. Exactly. They don't even... They don't know.
They don't know that they're over-serving you.
You can just go to a bunch of different machines... It's true.
And just keep getting vodka cranberry. And you know what? Your P-Stream the next day,
That thing's gonna be one, you're gonna have no chance of a UTI.
That's true.
Yep.
Impossible.
So, you're honestly, you're getting healthier.
Yeah, so I mean, so do whatever you want to your thing,
because you are not getting a UTI.
You can do it.
You can stick it in the dirt outside.
Yeah, you can blow dust into it with a straw, you're fine.
Yeah, you can take your pants off, walk into a Home Depot where they're cutting plywood,
just stand right next to the saw, let all the shit get in your wiener hole,
and you're fine.
- You're drinking vodka cranberries
or just cranberry juice in general?
- You can start hiding your boogers in there.
It's gonna be all right.
- And you know what?
This also goes back to dupe.
You're gonna have the clearest pee stream ever.
You're gonna, it's gonna be hard.
- Okay, I have an invention.
This isn't a slot. - This isn't a urethra egg out.
- I would like to pitch this idea to Brita,
the Brita filter company.
It's a tiny little Brita filter that you put in your wiener
and it purifies your pee as it comes out.
- Okay, so it's basically like a tiny brick of charcoal.
- Yeah. - I don't think charcoal,
not my, charcoal ain't gonna fix much.
- Well that's why we need the Brita Filter Company's help.
I don't know what company--
- I mean they have the science.
- I mean I know they got scientists.
- And you know they got science.
- They used to have Zach Braff do the voiceover
in their commercials.
So you know, and he's a doctor.
- True.
- I will say one last thing about Atlantic City.
It turned me into,
just the, it made me feel like a rich person
the entire time I was here.
And I started putting my boogers wherever I wanted to.
- Really?
- You could probably clone me.
- The back of the waitress's head?
- How much D&D I put, DNA.
(laughing)
- DNA?
- I put all over the Harrah's Casino.
- Did you put it on the lady that walked up to you?
- I put one on a slot 'cause I thought it looked funny.
I put one just on the screen.
- That was so fucking funny.
- I was treating every slot like a baby's eye pad, dude.
I was just fucking sneezing on 'em.
I thought it maybe would help my chances.
If you disrespect the slot.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- That is, dude, that is my biggest,
if you, if you tell, if you, you,
what you gotta do is when,
while the slot is spinning, before it stops,
you say, "You're a fucking disgusting piece of shit.
"Squirt out some money for me right now.
"Squirt, squirt, squirt." - Oh yeah, you gotta
make the squirt. - Oh, dude,
it's all about making 'em squirt.
- Yeah, the machine's gotta squirt for you.
- I mean, every time I said,
I think I went a little too hard.
I was sitting down saying, "You're a stupid slot.
"You're a fucking whore.
"You're a dumb bitch." - You were saying,
"Squirt for me, monkey."
You were saying that a lot.
I was saying, "Squirt for me, you little monkey," a lot to these different slots.
And they did not, at some point, it's like, it wasn't fun and sexy anymore to them.
They found it actually disrespectful.
Yeah.
You know, that I was saying, "Squirt for me, you little putrid monkey.
I'm going to kill you, you little monkey.
You're my little monkey and you're going to make me squirt."
Yep, "Give me the monkey."
"Give me the monkey bread, you stupid."
"Show me monkeys."
Yeah, "Show me monkeys."
"Please, five monkeys in a row."
"Five monkeys in a row.
Monkey bonus.
- Back pot.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that, yeah I probably drank a little too much.
- Over there.
- Yeah, oh my god, we were at that club thing.
That lady came up to us, I thought we were getting
in trouble and then she just wanted to dance with Caleb
'cause he was like, you were just fucking--
- I was dressed like Pitbull and I got great hips, bro.
I don't know what the fuck to tell you.
- Oh man, you were going off.
- I can make my shit move.
- Yeah.
That club was so funny.
- I'm playing Rockabye Baby with my hips at the club.
- Dude, I had like, I had an out of body experience there.
I was like dubstep is awesome.
- Yeah, I had an out of body experience too.
My body teleported to the stage and started playing music.
- Yeah, oh yeah, they played Lose Yourself.
You lost yourself.
- I did, I unbuttoned my shirt all the way.
- Yeah.
- Lucky ladies and the crowd that night.
- That freaking club gave me an out of wallet experience.
- Oh yeah. - I mean, come on.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah.
- It was in the pool.
- Gave me an out of money experience.
(laughing)
- Damn, I wish we could've swam in there.
That's the thing, we gotta go swimming soon.
- I would love to go swimming, dude.
We need to do that thing. I don't own a bathing suit. I have to go buy one.
What are you wearing one right now?
Look at that. This is a bathing suit to you? You can put that...
Any shorts are a bathing suit.
You got a pedigo in your baggies.
If you're a man... That's a bathing suit. That's an all-terrain vehicle.
Any shorts are a bathing suit.
Yep. No. Yeah.
Absolutely. Yeah.
I just bought new swim trunks too.
I bought... They got a frog on them.
You bought a frog on them?
There's a frog on them.
Is it like a little kid's bathing suit?
No. Why does it have a frog on it? It's an adult bathing suit with a frog on it.
Really? Yeah. A rain forest frog?
No, it's a little green frog.
A green frog comes from the rain forest. Everybody knows that.
Well, you don't. It's a cartoon frog.
Why would they put that on a baby? Put a shark?
Put a fish. Put a whale or a fish.
It's got a frog on it.
Well, don't have that on there.
Why? I'm not going to put it. I would never put it.
A frog doesn't swim.
Yeah, I'm not going to put a handle on my frog.
Frog doesn't swim. It jumps from the lily pad to the lily pad.
It like specifically can't fall into the water or it resets the level.
It has to hit the lily pad.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
You don't even know what you're talking about.
You don't know.
It says that they're in Memphis right now.
Oh wait, we have a good one today.
I'm taking it. Your frog shorts are in Memphis?
Those look like shit.
What are you talking about? Those don't look like shit.
They got a little green frog on it.
You paid that much for a swimsuit?
Let me see it. You are stupid.
Oh my god.
You're worried about Atlantic City and you're spending 60 bucks on a swimsuit?
Yeah.
Oh my god, dude.
dollars for a swimsuit and I never will.
That's true.
It's got a frog on it.
Fuck off.
So the transition here, I've been really into the Dog Man recently.
There's a lot of people on a lot of different forums and on Facebook who are really fascinated
by the Dog Man, which is a cryptid from I believe Michigan, which is if you can't guess
it's a dog and a man combined.
A lot of people...
Is it half and half like a...
It's like a big dog that stands up like a guy.
It's like a werewolf basically.
Okay.
There's a lot of crossover between people who believe that Dog Man is real and
people who believe that werewolves are real and the government is covering them
up.
And so I was looking for some werewolf stuff and I found this website called
ILoveWerewolves.com which it wouldn't let me send these links to myself over
Twitter to look at them because it thought that it was a spam website which
is how you know this is going to be a really good list I think.
Well it's not a list.
I got a few pages here for a story.
This is a list but I have a few different pages that aren't lists and the comments on here
are really great from this werewolf community.
It's called I Love Werewolves.
If I believed in werewolves, I'm not sure that I would love them so much.
This is a website that is mainly frequented by people who are werewolves.
And this website was, you can see in the logo, this website was founded by Werewolf967 and
Buddy.
buddy's I'm guessing buddy's a either an alter ego or a dog I think it's got to be
a sidekick yeah and before we get into this I just noticed that there's a
there's a head on the sidebar on for an article on this website called Johnny
Depp says the chupacabra attacked him I would like to get some more details yeah
yeah let's open that up really quick let's see here let this load a chupacabra
attacked Johnny Depp I believe it Johnny Depp was expected at a Japanese
press conference.
He put copper's name Amber Heard.
Earlier in the week.
However to the disappointment of everyone he missed it.
He had been recovering from being sick.
However that's not why he told report.
Oh he lied.
What a fucking piece of shit.
So this is just yeah Johnny Depp's a piece of shit liar.
There's so many good articles on this website I can't stop clicking them.
This is an article just called Abominable Snowman and it's just about the Abominable
Snowman.
Look at this.
I don't fuck with the Abominable Snowman.
You would fuck it.
I don't fuck with much Abominable.
Anyway, our first article we're looking at on ilovewerewolves.com is "10 Insults to Never
Call a Werewolf".
Okay.
I mean, like, what situation would I be in where I...
Number two, werewolf.
Yeah, I mean, like, I don't know what situation I'd be in where I would be, like, trying to
talk to a werewolf in the first place, really.
Well, here we go.
What if it's like you don't know that it's a werewolf?
Well, it's like fine, like I got time before the full moon usually.
Yeah, it's like when you make a Polish joke in front of a Polish guy and then he tells
you "Hey, you know I'm actually Polish."
Yeah and then you say "Yeah, I do know you're a werewolf too."
It's hard to not know you're Polish when you look like that.
Yeah.
So the very last thing you should ever want to do is insult a werewolf.
Werewolves are stronger, faster, and smarter than any human.
In a battle, a werewolf would win every time over a human.
So the smartest thing any human can do?
Stay away from the insults.
Now chances are the werewolf will simply ignore you.
an insult from a mere human is not worth the werewolf's energy or time. Every now and then,
however, you'll catch a werewolf in a mood where he or she just isn't in the mood to put
up with you. With that in mind, you'd be well advised to stay away from the following monikers,
which are considered insults to every werewolf." So it just has all ten in a row right here.
I'll read them out here.
Puppy is the first one.
Yeah, that's like calling someone baby. That's fucked.
Yeah, you can't do that.
Unless it's your beautiful wife.
breath. That one I think is okay. If somebody said guy breath to me, I'd be like, okay.
Yeah. What else is my breath going to smell like?
Yeah. Hairball.
That one, nasty.
That's just, that's not right.
That pops up when you clean, when a cat cleans itself.
Fur face. That one.
That's kind of fucked up.
That is.
Yeah.
Fleabag.
Oh no.
Mongrel.
That one's charged.
That'd be mad. I'd be mad if someone called me that.
yeah i'm i'm not any amount don't know
it's that one also feels wrong
scotty which i think i think it's supposed to be scooby and as a type of
scotty been is pro-fine dude i would i i i i i think probably calling a werewolf
scooby-doo
i think you would get killed and see if they said yeah i think that's a bit of
i mean what if someone can do you know like
what's up alice
you'd be like
yes most famous guy
that's what's going to do is you must be a star
no scooby is not aware of the scooby-doo is like the elvis of dogs did
maybe is the elvis but on the east that's the thing to do that's not a
dollar-a-mile is a little bit of an excuse if you to work talking to a dog
and you call them scooby-doo
what's that were also fucking dog
did you'd you better be careful
you better not say that we're on a dog
nancy you'd you can't do scooby-doo is the most famous dog uh... what about
total
yeah total I don't know who totally rinsing in oh from the total is a one
last I see
Scooby-Doo is way more famous than Lassie uh
Clifford Clifford the big red dog this is alright purely on our Scooby-Doo you
know he's not only counting Scooby-Doo cartoons here right Johnny Carson
because he's just like like decades and decades of hours and hours of him being
on TV. Lassie, what, four seasons of Lassie? Probably a couple movies. A couple movies.
Beethoven. Same thing, Beethoven, a couple movies. You know. Air Bud. Air Bud. Those are
different dogs too, they kept fucking dying. Scooby Doo's a different dog every time too.
That's not true. Literally every episode it's a different dog. No, that's not true. It's
true. You guys are just wrong about it. Even Scrappy Doo's more famous than Scooby Doo
nowadays. Okay, you guys are just trying to make me mad. Nowadays. You guys know I'm a
- Did you get into like Scooby-Doo's extended family?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you got into 'em.
Bunch of dogs.
- What?
- Yeah, you got into those dogs.
- Yeah, you found your way into them.
- The family of dogs, you got into them.
- You were deep in them.
- What?
- You got into their bones.
- Like the bones they eat?
- No, you were one of the bones and they ate you.
- What?
- You got into them.
- Oh, fuck.
- Okay, the last two insults here are kibbles and fluffy.
- Kibbles, that's food.
- That's dog names.
- Kibbles is like calling you.
if you're if you're a werewolf kibbles is what you call your girlfriend I think
there's way worse things you call a werewolf yeah yeah absolutely
what's up gay werewolf yeah yeah what's up bitch look at this first comment here
don't forget dog and doggy gir I'm a wolf not a dog it's offensive to call a
werewolf a dog you're a dog I think it's offensive to call anyone a dog yeah I
don't think it just applies to werewolves I guess these also apply to
of women yeah yeah yeah you walking up to a woman at the club you're using PUA
tactics you say hey kibbles yeah hey scobby yeah that'd be stupid
hey wolf breath yeah wolf breath it was up hair face hey wolf breath want me to
buy you a drink here's a comment from Sarah I would work actually yeah here's
a comment from Sarah my friends at slash boyfriend hates when I say good puppy or
good doggy I know my boyfriend hates most of those words my boyfriend has
sharp teeth green eyes that sometimes turn to blue or gold type of color he
He has hair all over his body.
He doesn't like sleeping at night and he stays up.
His eyebrows join together and he has hair all over his hands.
He gets mad really easy and he only likes meat.
He is also really fast and can run for a long time and he can hear really good and can see
good as well.
How many times have I have tried to walk up to him without him knowing and failed?
But that doesn't mean he is a werewolf.
My boyfriend's brother thinks he is a werewolf and a vampire and my boyfriend's dad is like
that as well.
My boyfriend and his dad has everything that all of you talked about, but they don't go
around saying they're werewolves because werewolves are not real.
only in books and movies and the same goes with vampires but I don't know about
witches because my Nana believes in witches lol just saying it's good good
thing she said it was she was just saying otherwise I would have she
clarified that her boyfriend is not a werewolf at the end yeah yeah I could I
was everything was leading up to it yeah my boy wears wears purple robes has a
tall pointy hat uses a wand has a big white beard but he is not a Merlin he is
nothing like a Merlin yeah I disagree that a werewolf would win every battle as
battles don't always depend on strength and size sometimes it is technique and
intelligence that determines a fight I mean take Derek Hale for instance for
Watchers of Teen Wolf that said I love your articles and they really get me
into the mood for writing my werewolf novels this article I think rings true
werewolves are double beings they're human and wolf would you want to be
reminded of your lineage and hate speak I think we call it being racist smiley
face wouldn't it be specious true species I just have I would kill a werewolf yeah
yeah I mean yeah you're always carrying that silver bullet with you just a case
or I would drive it in with my own hand I don't even have a gun do you guys have
any tips for a recently turned werewolf aside for telling me dating a werewolf
was a bad idea my boyfriend accidentally bit me a couple weeks ago and I've been
trying to find someone who can give me some tips on being a werewolf I got a
I got a tip for you.
- Yeah?
- Fucking don't.
(laughing)
- That's my tip.
- That's right.
- No, don't track mud in the house.
- Yeah, that's disrespectful.
- You're a werewolf, yeah.
- That's not right.
- Mm-hmm.
- You go outside, you play in the mud as a werewolf,
you come back in as a human.
- How you gonna let your boyfriend bite you?
- True.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
boyfriend no more.
Absolutely.
I'm not dating no bitch I gotta wear chain mail around dude.
I'm not doing that.
You wouldn't wanna wear chain mail?
I would take any excuse I could get to wear chain mail.
Yeah I know.
But what if they smell out all my shit?
What do you mean?
All the shit that I have, what do they smell at?
All my shit that I have.
You think they're gonna sniff out your shit?
They might smell you.
I got different kind of shit in my house that I don't want no bitch smelling.
What do you mean?
I've got different kind of shit in my house.
I don't want no bitch walking around smelling and shit.
Dude, what if, I would hate dating a werewolf because what if they got the zoomies and I
was trying to go to sleep and there's running back and forth everywhere.
Running on top of the bed.
Yeah.
Running on top of the headboard.
Plus my backup plan has always been mailman.
It's a really good pension.
Like, that ain't going to work.
I mean, a mailman wearing chain mail.
True.
That'd be pretty sick.
would be really cool actually yeah but you're sending you to the chain mailman
yeah plus a like it's a mailman but he only wears chain mail and then he
delivers you like letters from no return address that say yeah send this letter
to the other clown statue will come to life and slaughter you. No disrespect to
extremely hairy women that are covered in hair all over their body head to toe
but I don't want to date that. That's your problem. Hair all over their
face yeah hair all over their entire body
YP that's it that's not those teeth are too big and you know they got teeth in
there it's true and you know they bite mm-hmm they probably didn't give him no
sharp teeth for nothing true the most shame for soup it's for human flesh you
think you get more how many teeth does it a wolf have all right I don't want to
fuck an animal yeah but if you had to fuck an animal or not an animal if you
- If you had to fuck a human-animal hybrid,
what animal would you most want to be a half?
- Probably a human and a human.
- No, no, what animal?
- That's right, I know the loophole.
- Probably like a Irish-Italian.
(laughing)
- I think like a--
- Yeah, maybe like a Russian-Hungarian.
- I think like a shark.
- A shark?
- Or, yeah.
I don't know, dude.
- Something with smooth skin.
- Yeah.
do not have smooth skin. A whale? They have very rough skin. Like a dolphin? Dolphin!
Oh that's... I just felt something. A dolphin woman? Well dolphins are like the horniest animals.
Oh my god dude my bitch half dolphin? Yeah but that's the... you gotta keep her in the tub.
My bitch a dolphin she be fucking like a bunny.
Okay. Okay. But she got a bald butt if she's a dolphin.
It's like the opposite of a wolf girl.
Ba ba.
She got a bald butt.
Put grape jelly on it.
Okay.
I'll be up in there like David Baby Boy.
All right.
Okay.
Talking about like dogs and pets and stuff.
This is a pivot from this website.
Okay.
Hold on.
Probably like a...
Probably like half deer.
deer yeah like with antlers it's got they have like it's gonna be like tufts of
hair dude that's horrible and who do you talking about yeah who what's half a
hoof half a foot that's just nasty hands to you know hold on hold on is it worse
hand you didn't even you didn't even explain so it's like a hybrid but is it like a
mermaid situation or is it like 99% animal 1% human dolphin that wait
1% dolphin 1% human 1% human like 1% of every animal cuz that's got to average
up to something like really nice oh I'd be so hot just like all the worst parts
like a perfect pyramid yeah just I gotta say probably like yeah yeah a block of
flesh that just inches towards you it's gotta be for me it's gotta be a naked
mole rat sea urchin. What's the animals that are famous for having holes on them?
Yeah, a whale. A sponge. A sea sponge. Half sea sponge, half whale, because I need
something to grip on to. Plus warthog. Plus warthog. Yeah. Plus an anteater.
Yeah. You know. She'd get all up in that thing. Anteater goes
crazy eat the ants out your butt yeah yeah oh baby she walks home she gets home
baby so I but spilled a bunch of ants into my ass I said on a shit I was
having a you know you know what I do every day I go out to the park I have a
picnic by myself yeah somehow today my shorts fell off and I sat directly I sat
directly on top of an ant hill the biggest and it said they actually said
that the park ranger came up to me and said it was the biggest ant hill in
Central Park history. He says that it's like someone almost moved it there from a
different location. It's like it was being collected for months just ants just
being you know people you'd build in sand on top of it there's so many ants in
there I said I said directly on top of it I took that whole thing like it was a
like a tower. Anyway is your snout feeling okay? How's your snout? Yeah I just
realized I do have one lined up we're talking about hybrids this is an article
about a very scary hybrid. Oh my God. This is a hybrid called the
vampire demon. The vampire demon sometimes referred to as vamp
demon is a half vampire half demon hybrid. This type of
creature is generally considered extremely evil and dangerous.
Pure demons are of non human sometimes referred to as coke.
This is straight up. This is this is a human and animal
hybrid. Listen to this. Your demons are of non human origin
and some say are actually angels that have fallen out of grace
and now serve the devil vampires. On the other hand,
were once human creatures. When you meet a vamp demon, you are therefore meeting something
that is not close to being human and has little empathy for humans or living creatures, the
influence of the demon side, as well as little empathy for vampires themselves. This is what
makes them so dangerous. In addition, the vampire demons has powers that go beyond those
of the vampire. Combine that with sunlight not being much of an issue for them and their
ability to live longer without blood and you have a nearly unstoppable creature. They are
extremely rare. Human portrayals of this creature are that of an extremely evil being, but there
is some thought that they can mask themselves as humans pretty easily and
don't necessarily all look like the image picture below and the image doesn't work
oh fuck can you search a vamp demon to see if anything comes up yeah the
expression bad out of hell is a good reference to the vamp demon so it's like
a meatloaf basically meatloaf does look like a oh my god whoa oh my god shit
damn they're scary as hell this is really scary I would not want to run
into these. Isn't like a like a vampire oh what's Buddy say here? That's that's
the author. Yeah here we go. Here's the first comment. Whoa that is
UGLY. Here's a comment here from Mineski Canna Plus and they say can you
explain what on it is? Oh they're real and you don't want to cross paths with
them either. In my family's history book I ran across one of my great great my
great Gandad's journals. He wrote that some do look like part human and bat,
but some do have human bodies and he drew a pic of it. It was a young girl with
fangs, long nails and her hair. Wow, it was amazing to look at. But he said
that they don't kill just for food, but they also just kill to see blood on them
and the areas around them. And he said that they are even more dangerous than
others that don't look human because they get irritated, SLE, love the sight
of blood and laughed at pain, but they don't mind killing few living creatures
either. Oh, and the one thing that he put in cap and underlined, they love
pooblice places but they also go crazy if they're around humans too long.
Whoa.
I mean, a vampire is scary enough, but a vampire that gone crazy.
Yeah.
Gone crazy at the pooblice?
That's horrifying.
Damn.
I am a vampiric demon and it's taken a- What?
Werewolf name generator.
I already opened that.
Fuck you.
What?
I have that already up in a tab.
Just trust his plan.
What the fuck are you doing, dude?
I was in the middle of reading a comment.
Spoiling everything.
I leave the page for no reason. I thought that I have that tab open. I didn't know you had it open
Eat this you spoiled the fucking finisher. You need to punish yourself. We can edit the finale. No
Everybody's gonna know what you do
crap, I
Am a vampiric demon and it's taken a long time for my to see a reference to me
And yes, we are very rare and I'm thankful that Lycons have kept a record of my existence and that is more than I had expected
Oh that image is aquarium a dead harpy that is puppeteered much like a necromancer's golem
(laughing)
Yeah, I mean, this is, there's,
anytime you combine two things that are already scary,
it's gonna be twice as scary, right?
- Yeah, mom and dad. - Absolutely.
(laughing)
- Mr. Mom. - Yeah.
- Oh my. - That's the scariest thing
you can get. - Jesus Christ.
Yeah, Mr. Mom is scary.
Ghost and-- - Don't even,
don't even get me started on Mrs. Dad.
- Ghost and chores? - Mm-hmm.
- That's it. - Ugh.
- It's Casper. - Yeah.
Ghost dad?
Ghost dad.
Oh my God.
That's the most Cosby thing.
Scariest thing it could be.
If you combine a ghost and dad,
you get a creature twice as evil.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna move here to,
this one has a shit ton of comments.
And this is, these are the comments
where everyone is figuring out that they're werewolves here.
Oh my God.
I'm scared that I might realize something about myself.
Am I a werewolf?
This is a, you can, this is a werewolf quiz.
It says it's a quiz, but, oh wait, no.
Is it like a, is it like Scantron?
'Cause I don't, I didn't have a pencil.
- Let's see, is this an actual quiz here?
- No.
- Well, the quiz takes you to the test.
- Okay, wait, let's try the test.
- Click the test, yeah.
- It doesn't work, doesn't do anything.
All right, fine, we'll just read it.
Many of you ask yourselves, are werewolves real?
And if they are, how do I know if I'm a werewolf?
Is there an easy way to tell?
Unfortunately, there are no easy answer to these questions
because no one has come forward
and submitted themselves to scientific investigation.
If I was a werewolf, I'd do that immediately.
Anyway, but on to the better question.
How do you know if you're a werewolf?
Well, there is no real way to know.
Some of our readers say that when you transform,
you remember that you became a werewolf.
Some say this is the best way to tell.
The truth is though,
while some may remember the transformation,
for many werewolves,
who once they have become human again,
they do not remember being a werewolf at all.
Some say that an aversion to silver
indicates you may be a werewolf.
The truth though is that silver's not really bother
a werewolf in human form.
Some say that the only real way to tell if you're a werewolf
is to have someone watch you during a full moon
see if you transform. The problem here is that some older werewolves can transform
when they want to. The other problem here is that if you do transform and someone
is watching you, you may never know the answer to the question "Am I a werewolf?"
because your friend will not survive. Werewolves are not friendly after all.
So basically there's no way to tell if you're a werewolf or not. That's what
they're saying. That's fucking terrifying. Next full moon. When is it? Let's see. Oh,
July 23rd was a full moon. That was my birthday. September 20th. Do you remember your
birthday? Wait. Actually. Oh my god. Wait a minute. You were out and then nothing.
I could have blacked out drinking though. It could have been...
What is that? Listen, I know you. I know you wouldn't drink that much.
That's true. But becoming a werewolf. I don't know. I mean what else happened that...
I mean I'm drawing a blank. What does it say there? It says you
need to it's it says you need to kiss your your friend to find out which one
it says whichever whichever one is closest to you yeah it says you need to
kiss him and if he likes it then you're okay and you're not a werewolf all right
it's just gonna it didn't work didn't work on my end I don't know about you
I'm not gonna tell you if I liked it or not. Really? Yeah. It says that you need to
do it 5,000 more times. Okay. Well now I'm nervous because I don't remember one,
the last full moon. Right. Or the full moon in Jewel. Also there was a full moon
August 22nd and were we hanging out that night? What happened? I don't remember. I
don't remember that either. Wait, I don't remember. There was a night a couple
couple weeks ago where I was sitting under a palm tree and I was looking up at the
moon and then it a coconut fell on my head and then I don't remember the rest
of that night. Oh my god. Let's read some experiences here that people have had.
I think some of these might line up with what you guys have have experienced in
the past few weeks. Okay. The palms of my hand grow hair the size of toothpicks and
And sometimes when I feel threatened, which is rare like my steak.
Wait, hold on.
On instinct, I attack.
Look at the palms of-- there's-- oh my god.
So much hair on--
I've ripped flesh of bone and brought the strongest to their feet.
I've done that.
Wait, that sounds like something I would do.
I've tasted blood and want more.
No one has stoped me and no one will.
This sounds a lot like us.
Yeah.
I've never been stoped.
I am the alpha and deserve respect and fear.
Oh, that's me for sure.
Yeah, that's you to a T or someone else dies and it won't be me. This is Luna Wolf
Remember the name because someday if you're just so unlucky, you'll find we'll one day find me boiling and hungry
So sleep well and don't let the monster bite
Why would you give I would say so sleep well and let please let the monster bite. I wanted by you
I want to be I want to be the biter so bad and and sleep well and don't look under your bed right now
There's nothing under there don't sleep well and keep your window wide open
The way to stop a werewolf is keep your window wide open and keep a pie on the windowsill
That's a good idea. Yeah, maybe a blood pie. Yeah
Everything is bad. I'm nine
I'm a werewolf my friend looks like a werewolf like wired
But I still will not turn into a werewolf till I'm 14 or 17
I still got life, but it's hard to control my anger and hunger. I want blood. I still control my sister
I'm not sleepy at night in a full moon. I'm out of control
Then I get tired when it's back to half moon and I'm sleepy
I was scared of dogs then but no more my eyes get a little red when my tummy hurt it just the middle bit
I'm not cold when I'm not Polly I for the spells are not real
I said it but I knew it was not real but then I'm a werewolf
Whoa, that is a scary kid. Yeah, that's a
Haunted child. That's also it's also making me think maybe
Yeah, maybe I am a werewolf. I think you might be a werewolf. I'm thinking I mean
Let's think of the symptoms.
Yeah.
My sister.
Your sister.
My sister is hungry.
Yeah.
Yep.
I'm covered in hair right now.
But I mean...
Every night you don't remember.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You have...
I have a full moon on my birthday.
Right.
Scary.
That's terrifying.
That's very scary.
It was the buck moon.
No.
Uh-huh.
Not the buck moon.
Yeah, and the next one is the harvest moon.
- No. - The harvest, that's scary.
- But what if you harvest blood?
- That's true, what if I do harvest blood?
I don't know, I have to keep this,
hold on, what was the other moon?
- Wait, here we go, we got a symptoms list.
- Sturgeon. - The last one.
- We got a symptoms list from William right here.
- Oh, perfect, okay. - Okay, all right, good.
- It's actually a symptoms list.
- Oh, I don't know if I have any symptoms.
- I used to be weak, nerdy, not that good with girls,
and not cool.
Now here's where the bullet points start.
I became stronger, way stronger than I ever was before.
I've tried lifting weights and I'm way stronger.
Plus I have lifting weights gym class,
but my friends don't suspect nothing.
- Wait, I recently became stronger, I decided.
- All of my senses became better.
I can smell things from far away and I can hear things too.
My fangs are sharper.
Even when I talk, you can see my fangs.
- Wait, hold on.
(sniffing)
I think there might be a car outside.
You guys smell that?
- I think...
(sniffing)
(snorting)
- I think there might be car, maybe a lot of cars.
- I think there's a mailman delivering mail.
Oh my god, I think a wave just crashed on the beach.
I think a dog just barked and I smelled the breath.
Guys, I don't want to alarm you, but there's a crack in the surface of the moon.
No, oh my god.
Your neighbor's making pico de gallo.
With chips.
They're making, they bought the chips though.
On a plate.
Yeah, the plate is glass.
And a nacho cheese sauce.
And they're not wearing shoes.
they're inviting us over to help them eat it all. My nails grow faster and they are
stronger. My reflexes are a whole lot better than before. I accidentally used my
reflexes during class. People just stared at me. Oh man, I used my reflexes during
class. I used my reflexes. I blew my cover. I've grown muscley. I'm like 100% more
confident than before. I am NOT shy anymore. I am good with girls. I can talk
to them way smoother. Girls are attracted to me. Even my friends have told me the
way girls look at me. I get angry very quickly, short temper. I didn't used to be like this,
but I can handle my anger and I calm myself down. I am faster when I run, tried running
while I walk my dog, my dog couldn't even keep up with me. I like the dark, I didn't
used to be like this. For some reason my room is more colder than the others. I've heard
that this only happens when there is something evil or otherworldly in the room, meaning
me. Now when I dream, I can manipulate them. I don't sleep a lot at night, I mostly sleep
during the day. Every time during the full moon I feel different and I just can't stop
staring at it like today. When I am angry, I am way stronger, more than before.
Yeah, that sounds like me. It does sound, it sounds like me too. Yeah. I've become
way stronger than I was before. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and I'm much smoother and more
confident too. Yeah, when I'm talking. Oh yeah, I mean, I'm not smooth. I don't think I'm smooth at all, but I
think maybe, uh, well, smoother than before. Come on, you're smooth. No, I'm not, you know.
Here, give me a kiss.
I'm way hairier, I mean.
Oh.
I was smooth, now I'm too hairy because of all this lycanthropy.
That's so true.
I hate lycanthropy.
Oh my god, it's such a curse.
What's uh, what else do we got here?
Here's a comment, here's two comments in a row from Suzette.
Okay, Suzette.
I'm a werewolf, what about you guys?
Also once I ate a whole pig.
Yeah, I was in Hawaii, I ate a whole pig.
Yeah, I was at the Dixie Stampede. I ate an entire pig. I'm pretty much a werewolf.
Okay, I am a werewolf and I'm 11, but if you have a kill list, werewolf or not,
you're messed up, even if you're a werewolf. And actually, it's only movie
werewolves that are extremely psychopathic. I'm a werewolf and I'm a
peaceful person. I would say I'm less scared of werewolves than I was going
into this website because so many of them seem to be 9 or 11. Yeah, I think
maybe this is like PBS Kids for werewolves. Maybe we got to look up,
Can you look up this website for me?
Werewolf.xxx.
- Werewolf.xxx?
- Uh-huh.
- Nothing.
- Werewolf.sexy.
- Okay. - Nothing.
- Look up sexywerewolf.com.
- Dot com?
- Yeah.
- How about this?
- No, I wanna see, go on a--
Oh my god.
Whoa.
Female werewolf art.
That's interesting.
Oh my god.
Yeah, can we pause recording for a minute?
Sure.
Okay.
Okay, we're back.
We're back.
We're looking at sexy werewolves.
I feel a lot more relaxed right now actually for no reason in particular.
I feel like I got a huge release of something.
Yeah, I also, I feel drier.
I feel like my skin and all the moisture from my body is kind of like gone.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like there's one part of my body that there's like a weird film on that I can't get
off if I use hot water. Yeah, and it's, uh, it's, it smells like chlorine in here now.
Yeah, it's really weird. Is there, did you get a pool installed? Yeah. Yeah, I think I
might have got a pool installed by accident without realizing it. Yeah, that's why we
had to take a break to let the pool guy in. Yeah. Yeah. And that's it. That's it. Let's
see, let me see if there's any more werewolf comments on here. I think that we really might
be werewolves altogether. Yeah. I'm starting to believe it. I know I'm a werewolf. I am
I am always warm. I found out when I was, I was 56 degrees Celsius,
which is possible for a human.
And with my canines being huge and my balance is really good.
I've managed to read minds, predict the future and interact with my spirit,
which is a Wilf. I have always admired wolves. And every time I'm near a dog,
I have a connection woman. I'd like to fuck my spirit.
My friend said her dig is shy and won't go to anyone.
As soon as I stepped in the room, it came to me. I'd like to be an alpha,
but I know I don't have the responsibility to, so I'm a lone wolf for now.
Hope you guys find out if you're a wolf or not, but let me tell you,
There are lots of us, but it's hard to tell who are these days.
If you need more information, visit Experience Project.
They will find you real werewolves.
And to my knowledge, werewolves are friendly.
It's just they're scared of being a lab rat.
So that's why they come across as aggressive.
That's all I have to say.
Love you all.
- Sorry for the spelling errors.
My spell checker is awful.
- Hi, I think I am a werewolf
because if I get really mad, I growled
and have growled at my sister a lot.
I mean, this is not a one-time thing
and I have a lot of hair on my arms and legs and I love meat.
I don't know about Ro-mean though.
I like to stay up late and I love the movement
I'm really work and hot all the time.
- Who's real mean?
- Yo, I think Patrick might have left this comment
during our break, "OMG me and my BFFs tried it
and had all the side effects."
- Did you just leave that?
- I did just leave that comment.
- Under the name Alexa?
- Well I was saying, "Hey Alexa, can you comment on
where was that comment?"
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- It's like when you try to say send to Siri
and then it puts send it at the end of your message.
- I don't use Siri, man.
I've done that a few times.
I still got my hands.
Why would I need Siri?
I'm like making dinner or something or making a sandwich.
Dinner or a sandwich.
Sandwich for lunch.
So either dinner or a sandwich for lunch.
And you gotta use Siri.
Yeah.
Because you got these ingredients in your hands.
I mean, I don't want to put my ingredients down.
Just put your ingredients down.
Just put the ingredients down.
No, you gotta take care of your...
You're so addicted to me, you won't let it leave your claws.
You gotta take care of your ingredients, dude.
You are a werewolf, because you're greedy.
Werewolves.
What's the last comment I'm going to read?
That's a stereotype of werewolves.
Now it is.
Why?
Because of you?
No.
Greedy ass werewolf.
You're going to make a generalization based on that.
Wait, it says werewolves are terrible at gambling too.
What does it say?
It just said that, yeah.
No, it says don't trust sites.
None of us went on any sites you.
No.
And that's Zelda.
Zelda Claus said that.
Here's a comment from a real werewolf.
"Hey, I'm a wolf and I love pasta more than chicken, but not deer. You cannot beat the
sweet taste of deer, raw or cooked."
Raw deer?
You eat raw deer?
I mean, if you're a werewolf, you gotta eat some raw deer.
I guess you're right. You know what? I bet the best feeling ever is when you, like, when
you're a werewolf, you eat raw meat and you get that blood mustache.
Yeah, oh my God. I hate that shit.
That's when you know you're satisfied.
Yeah, you just leave it in there all day.
Right?
Yeah.
All right, now the part, the one that no one will expect. No one's gonna see this coming.
Big finale.
anybody? Werewolf name generator. You put in your first and last name and it's
gonna give you a werewolf name. Now that we know we're werewolves... Hold on. What?
Scroll down a little bit. Scroll down what? It's a video of the name generator.
Well click the purple text there because there's another one that you can do.
You are not a vampire. Okay we'll do both. This is where it
dude, this is what happens when you get all those symptoms. There's two paths you
can go down. Either the werewolf or vampire and it depends on which name is
better. Okay, so let's see Patrick's werewolf name. Mm-hmm. Come on, get his
name. Did it not work? It went away. I don't think it worked. Wait, try it again.
Get my name. Wait, what? Try a different browser it says. I don't have a different
browser do I? Yeah you got Microsoft Edge. Yes sir. Alright come on this better fucking
work. Oh man, I mean Microsoft Edge. I'm a werewolf name generator. Great site here. Patrick
Doran, Blood Lusterson. Blood Lusterson. I'm gonna wait to see what this one says. Oh wait
that's a vampire one. Come on. It's not working? It's not working. This is because you'd click
it. No. You fucker. Fine, I'll do a werewolf one. Ready? Look at me. What's your name?
You know my name. Dogg Watterson. Dogg Watterson? Cam, what's your name? Cameron. Fetter. Bone
Eterson. Alright, give me another name. I got this. Alright, uh, fuckin' Caleb Pitts.
teeth or sin Rob Roy sheeter hair dogerson okay Barack Obama four legs and
four legs Obama Obama yeah Michael what about Michelle Obama Michelle Obama for
four legs wait no hold on hold on I'm looking up okay werewolf name generator
yeah here I got it right here I got a werewolf name generator I'll get a
different one too. Okay. We're gonna have a lot of options here. This one...
Plus you have me, I'm like the other option. The first one I clicked gave me 10 random
names. Plus I'm basically a generator myself. So here's
10 random names. These are the 10 werewolf names
it gave me right off the bat. Alright, read them out. Okay.
Bosh, Clovis,
Roaldald, Grout. Okay, here.
to do this quiz together. This is a what's your werewolf name quiz. Ten questions. For
the most part are you more or less hairy than most? I'm way hairier than a lot of people.
Altogether we're average though. No, no way. Altogether? I mean on average. Fine. I'll be
on more hairy. I have enough hair to like keep Caleb warm. I have some hair on my body
but my head is not. What type of jewelry are you most likely to wear? I could have an afro?
What type of jewelry are you most likely to wear?
Costume right? Yeah, yeah gotta be costume
Okay, let's see here next question in a dark alley you'd be most afraid to bump into werewolf a vampire. My ex dude
Yeah, my ex my ex next question
When the moon isn't full you're someone who is very intelligent. Mm-hmm. Yeah, definitely smarty pants
Yeah, what do you do during a lunar eclipse is a dance freak out freak out freak out on the dance definitely freak out
How would you describe your friends in one word matured weird what weird you two are my friends
Oh, what the hell do you tend to feel a lot of empathy towards others? No, not no, not really
Definitely. Let's see
When bad things happen to you, do you see them as a curse? Yeah. Yeah often feel cursed next question
Come on. Romantically speaking, are you someone who enjoys dating?
I absolutely love it.
Next question. All right, this is the last question. Make it count.
When things don't go your way, who or what do you blame?
Astrology.
The moon.
My parents.
Astrology is the moon.
No, it's the moon.
The moon.
Result. All right.
Werewolf name. This is all of our werewolf names together.
Belvina.
See this? Why not?
Okay.
You're not even like anything about like water bowls or bones here.
this is stupid. All right, subscribe to the Patreon. Please. Yeah, Belvina also out.
(gagging)