You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- [Computer] Father God's to the west.
- Crap monster.
(screaming)
- Woo!
- Oh, God.
- Make a noise.
- Pow!
- Pow, I just shit my pants.
- Oh.
- Oh, that's nasty.
- Oh, hell no.
- That's what Mark Maron says, come on.
- Who?
I don't know who that is.
I'm 15.
That's father god to you, honey.
Oh my god.
Respect on his name.
I literally have never heard of that guy.
I know Howard Stern and Man Cow.
And those are the only people I've ever known to pick up a microphone.
Howard Stern, hottest man alive.
Yeah, I said it.
Still.
Yeah, I liked that him and like Gene Simmons just kind of melding into one.
Kind of like...
One big pro-Israel...
Candle.
Yeah.
I think they look good, man.
I hope that that's how I look when I get older.
Somehow I grow like insane hair.
Gene Simmons hair looks like that wind guard on your mic.
Yeah it does, so like frayed.
It looks exactly like that.
And you'd be lucky to have hair like that at an age like that.
Are you serious?
If I could get those plugs.
At 110, you'd have that kind of hair?
It's impressive man.
I wish.
We're here with Sarah Squirm, the richest person alive.
Mostly the richest person alive.
You see these crocs?
Beautiful hotel.
Oh my gosh.
You see these crocs?
in them. Yeah. Where'd you get those? The store, ever heard of it? I thought about getting Crocs the other day, but I
wasn't gonna get, I walked by the Crocs store and I was like, I can't. What store? You want them at all? Shut up! You're wearing Crocs, where'd you get them? The store. You're a fucker.
- Come on, were you born yesterday?
- Yeah, I told you that already, I'm 15.
- Oh God, I actually do hate that you guys
are younger than me, I don't like hanging out with anyone.
- I thought that we were the same age.
- Is that true?
- Yeah, yeah.
- So you don't think I look--
- I thought we were around the same age.
- Really?
Do I look 28?
- Oh, I didn't know you were 28.
- Oh, come on!
- Oh my God!
- What?
- Am I in trouble?
- I actually don't like hanging out with 23 year olds.
- I feel like we're so allowed to be in your hotel room
right now.
- Yeah.
- I got some boys in my hotel room.
It's funny because Pat loves hanging out with 18 year olds.
That's not true.
Yeah you do.
I hang out with people way older than me.
17 year olds.
So yeah, my bad.
No.
Why do you guys do this to me?
I actually don't know your guys' real names to be honest.
You guys all have weird names online.
Mine is Patrick.
No it's not.
Yeah it is.
Mine's Cameron.
No it's not.
My name is just my full legal name on there.
Caleb Pitsch.
I think all of us just have our names.
I feel like you don't.
No we do.
- Don't you have weird little images as your pictures?
- Well I have a phrasal impersonator in mine.
- Of course we have weird little images.
- Do you have a weird little image as your photo?
- Yeah, you better believe that.
- So yeah.
- But that is me, my photo is me.
- Mine is too, unfortunately.
- Yeah.
- I know somebody who said that they blocked you
'cause they didn't like looking at it.
- It's a scary photo.
Yeah, it's a photo of me when I worked at the UCB.
- You worked at UCB?
- I was an intern there.
Yo! For free?
For free. It was for college credit though.
I know.
I talked about this a lot.
What do you mean? An improv university college credit?
Pretty much.
Yeah.
That was a pretty fucked up life I've lived.
Do you guys like, you wanted to be a comedian
really badly, so you said
I'm gonna work at YouTube for a break?
No, you fucking, no! Fucker, no!
I went there and I fucking ate beef jerky
all day and like burped in
Matt Besser's face I have a photo of his credit card that my friend used to
fucking buy a ps2 on eBay I don't know I think we should scrap that cuz no one to
it's out so give it no it's no I don't care my friend fucking I took a photo of
his credit card cuz I thought it was funny cuz I was ordering him salad and I
said my friend he bought a ps2 on eBay yeah he like yeah it was like $70 he
didn't fucking notice yeah he's not listening I know this and we can do
another 420 lift sponsored show at UCB. No, did you guys all do UCB? No. Yes and to that.
You look like an idiot right now. I'm not an idiot, I'm smart. You were the only one. I
interned at I think maybe a worse place, was it Funny or Die. Oh my god. I dropped out
of college, I'm the only cool one here. So, fuck both of y'all. You meet Will Ferrell there?
No. Pretty much every day he would meet Will Ferrell.
Dude, I wish I met Will Ferrell and I could say, "You are so funny, sir."
You know what? He is!
He is so funny. He is!
I re-watched Talladega Nights the other night. So good.
Yeah. Still a very good movie.
I also re-watched that. I don't really like that movie that much.
What? Boris, they talk so stupid.
They talk so freaky and weird.
Yeah, they're like...
I don't get it. I don't understand what they're saying.
Why do you guys call this pod about list?
We'll get to it. You're the worst guest we've ever had. I wasn't mad at you before this, now I'm fucking furious.
I did, for the listeners at home, I did ask 75,000 times if everyone was mad at me before we started recording.
Because I did feel deeply. That, I think, is a symptom of being hungover.
You're like, "Everyone's mad at me and everyone's thinking about me right now."
Yeah.
"Yep, I'm hungover. Yep."
Be honest, how fucked up did you get last night?
"So what? I drink beer. So what?"
It's not the song. It's not the song at all.
I went to the same karaoke bar two nights in a row.
Yeah. Which one?
Planet Rose Karaoke for the listeners at home. It's the best.
Oh, it's called Encore.
They were clapping and saying Encore, Encore for 24 hours until I came back.
Did you kill it?
First night, Rob Zombie Dragula.
Wow. Nice.
Immediately convinced myself I gave vocal notes from screaming
everyone said, "Sarah, you can only get that if you're Adele." Okay? And then I, then
afterwards I sang "Voices Carry" by Till Tuesday. Wow. And then, what did I sing
last night? "Cool" by Gwen Stefani. What did I sing last night? "Magic Man" by Heart.
Didn't go over well. What else did I sing last night? Three songs. Needed it.
Needed to sing three songs. And, fuck. What was the third one? I don't know. "Beautiful Stranger" by
Madonna the Austin Powers song. Oh yeah. You know about that boys?
Madonna made that song for the Austin Powers movie. Really? Yes.
I don't care. You started it last night. Sing it again.
Oh yeah, that's the second one.
(laughter)
- The music video's awesome 'cause she goes crazy on him.
Like they're in the car driving and he's being Austin Powers
and she's like being sexy, Madonna-grinding all over him.
- Really, Austin Powers fucked Madonna?
- Of course he fucked, he fucked everyone.
- It's true.
- I had these coasters at my apartment,
they're like Austin Powers coasters,
but I think they just ran out of quotes by the third movie,
so all of the quotes are like,
pictures of like fat bastard,
and it says like there's something wrong with me mentally or something.
Like the picture of Austin Powers says "Core Blimey"
which is like what the fuck?
When does he like say that? I don't remember it saying it at all.
It says "Why so serious?"
I wish, I wish it just had quotes from like other movies
but like pictures of like Austin Powers and like maybe...
Get out me swamp.
Get out me swamp?
Oh you're not a Shrek fan?
Oh no!
Yeah I can fucking tell actually.
You've been owned.
That's so embarrassing.
I would school you in Cena.
If we're playing Cena right now.
That's a thought that I've been thinking about for forever.
All Gunners have layers in them.
Why so serious?
I did karaoke recently for the first time in a long time.
Dude, there's no better feeling.
There's like no...
You can't crush and stand up as hard as you can in karaoke.
Karaoke, people lose their fucking minds.
And karaoke is for you.
Yeah, care.
You are in service of an emotional need that you need to like
release stand up.
You're in service of your on your hands and knees begging them
to like you.
Yeah, and you're on your hands and knees begging that you're
like, I will do anything to get a laugh.
I need you to have a good time karaoke.
No, see, I'm sorry.
What is your painting of the wall?
My painting is your painting.
You're in the room.
It's your painting.
I mean until you check out it's your painting.
That's the ugliest thing ever. It's basically up there with tape apparently.
No, it's got hinges.
Wow.
So that people can do that.
They knew that somebody like Patrick was going to come in here someday.
So people can have an affair in the room or something.
Like yeah, how would that help?
I don't know.
Lift up the painting.
Look at my beautiful art.
You have sex with me now?
For some reason this is like, "Oh, secrets, secrets."
You can hide your wife behind the painting.
[Laughter]
If she's flat Stanley and then fuck somebody.
Yeah.
You can hide behind the painting for like an hour.
For no reason. Can you hide behind the painting?
You can also, if somebody breaks in
Look how big this is.
You can lift up the painting and if they walk behind there you can drop it
and hit him in the head and knock him out.
If you were in a casino royale kind of situation
Finding people in hotel rooms and shit.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
But karaoke, yeah, it's just like
up there. Karaoke is like, I think the closest, you're so comfortable in karaoke, it's like
the closest a white person can feel to being Dave Chappelle on stage. You walk up, you're
in the pocket. And you're jeweling. Yeah, exactly. Okay, what's your karaoke song? 5, 4, 3, 2,
1, don't think about it. Marty Robbins, El Paso. I don't know. Go, go, go, go, go, go,
go. Come on, you have 5 seconds. You're going up right now, it's Planet Rose Karaoke, there's
God damn it, God damn it.
Next on the list is Patrick Doran singing.
Wait, I do have the app that has the list on it.
Wait, hold on, just list the songs.
It's like a phone book sized book of songs.
Uh, Toc Toc, It's My Life.
Okay.
Or Gwen Stefani's My Life.
Uh, never mind, Patrick Doran's not coming to this stage.
I'm sorry. I'll also do Marty Robbins, El Paso, right after Caleb.
Oh, dude.
But you're in a full cowboy outfit.
I'll do it way worse.
I don't know the words to the song or how it goes.
or how it goes. I refuse. I'm not looking at the screen.
Don DeChant.
I can't do Don DeChant.
I grew up, I do Don DeChant.
No, that's not on the curiosity list.
You think that's so fucking funny, don't you?
Well, guess what?
That's his dead mother's name.
Oh, I thought it was just... I thought it was something he was saying.
I thought it was just a fun word he liked.
I thought it was like "bubba".
Yeah, I thought it was like that.
You thought he was being random, didn't you?
Yeah, I really did for a while.
Did you guys hear Kanye West's new album, Meep?
Yeah, do you hear Kanye's new album RorXD?
Yeah, that was actually his dad's name
Fuck what does his dad have a weird name Kanye dad I don't think
Kanye East
Make on this podcast one way way too much man. Just so much money. Well you
That's an Austin power. Oh that is an Austin Powers clone. Just kidding. I was gonna
Get a number
I literally gonna make a joke about like yeah, what did that be a random?
It would be like the one good one for the coaster
Which they probably already had if they had other Austin Powers coasters
It'd probably be like the first movie in one second Sarah thought there was a movie called. Dr. Evil
and it was from that movie.
(laughter)
Yeah, the movie Doctor Evil,
it's kind of like that
hero,
what's it called?
Despicable Me?
It's kind of like when
there's this anti-hero movie
about this guy who wants to
be a stand-up, but he's mentally ill.
Joker.
Yeah, Doctor Evil.
That would have been a good movie. They should have made a
Doctor Evil spin-off.
It's like the entertainment.
Like it's like that movie.
Oh.
Where he's like sad and like trying to call Mini-Me the whole time.
He's in like a phone booth just like, "You haven't called me in three weeks."
"Say something.
Just say anything."
And Mini-Me.
"I still love your mother very much but we're just not together now."
Mini-Me just squeaks.
Yeah.
Oh my god, this whole time I've been picturing Mini-Me saying, "Mini-Me doesn't talk."
"Are you serious?
don't let him talk? It's not that they don't let him. He says "Neeeee" when he gets out of the...
He's too small to have lungs. Oh my god.
[Laughter]
He's got a bag in there. It wouldn't fit in his body.
Give the guy a line. Well... He flips people off. That's his thing.
Are you ser... I literally don't remember that. He flips off Austin Powers.
No. He humps legs. You don't do that. No!
He humps legs and eats a bunch of chocolate. That's the beginning of Goldmember.
And he says, "I'm Fat Bastard."
No, he doesn't say, "I'm Fat Bastard." He says, "It's mini-me."
And he says, "I'm making waffles."
He's not making waffles.
That's Eddie Murphy in Shrek.
It's one of the funniest things.
I'm making waffles.
It's one of the funniest things anyone's ever said.
Yeah, it is up there for sure.
Then he starts talking about parfaits and it's like, "What the hell is that?"
"Oh, it's a parfait."
I didn't learn about parfaits until McDonald's put one out.
I think they did that for Shrek. I think they've the uh...
Well, the jury's still out on that.
You're supposed to say yes.
No! I should have never told you this. I fucked up so bad.
I fucked up. I know you've done so much stupid shit in your life.
You better believe that.
You're gonna drag me through the mud for being a part of an evil sex cult?
You better believe I was on an improv team in Chicago.
Yes sir.
And you better believe I wasn't really allowed to do it anymore because I was wearing a weird
outfit and it was a quote-unquote ensemble and everyone was supposed to sort of blend
in with each other and wear black and I was being annoying and didn't want to do that.
Yeah, that's annoying.
I mean, would they say that to Elvis Presley?
No, exactly.
Would they say that to Ellen?
Exactly.
Hey, Ellen, grow your hair out, sweetheart.
You gotta fit in on the UCB improv team.
I don't think so.
Let's see those tits, Ellen.
Yeah, where's your tits?
- The UCB improv team, I don't think so.
- Let's see those tits, Ellen.
- Where's the bikini?
Hey, kiss that guy, it's part of the scene.
Keep kissing him, marry that dude.
That's probably what they would say to her
'cause they're so disrespectful.
- Didn't she, on her show, didn't she,
like, one of her boyfriends on the show
was like Jeremy Piven on the Ellen show?
- What? - Boyfriend?
- Not the sitcom, but like the talk show.
- Yeah, that's how she came out.
- Called Ellen?
- Or the Ellen, I think, Ellen DeGeneres show.
- It was called The Ellen.
Yeah, yeah, no the Ellen DeGeneres show and then she walked out and she was like oops
I'm gay in like 1989 and then my grandpa was never the same. Laura Dern was the the girlfriend. Really? I think. Swag.
I don't remember. I wasn't born yet. I
Was dead actually. I don't remember that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it was basically like a fleck of dust
I was basically just poop in my dad's eyes. Yeah. Yeah
I was literally just like a sandwich my dad ate. Yeah, I'm yeah, I was just kind of like the earth. Yeah
Of earth. Yeah, I was like a spirit or a ghost
Yeah, it's pretty much like the wind that a hula hoop creates like that was like all I was at the time
But the Ellen show yeah, I was like a drop of rain like falling upward into the sky before I was born. So
It's actually pretty beautiful
You - it's like way too like cool and young
for you. Just sit back and enjoy it.
Yeah.
Just like you.
Just consider yourself privileged.
Because this is master work.
This is guy humor.
Yeah.
Adam Carolla.
That was pretty much just a beautiful
raindrop on a windshield.
Yeah.
That's the kind of man show stuff we like doing.
You guys are being really diceman on it.
Yeah.
Hickory dickory dock.
Before time was existing,
there was just a flat line in the middle of
It's a ridiculous doc, I used to be a boat at a dock.
Perfect joke, can't go wrong.
Yeah, it works every time.
Yeah.
Is he making a comeback anytime soon?
The Dice Man?
He was Lady Gaga's dad in the Shallow movie.
Oh, what? Really?
Yes.
I didn't see it, but if I had known, I would have gone and seen it.
Honestly, he tore that out.
Yeah?
I mean, yes he did, bitch.
He went crazy on it?
- He's crazy on it, he's like an old cab driver
and he's her dad and he's just fucking hot.
I love him more than anything.
- He's a good looking guy, yeah.
- You ever listen to his rap album?
- No. - No.
- Don't do it, bad stuff is being said on it.
- Well now I gotta hear it.
- Yeah, I mean.
- He's doing bad stuff on it.
- Like what?
- Like saying F-U-C-K and like S-H-I-T.
- Does he say all that?
- He wouldn't.
- Yeah, he would.
- I hope he didn't say A-S-S-S, no.
But if he did.
- Dude, why you said it?
- Oh, whoops.
(laughing)
I was saying sass. What the hell dude? He can hear you. Oh shit. Shit man. He's over there.
He is looming like Lex Luthor. See Lex Luthor you gotta be not saying all that guy stuff
on him. Which one's that Batman? Lex Luthor is the one that's me in Superman. He's the
one that's you in Superman. Because he's bald. Oh yeah. Bald and pretty much evil and genius.
yeah sure what okay air conditioning pretty cold pretty cool yeah and i do
the rest of my body on it uh i i don't because my dad i saw him like a month
ago for the first time in a while and he's like son like you have to you have
to tan your head it's like embarrassing how
so since then i've not put on sunscreen a single time yeah yeah you should like uh
you should put bronzer just on the top so like a statue where people rub it for
good luck and it's a completely different color.
Yeah that's not a bad idea I'd go to a cake decorator and have them do my hair like a
Dominican barber shop. That'd be sick. I would do that too. You should get like
frosting flowers on your head could look really good. Oh yeah that'd be beautiful
some piping around the back, some royal kind of up and down stuff.
Happy birthday, Mr. President.
[laughter]
Well, that's a thing I could do every day.
It could be like a new fortune cookie when I tip my head forward.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I could have a different saying on there.
Oh, what if you get like a magic 8-ball installed?
Installed?
Yo, that would be sick.
So like you, like, we just ask questions and then install it.
You definitely have enough room in your skull.
I don't have the room in my skull for that.
You definitely, okay, you can just like take out half your brain and put in one of those
triangle things with the words on it.
I need half of my brain.
You don't need that.
You only need 50% of it.
The reason that the brain comes in two halves is because you can take one off.
Yeah, and girls have one side and guys have the other side.
Is that true?
Yeah, seriously.
That's why guys are good at math and girls are good at, um, bee shopping.
They are good at bee shopping.
Forget about that.
That's true.
That's the thing about the 90, if you only use 10% of your brain, why can't you just
cut the other 90 out and put something funny in there?
You can, that's what I'm saying.
Yeah, it's true.
Yeah, you just need to get a window in the top of your head.
- Just make it like a, have it open up like a
luggage carrying compartment on an airplane
and let me put Doritos in it.
- I know people like full blown brain damage
and they're like kinda like normal.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's like you, it is testament to,
I know this guy, well actually,
well, maybe that's not necessarily true.
(laughing)
Is he gonna hear this?
- No.
- I went to college with a guy,
I went to college with a guy who was a wrestler.
- Okay, oh that's my biggest fan.
- And had so many,
(laughing)
little tiny wrestling guys.
He sustained so many concussions
that he couldn't wrestle anymore
'cause he basically had brain damage
and he staple gunned his sheets to his bed
'cause he liked the feeling of being tucked in.
So he staple gunned them all around.
- That belongs in an asylum.
- Yeah, absolutely.
As I was saying, 'cause it's like,
I knew he had brain damage,
but I'm like, this guy's kinda like,
he's kinda tearing it for someone with brain damage.
- Really, he's crushing?
I think that's a great idea. I don't know about you guys. I've been hit in the head a few times though.
Yeah I have I had like three rapid concussions in rapid succession as a
child. Yeah. I think I probably would have been like a superhero if it wasn't for that.
What'd they do to you? The football team did that to me.
They shouldn't let children do that by the way. I agree.
Play football? Yeah. Why not? It's bad for them. Look at this. What happened?
You turned bald. I'm so sick. He lost all his hair. Yeah, they knocked it out of his head.
He got tackled and all flew out. My football coach did tell me as a kid, he was like,
"Son, you got a big head. You better be using that on the field. Lead with it."
I was like, "Yes, sir. Yes, sir, Chuck." And I just tear kids up with my big ass head. I was
like a rhino or a giraffe. I was like a giraffe with a small neck using my head for defense.
Yeah, and also I was big and fat and so that I played center position,
which the center his whole job is just like just yeah
I we don't know okay all right have you ever played the game as a kid smear the
queer no you never played that yeah I was basically the one who was it all the
time. What is smear the queer? So it's just tag but you tackle someone. That they
decide is the gay guy on the team? We didn't even know what queer meant we
thought it was we thought I thought the first time I heard the word queer I was
like somebody who's it like what does that mean? Well now that's exactly what
it means. That's right.
friggin let him know this okay checking his watch basically wants to get out of
here you see yeah yeah I like of me I just like I like testing myself okay
start singing
(singing)
- Can we sign you a record deal?
- Yeah, I need $6,000 back.
- Sensitive gangster records.
- Yeah, we'd love to sign you.
- Yeah, all right.
- All right, we're finally gonna do the list.
- So it is a podcast about lists.
- Do you think this is just like an ominous thing
I think you guys gotta get a new name for a podcast.
What? Pod-about-list? What's wrong with that?
You say anything like that and it sucks. Sarah Squirm?
McDonald's? These are iconic names that work fine when you say them normal.
The Sarahs were McDonald's meal? What would it be? 5 4 3 2 1?
Poop.
Come on.
- I got the Saweetie meal.
Did you know that when celebrities do their celebrity meal,
it's just a meal?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I thought it was gonna be something weird about it.
- Well, they had a weird sauce, I think.
- But didn't that exist already?
'Cause it was Saweetie and sour,
but they already have sweet and sour.
- Oh, wait, that was the Saweetie meal.
- That's all they did?
- Literally, the Saweetie meal is literally
like a burger, fries, and chicken nuggets.
- Yeah, it sounds delicious.
- It exists already though.
- But the BTS meal, all they did was they put like a--
- The BTS meal, what was that?
- It was like a Cajun sauce.
- Oh, that didn't exist before?
- Yeah.
- So they made like a, or it might have existed
at like McDonald's Korea and then they brought it here.
- And when I think of BTS, I think Cajun.
- Yeah.
- I didn't walk no boys down on the bayou.
- I don't know BTS, boy.
Oh, they down there.
- Who like butter?
Who like butter?
(laughing)
- Well, I went to McDonald's to get a McChicken one time
and they gave it to me in a BTS meal bag,
and I so wanted to just be like,
can you give me a different bag, please?
Like, I have to walk home with this.
- I had a pink BTS backpack for a little bit,
and I gave it to Robbie,
but that thing, it was a bootleg,
and it did not close at all.
You find the hair on that?
- Yeah, but it was an eyelash, I think.
- Oh.
- It's probably mine, I kinda have Minnie Mouse eyelashes.
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
(laughing)
Ding, ding, ding.
- Okay, what's the list?
- The list is top 10--
- It's about lists.
- Worst things.
- It's not a pod about a list, it's pod about lists.
- It's about lists, yeah.
In like two years, every podcast is gonna be named like this.
This is gonna be the naming convention.
We're way ahead of the curve.
- There's only one list per episode.
- Pod about lists.
- Because if we said lists.
- Sometimes we do multiple lists.
- It's just so clinical.
- I'm defending us.
(laughing)
- Okay, what should we call it then?
Something fun like couple of two guys and one bald guy.
That's still a guy.
It's still just a guy.
It's not a different kind of guy.
It's a normal guy.
Bald guys are freaks.
No, it's not true.
It's actually not true.
He has cancer.
Yeah, I bet you feel real stupid now.
He's not even doing his chemo.
He just has a shaving set.
I probably do have cancer.
So I could just start telling people to get away with being bald.
Yeah, might as well.
Yeah.
The heist.
Do you guys know Ben O'Brien of Wim?
Yeah.
Ben O'Brien of William C. De Calvany.
That was my first like concert he opened for Dan Deacon.
Oh doing Earth Universe?
Yeah.
That was so good.
You want to hear a really funny thing I say about Ben O'Brien famous bald guy?
I go Ben O'Brien? More like Benno bald guy.
Ooh.
That's really funny.
What's your full name?
Caleb Michael Pitts.
Huh?
Caleb. Yeah nevermind. Kareem Abdul-Jabbar.
(laughter)
- Michael, wait, but why do you say it like that?
- Caleb Michael Pits.
- Why do you pause like that?
- But you said Caleb Michael Pits.
- You have to remember his middle name.
- It seems like you're stalling to come up
with a bald version of my name.
Caleb Michael Pits, go, three, two, one.
- Caleb Michael Pits Bald Guy.
- That's fucking sucked.
- Let's go!
- That was terrible.
- Is Michael a middle name or your last name?
- Middle, what do you think Pits was?
- You said it like it was hyphenated.
Caleb Michael pits I have a southern accent
Don't ball damage, you know, okay the list is top ten worst things to be magically turned into
Yes, you have magic is totally awesome
Random thing you guys found on the internet. Yeah, we didn't like try
To a podcast no, I'm cool
I listen to music.
Oh, what is that?
The idea of magic is totally awesome, but the idea of magic being used against you, it's totally not awesome.
One prime example or stereotype of magic is the power of turning an object into something else,
which again may sound very awesome, but you wouldn't want that power being used against you.
So, without further ado, here's some of the very worst objects that you could ever turn into.
I hate magical stereotypes.
Yeah, I'm sick of all these fucking magic stereotypes.
It's really annoying.
You see a wizard, you know he got that wand.
That is a harmful stereotype.
Dude, when I see someone on the subway in a blue pointy cap and I tap them on the shoulder
and I ask them to do a spell and they turn around and they're a gnome, I feel so bad.
So annoying.
That's a classic New York moment.
Yeah.
Come on, oh you're a magician? Come on, do a spell. Come on, turn me into a toad.
Is it, it has to be things? Like you can't be like something more abstract or a person?
like beauty you want to be turned into beauty yeah like or like turn and yeah
like turned into inspiration or something like that happens when you die
yeah that's for damn sure I know that's right number one is toilet I mean that's
pretty bad I would say but also like it depends like I'm never gonna be in a
situation where if I'm with a wizard and I get turned into a toilet with a wizard
It's probably gonna be like in a park or something in the middle of the street something like that
It's gonna be because the wizard is mad at me in a public space
I'm not gonna be somewhere where they're even gonna plug in my my body to a toilet hole
Yeah, so it doesn't matter. No, it's gonna take a shit at me
There's a point if there's a loose toilet on the street
You don't think someone's gonna take a shit in there Dave England shows up. That'd be horrible
Walking out the hardware store bump into a fucking wizard and he doesn't even have to have to shit
Yeah, do it on command. He doesn't even you're right. He gets a
Toilet, yeah, I mean I guess it's also did my toilet with like googly eyes who can move. Yeah, like the one who's talking
Yeah, exactly. Move my lid. I scared the
Looking toy. Yeah as a kid that scared the shit out of me
like I was like scared to go to the bathroom at night because it would happen to me too, even though it's like a
movie
That's one of the most incredible sentences I've ever heard. Yeah
- Yeah, that was brilliant.
- I thought like Mel Brooks' toilet was gonna yell at me.
- Absolutely brilliant.
- And I'll tell you what, there are people who pay top dollar
to be turned into someone's toilet, if you know what I mean.
- That's true. - Absolutely.
- We know.
- Well, yeah, so there's a comment here
from Blue and Black Midnight Rose that says,
"Ew, heck no, I would not wanna let people
"let out all their nasty body fluids in me.
"Like what if someone had to take a huge nasty dump
"or getting vomited in, ew, no thank you."
And then Caitlin the Mouse Boy responds and says,
"Um, I have that fetish."
(laughing)
I want somebody to take a big nasty dump and puke in me.
- One of my life's biggest, I truly do desperately,
and I think that I can shit in someone's mouth.
I would love for someone to pay me to shit in their mouth,
and I don't think it would count
as cheating on my boyfriend.
- Really, you think that one's fine?
- I think that one's fine,
and I've asked him this before, too.
- What'd he say?
- He was like, "I wouldn't love it."
- Well, but also--
- But he didn't say he wouldn't hate it.
- He didn't say that, girls gotta eat.
- Like if I could do that without the person like--
- Jerking?
- Maybe they jerk later, but also like
be that close to my butthole, you know?
Like if I could do it from like 100 feet in the air.
- That would be sick.
- Then I think that's fine, right?
Like I don't care. - I don't like an airplane.
- If I shit in someone's mouth from 100,
if they're like right under my ass--
- Out of like an airplane.
- Yeah, and hitting, 'cause then I'm like,
it's like sight unseen.
- Yeah, exactly, hey, if this hits someone, so be it.
So be it, if I get fucking $5,000 wired to me, then fucking whatever.
You know what they say, if you shit off the top of the Empire State Building, it could
cut through someone's skull.
I know they did that on Mythbusters.
It was really good.
That's why they don't, that's what happened to that one guy.
Yeah.
Granny Mahara.
Oh my god, he died.
He died, yeah.
What happened?
Well, basically a humongous shit fell out of the sky and cut him in half.
Like Final Destination.
It was serious.
And then he said, "Ow!"
and he said okay
imagine if they put that in a final destination
but like all these like crazy Rube Goldberg things
and then one guy just walking around and just a shit
falls out of the sky and cuts him
just perfectly in half
a razor shit
it's like yeah it's
terminal velocity and starts like fraying
at the front and turns into a perfect spear
they don't explain it all so it just
comes out of the sky
there's no set up like the other ones
no no it's not like
You just see on the news, "A shit fell out of the sky and cut this guy in half."
That's one of the Mortal Kombat fatalities, actually, in the new Mortal Kombat.
Just falling out.
Here's another comment. "Imagine having a hot girl poop on you."
Here's another comment. "In Lola Loud voice, gross." I don't know who Lola Loud is.
Lola Loud is from The Loud House. It was a show on Nickelodeon.
Oh, okay.
We've read this website specifically so many times that like I know what the Loud House is now.
Everybody be talking about the Loud House on this website?
It's all kids. Which makes wanting to shit on each other worse.
Yeah. Number one.
Number two is...
Kids are talking to adults.
True, yeah.
True.
Number two is pinata.
Pinata?
That didn't sound so bad. Damn, I'm full of candy right now.
- I think everyone's imagination is limited on this website.
- Yeah, I agree.
- What would your worst object--
- The worst thing to be turned into?
- Yeah.
- Like a hospital, some like hospital receptacle
that receives like not only, like a biohazard bin
'cause you're getting shit, piss, like bile, needles,
fluids you've never even heard of.
much via is it's true
catheter
the worst thing i would get turned into his probably like a shorter guy
uh...
like a bald guy and uh...
uh... and he was a young and he had an international and c_n_n_ one of the
children
sleek
because smeared clear
and i didn't get smeared anytime soon
uh... actually and i my head is fine and it's bald for
It's actually by choice. I could grow dreadlocks right now in five seconds.
Okay. Go.
They're really small though. That's like the trick, because they're microscopic.
Especially if it's in the shape of Barney, Elsa, Dora, or Justin Bieber.
That's a comic from Super Mario. Well yeah, that would suck to be turned into a piñata and be like,
"Oh, swag. I'm full of candy." And then see a glimpse of yourself in a mirror and you're a girl piñata.
That would, yeah.
That's gotta hurt. That's gotta sting. No, thank you.
But also things get hit harder than a pinata.
Yeah, exactly.
Like a jersey barrier.
Like with a car or like...
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
I don't know what to do with my immediate thoughts.
A jersey barrier?
Yeah.
I was thinking like someone in war.
Oh, like with a cannonball?
Yeah.
Evil Knievel.
That guy.
Wait, that would be sick because then you could just jump on anything or jump over anything.
You think he had a power?
Yes!
Are you kidding me?
He had the power to jump on anything.
Yeah, he's like Mario.
If anything hit him this way, he would die.
But if he got on top of it, he won the fight.
Exactly.
That's what he did to all those bosses.
I don't think I've ever been at a party with a pinata there.
I literally, for my birthday, my friends got me a Minion pinata.
Yup, I'm loved.
Shout out to you, Jesse and Scott.
Love you.
And there were chips inside!
Chips?
There were chips inside!
I love chips!
Bagged chips or loose chips?
- Bagged chips.
- Oh, okay.
- What kind of chips?
- Every kind of chip.
I love chips.
- Every kind of chip?
- There's a place down the street from here
called like Chips World.
- Whoa.
- Really, wait, are you serious?
- Or it's like Chip City.
- I gotta go.
- Do we have to go there after this?
- I saw this sign from far away
and I said to my friend Peter,
I was like, "Oh my God, it's Chip City!
"We have to go to Chip City!"
And then one of the employees came out
wearing a shirt and I was like,
"Yes, chips, chips!"
And he was wearing a shirt that said Chip City
and he's like, "Don't get excited, it's cookies."
- Oh, fuck that. - Oh my God.
- Come on. - And I was like,
are you serious, it's not chips?
- You shouldn't be able to name a place
Chip City if it's not chips.
- Is he talking about like chocolate chips?
- I mean, yeah. - Yeah, or peanut butter chips
or white chocolate chips or macadamia chips.
- All right, okay, okay, Jesus Christ.
- Those should have a different name.
I'm sick of getting excited over chips
and it's like chips ahoy.
No, fuck that, it's called something else now.
- What's it called now?
- Little Chocolate Guys.
- Little chocolate guys.
- I don't think it's called that.
- Chocolate rounders.
- Oh.
- I don't think you can say that.
- Why?
- I think that's a rude word for a type of person maybe.
- What, rounder?
- A chocolate rounder.
I don't think you can walk around the street
saying that around here.
- Well, let's go try it.
- I literally can't find proof that this place exists now.
- It's there.
(laughing)
They're hiding it.
- Did I make this up?
- Yeah.
- Probably.
- Okay, I'm not kidding.
It's across the street and I'm Googling it
and it's not coming up on the map.
- They replaced it with an FAO Schwartz yesterday.
(laughing)
- I saw--
- I see a bunch of umbrellas across the street.
I don't think that's Chip Swirl, is it?
- I'm not kidding, I can't find it.
- Oh my God, Mo.
- Oh my God. - You're a liar.
- You saw a mirage.
- Were you like really thirsty yesterday?
- I was really thirsty for chips yesterday.
- Oh, that's probably why.
- Favorite chip?
potato chips. You're serious? I don't know. I don't know. Salt and vinegar kettle cooked?
Probably like the Zapp's Voodoo, but have you had the fucking...
No!
It's... the uh... there's this like... this like Lay's, like it's called like "Numb and
Spicy Hot Pot" and it was like... it's from China, but it was so good.
Numb?
I gotta find that. Yeah, I bought it because it said "Numb" on the bag.
Oh, cappuccino Lays.
Oh, yeah.
Those are bad.
Yeah, I can imagine.
They're really bad.
They made them though.
Oh, do you remember in 2016, they had the like the promo thing where you could win like air
travel miles for like these specific like they had like four flavors in promotion of
the Olympics and they had these tikka masala kettle chips.
They were so fun.
I was like genuinely bummed when those like were like discontinued.
When Pat talks about chips, he starts not making eye contact with anyone.
He's like my weird cousin talking about maps.
He's just looking down.
It's beautiful.
You really tap in.
Yo, Ruffles Aldres.
Oh yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
I used to eat the Humpty Dumpty Aldres.
They were like two bucks.
What do you mean Humpty Dumpty?
I think it might be a regional chip.
A Humpty Dumpty?
From where?
the candy land but they had those all dress chips and I used to go to this there was like
two bucks and I would just buy that and eat that for lunch at the skate park.
I love chips.
You think they're gonna knock the door down?
I think we might be in a SWAT self-defense situation pretty soon.
Yeah could happen that's what I'm saying dude this painting is kind of hinged.
You're gonna hide under the painting.
What if he can do kick me out?
I don't know we'll fucking I mean no.
No, probably not.
Dude, the room's on NBC.
I'm not gonna get charged for this.
Oh my gosh.
Are you serious?
Wow.
Yep.
You are rich.
Here's another comment.
I don't want to be a pinata getting killed by that cursed stick.
Okay.
Facts.
Number three.
Why is everyone on this website randoms us?
Is there all, this list is probably from like 2014 and they're probably all 11 is my guess.
Number three's food.
I think technically everybody is food.
Damn.
If someone's a cannibal.
Yep.
That's true.
That's serious.
Top comment here is from Super Mario Fan.
You get chewed on by someone, go into their body, come out as you know what, and then
get flushed down the toilet.
Sorry this is gross, but that's what would happen if you were food.
Honestly, food might be one of the best things you can be because like you permutate into
different forms.
like energy never dies it just turns into other things so it's like kind of like
you're chill like you're chillin also you could make somebody's day true I'd
also be like so delicious - yeah also what if like what if you went into like
Pam Anderson's mouth maybe clutch social is hero what if you were like oh my god
what if you were a hot dog that Pam Anderson yeah but what if it was like a
hot dog and like she was like lady in the tramping it with Julian Assange.
That's fine dude. Yeah? Yeah. Okay you think he's a hero? Okay. He's a beast.
You actually like that guy? Someone can't keep a secret. Somebody else on this one
said imagine being eaten by a hot girl. Yeah. That's the answer to any of these. Imagine being a toilet under a hot girl's ass.
Imagine a hot girl loved candy and broke you into a million pieces.
Oh my god.
Yeah, McDonald's comments "vore."
Where'd you guys get these microphones?
Amazon.
D-Store.
I don't know where that one came from.
Yeah, he has a freak one.
Oh, that's the freak one?
Yeah, I got like three microphones for like $20.
Is that the Radio Shack mic from Moo-Yah?
Or is that a different one?
No, I don't think so.
I just ordered these myself because we didn't have mics.
I don't have one.
No, I don't think so. I just ordered these myself because we didn't have mics at one point, but then we got the nice ones.
Yeah.
Yup, you better believe that.
Number four is bubble.
Wrong! That's one of the most beautiful things you could be.
It is really beautiful.
There was a guy at Central Park the other day making humongous bubbles with a piece of string.
And I don't know how he made it.
Is that his job?
Yeah, and there was like a little kid that he was like clearly super mad at who just kept,
who just kept as soon as a bubble would be made the kid popped it like he would stand next to it and
just immediately pop the bubbles before they even finish. I mean you can't expect it's a bubble.
Right. Yeah. You can't make it in Central Park and like if you want your bubble to survive you
got to make it at home where no one else is. Yeah. What he could have done is put poison in
the bubble. That could have been very clever. He could have put ricin in the bubble and kill the
kid breaking that stuff. Or he could have made the bubble like really hot so the kid burned his
finger when he popped it.
It's not a bad idea.
The top comment on Bubble is, "This is one of the only items on this rather not very
funny list I'm willing to vote.
There is a certain way bathroom humor can be executed and the other entries are how
you don't do it."
That's just straight up true.
And by the way, Bubbles exist in a bathroom.
Yeah, true.
Mr. Bubble?
Yes.
Taking a bubble bath, bathroom humor.
What do you think people do in bubble baths?
Mr. Feeny's commenting over here.
- They're naked in there.
Bubbles are seeing penises, ass, boobs.
- Wait, really?
- Oh no!
- There's another comment on Bubble that says,
imagine being sipped by a hot girl.
(laughing)
- Imagine being what?
- Sipped.
- No, Bubbles could be in your drink!
- True, yeah.
- That's true.
you're getting sick girl or you could be you could be blown into milk are you
crazy
you get up all right you never got a man or you say I'll have two straws one for
bubbles one for drinking they bring it to you and you did I mean the bubble straw
the bubble straw goes in your nose the drinking straw goes in your mouth.
This is anti-semitic cuz you know I can't be drinking milk you sure is. I did know that.
You can't be saying anti-semitic shit with that bald head. I used to be able to say so much
much and now I just can't it's a number five is diapers oh we talked enough
about this show that's a toilet by any other would be fantastic view if you had
a scat fetish though or if you're a pedophile and I will say not to rag I
I'm going to be shooting a comedy video where I was going to be wearing diapers
and where do you think I bought diapers from? A pedophile? You better believe I found an
adult baby kink website hilarious adult diapers from it that look like they're
for babies but they're big do they have like a big like safety pin they have a
funny little pattern on it yeah one of the funniest adult diaper patterns I saw
was there was one that would just had weed leaves all over so funny yeah you
you should get a supreme diaper.
(laughing)
- That'd be tough.
- There is a diaper brand.
- It says juicy on the ass.
(laughing)
- There's a diaper brand called Supreme.
- Really?
- 'Cause I remember in high school,
that was my joke, I'd pick it up and be like,
yo, new Supreme drop.
- Nice, I think you were the coolest
high school kid of all time.
- Interesting you just made up a story
to cover the fact that you knew about a diaper brand.
(laughing)
No, seriously, it was like a hilarious joke.
- That's the funniest thing I've ever said.
- We used to make fun of those diapers all the time.
Although we should go to the store right now. We can go do it at the store. Seriously, like we should go ha ha buy diapers or something
That's a joke
The small ones walking into your the school into the school like wearing the supreme diaper be like yo, I got the new supreme drop
Just wearing it the whole day
The actual green stink lines. Yeah
Your diaper and your mouth just walking around school
Every time you see someone you're just like yeah, I got the new supreme drop like just so you know
You know, like it's a joke that I'm wearing this.
I've never met you before, but yeah.
It's funny, right? And not stinky?
You should smell the Supreme Drop.
No.
Yo, I made a Supreme Drop in the Supreme Drop.
Pee-ew.
Nasty.
Number six is punching bag. That's a boring one.
That's not a, that's, that wouldn't be that bad.
I think it would be inspiring to see somebody like
achieve their fitness dreams before my eyes.
I feel like a punching bag because I'm the only
woman in this room doing all the emotional
labor around here. Can you talk about my dad? Yeah. Did I tell you he actually said I have a big bald white head.
Can you like handle that for me? Yeah um let me just unpack that real quick.
I think that I can't think of anything funny to say because I had three shots
of tequila last night and I want to say something. Uh-huh. Drinking is bad. It's
It's poison and no one should do it.
Here's the thing, drinking is driving.
How about that?
You ever text and drink at the same time?
Oh yeah.
It's disgusting.
It's horrible.
The drink gets all over the phone.
Yep.
It gets all sticky.
I can't even type after that.
I give my phone to the bartender.
Are you flipping me off?
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
That's so rude.
- Stop, don't point that at me.
- Stop!
- Just flip me off.
- No, don't crank it up.
No!
- Crank it back down, crank it down.
- God, this sucks.
I'm, God, speaking of freaking punching bag,
yeah, I've seen every episode.
- Yeah, which one is the one of you guys
that gets made fun of?
- Yeah.
- What'd you do to deserve it?
- I don't know.
I have ADHD, so they yell at me.
- Oh my God, that's ableist!
- Yep.
You guys are so ableist against him.
- Which one of you guys is like the alpha?
- Cameron.
- Am I the alpha?
- Yeah.
- Big dog on campus.
- Oh, am I the alpha?
- I'm like the Robin.
- I don't wanna be the alpha.
- I'm like sexy in there.
- The Robin?
- Robin.
- Like Batman Robin?
- No, for Stern.
- The Batman Robin?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- She's in that too.
- Yeah, she is.
(laughing)
- She's just singing.
you will literally be a punching bag that's a car from punching that is
very clever number seven deodorant
well i could smell good
oak oak good old sweet hairy armpits
you know and i'll say this again one time
it wasn't
guys be paying a lot of money to be doing being wanting to be dealing with
i i want to have a guy wanted to like my armpits
this is true
He wanted to pay me to lick my armpits.
- Is that what you were here for this week?
- That's what I was here for this week.
- Some guy.
- Some guy, Donald Jason Trump.
(laughing)
Ever heard of that?
This guy was like, "All right, I'll pay you $200.
"I'll lick your armpits, whatever."
And then we went to dinner and ended up fighting
about Zionism and didn't make it to the armpit party.
- Wow.
- Still got paid.
- And dinner.
Yeah.
And dinner.
And how, honey.
Yeah.
And spirited debate.
You don't get that often nowadays, and it's good to--
I know.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Number eight is soccer ball.
Again, this is boring.
Yeah, it's the same as punching bag.
It's exactly the same as punching bag.
It's not.
You could see the world.
If being hit by baseball bats and other spiky objects
wasn't bad enough, imagine being kicked
by 22 professional athletes for 90 minutes.
hitting the crossbar would also result in extra pain.
Other sports balls would be painful, but the soccer ball is no different.
"Kicked by 22 athletes for 20 minutes? Oh yeah!"
Imagine being kicked by 22 hot girl athletes.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Imagine it was bikini soccer, though.
Mud soccer.
Dead or alive 3.
I don't know what you guys are doing with soccer balls,
but I'm taking a big ol' dookie on those.
Oh, hell no!
Yeah, but this hot girl, yep, she's taking a dump on her own.
- She's going through everything on this list.
Like, yeah, but I pretty much dookie on this.
(laughing)
I don't know why you wanna be that.
- Yeah.
No, let's see, number nine, balloons.
That's just bubbles.
That's a stronger bubble. - True, true.
- Yeah.
I just wanted to comment on this
because people were wondering
where the ballon would stop floating
or if it would just pop.
Actually, balloons will stop rising
once their density matches the surrounding air.
Then I guess it would run out of helium
and just fall to the ground
burn up in the atmosphere just wanted to say I'll tell you what when they pop
it's scary yeah it is like a gunshot I was that you know I was at like a dim
someplace with my friend and another fake story with two friends actually
their three names and well a fourth friend showed up so hold on well I'm
still telling the story but there's like a surprise party and like they pop the
balloon and everyone just thought there was just a gunshot in the restaurant.
That was it. That's why it's scary when they pop up. I'm sorry I didn't know where that was going.
I think the saddest thing in the world is when like you see in the distance like a
balloon
going up into the sky. I laugh.
I know that it belonged to a house with a little Korean boy in it
and an old man and they're about to go on an adventure. True. That's a good point.
If one balloon goes up they probably couldn't fly anymore.
probably ruin their whole adventure.
- Yeah.
- You better believe that one time my parents' friend
was sick in the hospital, so they went outside
the hospital building and released a bunch of balloons.
- Yup.
- So they floated off.
- And they started crying.
- Yup, yes.
- Woo hoo.
- Let 'em know.
(laughing)
Woo, talk that talk, OG.
Let 'em know.
- She really loved to see those beautiful white balloons.
- She did, she did.
- Outside her hospital window before her dialysis.
(laughing)
- You better believe that shit, bitch.
- I love that balloon shit.
- Motherfucker.
- Yeah, number 10's toilet paper.
This is-- - Enough!
- Yeah, it's pretty much the same as toilet.
- It's funny 'cause I usually just dookie on the paper.
(laughing)
It's weird.
- I usually dookie on the paper,
wipe my ass on the rim of the seat.
- Especially, oh, you have one of those ones
they have in Japan that it like--
replaces the liner.
Really? There's a Japanese toilet here?
Yeah. Where?
You've never been to a gas station in like, Altoona, Pennsylvania?
They have the-
All-Tuna?
Don't say All-Tuna.
I mean, it's not just some, but I'll tell you what.
Wait, the ones that automatically replace the liner?
I've seen those before.
Yeah, they really- remember we went to that place with-
Dude, what are you, poor?
Yeah.
No.
What was it like to go to Japan?
No, we went to that fucking, I don't, it's somewhere around here that like...
Dude, chill, you don't have to do gun fingers at us.
I'm trying to think of words.
Stop, don't put it yourself.
AHHHHHHHHH!
No, that like, that really expensive place that Potashnik took us to.
Oh, they had that there?
Yeah.
Did you walk in and fold your poop and put it inside?
[Laughter]
I took a video of it.
I did take a video of it, me pressing the button, because I was excited.
It's pretty exciting.
exciting. Yeah. You've seen the video of the guy who puts poop on one of those
and presses the button and it smears the poop all the way around. You haven't seen that?
No. It's so good. It sounds really good. I'm gonna be honest with you, the thought of that just made me sick.
Maybe you shouldn't have done so many drugs last night. You'd kill me eating a piece of crap.
Liquid, so what I drink smoke. No, you're a fool. So what I drink. Me and Jack Benzinger, we sang that for three
and a half hours in the night so what I drink smoke so what I beer weed shout
out to Jack I love you you're one of my best friends seriously man like I miss
you could you do it without him so I drink smoke so and those balloons floated
right up to heaven. Yes sir! Woo! Woo!
Ok we got the contenders here.
There's newcomers here, the newcomers to the list are Craig and Sanjay from Sanjay and Craig, which looks like a cartoon.
Why would that be bad?
Can you skip number 11? That's like so disgusting.
Yeah number 11 is maybe even too disgusting to look at.
Yeah, I'm a female comedian so I could talk about this
Tampon oh my god. Yeah again. I'm a female comedian
What's a month once a month Oh
Oh, I thought it was every day.
It's like a faucet that's on and fills up the whole room like the Shining.
What?
Yeah.
It's true?
It's like a murder mystery scene.
That scene where there's a room full of blood and a murder mystery.
Who filled up this room with blood?
That's the mystery.
Yeah, well it's like when the butler comes in and says, "Somebody filled the room with blood."
And I have to clean that crap? Come on!
It was the guy with the candlestick in the other place.
Filling up this place with damn barbecue sauce.
I wouldn't want to be a tampon.
I guess unless it was like a really hot girl.
I usually take a doogie on a tampon when I put that in my ass.
Maybe if it was a hot girl and she needed a tampon.
If she needed a tampon between her boobs instead, then that would be the perfect life.
Dude, that's nasty.
I'm just saying, hey, a guy's gotta be a guy.
And I want to be a boob tampon for life.
- We gotta go, I'm gonna get kicked out of this place soon.
- One more, one more, 13 is Ash.
Imagine being about to be turned into a beauty or a unicorn
or any animal or object of your choice,
but the magic trick fails and you get cremated.
This isn't a magically turned object, this is death.
This is a badly burnt corpse.
Death by being burnt, one of the worst ways to die.
- One of the worst ways to die is being
what happened at 9/11.
- That's true.
- The entire city of New York was covered in this stuff.
I mean, you couldn't escape this crap.
They were so sick of--
It was so annoying.
I mean, everybody was fine with ash before 9/11.
Yeah.
They just got too much of it.
Absolutely.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's like snow, you know?
It's like, it's cool.
Like, the first day, it's like, oh, this is beautiful.
But then after that, it's like, I just want this gone.
Yeah, I just, you know,
the first few days of ash in New York City--
Exactly.
It's like, I'm out there playing, sledding,
making ash man.
And where were you guys--
There's a lot of ash men, actually.
Where were you guys on the day of 9/11,
just pre-school. Yeah I was just a beautiful thought in a monk's brain.
That's how you know that guy interned at UCB! Let him know dude. I love them. I was just like a
sparkle at the top of a rainbow back then. I was actually the most beautiful creature
of all time back then but you wouldn't know. I was in my mom's
basement because she put me down there because she was afraid that they were
gonna hit New Hampshire. That would be very funny. They're like Twin Towers, Pentagon,
White House and New Hampshire. Yeah, the Red Arrow Diner got hit. And Adam Sandler's crying
because he's from New York and New Hampshire and he's just like, "They took everyone, they
took all my stuff!" Yeah. That would be really tragic. "They took all the things I love!"
him. Whoa, those are really good. Insane. Wait, do it again. Do uncut gems. That's pretty fucking
good man. Another moment of anti-Semitism on podcast about lists. Was that anti-Semitic?
Tune in for more on the Patreon. That's right. More anti-Semitic moments. Number 200 is a
Caillou DVD. Oh hell no. Oh hell no. Oh hell no. I'd have to spin around in a DVD player,
get a laser pointed at me? No. No. I hate that shit. I hate to be an iridescent
metallic desk that's the most beautiful thing anyone's ever seen.
But at least you'd be like one of the few like bald main characters
that is actually on television. You know, so that's something to think about.
They're probably gonna have a lot of, do show a lot of support for Caillou.
Uh, I follow a YouTube account called Bald Cafe that teaches you how to better shave the top of
your head. Bye. So. Is this gonna be behind a paywall?
Nope. No. Fuck you.
uh... yeah what would word pretty much done with these you wanna plug anything
that's i'd would love to
when does this come out
wednesday and said are you serious
yeah well listen if you're a little as a little scout for you know i'm having an
issue
people are buying tickets is show that i need them to buy tickets for
yes and
brain dead theater
hope so was not all the other sex sorry
so was i get a door
the gustavos comes again meaning holocaust is happening
uh...
brain dead theater on the twenty third of september i'm doing a show and not that
many people about tickets
you understand
and i guess i'll intake is
i bought a lot of our like ten years ago by a bunch of tickets and
watch their acts you know i mean cv police is it's very nice what else do
you have to do
check it out it's funny and it's fine
- Watch it. - Heard it here first
from the bald man himself.
- Not that bald, you can't even tell I'm bald
right now pretty much.
- You got a hat on.
- Yeah, I know.
- Take your hat off.
- No.
- Okay, bye everybody. - Bye.