Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Oh man, I wish I could get an elephant man disease
on my nuts.
- That exists.
- I know, dude.
I've seen the video, the guy just--
- The video where he's bouncing around on 'em?
- He has to wear the sweatshirt over his pants.
- Yeah, he wears like a onesie.
- He wears a hoodie.
- And he just bounces around on his balls all day.
- Dude, I wish I could.
- That's the life.
(laughing)
Yeah, I honestly if I had something like that maybe I will be completely fine with being just a zoo animal that yeah
We'll just like pay them. Yeah, cuz like I get I get everything taken care of you know what you could and I just fucking chill
Yeah, cuz I what's what's harder
And if you have giant balls that you have to bounce on all day or giant everything else or giant everything else is giant everything
Else tiniest balls in the world that's that no that's like the most successful man ever
But if you have just giant balls, is it harder to be like go like try to interview to be a
bank teller or is it harder to be a zoo animal?
It's probably way harder to try to be a normal guy.
It's probably easy to be a normal guy, it's just people will stare at you.
What you could do is get like a face tattooed on the giant balls.
But then if people are staring at you, you'd get mad but you wouldn't get mad if they paid
you five dollars to stare at you.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- I think we're just reinventing the freak show.
- A good bank teller gets tips.
(laughing)
- That's true.
- Have you not been tipping your bank teller?
- 10% of everything you take out and put in.
- Of every check.
- Yeah.
- 18%.
- There's a gratuity included.
- Gratuity added.
- In your receipt.
- Yeah.
- Damn, I went to the bank today just to put
like cash in my account.
- Yeah.
- And I,
I have not walked into a bank in a while.
Probably the last time I walked into a bank was to open up my checking account when I
was 17.
I used to pay my rent here with a cashier's check.
Those suck.
Yeah, it sucks.
And then I didn't know, I banked America and the lady, it was always the same teller every
month and I guess it takes forever.
It takes like fucking 15 minutes for them to do it.
And one time, probably the sixth or seventh time I did it, she was just like, "You know
that you can just pay this online."
Because I guess they have some bill pay thing where they'll basically just send an automated
cashier's check.
So she just got mad at me because I would just waste her time every fucking -- on the first
of every month.
The cashier's check, is that the one that costs money too?
Yeah, it costs like $15.
It costs like $10.
Yeah.
Yeah, because that shit's so big.
And also if you lose it, it's just gone.
It's gone, yeah.
You just lose the money.
Literally the worst idea of all time.
I was so terrified walking with my entire rent back to my house.
When we got accepted for our apartment here, I had to get a cashier's check from the bank
and I had to FedEx it to here from Boston.
And so I had to, basically, I had an envelope in my hand with thousands of dollars in it.
I had to walk from like Austin to Brookline to get to the FedEx store.
I feel like you're the fucking...
And it was windy as fuck.
I feel like you're the transporter, dude.
It was terrifying.
No, I didn't have anything that I could...
Well, also, I feel like it'd be way less secure to put it in like a pocket,
because it would just like...
Versus like holding it in my hand.
Any time I have a cashier's check in my hand,
I expect to be like trying to cross the street,
and then like a black suburban pulls up,
and a bunch of like Japanese hitmen get out and try to fucking kill me.
Well, if I put it in a pocket, it's going to fly out of the pocket.
But then because the mental thing that happens in your brain, you have to hold onto it.
Exactly.
If I let go, it's gone.
I would pay my rent in Boston.
Yeah, I wouldn't.
Literally, I'll only hold it in my hand.
What if somebody steals the jacket off my back?
Also, if someone steals the jacket, they can't even cash it.
It's just like, if I robbed somebody and I just had to frame it and put it on my wall.
$10,000 just that nobody could ever use my first $10,000 yeah $10,000 I stole
this is like a read it's like having the like a cash out voucher from a casino
yeah exactly which is what I do I have a cash voucher because I forgot to cash
out on the riverboat I have one for Caesars for a single cent yeah I have a
few I kind of want to just collect all my penny ones yeah well that's what you
you'll save them you bring them back. Oh see I just think it'd be funny to have like
maybe have like when I'm older like a scrapbook on my coffee table that just
like the cover is like maybe a photo of me and Jana at our wedding or something
and then you open it and it's all just one cent cash out vouchers from casinos. Yeah I feel like that's a good idea. Show it to my kids.
You could make like a museum like a gambling, a Caleb's
gambling museum. I cover an entire room. Yeah. Angela Sawyer in Boston, she has a
she had like her living room was just covered in parking tickets. Just do that
with yeah with Caesars vouchers for one single penny. I think I'd do that with
dollar bills. But then you can't spend that. You wouldn't be able to spend that. I live in a one million dollar home. No. You would live in a one dollar home.
You do it with one dollar bill. Yeah, because it's one dollar on the wall but I had to put it up a million times. No. You would put the same dollar up a
million times because you couldn't decide where to put it. Yeah, you'd be so
indecisive about it. Do you guys believe in Feng Shui? Yeah. Feng Shui. Feng Shui?
Feng Shui? You believe in Feng Shui? I never think... I don't know. Honestly, I didn't
believe in Feng Shui until that one time you brought it up that we were at
Wawa. Wawa is the strongest case for the existence of Feng Shui I've ever
seen. Because it just lacks it. It's, yeah, well it's the worst. You don't notice it.
So it's huge clog of energy completely. It's literally just stressful to be in
there at all.
It's like white noise. It's like you don't realize it till it's gone. Yeah. And
that's exactly how Wawa is.
Yeah. I mean I think I mean I don't I think it is like if you go into a house
that it like has like everything is like placed fucked up and there's like no
space like it feels claustrophobic and shitty. Like it feels bad. Like your
apartment feels bad to be in there. Like that's yeah there's an energy that
affects you.
Well it was way worse when we first moved in but now the living room is all about that.
I feel like I get distracted.
I feel like I'm recording.
It's bad feng shui.
I feel like I'm in a pinball machine when I'm at your house.
This apartment is pretty good feng shui I feel like.
Yeah that's why I'm never home.
I just realized that's probably why I'm never home.
It's feng shui.
Yeah.
Shit.
Feng shui is real.
Oh that's because the winter is coming up I'm going to be forced into my home.
Feng shui.
What are you saying?
What the fuck are you saying you idiot.
- Oh, fung, not fuck.
- Feng Shui.
F-E-N-G.
- Yeah, I know it's spelled.
- Feng.
- Fwong.
- Shui.
- No.
- Fwong.
- Don't like where this is going.
- Okay, it's kind of going Muppets right now.
That's better, that's a better direction.
That's funny.
- There we go.
- I did find, this just reminded me,
I found a website about Feng Shui.
- FengShui.com.
- Weeks ago, I was reading,
I was reading a bunch of articles about different Feng Shui,
so let me see if I can find it.
there's like a guidelines of like what kind of welcome mat you can have or not
have
so it's like a lake welcome mats with like like jokes on them those are really
like negative and i had fun yeah i will like it's a little like well it's a
little like a little you're having in the like a dot like a welcome mat
there's a little about like this was about the the colors and stuff to like
there's always yell and say i would agree any any sarcastic uh... the
sarcastic welcome at you and i guess what you're saying is saying a bad
Yeah, every single day you come home from work and you're like a reference you're treated with like fucking sarcasm or a fucking TARDIS on your
Welcome hat dude fuck that. It also depends on the direction of the door
That's like how what color the the mat is is like depends on which direction the door
I think I'm gonna forget believing in everything. Forget cutesy sayings and monogrammed mats. No one's home
No rugrats allowed and beware the cat are guaranteed to chase away positive
chief she or at least give a pause placing your name or initials under foot just
means people are stepping on a wiping their duty dirty shoes on the smith
jones residence every time they visit why would you want that
holiday match should be displayed with extreme care
no kids here clutter designs and removed promptly when the holiday period ends
faded bt flip-flops in february or happy holidays with points that is
in july signals that you're lazy or just don't care about the all-important portal
at the gate of your home
That's not a good message for guests or good fortune.
- I will say that on my street,
they put up, they already put up the Christmas decorations.
I'm getting bad vibes on the street.
- Sucks. - Dude, yeah.
- I'm getting really bad vibes.
That is a chi blocker.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Those are chi catchers.
They are catching the chi.
Put up like a turkey.
You don't have to put up like a Christmas tree already.
Bunch of jingle bells and fucking--
- I hate this. - I hate the smells.
- Christmas on November 1st is horrible.
- Yeah, that's the worst.
been up since since the 15th of October. Yeah, no, I saw it on Halloween and I was
getting mad. Yeah, no, it's pretty upsetting. Yeah. Yeah. And if they're
gonna be there at least turn them on. They just don't turn them on till
December. Yeah. It's like I'd rather, you know, I'd rather have some
beautiful, like colorful, beautiful, most beautiful lights, you know, nice lit-up
Star of David. Why not a cornucopia? Mm-hmm. Well, that's the other thing about
Thanksgiving is it's a colonizer holiday. So is Halloween.
ever think about that so it's Christmas you ever think about every holiday is
Easter Easter's the most colonizer holiday eggs fucking colonizing the
bushes in my back you know it is rabbit trying to come through indigenous
people's day yeah yeah big time big time dude yeah do you know why it's on that
day because of Columbus because of Columbus yeah yeah you know what he did
mmm no he discovered America that's right and they called they colonized that
holiday away from him yeah dude they stole it from him that's right that's a
good point he discovered that day he was living on that day for years and they
found it they're like oh this is our day and he had a beautiful culture on that
day of being off work and having 14 beers yeah and then all of a sudden
indigenous peoples are taking over. Now they're making us watch Buzzfeed videos instead.
That was a holiday where you have to watch Vox.com fucking Carlo tell you that
Columbus was actually not a beast. And where's my presents? Yeah also I don't really remember but I
think we used to get presents on Columbus Day. I remember. I think that's true.
I think everybody got a check. Everyone would dress up like a like the boat you
You could pick the Nina, the Pinta, or the Santa Maria,
and you would go around and you would find candy in bushes.
And now, you can't even do that because of cancel culture.
- Yeah, it's fucked up.
That used to be a day when the Santa, the Easter Bunny,
and the Tooth Fairy all worked together.
- They maybe took down my Columbus Day tree.
- Yeah? - They did.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- Were they using the wood to make a tiny boat?
- They made a kayak and they rode it in the street.
- Really?
hip hop real loud to
these kayaks that are always blasting hip hop. So when I'm trying to sleep
kayaks, go by these iced out the news,
sub woofers, God it's fucking annoying did horrible when they have the
hydraulics on the back of the canoe.
Yeah yeah, they're floating up and down, they're bobbing up and down like
in the water fucking annoying dude you know what the next future and like
vehicle invention what should be they should give up on like self-driving cars
and shit they should have walking boats yes not wheels on the boat either not
like a duck boat but like robotic legs on a boat you know we got to bring back
what fucking the thing where that you got four guys and they put you on their
shoulder oh yeah like a king that what happened with the holes the chair on the
poles. Why is the Pope the only guy who gets this now? Why can't I have... He has a
big bulletproof car with it looks like a condom. Yeah, why can't... Is that
what the Pope mobile looks like? Okay, how many people probably... so for every
10,000 like Honda Accords, probably four guys die. Yeah. So why
can't we just have those four guys? If you can afford 10,000 Honda Accords, you
could just... you should just be able to pay to have four guys do that forever from
for
- A huge part of that setup is suffering.
- Yeah, you need to--
- Is enslavement, that's very important.
- You need to be sitting there and feel how unlevel it is
because there's one person who's obviously--
- You need to be able to kick someone
in the back of the head if they're not carrying you.
- Yeah, and then they're carrying you
kind of like using the tension of their arm
to just carry you with their wrist.
You want it on the shoulder.
I wouldn't bruise there.
- I wouldn't go to McDonald's if the food was automated
'cause there's no one to yell at.
- Exactly.
also this food out here too fast put it back if they were salt if mcdonald's
if mcdonald's people i mean i i hesitate to call them people if they if they were
as as uh as uh cheery as chick-fil-a employees i would not go there yeah
absolutely because that is the way yeah the employees are happy but the food's
good mcdonald's the food is terrible but you're fucking mcdonald's mcdonald's is
like on the worst day of their life that's like the modern equipment going
to like McDonald's is the modern equivalent of like going to like the
gladiatorial games. Exactly. You just go to see somebody have literally the worst
day of their life and like experience like suffering in excess of what should
be possible. At a city McDonald's but a small town McDonald's I feel like they're even
worse. What are you talking about? Yeah the people working at a small town
McDonald's you think they're happy? You think they want to be there? I saw a
video of a McDonald's employees hit a blunt. Dude the small town
McDonald's of people the people and it was when I went I saw minutes to fucking
get there yeah true yeah and they're all owned by a guy who like yeah there's
every McDonald's in town looks as you got your porky pig it's all it's sort of
guy it's like a always a five-foot guy with a big fat face who's just
completely red oh yeah completely red like like he he has like like he's not
bald yet oh he's getting there though but he has working on it like he's got
like slicked back like the last like five hairs he has and he's filthy rich every
he thinks it's cool to he is like so many he's got like six ATVs once a month he
goes into every location he mistakes five different people he calls five different
people Jose there's one guy named Jose calls five different people Jose yeah
the guy named who's that Jose doesn't work there yeah he's a customer years
ago yeah yeah he but like he refuses to install any of the new cool McDonald's
like the panels, they still have the fucking greenhouse glass on it.
Yeah.
And when he goes in, he likes to give the assistant manager or the manager just shitty business
quips.
Yeah, he tells jokes.
Just advice.
Jokes and then advice that he has.
He tells jokes about-
He's like, "Well, I've been running this McDonald's for, I don't know, 10 years now, and what
I learned is that you gotta treat the customer, you gotta greet every customer with a smile."
That's right.
And then he turns to the other employee and he tells one joke about each woman in the restaurant.
He also thinks he's like a powerful smart business magnet because he opened the most
popular restaurant in the fucking world.
And he's like, "Yeah, I did pretty well for myself.
It was pretty smart of me.
I opened a restaurant that is like fucking selling water bottles in the Sahara."
He's Gus Fring.
Yeah, exactly.
he also he walks into the restaurant like a like the one shot like one take shot at the
beginning of a movie where like the guy's like walking through and like talking to everybody
and like oh dude he loves opening that counter door yeah exactly yeah like a camera's following
behind him yeah it's like he's about to go it's like the beginning of a louis special
short sleeve button down you can see like a pit stain starting to form yeah you just see
you see his tires his tires of his Subaru like just pull into the parking lot that
you see like his cowboy boots as he walks out and up the legs are way shorter than
you thought. Pants up past his head and then correct.
Yeah and then you just see him walk in and then yeah he's talking shit to
everybody he walks in he asked for a thing that's not on the menu that he
named after himself and they put like a urinal cake on a bun. Give me the big Brian!
Just give him the most disgusting thing of all time. Something that does not pass any sort of health
code. He wants like, he literally wants a burger with ice cream on it. A filet of fish with
the Big Mac sauce. Yeah, yeah. Something fucked up like that. Yeah, and then yeah he
reprimands somebody. Somebody else behind him in line tries to order the same thing and he
bans them from the restaurant for life. Yeah, he's like that's my thing. They don't
call it your fucking name. They call it the Brian. Hey fatso, get out of here. He's way
fatter. He's way fatter. Yeah. Oh man, just him trying to like have the employee like
take a bite. It's just like, come on, try it. It's good. They should put this on the
menu. I've been in talks to put this on the menu. I've been talking to regional headquarters.
I've been talking to corporate to put something on the menu that's just... Roy Croc, heard
of him yep I've been talking to him from there's just it's just one of the it's
just a soda cup filled with fries yeah and he's like I've been thinking this
would be great on him yeah he stole he just stole the idea from five guys right
he went to the five guys next door and he came in with a cup of fries that make
this I don't know what this is but it's so good see I think the burgers at five
guys are pretty good but uh can't beat you can't eat a free burger my I know
All this McDonald's needs is one guy, me. I know that guy in my hometown.
Yeah. The McDonald's man in my hometown. Mr. McDonald's? He went to my mom's church, yeah.
What was his name? His name was Tim. Okay. Yeah. He was exactly how I just, I mean,
just completely Porky the Pig. Yeah. I mean, he like waddles. He's one of those dudes who wears
jeans that go up to his nipples. Oh, hell yeah. He's got a power mask. Little white button down.
And this guy fucking, this guy would do anything for Jesus Christ.
Oh yeah.
Dude, he would fucking, he'd do anything except fucking sell McDonald's or pay taxes.
Yeah.
Oh man, the day that he comes in and works a shift for like 20 minutes.
Oh yeah, anything.
Yeah.
Dude, that's always the, you know what, you know that like stench that you start smelling in a
restaurant when the owner walks in plain clothes and just starts like asking people how their food
is?
Yeah.
Oh, it's horrible.
horrible. You know what the best though is if they're like hey is like
everything going good and you know this guy's like a millionaire and you're like
yeah could I get a could I get a sprite please and then that guy has to go get
you a sprite yeah that's so sick yeah that's the best feeling ever dude.
Yeah well I mean what you should when they walk up and ask you everything just be like
who are you? What are you doing? Why don't you have your getting fired. You're not dressed like everyone else.
They're not a waiter. Yeah, why don't you have a way? Yeah, why don't you have your skimpy little hooters shorts?
Oh, we're busy over here. Yeah
Yeah
that was like when I worked at Cracker Barrel and like the corporate guys had to come in because they were like
There's like a shit ton of fights that kept happening between the kitchen. Mm-hmm
the one of one of the guys like
Checked my bag to see if I was stealing food
Like like one of the like this he thought he's gonna fucking open up see pork and beans. Yeah the brim
I don't know I ordered food before I my shift ended and the guy was like uh yeah
you know just company policy I gotta check that real quick and I was like man
what what yeah like Sebastian Maniscalco like next time that happens to me and
one of the managers come up and they're in plain clothes I'm gonna pretend I
don't know they work there I'm gonna be like you should get on this we're
planning on bombing this fucking dropping a stick of dynamite in the
kitchen running. You should get in on this. Yeah, we're gonna put this in all the deep fryers.
Yeah, or also like a guy comes up he's like he's like I like can I get you
anything and you just since he's not dressed you think he's like messing
around you're like yeah yeah I also work here can I get you anything? I don't know.
Get up you walked every table.
I'm that guy. I think I work here. We're pretending to work here today. It's
gonna be really funny.
Yeah, yeah, dude, I
the guy who owned the Jersey Mike's that I used to work at he he was he was like
the hardest worker ever, though yeah yeah he was like it was clear that he
he opened the store with his wife and then his wife left him. So all he had
restaurant and he was like trying to pay fucking like alimony and shit and he was
just drunk he probably worked like 60 hours a week my bet my best uh my go-to
is the number seven that one I can make in under six seconds like that he taught
me how to fucking roll up the sandwiches bro yeah whoa to skill I will have for
the rest of my life oh yeah dude me too I know how to fold the so you know it's
a story to read I know how to fold the the paper for the Peters at Clover food
lab I can I can still do that in my sleep yeah you can't do that you're so I can
do that my you can't do anything you guys get I can get that sandwich out in six
seconds flat you can't not in your sleep in your I can do it in my sleep no you
can't oh another thing about that Cracker Barrel guys he used to call me
chief that's cool me off so much I don't know why just like him just be like
chief I was a chief like have I told you guys about that my my friend's dad who
hates being called chief no oh yeah I know maybe I don't think I said on the
podcast, but I have a friend whose dad is like Puerto Rican, and when he was
like at work some guys started calling him Chief because he like like just as a
thing that he said, but this guy's dad took it as this guy thought that he
was Native American. It pissed him off so much that he like tried to like fight the
guy at work about it, and then and so everyone knew that this guy hated being
being called Chief. And then my older brother, one time when they were like
sixteen, he like brought some other sixteen year old over to this guy's
house, and before he met the guy's dad, he was like, 'Just so you know, this guy,
he doesn't like being called by his name, he only likes being called Chief.' And so
the guy walks out to like meet them in the driveway, and my brother's friend is
like, 'Hey, nice to meet you Chief,' and then this grown man just punched this
sixteen year old in the face.
He got so mad about it.
so cool yeah he's like not native american getting so offended of like by
getting called yeah native american that you punch somebody in the point a child
yeah insane you know another really good like like before you meet somebody prank
is my my dad my uncle like did this to my dad before it's like he was like
bringing his friends over to like hang with my dad and but like I guess before
before the hair on he like told all the people like just so you know like he's
like super hard of hearing and he's like really insecure about it so just like
talk really loud and like but don't bring it up like don't like hi there
like how are you like what the fuck is going on that's so good yeah yeah it's
a good that type of shit so funny it's so funny it's the best it's the best
like the just making somebody feel like they're in a dream. Yeah.
Like they're going crazy. Yeah. Yeah. So fucking funny.
Yeah. It is good. I got like a hair in my eye.
No. That's called an eyelash. No. Or I don't have those. Should we do this list?
No. I don't got those. Yeah. We could do. We're doing. You ever
thought about cutting your eyelashes off? Speaking of thinking,
this is a thinking man's episode. Yeah. Which I'm sure you could tell
already. I mean we've already tackled a lot of serious. Some
- Heady concepts.
- Yeah.
- We already basically just (mumbles)
- Like this thinkers.
- This is--
- Thinkers of stinkers.
- Top 10 mind blowing philosophical ideas to think about.
And it says,
philosophy has always been a weird subject
to wrap your head around.
And this list contains some of the most mind blowing
philosophical comments, concepts and ideas
for a person to think and wonder about.
- I think this might cause,
This could cause a crisis in my life
if somebody's blow my mind too hard.
- This could cause the listeners to have a brain blast.
- I'm smart enough that I could handle this,
but I think some listeners may wanna turn this off.
- If you have somebody who's very mentally weak
in the car with you, maybe a child,
you should probably turn this off.
- Yeah, or put the child out of the car.
- Or put the child out of its misery.
- Just put it out of the--
- Put the-- - Just snuff it.
- Put the child-- - Just put it out
like a candle. - Put the child in a home.
- Yeah, just snip that, the thread of fate.
sever it. Number one...
Sever the child.
The sorites.
So I looked this up.
Paradox.
So this is pretty genius.
Wait, no, this person just
explains it. That's fine.
Would you allow someone to cut off one of your fingers
if they paid you one cent?
Well, boys, answer that, please.
Yes.
finger. Yes, you also get to choose what kind of penny it is. You could choose like a million
dollar penny. Exactly. I feel like a missing pinky is a cool enough look that I'd do it
for a cent. I could make that work. If I would lose my left hand pinky, if it was painless,
I would probably just do it. Yeah, why not? Like I would never use this finger and that
would just be cool. It would be cool. It would be interesting. It's a conversation starter
and they'd be like, "Oh, how'd you lose that?" and be like, "For a penny." Honestly, I could
probably get like a 15 minute comedy central special if I lost probably yet
the comedian with yeah with just with who only everyone yet the only way
wondering how this happened the only basically I made a deal with a guy on a
website and I got one cent for it so nobody remembers your name you're just
you're the one pinky yeah you know that one guy with one pinky that one
exactly and yeah probably not okay I restart would you allow someone to cut
your fingers if they paid you for one cent? Probably not. How about four billion
dollars? I know I would and I'm confident that you probably would too. This
establishes two things that there are sums of money that you will accept to
cut off your finger and there are sums of money that you will decline to cut off
your finger because of how money works. The difference between the highest figure
you'll say no to and the lowest figure you'd say yes to is exactly one cent.
These numbers objectively exist but they're impossible to grasp. Pick the
lowest number you can think of accepting and tell me honestly that you'd decline a
a counter offer of exactly one cent less. So that is not an explanation of this at all.
So from what I understand about the SoWrites paradox, the SoWrities paradox, is that this
whole thing is just would you suck a dick for one million dollars.
Yeah.
That's the paradox.
They had to reframe it for books.
Uh huh.
Yeah, you can't say that.
That's been around since caveman times.
I know.
How many rocks would you suck a dick for?
since before money. Yeah, would you suck a dick for ten rocks?
They were, yeah, well, they were like, would you suck a dick for a million
dollars? And they were like, I don't know what dollars is, but yes.
Yeah, we haven't invented dollars. Well, they started with that question and
then they were like, I guess we finally should invent dollars. Yeah, yeah.
It's high time we put something... Yeah, we've had shekels and rupees,
we need to... But let's just finally, let's get dollars out of the way.
And that's why they started America.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So that someone could get their dick sucked
for one million dollars. - Yeah, someone's been asking
for quite a long time.
Nobody'd ever gotten their dick sucked before.
- The first millionaire only existed
because he wanted to get sucked so bad.
- Which one is higher, your suck a dick number
or your lose a pinky number?
- They're exactly the same.
- Yeah.
- They're both pure pain.
- I think the pinky one's probably higher
'cause like maybe I would miss it.
- Yeah, pinky, that's a more permanent effect on your life.
Also the suck a dick question is always,
I've always been confused about what kind of time frame
we're working with here.
Do I have to suck a dick forever?
- I've never thought about that.
- If the guy--
- If it's forever, I'm not gonna do it.
- 'Cause what if that would be the genie twist, right?
- Yeah, 'cause it works like the lottery
where it's like, oh, you can get the $1 million
in one lump sum over the course of your life.
- A dollar a day.
Yeah, I wonder like--
You have to suck a dick every day.
- But like if the guy has like,
like what if they're like,
okay suck that guy's dick to completion
and it's like somebody who has no feeling below their waist
and I'm just like sucking a limp dick forever
for a million dollars, that's not good to me.
- I guess if it's a genie asking the question,
should probably say no.
- Genies are tricky.
I'll say genies are tricky people.
- Here's another question.
So if it is the lottery thing,
would you suck one dick a year for like $33,000 a year?
- Probably.
- Until you get the million?
- If it was like 10 minutes, like yeah, I don't care.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Well, 33,000, that's maybe not enough.
- Well, I mean 3,300.
- Oh, no.
(laughing)
No.
If it was like--
- 3,300,000.
- If it was a--
- $33,000 isn't enough?
I have this Calculia. I can't go past. We just be it would just be because
that's not enough to just like live on comfortably. It would just so you want
to suck a dick and also that you want that to be your job. Yeah, is what
you're saying. I do want to be a
yeah, I do that yeah, if I like a supplemental thing like you want that to
be a support. If I had one if I had to yeah, because I like doing nothing. So I
had if I had one like fucking John that I sucked off like once a year yeah and he
can he was like the rich Saudi Prince or something yeah yeah did I do that yeah a
hundred percent like like sixty grand I would do that to you like public school
teacher salary for like fucking sucking a guy off one day I'll even do I'll do
all day like I'll have a three hundred and sixty four day year you know what I
like and then just one day is just a just a wash just cuz I just fucking sucked him
yeah but then that's the thing think about like dude would you know what day
is dick suck day that would be the big thing to me that's why yeah I think it
would just like sprung up on you at rain I wouldn't drop everything going on like
if I if I was like like what if I'm like about to walk down the aisle on my
wedding day yeah and then I get like in my all I get the big red phone on my
desk range. Well that's if you don't have a job, if that's your job you got to do it.
I guess on call. It plays that I got five on it remix from us. You're waiting, you're
walking down and then your phone just goes dun dun dun. You're just like oh shit I'm
going to suck a dick today. I think the big thing would be if it was 33,000 and I had
to do it once every year I would be worried that I would have some kind of like what if
What if I got really successful and then I'm making like 800 grand a year, but then still
one day of the year I have to go suck a guy's dick for 30k?
You have to?
I think it's a binding contract.
I think you can...
Binding contract like $25,000 for over four years.
Yeah, yeah.
I think, yeah, if there was a guy...
I would totally...
If there was a guy who did that...
Suck off a guy for $25,000.
Let's call them patches. If there's a guy in patches who's hiring me to do that once a year,
he probably would sue me for everything I have if I didn't suck his dick.
Yeah.
Because we had a binding thing.
Yeah, true.
Okay, that's why the pinky thing is better because it's one and done.
Yeah.
You lose one pinky, they're not going to reattach it and take it back off.
So you'd rather suck a dick four times for $25,000 over four years.
- It's been one time for 100,000?
- What, really?
- I did the math wrong, I thought that added up to 1 million.
(laughing)
It would be $250,000 four times, that's up to a million.
- Dude, you know I can't do peak numbers.
(laughing)
- You'd rather get $100,000 than a million.
- Yeah, I'd probably--
- Yeah, I'm lowering the price.
- $25 four times, that's a million.
I would do it for $25 over the course of one weekend.
This is the number two mind blowing philosophical thought.
Linguistically, it's possible for two people to have a conversation that each believes to
be meaningful but actually has no meaning because one or both of them don't know what
they're talking about.
This happens to me all the time.
This yeah, I feel like that's, you probably experience this a lot.
I experience this every day of my life.
Would you consider it to be philosophical when it happens?
Indubitably, I do.
Mind-blowing, in fact.
I concur that, um, this...
Yeah, continue.
Keep going.
I can't keep talking about that.
I cannot say that.
I cannot keep...
I cannot continue this line of...
I cannot keep speaking that way, in that regard.
He said something... what did you say last night?
Rather.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. He said rather.
All I said was rather.
I had never heard you say rather before.
You said something and then corrected yourself by being like rather and then the correct thing and I was like it really
It was like a sore thumb dude. It's really stuck out. I do that like all the time
You're changing dude. You're going Hollywood on me. Yeah, you started to say rather
the fuck man what
So hard once because I I think I was asking if we would bring the mics to North Carolina
Or something or like what did you say? I forget what I said. He said something crazy
I said, oh, yeah, like like ultimately like it doesn't
Ultimately it does not matter to me
Yeah, and then I I did not know I was getting flamed for that for saying ultimately
Yeah
Because I would say there's probably not a higher stake word to set up a sentence with then ultimately
because that that kind of establishes that it's the most important thing.
And then for you to follow it up by like, it doesn't matter.
Even better. I searched it in my message. It wasn't ultimately doesn't matter. It was
a home turf episode would be good, but ultimately pointless.
Wow.
Ultimately pointless.
That was a Boston thing.
Ultimately, ethereal.
Yeah.
we got him already at that we did i don't talk like that we can remind said i
said so you said but ultimately pointless me yes i said studying for the s_a_t_'s
you said fruitless and futile attempts to record would be
i find it would be rather in a minute should you say our equipment yonder
and patrick said
I'm downstairs
no, you know, I was just fuming on the tree. Yeah, it's like no fuck like why
the fuck did I say that I thought that made so much I thought oh fuck. I
thought that makes sense. Number three most philosophical concept ever is no
matter what you do you will be plagued by regret for example if you marry you will
regret it but if you don't you will regret that too
damn this person sounds sad yeah this idea also gives you the advice live for
what you have not for what you could have had yeah live free or die here's
here's a comment from Rocco I could express my thoughts but if I do everyone
will think that I'm one of those people who rambles on if I don't people will
think I'm one of those people who looks through lists and never vote on anything
If I write this people will see it on my profile and think I'm weird if I don't include this in my wording people might
Have no idea what I'm talking about just like the first item on this list which is about people not understanding what you're saying never mind
I'm definitely one of those people who rambles
Morocco took to me Benadryl yeah
Morocco got a visit from the shadow man. You know I've been reading all about that shit's so funny
yeah, I knew some people in high school who did Benadryl and like fucking like
DXM and shit. But I didn't realize how crazy it is. It's so funny, dude. It's like an objectively
terrible drug that people just do because it's like kids just do it because it's in
their house.
Yeah, because it's easy.
You can't get weed yet. You don't know where to get weed.
I was thinking about like we used to like the big thing in my group growing up was like
2,5-I like inbomb shit, you know, like the research chemicals that are like insanely
strong just make you crazy yeah and I was like I guess that's kind of the same
thing that and like k2 yeah I didn't I never did been a drill and shit that's
you know yeah or like yeah I was always a no it is the funniest one I tried to
smoke nutmeg you see you don't smoke you boil it you boil it you boil and drink
I heard I heard from answers that you smoke it
answers was trying to they threw you off yeah I remember reading trip reports for
nutmeg and it's like they're all like they're all like I had a nightmare in
in real life and then there's there was one that was like I went blind for two
hours and fell down
one of the Bennett. I did a deep dive on it yesterday. One of the Benadryl ones.
I saw a guy took four thousand milligrams of Benadryl and then he like
immediately like lost consciousness and then woke up and looked he like looked
down at the couch and saw his body and then he walked outside and his entire
family was a beat was being crucified on his front lawn like on crosses and they
were like why'd you do this to us and then he walked inside and he had to
fight his dog and then
it's so funny that just like that that does that Benadryl yeah and then he
went into he said he went into a white void of like that that episode of
Spongebob where he like time and he says that he was there for seven years and
that he like it like replaced seven years of his real memory and then he just
up in the hospital and he was like don't do this drug like I they said that I
have like I'm like mentally disabled now and also you have to do dialysis every
week people still do it I mean it's just like you're just trying to kill yourself
I guess yeah yeah it's just a horrible way to die that's awesome
you guys don't want to do it when I smoke nutmeg I put it in a post-it note
That's just like a, that's like a, that's like making a potion in your backyard.
Did it do anything to you?
That's happened to me multiple times when I was like in the eighth grade.
I think I like dissected a cigarette butt that like it was in an ashtray and put it
in a post-it note and tried to smoke it.
And I did that with tea too, but every time I like, I was like, you know, trying to like
roll it up in the post-it note because the sticky like the adhesive thing and
like I would like try to like smoke it and then like tilt my head back like
just a little bit and just like inhale everything that was in the post-it note.
Did you get high? No, didn't work. You have to do a lot of nutmeg.
One time when I was in the fourth grade, just remember this, got in a
lot of trouble for this because I heard the term smoking grass so I went outside
and I cut a bunch of grass from the ground and I put it in a piece of paper
and I tried to lay it down. You were doing this as a fucking nine-year-old? That's like honestly
really impressive that you're not a drug addict. I was doing it when I was nine. And then I think like...
that's some like million little pieces just blades of I think my brother and I
shared a closet at the time because we like shared a room and you got it how do
you get a trouble I mean like how do you get my mom was pissed cuz like I was
burning shit yeah I was burning just like the look on her look the look on her
face of just disappointment I was like trying that's like worse than our than
my kids cuz like if you if your kid is nine years old and you find like a joint
in his hat in his room that's an actual problem well it's a problem but also
you're like he's kind of like competent if you like do even if you can get that
- Yeah, yeah.
- You're holding a buy weed and fucking roll a joint?
- Not a piece of notebook paper with the grass on it.
(laughing)
How did I get into college?
- I don't know.
(laughing)
I don't fucking know, dude.
I don't know how you're alive, honestly.
Yeah.
- You know it's the blue lines that get you high.
- Yeah.
- On the notebook paper.
- That's true, actually, yeah.
- You can feel it, 'cause as you smoke it,
it'll be a period where you're not high,
and then it gets to the blue line and you go,
whoa, that ink.
- What?
I was watching the Woodstock movie and that's what inspired me to do it.
That is like honestly one of the stupidest things I've ever heard in my life.
That is so funny.
I was a fucked up kid.
Fucked up but not like a cool jaded.
No you're just like.
I was just impressionable.
you were like just impressionable you're like a dog's yeah that's insane.
I can't believe I just remember damn fuck man dude that was I mean my my
older brother almost getting in trouble for it.
Let me be having to be like it was me.
I'm sorry.
I admit that I have the wave of disappointment that walked over my
mom's face.
so funny number four is the idea of moral luck and how it affects the goodness of
people getting getting banned like from listening to the who as a nine-year-old
because you fucking put grass you made a taco out of grass and notebook paper it
definitely wasn't rolled well it was like it was like twisted at the end like
just imagining what it looked like to my parents like them finding it being like
is that a joke and then like inspecting further and just being like what the
fuck not not a joke it's just nothing yeah like might as well not even I mean
he's just like pocket yeah it's so funny I don't really know what this means I
don't care number five this one's out this one's smart number five the notion
notion of solipsism. The very notion of solipsism. I feel myself becoming a bit
intrigued by this item upon this list. Solipsism is just it's all in your brain.
Solipsism is yeah you're the only person that exists. Yeah I'm pretty sure that's
true. Yeah I'm pretty sure it's true too. Yeah I think it's me though. Yeah I think
it's also you. What? Wait Pat. I mean I messed up it's me yeah it's me. I have
internal thoughts. Who's the only real person me or you? Probably me. What? No it's me.
He didn't hesitate either. I don't know. You guys are giving me bad vibes. I feel like
it's now I didn't actually think that now I kind of feel like it's true. Yeah it's true
not true. It's true for me. You are covering your tracks. I don't like that at all. This
could row here's a rock. This could be true in your case anyway. I mean I'm not real. I'm
I'm a bloody cartoon bloody cartoon. You hope he's not bloody. Yeah, that's a
hope yeah, but I'm a happy tree. Yeah, what is this the Simpsons tree house of
blood? Yeah, what's this the South Park Kenny special spectacular? He gets
blood all over yeah, because all because something happened to him. Here's the
thing a lot of people make they make fucking they make two hour fucking
videos on YouTube about how Marge is mistreated and about how she should be
you know she's need has to like some guy who made like a 45 minute like an hour
45 minute video of him like revisiting iCarly yeah and they talk about how all
these women in cartoons and shit are not not always on TV aren't treated well how
about Kenny that's right Kenny gets fucking killed by a by a spike every
episode should get his own show where he gets to live and thrive exactly he get a
show there should be he should never die again yeah he should get like his own
his own like he's like a She-Ra yeah yeah I would jump in front of a bullet for
Kenny I wouldn't yeah why do you know cartoon do you know there's like South
Park like role players really oh yeah yeah those are great yeah like like LARP
they'll be yeah no like on like Twitter and stuff and they'll be like they'll be
like like hi my name is Michael Cartman I just moved to the town I'm really
excited to make new friends. I'm Eric's younger cousin. Yeah. What? Really?
Like inventing new characters? Yeah, making like, like what's it OC's? Yeah.
Yeah, South Park OC's and like, what's OC? Original character. Some people make like
their own like Sonic character and stuff. Oh, it's like, oh I know the Sonic thing.
But for South Park. Yeah, they do that for South Park. Like Sonic characters. People do it for
everything. You know why they do it for South Park? It makes more sense if it's a video game, but like for South Park, that is so, like, makes no sense.
South Park because there's like fucking 500 like South Park yourself fucking flash
games it's easy it's really easy. Sonic you gotta hand draw that shit. I texted I
texted my mom asking her if she remembers finding the grass joint in my
closet and she didn't remember that I was that young she says you were that
young I hope I beat your ass. Nice. It probably happened. I'm sure she did dude.
He's looking for excuses. What's this a blade of grass?
Being the show your gigs they just fucking had
You probably thought this was a toilet paper so stupid
Fucking sick number six is possibly the most intriguing yet fascinating entry. Okay
Number six is you can have a doppelganger millions or even billions of light-years away
whoa I don't think so I have a few doppelgangers it's you have many I would
say most people kind of look like yeah yeah I think I think Streeter said it
but every country has a Patrick yeah that's true because there was that um
there was that did you guys see that video like the like there's like a
really fat cop on tick-tock now in like the Ukraine they look like you looks
like me. Really? Yeah. You just have a very, you just look very plain and kind of
nothing. Yeah, it's kind of just like a blur. Yeah. Have you seen, you know
like, you know Slenderman? Yeah. Yeah. Not Slenderman. Mm-hmm. You just, yeah, you
just have like kind of no facial features that stand out at all. Like a Lego, the back of a
Lego guys. Yes, exactly. It looks like you're gonna turn around and there'll be an actual
guy on that side. Yeah, you kind of just look like a Halloween mask like anybody could purchase
it and put it on their face. You know, the worst comparison I think is right now you
kind of look like a pumpkin with your hat and your and your that. I've always wanted
look like a pumpkin. Really? Yeah I can tell. Yeah. Well if I looked like a
pumpkin my hat would be green and my face would be orange. That's a good point.
You also, you clearly have a pumpkin. Like friggin Donald Trump. Mm-hmm.
Well he loves his green hats. All his supporters are wearing green hats all
the time with the words on it. Quick pause Cameron. Yeah and fire trucks they're green too.
I will say. Cam you're on fire today. Yeah. You're crushing. I will say, remember
the mega jack-o'-lantern hat? Dude, honestly dude, every single piece of, let's admit it
dude, if Virgil Abloh came out with the mega shit, that would have been on, everybody would
have been on it. Oh yeah. That shit, it just like fucking, just serif text on it. It's a
cool hat. It's cool as fuck. Yeah, I think it's been four years now, I think we can say
it. I think we can say it with it. Dude, I'm wearing it right now. I'm wearing it right
Dude, I wanted to grow my hair out. I show you guys this. I saw it the other day. I think I'm just pretty good
I'm going for it. Dude. I'm can I see can you can you like lean the top of your head? Yeah, let me
You have to go for it full halal car. I'll go for it. Oh
Man, yeah, yeah, you're growing it back out. Not really cuz I think I can't stand to do it much longer
But no, please
Get to q-tip level q-tip level baldhead
Oh, really?
You think I should do that?
Like, like, whenever I would shave my head and I would just have, like, completely, like,
rounded hair.
I don't remember that.
You don't remember that?
I shaved my head, like, a year ago.
No, I'm gonna get, I kinda wanna grow it out and go like, uh, like, like, Walton Goggins.
Oh, yeah, you should just shave the, the, the part up front.
Uh-huh.
So that I have a nice back, like, really far back hairline.
Yeah, yeah.
That would be sick.
Oh, you get, like, the, the Chairman Mao.
That's the problem is that I still have hair at the front.
So it's, it's bad.
I want to have just a hair, like no hair until halfway down.
That's probably a good idea.
Yeah.
Maybe go full fryer tuck on them.
Oh dude.
I don't know if they could handle it dude.
Yes sir.
I think I might make too many women fucking cream and squirt walking down the street.
Could be.
Fucking cream and squirt.
Well that's the thing, like maybe people, like, I don't know, maybe people are just
so used to the bald now.
You know?
Maybe they are.
I'm used to the bald.
Yeah.
I look in the, I don't even.
I think you grow your hair out, I shave my head.
No.
that's it I'm trapped with the worst hair then I'll just regrow my hair it won't
be a big deal don't shave your head yeah I'm like I might shave my head too we
could I mean that was actually that's better than just two of us having it
all three of us had shaved heads I'm not but only one of us is bald that'd be
cool our seven is the problem of induction I don't know what that mean I
mean well that makes sense that you wouldn't understand this one yeah I
I actually understand it perfectly.
That's right, me and Pat understand it perfectly.
No, you know, it's that this guy is such a mental moron that he phrased it so simply,
with such simplicity rather, I should say, instead of that.
The words of a dimwit seem to ring true to many.
I concur.
He concurred.
And you can turd.
You can turd.
Number eight is slugs are just snails without homes.
Damn.
Is that to be?
Throw this on a snort tea.
It's a bit of a drop.
Right quick.
about a fucking a bad welcome mat cheese style true yeah yeah I get some more
chi also like what she you have to figure out what direction I mean you go
to the guy for half you can meditate I think honestly I didn't believe in chi or
energy and spaces until we started going to casinos yeah and then I feel like
you believe in a strong literally I literally could like if I follow the
system of just believing in myself and my instinct.
Energy literally is real.
Yeah, people, yeah.
People try and discredit it and make it seem stupid with like stuff like aura photography.
That's stupid.
That's dumb.
I like aura photography.
It's dumb.
That shit's dumb.
But energy, you can't tell me you've never like walked into a place and like felt energy
before.
It doesn't matter if it's like, oh, it's actually just your, it's actually because you don't
like the store.
I was like, well, duh, I don't like it
'cause it has bad energy.
- One time I was in Provincetown, I walked into a--
- Don't say there was bad energy in Provincetown.
- You are a weird energy from some women.
- No, there is a, I went into a place
that was selling gems and stones,
like a place where people go to buy vibes.
- Yeah.
- And they had a big Allman Brothers tapestry
and I was like, why the fuck do they have--
- Bad.
- Why do they have an Allman Brothers tapestry?
- That's bad chi.
- Yeah, like Grateful Dead, that one,
I mean, it's a staple, it makes sense,
but the Allman Brothers peach thing,
I was like man what the flick it's it says all my brothers - and then like the lady behind the counter went like
I'm sorry. I just have to go outside real quick and
To her co-worker and she was like, oh why what's what's going on?
She's like, I don't know just some people in the store have negative energies like stood outside
Meditated like in the front of you or cuz of you dude you you like attacked her
I'm a negative force in this world. I
Deplete energy you you're a vampire on women
No suck their energy out yeah, you drain them you just prove a vampire everybody dude
I don't say that as women come on. I'm a vampire. Why would you rather say everybody?
It's I just half the people cuz I'm depleting energy what I go in I destroy vibes
I'm your vibe destroyer. I'm a vibe destroyer. I'm a you're a vibe cannon mm-hmm
An energy print I don't believe in energy except an energetic predator, right? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
What call me the word not okay?
negative predator
Negative predator sounds like a
Really good or been yeah, that's that's yeah. Yeah, I don't believe in energy. Also. They be called for it because they were a hardcore
Yeah
Number nine, what I may be, this one will blow your mind, what I may be seeing is
green may be seen by someone else as red, it's just that we both have been taught
since childhood to call that particular color green. True. That's true.
One time my brother said that to me when I was a kid and then I was like
what are you talking about and he just said butterfly effect. So then I watched
that movie, I watched that movie and I thought that was gonna be like a part of
- No, no, no. - It's not at all.
- Dude, you-- - Butterfly effect.
- I saw that movie so many times when I was a kid.
- That's a mind crusher, dude.
- Yeah, dude, when you're like--
- When you're a kid, dude, that's like the first--
- Like, when you stay home from school,
they play that on FX so much.
- 'Cause you're not smart enough to see
what's like philosophical about the Matrix,
but there's something that is just so in your face,
like annoying about it.
When you're a kid, it's all you understand, so.
- Dude, the butterfly effect blew my goddamn mind
when I was nine.
- Hey, it blew that pregnant lady's mind
when she opened up that mailbox, remember that?
- Yep.
She exploded.
And then the dog in the bag, dude.
Dude, D in the B.
Yeah.
Dude.
I never saw it.
I've seen the Butterfly Effect probably a hundred times.
What?
I think it's probably-
A hundred times?
Probably 50 times.
Ballpark, I think that sounds-
50 times.
50 times at two hours each.
You spent a hundred hours of your life watching-
Well, that made for a TV movie.
Oh, okay.
So 90 minutes.
It made the edited for TV version of the Butterfly Effect.
You saw Kutcher tear it up-
Yes.
90 minutes for a hundred, 50 times.
- That, in 2007, 2008, that was on FX all the fucking time.
- They cut out all the cool shit though.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, pretty sad.
- Mm-hmm, like the swears.
- Yeah, I love the swears.
- Yeah.
- That shit's so cool.
- That scene where he wakes up and he's going like,
"Oh, oh, oh," remember that?
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh, the dog is in the bag and the dad's a pedophile
and then, don't spoil everything about it.
- Yeah, I get that, I mean, but what happened in the movie?
I get that you're, that was your life.
number one the theory of six degrees of separation that is fascinating I hope
Kevin Bacon doesn't I get fascinated when I think of something like that yeah
yeah who could we let's who do we have let's nail this Elvis so my no Elvis my
uncle was Elvis somebody else somebody else yeah okay well well I'm at like
that Kevin that's one degree so I know Patrick yeah Patrick two degrees for us
one no I met him yeah I know Patrick one degree met him well I mean the obvious
one is Kevin Bacon I know he's right he's over there yeah one degree it's one
it's like 30 feet I can map this one I can actually map this one my mom watches
city on the hill one degree mm-hmm yeah mm-hmm let's just try Hitler one degree
you know what no whoa maybe for you it's seven for me it's outside I barely lost
but I did lose yeah I'm pretty proud of that 25 degrees from Hitler 25 degrees
from Hitler I hope he's burning at 9 I have 360 degrees from Hitler yeah I got
to turn around and walk away from him mm-hmm you're facing him directly now 60
360 degrees same direction you started from now. Yeah, I don't think so yeah,
no because you spun around so you could see your whole body. I'm a hundred
eighty degrees from Hitler turn around walk the other way. I don't want to be
anywhere near that guy. You walk all the way around the earth, three hundred
sixty degrees, you come up behind him and you hug him and you turn to put my
hands on his eyes like this. Yeah, guess who yeah, you turn who in you turn
three hundred and sixty degrees and then you put your arm at forty five degrees.
you see him yeah down to pointed his badass shoes.
Say what are those? Yeah and I say what are those? I say damn. These are my boots. I say
damn Hitler. That's boot. Hitler back at it again. Here's a really fascinating one from
the contenders. Okay. Number fifteen, we're both heaven and hell. That's not true. It's
fascinating. I'm just Caleb. And here's the- And I'm so sweet. Here's the last one. This
This one is probably the most mind blowing of all.
Number sixteen, rule based systems are inherently chaotic due to the principle of exquisite sensitivity
to initial conditions.
I completely concur.
Yeah, I concur totally and utterly.
I would like to respectfully disagree but keep it open for debate.
Okay.
Salutations.
And adios.
Yeah.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Bye.
(mumbling)
- Do we have a thing to, oh no wait,
the tickets to that are sold out, who cares, bye.