Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- You're a crap monster.
(explosion)
- So which Impractical Joker did you--
- I was Patrick.
I think I was a guest.
I had a dream for, we kind of just jumped into this.
I had a dream I was a part of the Impractical Jokers.
- Yep.
- And we were doing a Venmo sponsored challenge.
- No way.
- And we had to fit the word Venmo as many times
into a conversation.
That I cannot imagine a more hilarious challenge.
Yeah.
That's a good challenge.
So I'll be, alright, pretend I'm a stranger, okay?
Like give me an example of the show.
I don't remember.
Come on.
Do it.
We'll just do it.
You already get the concept.
Okay, so hey.
Hi, welcome to Target.
Can I pay you in Venmo?
No, you're horrible.
Okay, wait.
Let me pay it in Venmo.
You're so bad at this.
If it's about hitting the maximum.
Okay, go, yeah, yeah.
Hi, welcome to Target.
Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo, Venmo,
yeah hi I'm a target and move in a little bit of a bend over and over and over
here's a hundred million dollars I'd like to blowjob you and I'd like to get
married no Ben that's the punishment on the show
it's a nice punishment Sal has to get married and a 1 million dollar blowjob
yeah Sal who hates sex yeah yeah Sal volcano has to get a blowjob
he's a he's a
Know I hate blowjobs every single episode the the punishments like and you have to you have to suck the entire writers rooms dicks
No, Casey Jost Colin Jost's brother is like head writer of impractical jokers - - superior comedy minds
Mm-hmm - - beautiful wasp comedy brains Colin and Casey created the two greatest
What do you think their third brother's name is?
Charlemagne Jost.
Crinthony.
Yeah.
It could be Caleb.
Crinthony's a little better.
Yeah.
It could be me.
You never know.
Not you.
Caleb Jost.
I feel like I got a Jost thing going on.
Oh wow.
Look at that eyebrow.
Uh, mmm.
Like that.
Okay.
You know?
Yeah.
Do it again.
There is a camera in here.
My mom said I had to go to bed because I was up too late.
Uh, how about no, mom?
Whoa.
Whoa like that yeah yeah good yeah wow good pretty good jokes there I'm pretty
much I'm in practical just maybe yeah I'm practically Joester when you think
about it who I'm so close to Joester damn yeah they won't let me do it I think I
think they should do do you think they have like impractical jokers like in
other countries the way that they do the office definitely yeah yeah or like they
have SNL in Mexico and shit yeah yeah have you ever seen the the opening credits
for SNL SNL Quebec no oh man the names in that are so good really yeah it's just
like the most like Quebec quad names introducing dole is st. Germain Guillaume
home love flam poster poofy gee-gee
do you you aahj
it's cargo that's an all that no that's Kenan Thompson in the tub that'd be a
good yeah we should sir s and oh you just said it exists fuck mm-hmm God
there let me look up because there's one name that was really fucking good was it
was a poopoo Dubois it was poopoo to block but that is that is a really good
name. Crunch Decapitan! Pierre, Pierre-Luc Funk. Pierre! Yeah. Like that guy already
sound... Jean-Luc, Claude, Pierre, Guillaume. There's a thousand first names. Pierre-Luc Funk. Peter-Luc Funk?
Pierluke Funk. Funky probably. Pierluke Funk.
They only have one that's not... wait is it... it's like... It's SNL Quebec and they...
It's not just SNL Canada? No. Dude, Quebec is one of the most fucked up places in the world man.
Can you imagine being born... there's a lot of people in Quebec. Imagine being born in Canada and you
have to speak French. Well there's a lot of people who are like from Quebec who
like didn't have parents that spoke French they're like from some other
learning French in school well exactly you grow up until you're like five or
six just speaking English all sudden you get to school it's like you're a
fucking France also you're gonna get hit in the head so you know how to speak
French exactly yeah yeah yeah I think that's a it's a truly evil part of the
world yeah every I mean every place should just be one language plus Spanish
that's how I feel yeah right absolutely be the main language and then they also
to speak Spanish there because it's funded. I don't know why as a kid I
thought that they spoke French in Canada because it was colder up there. Like
France. Yeah cold like France. I don't know why I thought that was the reason
and then I learned about freaking colonialism. Oh wait it was. Yeah I'm
going there. I'm fucking going there. Do you have anything else about the
thought process there about what you mean by it was cold so they spoke French?
I kind of know what you mean. Okay, Caleb kind of knows what I mean so you're the
you're the odd duck out. I guess I'm the weirdo here. You're the weirdo idiot. It's two verse one, stupid.
What's it like to be stupid and developmentally... What's it like to have poop for a brain?
What's it like to have a piece of turd? It's adorable. It's normal. It would be adorable to have a little
Hershey kiss for a brain. Yeah. A little Hershey kiss. I think you might. I think I
do you might have a little bit of poop in your brain I think I my brain is a piece
of chewed gum really mm-hmm like a Renan Stimpy gag yes getting caught up in the
spokes of the you you put your the what's that thing called thumb no the
ear ear viewer your viewer at the doctor oh yeah the ear viewer yeah
I love it. You're you're you're.
Cause you did it. That's how you hold it.
Yeah, it has a light.
He's the stupid one.
Yeah. Oh my God.
What are you talking about?
Damn.
They finally vindicated.
I'm finally vindicated.
Have you never been to the doctor?
He didn't even say ear though.
He just looked at me and said,
"What's that thing?"
He held it up to his ear.
I did do that.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my God, dude.
Cameron, no.
I'm alpha in camera right now.
Finally, I'm the alpha.
Wait, I bet he won't get this.
You don't even know what alpha means.
Yeah, it's the one before beta.
Amron Amron K is
OOP it's day. I thought we were done with the French name stuff
Yeah, I hate those pig Latin motherfucking oh my god it French
Oh my god. You think the Quebecois
Don't fuck with the French like that. I think so you think they got their own thing going on
I think neither of them fuck with each other you think it's like like circle small kind of thing mm-hmm
Yeah, all right. I mean, I don't I mean we were just on
Bottleman look out for that yeah, we're just on that and I think now as many times as we've been on it
We can say whatever we want about Canada. I agree. Yeah, they're they're from Quebec, right?
no no I don't know I have no idea I know but then Riley's also like in the UK for
some reason Riley said he's from Niagara that's Canada yeah well yeah Riley could
be lying he could be from the New York is he lying it could be from the New York
side it could be from the water side to that boy but you ever now she belonged to
the seat nah man you don't want no part of her she belongs that's that's
Poseidon's girl. You stay away from her. Yeah. You ever been to the, I went to
Niagara Falls on the New York side because I don't have a passport. Yeah. And
when you get past it yeah I want to get a passport I just want to at least go to
how about this go to Quebec. Matching outfit passports. Uh-huh. You know I already have a passport.
Sorry. Can you get it redone you idiot? Why don't you guys just wear the same
outfit I'm wearing in my passport. What do you have on? That's a good one. I don't know I
I don't remember. Well, I'll probably like a dress.
Your passport is from like years ago, right?
Probably like three years ago. Three years, okay.
Yeah, probably like a dress or a tutu.
Yeah.
Well, first of all, you wouldn't be able to see a tutu in the passport.
I wouldn't know. I never got it. I assumed it was a full body thing.
And it gave you all your stats, too.
I thought it said your strength, your intelligence, your charisma and shit.
And also I thought you could rotate yourself.
And maybe if you're lucky, you can move the camera and look up your own dress.
dress yeah your own dress should okay okay they should just make all passports
digital at this point okay and you can do that and it's a full-body 3d scan so
I'm saying mm-hmm they should scan your brain give you different stats that you
have scan your muscles and your fibers as well maybe it's your bones and see
what kind of shape you're doing the vats on you should be able to change your
appearance with sliders and give yourself big pointy cheeks but you have
to spend special coins you have to spend a bunch of money become a lizard but only
in your passport yeah you can't change a real but you can change your passport yeah
yeah or you can become a big mochi just like a just like an IMVU style passport
yeah that's not a bad idea no you see I'm on the top of my game today I don't
know what I think it was cuz I ate some pretzel M&Ms before I think I really
Caleb's idea though what eating pretzel M&Ms no with this passport thing what
fucking stealing my idea. You're on the top of your game? I'm on the top of my game I'm back in my
invention swag. Caleb was the one that said that he said you should be able to rotate yourself and
stuff. Well I said we should have the digital, I think me and Caleb collaborated on this. I'm
fine it split 50/50 all the money. Yeah. When all the different countries invest except Quebec which
can't invest in our new idea. Yeah that's right. It's also not valid in Quebec you got to use a
regular passport. That's right, yeah you gotta use probably like I don't know a piece of
paper. A dog turd in your hand with your name on it. Fucking stupid ass part of one country.
I'm sure I go to Quebec I love it. I think we need to start making, where do you? I'm
sure I'm gonna go up there and be like I regret all the things I just said. You know what
we already took down Hawaii a couple weeks ago which everyone loved it by the way. Everyone
loved it. Huge fans. I think I'm still on the side of Hawaii. We should be doing this
every week drop that motherfucking beat let's take down that's right all right
here we go yo Quebec I got something to say to you yeah come over here which you
goofy ass what do you got straight lines on your borders true day that's right
yeah what's that so you can grind them what are you a skateboarder Quebec what's
up man y'all got yeah what you guys have it well you guys have the Eiffel Tower
yeah you don't have that make you know what you don't have you don't even have
an Eiffel Tower what what do you guys what their city of Paris is there yeah
what y'all got y'all got a beautiful countryside with mad wine and shit
you got amazing as if amazing cuisine fuck you fuck you mm-hmm guys I think
we're doing France yeah I think we're doing France what's in Quebec I think
I think I got a second Eiffel Tower and it's red?
No! That don't make no sense. And it's smaller. And it's a small Eiffel Tower like the one in
Las Vegas? What? And it's even smaller than the one in Las Vegas I think. I think
it's the size of a keychain Eiffel Tower. And you guys worship it like Mecca. Yeah.
And I ain't talking about the Godzilla though. What? Mecca Godzilla though. I thought you
in Mecca Eiffel Tower. That's scary. Why they're not at Eiffel Tower kaiju?
It's like a spider it climbs out of the ground. Yeah. Dude what the fuck? I'm so
smart. That would be cool. They should do one that's just all the statues and big
shit in the world fighting each other. They have one with statue. With one
statue? They have one with a statue. No. They have three movies with the same statue. The
Statue of Liberty fights Godzilla? No it's a Japanese statue. I'm trying to see
the Wall Street bull fight that little girl mm-hmm that little girl statue
take her out just yeah I'm sick of her man what the one day the thing what the
bull finally she's trying to stop the bull she can't stop a problem she's a
little baby 60 years old that statue grow up the girl or the bull girl that's a
60 year old grow up I thought it was just put there I thought that was new
nope 60 years old grow up I say get older grow up man and to that bowl kudos on
the balls my friend yeah I put those I haven't seen I've not seen the Wall
Street Bowl I've never actually what I took you there no you didn't take me to
Wall Street oh I went with I went with with Jubio and Noah and yeah there was a
guy there's a guy taking a shit on the ground right next to it and then he he
shit into his like blanket that he was using and then just kept rocking the
blanket dude damn I was like that is an advanced cocoon move that my friend has
just invented I guess I guess that's where that guy there and then I put the
balls on my face I guess it deters people from stealing his blanket yeah
that's okay here's if you can't afford like ADT or Brinks or any of these home
security companies take a doo-doo on you put poop on your stuff yeah yeah I'm
I'm a criminal. Yeah, you can just put poop on the doorknob. Put poop on your
doorknob. I'm not gonna do anything with it. Or also like take a shit in the
like the underside of your car door handle so that when people like
you know they walk down the street just lifting every handle they hit one
doo-doo on their hand. Yeah, although that might be they might go for a revenge
robbery. Yeah, they might just break your window at that point. Yeah, well get this in
between the two panes of glass in your window. More dookie. Lots of poop. Okay, yeah
plus fill your car with dookie and all the crap in it it also has dookie on it
that's right if you don't have the time to do a dookie just a tootsie roll will
do here's another trick if you don't if you're worried that your stuff's gonna
get ruined from putting poop on it you take your stuff out of your house you
put in a different house and you just have one house that's filled with poop
that you live in yeah we're gonna try to rob that house because you live there
yeah turns out all the furniture is made of poop everything's made of poop it's
sculpted they walk in they say they say it smells crazy in here yeah exactly say
oh that's just my scented candle I hope you don't pick up anything yeah I'm
gonna go slip into something a little more comfortable you spend an hour while
they pick up all the stuff you come out and poop lingerie right they start
fucking you you know fall in love with a robber then you cut you mold him to your
beautiful perfection like the skin I'm in twist is he's also yeah I'm also made
at a poop. Yeah. We're so good at writing movies and shit. Oh my god. We have a beautiful mind.
What would that movie be called? The movie would be called The Dookie. The scent of a
woman. The what? That's good. That's actually good man. Yeah. The scent of a woman too.
What about Poop House? Poop House might be good. Could it be like the scent of a woman
colon poop house how about how about scat midnight it could say colon
spelled out it's not bad at all colon poop house colon poop house that's
actually the Iraq war that's actually colon poop house is actually a cast
member on the British SNL oh it's a hyphenated last name they did they had a
had a SNL in England. I think it was called just Saturdays. They don't have
night over there. Yeah. Darcy Fardington.
Emil. Crumpus. Emil. Shit.
Joe Poo. You know, British names like that? Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Yeah, but Quebec really needs a... Honestly, I'm fine with them. I love
I'm literally fine with them.
They need to clean up their hand to wean out them after them.
But my problem is they got to get real at some point.
Yeah, I mean pick a lane to them.
Yeah, are you fucking American or are you a French?
Or are you a frog freak?
Are you a frog eating fucker?
Yeah.
Right?
That's a question.
Yeah.
What are you fucking, are you going to sesh burgies with your boys down in the beautiful
USA, where it's white and blue?
Are you going to eat a plate of armpit hair like spaghetti?
Yeah.
Did you say sesh burgies?
Sesh some burgies.
Oh, okay.
you said Bernie's and I was like is that what like are you saying like smoke weed
or no dude what kind of it's illegal yeah no burgies I think it's legal in Canada
you can buy it's just another reason why Quebec is fucking sucks a bunch of
stone or pedophiles undercover as Canadians I had fucking dog shit ass
province yeah I hate provinces I'm gonna be real with you
But states though, states go crazy. States kinda smash, but the provinces...
No way, no way Jose. You want me to get into a province?
Get me out of this damn province. That's what I'd be saying when I'm in one.
Yeah. I'm like, I don't need this. I'm not trying to be provincial.
This is not what Sir John A. Macdonald had in mind.
What am I, what am I, king in a castle? Am I gonna be in a province? Straight Borat up?
King in the castle? No.
Um, they should bring back like baronies and like fiefdoms and stuff.
A fiefdom? I might be good with a fiefdom.
How long was Canada a territory of England?
Probably like a thousand hundred years.
Didn't it like stop being a territory of England like pretty recently?
I feel like there's some-
They still got mad respect for the Queen.
Yeah, aren't they like kind of loyal? Like there's some loyalists in Canada or some shit?
I don't really know what their deal is.
Uh-huh.
It seems very confusing. They have a parliament, I learned.
They have a chip made out of ketchup.
which is like the second most confusing part about it.
Yeah, they have a prime minister, they have a premier.
- Uh-huh, of what movie?
- Yeah, what?
- Yeah, what a prime minister, what is this, Transformers?
- Yeah, a premier, what is this, Transformers?
We're gonna see the premier of it?
You know, that's how I feel, right?
- Yeah, they got, what, they have fire trucks there?
What is this?
- What is this, a fucking Transformers?
- What is this, what is this,
gonna transform into a fire truck?
- Yeah, that's how I'm feeling.
- That's the name of the fire truck.
- They got frogs there.
was Beast Wars yeah that's right I'm fucking that's right attention these
these frogs trying to wait for them to turn into a some kind of automobile
how's that make any sense man Quebec's got me walking around going crazy this
doesn't make any sense dude fucking Jacob's ladder yeah why don't why don't
you transform into a better yeah all of a sudden you finally see McDonald's right
I bet the whole I bet the Quebec Club McDonald's goes crazy well you walk into
McDonald's you're like I bet this is probably probably this is a little taste
to home I'm gonna feel normal walking into here you walk in you know if I can
see that you see the client say that doesn't make any sense he looks a little
different the clown does right name plate I'm Rinaldo McDonald oh and you
know and you know and you go behind pieces shit you go black and white you
go up there and you you try to order a burger they say we don't have that there
you we hear we don't have that here you don't say what you say what you say what
What do you have? They say it's called a Royale with cheese here. Oh my god. It doesn't make any sense, right?
Yeah, they got a damn they got a paneer sandwich. Yeah, I wish I was paneer some fucking beef right now
I'll tell you that much cuz this shit is dumb
I do want to eat the McDonald's the McPaneer so bad you want to eat the McPaneer?
I'm gonna steamroll the bit to just say that if someone wants to send me the McPaneer in the mail
If we have any Indian listeners, we get cold you fucking doofus. I'll reheat it in what okay?
Send me the ingredients of the mcpaneer. I'll assemble it at home
That doesn't you just gonna suck. No. It's not it's gotta be hot
They should have a McDonald's exchange program. We're like they like
Shit that is so smart. That would be so literally all fucking 50 employees. Yeah
the building you yeah everything they literally the entire thing take it up
with a crane with everybody still in it plumbing falling out of the bottom
customers who are still eating that's the experience and then you put it on a
shipping container you fucking send it over here we say you guys were
essentially an embassy yeah yeah yeah yeah it's foreign soil uh-huh yeah
that's where the customers are yeah I get to live there in McDonald's mm-hmm I
I mean, one was the play place preferably.
That would be so good. That is so smart, dude.
They do do that sometimes where they'll put menu items from like, remember like 20...
Yeah, but I'm not talking about the menu.
18. I know, I know, I'm just saying. I want to see what the Chinese Ronald McDonald statue on the bench looks like.
That's right.
Good point.
He's probably sitting silently. He's not so fucking uppity like the American one.
That's right.
more respectful. You know, that's what I would say. I would hope so at least.
I don't think that they don't have... they have China McDonald's?
Yeah. In China? They got China McDonald's. Not Hong Kong. China? Yeah. Straight up Chinese
McDonald's. I think they have it. I don't know about that. I know that they have KFC over there.
Oh really? In Beijing, I think. That sounds pretty fucking good actually.
I think it's uh because the the my my high school band went to the Beijing the
the Olympics in Beijing. They must have been pretty talented. I guess. Yeah I guess I guess you
could say that. Must have been the fastest band in the world. They were they were so
fast at marching but yeah they went to they went to China and like all of them
came back and we're just like yeah we tried McDonald's over there. They were all nervous to eat Chinese food.
Really? They didn't want to eat Chinese food?
I don't remember.
What? You don't remember now?
That was the best setup I've ever heard for a story.
And the worst ending of all time.
Like kids would come over. I heard all these stories second hand because I was in like fucking sixth grade.
I didn't really know anyone in high school. So like my cousins, friends were saying like oh like the menus are different over there.
You guys heard Joe talk about his trip to China? No. Where he went to a like
a school trip to China and went to a school and arm-wrestled the
entire school. What? All the kids were like, he's big, he's like fucking huge. Oh
yeah. We want to arm wrestle you and just arm wrestled everybody in the school. Why? I don't know dude. What? Yeah, because Joe's like 6'5"
six six or something yeah which he was just like how tall is what age was he
like he's probably 23 went to a middle school and was just like hey guys I'm
gonna arm so sick dude yeah I mean you got to feel you have you he's literally
he dominated a province of China yeah it's crazy that like I mean I've heard
stories of like black people going to China and then just getting photos taken
yeah yeah I like people yeah my yeah I'm I'm my mom that happened to Joe - maybe I
don't know my mom was when I ask him but he's not I think he's coming home today
he's been out he hasn't been home for like three days okay okay my mom lived
in Japan for a year and she said that sometimes like little Japanese children
would see her and start crying because they were scared because they saw a white
person yeah it's because she's white that's why yeah your mama's big sharp
teeth though yeah yeah like it looks like a red demon eyes yeah I saw a dog it
looked exactly like an anglerfish two days ago really literally at the
aquarium yeah yeah he's always in water they had to keep the dog alive but it
wasn't water he's in a blue room like an idiot wasn't why would a dog be under
water. He was a bulldog that his face was completely just like on top of his head.
Yeah. He's like final evolution just like you can't push. He was reaching the
boundaries of the dog physiognomy. You could not do anything else to this dog.
Yeah he was like he was like like like the complexity hit maximum in sport.
Exactly yeah. He looked exactly like an anglerfish. He could he was rolling his
his eyes like like he had to look down his eyes his like pupils are at the very
bottom of his like eyelid the entire time because that's the only way he could
see in front of him yeah his eyes were just like if you didn't do that you'd
be looking directly at the Sun all day both like Bulldogs and like pugs like
when they get real old they always look like they're like on the brink of death
they are yeah and they're a bomb and God punishes them by making them live so long
Yeah, like a lab lab will live like nine years and then die because of a firework a fucking bulldog
We'll just it lives until like nothing wants to kill it. Yeah, cuz like why would you want?
Why that's why they're so prone to dangerous things like skateboarding. Yeah
Exactly. Yeah, cuz they feel invincible like a dachshund dachshund is a delicious bird food
Like you know, I mean they get picked up all the time. Yeah by a hawk
Can you imagine a pitbull or not a pitbull a fucking people getting picked up by a hawk?
I would love to see that'd be really scary. Yeah. Yeah. No
Tag team. Well, it's like a dog or a pug. I'm not touching exactly
Yeah
It's like it's like if you're like going to a farm to like like pick out which like chicken you want to eat or something
You see there's like a normal chicken and there's one that's just like upside down. Yeah
It's beat
No, yeah, can you imagine what a hawk fucking thinks when they see a bulldog like that's a rock? Yeah
That is not a living thing.
Why is a stone walking around?
This is a golem. I don't want anything to do with that.
Also, I couldn't pick him up.
Too hefty.
Imagine a hawk
picking up a pit bull
and then it swoops down because it wants to eat
your fucking ice cream cone or something
but it still has the pit bull in its hand.
So it drops the pit bull in front of you. Pit bull gets scared and starts fucking
biting your leg or whatever and then the hawk
starts attacking you because it wants your ice cream.
Wow.
this we could harness this power to real battle the Titans and send this shit
over to fucking fight Isis what do you think that did they breed was a pit was a
bulldog they had like a normal dog and then they made it fuck like a cannonball
this is gonna be the best dog ever yeah yeah it's a fucked up dog that was I
mean pitbulls or bulldogs were originally bred to none of us could say the word
bulldog that's a pitbull. I don't know why that is. Pitbulls just have big-ass
heads. Yeah. The wider a pitbull's head is the more... Scary it is. No, the kinder
they are. No. In my experience. Pitbulls that have like dinosaur heads,
like there's pitbulls that have like alligator head sized heads. Yeah. That's a
good dog. Their bite... I mean have you ever tried to make a pitbull bite you? Oh yeah dude.
Oh, man, that's the thing a pitbull. I try I go to the park. I start poking them with sticks
It was really like me and I say ow. Oh, what a dangerous breed
Pipples really want to fight the their image, you know, they try to be really yeah, that's why they attack me
But meanwhile me I walk around bed stock covered in barbecue sauce
Get one to get me dude. I'm getting one of those one of those brownstones out of it one one day. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna sue this you're gonna name your pitbull
Brownstone? Yeah. Yeah. My pitbull his name is Brownstone. Not a bad idea. Yeah.
Alright, today's list is on the top tens is most beautiful things to look at by
Roger McBeloney. Whoa, that's a familiar name I've heard that before. Really? Yeah,
it's my dentist's name. Number one here is sunsets. True. That's pretty beautiful.
When the sun sets and it starts to get dark, you usually get this beautiful color of red,
vibrant orange, pink and blues in the sky with the sun coming down.
Simply just wonderful.
The sun may rise on the east at least it settles in a fine location.
Whoa.
You got my butt there?
Did you just write that?
The sun may rise in the east at least it settles in a fine location.
Did you write this?
You wrote it again?
You wrote, wow.
understood that hollywood
is something can't fornication
something can fornication
i think we got a hit
i think this could be big
how about new york fornication
new york
rest in peace, simultaneous release
there's tons of streets and tons of cars it's new york fornication
times square is the biggest
place here but you know that it is so small
there's a bunch of people in the place
and you know the buildings are so tall
it's understood that hollywood is
new york fornication
we need to do the new york red hot chili peppers so east coast chilis
hot normal peppers no not peppers the blue cold normal chopped cheese
no it's gotta be a vegetable ok then the onions the new york cold normal onions
yeah we could do so many fucking
yeah fucking good songs dude. That would be good yeah yeah.
Keepin' it all, keepin' it all, keepin' it all now.
We do that. Yeah. What other? Over the bridge
like and be about the Brooklyn Bridge. I wanna be
like I was that day.
Yeah dude just do the east coast version of all the songs.
Instead of Danny California, Tony New York.
Yeah. With the name like Tony New York.
blow my hug. Damn, that's pretty good. It could be good, right? Yeah, that's not bad at all.
The problem is, do we do the higher ground cover? Is it because it's a cover? Lower sky? Yeah,
but do we do we do that or do we just do higher ground? I for one love to disrespect the blind,
so we could do that. Okay, lower sky. Lower sky, yeah. People keep on living. Animals.
animals keep on living. The moon keeps on staying still and it's gonna be real short.
Yeah, it's pretty smart actually. It's actually kind of a clever. Cerebral kind of thing you know.
I'm walking with my worst enemies. I honestly I don't know any I know like the
hits of the Red Hot Chili Peppers. Yeah I don't know very much either. You're gonna have to carry
the rest of this. I'm walking with my two worst enemies we don't have anything and
we're gonna freeze. That's the the road tripping song. Okay. You guys trust me you
guys stay in my car long enough you'll be pretty familiar with that one. Yeah.
Road tripping with my two favorite allies wait it's kind of a song about us.
Okay. Wow. The next line. We're fully loaded we got snacks and supplies. Whoa. Tell me
that doesn't sound that's amazing that like kind of eerie and creepy yeah right
wait what was that written 2001 maybe Wow oh my god it's kind of like
prophetic yeah I would really that what would you call it I don't call it
pathetic I mean perfect Oh prophetic not pathetic it's cool we got a song a song
written about us okay number two most beautiful thing to look at is the stars
okay yeah no guys I'm actually crazy about like dots yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's like my thoughts the candy yeah that's that's what you want our dots the
ones that are on paper or are they the ones that are like a pregnant woman's
nipple thing you know what I mean when they get really long and fucked up yeah
What is that dude?
It's so the baby can touch it.
Put those away!
I don't want to see that.
How many... you don't see many pregnant women.
How often are you seeing that?
Probably every day at this point.
In what situation?
Are you on the subreddit again?
No I'm not on the subreddit dude.
Alright my favorite sandwich place
is also
a maternity ward is right next to it.
So sometimes I go in
and i'm trying to eat and i you know i'm i'm always getting
being pulled pork
you know
and i get home and pull your damn pork i'll call my poor maternity when i want
to see them those nipples it is your fucking it was a like earplugs bitch get
that shit away from me
dots and dots of the year put
well dots are in between a candy corn in your book
they look yeah gumdrops right i don't like those yes he has candies to the
wax bottles akha pocket i mean the the the liquid in the wax bottle but then
and it's like, now I just have trash.
- Why not just buy, why don't they just sell the liquid?
- Sell me the liquid.
What are you doing?
Hey, here's an idea, sell me the liquid, carbonate it.
Maybe add a little water.
- Maybe you could, yeah, just sell them separately.
Some people like the wax more.
They can just buy the wax, a big block of wax.
That'll be really good for some people.
- You guys ever eat wax lips?
- I never ate them, but I--
- I thought you were supposed to eat 'em when I was a kid.
- I'm sure you did. - I mean, eat your wax lips.
- I mean, they don't tell,
when you get that in your Halloween basket,
they don't tell you that it's not candy.
- That's right, but if you got something
in your Halloween basket that was called,
that was called like, like, plastic ball,
would you eat that?
- Yeah. - They have a fucking--
- I used to eat the toothpaste.
- They have candies that are called like--
- I thought it was like a sour--
- Fucking squirt. - Snowballs.
You're not supposed to eat snow.
- You can eat snow.
- No.
- You don't eat snow? - You can eat snow.
- That's why you eat clothes all the time.
- They have a candy called crows.
- You can stick out your tongue in the snow.
- Would you eat a crow?
- I've never heard of that candy.
- Crows?
- They're like, they're dots, but they're black licorice.
a candy called the three musketeers. Oh no, why are they called crows? Yeah. Oh God. Scary.
Yeah. I'm saying is if it has the word wax in it you should know not to eat it.
I thought it was like a euphemism. Also, you said you ate it right? Well cotton candy.
Yep. Says candy. Says candy but if it was just called cotton. Then you, it wouldn't
be the same thing. But it's clearly not made of cotton. Because cotton is already
cotton yeah there's a there's one candy okay yeah I'm thinking of what is it but
it's on the tip of my tongue but I can't think of it you're probably gonna say Oh
candy corn you're not supposed to eat corn no that's probably what you're
about to say eat a lot of corn you don't eat a lot of I eat so much you don't eat
any corn shut up I thought so much made of wax if you think corny be a foot
taller I what are you talking about corn there's pictures of me there's a baby
photo of me eating corn the long way my mom my mom put that in the yearbook well
that's it that was a stage photograph no it was a moon landing situation you
think my mom photoshopped a corn in yeah dude I think Stanley Kubrick gave you a
fake corn no something like that yeah if you ate corn you have the you have the
broad shoulders of a corn fed boy who is deprived of his of his God God think
God-given corn. I've eaten so much corn in my life. You needed more. I needed a lot
more corn. Less wax too. I like eating wax. You would have been a movie star. You like eating wax?
I like eating it. Okay this is my point, okay, if you didn't realize that it was, if you ate it,
you, within one bite, you should know that that is not candy. And you said you ate it. I didn't eat
the whole thing. Okay, all right, so you took a bite of it. You swallowed though. Yeah. That's fine, I used to take a bite of my shirt.
I don't know what makes me weird yeah you say eat my shirt I used to chew on my
shirt too I said eat my I never ate you don't my sure I had a cousin sometimes
would fall off and I eat my shirt your shoe with your shirt I always wear long
sleeve shirts and I just chew on them all things you chew a hole into the
sleeve and put your thumb in no no I would chew it because I like to taste my
own sweat oh you fucking friend then we didn't get this when pieces of the shirt
would tear off eat them you guys ever think you're a pica no I thought I had
pica yeah yeah I was eating my fucking shirt every day I was I would eat corn
you didn't eat corn corn is a perfectly edible
I think I have pica. Somebody puts a plate down in front of me. I gotta eat every damn thing on it.
God damn.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
I did have a...
What else did you eat?
I used to eat something that was weird.
Really?
Do something else.
Please pray tell.
What is it?
Fish.
Fish?
I bet you ate gum. Did you eat gum?
I would swallow gum, yeah.
I used to eat my toenails too.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, yeah.
That's disgusting.
No, it was awesome.
That's so gross.
It's the same texture as a popcorn kernel.
It was, yeah dude, it was crunchy.
Eating a popcorn kernel?
My mom said you're gonna get a worm from that.
You are gonna get a worm from that.
I'd still do it if I could reach.
Slice open your esophagus on the way down.
I could reach.
You could reach?
Any reacher toe.
I could reach.
I eat so much fucking, no don't eat my toenails.
Those are mine.
I'm hungry for them.
But I used to eat my toenails and my mom hit me on the head and said you're gonna get a
worm and did it again.
Yeah, corporal punishment works.
What else did you eat?
You ate coins, too.
Yeah.
Did you eat dust?
No.
I think sometimes a mustache hair will fall off into my mouth and instead of spitting
it out I just swallow it.
Sometimes it's easier to swallow something that falls into your mouth.
Yeah, if it's not nasty.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, that's pretty okay.
It's picking something up and eating it.
If something ends up in your mouth, you know, so be it.
I knew a kid who ate the dead skin off his hands.
Yeah.
Yeah, he would like, swam all the time and get these like real wrinkly hands and rub
them a bunch, get a bunch of dead skin, eat the skin off it.
And then his mom was like, "My son's a genius."
And he got put in all these like accelerated programs and shit.
Yeah, they were trying to accelerate his life so it would be over sooner.
Yeah, so he kills himself earlier.
Like a freak.
Yeah.
He was awesome.
If someone's put into like accelerated classes, usually they got some weird quirk.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, yeah, I knew this kid. There's this kid like a rolling backpack or something or
Dude, there was just there's these two Ethiopian kids at my school
Who were like always talking mad shit about me because I wasn't Ethiopian
They were like not even I was white. They were just like you like if you're not Ethiopian you're gay
Nice, that was the first of many times I experienced racism. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, but those kids skipped like 10 grades because I came from Ethiopia and I guess Ethiopia has like the best schools in the
World or some shit Wow and they were like this. I was in like fifth grade these kids were like
Seven yeah, and they were like so much smarter than me. They're dominating me and then letting me know that it was
Ethiopia yeah, I got dominated by two Ethiopians in fifth grade
That's what happened
All right, it's crazy dude number three full moon at night
I wish I was a wolf so I can howl at the full moon at nighttime with the beautiful stars and cool dark blue sky
That would be amazing
Do you guys wish that I would I I wish I was a werewolf
Just so I could scratch that damage behind my ear. You can't reach. No, would you use your leg?
Well, I want to use my leg. Can you imagine though if you were a werewolf you'd have almost you have an infinite
Amount of itches all the time. That's true. Yeah covered in fucking hair. You have tufts. You don't have tufts right now
Here's a really insightful comment from Oliver Skye
That's kind of about what you're talking about
werewolf a - in turn will you but Wow
Words out of my damn mouth where it's all H love word is capitalized - did you get
Did you wear a little bit - is all over sky Oliver Skye?
Oh, it's a pun. All over the sky. Yeah, 27 years old. You ever seen a, you ever seen a Lykoi cat?
No, I don't know what that is. That's a cat that looks like a werewolf. How do you spell it? L-Y-K-O-I.
Let's see here. I'll be the judge of this.
This doesn't really look that much like a werewolf. That looks like a werewolf? It has yellow eyes. Yeah. It looks like a rat.
Oh, it looks like a big werewolf.
It looks more like a beast to me.
Yeah, it's like a beast cat.
I'm thinking maybe, maybe I get an army of them.
Have you guys seen werewolf?
How many is an army?
This is an animal that looks like a werewolf.
Whoa, look at this.
A vampire bit a werewolf.
Do you guys believe in werewolves?
I hope they're not real, but I don't want to rule it out.
I feel like, okay, so I like cryptids and shit, and I generally think that they don't
exist but I feel like one of them has to be the one I have my money on the like
the monster that I think is real as I think water monsters are real me yeah
yeah that's the one is like anything that anyone has seen in a water any like
the kraken like that has to be yeah right just a generic water monster
there's too much water I think the look could be real who could do Lou what you
speak up Kokomo Cthulhu could be real who could Cthulhu who could do who but
nobody was late from the network oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I want to dies all the
time yeah yeah be real can be real but yeah I'm with you like any big monster
in the water not big or even like this small no it's actually small it's the
smallest well also like there's so many things like the giant squid they find I'm
I'm like if I saw that 200 years ago and it was alive,
I would think it was a monster.
- Well, I literally, I spend most of my free time nowadays,
I watch shark and crocodile videos.
I've been doing that for like a few months now.
And some of those sharks,
those are just straight up water monsters.
- Dude, that 600 year old fucking shark.
- Yeah, the Greenland shark.
So there's some deep sea sharks where their eyes
literally look like a cartoon character's eyes.
- Really?
- Like I was watching this footage of like these people
in a, you look so scared.
- You mean, you mean.
- I lost my train of thought.
- It looks like Toon World is real.
- Looks like Judge Doom.
- What?
- Yeah.
- You can't tell me that there's Toons in real life.
- There's this footage of like people in like a submarine,
like in the deep sea and they're like filming
and like this shark comes over and it's like poking around
and then it's eye like opens and it literally looks,
it looks like a Calvin and Hobbes eye or something.
- Really?
- Like it's like a, just a perfect like circle
with a dot in it.
- Yeah, that would scare me a lot.
So a shark shouldn't have an eye like that.
It's supposed to be black.
- You know what would scare me a lot also?
This is like a similar story.
If you were, like I was saying about this,
if you were swimming down to the bottom of the ocean
and then you hit the ocean floor
and you're like, well, here's the ocean floor.
Yeah, there it is.
And then you're on a giant eye and it opens.
- Yeah.
- That's also pretty scary.
- That is pretty scary.
- What would you even do?
- Probably poke the eye.
- Yeah.
- Poke the eye and make it, flip it off,
then poke it with the middle finger.
- Well, it probably wouldn't be able to see me, actually,
if the whole ocean floor is an eye.
Like, if a speck of dust was on my eye,
like right here, right now, I probably would barely
be able to see it very well.
- Here's a scary thought.
What if the world was an egg?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, what if, and we're all sitting on it?
- Yeah, hey, don't worry about it, buddy.
The world's just an egg, and we're all sitting on it.
- I think Shakespeare said that.
- Yeah, Shakespeare said that.
- Shakespeare did, yeah.
- Shakespeare and Bill Hicks,
but I think he was quoting Shakespeare.
I think Shakespeare was Bill Hicks.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Fuck.
Number four, Aurora Borealis.
Yeah.
I don't care, ugly.
I mean, don't get me started on Alaska.
What's wrong with Alaska?
Earlier today I had a hororobolbowlyalis out of my...
I had a fucked up shit.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Looked like all the colors.
I had one too.
That's because I was drinking beer last night.
I was drinking a bunch of colors.
I can't drink beer anymore.
I broke into a Baskin Robbins Dunkin Donuts mix, just started eating all the cake dye.
Oh, this is what we're talking about.
Here we go, number five, the ocean.
This is what we're talking about.
Here's the top comment.
This is something that this Markiplier would freak out if he saw some pictures of the ocean.
He hates it.
Watch him play Subnautica, Drowning Simulator, and Raft if you want to know why.
Drowning Simulator?
That's a game?
Oh my God.
These games are going too far now.
I know.
Drowning Simulator?
Why would you ever want to simulate drowning?
like drowning drowning and getting crushed or we all know like no Russian
great fucking level of modern warfare mm-hmm but if my kid walks up to the
GameStop counter when I'm bringing him there and he's trying to buy drowning
simulator no way I'm calling I'm calling I might call the police
something very wrong horribly this kid must have some kind of diet issue that
that is causing him to be weird.
- He's eating, the 5G has made my son weird.
- I've been feeding my kid ginseng and creatine
every single day since he was one years old.
- Yeah.
- And now he's-- - He's not even strong yet.
- He's not strong and he's way too weird about drowning.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I get freaked out.
- It's not, it doesn't sound like a fun game either.
- No, what do you do?
Press, what, you can't even win.
- Yeah.
- You lose.
Do you win when you drown?
- Well, maybe you lose when you drown
but you win if you don't.
That's not much of a drowning simulator.
I saw - dude, I saw this thing the other day. It's like some article about virtual reality
because you know I'm into that, other worlds and stuff. Like I'm - it's pretty much my
thing.
You're into exploring the planes of -
Yeah, pretty much the different planes and realities. And this guy has been for like
twenty years doing this therapy for people with arachnophobia where they put on a virtual
reality headset and they're in a room and there is just like a giant spider in front
And I just got, I like was scrolling through like every link that they linked
to see if I could just find a video of the person.
Just like freaking out.
Yeah, just like, just like, and because the guy, the whole thing is the guy's
like, yeah, we don't tell them what's going to happen.
So we like lock this VR headset on them and then they just are in a room with
like the biggest spider in the world.
I thought I was so cool, dude.
That's sick, yeah.
I just wanted, I would do anything to see that.
pretending to be like severely arachnophobic yeah and then just like
going in just seeing the spider and just immediately just being like whoa I'll
take any excuse to piss my pants yeah yeah right any any because that one's
justified right mm-hmm that's why I love theme park I we got to go to Canobie
yeah we can go we just my number six is mountains yeah I want to skip ahead here
Yeah, these are six mountains seven sunrises eight snow nine forest. These are all boring number ten is animals
Here's the top comment. We were just talking about seeing an animal exactly animals are such wonderful organisms in my opinion
The most beautiful animals on earth is the tiger scarlet macaw and Siamese fighting fish the blood one of the Siamese fighting fish
That's what they said. I
Would pick a different animal I'd pick maybe I think most of the animals I'd pick are different types of cats
you like cats I think like a caracal yeah you think that's beautiful to look at
have you ever seen yeah yes I have you being into cats makes no sense dude
it's fucking weird boy just like a grown man you like cats big cats and like
tigers and shit like tiger it's okay to like a cat if it's like your parents cat
yeah yeah if the cat like but like a like have you seen a video of a serval
cat no I don't look up videos of cats dude I'm not I'm not an old lumpy lady
okay I'm not all right Jerry's still out on that look up pornography that's what
I look up but if you were if you were watching a pornography and a cat walks
in the background you'd probably be like damn there's a damn cat in the
background hold up I got a zoom in on that shit I wouldn't even notice dude I
I would.
Dude, I got a, I have a, I'm locked on a guy's abs.
Trying to get inspo.
I'm locked on.
I say, he's doing fucking quarter crunches.
Well, okay, okay, you're watching, you're watching a video that's called like, "Milf
gets the cops called on her" or some shit, and then out of nowhere a tiger walks in the
background.
Milf gets the cops called on her?
I don't know.
at least I didn't say like... Milf gets the cops called on her and she has sex with the
cops. Hashtag back the blue. Yeah now that's a good video. And a tiger walks in the
background. You're not gonna take, you're not gonna look at the tiger and be like
that's a damn tiger. I'll say, I mean I'll, I guess if it was a tiger I'd notice. Okay.
But I'm also like trying to make sure that the cops are like following basic
procedure to you know reading the Miranda rights and all that mm-hmm yeah I would
have some sort of giving her oral sex see I would skip her like if someone if
somebody said like if like you know how back to blue hashtag there's a damn
tiger in this video you know how porn videos now have like the different
sections are like labeled to say like what's happening no I'm not a free now
and if I want them just tiger tiger walks by yeah tiger walks into frame
yeah eight seconds no one even notices but it's just like later in the video
like someone's like hold on yeah one of them stops it's like I'm sorry but was
that a tiger there was a there was a tiger that walked by right I don't know
real cops show and the real cops say like there's a tiger on the loose there's a
tiger on the loose hold on why are you guys dressed like us wait are you our
brothers and then they fuck the real cops - yeah yeah real cops teach fake
cops to fuck a prisoner how to fuck a tiger yeah yeah there's a really good
idea this is one of the most beautiful comments I've ever read on this website
number 13 is flowers and this is a comment from listlover 77 which is
already a beautiful username listen to this beautiful comment this is so kind
nothing adds as much beauty to a landscape as gorgeous flowers yeah yeah
that's better than tears that's nice did you read number 12 number 12 pictures of
loved ones see that that combined with that last comment I think we have the
most sentimental episode of all that's just poor yeah another porn star was that
dead girl which one there's like six dead the dead one there's six dead women
in the world. I mean Helen Keller. No, don't you ever say Franklin.
Aretha Franklin's alive. She's dead. Oh shit. Number 18 lunar eclipses. Not as
beautiful as solar eclipses, but there's still a sight caused by Earth casting
the shadow on its moon during alignment. It's way more beautiful. You can't even
see a fucking solar eclipse without special glasses. Yeah, you gotta look like
a nerd, which I'm not wearing that bullshit. That's right. Yeah, nothing's
stopping my day at the beach. Yeah. Number 19 is fjords. Is Aretha Franklin dead? I
I don't like fjords.
Number 20's fire.
Only comment is arsonist here, so it's very pretty.
(laughter)
Dude, I do, you know...
You love arson?
I get it, the pyromaniac thing.
Yeah, of course.
You look into a fire, something is calling.
Yeah. The devil.
I don't think it's the devil.
How come every time I look into a fire,
I hear a voice in my head that says, "Put your hand in it."
that's me oh really yeah oh it's me when we go camping oh yeah I like to scare
you I thought it was the devil no I have a big of a big horn that I talk into it
blows directly into your ear and I just whisper in it yeah I said I thought it
was an earring there you go the fire is the best part of this morning you say I
think I'm having the most awesome thoughts today for some reason something
something cool is happening in my mind Caleb's you have your skateboard you
You should teach Caleb how to skateboard.
- No.
- I think the devil is telling me awesome crap again.
- You don't wanna learn.
- I don't wanna learn anything.
I'm done learning.
- Yeah.
- There's no way that I'm learning to skateboard
or like snowboard or play an instrument anymore.
I'm done learning.
I had until I was 17, I whiffed it.
I biffed it, I buffed it.
I'm not doing it again.
- Yeah.
- Done learning.
- Here's another really beautiful comment.
Number 22, family.
- Whoa.
- The world could die for all I care.
If I see a genuine family,
a community that's more beautiful to see than anything,
love, a man and a woman doing everything they can
for the kids, the next generation.
Family doesn't mean blood related.
- So true.
- Wait, wait, guys, can your friends be your family?
- I think your friends could be your family.
- I think homies is family too.
- No.
- I think it could be.
- Are you serious?
- I think homies is family too.
- I think I'm serious.
Well then you guys are like my two ex-wives.
- It's not family.
- Not anymore.
- What the hell? - Bitch, bitch.
- Okay, we're like-- - Bitch, bitch, stupid, stupid.
- Me and Patrick are like our normal wives,
are each other's wives.
But you're jealous. - Y'all two wives?
Damn.
- And we got sister wives.
- Y'all selling tickets to the show?
What's up?
- Okay.
- Oh, we have a restraining order against you.
- Yeah. - Nice.
- 'Cause you wanna-- - 'Cause you wanna
- Do you wanna restrain me down and fucking--
- Yeah, I know. - Somebody kill you.
- You threw a brick through a window.
He is when I'm no one that says damn. Can I see the show? Can I see the show dope?
Yeah, he divorced he divorced us at different times, and then he kept throwing bricks through our windows that said damn
Can I see yeah, here's another really trying to watch unsolved mysteries sent to this is facts number 24 beautiful women
Yeah, you know when you see a hot woman walking down the street
It's so beautiful to see those hips legs beautiful facial features breast and ass. There's really nothing more beautiful and attractive
My name is Rachel Features. Plus the pits.
What?
My armpits.
Many are beautiful.
You only say that because you're last name.
Nope.
Here's a comment. Many are beautiful and we should focus on their bright side and stop
thinking negatively about people and stop thinking about sexual abuse, violence and other garbage.
What?
I'm done thinking about that crap. I'm done thinking about sexual abuse whenever I see a woman.
Here's a celebrity guest comment.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I agree and I think that women are the most beautiful creatures on earth. Remember guys treat your girlfriends or wives good and that's from Kenny McCormick
Who's a beautiful creature? Oh, I thought his name was Cthulhu. I thought he didn't talk anymore. Well, no. Well he can type
Here's a comment no comment. Tee
Number 26 is handsome man. That's just not that's one comment. Oh, yeah, like she mar more. Oh man is
That's just not true handsome
Who cares about handsome men are you kidding me have you seen Shamar Moore's Instagram? I hate handsome men
I'll be on have you seen Shamar Moore's Instagram. No, I do this
You have to follow interested a bunch of photos of a hot guy in a grid that I print out on no no
videos of him where he's like
I haven't talked to my hot my baby girls my my baby dolls my homies and something in about a hot minute
Yeah, I just want to say that
Your love and appreciate I'm lurking. I'm lurking. I'm stalking when you least expect
What he goes I'm silly. Oh, yeah
Sexy, I'm silly. He's like a guy takes a shirt off. Yeah, he takes his shirt off and makes videos of him
just like you got a
You got to love yourself before you can love anything else. Yeah, not my thing. Does he have a sister?
Maybe he has a sister. Really? Yeah. Oh my god. What's her name?
Hemar more does he take she take a shirt off?
She get her boobs on TV. I
Don't know number 27 the open road. I crave it. It's my oxygen
It's just freedom the wide open road good company and some belting driving songs amazing
What's better than a highway, you know?
Ultimate freedom to go from Oklahoma to Kansas City.
What did he do?
- Oh, Lord.
I'm sorry.
(laughs)
I'm just in a silly, goofy mood.
- Dude, he's the best.
He does rock, dude.
Number 37, beaches.
- Yup, yes, I love tropical and nautical aesthetics.
Number 38, gemstones.
- Yup. - Yes, sir.
- I mean, what is more beautiful in this world
than a diamond?
- Absolutely.
Art, birds, ancient ruins, sand dunes, rocks, yourself.
- Shut up.
- Delicious food.
- What is this?
- That's actually, that should be number one.
- Look at this meal.
- Oh, that is a gorgeous meal.
- Oh, lordy, oh my.
- That beautiful roast.
- Okay, I'll have it.
- What is that?
That's a British type of roast.
It has that bread thing.
- I love family dinners and all those meals
neatly placed on their plates babies classic cars fire I see a hot rod oh
god dude when I see 52 a pregnant woman it is so beautiful and sexy to see a
pregnant woman given to her cravings and stuff her already big belly with more to
make it did that freaks me out when people if someone's into pregnant women
- Like my head bone was?
- I think if my wife got pregnant, it's over.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- My fang is not getting near that.
Nope.
I don't wanna, what if my baby sees my little dick?
- Yeah.
- And says, "Pee-ew, stinky."
What if he smells it?
- Yeah, your baby comes out making a sour face
'cause he smelled your stinky penis for nine months.
So he looks up at you and says,
"Dad, you gotta wash your balls."
- Exactly, and then he's at the lunch table
when he's in sixth grade they're all talking about how dad dicks are huge and
he's like yeah plus they smell like total crap you know it's a weird kid I raised
yeah he's a stinky dad dick kid you guys ever think your dads think about our
dads think about what we do and what guys ever think our dads think about what
we do and talk about on here my dad and they get mad my dad doesn't know who I
I am my dad doesn't know who I am number 54 concerts I love the moment when my
favorite singers go on the stage and perform their music all right my dad
really read a Leonard Skinner concert once yeah yeah my dad took me to a u2
concert he told me I had to get on my shoulder so you could see the stage
I was six years old.
He used me like a stool.
You stood on him?
He sat his beer on my head.
Yeah, I tried to do that last night.
When I was growing up,
he used to put a big metal plate
on my head so it would get real flat
so he could put beer on it.
My dad used to put out his cigarettes on my head.
He didn't even smoke. He would ask people
walking by if they wanted to put their cigarettes
out on my head.
He said, "My kid's name is Ashtray."
(laughing)
My dad burrowed a hole in my leg, right?
With a little gardening shovel.
- Yeah.
- And he would just like work at it
kinda every year for Christmas.
That was my gift somehow.
And then he started using it as a dip spit cup.
He would just spit on my legs.
- My dad, my dad, he--
- And he would always miss.
I would just get it all over my shorts.
- My dad would use to, he used to sleep inside me
like a tauntaun.
(laughing)
It took like years and years for that to heal.
- Yeah.
My, there's been a few times where I've gone
to go drink a soda at a barbecue and my dad has,
my dad or my uncle has put dip spit in it,
so I know exactly.
- Really, my dad used to use me like a wrench.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
My dad would use me as the can recycling machine
at the grocery store, he'd put cans in my mouth.
- Yeah, I was a can opener for a bit.
- Yeah. - That's why this tooth
right here, you see that?
- Yeah. - Yeah, that's my
can opening teeth. - Wow.
- My dad used me as a lawn mower to eat
thousands of pounds of grass.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
because he was like, "I ain't cleaning up the grass after.
"Just swallow it, you homo."
- Before. - I'd say, "What, Dad?"
- Yeah, my dad, he used to use me,
he was getting really into sous vide,
so he'd make me swallow all the raw ingredients
and sous vide them in my stomach.
- Yeah.
- I'd have to puke them back up.
And I'd have to puke them back up.
- Do you ever, in the summer,
you ever have to work as the carbon monoxide detector
for your house?
- Oh yeah, when you get too sleepy?
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
go beep. Yeah, I did that. My dad, he put Bluetooth capabilities in me, he used me like a universal
remote. I'm serious. I used to turn all the lights on for him by opening my eyes.
Yeah, my dad used to use my teeth as a comb. A lice comb actually because it's so the gaffer
to my teeth.
Yeah, on the dog.
Yeah.
It's pretty sad.
the poop out of the dogs the dogs for on its ass you know it's like you didn't
want it scooting on the rug so my dad used my took my tongue as toilet paper
we were camping and they eat his poop the email dad's poop fire one year yeah to
be my dad used to use my blood as diet coke yeah he's a drink it drink all my
blood all day I'll just walk around pale as fuck falling over fainting the worst
16th century woman in a tight corset. He also used to make me wear corsets.
Yeah. He just thought it was funny.
Going on vacation, going to like the Disney World or something and you have to be the backpack.
Oh my god.
And then on the drive home, 11 hour drive back home, dad used me as a car.
Yep.
I had to turn into a car. My dad was so mean to me.
Oh dude.
Used me like a fucking car.
Dude.
can only tell me and what i was well as his wallet at the red sox game that was
the worst
you know i'm picking me up the swing in the senate the vendor at the hot dog
when i can see that he was the bible a hot dog got and i'm glad to report
that i have a lot of it would be every time you'd make me use my hands as the
bone for the hot dog
torn
so i said i did so many burns in
he's embarrassing me to any time i saw a buffalo soldier came on
he pointed me say it's about him
It's like, "No it's not, Dad. I'm not a buffalo soldier, I'm your son. You know my name."
He'd listen to Buffalo Soldier and then use me as a joint.
Yeah, yeah. It's true.
Use me as a shoe. One shoe. He said that's all he wanted.
A single shoe.
The worse in the winter when you become the snowshoe.
I have other brothers. He could have been two shoes. Of course, I'm the one who gets to be one single shoe.
The other shoe?
Fucking Nike Cortez.
But I have to be... Why would you even want that? Doesn't make any sense. He'd duct tape me to his fucking foot.
I had to work as a ceiling fan for two summers too.
I had to spin around as fast as I could.
My dad, he used to use me as a telephone.
I'd have to make up the other end of the conversation and if it didn't make sense or if I said something
that the other person wouldn't say, he'd make me stand outside for like a month.
My dad did that too.
Yeah, he was telling me, he was like saying names I'd never, he's like, "I want to call
Dean Martin."
I was six years old.
I said, "I don't know, who the fuck is Dean Martin?
I don't know who the fuck that is."
like he put me on the phone with Rodney
that's all I knew yeah well he was like no Rodney not Rocky I'd be sitting around
and he would go ring ring ring ring ring and and and he'd pick me up and and he
would say hello who is this and I would be like oh is your friend he'd be like
no it's not I'd have to figure out who was calling exactly the worst the worst
is when he finally made me a cell phone I had to be brick breaker
Oh, oh, fuck. Awful.
Put Brick Breaker, playing it with the burgeoning chest hairs that you had as a prepubescent man.
As bricks?
Yeah.
I want to have hair in the locker room.
Yeah, why is my dad, my dad's fucking removing lines of my chest hair like Tetris.
It's like, come on dad.
Yeah, what are we playing, Brick Breaker or Tetris?
Yeah, exactly. You're mixing up your phone games, you fucking old moron.
Oh man, the worst was Snake.
Ugh.
You think I can, you think I can squirm that?
You don't want to know what, yeah.
All right, the last thing on the list was beautiful eyes.
Oh, okay.
I used Patrick's dad like a condom once.
Subscribe to the--
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
And also on the 6th of October, come to Laugh Boston, me and Brandon Wardell and Gavin Matz
doing a show there at Laugh Boston and come to that show.
And we're gonna also be at the Shaking Crab before that.
Yeah, we'll be eating.
So everyone, we're gonna do a meet and greet at the Shaking Crab.
We'll be eating over $500 of lobster and you guys can watch if you want.
And you all pay for it.
Yeah.