Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughter)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- You better not say what you--
- Chucky, Chucky Cameron.
- Don't say that.
- Checkin' out my toilet.
Check out my toilet.
- Stop, please, Chucky Cameron.
- You wanna play with my toilet?
- You wanna play a game with my toilet?
- That's not a real--
- You wanna play?
- I'm small enough that I can fit in my own toilet.
- No.
- I'm Chucky Cameron.
- The toilet's big.
- I'm not small.
- Chucky Cameron's not small.
- I'm small.
- And also Chucky Cameron doesn't exist.
- Chucky Cameron.
It's me Chuckie Cameron. You wanna play the game?
You can only play it when you're peeing into my toilet that I'm in. Chuckie Cameron wouldn't say that.
I'm Chuckie Cameron and I would say that. No. You bitch. Wait, what does he say?
Chuckie? Yeah, Chuckie when he gets to the toilet. I think Chuckie goes like, "You stupid bitch, you want to suck my dick? You wanna fuck with me?"
He says, "If you'll excuse me, I have a date with a six-year-old boy." So Chuckie Cameron says he has a date with a six-year-old boy.
I thought Chuckie says that. I thought Chuckie's thing is like, "Heh heh heh, I farted."
Isn't that Chucky's thing?
No I think that's Caleb's thing.
No.
No I guess.
I'm getting farted up in your room.
Your cord is fucked up.
Let me get the other one.
Oh my god dude.
I'll just pause.
Oh I think that I found myself Chucky Cameron.
I'm a melted toy.
I'm a fucking freak.
I think he says that.
I got blood and I'm a toy.
Yeah I think he said.
I'm Chucky Cameron.
My toy knife is sharp.
I think he said that too.
Chucky.
I thought it was funny.
Chucky Cameron isn't a thing.
- It's funny that Chucky has like a little,
like an actual little knife.
- You would give off, honestly, I'm gonna be honest,
I mean this might be true about anybody,
if you were a foot and a half tall,
you would low-key give off Chucky vibes.
- I don't think that would be true.
- I think I would probably give off more like Gnome.
- No, you would be Chucky.
- I think I'd be more of a Gnome.
- You'd be Gnome named Norm.
- If you had a--
- You'd be like, "Oh, big rounders."
- If you were a foot and a half tall,
you had overalls on and a scar, I think you might low-key, like, just thinking about it,
you might give off some Chucky vibes to someone like me.
I don't think that I would do that.
Okay.
I don't think...
I think I might see you in, like, at first, even though I know you, at first, from the
back, I might be like, "That might be Chucky."
If you saw me in overalls, I would probably give off tiny farmer vibes.
Yeah.
No.
If I was really small and wearing overalls.
No, you don't have a sweet look to you.
You have a diabolical look.
I would look sweet if I was small.
If I'm sitting in my bathtub and I'm holding...
I was really small I would be cute and adorable. Which one of us would look the cutest?
Me? I would look like a literal baby. No you wouldn't. You would not. Yeah but you'd have the face of a grown man.
You would look like a baby. Yeah you'd look like
somebody like pretending to be a baby to like get into somebody's house.
You'd be like, "Ooooh." Oh dude, wait, has anyone... I know that people do that thing where they're like
like there's been a couple people who pretend to be like a missing kid. Yeah.
and then like go to the movie Orphan. Yeah. Is there anybody who is like a really small person
and pretended to be a baby? Yeah, you. Yeah. Might be a good idea. That could work. Yeah,
I'm a baby. Why is our baby not growing? Yeah. Yeah. Well, you would be growing too.
It has to happen, right? No. Someone pretending to be a baby, a midge,
babying up, has to happen, dude. A midge? I'm not going to say the full word.
It feels worse.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
He's trying.
He's testing the waters.
I don't know.
I mean, yeah.
A little baby, I think you're supposed to call that.
A baby person?
Yeah.
They want a person of baby.
No.
No, that's so disrespectful.
I take everything back that I said.
Because like they don't wear diapers all the time.
Yeah.
Right?
Have you guys been since I've been gone?
Honestly, I was telling him earlier, I have never, since you moved here, there's not been
five days where I spent less money than when you were gone.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I literally spent $10 in five days and I was like, "He needs to go out of town like every
week."
I was like, "Oh my God, I'm rich.
If Matt didn't live anywhere near me, I would be a millionaire."
Shit.
Yeah.
and sobbing and lonely.
- It's true, I went to the big needle.
I went to Seattle.
Thank you Mike and Lindsey for having me.
- Thank you very much.
- That was his host friend time.
- He was doing a podcaster's exchange program
where he switched with a 12 year old boy
who had a Minecraft podcast.
- Yep.
- Caleb got to house the boy.
- Yeah, at Mumpits.
- It's like everyone's dream.
- No, you have a grandma bed.
Don't try to hide your grandma bed.
I would swap out my grandma bed for,
dude, I need to pitch bunk beds to Jana.
Yeah.
'Cause she fucking--
That would fit the aesthetic.
She's literally, it would, right?
Yeah, you could get like, yeah, big like,
grandma bunk bed.
Or you could get like three cots next to each other
and we could all sleep there whenever we wanted.
Dude, she's just a fucking, she's a maniac.
She's a freak in the sheets in the way
that she just pushes you off the bed
when you're trying to go to sleep.
Yeah.
I need a bunk situation bed.
- Or I just need to break up with her and move out.
- Yeah.
- Might be a good idea.
- Or yeah, you could like put on,
you could make yourself really heavy before you go to bed.
- You could get a weighted blanket.
- Yeah, you could eat a lot of food
or you could wear like armor to bed or something,
but then it would be harder to push you around.
- You guys have weighted blankets?
I have one.
- No.
- I have a 10 pound blanket.
- We used to have one, but we got rid of it.
- I slept under one.
- It's not heavy enough for me.
- I slept under one one time at my brother's house
and I had a dream that I was being crushed by a car.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- All right, yeah.
- I was doing this bit this weekend.
Me and Mike were talking about Austin Powers.
Oh, did I show you guys my Austin Powers Mike got me?
- No. - We went to this flea market
and he found this Austin Powers plush doll.
- Oh my God. - Oh wait, yeah, wait,
hold on, I forgot to tell you guys this.
- Yeah, tell.
- Do tell, pray tell.
- So big news, big appearance for me.
I was leaving, it was this thing called the Punk Rot Flea Market.
I bet that's seriously cool.
It had the Austin Powers plush doll there.
It's what got me that we were leaving.
I'm standing outside getting a pic of it and this woman comes up to me and she has like
two cameras with her.
She's like, "Oh, what?
Can I take a picture of you and your doll?"
I was like, "Oh, okay."
Wow.
People of Seattle?
he took a photo of me on two cameras and says, "I work for the South Seattle Emerald."
No way.
Wow.
So there's going to be a photo of me in the South Seattle Emerald.
Look for me in there in the South Seattle Emerald.
It's going to be great.
It's a big moment for me.
They would never take a photo of me with the kind of things that I find at a flea market.
It's going to be me holding an Austin Powers doll in the South Seattle Emerald.
That'll be big, dude.
Headline, yeah.
We were doing...
Weird freak found on the streets.
Does not belong here.
Weirdest guy.
We need to kill him.
Yeah.
F-file detective.
No.
But before we found that, we were doing this bit where it's like you tell someone you're
about to do this, like, "Oh, do you want to hear my Austin Powers impression?"
Yeah.
And you just do Alan Alda's voice.
It's just like...
Yeah, yeah.
I hate to ask this, but do I make you Randy, baby?
Do I make you horny?
I like that you have, that's probably the third time you've told me about something you've done
and it's just something in Alan Alda voice because that's your go-to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm sorry to bother you but can I have a one million dollars?
He's more polite than anyone in that movie. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm the fat bastard. I'm here to eat your baby.
Basically, I'm the fat bastard.
I'm the fattest bastard of all time and I would absolutely love to eat your baby.
What's that one line, blimey or kibble?
What?
Blimey or kibble from your coaster?
Oh, oh, core blimey, yeah.
Blimey, or kibble.
Does it say or kibble?
No.
It says something kibble.
I don't forget a kibble, man.
Come on.
A kibble would be a hard word to make up.
The fat bastard coaster that I have just says,
there's something mentally wrong with me.
(laughing)
It's not even a recognizable quote.
It's just like, "No, I don't remember fat bastard saying there's something mentally
wrong with me at all."
There's something mentally wrong with me.
But also you could picture him saying it.
I would picture him more saying there's something physically wrong with me.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, you want to start with how you're the biggest, fattest guy I've ever
seen you fucking piece of shit.
The other thing is like the gold member one doesn't say like, "I love gold," or like,
smoke in a pancake it says I've completely forgotten what I just said
so I think that maybe these were being dictated by somebody who contracted
Alzheimer's yeah in the middle yeah exactly what I just said you know you
sell to do like Amazon m-turk for like extra money yeah did you ever do any of
the transcription stuff yeah like a little bit yeah where they would play
like the task was like they play 10 seconds of like an old movie or
something and you're supposed to like put what it's supposed to say and they
don't check any of it. Yeah. You can just put anything. Well that's because I'll watch like movies on
Amazon that clearly only like 10 people have ever watched and like see that
there's a mistake in the subtitles and be like oh yeah I get it now. I did that too.
Amazon what? Amazon Mturk? Mechanical Turk. I mean it was like I was so broke in college
to just like I would spend my extra time at my job where I was like if I had
access to a computer doing these like tasks for Amazon that not for Amazon
Amazon is a marketplace for like people hire people to do you basically work as
a computer slave and it's basically like two cents an hour it's like probably two
bucks an hour yeah damn but you can do it we could do it while we were at our
job our real job also so it was we're doubling up yeah yeah but it was this
- Wispod and Amazon Mturk.
- Yeah, it was a lot of crazy shit.
Like you would do like,
it was a lot of that kind of shit,
like transcription and then a lot of like marketing surveys.
- Yeah, the best part was to try and like luck
into like a high paying survey
by pretending that you were like the,
like it would be like a survey where like,
you'd have to be like a middle aged woman
with two children in order to take it.
But it like rewarded you like $5 for like a 10 minute survey.
So you'd have to try and answer the questions
and make them think that you like,
you have to guess what they want for the survey.
- The answers that got you into the good surveys
were Asian American, 35 years old,
three kids, $120,000 or more.
If you said that, that is like the survey golden goose, dude.
'Cause apparently those people are,
'cause why would, if you're making 120 grand a year
when you have like kids,
why would you be on Amazon M-Turk
fucking like filling out surveys?
So they gotta make it worth their while.
- Yeah, $5.
I'm trying to remember what the other tests were. There were stuff where like you had
to like look at pictures and like and like say yeah yeah a lot of them felt
like they were just like trying like it would it's like a test that they give
like a psychic child in a movie where it's like made me go crazy yeah look at
this yeah look at this picture of the of the devil and type in like five
adjectives yeah no it was like that it would show you like a picture of like
like roadkill and it would be like like what do you like this is this good or
bad yeah it would be like because you're trying to teach an AI like these things
are good, these things are bad.
So you basically did-
There were ones you had to draw stuff to, I think.
Yeah, there was that shit. But you know that job that everyone could play? They're like,
"Oh, we want to kill ourselves because we're the people who have to go on YouTube and remove
all the murder videos?"
Or Facebook, remove all the murder videos and stuff. We were basically doing that job
for $2 an hour sometimes. And it made me go completely insane. And I think in the year
and a half I did it, I think I made $800.
dollars. Yeah, I did not do it as much as you did it. I did it like very, very briefly.
You made $800 over the course of a year, so that's like...
I mean, and I was working, I did it every single day.
Yeah. Yeah, it was fucked up.
Yeah. It was not fun.
It's evil.
And then I had to, and then they don't withhold taxes, so then like, I had to like pay taxes on
it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's diabolical.
Well, the thing, it's nice when you're, when you have a job that's boring.
Yeah.
Because it's, yeah.
I guess, yeah.
It's just a, but yeah.
I should have been playing World of Warcraft. I could have made more money
leveling an account on runescape in that time and then selling it. That's true. I could have weighed like I made like literally
Way more money. Yeah. Yeah, but you would have to see all those cool pictures. That's true
I would have learned right from wrong as a hitman
You'd be a terrible hitman. I would have yeah, I would have
It's too obvious. I would be a great hitman. People you walk in people like people just Agent 47's here
If somebody like kind of real things to like oh
Maybe someone's trying to kill me and then they see me walk into the coffee shop that they're in they're leaving
I think they no one would suspect me of being the hitman, but I would do such a terrible terrible job
With the murder aspect. I don't think I would be silent or or like yeah
I like start to strangle someone and then like fart really loudly
Yeah, cuz you're trying to keep some deep cover so you're doing like
Healing you
Well, the thing is if you walk into if somebody thinks that they're they're about to be killed and some guy walks into a restaurant goes
I'm in a pinwheel hat
Yeah, like a big lollipop.
A big lollipop with like a tight like, you know, like the suits that like bicyclists wear.
So I'm like, "Oh, I just got back from the Tour de France!"
It's just like they can't tell that I'm a hit man.
It's just like, "Oh, I got 67th place in the Tour de France!"
Yeah, they're like, "Oh, that's too many details.
You can't be lying."
I mean this guy must be kind of famous. I actually go up and get his autograph
I should get really close. I have like a big like belt buckle - that has just a gun
It's just like a gun like pointed straight, yeah, it's just like an AR-15
You're trying to play it off as a belt buckle
Oh this is my big Parisian belt buckle
Oh I got it after winning the tour
I did have to win the tour. Actually I was 67th place, the more modest place.
Yeah, I think the more background you give to somebody, the more likely it is that you're
going to kill them.
Yeah.
The more they're like, "Why are you telling me this shit?"
That's why dating is so hard.
I would walk into a coffee shop and I'd be like, "I pretty much didn't have a childhood
and nothing ever happened to me up until now. And there's really nothing interesting about
me in any way."
And they go, "You're a man I can trust."
Yeah.
I'm pretty much a blank slate.
- Basically, basically nothing ever just happened to me,
so like I just didn't do anything,
nothing really happened either.
- I was basically an orphan and I forgot 25 years
and then now I'm in this coffee shop right now.
- I was just chilling for a long time too.
- Also there's certain words that make me act up.
- Yeah, there's a barcode on the back of my head,
you wanna scan that shit?
- What do you, if Agent 47 went to the grocery store,
what do you think he gets rung up as?
- Mm, bananas, 'cause that guy's crazy.
- You think he gets bananas?
- Yeah, maybe.
- Yeah. - 'Cause that guy's loco.
- Yeah, damn coconut, 'cause I guess he--
- Probably a white coconut.
- Probably a shrimp.
- A coconut.
- A young coconut.
- A melon.
- A melon maybe.
- An egg.
- A single egg.
(laughing)
- One white egg.
- Code for a single egg.
It's a gun, they don't sell them at the grocery store.
- Dude, that's probably what it is.
- Probably is a code for a gun.
- Yeah, that would be cool.
- It is cool that he has the barcode on the back of his head.
- I have never played those games.
Why'd they put a barcode on his head?
Let's be honest.
Like what is that?
- So he can purchase his services?
- I don't think that's how,
I don't think you explain that you need a Hitman
and then he's like, "Okay."
And he turns around.
- I need you to scan this first.
That's my price.
- No, no, no, no, don't swipe it, tap it.
It's a chip, you gotta put it in.
- You can scan it, it takes you to his website.
It's like a QR code.
- Oh, see nowadays if they made a Hitman game,
they haven't made one in 25 years.
If they made a Hitman game today,
it would be probably a QR code.
- Did I tell you guys about the time
I almost accidentally charged somebody
like five billion dollars. Did I tell that on the podcast before?
No, you told me it outside of this.
Okay, well I was working at the liquor store and with the way that barcode, the barcode
scanner works is you scan a barcode and it's like a number associated with it and it just
auto fills. It's actually a skew number, but it auto fills the skew number into the like
into just the text field, like whatever text field you have selected. So I like I was like
I accidentally had the price selected before I scanned it. It scanned in the skew number,
which is like you're like one five two nine six one five three and I came so
close to pressing the like finish and pay button like or like the charge and
it literally would have been like like like five hundred billion dollars.
It would have been so funny if that just like if it was on like like a debit
card that like it it went through like it like you just overdrafted. Yeah,
- $500 million?
- I didn't notice.
- Dude.
- That would be so sick.
- So, 'cause the person didn't notice
'cause I canceled it in time,
but I just stood there, just scanned the thing,
and just going like, oh!
Just 'cause I realized how much of a close call it was.
I was just laughing, all like ringing them up.
- That would have been so good.
- It was so funny.
- That's why we should get a Square Reader.
- Yeah.
- And tip, please.
(laughing)
- We should get a tip.
- Dude, that is such a good scam,
is just get a Square Reader
and just charge people a lot of money without telling them.
You guys get one of the small ones
that like attaches to your phone
and be like, "Oh, my phone screen's broken
"so you can't really read it."
But just put it--
- Well, dude, I get freaked out
'cause I just got a new debit card
and it's one of these tapping ones.
- I gotta get a new debit card, dude.
- I just got one and--
- Did I show you mine?
- No.
- It's so fucked.
- I got the, I just got a new one
and it's a tapping one and those like,
you just get it close to the thing.
- Yeah.
- So like if I, if somebody just like--
- Yeah, yeah, if somebody had those
and just held it.
- Just put it near me.
- No, it's crazy.
- And they wouldn't be able to get much money.
- That's why I like you doing the tap,
when it's tapping, I like using my phone
'cause I have to like--
- Oh yeah, yours is fucked.
- Yeah, my credit card's so fucked.
- Yeah, that is fucked.
- It's about to snap at the thing too.
- Just get a new one.
- I was trying to buy, I made my,
I couldn't sleep last night and mimosas make me sleepy,
so I tried to buy mimosas and I had to put it
on my credit card.
- Mimosas make you sleepy?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Why don't you just buy like melatonin?
of them and then I think they make you sleepy because you usually have them in
the morning yeah it's and you're like oh I should be awake right now but I'm
drunk yeah yeah that's in you know what it is I usually have mimosas at
Christmas too so I'm up early dude cuz I'm so excited about the presents we did
the fucking Andre champagne that shit at Christmas it's $2 a bottle oh man get
fucking 15 of them yeah oh dude it's the best God I actually don't drink on
Christmas because I think is disrespectful to the Santa Claus yeah
It's not disrespectful to Santa.
It's very disrespectful to Santa.
What do you think?
You give Santa eggnog, he drunk drives.
No, you give him milk.
No, you give him eggnog.
You give him milk.
By the end of the night, you know Santa faded by the end of Christmas morning.
He isn't.
He doesn't do that.
He's swerving that sleigh.
He's like, "Skrrr."
That's not true.
Don't say that about Santa Claus.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Poor kids don't get presents.
Well, I guess that's that.
God, fuck 'em.
I don't need to do this 'til next year.
I guess I know two guys who aren't getting presents this year.
Yeah.
I don't have a brother.
I grew up.
You're not getting a present from me this year.
I grew up and I don't get presents anymore.
You're not getting a present from me this year either.
What?
Not from you?
What the fuck?
I got, I, you know.
I don't give a shit about Santa, but you?
You guys were really disrespectful towards Christmas just now.
Which one of you gave me a gnome outfit last Christmas?
That was me.
Oh, yeah.
And you gave me a Paw Patrol helmet.
Yeah, which I've never seen you wear.
It's too small.
So?
I can't put it on my fucking head.
Also, don't shrink your head.
- You drank your head.
- You didn't even take a single picture with it ever.
- I did take a photo with it, I showed it to you.
- No you didn't.
- He took a picture of my gnome suit.
- He did, he loved the gnome suit.
- The gnome suit was way better, dude.
- Yeah, see this--
- It's a way better gift.
- I'm definitely not getting you a present this year.
- I'm gonna get you one.
- You didn't even, you didn't get me one last year.
- I'm leveling up.
- I didn't want to.
- Or for my birthday, or for my other birthday,
or my other birthday, or my other birthday,
or my other birthday, or any of my other birthdays.
- I don't like giving presents.
(laughing)
That's kind of true. I kind of hate giving gifts.
Giving gifts sucks unless it's you can give somebody like something like a
Paw Patrol helmet.
Except I got Rex. I realized this the other day. I bought Rex something and I'm not
gonna say his real last name but he has a very pretty normal last name but I
didn't know his last name at the time so I and I bought him a Christmas gift and
it was a kettle with the Star of David on it and I put his billing address
I put his name as Rex Shlomo Eisenstein.
They never delivered it because they were like, "This guy doesn't exist."
I forgot about that until the other day.
I ordered something on Amazon.
I was like, "Do you want to send this to Rex Shlomo Eisenstein?"
I was like, "No, this guy doesn't exist at all."
Yeah.
Then I told him he was mad at me.
probably wanted that kettle. He wanted it so bad. Yeah, it wasn't even started. It
was an Israeli flag on it. Oh, okay. Yeah, but she was because he needed a kettle. I
just got one of those the other day. I actually just purchased one. Really? Yeah.
That's nice. Yeah, for the for the... Can you imagine if Israel was in like the
like World Cup of Soccer one year? Isn't it? No, like in the finals
or something. Oh. That would be the most buck wild fucking... Yeah. The cross
Palestine? I don't think Palestine has a... I think Israel versus Palestine would be
a good... The World Cup? The Marlboros.
Yeah yeah yeah Palestine will get free cigarettes for a year if they win and
Israel wins well they get this. They get Palestine. That would be a... If Israel wins
Palestine will also get free cigarettes but it's because they'll all be executed
- It's very funny to me.
- They're all filled with racism.
- Not Israel Palestine, but it's very funny to me
that there's still like countries that now,
like young people from these countries,
hate people from like the country right next door to them.
- Oh yeah, like Armenia and Azerbaijan.
- And like Turks and Serbs.
I played a fucking game of Valorant two days ago
where it was like four people on my team
that were all playing from like that area.
And it was like two Turkish guys and two Serbian guys.
And they just said like, "Fuck you, you fucking piece of shit,"
to each other the entire time.
I was like, "I can't believe that these guys still..."
- That's sick, dude.
- I don't even know what happened there, and I don't care.
- It's kind of like the US and Canada.
- Nah, dude, no.
- We have a pretty sour relationship with Canada.
- Do we?
- Yeah. - What'd they do to us?
- I mean, these fucking Quebecois people
coming down and going to Hampton Beach.
- We deserve that land.
- That's actually true. - You gotta annex it.
At least Montreal.
i think montreal should become part of uh... vermont i don't think there's a
single part of canada that i would care to have
they can just make it falls
the good we have a good part of niagara for all we have the good part of you
know i went out of the new york city by the fall and a shit they should divide
up canada into different size pieces and unlike can have its be so that every
whatever no so every state is the same size so like they could give a lot of
canada to rhode island
like a tiny bit to texas and just make them all the exact same size as a split
a weapon
provinces
right and then
and then and then what
now let's keep going here and then i will let you know so anyway you've been all
the states will be the same size and then the flag would make sense 'cause
right now the flight makes no sense 'cause all the stars are the same size
that is really far how can you know how can these represent different states
not no are our flag
but the hell is wrong with you
Well the Canadian flag makes sense because it's one leaf that's the same size.
Yeah.
Which is Canada's one country that's the same size.
We have all these fucking white stars.
Yeah, and it's like how am I supposed to tell which star of this...
How am I supposed to tell which star is Hawaii so I can cross it off my own personal flag?
[Laughter]
It's...
It's so I need it.
Honestly dude, fuck Hawaii.
For real.
Yeah.
What the fuck do these people do all day, bro?
Sure.
for sir is all good like get a fucking job you feel like what's wrong with you
do don't touch it when you do it do it he plays a beautiful country getting drunk
on cooking literally water and falling into a volcano connected to hell it
literally is a portal to hell dude it shoots hellfire I think Hawaii is good
dude you are Hawaiian breakfast you only like Hawaii because of Lilo dude they
think that fucking no they think that that leaves and coconuts are like they
They think that's like business casual.
They think you can make a necklace out of a flower.
I swear to God.
You make that out of a chain.
Walk into a WeWork in Hawaii.
Count how many fucking like giant dresses made out of leaves you see.
Why?
It sucks dude.
No, Hawaii is goaded.
I swear to God.
Hawaii is goaded.
They have what?
What do they have?
Spam for breakfast?
Dude, I actually did some freelance work for a Hawaiian guy like two or three years ago.
I did some freelance stuff.
His name was Tito.
Tito.
I did some freelance work. I had to skateboard and snowboard and surf.
We agreed on a price. It was $1,200, right?
I do the work. I send it to him. He sends me a box full of fucking shells.
Okay? I call him. I'm like, "Tito, what the fuck is this?" He's like, "Count them. It's $1,200.
Right there."
You can eat those.
Yeah. Plus, they're food and clothes. So, come on.
I was like dude this is the worst place in the world.
And then he said "Aloha" which actually also means "that's just enough shells".
Aloha, they literally, they have a language, they have their own language.
Oh, we have our own language, we're a state.
Their own language, it's one word.
Over and over again.
They're like fucking, they're like that, they're like that fucking, what's his name? Hodor.
They can only say Aloha.
They're like Pikachu.
They're exactly like a Pokemon.
They can only say Aloha. Half of them are named Aloha and then the other ones are Aloha Jr. dude.
yeah it's literally every Hawaiians name I had a big Maui trip planned for yeah
there's a guy there's a big Maui guy named trip the really big guy in Maui
his name is trip yeah and he says what's up oh yeah aloha and he's water type
they're literally like I mean that is the worst place in the world it's Hawaii
is ugly it looks like it looks like a postcard it's a what am I had guess
- Are you supposed to hang out on a piece of paper?
- Hawaiian coffee's really good.
- Hawaiian coffee?
- Yeah.
- What is that?
Is it coffee made out of sand?
- It's coffee, they put lava in it to make it hot.
- They put vanilla and macadamia nuts in it.
- Oh, that sounds so good.
- Yeah, that seriously sounds awesome.
- No, you guys are talking--
- Hey, hey, Pat, aloha.
That means fuck you.
- Talking shit about our 50th estate.
- No, it shouldn't even be a state.
Here's what we do.
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
- We swap out Hawaii for Puerto Rico.
- Yeah, absolutely.
We just Puerto Rico should be a state. Yeah
No, no, absolutely, yeah if you want to have another civil war
Try and merge Puerto Rico and Hawaii because Puerto Rico are the most upstanding
Hard-working people in the world and Hawaii are just scumbag fucking pieces of mango addicts
Who sit around all day fucking too far? No, they're pieces of shit too far every single person in Hawaii
I hope, I honestly hope the big one hits.
- No.
- I've been, I hope the big one hits Hawaii tomorrow, dude.
- You know why?
'Cause they would all, you know,
a big wave starts coming to wipe out the entire thing.
- Yeah, they'd all grab their boards.
- The entire island starts paddling towards it, dude.
It's a stupid thing.
- That's right.
- Don't, right?
- There's so many concussions from coconuts
falling onto their heads.
It's fucking embarrassing, dude.
I don't, I want nothing to do with Hawaii.
- Stop talking about Hawaii like that.
news from their more right he got
my chance to really change but in
right he gets the path of the
i_d_ not at the worst i mean i think it's a very absurd me how to be ninja
worst-case scenario
i go to hawaii
right at some point
they arrest me
put me in a hawaiian jail what i have to do i have to split a piece of bamboo
with the other leg and i'm fucking free at you after a year you have to do you
know that
yes they'll say it where you were sending were you in what it's all bamboo
the entire it's all bamboo and leaves. Yeah they're saying like oh you have to do a
work program during the day here in prison and they hand you your
hollowed out coconut with a pina colada. They hand me a snorkeling mask and they say
find 10 fish. You have to tan all day.
Oh no. Yeah that's I mean it's literally the worst place in America.
It's not even in America. It's in the sea. God literally within the
next a thousand years, the reason that God had created global warming is to put
Hawaii back underwater. No. How did people even find Hawaii? He didn't do that. Like what
the fuck? Like why? People have... some... like Hawaii... is that just where they
put all the worst people in the world? That's not what... no. For like a million years
they were just like... if you had like like a cousin who couldn't get his act
together, you'd be like, "Oh no, there's this beautiful place. Go to Hawaii."
Well yeah, that's people who couldn't grow out of making macaroni necklaces
got sent there. This place is a joke man. It's a fucking joke. And not a funny one either.
No. No. Why are you guys doing this about Hawaii? What's wrong with this? Why are you so pro-Hawaii? It's
great there. You would fit in. I've never been. You would fit in.
You would fit in. I had yesterday, I had these chips. They were Hawaiian chips.
so Hawaiian barbecue flavor. What the fuck are you even talking about?
Hawaiian barbecue chips. That's not Hawaii dude.
A Hawaiian barbecue is when they just leave the meat out and
hope that some lava comes and cooks it for them.
Yeah. Are you kidding me? Hawaiian barbecue is literally rocks.
You want lava in your life? Yes. More lava in your life? Yes.
Dude, you would be like, you would die.
If you move to Hawaii, I give you seven days before you literally like
sit in lava accidentally don't notice till it's at your waist and then you're
just gone.
I would notice. You would move to Hawaii and you would
go to your roommates every day and say I think there's lava in our house.
I think I saw a piece of lava run across the floor.
And they'd say
Aloha, Mahalo. Which is the same word by the way.
I think I have lava sickness. Look at Aloha and look at Mahalo.
Okay. Look at the letters in them. It's the same word. No. Yeah. It's Mahalo. People in
Hawaii go up to they go to McDonald's they say, "Uh yeah I'll have the Aloha
Mahalo." Yeah. And a Mahalo Aloha. Every single thing on the menu is the Aloha
Mahalo Aloha. You can get um. You can get an Aloha Mahalo there. I think you can get. Yeah.
Some there's like some Hawaiian. Did you know that the Hawaiian language has over
50 different words for recliner. And no word for job. What dude? That's so messed up to
say. About Hawaii? Yeah. Why? They're great people. They're not. Every single, I mean
scumbags dude. They invented the worst shirt worn by the worst white people in
the world too. They literally invented the most annoying fucking shirt and they were
like you know they saw it they made it annoying on purpose they call it Aloha
Mahalo there and they were like you know what we'll call this we'll name this
after us this is the Hawaiian shirt my nuts tank yeah oh yeah we there's this
app called big you can just type whatever you want into it and then shake
it and yeah green flashes really fast and I'm says my nuts dank hypnotic what are
you eating you just did you just take something off Anna's desk and eat it
yeah he took ice off of me. It's just a pen. It's a kind of pen. Look over you have like blue ink all over your mouth.
Did you eat a pen? No. I'm just chewing ice. No. I was just breathing really hard.
Okay here's this list. This list was sent to us by a listener on Patreon by World
Park. So thank you World Park for sending this because this is a good website.
This is from factinate.com. Okay. This is a list called "Call the burn unit.
these epic comebacks are deadly. And then it says fact in a video of the day,
but it's not a video. It's just a list. There's no video on the page. Um,
but so I'll just read this first, this first comeback here. There's only four,
but I found a second list, you know? So here's the first one. Um,
it's kind of a story based thing here. So number four,
keeping him in suspense.
I was at a friend's place with a lot of people who I didn't really know too well.
We were all having a few beers. Whoa. Suddenly this dude from across the
table says to me quite aggressively that my suspenders were ugly and that they
made me look like I was trying too hard which to be fair I was and then in bold
but I still dealt him a crushing blow all right without skipping a beat I stood up
unclipped my suspenders and put them in my pocket when I sat down I looked
straight into his eyes and replied now let's talk about that face tattoo of
yours yeah that's fire that is a crushing blow you guys ever had an epic
- Was that a comeback moment?
- I think so.
- Which was what?
- I think I was,
yeah, there was like a guy,
like a guy making fun of me.
I think I was ordering food.
I said,
"Thank you, have a nice day."
- What?
- I said, "Thank you, sir, have a nice, I don't know."
have just you know I'm jet-lagged I straight up I aborted that joke midway
through cuz I couldn't figure out the setup yeah hey you uh your parents wish
they aborted you halfway through yeah you after saying that fucking bullshit I
I just said Jesus Christ that is that is I've said
Some fucking horrible like
Stupid bits on here. I think that is the worst one I've ever done by golly. You didn't even say anything. I know
How the fuck no it was better fuck the people listen to this like people listen to this and they like to listen to it
Yeah, and I'm on it. Yeah, you really do suck. Yeah fucking shithead
God damn it. I should just you should all get your fucking brains checked
This crap, I mean
Probably true you might answer you could have cancer you have a tumor in your brain that makes you stupid
It could be what that would be so cool if we found out every single one of our fans
Some tumor that like like yeah, really like cuts brain fun. Yeah
Like yeah
like a contagious tumor
Like a new disease and it turns out like the only like it is everybody who listens to this has
That could happen they have a brain eating it's like video drum everybody's been everybody's been to the same river in Brazil. Yeah
Wait, I also went to Brazil in like 2017 wait
Oh, and there was that huge outbreak of that evil worm that eats your brain?
Yeah.
Did you also pee into the river?
Yeah, I did.
Wait, and did you also drink the pee with the straw afterward?
Well, yeah, of course.
The pee sits on top of the river.
Whoa, dude, alopecia alert.
That guy doesn't have any fucking eyebrows in that car.
He just saw me.
Whoa.
He saw me and he heard me say that and he looked at me.
Yeah, well, that's a baby.
He's picking his nose, dude.
Holy God.
Get your act together, bro.
Oh, I see him now.
Oh, he ate it!
He ate his book?
He ate his book!
- He ate his bug!
- Damn, okay, this guy's actually cool as fuck.
- He ate the bug.
- Grown man eating his bugs.
- Yeah, in the car, dude, in the car with your kids,
just eating boogers. - I got nothing
to say to you, man.
You, I can't touch you, bro.
- Right, yeah. - If you're a grown man,
if you were like in a presidential debate
and you just fucking licked a bug in the middle, dude,
I think you might win.
- Yeah. - Right?
- Shows that you're human. - Could, yeah.
- Well, it also just, like, yeah.
- It shows you don't give a damn fuck.
- Let's be honest, when was the last time you guys ate a bug?
I don't think I ever have. I think that is always disgusting. I've picked my nose a bunch
of my life, but I've never eaten it.
I was really hoping you guys would, I would trick one of you into saying today.
Today.
Ha ha.
Oh, you got me. Oh no. No, I don't understand what's, I don't understand what's attractive
about like why would you want to do that? That doesn't seem like it would ever seem
like a good thing to do.
Yeah. It's funny to make like your little brother eat your booger.
but like a like a baby maybe would eat dirt but I feel like when you get like
there's an age where you know you're not supposed to eat dirt or poop and I feel
like when I have a baby go along with that babies will totally eat poop if
they could know they well babies probably eat stuff that they would
apparently disgusting just whatever they can get as a baby like that baby like a
booger should be included up the apple and eat it when I was a kid apparently I
I would poop my pants and then I would smell it and vomit. I'd poop or fart and
then I'd just go, I was so gross that I would just vomit immediately. My little brother had like a
bad like, I guess, like he had like a sympathetic like gag reflex. Oh yeah.
Yeah so if you like went like or like around him he would like start going like
like, "Eh, eh."
Ugh, that's a bad place to be, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, that sucks.
I was, the only time I think I've ever really hurt someone's feelings like a stranger.
It was like every episode of the show for me.
No, no, no.
You've never had your feelings hurt.
I've never hurt your feelings.
What are you talking about?
Shut up.
One time I was at a bar and a guy, I was at a bar in, I may have said this actually, I
was at a bar in California and this is when I had my fucked up stupid haircut and I sat
next to this guy trying to get a drink. And he's like this old fat trucker dude. And he
was like, very playfully, he was like, "Huh, your barber messed something up?" Said it
like that. And he laughed to himself. And I just looked at him and was like, "You're
really fat." I was in the mood to get into an argument or a fight with this guy. And
just looked like so sad he was like you took it too far man I think about that
guy a lot just like a guy like you think would be able to take that just just to
go for someone who looks psycho like you with the skull it specifically I like
that person to be like oh yeah we're gonna do like a playful ribbing here and
neither of us are gonna go too far yeah it's like did I look evil yeah you can't
do that to yeah I mean what he would kill me was bare hands but oh yeah yeah he was
a sensitive trucker he was a sensitive trucker dude yeah he listened like Dolly
Parton as he as he drove his truck yeah he's like damn dude you suck a sensitive
trucker yeah to make him playful again yeah dude 100% yeah you know truckers
suck - they're all babies I agree yeah truckers might be the
- He's the least heroic people in the world.
- Absolutely.
- You guys know about Trucker Sucker?
- No.
- It's a guy that, it's a guy online.
- Let me guess, he sucks truckers.
- Yeah, this guy's addicted to sucking off truckers.
- He's addicted?
- He's addicted to it.
(laughing)
He's addicted to sucking truckers off.
- No.
- That can't be true.
- He can't be addicted, there ain't no nicotine
in a trucker cock.
- There's nicotine, baby.
- God damn, you didn't say it ain't so.
Okay, so this one this list is longer than I thought because it starts with four
So I thought it would maybe be counting down from four, but the next one is five. Okay, interesting
It's like Star Wars number five not my type a
Friend of mine in first year university had never really dated any girls yet
Yeah
This dumb meathead who were kind of friends with him who were kind of friends with told him one day when you do get a girlfriend
I'm totally going to sleep with her the guy absolutely slayed him
He responded if I had a girlfriend who would sleep with you her cheating on me wouldn't be the issue
Dan that's actually fire if you're if your girlfriend folks your best friend you it's not an issue
I actually didn't ever care in the first place cuz yeah, he was to be that low
Doesn't bother me. Yeah, I wasn't supposed to be fucking this stupid whore, but he slayed him though that doesn't he did slay him
Yeah, I think all of these could be spiced up by saying I don't you're fat at the end. Yeah
No, all right. Well, maybe you'll get this one number six family. Oh you fucked my girlfriend
Yeah, actually that reflects poorly on her character. So yeah, that that's that's not oh
Not nice of her. Yeah, you throw a pokeball. Yeah
Maybe maybe you'll get this one though Patrick. This is number six family rude. Okay, this is this is like
Done like Star Wars. Why does it go four or five six? I
I still think about this comeback to this day. I have two little brothers and it was my dad's birthday
So the semi-extended family was all at a restaurant to celebrate
I just graduated from my dad's alma mater and my middle brother was currently a junior there
However, my youngest brother a friend. What is this a logic puzzle?
What?
Burn a freshman had opted to go to a state school at one point back. My uncle said so youngest brother
How does your dad feel about you breaking the trend?
My little brother thought about it for a moment and then said, "Well, he probably doesn't mind considering I also broke the trend of not being able to get higher than a 3.0."
The table absolutely exploded in laughter and whooping.
My other brother and I just stared at each other across the table like, "Oh my god, did we just get crushed?"
It's especially funny because my little brother is one of those shy high school kids who went off to college and then suddenly came back fun and socially confident.
I was hoping that development would happen. I just never expected it to stab me in the face.
3.0 is the blood alcohol content.
That's a BAC.
He blew a 3.0.
That would be impressive.
This is a kind of a baseline 3.0 BAC.
It's kind of sick.
If it dips below 2, you die.
Like fucking like that.
Like speed.
Like that statham.
Yeah.
Hurt in a crank.
Yeah, like crank.
Yeah.
Like heroin.
If your blood alcohol content goes below 2.0.
That would be a good movie.
you're driving a bus like speed. That would be a sick move. And if he goes below 2.0 the bus explodes.
Doesn't matter how fast you go, you can go as fast as you want. You just have to do a normal route on a city bus in Cincinnati.
You can't get caught drunk driving is the thing. Yeah exactly. Like everybody on the bus is old.
Yeah. So they're always talking to you about the routes or whatever and they're
like, "Oh I used to go over..." They're always like doing that old people thing where old people ask for a bus
exception and they're like can you make up four stops for me that are actually
between two stops? And the guy goes, "I don't fucking care."
Yeah, "Man, I wasn't supposed to do this today. Somebody called out. I wasn't
supposed to be here. I wasn't supposed to be driving. I was supposed to be at home."
I think about becoming a bus driver sometime.
Yeah, you could never.
I could.
A bus driver is a job--
Neither of you can drive. I'm the driver.
A bus driver is a job where you can be psycho and
and there's nothing that anybody can do about it.
- Yeah, what are you gonna do?
- Because you are, that is one of the ultimate,
like, you are in power.
- Especially in Boston, yeah.
- The crazier you are, also,
the straighter you are, - Anywhere, anywhere.
- the bus driver you are.
- Who's gonna, who, if a bus driver's being psycho,
what's the passenger gonna do?
They're gonna get off the bus, that's literally it.
- You also, you have diplomatic immunity.
- You can't touch a bus driver,
yeah, you can't talk to them.
- But what if they're so crazy they don't let you out?
- That you could do that, that's what I'm saying.
As a bus driver, you could literally do anything you want.
- If someone touches you as a bus driver,
you like immediately make $50,000.
- Yeah, they get fined like a billion dollars.
- Yeah. - No, it's like sick.
- It's so cool.
- It's the closest thing you can have to like
the kind of protection that they give police officers.
- It's like being the king's son in like a fantasy world.
- Oh, I thought you meant if the bus driver hits you.
- No, no. - If the bus driver hits you,
you also get fined a billion dollars
'cause you touched the bus driver and it's on camera.
- It's literally a cootie situation.
- Yeah.
You know what's funny?
I guess it's such a problem in New York,
we're like moving here on the train
where it says like assaulting,
assaulting MTA employees is like a felony or whatever.
- Yeah.
- Man.
- Dude, I mean those--
- They had to put up a sign 'cause it kept happening.
- Those signs have talked me down the ledge quite a few times.
- Yeah.
- Swear to God, dude, I've been in there--
- Well, that's what I'm saying, maybe it used to be hard
or bad to be a bus or train driver,
but now that they have that stuff in place,
even if you get the shippy out of you,
you're gonna become rich.
- True.
That's literally the goal.
That's why bus drivers are so cantankerous.
Is because they're trying,
and they tell you in the orientation.
Basically, we'll give you a million dollars
if anyone touches you.
And so they sit there all day being like,
"Fuck you, stupid fucking pussy."
Skipping stops for no reason.
Yeah, exactly.
Skipping a stop, flipping the bird.
Yeah, driving by truckers and doing this,
trying to get them to honk their horn in everyone's face.
Scare someone's dog on the bus.
Just putting the AC all the way off
in the middle of the summer,
the heat on, right, just cranking it.
They're all just like sweating, dying, trying to get to work,
they're in such a bad mood.
- Here's my idea.
- And then when they leave, when you go,
whenever you pull up to the stop,
you stick your face out into the aisle
and you say, like smile, then like,
have a nice day, right?
Just waiting to get just whopped.
- Yeah, here's my idea.
So Caleb does become a bus driver, right?
- Okay.
- We hire somebody, beat the fucking shit out of him.
- He's literally genius. - He's the bus driver.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Just fucking like broken body.
- We don't even have to, we can just get a homeless guy.
We just get like the, we pay him--
- No, no, no.
- We pay him in Seagram's Escapes.
- Ric Flair.
- Ric Flair?
- Yeah.
- And we still pay him in Seagram's Escapes?
- Yeah, 'cause I want it to look real but not hurt.
- Mm-hmm.
- So I'll--
- Oh, you'll keep like the, what's it called?
The thing, it's like the little razor.
- Oh, keep the blood packet, oh yeah.
- The little razor and you cut like your,
- Yeah, yeah. - Above your eyebrow.
as soon as people get on you just have you have it already cut because you
forgot it's just like blood dripping down your face like Wrestlemania just like
good afternoon we hire a special-effects person to help them make help make the
like fight look the fight look real on the on the bus cameras and they go way
overboard by accident it's like your head blows up my head blew up is that
what they do in wrestling they cut their own head yeah yeah they cut above there I
I forget what it's called, but they cut above their eyebrow.
- That's, okay, that's my, whenever people say
wrestling's fake, it's like, dude, what's this?
- Some of it's real.
- The Undertaker still threw that fucker off that cage.
- Yeah.
- Like, they get fucked up sometimes.
- Yeah, no, absolutely.
- It's an honorable job.
- Yeah. - Right.
- Oh, like, people were complaining, it's like,
oh, like, fucking, oh, this person didn't actually sleep
with this person's wife or something like that.
Like, who gives a shit about that?
They're throwing each other,
they're cutting each other's heads.
- Yeah, like, this is, it's not, it's hard.
They feel bad after it.
- Oh, fuck.
Rachel was telling me-- - I think they're like coal miners.
- There's like some dude,
his move is pulling out like a pizza cutter,
and he cut Chris Jericho's head with a pizza cutter.
- That's sick. - Yeah.
- That's very cool.
Oh my God.
- She was telling me that we gotta go
to like a wrestling tournament. - I would love to.
Wrestling is one of those things
I feel like I missed the boat on,
but it would've been a good thing to be into.
- I wanna go to like an underground one
where they throw each other into like light bulbs and shit.
- Yeah, that's good.
I only like wrestling if they're dressed like monsters.
You missed the drag wrestling show the other day.
Where they literally...
Were they dressed like monsters?
No, no.
Janna tried to go but she couldn't.
But at first I was like, "Oh, that sounds like fine."
And then I saw a video of it.
All of them have like five mouths on their face and shit.
It's like this crazy like special effects makeup, pan-slappery shit.
It looked pretty cool.
Yeah, Jacques was trying to get us to go to that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Number seven.
Do I know you?
I witnessed this exchange between two of my friends when they were having a fight.
My one friend yelled, "Everyone thinks you're a jerk!"
Without batting an eyelash, the other one replied, "Well, you know what everyone thinks
about you?
Nothing.
No one ever thinks about you.
I know I don't."
"Welp," points to my second friend.
Whoa.
Sounds like that guy is a jerk.
Yeah.
That is not very kind.
He has three friends, and that's his second one.
Number eight, "Belt it out, Granny."
"My dear grandmother. She had a quick and savage wit. My fiancé and I held up 'meet
the whole family, get together at my house.' It was the first time his father
met my grandmother. His dad was a large physically--"
That was a lady or a gay man writing.
Huh?
I didn't know. I thought this was a--
What on earth are you even talking about?
I thought the author of this was a fella.
Why?
I don't remember.
You think women can't do burns?
No.
You think women can't have grandmothers?
Are you kidding?
- What are you talking about?
- What is leading you to believe this is a woman?
- Well, it's a fiance with one E, so it's a male fiance.
What does it matter?
- I thought that's it.
Nevermind.
- I'm so confused.
- I'm shipping you off to Hawaii.
- Yeah, dude, honestly, that time zone makes sense right now for me.
- True.
In Hawaii, dude, you would be like, "I'm gonna be jet lagged for three days."
- The Hawaii time zone, it's 5 PM.
- I'm gonna be jet lagged for three days.
all day. It's always sunset. Yeah right and they're like well we're not gonna work it's
sunset. Yeah 5 p.m. I just got off work yeah I better go get a beer.
Oh great. A Hawaiian beer. You guys are making fun of it. It sounds better and
better every time you do that. Yeah it actually does sound pretty cool. Yeah
yeah no no jobs. I think you're just jealous of Hawaii. I'm not jealous. Not
really there's no jobs the men there somehow get 600 pounds eating only fruit
it's fucking impressive yeah they have to fight spirits all the time yeah yeah I
know their spirits in Hawaii yeah if you do I know there's elementals over there
you take a girl out to go dancing right they start playing they start playing
evacuate the dance floor and you're out there with the girl just like banging on
your chest and fucking doing a bunch of slap dancing and shit it's a beautiful
beautiful place yeah it was the first time his father and my grandmother his
dad was a large physically intimidating man with a beer gut he began telling
stories to my grandmother about how my fiance was a mischief maker when he was
young he then told my grandmother how he would take off his belt and whip him for
being bad my frail little grandmother still stares directly at my husband's
dad's tummy that's a great phrase my husband's dad's tummy and says your
belt however could you find it future father-in-law was gobsmacked these are
very polite usually what are you talking about think he got destroyed I mean he
got destroyed but like I've got a smile when you rushed and usually when you see
somebody own someone in public they use a very naughty word and none of these
have yeah how many more are there there's several more whoa why'd they start at
four yeah I thought that they're only gonna be four here what are you
complaining also long - fucking complain oh here's a good one number 14
something's fishy the cafeteria lunch lady got me in front my whole class
I smelled her snitch. That day...
[Laughter]
Smelled like straight tuna.
I got my daily dose of Omega-3s
just from the smell of your pussy, lady.
Wow, the lunch lady smells like tuna.
God damn.
That day we were having tuna fish for lunch.
I was upset at this option and said,
"Tuna fish? I'd rather have a poop sandwich."
[Laughter] Without missing a beat, this 80-year-old
lady fires back, "Wait right there.
I'll go make you one in the back."
Needless to say, I went with the tuna.
what dude what you asked for a pooping honestly if I'm calling that cafeteria
ladies bluff yeah yeah I'm saying sandwich right now don't make me a shit
sandwich see what happens to you trying to serve a child a sandwich of your own
shit on it yeah an idiot the only reason that this that this child lost the
comeback war here is because they they went with the tuna yep yeah yeah yeah
sounds yeah on the double toots yeah like dude he's this kids getting a huge
Yeah, with extra poop. That would be a good thing to say too.
Yeah, poop with sauce.
Yeah, open face.
Open face poop with sauce sandwich.
I want sausage gravy on it.
Cause I think some...
Oh god.
Poop with gravy on it.
Something about eating poop is normal to me.
Eating poop with like normal food condiments is disgusting to me.
Mayo.
Oh no.
That's so gross dude.
Like cause it's like trying to make it more palatable.
palatable. Yeah, it's not just like a funny thing to eat. It's like
Like if you ate a burger in the middle of it was poop. Yeah, like that is so much more disgusting Lucy
Juicy Lucy with poop in it. Yeah. Oh
God, well, I would probably probably get away with it cuz like you don't know what's in there till you take a bite
Yeah, you know right yellow poop. Yeah
this
You ever taken a yellow poop? No. You're gonna make me vomit. Yeah, you ever taken an orange poop?
Look how long it is. Look at this scroll bar. Somebody I knew had an orange poop on them. That's a really long scroll bar.
Yeah, I'm on I scrolled down to number 27 and we're still like maybe a fifth of the way down this scroll bar
So we're not gonna finish this. I messed this one up, but here's one
This is a comeback that maybe Patrick would use it seems
Number 27 this comeback gets an A.
Another fucking thing for me to know.
Piece of shit.
Hey, you need to speak up idiot.
Yeah, one day I'm going to snap.
During my university days, he had university days, that's what I'm referring to.
I ran into an acquaintance of mine as I was holding a Green Lantern graphic novel.
This acquaintance was with his girlfriend and when he introduced me to her
her the first thing she says to me while shaking my hand was aren't comic books
for kids my instance was my instant response shocked even me I replied aren't
those a cups for kids flabbergasted that someone I just met would say that to me
that I replied on instinct still my greatest comeback ever shit dude a woman
saying something not even Rudy and you say you have the boobs of a child you
literally have a child this is my great yeah one eyebrow super high hmm nice
comic books for kids I'm a pedophile so I should know yeah I recognize those tits
they're from a kid there's so many of these dude holy more disgusting ones
Yeah, is there any more with like poop and tuna? Well if you guys keep talking I'll scroll through and yeah and find some
Cut the hems of my pants somehow skating I think I think the grip tape is rubbing up against the hems of my pants
What do you have any you have anything to say about that Caleb Caleb we can't have dead air
You realize that right? We can't just fucking sit here and let this guy scroll
You should probably get some new pants.
Yeah, I bought too many pants I think.
Yeah, you did.
Do you remember those gigantic pants I bought?
Those big black pants?
Oh yeah.
I fucked those up pretty bad.
I tried to fix the hem on them.
I just ended up cutting them.
And now one of the legs is shorter than the other.
I think I have to turn them into shorts.
Same with my white pants.
I have to turn those into shorts too.
Those are too short now.
I washed them once and now they shrank.
Oh, that's not right.
Yeah.
You know, it's crazy too, because a good pair of pants, you can't really beat that.
You can't beat a pair of pants that fits great.
Yeah.
But I don't feel like getting them altered.
I don't feel like going to a tailor or something.
Do I work?
Yeah. I mean, you're spending probably like $20 per pair or something.
And it takes you a while to get them back.
And it's just like, damn, I just want to wear those pants.
I want banjo.
Yeah, I just want to get the pants on.
I want to--
There's a hundred of these.
Oh, fuck me.
Thank fucking God, dude.
None of them are good.
Holy shit.
I can't-- I control F. Poop, gay, sex, nothing.
Nothing good.
No poop or gay sex?
There's a few gay ones, but none of them are--
None of these are good, dude.
This is a-- I take it back.
This is a bad list.
read the first few I thought it was fun but it's too long and none of them are
good so we're gonna punish whoever sent this to us I don't remember the name
blocking on patreon number 100 the last one rejected a quote popular girl who
definitely had no interest in me once jokingly asked me out to prom in front
of the whole class I knew she was just trying to ridicule me so I gave her a
brutal taste of her own medicine without a moment's hesitation I said no thanks
Lauren I have standards the whole class and the teacher lost it damn dude holy
fuck you Lauren that is what a fucker yeah that is one of the ones that where
you know that guy did he mumbled that yeah yeah making clearly making fun of
one of him still and they're videoing it. They're playing grinding with a
pencil on the desk.
My God,
he just said
standards. Oh my
no, thanks. Learn you guys. You got
like in a cafeteria that kid and like just like a Michael fucking like rap
battle in a cafeteria. I was like losing their mind and everyone
He went crazy
Too big of a fan of this kid now
uh... her and uh... your hand
the
all my i was going to go on a
and uh... you know you
when i'm going to be a pussy stank
but i were too young for that i had a very nice the area of the room
so you've got a child's tits basically and you've got a little bit of a
security and send
I ain't scared of you motherfuckers. I ain't scared of you motherfuckers. I pull my shit out the whole room gets knocked.
Okay. Alright. Subscribe to the Patreon. Subscribe to the Twitch. Subscribe to...
I'm not pressing stop until you say something else to subscribe to.
Subscribe to BeautyBine.
No!
No! No!