Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Okay man, I don't feel like,
I don't feel like, you know how they invented the wheel
and whatever, all that shit?
I don't feel like the wheel was all that useful.
- Which came first, the wheel or the egg?
- Well the wheel or the car,
'cause like what are you doing with a wheel?
Stop touching my leg.
What are you doing?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop dude.
I can't talk that dude it stopped yeah I have a concussion yeah you're stressing
me out I my cortisol levels are spiking and I'm gonna be stuck like this forever
I'm stuck in hell and you don't know I Caleb insisted that he didn't have a
concussion for I'm literally like two days ago we were on the bus and and he
was asking when something was and I was like oh it's a week from tomorrow and
he was like oh yeah it's four days away when were we on a bus we were going to
see the movie you don't remember that holy shit I'm without a paddle yeah
Caleb badly we were in North Carolina last week and Caleb fucking full-speed
bonks it stopped a sexual assault on the street no full speed at maximum velocity
I stopped it and a soldier on his head on the corner of a shelf which was yeah
what the guy's name who was trying to do he was a box man yeah and he did have he
was wearing shoulder pads he's a businessman you've got to look out for
those and I hit my head on the heel toed shoulder yeah and little did I know
they yeah he did he was he's broken heat in there Caleb and I are at the same
level at the same level now I got knocked I used to be between you guys I'm gonna
knock down one whole strata.
Yeah.
It's going to be interesting to see how we keep up with Cameron.
I'm going to need, it's going to take me a couple weeks.
I just ate a big chop cheese, so I'm like halfway down to your level.
You're at where my old level was?
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, it's going to be a couple weeks before I recoup.
I'm going to need to get a lot of rest and I can't, you're not supposed to look at screens
when you have a concussion.
I just I just had to sit in my bedroom with all the lights off and just kind of
hope I don't get terrified. I'm also pretty scared of the dark is a
big problem for me. Why don't you just get I feel like you just got blue
blockers. I don't think it's the blue. I think it might be the blue.
I don't think blue is bad for you. It's blue.
mm-hmm that's because your brain is red or the blood well no it's red it's blue
so if you think about it it's blue until it touches oh yeah your forehead turned
red mm-hmm it did so your red don't like blue if you ever seen red versus blue oh
I have they versus each other yeah so you block the blue from the red I love
watching two things versus each other this is one of the best genres of yeah
- Yeah, that's why Deadliest Warrior was so great.
- Warrior.
- I love the warriors.
(laughing)
Oh, the warriors.
- Yeah, Patrick is kind of a deadliest voyeur.
- That's true.
- In a lot of ways.
- Yeah, 'cause he looks and then he touches.
(laughing)
- No.
- Yep.
- Yeah, you do.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- Not true.
- Yeah, you designed, you know those like little--
- There's no designs that I can come up with.
- You know like the play place versions
of like kitchens and stuff that the kids use?
you did one of those for that that hotel in Vegas where the guy was like
Wandalei Bay walking through the air ducts and looking at people's bedrooms
well when was that I don't you never heard about that I didn't hear about
that you made that up no I swear I got it did that no it's one Caleb did it's
one of the coolest stories ever there's this guy ran a he ran a voyeur I don't
know if it was in Vegas but it's somewhere in the middle of the country
he ran a motel that he constructed specifically that so that he could just
watch people in their rooms he had like this is different from HH Holmes yeah
Yeah, no, this was like this was like 20 years ago. Okay. Yeah, and he was just like just he had like a whole
Upstairs thing where he could just look through all these like holes in the shit. Are you eating a high - I tell you the most
Fuckin amazing story of your life. You can't eat a high - that is so disrespectful you fucker
Why are you eating a high - cuz I'm hungry and I didn't eat lunch. That's not gonna hell. It's not gonna you carry
- you know what that's gonna do it makes your mouth wet
It's not gonna fucking fill you up.
It makes the worst sound of all time too.
I do have a plugged salivary gland, so this is medical.
This is not medical, it's annoying.
My doctor told me I have to eat candy.
You have to do it-
When you're at your job.
Yes.
No.
You can't wait one hour.
They did not write you a prescription for a Haichu.
They told me that-
Also they said sour candy.
Haichu's not sour, you fucker.
This is kind of sour, it's acai.
I'm through with you. I'm done. Do you carry your backpack just so you can bring acai
haichu with you? No, so I could carry my microphone with me. I think it's because of the haichu.
No. You look like Green Day. Because usually you just wear that thing over your chest with your
mic, right? You are giving me Green Day vibes. Is it because of the tattoo? No. Speaking of,
we all got tattoos in North Carolina. I realized I really was paying respect to North Carolina by
getting a concussion and a tribal tattoo. It's the most OG North Carolina shit of
all time. Yeah, yeah. Cameron got mouser. I got mouser. We did, we did hang out.
In North Carolina we were hanging out with Ducker. Chilling with Ducker a bunch.
I don't know what happened, I think we might have left him there. Really? I think he
didn't get on the flight. He's been going through a lot. He has. Yeah. He's been figuring
his stuff out. I mean you know. Well like Goober saw him. Yeah, Goober saw him. Yeah, it's
pretty bad. Yeah, I heard. And you know what happened with Mommy Duck? Well, that was
Tom. Tom, Mommy Duck was angry. Well, it's been stressful in his house. No, not really. They don't live together anymore.
They don't? No. Well, you know, Mommy Duck's always calling him.
Talking about, "Oh, I'm angry on Tom. I'm angry on Tom." I feel like you don't know him that well.
Yeah, it doesn't sound like. I don't, honestly. I just know he's going through it right now.
Yeah, because the Mommy Duck situation's bad, but that's a whole other thing. I mean,
that's more of a like a product of like Jerry with the brain. True. There's a lot
that a lot more what is affecting you know the Tom and Mommy Duck situation,
which is angry on by the way is the situation there. I've been walking
around just in every store I'm in just doing the thing where you walk you point
at things and say and you know I must do that.
Make me laugh so much. It's like that. Did I get a wrist or I was just like
I'll get a Dr Pepper and you know that's gonna be free. Yeah, can I get a
get a Caesar salad with shrimp and you know I'm not gonna pay for that. It was
making me want to do that on the train, on the plane too. Get on the plane and be
like and you know I'm stealing that. Like just pointing in the cockpit at some like instrument.
Yeah, and you know I'm gonna drive the plane. Can I get a ginger ale?
Just like a crib. You know I'm not paying for that. It's like someone who can only read out loud. He just like can't think.
his head yeah yeah it's very funny you know I'm still in the decoration of
independence
and you know that belong in the museum low-key he's doing like a tour in like DC
yeah he's just walking around like the air and space museum he's like and that
up there is the the Apollo 11 sir you and you know I must do that sure is it
true that you are had to do that yeah yeah yeah yeah you sir I'm gonna steal the
Hubble telescope so here's the Mona Lisa it's the most famous painting in the
world yeah oh really I'm thinking about him being the tour guide itself yeah
he's pointing at things that you he's like here's the Washington Monument it's
the largest structure in fucking DC plus I'm gonna steal it and this is the
Lincoln Memorial it's a no I'm gonna steal that and live in there and you're
no they're like yeah they're like the Washington Monument has been stolen
today and there's one suspect they like roll up to his house and it's just a
the Washington and he walks is like talking about. I stole the one and you
know I stole the Washington,
my house kind of looks like the Washington Monument and you know I stole
it. I hate windows. Okay,
press. I stole that. I stole that shit.
Yeah, and you know I'm going to tickle the camera man
and you know there's about to be a tickle fight. You want me to look into
that camera yeah take that guy I'm a tickle him yeah and how does it work in
the van and you know I'm gonna do my own new show out of there I'm gonna do a
reality show about how i live in the washington monument are there are
there's
when there's laptops in the van and you know i'm going to play to town on them.
You know that's part of the show too.
Is there an arcade cabinet in there? No i'm gonna steal an arcade cabinet.
Yeah,
there isn't there isn't that guy would be a great we'd be probably best
in all of the time. Probably yeah yeah just so prolific such a prolific thief. He kind of
steals everything when you think about it. He's a bit of a kleptomaniac in many ways. I don't like
kleptomaniac does sound sex sex. A kleptomaniac sounds like a disease. Are kleptos people who
they steal shit and they go fuck that making me cum? Yeah. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. I'm stealing shit. Woo!
- Woo!
Fuck.
- Well, that's how you can identify a kleptomaniac
versus a normal shoplifter.
- Fuck, I'm gonna steal that.
- They walk out going, fuck, fuck, fuck, yeah.
- Huge score.
- Woo, I stole it.
I got a bunch of pencils from Staples, fuck.
- Is walking up to the CVS employee,
it's like, I'm not supposed to be walking out with this.
I'm not supposed to.
- Yeah, well, it's the thing, they're more of a maniac
world shoplifter is more of a lifter true yeah yeah yeah shoplifting is a you're
doing it because you need it kleptomanias you're doing it because you're a mania
because you're a crazy yeah you're a klepto yeah a klepto.
Klepto sounds sexual klepto is like sounds like a really fucked up cgi
character from like a Pinocchio movie from the eternals yeah true it is the
new eternals character yeah. I wish I was a mania. And you know I'm going to
you the movies when I see that I know I'm in the movie. I was thinking when I was
watching when we were watching the new Halloween, I was saying it would just
once I want to go to a movie in the theater and I'm like in the movie and I
didn't remember being in the movie.
I want that to happen. I want to see myself on the screen and be like, whoa,
I was I didn't know I was in this. You're not invited to the premiere. You're
seeing it. Yeah, and I didn't realize I was in it. Yeah, you just stand up at
end and she's like thank you thank you everybody yeah I just I want that so bad
just but now I've seen now that I'm saying it people you can't ask now I
know it's coming right I know somebody's gonna put me in the movie and not tell
me so I shouldn't this I might edit that out cuz I really wanted to I really want
that just to happen like you know just a shot of you in the bathroom no I want to
be like a character they put a picture of me and my older brother on clickhole
once really photo of us when we were kids and then my mom what I show my mom is
like isn't that funny like they use some photo she's like where the fuck they get
this they're like ripped it from her Facebook whoa and so she like I she was
like emailed them I got it what is that weird yeah yeah there's a photo of me
and my brother Josh how did they get that why did they get it Cole Ryder was
like trolling Facebook photos of kids man don't you stop you have like a fucking
stock photo library you can use why using a photo of my ass hey that guy that was
a bit of a stock a stalk yeah no he tried to click on my hole yeah fucker
yep and a click click yeah and his on Facebook check this out I tried to click
on my hole yeah I already said that I tried to on Facebook try to put it put a
book in wait okay. We got this we okay. He tried to put a book in my hole. He
tried to put he tried to bury my face in a book and then put his clicker in my
hole.
Clicker yeah, it's just clicker yours doesn't click anymore really mine when I
come it goes yeah, it's double jointed. Yeah, I don't I don't come you don't
come you retain it. Yes, I'm getting into that did yeah. I think it's the way I
think it is too. Yeah I think that you I think that there's I say I personally
think it's poison you got to get it all out of you as fast as possible. Really?
As many times a day as you can. It's weighing me down. You know when you're your stomach's really
upset and you take like a really disgusting poison shit and you feel
better? Yeah. I think it might be like that. It's like that? I think it could be like
that. It is the it is white poop. It's the white poop. It's not white poop. It's the white poop.
white well the stuff that I shoot out is white poop yeah it's like that like like
silly it comes out like a big white snake yeah give yourself a lot of credit
there but no no no it's small as shit but the you know come that come the white
poop that comes out mine is like I'll take it I've I'm holding it in yeah
mine's like when a spider shoots a string in a cartoon yeah it just has a
little wiggle to it yeah I can wrap people up and I'm that it looks like
white play-doh when it comes out. Really? It looks like white play-doh snakes. Yeah.
For me it's kind of it's like a bunch of dots. Mine's like when LeBron throws
the chalk in the air at the beginning of the game. As a warm up. Mine's kind of like if
you like when you know when you're like washing the dishes in the sink and you
turn the water on and you accidentally like hold a spoon under the water.
you've seen that guy he's a he's a semen retention Satanist I have seen that guy
he rules he's cool I think I'll become that yeah I feel like honestly raft 6 6
I've never met someone who is like super into semen retention or heard of someone
who's super in semen retention who wasn't like a pretty cool yeah you know
like that two roads no no Catholics aren't semen retention people well they
are inadvertently well they just don't God wants you to retain a Catholic guys
loved to jack it true they do they jack and they go oh no so many hail mary hit
my wife so many times that's gotta be such a nice feeling it's like because
like they all they have to do to feel like real freaks is to jack off yeah you
know they're not like it no matter what it's - they're not getting a microwave
involved you know they're just fun microwave sometimes you know there's you
know there's some freaks out there's probably a guy you know who puts this
thing in the microwave? What are you talking about? You to put your thing in
the microwave? Not in the microwave, I put my thing and stuff that's been in the
microwave. Yeah yeah hot pocket watermelon. Hot pocket? That'll destroy my penis.
Watermelon is gonna explode. No. What about a tinfoil? Rhymes. If it was an
animal it'd be an antelope. So a deer? No a beer.
that's right okay fuck a beer some to hot beer they do I do think that it's funny
that the they make like the the flesh lights that are shaped like a beer can
do that they do that's cool you're not fooling anyone with that I know it's
definitely for college kids who want to hide it in their room oh I see but the
same size as a regular can no and it's like and it then what's it like beer
your light somebody's going to throw it out to yeah that's like the knob that's
like that's like if I like it. I was going to try to think it's thing as one
simple. I've drank my come out of it.
Yeah, that's like your that's like having like but that's like having
something like that's like like it's like oh it's money, but it's just guys
like a crumpled up piece of paper. Yeah, like what
yeah people some is just going to get rid of it. Yeah, the one that I always
I liked was the flashlight. It's just like you know what it should be the one
that is named something that no something that
they'll never that they'll never throw away. If they find your room, it should
be it should be should like an urn. Oh, nobody's touching that ever. Yeah,
definitely be like the smallest urn in the world and it's yeah, it's for your
baby.
That's yeah, that's my baby brother's urn, but then if someone walks in on
you
(laughing)
- You're fucking the bottom of the urn, dude.
That's a...
(laughing)
Oh fuck, we have to delete that
and send this to American Pie.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Jesus Christ.
- Yeah, that's a bad situation to be in,
is your mom walks in.
She, first of all, she didn't know you had a baby brother.
(laughing)
- I had a baby?
And it died?
- Yeah.
Oh man, yeah, that's nasty.
- It is.
- That's nasty.
- Why did we say that?
That's terrible.
- I didn't even say that.
- We didn't say it, you said that.
- Why did Patrick say that?
- Why did you pretend to be Cam and throw your voice
and perfectly do an impression of him
and say some nasty shit about fucking a player?
- I'll do it again, you ready?
I'll pretend to be Cameron again.
(coughing)
- It's very offensive.
- Yeah, that was not cool, dude.
- Very fucked up.
- Do you wanna hear something that I think is,
I don't know if you guys will find this as funny.
I really did DTD. No, I did Tusken Raider voice. Is that what you call them?
What? At least I didn't say sand people. What the hell? That's what they say in
the movie, isn't that fucked up? Sand people? Yeah, in Star Wars, they call the
Tusken Raider the people who were like,
like, like that. They're like, oh, fuck the sand people.
I feel like, well, I feel like if in real life you called, you called like
somebody a Tuscan raider that would probably be worse.
Yeah.
Well, Tuscany is in Italy.
So yeah.
I don't know.
Now I'm just confused as hell.
This has been making me laugh a lot.
I've been sleepwalking recently, which I really don't like.
I need to find a way to stop.
So if anybody who listens to this knows how to stop from sleepwalking, please message
me.
If we have any hypnotists listening.
Please.
block the other night and I sat up in bed and I like open the window curtain. I
was like looking out the window and Anna woke up. She was like, "Why are you
looking out the window?" And in my sleep I was like, "What? I can't look out the
window?"
Dude, I'm like that too when I sleep walk. I'm like so defensive.
It's making me laugh so much. You told me that in the morning. I was like,
"Oh my God, that's so mean."
Apparently, I turned to Jan sometime recently. She was like dead asleep and I
woke her up and I said, "You need to make me some food."
(laughter)
It's like fucking four in the morning,
I'm completely asleep.
You need to make me some food.
Yeah, and she fucking did.
- That's just what happens when you sleepwalk, I think,
is you just become really rude and mean.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Is that, yeah.
- I think there's something about,
I think it's maybe just 'cause you're tired
and you're half awake.
You know, when you're like really sleepy
and everything's pissing you off.
- Yeah.
'Cause that's the ultimate, you're already asleep,
but you're half awake.
- To me, what I think it is for me is like,
when somebody talks to me and I'm sleepwalking,
that'll like wake me up.
And then I'll be like, I'll wake up and I'll like realize
that I'm like up doing something that I,
like I'll be up like putting my clothes on for some reason,
but I'll like feel like I had a reason for doing it,
so I'll just get like defensive about it.
I'll be like.
- I'll wait, continue.
- No, no, that's--
- I just remembered something so funny.
Last night, I woke up in the middle of the night
and I like looked over at Jana and I was like,
what the, that's not Jana, and I thought it was you.
And then I was like,
I don't want to sleep in this bed with Cameron.
And I went and got on the couch.
And then Jana was like, why'd you like go to the couch?
I was like, oh, I thought that Cameron was in the bed.
(laughing)
- You didn't want to sleep with me?
- Well, you were like pushing me off the bed.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, and I was like, this sucks.
This guy's a fucking, fucking comforter hog.
You just fart.
no you did no i did i heard that no i was in his chair i did not for that was
your act i would admit to a better your ass and i see your face
now you're a fart favor
out of four you're going to have a hard not
yeah
is not for your pro-life or favor
speaking of for it
to support our duty
Now I have to fart just so I can prove that it wasn't me.
I'm loving the concussed era, dude.
I think it's a totally different for us.
I hate being in your zone.
You guys were in my zone.
We didn't even talk about being in North Carolina much.
We went hog hovering.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
Speaking of fart stuff, your dog crashed.
Oh, my fart slave.
He's a fart slave.
Yeah.
So my mom has a dog.
A dog is addicted to farts.
mini dachshund who every night when you go to sleep he buries his huge like
like evolutionarily long anteater like yeah big nose that's made for sniffing
he shoves it in your butt like a vacuum and just sucks on your farts out. He's a stink
drinker. He completely is addicted to it. Caleb had mentioned it before and I forgot about it until he did it to me
one night he's a he's a he's a a fart hag he's absolutely a fart hag dude he's a
yeah I mean we were all just we all took we got our turn with him no I was yeah I
was I ran I was on the top bunk I ran a toot train on that yeah well yeah that's
the thing too is like well we also were on that like boat so we're getting seasick
and getting like shaken up like I didn't get see yeah cams are you sure you know
up like a can of soda
and crash pop just tab yeah just shoot did I shoot clouds down is his
father. I was blasting. I was yeah he was like he's like he was like a like a
cartoon snake who's like eating like eating a bunch of animals. You can see
like the
just puffy clouds going down bursting hadoukis into him yeah
yeah, I was saying he's a
bit of a shark harpy one of the
Yeah, a lot of ways. Yeah, one of the best fucking stink detectives we have.
Absolutely. Can you imagine he, you know, people get hounds and shit to fucking
hunt murderers. If we were, if we had to find out who fucking dealt it. He's not a
bloodhound, he's a mudhound. Yeah, exactly dude. He was on the trail. He could have,
honestly, we should be canning people's farts and if they go missing, give him a
little sniff of it he'll find him in an incident. He'll literally tiny as shit,
so he can run yeah. I mean not he's a dox and he can't run that fake camera very
fast, but he will but will you search out that he'll have fun. He'll find it
eventually. Yeah, yeah, he'll find you, but it'll take like three days. He'll
gobble your gas. I literally blew him up like a balloon one night.
And then he flew around the room. Just re just burping. I was yeah, we were
talking about shooting. We were shooting just a concentrated lot like a an
Anton sugar yeah,
yeah, the most insane PSI behind the shit that I was putting like I think I'd
maybe blinded him yeah sort of God yeah yeah, just shooting a hole through his
head with a just concentrated air yeah yeah he's like one of the you know like
an old fashioned fireplace where you have like the bellows yeah yeah he's
one of those doing to him and he was you know I mean yeah, I was I was throwing
smoke stacks into the boys face. Oh yeah. Just black clouds coming out of my ass.
Like I'm having dreams that I'm like it was like using like a it's like a using
like a air Zuka at Chernobyl. Like glowing green gusts. Yeah I mean he is
right down. He's like elephant's foot radioactive now. He's like walking around
everybody's face is melting when they get near him. Try to pet him dude. My mom
throws treats up in the air. They vaporize as soon as I get within a
a radius of him. He couldn't get to the top bunk. I didn't. You saved so many lives. I
know. He would have, I mean if I was there, it would have been trouble. It would have
gone down different. No dude, me and Cam were putting down heaters bro. You couldn't compete.
I was eating barbecue all week. So were we. I've been eating barbecue my whole life. You've
heard. This guy was like the fucking, was like the sultan of shit the entire fucking
weeks dude. He was like having he was taught he's leaving the bathroom and
just being like yeah just blasted a crazy rock. I was so I was so constipated
too before that I was and I was well I was like I already was like my stomach
was already not doing well going into that trip and then yeah it was it was
rough. I that it's I'm glad I did I'm glad that I I did I took my first really
disgusting shit on the boat because I feel like it would have left like a
grudge you did on the boat like I did it on land is it Japanese ghost forever
cuz I how nasty your shit was I think it could have happened
yeah he's a boat cold wind people walk into a very soft blue light yeah it is
- It was a rough weekend for my butt, for sure.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my butt was taking a task.
- Day one, we went to Smithfields,
and we went out immediately.
I think we went to the, what was that museum?
- Oh, oh, the Museum of the Bazaar.
- The Museum of the Bazaar.
- That museum rocked.
- Yeah, it was sick, but we went there.
- Matt says it's hard.
- Oh yeah, true.
- Yep.
- We went there, and as soon as we got to your house,
after eating the barbecue in the car,
I was just like, "Man, I gotta lay down, dude.
got like the itis I got a fucking I got I got lay I guess spread out the Patrick
itis mm-hmm yeah the Patrick itis huh oh it's what it's known as the Patrick itis
huh yeah and I had we had to walk all the way or did we drive there yeah yeah
okay then we just walked around down we had to walk all the way I free I
completely ran whether or not that we were hanging out in no it was they had
They had Pinhead there?
They did, I do have a picture of you guys with Pinhead.
They got Pinhead, they got uh...
They had Pinhead, they had Freddy, they had Michael.
They had Chucky.
They had the Mirror Maze.
They had Mini-Me.
Wait, did they actually have Chucky?
I don't think they had Chucky.
I have a...
fastest time as you can without touching the lasers. I just ran through all of them and
hit the button. And you lost big time. Yeah, my score was like two minutes. Maybe we should
have been blasting farts in there to reveal more lasers. Yes, that's probably what it
was. You know when they throw a little smoke to reveal the laser? Maybe we needed to take
a stinky cloud with us. I think all the lasers are present. I mean dude, I was like swat team
level smoke grenades that I was popping off through the entire week. Especially
Alligator Adventure dude. The alligators, they were literally smelling me when I
walked by and then and then flying up like goldfish and just sitting there.
They were just sitting there with their mouths open. They wanted to, dude, there was I
think it was one of the the crocodiles we saw. Yeah. That thing that thing opened
its mouth and I got a more like a wave of stink. Oh he bucked at you. Yeah. Yeah. He
was like what's up and then he burped and then I he smelled my fart he turned a
stone. I swear to God. Dude, that's the fucking, oh man, that was the weirdest part about fucking
looking at all those alligators and crocodiles and shit. They just sit there in the sun with
their mouths open. Yeah. Fucking. Like nobody I know. Who are you talking about? Cut to Pat
at Maria Hernandez just. That's not what I do. I'm spinning in a circle there. No, you're throwing,
your only thing that's moving is your left wrist as you just arch a haichu right into your mouth.
Don't even chew it. You just swallow it like a big pill.
They don't have like a... do they not have a mouth hole till they close their...
Yeah, that's what was tripping me up too. I didn't realize they...
I've never seen a crocodile in person.
Me neither. They don't have...
Y'all don't know gators like me?
They don't have...
They taste great.
They don't have throats. They do taste good.
How have you never seen a gator but you've eaten it?
What is that?
I've seen them at zoos before but never saw one in the wild.
Oh yeah.
I had some alligator bites one time.
Oh, really?
Yeah, they were good. The tail is where it's at. The tail is, fried alligator tail is very good. Fucking strong, dude.
Delicious. Yeah, I wish we had done some other southern stuff. I might have seen, I might have seen an alligator, like a baby alligator,
but I don't count that. Yeah, yeah, so I said they definitely brought a baby alligator into like my school.
Yeah. We need, we should have tried to see some hogs. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. We did. What? Saw you, bitch. You kidding me? You're gonna do that to me right now?
Yeah, I've literally been mortally wounded
Okay, I'm bleat. I'm bleeding and you don't we see a hog. No, we didn't see a hog you fuck talking about
What is wrong with you?
Why I see a big pig
the mirror
What?
What is up with you? What is he stop doing this? Can you stop? I saw a big pig at hemp fest in 2018
They had a pig this much weed some guy had a pig I forget the pigs name
But it was some kind of weed pun. It's new piggy pig mm-hmm and that thing
If you snoop hoggy hog could have been it. I don't remember
There's a hemp fest in Boston this pig it would come up to you
And it would like basically knock you over if the guy wasn't like you you could go up to it and pet it
But it would like you know come up to you is very excited to see you, and then it would just like
It's trying to eat you it's a fat fucking eat you bro. Yeah, I wonder if that guy feeds his pig edibles
I mean if he's bringing it to him fest. He totally feeds his pig and I never see you ever see the show that show Hannibal
No
Cool stuff with pigs in that show really well pigs will eat anything right? Yeah, I'm cool. So cool
Cool stuff happens with pigs. I've seen snatch plenty of times. Yeah, me too. I'm saying I had it on DVD is
Why that's a lot. Oh, that's a movie. Mm-hmm
I'm talking about a sexy MILF snatch.
Yeah, I'm talking about DVD, Dick, Vagina, Dick.
Stacked up.
Yeah.
Stacked up like a Dr. Mario pill.
In that order.
I've had MILFs on the brain, dude.
That's cool.
I've been having a MILF fest.
In your mind?
In my mind every day I get on the carnival.
You are so concussed.
I get on the Ferris wheel and then I get off.
and then I get off. Every day on the carnival? What are you talking about?
Can I, can you guys finish the episode and I can think about a MILF?
No. What carnival are you going to? What if she's sucking my balls? The MILF-Fest
carnival. Oh. Yeah. Where they
deep fry my cock and balls and they feed it to themselves. What kind
of dreams have you been having? I don't remember what's real and what's not.
Yeah, I think Cameron was in my bed that you were in my bed last night
You did already tell that story. I had a feeling I did. Yeah. Yeah
He's gonna kill us yeah, how am I gonna kill you I'm killing myself your say-o on us you're gonna go Chris Benoit
I don't know who that is getting too close back up why back up? Yeah, are you afraid of me back up?
Well, you think I'll do something crazy cuz my brains broken. I think your brains too broken
they put a hole in my head. Who's they shelf shelf put a hole in my head when a
couple days ago you were there
when you were at my house a better list day. Oh, you did yeah top ten everyday
aspects of life that will be weird in a backwards universe.
Okay,
positron wild hug. Oh, there's our boy yeah. Imagine these things acting where
time runs backwards. They would certainly be bizarre. Oh, okay, all right, so the
saying just if you saw this in reverse, it would know it would be weird in a
backwards universe. Yeah, there's an important distinction there. This is not
it does not say on a reverse. Yeah, it's a backwards universe.
Are you so concussed? You don't remember what a backwards universe is. That's
where he's living right now. I am so backwards universe is a forward universe
him. I have I felt this and for the last four days I felt like I had a half of a
of a Klonopin. Yeah? Yeah. And I'm just kind of walking around like kind of
enjoying myself honestly. Concussion might be like I might have ascended to a
higher plane. I tell you that the the first week I was here I went to Blue
Park, fucked up a 50/50 and fell straight to the back of my head. Did anyone check
you? No. Nice. That's badass. I just kind of went home. Did you take a couple naps?
Yeah. All right, you're fine. Yeah. I'm just a couple naps short of being normal again.
Yeah. Could be. Could be. Could be. Could be. Number one, pregnancy. Okay, let's
let's hear them out on this because it's already pretty weird. This would be a
tough ordeal for both child and parents. When the kid ages backwards, it shoves
itself up into the mother before the baby shrivels into nothing and nine
three months later or earlier splits into a sperm and an egg, the former of which
promptly shoots back up into the father. A backwards world would be odd, so you
the mom would be older than the kid. Here's another comment, though this
doth fair maketh the eyes water. It shoves itself up into the mother such
grace such style. This would be bizarre and extremely traumatic for all involved.
Thank goodness. This is impossible. Could you imagine just like like
- Anything's possible. - Mother's just running away
as their child is just cosmically,
just like leashed to their pussy trying to get back in.
Be kind of funny.
- You think it would be like a goo?
- No, it would be like a gravity that's pulling them.
- Like fate.
- Yeah, exactly, it'd be this invisible
kind of like fishing line of fate.
- I was thinking like the-- - As the moms just run around.
- You were thinking like goo. - Trying to keep--
- The umbilical cord shoots out like a Hellraiser chain.
(laughing)
To the kid. - Yeah, that's what it would be.
That would be pretty cool. - That would be
corn yeah so it would be like even if you said a biblical corn I did say corn I
found a hair on my hair he has truly descended to my level I have hit a wall
Wow I was in you've already you fucked up a word and said something that just
makes no goddamn sense I found a hair on my hair I like a mom's in China and then
and the kid, that's the opposite of China.
(laughing)
Don't you almost say Japan?
- No.
- You almost said Japan.
(laughing)
- It is though.
- Yeah, all right, the mom's in China,
the kid's in Japan on the other side of the world.
(laughing)
And just yeah, she's just sitting there reading a newspaper
and then she looks at the day and says, oh no.
- Oh.
- And then a fucking giant--
- A tentacle.
- Tentacle climbs out of her--
Yeah, but then imagine how often that would happen because it's maybe we have
to have like air traffic controllers. Yeah, they were trying to get the wires
got crossed the wrong kid went up the wrong mom. The kids would just be
colliding in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean. Just it'd be bad dude. Yeah, if
you I was the mom, I'd probably sit on a plate.
Think it might stop it. Maybe put a cork up there. Yeah, it's that thing's
beasting through a cork yeah can you made a pressure behind that a wooden cork that
might actually work see if you put a student I even a steel steel door of a
bank vault is not gonna hold a mother from its child this you just got snip it
sniff it snip it oh yeah they could whatever if the cord yeah but not
regrows it's like a lizard tail you're just making up rules for this wouldn't
it be the kid has been stoppable and it's invincible wouldn't the kid have to
die for this to happen? Well the kid dies when he turns into nothing in the womb.
Well the kid dies at the beginning of his life because it's a backwards world. He
undies and then he unborns. Man this is breaking my fucking head. Well here if you
want something else that's gonna blow your mind even more number two money.
Money would be avoided like the plague in a backwards universe as when you
buy things you are in fact selling them and vice versa so throwing out your
money would make you richer but you'd also be unable to buy something unless
you sell it. God, I hate living in this backwards world. I hate. It's confusing me so badly.
It's like everything that I know has been flipped upside down. Backwards even. No, upside
down. Number three is education. When you graduate, you're basically confirming in a
backwards universe that you don't need your knowledge anymore and over your backwards
courses you lose it into thin air as your teachers teach it backwards and you'd begin
to lose your degrees as your exams are undone until at the end of your life or
after your reverse education you're no longer toilet trained horrific thought
right well that's just Jupiter true we're going to get that is Jupiter so I
guess the backwards world is Jupiter's had done the concussion made me I
googled the day after I literally went on my phone and googled it can a
concussion make you stupider what's wrong with that that's the right word
stupider is not the right word stupider no yeah it's not a real word it is
stupider well what else rhymes with Jupiter almost nothing yeah cupid or
something could be number one sir come pupator which is what you use on the
computer it's an app yeah it's an app where you mind poop you say mind poop
mine you have a mind poop you do I don't you have a you have a butthole IQ test
us against you right now. I don't want to do that again.
I was drunk as shit and I took an IQ test and got an eighty five.
I was trying to speed run it.
No, I watched it. It was yeah, you were giving yourself way more credit. I
didn't try to speed run it. I really don't remember that fast, but that was
because I think you kept getting distracted.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- True. - It was so funny though.
- I forgot about that. - It was one of the
funniest things ever.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I mean, I don't doubt that my IQ is probably--
- I think you got past 100, brother.
- I probably shaved like 10 points off.
I think it's probably around 95.
- I think you got a 95.
- I think I'm probably at 95.
- Hey, that's an A.
- Exactly. - That's right.
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
- There's no way that I'm an intelligent person.
- You know, who knows? - There's no way.
'Cause you look at those pattern things
you're supposed to look at? It's all lines and squares.
It's a gobbledy-goo.
Yeah.
Put it in words.
I don't, fucking, you think I can...
Smart enough to read.
Yeah, I can read words.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe just turn the shapes into the words that the shapes are.
Think that might help you?
But then you're also dyslexic.
So it's just this line, line, shape. Oh, yeah, true.
So you'll be fucking up all that too. Maybe you are stupid.
Maybe.
Number four is...
Oh, no, wait. Here's a comment on education. I was waiting to read this one.
Okay.
our education system is kind of backwards already.
Instead of learning stuff, we are rote memorizing.
- Shit.
- This guy should be maybe the president
of the Queen of England or something.
- Yeah, the president of the Queen of England.
- Okay, now you can do number four.
- Number four, I believe it says health care.
(laughing)
- You're just, no, no.
- Can I take a 90 second break?
- You are faking, you're completely faking.
- No.
- You can't, no.
- Health care, I said health care.
- You said health care.
I can't be looking up words is not concussed you guys are stupid you've
never done that before you I've fucked up words all the time like this I thought I
did constantly I'm like known for that no Patrick is known for that I don't so
Patrick does you guys are supposed to make me feel better and just ignores I
just need a couple naps and I swear you know what no one ignores it when I do it
Well that's different.
It's different.
Oh God.
Alright, what does healthcare say?
This can be a minor irritation, like a doctor taking your cough pills away while your throat
feels like sandpaper.
Cough pills?
Or it could be an amoral Armageddon, like it would be if surgeons were to implant a
pus filled appendix into you before applying anesthetic.
So it's just my doctor.
True.
Is that what your doctor does?
My doctor's a damn savage.
low key is how health care is in the normal universe to it's already
backwards. You tell you what going backwards and see if I give a fuck
that's right. Yeah, your number five is puberty would not like to have that
happen backwards.
That's the only thing that'd be awesome. There's one other comment that says
that would be so awkward. That would be are you kidding puberty. You read of
sexual desire that would be perfect. It'd be so cool. You lose all your fucking... my
top hair comes back, my bottom hair go away, my penis is extracted, and my balls, they
hide from me. This is like the perfect life. Plus I get really short. What? You guys wouldn't
like that? To go backwards puberty? No. I'd love that. I just pretend I never... I do want
I do want to accelerate it. I want to get my ball done. Patrick does want Caleb to
go through reverse puberty though. No, you do and then you want to control my body.
You want to put you want to put an RC receiver in my brain. You want to do being
John Malkovich with with baby Caleb. You want to you want to shrink I'm you want
me to shrink into a child, you to shrink into a microscopic object and then do
Gundam with my body. No, I don't. Do you sit and get it? And then you want to fight me and
kill me because you hate me. That's not true. And then. That's how you know this isn't true
at all. Maybe it's not true. Maybe it's not true. Maybe we're just making this up. Number
six is memory. Maybe it could be real. Memory. Memory. I'm very familiar. How would anyone
live with memory capacity acting back through time? I also couldn't remember what a glove
box was yesterday. What? But I think that's a normal thing. What are you talking about?
I forget the name of the glove box all the time.
I text, I was trying to text my...
Like were you looking at a glove box?
I was looking at it and I was like, "What is that?"
I couldn't remember the name.
You couldn't remember the name or you were like, "What is that?"
No, I knew what it was, I just couldn't remember the name of a glove box.
Why is this in my car?
What is that?
What's the one under the passenger seat?
The glove box.
That is the glove box.
Oh, okay, I feel way better about this.
I thought you meant that you didn't know what it was.
car in the car. You were just like what is this? Oh yeah. Now what is this is
very different from what is this called? The thing I get fucked up now is
because all cars have like a center console or whatever the center console.
Yeah, the thing yeah, the console. Yeah, thing where you where you push
there should be a better name for center console. Yeah, because glove box
is great glove box. You can tell but now that they're throwing all these
center console based on based on my mom's car. They should call it the
sand area. It's always filled with sand in that car. That's right. Get off
beach you idiot what the hell's going on um why are you putting sand in there
she got like more like people would tell me like oh like this is in the center
console or like this is in that and I would always go digging through people's
cars a lot no I get stuff out of the car like my mom or my dad asking there's
sand in there people tell me people tell me all the time people are always
(laughing)
- You ever notice that people always tell you
to do the dishes?
- And people are telling you.
- People are telling you it's your bedtime.
- People are always like,
"Dinner's ready." - People are telling you
it's your bedtime.
- People are always like, "Dinner's ready,
"you're going upstairs, it smells horrible."
- I hate people.
I hate dinner.
(laughing)
- Well, he loves dinner.
- Oh, true.
- We have established that he loves all food.
- True, yeah.
- Food Seinfeld, yeah.
- Come on, man.
- Oh, fuck, what was that?
- Food Feld.
- We were doing Food Seinfeld.
- Dine Feld.
only took us 60 episodes huh we were doing Dinefeld in North Carolina yeah I
forget what weirs oh it was like what's it called a sandwich oh no no no no all
the sands and some people Center consoles who's that the comedian we made
up Oh dog dog the comedian oh I kind of don't want to tip that on yeah I think
we have big plans okay we have big plans for dog the comedian but trust you guys
you guys are going to love this crap. What's the deal with this guy dog the
comedian is he a hot dog is he a guy is he a dog? I wish it was a guy
so I get a hot dog with him. What's a glove box? I can't get over how funny is
it. Patrick's trying to generalize people as your mom and dad is so funny.
Well, I was going to say my sister to
people. I hate when people make me do stuff. Number seven is invention. That's
actually pretty funny. A world where people already have things invented and
then they just forget. They have to invent it not existing anymore. Yeah,
like lying. Yeah, it's like the invention of lying. Thomas Edison comes in and
he's like, "What if it was really dark in here?" He's just smashing light bulbs
hammer. Yeah, the guy was like really sick and be like what if that guy just
died?
What if we just let him die?
Oh, fuck! Who's another guy who invented something? Yeah, what are the guy has
to
or yeah, just put in a bunch of nasty shit in the middle.
I think like it is undrinkable. I took a shit in all the milk, whoever the
whoever invented car the car was like I wish this thing was alive. I wish this
was yeah. I wish there was like four or five animals that pulled me instead of
this crap. Yeah, the right brothers, the right brothers.
yeah yeah Oppenheimer he's like just chill now I am become what sound I become
party that would totally happen in backwards universe they call the pussy
hounder now I become MTV's can't but what was that God damn it MTV you tried
spring break in Cancun. Now I've become, now I'm become MTV's spring break in Cancun.
Destroyer of worlds. Destroyer of beers.
It's pretty good actually. I didn't give you a chance there, my bad.
Yeah. Now I've become, now I'm become Girls Gone Wild.
Destroyer of girls, dude. Destroyer of girls.
Number eight, crime.
Criminals will put money into vaults and seal them up,
or might suck knives and bullets out of corpses
before they come to life.
Sucking a knife.
Oh, hell no.
I know you ain't sucking a knife and bullet out
of that corpse.
Here's the other comment.
Ha ha ah, that's epic.
From Toucan.
Here's a good-- number nine is menstruation.
Ooh.
Positron Wildhox says, I don't know how it feels forwards,
but I can imagine that backwards would be a lot worse.
I feel like it'd be fine, right?
Yeah.
Might be.
Well, you would start out in pain.
Just be like an OxyClean commercial.
Yeah, it cleans up.
Yeah.
It's a cleaner upper.
Yeah, it's like when they put the bounty wipe.
Yeah.
What is that?
What?
That was a really scary cough.
I had something in my throat.
You made like deep eye contact with Patrick and were like...
Until now.
I don't know forgot how to cough number tens digestion. Oh, oh hell no. I think I
know where this is going. Oh, are you telling me I'm gonna up Chuck a full
hamburger full BTS meal. Here's the top comment. See this is why I like the world
even with its problems. Do you what would make me hate life having your poop being
shoved up your butt every time you try to eat something but where's the poop if
it's not being sucked up yet it's not in your rectum. You're still trying to eat
eat something like you're like you know you're in a backwards world, but you go
in like maybe this time I'll actually eat it. It's just poop going on my ass
fuck see, but I guess poop going up your ass is not as bad as poop going in your
mouth right.
I don't know that might be the because I know the greatest questions. I
well, because because a backwards universe that's poop going up your butt,
but like a topsy turvy universe could be that you're eating poop. You know
I much rather live backwards in topsy-turvy. Absolutely. Or like a twisted
universe. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Some kind of fucked up genie magic universe where
everything's wrong. That is, I definitely don't want to eat poop. Yeah, which would you rather?
Would you rather eat poop or have it shoved up your butt by a force? It has to be by a force.
By a reverse gravity. So, okay. It's an easy question. It's two very simple and
and attractive options
each as it's frozen on your mouth in the other one use the second one you put
okay well okay it's
we're going to run your okay well we're not considering that right now it's just
a would you rather those two things but
if you're getting poop that does mean the food goes up your butt
but this ignore that
so i think the second probably
it goes up your butt
the second one eating poop? no. well did it come out of your mouth? oh the first one eating poop
okay so pat would rather eat poop
what now the second one where the poop goes in your body and your mouth yet
and now you know you want one that does
you want a version where you get poop up your butt and in your mouth
yeah i think i didn't consider that
that i don't know when that's not a backwards topsy-turvy universe yeah
where you have to eat the poop and it goes up
well there's also a really good love it's a backwards world is in poop food
no i don't like to turn it
Oh, but in the Topsy-Turvy universe, you would like the poop because I like food.
Right.
So yeah, I'd rather have that.
Rather eat poop.
If I like liked, every day I was like, "Uh, if I was putting a bib on to eat poop and crack it
open like a lobster tail, that'd be sick."
It's got meat in the poop.
Yeah, well, it is meat.
But you'd also, I mean, a backwards universe, you'd probably like putting the poop up your butt,
right?
I like normal pooping and I like eating.
Yeah, so you probably like both of them.
I guess you're right. I mean I'm I'm big not backwards one. You have to have
backwards one you the food comes out of your mouth when you when the poop goes
up your but then what happens the topsy-turvy someone's universe
constructs the topsy-turvy universe when you eat poop does food come out of your
butt or is it just poop again because it did go through the digestive system it's
not like it's running backwards I think we got it I think we got a like I think
we've got a message a scientist I think you have the grass Tyson to do some kind
kind of math a radical experiment. I think in the but we're going to put it
will put will put comes out of your butt right food would come. We're going to
will dog here. This conversation will come back to this and we're talking to
a science. Okay, all right, we'll get a scientist on full week. So a full you
would poop a full burger. Well, no, it'd be bites of a burger and then when it
depends on it depends on which universe you're in if it's if it's backwards
upside down topsy turvy twisted or strange. There's also the poop universe
everything is made out of poop so you don't really so it doesn't matter if it
goes up your butter in your mouth because it is your butt and mouth yeah exactly
it's called the poop averse they're actually doing a spider-man movie about
Venom's with Alfred oh yeah dude poop I'm so excited for poop venom to my god
PCU you want to find a venomous poop yeah I already found one is in his own
mouth no it was in your mouth why are you looking at my mouth because you're
were eating poop and it was disgusting. You were on the hunt for poop and you
don't why you watching another man's mouth. Stop mouth watching
all right now we're to the contenders. Yeah, we're to the beautiful contenders
on this lovely list. It is a lovely list isn't it well. Oh there are some there
are some another comment here. Maybe there's some people with answers.
There's there to really good there. Okay, you would have to sit on a toilet
before crap rises from the drain and into you, which would materialize into
pieces of poop or into pieces of food, which are fused together by your teeth
until you before you pull it up your throat and out of your mouth. I think
I'll pass and then here's the other crap rises and here's the other comment
from the toilet to the plate
farm to table dude from the toilet to the plate that's by to can number
eleven murder.
You'd bring people back to life. Can you imagine the thrillers detective who
brought him back to life. Murder victim. It was him. That sounds thrilling.
That didn't sound thrilling. It's a backwards universe. It would be thrilling to me. A chiller.
You know the answer at the beginning. You can just relax. It would be a relaxer of a
movie. Watching a movie. Number 12, yeah, watching a movie, you start at the credits.
Number 13, farts. That's similar I think to food. I think it would be burps. What? It
like with your no with sucking it all day like like crash he's already living in
the back he escaped from the backwards universe the backwards topsy-turvy
universe where you suck up farts with your mouth yeah set up with your butt
yeah he was like he was a professional cloud chewer yeah he slipped through a
rip in space-time and he ended up in my bed with my butthole in his mouth just
absolutely sucking up farts I'm giving him it for Christmas I literally do go
go there mostly on Christmas and I that's like you just you just pump dumps into
yeah and and my mom's always like what'd you get like the dogs for Christmas and
I say I already got him a present brother yeah yeah and it's and it's not
not safe for work absolutely yeah yeah PG-13 mm-hmm number 14 crying mm-hmm
yeah they should people just should stop crying that'd be a better universe
crying so annoying 15 proposing yeah the woman would do it oh my god are you
you
from the same universe as Crash.
- Yeah, she actually, and Crash, she was farting in Crash.
- Sometimes it feels-- - They came here together.
- Sometimes it already feels like
we're in a backwards universe
with all these masks and vaccines.
- Yep.
- So true.
- You can't say that on a podcast.
- I have a, I am legally concussed.
- Masks and you know what's.
- You know what.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, you know what's.
Number 16, death.
Here's the top comment.
This would be a birth.
It's true.
Okay, this is officially a birth.
Yep, and then when you reach age 0.0000001, death.
Why don't they just let you keep going? I don't get it.
Yeah.
True.
So you would start out dead, then wake up somewhere just like...
You'd be old as fuck.
Here's a genius here.
Dude, that would actually suck. What if you woke up, like you're born, right?
Uh-huh.
But you're like 18.
Yeah.
that would suck you 18 you're climbing out of a car and you're like so drunk oh
yeah clothes yeah you're like oh he's gonna suck dude yeah yeah but then you
also you're like reverse I dad like this I'm gonna be at a lot of pussy yeah what
if you wake up and you're like like one year old and in your your your college
age brother's dorm room on his shelf yeah what about that what have you yeah
you wake up and you're as ash yeah you wake up and OJ Simpson is putting your
head back on your body you're like fuck me dude oh shit I'm ash that's what you
would say yeah here's a really smart comment here number 19 is writing and
the comment from funny user is would you write with your foot or just type
everything that is pretty funny it's probably right shit back it is pretty
probably right back probably erase stuff yeah oh yeah true yeah like painting
thing would be who can get rid of paint better right. So it would kind of be
like it would be like garbage men and painters would switch places yeah yeah
true garbage men might be the highest people in society. It's meant garbage
people would hate garbage and so much in the backwards universe. They were
everything they show up and drop the stinkiest most disgusting trash right
and then you have to make it good yeah. Yeah, you have to use it to make your
all your meal yeah, just a appeals, they have to show them up your butt.
I hate this world. You have to show poop up your butt to spit out a banana into
the peel and they have to bring it back to the store.
I'm going to drop groceries off. They do give you money to do that, though.
That's kind of worth it. That's everyone, but you also have to throw
the money out to become rich shit. I don't want to move out of everything
Number 20, hangovers.
- Well, you can reverse a hangover pretty quick.
- Hair of the dog.
- Mm-hmm.
Blogging.
(laughing)
- That would be so weird.
- Yeah, people would read them.
- So strange backwards.
Hey, hey.
- That was insane.
- How'd you do that?
- Number 29, injuring yourself.
You would be healed all the time, I guess.
(laughing)
- So true.
I guess that person injures himself all the time.
- Number 31.
- That's what I'm getting at.
- Number 31, we've already discussed.
- Yeah, the final comment.
thirty is urinating and thirty one is pooping. That's a nasty crap. All right,
kind of I will say it feel probably pretty good to watch the water go white
when you suck up a P. That would be pretty good. You know, it would be
annoying, though, is you it would it would leave streaks of poop on the
toilet bowl. You're right yeah yeah, it'd be sucking the poop back up. Yeah,
you I love playing that game. Yeah, get the poop stains off the toilet bowl. My
penis yeah ah so awesome. My penis is my tool. You kill someone with a gun not a bullet.
Okay. Subscribe to the Patreon. Bye.