Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Hi!
Hi!
- Hi.
- Hi!
Hi!
- Went and saw Licorice Pizza last night,
I was waving at Alana Haym like that on the screen.
I was sitting there going, "Hi!
"Hi!"
- Yeah.
- She didn't say anything.
- I really respected what she did to that boy.
- Yeah.
- She didn't say anything back to me.
Pat's in a pitch meeting two weeks later. He's like, "What if we did a gender-swapped
licorice pizza?" And I play the older one.
And it's called Pizza.
Well, think about it. Hold on. Why is that movie called Pizza?
I don't know.
Think about it.
It's named after your employers.
You're doing some...
What's that shit called?
QNN.
in QA mom Q and then comet pizza shit they don't even go to licorice pizza
maybe I was in the bathroom I think there's a story you're in the bathroom
why'd you have to leave the liquor is moving go to the bathroom I think I
isn't a licorice pizza a word for like a record shut up isn't that what that
means shut up just shut why do you have to know everything fucking stupid
asshole funny if that's not true Rick I feel like I saw somebody say that
I hope that's not true and I just made that up. No that is it that is true. Oh
it's cool. Look at what COVID-19 is doing to my face.
Licorice Pizza chain will be sold to American Canyon. Oh there was a store?
Licorice Pizza, a Southern California record and video store chain that got its
name from a 1960s record album is being sold to the Musicland group. That's from
the LA Times in 1986. Musicland. There's a land I'd like to visit. Tax Haven.
Dude, oh man. I'd love to go to Musicland and kill Stevie Ray Vaughan.
It's an amusement park with audio only rides. You sit in a room and you close your eyes and
it plays the sound of a roller coaster. Did Stevie Ray Vaughan also die in a helicopter
crash? I think Stevie Ray Vaughan's alive.
We're trying to do the Musicland amusement park planning here.
Yeah, but that's the thing. Okay, well if you do the Musicland amusement park, you cannot
cannot have any helicopter stuff. What? Because of Randy Rhoads and Buddy Holly. And Skinnerd.
Come on. Yeah. Okay, I guess any kind of music land, there's going to be no plane. There's
going to be nothing that goes in the air. And JFK Jr. Uh huh. I don't think there's
usually planes in amusement parks. Well, no plane rides. I don't think they usually ride
planes and a musical. You can't have the Soul Plane. It's usually roller coasters. That's
a big downside. More than planes. Well a plane themed roller coaster. They have that already.
There's like tons of plane roller coasters. Yeah Cameron you idiot. You said you can't
have any planes. Well we can't have any plane themed stuff. You can't fly a plane over Disney
right? It's like an airspace thing. I don't know what you're saying. There's no plane
already no I'm saying you can't have any plane themed ride yeah there'll be no
planes there what a way right to ride you don't need what do you mean that you
can't fly a plane like are they gonna shoot it's like a lot of the fucking guy
they're allowed to shoot the yeah are they gonna iron dome you if you fucking
fly your plane over the haunted mansion?
Somebody flying a plane over Canobie Lake Park and it just gets shot down immediately.
No, there is.
You can't fly a plane over Disney because of 9/11.
Really?
Yeah, there's like a no-fly zone over it.
So they said Disney World is the only place that we don't want another 9/11.
Dude, imagine...
You can fly a plane over anywhere but Disney World.
Even if on 9- like on 9/11 one of the targets was Disneyland.
They should have said you can't fly a plane through a building.
That would have been a very good...
That's like an unspoken rule.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
If they'd taken out Disney World, we'd be living in a much scarier and more tense security
state.
If they took out Disney World, they would have fucking launched a nuke.
They would have launched a nuke immediately.
questions asked as soon as the plane hits the rock and roller coaster fucking one
big nuke going over the middle of the love Darrow Smith man yeah he did all the
rides would do that thing from the Jimmy Neutron movie where they'd blast off and
they'd all fly into into the Middle East and explode yeah but then they'd
accidentally but what if all of the explosives malfunction now they just
have a Disney World.
That was their plane all along.
Right?
What if they hijacked the plane and they made sure they got a bunch of, they packed a bunch
of luggage with magnets in it and they flew really low over the Disney World and it became
all the rides.
Way more of a tragedy.
We launched a nuke because they stole Disney World from us.
So much imagineering gone to waste.
Yeah.
It's not like you can build a new Disney World.
That should be Ocean's 14.
Yeah, Werner Von Braun is dead.
He's the one who designed the wheat tissue.
Ocean's 14.
He was a Nazi Imagineer.
What is the biggest thing in Operation Paperclip was the creation of Disney World?
Dude, we had all these Nazi Imagineers come over and design all the rides.
What is the use of rollercoaster that was done with the music of Aerosmith?
Well, sir, what the hell is Aerosmith?
we will have to create Harold Smith first.
That's what all the Flynn experiments were.
They were doing experiments on groups of guys.
That's why they, Steven, not many people know this, Steven Tyler was a Nazi experiment to
create the most beautiful man in the world.
The most beautiful looking androgynous person.
The perfect mixture of a girl and a guy.
And evil.
Yeah, he had some crazy shit going on back then.
It's cool that Liv Tyler didn't know that was her dad until she was like 18.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like you look at her and you're like, "Really?"
How the fuck do you not know?
Yeah.
Also, her name is Liv Tyler.
Yeah, I feel like it's a dead giveaway.
Hey, bitch, it says it on your Wikipedia page.
It's like, "Oh yeah, that's Stephen Tyler.
He comes to my house sometimes."
Yeah, he feeds me and clothes me.
"Sometimes he'll go to the kitchen and make a sandwich.
The story is that she had a poster of Stephen Tyler in her room when she was growing up,
which means that she used to fucking rub one out.
Thing her one.
She used to thing her one.
She used to thing her go-woner.
She used to go thingy on her one.
And then to her own father.
now she's her his daughter yeah yeah now she's elrond's daughter exactly in in that was her
way of of of begging for forgiveness from the universe she became one of the the most chaste
and beautiful races of all time an elf the most beautiful elf of all time facts the most pure of
heart yeah that's crazy though that's i mean elf if my if your dad was a rock star my dad is
Really?
Yeah, he's in Saxon.
[Laughter]
My dad's Saxon.
Your dad is Saxon from Saxon?
Yeah.
Okay, that's sick.
That's sick as fuck, dude.
Yeah, my dad's AC/DC.
Yep.
That's true.
That's my dad.
Yeah.
My dad sings Back in Black.
No, just like...
I was gonna ask, like, fuck I don't remember, I was just gonna ask what would you do if your
dad was a rockstar?
Probably rock out with him, probably shred, probably learn how to fucking shred, probably
fucking fuck his groupies too.
Hey, if you're like my dad, you're gonna like my young penis.
Dude, like Kevin Gates with his dog?
What?
Didn't Kevin Gates say that like- My dad's not gonna like make the girls fuck me.
Kevin Gates said, he was like, "If you in my bed and you fucking sucking my dick, you
you gotta suck my dog's dick.
And apparently kicked a girl out of his house for that.
Yeah.
That's so dude.
That is so fucking funny.
It was a werewolf, like from Twilight.
Yeah, it's his werewolf homie.
It wasn't a dog.
Yeah, it was.
Hot ass Taylor Lautner.
Exactly.
Sitting there.
And if you don't, if you're not gonna fuck Taylor Lautner, if you're not fucking the
crew, especially with a hottie like that, you better get the fuck out of my bed.
If you're not fucking, if you come over my place, you sucking my dick, you gotta suck
the wolfman's dick, you gotta suck the mummies dick, you gotta suck Dracula's dick.
You suckin' a whole squad, baby.
Yep.
If you ain't sucking off the creature of the black lagoon in my house, in my- I live at
the black lagoon.
If you're not- You gotta suck me, and you gotta suck Flubber,
my number one homie.
And Abbie and Costello.
You gotta figure out how to suck-
(laughter)
- Who's on first?
That sucks.
- I don't fucking know.
- Who's on my one?
Who's on my one?
- Calling it your one, dude.
I think that's gonna catch on.
I think it's gonna be a, it's gonna be called,
it's gonna be my one.
- Yeah, 'cause that's where the number one,
that's where the number one comes out.
- Yeah, you go number one out of that.
- Yeah, and then your number two is your blood.
I don't want to talk about that.
No, that's nasty.
It's going to be a number one winter.
We don't go there.
Well, you have, no, it would be your number, your butt would be your number three because
there's two under the one.
What?
There's two balls under the one penis.
Why would your ass be number three though?
Because that's behind it.
You only got one.
Really?
Hold on, I'll tell you, Caleb.
I guess you do have three things there.
Two butt cheeks and a butthole.
Take a three, take the three, right?
Uh-huh.
Flip it on its side.
What does it look like?
It's a nine now.
What?
Turn the three upside down, it's a nine now.
You no.
It's a Drake song.
I was, well the three.
I turn the three upside down, it's a three now.
Three upside down looks like butt cheeks.
It's an E.
Or balls.
Turn the three upside down, it's a E now.
He should have done that like 50 more times in that song.
Yeah.
I turn the I upside down, it's a line now.
There needs to be more math.
She fingered on my one and then I run my hand through her 10,000.
her hair. Oh silly you, only God knows the number of hairs on a person's head. She's
thinking on my one till I have four. What? Four is a con. She's wondering on my one. Oh
no, four is because there's two balls and that's what they make. Wait, she's fiving
my one. Oh, you're right. Fiving my one. She's 32ing. How many sperms in a spray of sperm?
(laughter)
- 100 million per milliliter.
- No way.
I have way less than that.
- She's having my one till I have 100 million.
- 500 million?
(laughter)
- That's disgusting.
- I have way less sperm than that.
- Yeah, yeah I guess, yeah.
- I think I have one big one that shoots out.
- Until I, 30 million plus 70 million microplastics.
(laughter)
I can feel the microplastics dude.
I can see them in my cum because I have micro eyes.
They're pink.
They look like the beads in hand soap that they used to have.
Remember when they used to have that?
Remember when they thought that was a good idea to just put pieces of plastic in hand
soap?
Yeah, they put pieces of plastic in hand soap and then it would fuck up like fish.
Yeah, you'd just, you'd fucking, you'd bite into a fucking roll of sushi and you'd get
just like plastic in your mouth.
cool dude yeah such a genius imagineering feat. Remember when they think it's cool to put like a toothpick through a sandwich yeah it always gets stuck in your throat that's right
they put a fucking napkin on the side of your plate it's like okay I'm gonna eat
this yeah I wipe my head on it there's food on it yeah I gotta get the food off
these days I might think the napkin might be cake or something honestly the napkin
the napkin is one of the worst garnishes of all time definitely stop putting napkins on my food
on my food.
When they fold it to look like a swan?
I want swan.
Yeah.
I've never tasted this before.
Now I'm hungry for swan.
It tastes like cloth.
Have they made, is there a swan burger?
I'm so hungry for swan.
Can you eat swan?
Dude, you can totally eat.
I need swan.
I'm so hungry.
Oh, my stomach.
I need to get home.
I need some swan.
Oh, god.
I need swan so bad.
I need a swan song.
I need to get home and butcher a flamingo so bad.
My stomach is so full.
I need a swan song.
I need to get home and butcher a flamingo so bad.
I need to go home and butcher a flamingo so bad.
I need emu.
I need jerk flamingo so bad.
Oh I need peacock.
Oh god.
I bet any one of those tastes pretty fucking good.
Yeah they probably all taste like chicken.
Every bird tastes good.
Oh I need emperor penguin nuggets.
I heard penguin's the one that doesn't taste good.
Really?
I looked up what penguin tastes like and I guess it tastes like, it smells like shit
and tastes like it too.
I guess it's like super oily.
It says they taste like a piece of beef, odiferous codfish, and a canvas-baked duck roast together
in a pot with blood and cod liver oil for sauce.
What?
They taste like what?
The meat is smudge-like pork, sweet, succulent, rich.
What did I read then?
You read about that dookie penguin dude from fucking Dookie's Burg.
it
it's
I feel like it might not. I don't know. I think it's too cold. I've never touched a penguin but it looks rubbery and disgusting.
I'm looking up penguin burger. I feel like penguin would be hard to chew.
Yeah. Especially if it was raw. Yeah, the feathers on it.
You know what would look... You know what... Also they're covered in oil, aren't they?
You know what might taste really good?
Andean condor.
you think now condors not any any scavengers not gonna taste very good nah
dude I think condor would taste amazing I think some yeah some some condor tenders
condor wings condor to look at think about how big those wings are yeah okay
okay that's the biggest way you make it a fucking any bird if you cover it in
garlic parmesan or or that'd be like a wing the size of this fucking mic arm
Yeah. You don't want that. That's the biggest, dude that's, yes I do eat a flint stone sized wing.
A condor is way bigger than your mic arm. Really? Condors are fucking huge.
Condors are like, have like several wingspan. I'm so scared of big birds.
But I mean who knows how much of that is actual wing meat.
You know. Oh Pat I have a, I have a prehistoric animal for you to look at.
Oh man. If you're afraid of big birds. This guy, dude, oh fuck dude, the California condor it's like.
I really hate looking at this picture.
Am I going to be scared of this?
It's a pterodactyl the size of a giraffe.
This doesn't scare me because it looks like it's made in a Playstation 1.
Look at the size comparison to a human.
It's huge.
A condor?
No, no, as darkid.
That thing is weird.
It's the largest flying animal, but they believed they were ground hunters.
So they would run around and eat shit up.
This thing could fly?
Oh fuck dude, it would run?
The size of a fucking giraffe?
Holy shit.
Dude, a big bird like this shit, like a big bird like this is so fucked up.
I saw like a video of a bald eagle at the vet and it was just like, it fucked me up
realizing how big a bald eagle is.
Yeah, for the listeners, the As Dark It had a wingspan of 33 to 39 feet.
Oh, God.
Oh, look at it!
And it lived alongside humans in the Garden of Eden.
I fucking, you know what I hate too?
Looking at baby birds.
Baby birds look fucked up.
You sound sarcastic.
You know what I hate?
You put the emphasis on birds in that.
You hate looking at baby birds.
You only hate the bird part, right?
Yeah.
What?
See, I don't care.
I hate looking at baby birds. Yeah, you hate baby bird. Oh, I hate baby birds. Yeah, I hate when babies are birds. I
Hate when somebody tells me
Dude the fucking oh, oh
There's looking at pictures of baby birds now, it's like retching and
Squetching and being weird when you look at a baby bird. I will check is like a little like a little chicken
Condors have some serious cock face on them. Yeah, they got some cock and balls head
Holy condor face. Oh, yeah. Wow serious fucking nuts and cocks and balls for the ice
I hate big birds, but I do love I do love a cardinal you hate big birds. I
Love one that'll change your mind. Yeah. Yeah, you hate big birds. So he turns he turns it
I'll fucking know some fucking hippie piece of shit town. Yeah, so liberal some
It now the fuck is that fucking college town, that's right, that's right school town
That's right. They got all these fucking stupid. It's liberal fucking preschool town. I'm so sick
I'm so sick of these motherfuckers. I'm so sick of not living there
That's what you say signs up in front of their fucking restaurants and shit. They say today's letter is M
Fucking bullshit
Yeah, singing to me about sharing
Yeah, I'm not sharing shit with you. Tell you what there's a whole lot of America between San Francisco and Sesame Street
Lot of the people in Washington seems like they forget that sometimes
Yeah, I would hate to live on Sesame Street, bro. Yeah, every day you wake up suck dude. You're trying to fucking babies everywhere
Don't know adults
Famous actors
Famous actor
And snuffle effigies starts talking to mr. Hooper. Yeah, yo, I would I would chill with snuffy
What's his name in the fucking toilet or the trash?
Oscar?
The green one.
Yeah.
Oscar, did I ever show you my Oscar the Grouch costume as a baby?
Was it similar to your Grinch costume where you chose a much too dark of a shade of green?
No.
Okay.
It was light green.
My mom did it.
And what color were the lips?
Brown.
(laughter)
Look, that was... alright.
And what'd you do with your hair?
(laughter)
That was a mistake. I didn't realize how dark that green was when I was the Grinch.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure.
And you didn't realize how gold the chain was either. That was a big problem.
(laughter)
(laughing)
- Go ahead and make excuses.
- I don't think the green was that dark.
I think the only problem--
- Bro, you are losing your fucking mind
if you don't think that you wore full blackface on Halloween.
- I didn't wear blackface.
I was dressed up like the Grinch.
There's photos of me as the Grinch.
You were blacked out Santa all the way.
I was not blacked out Santa for Halloween.
You absolutely were.
I was not.
You were blacked out Santa with Morgan Freeman freckles.
Oh my god!
What the fuck dude?
A slime monster just came out of Matt's nose!
I'm so sorry.
Oh my god.
That was so crazy.
That was so gross.
Oh my god.
That was insane.
Where did you put it?
I just sucked it back up my nose.
No.
Oh shit.
Oh dude.
No.
He's gonna come back later for sure.
It's under his desk.
It's under his chair right now.
There's someone in my...
Oh fuck dude.
I gotta...
Hold on.
We gotta pause.
I gotta get a napkin.
We can't pause.
Just go.
We'll just keep talking about it.
Holy shit dude.
That was insane.
That was like...
Did you not...
It was like blue.
It was like perfectly blue.
It was like when the fucking android dies an alien and he just sprays like milk everywhere.
Yeah, no he's definitely, like me and Cam have this theory that Pat's just gonna get
COVID every two weeks for the rest of the year.
I think that's gonna happen.
I think he's back, this is round two.
I think this is proof, yeah.
I think this is hard proof.
This is hard proof that you have COVID again.
I don't have COVID again.
You do.
I
for
Are you, it was the shade of the eyebrows maybe.
It was not the shade of the eyebrows.
I didn't wear blackface on Halloween.
You I have, there's so much photographic proof that you did.
I did not wear blackface on Halloween.
Also the Grinch.
I was dressed up like the Grinch.
Why did you not get a lighter green?
The Grinch is such a light green.
I literally, I went to the one, like I went to a place in my neighborhood and found a
a dollar tube of green face paint and just put that on.
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm. There's so many pictures of me and like hanging
out in my apartment that it's all you all we really need is one picture that shows how
it looked in the bar lighting. Doesn't matter how many.
That'd be so funny if like that comes out like people like try to like cancel be whatever
for it. I'm canceling you for it. Here's Patrick Doherty blackface out of a bar. I'm gonna do
it. This is the pig I have. No, no, that's green. That is green. That is not green. I'll
text it to you right now so you can have it. That is green. Who am I with in that photo?
uh... i don't know
i think i could get
stressy
does mean jesse okay but yeah i don't think it did photos are
because i think that i don't mean a friend
and i think we're blurry and you and your and uh...
brown grease paint
no no no
dot you you clearly no moments of clarity and that's really that's great
That is, that looks green dude.
No fucking way.
If it looks green then post it right now with no caption.
It's way worse by the way that you didn't do your neck.
You did a perfect circle over your face and the rest of your body is white.
Yeah.
Fuck you man.
If it's green put it on Instagram right now.
I did!
There is a picture of me on my Instagram.
I want an Instagram right now.
I don't have to do it.
Halloween is over.
You're like a deleted boss from Cuphead.
Don't snort again.
Please don't slide again.
I can only take it once.
Oh man.
Alright.
You guys want to do our beautiful list?
Yeah okay.
Is there anything else important we have to talk about?
Oh no.
By the way, I was gonna come with a costume today, but I have COVID and I can't go to
the costume store. So Patrick, you have kicked the can down the road just one more week.
But I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you good.
I can go outside.
If you... no. You can't go outside.
Yeah, I can. I can go buy a costume right now.
No, that's cheating by the way because we're gonna have a war and that's not how a war works
You can't cheat in a war so I can cheat in a war
You actually can't because I just looked up the rules of war on Wikipedia and it's one of the Geneva
Conventions that you can't any verse you can't cheat in an actual war. So don't call them that Patrick
What you can't say that?
Geneva can't say that. Oh my god. Stop
Stop, I'm sick of these Geneva's at my convention
I was laughing at myself last night imagining I was actually thinking about
war. You were laughing at the war? You must be a psychopath.
The seagulls from Finding Nemo but they're saying war war war.
like strife strife pain pain pain yeah that was really getting me pretty good
so I'm glad you reminded me of that okay anyway today's list top 10 most wanted
superpowers from l9me line nine me line it nine me probably line nine yo she
She nining on my one.
Line me, nine me, get down on my one and make my spine creak.
She nining on my one because the wedding ring finger doesn't count.
True.
Is she not married tonight?
Okay, number one is teleportation.
This first person is very creative with the power of teleportation.
If you could teleport yourself and other objects, it would be the most powerful power in my opinion.
Teleport sickness out of others' bodies, teleport heads off villains in a superhero villain
world, teleport yourself out of bed, your clothes on, dirt off dirty things.
It beats seeing the future because you don't need to if you are ready for anything.
Even someone with regenerative powers.
Just teleport every atom into a star in our universe.
You could even see how big the universe is or if there are other dimensions by teleporting
there.
This is, however, just hoping that you can also teleport other objects.
That's a good point.
He's very liberal with the term teleport.
Bro, drop me into the fucking Jumper universe and I'm gonna change NBA history forever.
He's teleported!
Oh, and Kayla Pitts comes with a beautiful teleportation dunk over LeBron James.
Oh, and he teleported into LeBron's body and he made him explode!
You think they would make a...
LeBron James' brains and entrails are all over Madison Square Garden.
and
hundred times a second yeah you just tell you what just a million times a second
just go that's right just the ball back and forth I also teleport objects
teleport the ball Disney World I tell her the ball I'd score one point on a
free-throw I'd miss the second one then I teleport the ball into my stomach oh I
don't know where the ball went Oh me oh I don't know I've always been this fat
Oh, I guess we just had to wait for the time to run out.
Oh no, my baby's being born and then teleport a random baby from the hospital onto the court.
Oh no, it was twins! Now we have two.
Now I'm just wasting time.
But yeah, I think teleportation, the obvious move is to go sports.
You know, yeah. Yeah, I guess I mean I would I would teleport I teleport to the front of the front of the line
Yeah at the line at the line store. Yeah at the queue
Here's a comment from master hand. I would definitely want this
I can go anywhere without having to spend five hours just to get to my destination
This guy takes five hours to go anywhere. Okay, five hours to go to the grocery store. Yeah good. This is good. Okay, would you
Would you rather have travel as it is now, you know, where different things take different
lengths of time.
Or teleportation.
Or it takes two hours to get anywhere in the world.
Two hours to get anywhere.
Okay, does that count like if I want to like step, take one step?
No, no, no.
If you're going from city to, or not city, if you're leaving your neighborhood, it takes
two hours.
Okay, my neighborhood's the whole world, because I'm a world.
not a world citizen, you're not a citizen of the world. I would be in this world.
No, in this world you're explicitly as the god of this world, by the way I'm god
in this universe. Okay, I would not want to live there. You would be lucky if I was your god,
by the way. You'd be very lucky because I take good care of you because you're my
friend. Lucky in the way that people who get struck by lightning are lucky, no thanks. No, lucky in the way that
like got 50 year old guys who hook up with 18 year olds say that they got last
night. That kind of lucky. So you are you are gonna get seriously lucky if you let me be
God. Mm-hmm lucky like the first guy who dies from 5G. No. No thanks. No I'm not talking. It's gonna be
it's gonna be one of us. 5G? For sure. First guys? I'm gonna I think it could be me. You might be 5G.
You might be completely 5G at this point. Yeah. Yeah there's nobody in this world who has more
artificial thing sitting in his body than you. Yeah thank you for saying that.
So you're not gonna answer my hypothetical then? You're just gonna complain about me being God?
No Patrick you can answer. I already answered. What'd you say? I said two hours.
You take the two hours thing? Really? Yeah. I feel like that's cool man you could split
your time between here and Seoul. Yeah. Oh my god. Dude, if I wanted to go to a Korean Costco.
Oh man. I go to India. Crazy shit. I come back. I can bring Yummy Say Tummy back to my house.
We're like, Pat, where have you been? He walks in with 50 bags from Hitler Men's Clothing.
He's like, "Ah, just shopping.
"I just went shopping."
- Can you bring stuff?
- Dude, are you kidding me?
That'd be so funny.
- What do you mean, what if you bring stuff with you?
- I go to Yummy's to tell me I bring the whole restaurant
back and I put it in my neighborhood.
- Oh.
- It doesn't take me two hours to get there anymore.
- Okay.
- Even if I'm carrying something,
it'll still take me two hours,
so I'll just carry the whole restaurant.
- Here's, you know what?
If I'm your God, I might make it so you have super strength
and you're able to pick up a restaurant,
but if you don't accept me as your God in this,
then you're fucked honestly
okay i definitely accept is my god
okay first thing i do i have a lie
i'm a little bit camera girl mccain a girl making a girl
yes
and you can redoing or one-to-one recreation of the book of jobe with you
it's gonna be the book of cameras
and i'm gonna punish you know i would have a lot of first tribulation
really i'd my be i'd lose my keys and i'm i'm not going to
I must be the new job
is there any other good comments on this one
I can visit every single tourist attraction in one summer
wow that guy's a serious tourist yeah
I gotta take tourism seriously
I would visit every single tourist attraction
in one summer not even like a week
oh here's a whole summer
here's a comment here
can go and come back
through that is what's up with the parties white and his power you can do
anything
cool yay
nightcrawler jumper or that book about john's
truman did i look at night crawlers and this time of night crawler
my colors cool the blue guy
you know i would recommend you dress up as a map
well i thought it was blue
guys i thought it was a dark dark blue yeah he is dark blue yeah that's yeah damn i can
never be nightcrawler huh no no number two really really you really brought down my energy
just now i'm sorry you could be a nightcrawler this will bring you back up this will bring
you back up i've been like like completely like i look more like a mime than nightcrawler
and like no I'm white crawler yeah I'm scared I'm scared of what would happen
I'm a white baller damn damn yep did you just slime again I did stop sliming I
put this like nasal decongestant in my nose this like a fresh stuff and yeah no
it's been cleaning me out I'm getting slime you know what I've been doing to
To battle my COVID-19, I've literally been eating candy that I can't taste at all. And I've just
been eating tons of candy because I got a big belly. You got the no taste? I just, I can taste
it a little bit. You bet had no taste. Oh, shit. Damn. Fuck. Fuck. Mm-hmm.
I didn't get the no taste thing. My taste is like, I wouldn't say I have no taste,
but it's definitely muted. So today I ate like 15 Reese's Pieces.
That's not very much. It's just a handful.
That's a small amount. I thought you were supposed to eat like one.
What are you talking about?
I get the individually packaged one.
I get the individually packaged one as a, they all come in a little box, you open the box
they're twisty wrapped.
The individual packaged Reese's Pieces?
Yeah.
I just get, I eat one at a time, so I had 15 today, I went kinda crazy.
It's like, you know when you get like the Advil from the, like the, the one thing, the
two of them?
It's just one Reese's Pieces.
My stomach was hurting last night because I had seven grains of Fun Dip.
Oh my god, my stomach, I'm having a, I had a pop rock.
Yeah.
Number two.
Imagine flying over everything and seeing everyone super tiny down below and yet you
were up high doing your own thing.
You would feel so good and free.
Flight is A-M-A-Z-I-N-G.
Flying is the best superpower and no one can argue with that.
kind of transportation and helpful for certain situations.
I believe I can fly.
Ever since I was little, I have dreamed of creating a device to make us fly.
What does this comment mean?
Pasco Dodo's kendo was the way I can get the one room to get my baby.
True.
Who is Pasco Dodo?
Here's a comment.
Flight is a born savage.
True.
I can fly to not get bullied.
sad
they get bullied way harder if they're not a school was flying yeah sub-u
fucking fly and has prisoners
you know i think there's a good school would see you flying say this kid can't
take the bus
yeah right
this has to go for the bus
as i don't have a car
that's why i don't like to school is not to have a car can't even a policy like
get your head out of the clouds
come back to earth. And people online would probably bully you and say touch grass.
Touch grass with your feet, you can't, you're levitating. Plus a football team would probably
fuck you if they caught you. Probably turn you out. Probably fuck you out of your sandals.
They fuck you silly probably.
They might corner you in the locker room and like, I don't even want to go there.
That would suck so bad.
Let's just say it includes 1's and 2's.
There's gonna be a thing on your 1.
And unfortunately a 65.
Ohhhh.
Sorry.
Sorry. Number three is telekinesis. What? Telekinesis species. I think, okay, two, these two battle
it out in my superpowers I think. Flight and telekinesis? No, no, no, no. Teleportation
and telekinesis. You don't want time control? Hmm. Time control, there's too much temptation
in
time
That'd be kind of scary, right?
You worry about getting paused forever?
That's crazy to think about.
Yeah, I know. That's some real shit.
That's some fucking Isaac Asimov shit.
I wouldn't do time control because, um...
I don't want to waste any time on anybody else's time, you know?
I don't want to...
Think about everyone else.
Oh my god, if you were in charge of time, kill me, man.
I don't want to for you to be I mean yeah horrible man just fast forward every 10
minutes like as you got yeah everybody's this is a bad 10 minutes yeah yeah
about telekinesis if you really think about a telekinesis would be considered
would considered to be one of the most destructive superpower you could have
let's say if you are somewhere surrounded by people and your nemesis is
in the same room with you. You could inflect pain upon your nemesis by using your power
and move things around. You could move and item towards that person and he/she can trip
or you cold make something fall on top of them. And the best part is that no one can
see you doing it. If you were among for the kill you can just move and random object and
keep hitting the person until they die. Also it is also good for stealing things. You can
just move the things towards you and then you can claim that item as yours. It also
good for defense too. You can just move and object around you quickly so that no one can
come through you. It also saves you from doing the bloody job. Like if you want to cut a
carrot but you are afraid to risk your hand. There are many stuff you can do with telekinesis
including conjuring water, freezing ice, and etc.
The bloody job?
Yeah, cutting a carrot.
What is the bloody job?
Like if you want to cut a carrot but you are afraid to risk your hand.
The bloody job?
Well if I was afraid to risk my hand, I'd wear a glove.
I would use my telekinesis power. Yeah, that's true. It's basically just like the force if
you think about it. Now do you like it, Pat? Whoa, okay. I can get stuff with my mind if
my arms are weak. True. I would just be, I feel like if I had telekinesis I'd probably
pretty quickly reach six, seven hundred pounds. Yeah, that's true. There'd be no reason for
me to ever fucking move. You could remove the food out of your stomach without having
to throw up yeah yeah oh that's a good point yeah I guess so but I wouldn't do
that no I of course I would be if I had the chance to be 700 pounds I would I
would do it if I gets just skip directly to 700 pounds right now you would do it I
feel like I would do it I think I would do it is that's the I would like to do
it for one day yeah you know what be 700 pounds for one day I just want to I just
I just want to prove to people who are 700 pounds that you can actually walk around still.
Like I just want to like kind of rub it in their face.
Like you're 700 pounds for one day, immediately be like the most fit 700 pound guy of all time.
If I was 700 pounds for one day, you know my ass rolling down a big hill.
I'm rolling you down the big hill if you were 700 pounds for one day.
And you're also 700 pounds.
What if like it's all three of us and we're 700 pounds and we're playing with a stick of
butter together. That might be good if like all three of us got like really really fat
like insanely like I feel like we would pretty quickly have like a Comedy Central 15 minute
sketch show. What if you guys are like 700 pounds and I become like 50 pounds? Yeah.
Like maybe we took all of Cameron's weight. You should be one of those guys who like loses
every part of your body except for like your head and like half of your torso. Yeah. Yeah.
you wear it where a 700 pound guys who just carry you around like a backpack
yeah we have a travel show yeah Thunderdome I was singing about that I
got when you got nothing like that you might as well just be like a slice of
bread yeah absolutely might as well be like a paper bag at that point you bro
I'm in there I mean like you were just a torso there's guys who are just torsos
I'm gonna search up just "torso man".
It's one by Metallica. They invented it.
Yeah.
Isn't that... yeah.
Wait, is that what one is about?
Yeah.
I thought it was about a guy, a fan that killed himself.
What?
I thought that one...
You think it was Stan?
By Eminem?
I thought it was a Metallica fan who killed himself.
Imagine me in this guy.
Let me take a look at this fellow.
Let's see here.
That guy is not much.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Well good for him, he's like wrestling and shit.
Yeah.
That's sick.
It's cool when like someone's like half a torso or whatever and then they like, or like
there's a, what's his name?
Right, I mean cause it's cool cause he's trying really hard but he might as well just be a
plant.
*laughter*
Well he doesn't have to do all this trying hard shit.
Oh, Felipe, Felipe Nunez.
Felipe Nunez.
What about him?
He's sick.
Felipe Nunez is sick as fuck.
Is he a skater?
He's a skater with no legs.
Alright, I'm looking at him and he has legs that are just very small.
Well, hold on, does he have legs?
Yeah.
No.
I'm looking at him right now, he has legs.
Oh he does have little legs. What? Oh and here he has big legs. Oh man this guy's faking it.
I think he's faking it. I think he's just faking the whole thing. He's got legs under there.
fours invisibility here's a comment invisibility would be fun I love being
invisible
I didn't seek imagine you've been you've had the power to go invisible for like
years and you're like you're keeping it a secret like the CIA is after you they
finally catch you because they trace your IP because you posted on the top
ten we need you we need you to be a spy I would just go invisible in that
situation to true what when would you guys put your invisibility cutting in
line all the time yeah that'd be really good well wouldn't a teleportation be
better for cutting up no because then people would see you teleported with
still see you be invisible people would see you teleport to the front of the
line and get freaked the fuck out at you so you think you think that if you're
invisible and you cut in line people would just hold the empty space that you
were standing in in the line yeah I think so before you only got like three people
ahead like you know yeah well yeah I would just go straight I'd go right into
wherever I was going and then I'd do I'd walk to the front of the line I'd walk
into the into the bathroom invisible and then I'd come out of the bathroom mm-hmm
I bet what if all the stalls are taken there's a line for the stalls then I
I pick something up and pretend to be a ghost and scare everyone out.
That's pretty good.
And then after that, yeah, and then you'd walk out and say, "There was a ghost in there?"
That's the thing.
I think invisibility, there's two ways to cut a line here.
I think teleportation is the one that people will get mad at you for because like, yes,
you're cutting the line, but like they can see you teleport from the back to the front.
like invisibility you can just get rid of the line by becoming a ghost.
That's another good power.
Like camcorder.
Yeah, because invisibility is the second if you're invisible you have two powers which is the power
yeah it's the two powers that you have you have invisibility then the power for the fright
and then also third power uh line destruction
third power line destruction fourth power uh uh toilet paper suit toilet paper suit
and wrap yourself up that's part of fright is that okay yeah because that's a mummy
so that's under fright yeah all right if you're the invisible man under the mummy suit
the invisible man was wore a mummy suit in the movie
Remember he wrapped himself up with those bandages.
They should have called that movie "The Mummy".
He was the cool mummy.
He was just wrapped up in bandages with sunglasses on.
True.
That was his shit.
He saw the mummy and thought, "I'm gonna go cooler."
Number five is
Immortality.
The question is, is this a power or a curse?
It's a curse.
Because if you're immortal but you're like aging
I ask myself that question about everything
that happens to me in daily life.
I make myself a sandwich, I think it's just a power.
Going to the bathroom?
We'll find out.
Yeah.
Going to the bathroom, kind of a little of both, depending on the day.
Oh, screw off, naysayers.
I think that immortality rocks along invincibility.
Besides, who wants to be weak and mortal?
Okay, the devil.
Yeah.
Here's another comment.
It is the best.
That's the same guy.
He's invisible and fucking immortal.
Yeah.
best. That's the same guy. He's invisible and fucking immortal. If I was immortal, I don't
think I'd have a good time. Here's a comment. It would be useful to a chicken. True. That
is true. Chickens have pretty short lifespans, I guess. Yeah, that is true. Number six, predicting
the future. I wouldn't want this. See if I get a beard. I mean this is useful pretty
much only for the lottery right? Yeah. Like everything else is like you're kind
of like you don't really want to know. Yeah definitely. Oh you kidding me?
Here's another good comment. Imagine knowing what comes next at
at any time or in any time zone.
- If I could predict the future,
I'd see who my spouse was,
and then I would immediately--
- I would see who your spouse was and marry them.
- Yeah, I'd seduce them instantly.
- I'd see who my spouse was
and then immediately play a trick on them.
'Cause then it's like, well, I know
that you're gonna be my spouse in the future,
but I can't try to do tricks to you now.
- So you wanna start a relationship
founded on deceit and cruelty.
- And tricks.
You'd rather like, like kind of subdue someone into marrying you with tricks.
You didn't trap them more than like, I didn't think this relationship is founded on tricks.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing a gesture thing.
What number seven about shape shifting, okay, shape shifting maybe is a third place for
me.
I think it's like teleportation would be sick telekinesis and then shape shifting.
You want to just be Kirby.
It would just be cool.
You want to be...
You want to just become Kirby?
You want to just turn into like a monster or something.
That would be tight.
Dude, I'd give myself two huge boobs if I was bored.
Here's what you'd say.
Disguise yourself as a sexy girl would be a great choice, but I prefer disguise as a
president so that I can fix this poor country.
I left that comment.
You better.
That's actually pretty good.
That is really, yeah.
It would be awesome.
I love animals and it would be cool to be able to become one.
Someday if I'm rich enough I'll hire a scientist to make a vaccination or something to give
me the power of shape shifting.
When I was a little kid I was convinced that I had this necklace, I got it like a swap
meet that had like a little piece of blue stone in it.
I was convinced that it was going to give me super powers and so I'd sit in my bed for
like an hour a day just trying to turn into an animal.
(snorting)
(laughing)
- It never worked though, I just put it on,
I just sit there and be like,
it's time to become Beast Boy or Meat Pie, it's right now.
- I wanted to be Beast Boy so bad.
- Oh, he was the coolest one.
- Beast Boy was so sick.
- He was the coolest one.
- Here's a comment, a bug, enough said.
(laughing)
- That would suck to turn into a bug for one second,
just immediately get squashed.
- Dude, yeah, you're a fly and you get
the fucking shit kicked out of you.
or you like because they they have such short life spans you like turn back to
being a person you're fifteen years older
yes i sucked it
you know whilst i love what i am sometimes i wish i was human
ten
uh... police
and
that has a bug
uh... i thought i was a little while ago but i keep his yeah
uh... could you
halfway shapeshift stuff, it would be awesome to go to school with a fluffy prehensile tail
and giant wings please. Plus you could shapeshift yourself so you have more powers.
True.
It's true.
Okay, number eight, super speed. What do you guys think? I think teleportation's just better.
Yeah, teleportation's better than super speed.
Yeah, super speed is worse in every single way.
Definitely.
I can't even think of one upside.
I don't know, I think maybe, yeah, super speed would be kind of cool.
No, it's worse than teleportation.
Okay, you're right, it's worse than teleportation.
Well, alright, what could you do, I mean, I guess if you had a job, if you were like...
Alright, it's better than teleportation now.
Okay, number nine.
No, if you had a job, it's like, if you were like...
Alright, it's worse.
if you were to u_p_s_ or something
and you had a like do stuff like we'd like it you to package it all day
located is it speed manipulation or super speed
what's what i think i think what you think that's what we know is to things
are
like okay so calypso
positing the question here if you were to do you think i would be what got into
you in the last thirty seconds
your your posit in the question if if you work for u_p_s_
Do you mean USPS or UPS because you're driving a truck for UPS and that's what I mean by speed
manipulation you would have to manipulate the car not like...
I was thinking you guys could still drive a truck.
Well yeah but like I'm talking about like a USPS guy in like a neighborhood like you
see them like walking around here with the carts.
They can still drive a truck.
I'm talking about the carts guys, the guys with the carts.
Still can drive a truck.
Yeah they can still drive a truck but it's speed manipulation when you're driving...
- I feel like I've been violated.
- I know what you're talking about.
- You have completely hijacked my hypothetical
and injected words that make no sense
and turned it about, now it's about your mailman.
What are you doing to my question?
- I'm trying to kill my mailman with speed.
- I'm skipping my question now.
I'm so upset I don't even wanna hear the answer.
Super speed sucks, we're moving on.
- Number nine, time manipulation.
Oh is this where you got the speed manipulation thing from?
No.
It is.
It's not.
You looked at this and you were like I'm going to combine the two.
No he was thinking about the other manipulations he's doing to people.
Yeah.
Why do you do that?
You're a manipulator.
I didn't do anything.
You talked about how you're going to manipulate your future bride.
I'm not going to do that.
You said that.
You said I'm going to manipulate her.
You said I'm a regular Robert Durst.
Yeah. Time manipulation, it should just say time travel.
That just means like slow and sp- slow it, slow it up and speed it down.
And pause it and play it.
Yeah, okay so this is click.
Subtitles on?
Yeah, this is click.
Yeah, that is click.
I will say click remote might be my number one.
Yeah, click remote would be sick.
Click remote, you can do pretty much whatever you want.
I mean yeah, it was awesome in the movie. He farted on girls boobs.
He fucking, he would take a shit on his boss's desk.
He farted in David Hasselhoff's mouth.
Yeah, he would rewind and press play when the girls jumping boobies were running and jumping.
And I mean, I feel like I'm a very much, I'm probably not anything like the real Adam Sandler, but I'm a lot like his characters.
And so I feel like that appeals to me a lot.
Here's a comment that's very mysterious.
I could go back in time so the list I regret making was never made and I could time travel
to June 29th.
Hello.
What's on June 29th?
I don't know.
Let me Google June 29th.
This guy's a seer.
Let's see what happens on June 29th.
June 29th.
It's Colin Jost's birthday.
What are you going to...
It was Colin Jost who left that comment.
I don't know.
I'm not going to read it.
He loves you's birthday!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
June 29th, 2012, the day Ted was released.
Oh my god.
June 29th, 2001, PoodieTang.
Wow!
Speaking of, rewatch that, my parents on Christmas, that's a perfect movie.
How can you steal powers with this?
Nobody's saying you can steal powers. Whoa hold on number 13 released in 2018 the
movie Patrick. Oh my god you're in trouble this guy's gonna find you. Number 10 is
super strength. Pretty lame. I already have this pretty much so it's fine. Yeah I got this by
earning it in the gym right with G fuel so it's not I would never ask for this
power here's a bunch of comments can say a consecutive comments i can lift heavy
stuff i cold lift a building you could punch planets you could be turtles
give me the power of devils
(laughter)
- Alright, now we need to continue.
- That kid needs his internet approval just taken away.
- Yeah, I know, Moe needs Net Nanny banned.
Number 11, mind control.
- Random website supposed to give me the power of the devil.
- I need to be the devil.
- Make me the devil now.
- The kid's not looking at like Porn or like
ISIS execution videos, he's just looking at
He's on the devil.com. I must be the devil.
I have to become the devil, please. Give me devil power.
Uh, so the contenders, we have mind control. Mind control, I think, would freak me out too much.
Yeah, I would not. Here's a comment.
I'm gonna go jump off the Golden Gate Bridge now.
What the hell? That's on mind control.
That's somebody's suicide note on the top tens.
I control you you're now a pig oh yes that works number is 13 super healing so
if my bro beats me up again then healing powers is the best then I can kill my
friend Ellie who currently has cancer oh don't let the devil see that one don't
worry Ellie I'm getting the power of devils to get the super healing and I
will save you and then I was how it was dude the powers that the devil
superhearing that's not good healing for the devil is hurting true number 14
intangibility yep Wow number 15 super intelligence again I already have it I
would have I would I would take a super intelligence number 17 this is pretty
low for this one number 17 is omnipotence Wow you would essentially be
Bruce Almighty.
(Laughter)
I think I'm nipping it, I think.
Bruce Almighty.
Yeah, Jim.
Number 19, mind reading. I would love to have this power
because then I would know why my dad is always so mad at me.
(Laughter)
I would hate mind reading.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, that would suck.
the worst one appendage generation walking around like hearing everybody's thoughts
say I'm gonna hear them like talking about me or something and they're all
just the same bald bald bald bald it's all I hear number 24 is x-ray vision you
can see girls boobs and footsies
You can see girls footsies in the summertime.
They're wearing them damn flip-flops.
Omni-lingualism.
Mm-hmm.
Shrinking ability.
Magic.
A smaller you means a bigger world that's ripe for exploration.
Number 34, er, 35.
Make anyone love you.
True.
Yeah.
That, there's a comment here.
Are you a bit messed in the brain?
brain you could do that and much more with that useful nun sad loner style power.
Number 39, summoning, levitation.
That would be pretty good.
Vision replication.
Yeah, I don't know what that means.
Sensing death.
Freeze ray, just like Gru from Despicable Me.
Nihil likenesis.
And then number 53, the last one, concussion blasts.
Dude, I would do concussion blasts.
Yeah. You've already been blasted with plenty of concussions, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, wait. Can I plug this something?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Me and Kai started a podcast about monsters. If you like monsters, you should listen to
it. It's called Monster Crazy.
Don't listen to it. Only listen to this one.
Only listen to this one.
But if you like monsters, you shouldn't.
And you don't listen to his traitor podcast.
When does it come out?
It's out.
Oh, my God.
It's out today, I listened to it.
I listened to this and then I had to record this fucking shit.
I'm not done, I didn't even finish listening to it yet.
I wanted to listen to it more.
- Pray for me, because of how sick I am.
- And don't pray for Caleb.
- Yeah.
- No, pray for Caleb.
- Go to Caleb's house and make him sicker.
- I do have the devil in me.
- Because otherwise I'll revenge you.
- If you're sick right now, you have a free pass
to go on the train, go to Caleb's house
and sneeze in his mouth.
- I'm gonna put a clip on you.
Caleb's address is...
I'm gonna twist one part of your body so many times that it turns into a real sensitive
clit and I'm gonna flick it to death.
Really?
Yeah, Pat.
So keep talking, buddy.
See what happens.
So I'd have a clit?
Yep, but I'm gonna put it somewhere really inconvenient.
Like that part of your...
You will never be able to find it.
I'm gonna put...
Hell, I already can't.
I'm gonna put a clit on that one part of your back that you can't reach.
Oh, yeah.
Rats.
Good luck, buddy.
Bye.
I'd love to go down on my thing.