Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- You realize that when you tell stories,
you are the hero of the story.
So you have to have a happy ending.
You can't just fucking hurt yourself.
- A beginning, a middle, a happy ending.
- I'm just telling you, it's not a story,
it's an anecdote of when I got hurt.
- What is a story?
- An anecdote is a story.
- It was not a story.
- There was events that happened in that.
story no it was an anecdote there's a set there was a setting note is a boring
story that's exactly what an and that's all I'm good at you're not no that's all
I can tell is anecdotes I don't want to hear about you getting hurt that makes
that makes you take your anecdotes you add a turn it so I went I went to grab
some beers for my roommates last night and I went down a hill okay on my
skateboard okay beginning the story beginning beginning and inciting
incident.
Yep.
And now we have the rising action.
Yeah.
I it was wet from the rain.
That's rising action rising.
It rained previously.
Climax climax.
Okay.
And I was trying to do a power slide.
It's a boring climb to to slow down speed.
Still the climax.
Okay.
The peak.
And then I snowboard slid out.
Falling action.
Mm hmm.
Well he's about to have some falling action.
I got a bruise on my hip and my wrist.
So everything low point, low point, low point.
That's what that is.
Low point, yeah.
Then my board rolled into a tire and shot back out at me.
Okay, second low point.
But then I picked it up and I walked to the grocery store and I got beers for my friends.
Happy ending, denouement.
Yeah, back to, back to, happily ever after.
And then we drank the beers.
Back to the beginning but something's changed now.
Yes.
He has beers.
The new normal.
We drank the beers and then I ate some chips.
Okay, so this is the beginning of a second story.
Okay, and then what happened?
The chips were so good that I rubbed my belly.
Rising action.
I rubbed my belly and I went, "Ooooh."
Oh, that is a big climax.
"Ooooh, that's great."
Wow.
That's very exciting.
Actually, I didn't buy chips,
I bought crackers and I had cheese and crackers.
Okay.
This story sucks.
This is the worst story.
Is it possible to plot this straight?
How am I supposed to make a movie out of this?
That happened in movies like at the end of Clue
where they just like they go for like 10 minutes like oh wait no actually though
no no it was something different that's what they do at the end of clue there's
no I'm saying like at the end of clue if movies did that you should have this in
the middle like you know in Star Wars like oh wait no no no no no no Darth
Vader he wasn't that wasn't true that was like is we'll think of something
else yeah the chips are poker chips actually and they were it was a million
dollars worth of him and I ate it all of them resolution ending day new mom they
knew me new mom in the moon folks we're supposed to have Mike Racine on the show
today but he has come down with some... He has a flesh-eating disease in his face.
Yeah he's lost half of his body. He looks like Two-Face but he's two-body.
Yeah yeah and he'd look and also he's really short he's one inch tall now.
Yep and oh smelly. He smells like complete shit. I could tell from the picture he sent us.
He sent us a picture? Yeah a picture of his decayed flesh on half of his body.
Oh, I see I didn't even recognize him. Yeah, I mean the bone. Yeah. Yeah, I'm a guy served him at a restaurant
I'd be happy looks pretty moist. I am out in a little scene be or to you. Yeah, that's right. That's right
Mmm, you're gonna come over cracked pepper on him. Oh my god say when and then you go when yeah, you know
Oh, I love doing that. I love waiters. They fucking eat that shit up
Whenever they that's right whenever you do that if you say win that they chuckle you don't have to tip
That's enough. Yeah, that's enough. Yeah to just that'll get them by just some laughter. Yeah
It's a laughter is the best money. Yeah, it is true. That's what they say - yeah, we get paid in laughs
Laughter's the best money. I don't need money. I need money. I want money. I'd rather I
Yeah, I just the best money, but not for way to bars
I give my laughter away cuz I'm like charitable laughter is like way more
important than money so I give away my laughter and I just keep the money
return is money basically nothing it's what paper made of dirt yeah it's
basically nothing man it's paper made out of it's metal made out of circles
what is what it's just like a t-shirt pretty much like cutting a bunch of
second yeah what is learned what money is this is a credit card that's wiggly
yeah what this comes some kind of wet credit card credit card credit dollar on
- I know, come on, the money I get is wet.
- This is a credit card from the bottom of your shoe
that's crumpled up?
- It doesn't make any sense.
- All the money I get is so wet.
- A credit card with a spending limit of one dollar?
And I never have to pay it off?
You guys wanna see something cool?
- Yeah, check this out. - Yeah, what is it?
- Oh, the gas detector?
- Yeah.
- We're gonna play today?
- Let me put that up to my butt.
- Are we gonna play?
- Are we gonna play with this today?
- I mean, you tell me.
No, wait, I have to calibrate it first.
Let's do it quick. - We also have to...
- Oh yeah, we--
- We have to explain.
I mean, not everybody has seen the news, I'm sure.
- I've had a gas leak in my house
for maybe since I moved in.
And I--
- Which is over a year.
- So yesterday, so I bought this thing
'cause I was like, first of all, this is cool to have.
Also, I've been smelling gas.
Maybe there's something, maybe I have a gas leak.
Who knows?
- There's literally been, there's been so many instances
on the show where we've recorded here and been like,
there's like a gas leak or something.
Does that mean there's still gas?
- Put this on your penis.
Okay.
(loud buzzing)
Wow.
That's an alert, that's a red alert.
Did that feel good or what?
It felt, I know that my penis extrudes gas now.
Wrong word.
Expunges gas.
Expels gas.
Yeah.
Oh, that was pretty good.
Yes, I had a gas leak and I was,
I literally, I just, I turned this on for shits and giggles.
I was like, oh, it'd be funny if I had a gas leak,
started moving around my apartment and I was like I got near the oven and I was
and it like went up one bar and I was like oh that's all interest I was like
okay well that makes sense this is where gas comes out I'm sure there's some
residual gas around here and then I put it behind my oven and it hit the maximum
reading on the thing and I was like okay I'm fucking out of here so I love there's
that fucking the video you made with Joe and Alex you literally say there's a gas
There's a catholic in my oven.
Yeah, dude, God was telling me something I didn't even know.
But I, then I called National Grid, they came out,
and the two guys seemed like very non-plus, you know,
they do this shit, they do this all the time, right?
Yeah.
Until they got to my oven, and they put their meter,
which is more sensitive and has a higher cap than this one,
behind my oven, and the guy, who again, does this all day,
It's his only job is investigating these things.
He goes, "Holy fuck!"
(laughing)
- Dude, how, like, it makes so much shit make sense.
- Dude, I literally--
- I feel like we've lost the fifth member of the show.
- Dude, I literally have just spent like every,
the fifth member of the show.
- Yeah, Patches.
- Yeah, but he's not in these ones.
- Yeah, but he's the fourth member of the show.
- I'm kicking him out of the podcast.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Patches, we're starting here first.
- We heard it here first.
- Yeah, yeah.
I like just sit in my apartment all day for the last year just like, "Oh, how am I so
tired?"
And then I walk outside and I'm like, "I feel incredible.
Outside is amazing and my apartment makes me feel so sleepy."
And so I think it might have been a mixture of natural gas and carbon monoxide.
My brain hasn't been getting enough oxygen for close to a year now.
Maybe even longer.
I mean, truly, I don't know.
That's sick.
I mean, completely.
And they showed me the fucking-- you can look at the tube behind my oven.
Just a giant hole in the tube.
Just like a huge ass hole.
And it's just been spraying gas.
That's sick. Do you think maybe
your mice friends did that?
I maybe considered that, but then
I was like, a mouse doesn't like eat metal.
They do.
I don't think so. Every mouse eats metal.
I don't think a mouse can eat straight through a metal
post. Maybe it wasn't eating it, maybe it was
like grabbing onto it.
You know, and swinging on it
like parallel bars. It could be, yeah.
I don't think so, but you could be right.
That could be it though.
Yeah, he's having a little adventure back there.
He's trying to get ingredients to come back to his house.
It could be like a gremlin who did it too.
Like a gremlin with a grill.
They put a sticker out front of my apartment.
I don't know if you guys saw it on the way in.
It says, "Warning of hazardous conditions."
It's still hazardous.
It just says you can't, no, it's not still hazardous.
It just says that you can't--
Set it on fire.
Don't set my house on fire yet.
Right, 'cause--
But I do still have this.
It'll go on fire too good.
I guess it's good that you don't--
I'm gonna actually calibrate it and I'm gonna try to burp into it. I guess it's
good that you don't like smoke weed. I do smoke weed.
That's the window right next to the... Oh right yeah you've burned
incense. Also right next to the oven, that's the window that I
will smoke cigarettes out of sometimes. That's crazy. We got him. Caleb's
landlord if you're listening. Alright let's try this out. Okay.
[Laughter]
Holy shit.
It hit four bars on that.
There's only six bars on the thing.
[Laughter]
Clearly there's some...
That's crazy.
It's like a breathalyzer for farts.
super.
There's a residual.
Body
oh my God.
Burr
yeah, it's
pretty fun little is true. Yeah. I mean somebody has to fart into it. Yeah.
Yeah, let me know if anyone has to fart will will stop whatever we're talking
about and will the thing is like we should have worries you can't eat it's
raise your hand about like like yesterday I was like before record I'm
gonna eat like a fucking just a can of pinto beans cold or something but I
forgot to get him this morning damn yeah that would have been so funny I'll be
great because my birds are doing that it actually might catch on fire if I yeah
that thing's diabolical but yes now I'm recovering from my gas leak brain there's
There's so many times, literally, I think I've said the word "gas leak" in this apartment
probably 50 times.
Specifically in this apartment, yeah.
50 times in my life.
Do you guys feel different?
Do you feel different in here?
No.
A little bit.
Do you feel like you can take a deeper breath?
No.
I mean...
I feel completely normal.
Most of the time.
You're in every way.
Like sometimes there's like, I'll come here and I'm out of breath already because I like
skated over or like walked over.
Mm-hmm.
And honestly, it feels no different.
Yeah?
Still feeling out of breath?
Yeah.
I feel amazing, dude.
Yeah?
I feel incredible.
I don't know if it's just, I mean, it's definitely my brain pulling a trick on me, but it also,
I read that if there was trace amounts of carbon monoxide in there and I got poisoned,
it'll take 120 days for me to recover, for all my platelets to be replaced.
Holy shit.
They have been deoxygenated.
So you have about 120 more days before I even know who I am anymore.
Right.
Yeah, because of the effects of the gas leak.
It would be so funny if like 120 days later you like test into like Yale.
Well, I've been, dude, I've literally for the last year been saying, like I feel stupider
since moving here.
Like I feel noticeably stupider.
I barely have an attention span.
I can't like read a book for more than like 20 pages.
And that's crazy.
- Yeah, and I think it might be that I have had a gas leak
and that my brain has been, I've been neurotoxined.
Could be, yeah.
- Goddamn.
Well, I mean, I can imagine like,
we've probably got 60 days.
- I've also got a lot worse than,
I've been a lot worse at singing.
- Yeah.
- That makes sense.
- I think I've lost my key.
- Yes.
- He's at perfect pitch.
- Sing something.
- Gas makes singing so hard.
- What should I sing?
Just sing something.
You got the right temperature for shelter me you from the storm.
Oh I'm gonna gonna run around thinking turn you on.
Angola.
When I meet a papa you can be the mom.
Oh oh when you roll with a player like me with a brother like me there is no other.
A cloud like obscured the sun when you started singing.
See that's a sign dude.
My perfect pitch has been robbed.
God is turning his back on you.
Robbed for me.
I used to sing all kinds of cool songs.
Yeah.
I remember your ditties.
(laughing)
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ The troubles I've seen ♪
- That's pretty good.
- That's crazy.
- What, you think that's crazy?
- The cookie monster?
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- Can you sing "C" is for cookie real quick?
♪ C is for cookie ♪
♪ And cookie is for me ♪
- You sound just like him.
- That's crazy.
- Maybe that's the, maybe the gas is making--
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
- That's a real, that's a fun one.
- Maybe the gas is making you, you have a deep voice.
Wow. I think there might be a grumbling fire in my belly. It's spitting out.
Does it try to order like that at the deli? There is a house in New Orleans. Can I get two pounds of cheese?
They do mother eyes instead. And roses too. I see. We're gonna do the whole episode like this.
It hurts me. It's one of the most fun voices. It's so fun but it's just you
can't do it for more than 30 seconds. What are you talking about I could do it for
way more than 30 seconds. You're not rolling. I can do it way longer than that.
You need to be heard. It feels like there's a dust in my voice.
When I do it it feels like there's a natural baritone. I feel like I have a dust in me.
beautiful baritone. You do have a beautiful baritone. You do. Pull it out. Yes I do. Do a normal baritone.
And I have a beautiful alto. Yeah. Man we gotta... Can we we keep keep each other company?
Oh company. You don't have to call. Yeah that's right.
You need to sing something beautiful right now. I did. What'd you sing? This is the sing-along
episode. All right what should I sing? I gotta testify, come up in the spot
looking extra fly, till the day I die. That's a rap, that's not singing. I gotta testify, come up in the spot.
Twinkle, twinkle little star. This sucks. How I wonder what. See the gas leak's fixed guys. There's nothing weird in here anymore and we feel normal. Oh my god. I feel beautiful. I don't feel completely normal.
Oh yeah, see that's that's I'm glad that I immediately felt normal because if it if
I just felt the same I would have probably probably ended my own life.
Hmm yeah I probably would have gone over to that their gas valve.
I mean they claimed they teed off.
Concussion and gas leak.
Well it's not even back-to-back it's middle of yeah I got concussed.
My brain has been through the ringer you know and now Mac would like the ringer.
You know what I'm saying?
I know exactly what you're saying.
Because I'm athletic.
Right.
And I can do hurdles better than some people at least.
Yeah.
Crazy Brian Cox is in that movie as the evil uncle.
Yeah he's kind of a, it's like, was that after Rip Torn died?
Feels like he's just kind of doing Rip.
No, Rip Torn died like pretty recently.
It feels like he was just doing Rip Torn in that movie, right?
They kind of just couldn't get Rip.
Yeah, he was busy with dodgeball.
Yeah, so they got little Brian Cox.
Is Rip his full first name?
His name is, I think...
Is it Ripley?
It's not, no, it's a nickname, but it was his dad's nickname too.
So his dad was also Rip Torn, and he went by Rip Torn,
and then he had a brother who also went by Rip Torn.
That's not, that shouldn't be allowed.
I don't like names like that.
Army Hammer, Rip Torn, you know, just fucking, just get a normal...
Absolutely.
I want your first name and your last name should be complete opposites.
Whoa.
What if Torrin's real name was Elmore Ruall Torrin Jr.
Whoa that's cool as fuck.
Elmore.
Elmore Torrin?
That's a good name.
Yeah that was wasted.
Elmore is a better name.
Not even Elmer, Elmore.
I wish he would L less.
He didn't catch a single L his entire life dude.
Yeah exactly.
He had an ideal life.
Did dodgeball.
He should L less.
Except when he died.
That honestly has ruined so many lives.
his life for sure. Oh great life is my life's officially ruined I died. Oh crap
my life is over I'm dead. Great. Oh this is so embarrassing I just died at the mall
and all my friends saw it my life is over. I've also been here. I can never go
back to high school again. Only in this house I just have crazy dreams every
single night that then I wake up and I text you guys about sometimes. Mm-hmm. But
any anytime I sleep anywhere else I've had almost a perfect dreamless sleep
every time. I don't dream anymore really. If I do it feels very lucid and it scares me.
I would say dreaming is a byproduct of a gas leak. I hate dreaming. Me too man. It sucks.
I had a dream where I was in a dark realm the other day. It sucked. I woke up I was in a
dark realm version of my apartment. There's spirits everywhere. I had one eye. Couldn't
use my right arm. I was walking around I was like this is fucking fucked man. Dude I have
I dream. It's just always make me sleepwalk. I'll have I'll have dreams
where it's like I think I've definitely talked about this. I've had dreams where
I'm like landing skate tricks. That is cool though. And then I wake up and I'm
like I'll never I'll never be able to do that. I never have a dream that's like
aspirational. The only dreams I have nowadays that are like it's either like
stress nightmares or I'll have a dream where it's like my dream in my dream I'm
like I need to open the window shade and then I sit up and open the window shade.
horrible. You might have the burbiglia disease. What's that? Where he has he
sleepwalks and does crazy shit and he like jumped out of a window. I haven't
jumped out of a window yet. Well I think he hadn't done that either until he
jumped out of a window. I don't think I've done anything that would approach
that though. It's mostly opening the window shades and putting on pants. Those
are the two things I usually do. You never know man. You might have a window
dream pretty soon. Who knows I mean if if I who knows what I do after I put on
pants probably put on a shirt but after that it could be anyone's guess. You
should go the other way around. What other way around? Put the shirt on first
put the pants on last. I would if I was awake. I put my shirt on first. Yeah. I
always do. I always put the pants on first. I put the pants on first
usually. I go underwear. I go bottom. I usually put underwear on last. Yeah that's typically my rule. I'm totally
serious and then for me the first would have to be my hat. Mm-hmm. First hat. That
- It makes it really hard though.
- Then I put my shirt on and all my shirts have,
I use extra wide collars.
- Do you guys sleep in your chain?
- I sleep in my clothes.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I sleep wearing my chain and I wake up
and it'll be like, on my face or like--
- You ever wake up and you ever get caught on something
and it's choking you to death?
- It's gotten caught on my chest hair before.
- That's horrible. - I've had to yank it out, yeah.
- That sucks.
- Man, getting a chain was the best decision.
- Do you guys sleep with all-- - I look so sick.
all the with a popped bubble gum bubble on your face yeah a big
giant pop bubble bubble. Do you sleep with a feather on your nose?
Yeah sometimes. Yeah you go oh me me me me. It's just to make sure that Jana knows that I'm
breathing. Yeah. She gets worried sometimes. Do you guys use like nose and mouth and ear plugs?
Yeah yeah of course. I breathe I breathe through the you know that like a little bit of air.
Yeah. You get through your eyes. Do you guys usually let you guys usually fold up the Murphy
bed when you're sleeping in it? Yeah I let it fold up. I have a secret bed that folds out of my
my door. It's in my door and I fold myself back in. I really like being squished.
Yeah. I like the great Muppet caper when they all get stuck in the Murphy bed.
Yeah.
Ever since I saw that as a kid, I've always wanted to swing up into a Murphy bed.
Weren't you telling me that you got stuck in Murphy's bed?
I got stuck in Murphy's bed but not in a Murphy bed. Yeah, Murphy Browns.
Cool.
Yeah, I'm the-- I was one of Murphy Brown's boyfriends. I've never seen that show.
No. I thought Murphy Brown is what they call Frosty the Snowman.
That's-- that's in the spring. That's when he's made out of mud.
They call him Murphy Brown?
No. Oh, you're thinking of Parson Brown.
Parson Brown.
Yeah. Do you remember that guy, Parson Brown?
No, I don't remember him. I just told you. I thought-- first of all,
I thought he's a different guy. Second of all, I only know him from Frosty the Snowman, the song.
Isn't that Frosty the snowman? He's Parson Brown the snowman. And they call him Parson Brown.
And he can do the job when you're in town. He's Brown the snowman. Who do they call
Parson Brown? Is it Frosty? No, they build the snowman and then they pretend he's Parson Brown
and then he asks you if you're married and then you say no man and he says well you can do the
job when you're in town. No, you're right that's not Frosty. It's different. Frosty would never ask
that by the fire you'll have a sexual desire yeah you'll have a sexual desire
for Parson Brown right that makes sense to me he was like so crazy in the 70s
though Parson Brown he was honestly like he changed the game yeah yeah yeah well
there's like all those pictures of him at like studio 54 yeah shit yeah like
Elton John yeah yeah and they're like they're bringing you died in the hot tub
- yeah he died in the hot tub cuz he melted yeah he took all those drugs
really hot
heating up the spoon to put in your vein and then he was like oh my gloves on
fire so he jumped in the hot tub yeah what a tragic loss yeah dude I did yeah
but then they had that tribute show to him or like Prince play I was just gonna
I say Prince. Yeah, we're really close right. It's played like while my guitar
gently a lot of a lot of people got kind of mad. They thought that Prince was the
one to kind of like put them on all that shit. Prince used to be like yo try
that try the fire pill like the fire. You know it's like a little ball of fire and
person was like super green like he was literally from the ground. Yeah, like he
did not know what was going on really actually. He also didn't speak any
English like kind of because he was never in school. Well he spoke. I mean he
speaks the sentences that are in the song. If you learn those from like a phrase book.
He can say, "Are you married?" and that was about it. It's like guys who like
Mexican coaches speak, "Do you know where the bathroom is?"
Really? He'd say, "Are you married?" and they'd say, "No man."
And he'd say, "We can do the job in the bathroom."
"Kay?" He'd say that a bunch. He didn't understand what they were saying back then.
He knew one Spanish word and one phrase in English.
And all the rest was in Snowy's.
Yeah, which almost nobody speaks anymore.
Right, except Santa and his elves.
Yeah, you say like ho ho ho, there's like a million different things that could mean.
Exactly.
It's like aloha.
Yeah, exactly.
Aloha can mean almost anything.
It can mean get out of my house.
Get out of my house, you're touching all my shit.
Stop touching all my shit, get out of my damn house.
Exactly.
And that's why they say aloha.
Aloha is, yeah, it can mean...
Maybe the gas is still on.
It can mean like, I'm gonna surf this big wave, I'm gonna sit down and watch you surf this big wave,
I'm gonna sit down and I'll watch TV, I'm gonna sit down and turn the TV off, I'm gonna stand up
and watch TV, I'm going down to the beach to watch you surf this big wave, I'm gonna sit at the beach,
I'm going on the beach, I'm going home from the beach to watch TV, I mean there's just like a
million meanings. I mean what's the deal with these Hawaiians though? I know. Hey Pat, you want to weigh
- I'm not weighing on this one.
- Not again.
- I want a rating from one to 10
(laughing)
on what you think of Hawaii
and the people that live there indigenously.
- I think that--
- Indigenously.
(laughing)
- I just wanna make sure it's clear
what Pat's talking about.
- I'm just chilling, honestly.
I'm like doing so much in my life right now.
- Blow the vape smoke--
- Oh, that's smart.
- Oh yeah, let's see that.
- Blow the vape smoke into the gas detector.
- I gotta calibrate it, hold on.
(laughing)
I love that it makes like a fallout.
It sounds like the mousetrap timer.
I don't know that.
I think it's a cool, I've used it so much it's already saying low battery.
Just put batteries in it.
Maybe the warning for the gas was just...
Alright, I'm going to do it.
Okay.
Wait, hold on, I've got to calibrate it more.
This thing loves being calibrated.
Whoa.
Okay, let's try it.
Alright.
Let's see if this vape is made of gas.
Oh my God, the smoke's coming out the tube. I I breathe that in every four
minutes. That's pretty good. Yeah, that's pretty good. It's pretty good
smoke though, like the vapes the vapor is just coming out of like every
couldn't even handle it. It looked like it was on fire. I think I need more
devices that can detect dude detecting absolutely the vice. I think I might get
needed detection. I mean it like I kind of want to get a metal detector. Metal
detector is not, yeah. I was just going to say. How we never talked about metal
detecting before? I had a metal detector when I was a kid. It's so cool. Yeah. I
got one for my birthday or for Christmas or something. I would just do it in like
my backyard. It's just like, oh, yeah. Well, there's a, I should have taken you
guys here. There's an island. There's an island in North Carolina called Topsal
beach which is apparently where Blackbeard buried his shit.
That's cool.
Yeah, so there's like...
Yeah.
I mean, that's like his last recorded place was Topsail Beach.
I mean, this guy's also a pirate, so he might have been fucking lying.
Yeah.
You know, he might have went to Las Vegas.
But yeah.
You gotta gamble me winnings.
There's a bunch of shipwrecks and shit around there.
When I had my metal detector as a kid, I was like hanging out with one of my friends and
I like he's wearing like a baseball cap and I was like I was holding it
because you know they had the little metal thing like at the top of it and I
would hold the I like held the detector over his head and like it would like go
like beep beep beep and I'm like dude you have to go to the doctor like there's
yeah I would love like honestly I feel like there is a 20% chance I will find
treasure in my life hmm like I feel like I have a pretty good luck with stuff
like that. And I feel like I have a true cosmic feeling that I will find a bunch of gold bars
or something. That would be cool. I actually thought this so earnestly, again, gas leak
in my home for a long time, that about a month ago I googled how many gold bars would make
me a millionaire. I was like, I should shoot to find that many gold bars. How many was
it? Sixteen. Only sixteen? Depends on the size though. If it was the big ones, it would
only be five. That makes sense. Yeah. Well, there's big ones that are like 200 gram or
something yeah and those are the those are those ones you'd only need probably
five to be a millionaire I think they're the ones that are a thousand gram you'd
only need one yeah it would be just so I'm such a bitch to carry that not for
me strength yeah I'd probably just walk around with them I'd probably not I'd
probably forget there were you on me well it's like yeah it's like this I
think I in your pocket I would like to buy this restaurant that's what I would
do are on the counter what I would do that if I had gold bars I like found
gold bars I definitely wouldn't sell them yeah I would have people like I
I would even put them in the bank.
I'd just, I'd carry around a little like potato peeler and I'd shave off little pieces of gold
to give to people instead of money, you know.
Because if it's $250,000 for the entire bar, then that means there's $250,000 valued little
shavings that I can give people that make up the bar, you know.
And who cares if it's exact, you know.
I'm a gold, I'm a goldenare.
A goldenare.
I don't care anymore.
Yeah.
I'm a goldenare.
like a cookie cutter type thing that just like presses out coins off you know it
stink what you did that would stink pretty bad
it would seem to be on a treasure hunt and you finally get the big hit you
fucking dig down 10 feet or ever spent all day doing that maybe even takes two
days then you you open up the you find a chest you're like this is I've struck
gold you say that out loud I've struck gold you open it up silver that'd be
fine for me I like silver mm-hmm it's not worth as I probably find that where
I probably found diamonds though in my scenario I've done a platinum together
I'd find out a first try I found the dragon's horde so it's like diamonds
aren't worth a single thing in this story that you told I already had found
the dragon's horde with treasure a gore so the dragon's horde was found like
forever go as some soviet by me no yes i you it was by me i have it
in my treasure box
but i think that uh...
again
as awesome
disregard when does so cool as we are going on i'll uh... i still love
gargling
that
you know it's not going to let's say it is a blown bubbles in the drinks
you know i don't know what you know
yet you know when the milk about your nose
i was that's when you know you let him
I forget you laughing when you spit out that food. Forget who I was with, but I
thought it was really funny to blow bubbles into a gin and tonic.
When you're sitting across from them, when you shoot the boogers in the tissue, you
know you're sneezing.
Mm-hmm. What's the funniest food to do a spit take with?
Probably a bunch of ham. Yeah, something with bones in it. Yeah.
Yeah, bone or maybe just bones. Bones. Yeah. Maybe a fish skeleton.
Ribs. Yeah, ribs would be perfect. Or you put a whole fish in your mouth and
and then you shoot out the entire
hit you need in the face or a bunch of
chili like an entire crock pot of
chili. I guess you don't spit take food.
Usually it's usually some kind of liquid. Yeah, funny as
liquid would be like that's why it's fun. That's
why it's funny. True to be
for it to be food. Yeah,
I guess you're yeah, but
most people don't laugh that hard that they need to spit
their food out or like
if it may be just like a single
like like concentrated stream of
of boiling hot oil.
Yeah, that melts anything in its path. Yeah, man, rose of acid magma will be
Whole right there. So that'll be funny or a laser beam. Yeah, that'd be pretty funny
Yeah, if you're eating a laser beam and yeah, I mean we're just going for laughs. Oh, yeah, let's see a dozen eggs
Yeah, that'd be funny ping-pong balls. I might also be funny. Yeah toilet paper
What else would be funny? Maybe a Ruben? Oh, hold up. Hold up popcorn or um a
shoot out you eat like a bunch of watermelon and all the seeds yeah like
ball bearings maybe ball bearing could be banana peels or fake vomit or maybe
Chinese finger trap that would be cushion shoot up gumball but because
when you spit take it comes out as a bubble
bubble bubble like bubble mixture maybe a whole cup you ever tried a flag in you
ever as a kid drink bubbles and then try to burp out bubbles like this like I
didn't live in in the whatever candy land you grew up in where you thought
you see that you see that in a movie or in a cartoon like kids are like I you
You know what I did when I looked at cartoons?
Like the bubble, the stuff you make bubbles with.
Yeah, I didn't do that.
Yeah, well I guess I was a very smart kid.
I guess I was a very impressionable kid.
Well you looked at-
You probably also drank a poison potion based on movies.
Yeah.
You ever eat an apple and get so sick that you fall into a coma until you become kissed?
I did that all the time because I saw it on a cartoon.
I would like told you guys like two days ago. I smoke weed when I was nine.
That's true. I saw them in Woodstock. Yeah. I basically like eat a hot pepper and run
around turn red and shoot steam out and run around and bounce around out
everywhere so. It was mad embarrassing when I was a kid. Yeah no I was like so
strange. I like ate a piano and the keys were my teeth too. It was like I felt like
weird doing that but it was like fun. Remember when Nancy Reagan tried to get the Looney Tunes
taken off a TV because they were a bad influence on. You're thinking of Marge Simpson.
I remember that, I was like two years old when they said that.
So many kids are painting streets on the...
I wasn't alive for the Reagan administration, motherfucker.
You weren't alive for when Nancy Reagan was saying that too many kids were walking off
a cliff and standing there for a minute looking down and then realizing that they were going
to fall and that's when they fell?
Wait, are you thinking of cartoon logic?
God, I love it.
No, wait, no, no, you're thinking of Tibber Gore.
Huh?
You're thinking of Tibber Gore.
I'm going to put my tip in you until you're gored.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Checkmate.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
- That, that fuckin'.
- That burn was epic?
Yeah, you're right.
- That was a good burn, honestly.
- Yeah, thank you.
I think I might post that.
- Was that trial?
When she put Twisted Sister on trial?
- Did they put Twisted Metal on trial?
- Yeah.
- Time trial, to see how fast I can go around the track.
- This is making kids go too much, too fast.
And they're too mean when they drive.
- These kids are trying to turn their arms into wheels.
- Yeah, great, awesome, cool.
- Okay, this kid's got a flaming clown mask.
- Okay, great.
- Yeah. - Awesome.
- What is he, some kind of evil clown now?
- Great, this kid's granting wishes.
- Oh. - This kid's holding
a tournament to grant ultimate wishes.
- Okay, this kid wants-- - Is that what we want?
- Yes! - Yes!
- So, ultimate wish? - Calypso.
- You don't want an ultimate wish?
What is your deal?
- Every video game is about an ultimate wish.
- There's not a catch. - Everything where someone
fights someone else is about an ultimate wish.
- Right, like "Coggedy Modern Warfare 2"
is the wish to destabilize Iraq.
exactly
yet talk that shit yet
political and what else i don't know what else what else politically and call of
war called duty call of war is about
i wish hitler was dead that's the first one
well damn you know that's a thing
yeah and that's i like i think i think we said it's a little there on hitler
yeah
he really did he went there
i'd be snatched away i would be on the other hand i think all their thing to
I know you guys are friends with him, but I'm not.
I don't fuck with him anymore.
I do not fuck with him.
Yeah, no, he was like weird at one time.
Yeah.
I found out he was like weird to women.
I don't like him.
And I mean a lot of other people too.
Nah, I only heard about women.
Yeah, Hitler was like mad weird to Jewish people.
He was just like weird, you know?
It was like clear to the--
He was just like, yeah, just misbehaving.
He was just like, I don't--
He just like--
And he was racist.
I heard honestly just like some real out of pocket shit.
He's just putting out weird vibes too.
When I last I was with him, he was just like...
Plus he would always be like, "Yo, check out my music,
check out my music."
Yeah, he would corner people and talk about his music.
Yeah, and it's like, "Dude, IBM is over."
Like, you don't know he's making IBM anymore.
Nobody has a fucking cassette player either.
Like he's like trying to sell cassettes to people
for like $20.
He loves Apex Twin.
Yeah, no, it's like, "Get over it."
Yeah.
It's like, "Dude, you're not gonna be..."
You're not gonna be the next James Murphy.
Exactly, dude.
Yeah, and I know that you guys are already friends like Barry like you burial like you're just ripping off burial
Absolutely, like yeah, this complete just garage rip. Yeah, you're not even from like the UK. This is feels just weird
You know, yeah, and what he did since like bad - it's going
Just killing he was a killer plus. He's a killer. He crushed on stage. I'll say that much
absolute killer
He used to do I always said do open mics, bro
Yeah
And then he would go and he crushed you to kill and I'd be like, dude
you come back next week?" He's like, "No, I just wanted to make sure. I just wanted to
like prove to myself I could do it." Yeah, you know. Yeah, it's like dude, just like
have some fucking like, have some dedication or something. Yeah, I know you're not busy.
Yeah, like you like already made it. Like you have rich parents, you know. Yeah.
Just fucking, just do it. Yeah. A lot of people think he didn't go to art school. He did.
He did and he was like pretty good, you know. I've actually never seen Hitler's
paintings were they any good? No. Not really. They're boring. They're just like... All paintings
are boring. No. Paintings suck. I'll show you. Paintings are stupid. They're just like
houses and landscapes and stuff. Arts suck. Here look, this is his paintings. That's pretty
cool. I mean they're just boring. They're pretty good I think. They're pretty dumb.
I think he's... They're pretty dumb actually. He's decent. I think they're all crap. I mean
better than me yeah dude I can really tell what I might do there might be
trouble just like poorly drawn like circles yeah come on let me into
I'd like to do art school here.
Yeah, that's why art school is easy to get into now.
It's all bullshit because it used to be something but then they turned down Hitler and look
what happened.
They said we're going to change our ways.
Yeah.
All right, the list for today.
Before we go any further, we seriously hate Hitler.
I just want to clarify.
Why are you rubbing my foot with your foot?
This is a secret message.
Oh, okay.
Oh, now both of you are doing it.
Keep talking about how much you ate Hitler.
Not gonna lie, it feels so good that I couldn't think.
I did not like that.
It's not as, you of all of my male friends I find the least repulsive to touch.
Why?
That's for us to figure out later.
Shit, I guess you're right.
Top 10 things your parents don't want you to know by Finch.
alive has or at one time had parents. Chances are that when they had their kids
their lives changes forever. Probably not for the better. Sure they tell you they
love you and that you were an angel or a blessing but in reality the first words
out of their mouths when you were born were probably a little different. Below
are the top 10 things that your parents don't want you to know. Either about you,
your siblings, or life in general. Yeah now I can't see it so like great thanks
so much. I can see it, I have a front row seat. You see this? No. That's my middle finger.
my penis that's what I got it's putting his it's not your penis then suck it
then if it's not my pocket I dare you did not prove it was my penis
because you didn't suck it.
(laughter)
What do you mean? I just don't know how.
I never did it before. Is that not right?
Dude, the gas leak is gone
and we've become so sexual.
Oh my god.
This is insane.
Number one, your parents
have sex when you aren't around.
No! Whether you're asleep staying at
a friend's house or just down the street at the store for
30 minutes, your parents have
utilized that opportunity to have sex.
they send you out on an errand or say that yes you can stay at your friend's
house for the night know that they are at least considering what to do with
their privacy I'm freaking I don't think so I'm ready to throw up I don't think
my I think it's really I think my parents are not having sex yeah they're
worse probably 15 years yeah I think it's pretty unlikely that they're doing
that when I'm not home yeah I think that I they're not even trying to keep it
from me anyway yeah the fact that they don't have sex yeah I think they tell
tell you that yeah they I mean pretty every time I see my dad he's like I'm
not having sex with your mom anymore yeah I say okay they say right I just be an
act though me either dude I wanted it at the table every month and you're just
like just to let you know like we're not having sex yeah that's nice it's a nice
reminder so you guys ever walked in on your parents fucking no no no my parents
don't they do Patrick has eight brothers and sisters I have some drawings that
prove your parents have sex but you drew my dad and my mom having sex yeah your
dad is like it's a beautiful like rendition of your dad it looks like the
one from the Titanic and then your mom's just like his like big beefy cock and
and then it's just like just a stick figure that says an arrow that says
bat's mom.
Or four says I hear them almost twice a week when I'm asleep. They think I
don't know they think I'm an innocent person.
Whoa,
that's a serial killer.
They know those horny those horny parents created a villain. Yeah, that's
a super villain or you know, I fucking hate dude. Did you ever know anybody
growing up maybe you guys have parents like this but like did you ever go to
someone's house or something and their dad says their mom like he's like I love
the love the meal hun can't wait to eat your pussy later like shit like that
people like that who were like just we they're like yeah they're like I'm gonna
give you my thanks for this dinner I feel like Patrick is maybe the first
person I've ever been friends with whose parents are like don't seem like they
hate each other yeah I like just being in the same room as each other yeah it's a
yeah most parents don't like each other very much yeah I think I think having
kids my parents like to hang out yeah did your dad ever do this like Homer
like I know but talking about like the sexual parents the sexual parents your
mom ever go homie? Homie? Does your mom ever do that? Homie. Homie. Homie. Homie. Homie.
Homie. Hello homie. Homie. It's cool that he heard a Disney game. I had a thing about
the sexual parents and then I forgot it. Yeah. Anyway. I knew somebody who had his parents
still you guys know this guy. His parents. Oh yeah. His parents. Say it, mouth it again.
Noah. His parents are disgusting to each other. It's freaky, I don't like being around it.
It's like if you're 50 you shouldn't be in love. At least not publicly. That's what you
guys think my parents are happily married I don't care if they're happily married
not about being just don't show me they're being like they're being whores
to each other yeah no that's just weird thing they're schmoozing up on each
other they're sliming all over each other like slugs until you if you until
you hit if you're like 80 years old it's sweet if you're like if you're like
cute yeah that's adorable yeah if you see a really old car really old the old man
is like horny as hell he's like I'm addicted to your sliz cool mashed
potatoes were great hun they're almost as good as your pussy yeah that's good
dude that is great quit like a rhino horn honey I can't wait to brush my teeth
with it that's really good that's adorable
know the couple and up yeah yeah and they were using balloons yeah yeah talk about
using a rubber rubber balloon okay on his kid dick yeah blow it up and then let it
kind of like reverse yeah kind of explode yeah on it like when you make a
phone case with it sure oh dude hmm yeah yeah who do you think blew up all the
balloons is her yeah and then she did all by the way tragically yeah she used up
all her breath.
Yeah, she's got every every breath.
She's like, oh, don't tell you about the wisp of her soul, leaving her body as
she blows up the last balloon.
Keep fucking blowing the balloons, you bitch.
I'm in love with you.
Yeah, and then yeah, she died and you had to get a little like a little slave
boy with strong vitality and millions of breaths left.
Yeah, he had so many bros tell you give that you only have a start. I know a
little boy. That's what he said. That was what deleted scene start blowing
little boy. Yeah, yeah, start. I need you to fill my sack very low Dutch angle of
him hands on his hips. He had giant blowing boy.
He had giant mystical sacks filled with breath that he stole from people.
That's why they were trying to knock down his house. He was he was he's a
serial killer. He was stealing everyone's breath away and I don't mean
that he was handsome but it was handsome why do you think you had to flee new
york city
yeah
exactly charge
strew
yes uh...
stance for urban predator
that's a new york yeah do you don't see the little tiny periods between the
other day and he's a he was a much more dangerous urban predator than the one
in predator to uh... yeah
as a mission called predator to urban predator
that's what the what the movie is
uh... yeah there is a well like what if instead of the jungle we do it in l_a_
the man is a that is kind of clinton's in the movie is cool
therefore movie i've seen any of the only predator movie of seeing is the one
that came in a couple years ago
you know i was so bad
resis get the i watch it i want to know if the reader yeah watching the every
different
sitting or a movie horrible movie as would go and i watch thirty minutes
really
no that's predators ok that one's for you know it's ok it's pretty good
yeah i couldn't have a lot of that was directed by a guy named nimrod
well now yeah nimrod himrod
there is not a lot of street
uh... in number two of him right here parents considered abortion at least
once a set of having you not true i don't think that that i was a little way
too quick
i would say my parents
I would say my dad definitely did.
Me and my older brother are 13 months apart.
So you think they just didn't even have time to think about aborting you?
I think I got in mad quick.
You knew that there was not a lot of room for error to pull this off.
So you got in, got out.
That was a big heist.
So here's some comments.
Oh gosh, I hope not.
I'm the only one that isn't spaced out.
I would call you pretty spaced out.
- What?
What are we talking about?
- So my sister is four years older than me,
my brother is a year older than me,
and then my little brother's two years older than me.
Or two years younger than me.
- Your little brother's two years older?
I think you're pretty spaced out.
Hey.
- Hey.
- My mom tried to have me aborted,
but she keeps denying it.
Here's a comment.
I have Asperger's, autistic,
and sometimes my mom wanted to know why I had to be born.
well that's very racist and offensive
that's a
so very nice
uh... mom number three other kids are smarter kinder and better looking than
you not true yeah
son
that's a lot of handsome boy
come on son let's be real silly hot kids over there
you're not really a little like why can't you look like a g dress like them
are dressed in the gap
i think this is funny because this person messed up the joke here
me feel english that's impossible
what's that you know the words like me feel english that's on possible
uh... we have no but they were impossible which is this correct his
layout this guy i was just too smart is that maybe this actually means that
there's a point here
uh...
me very good at me grammar yes
yeah i feel inferior to other sometimes
I felt so... I was number one when I was a kid, bro.
Yeah, I was probably the number one person I ever met.
You're the second child, right? Yeah, I'm the middle, dude.
That's why I'm so beast. They say I'm the middle child, but I'm the third.
Middle child is a state of mind and you definitely are a middle child.
I would say you're a little child. Yeah.
Well, I'm the tallest one in my family, bitch. What's up?
That's so embarrassing for you to know. I'm 5'9".
my dad so tall and then the rest of us are like like my little brother's five
seven
how close your dad
slick six one so you're not the tallest in your family the tolls boy
your dad is a boy now
you can check on my drawings was a man
yeah and
uh... here's a comment this was really sad
they always would say you are the most beautiful kid in the world but that is
not true and that's from mickey mouse
are you still so far for a quote says that i think mickey got his his
kind of every every need i know you and i mean you look at anything that was
successful guy
yet his problems to why do you think he he's like
open up all these theme parks and shit
yeah all three of the kids who don't feel
love by their parents like they're on a sailboat by himself
as we're going to why do you think he's doing all this shit
use the looking for his parents love one validation yeah yeah
mister mouse and mommy mouse never never they never loved him
Yeah, they didn't.
It's true.
Number four, your opportunities in life are limited.
Not true.
The sky's the limit for me.
My mom told me this.
I pretty much have an unlimited potential.
Watch this.
You guys want to see me become a superstar?
Yes.
I already did.
Hold your breath.
Hit me baby one more time.
Hit me baby one more time, that fucking sound, down in the fan, as I was a, just believe,
give me a sign, hit me baby one more time, wow.
I'm gonna have to hold my breath for that.
When's it gonna happen?
I've already became one.
I think I became one so hard. Don't mind the paparazzos when you walk out of my door
Yeah, yeah, they're there every second
This man has not registered with the
Come on make way make way for my client. It's just me. Come on. He's coming out any minute now
I'm gonna grab that camera. That's a gun
I'm done.
Any good comments here?
Everything depends on money these days.
So true.
This one comment that says, "What I know when I was four."
What I know when I was four.
Yo, what I know when I was four.
So now the list takes a turn here.
Those are making me laugh.
Number five is, "Rated R movies are realistic."
True.
We're just talking about Predator.
Facts.
As realistic as hell.
This could happen.
Some alien fucker.
Yeah.
alien right now. What's another Raider movie that's realistic? I mean Matrix is probably
one of the most realistic movies of all time. VR basically stands for realistic when it
comes to these movies. Matrix Reloaded, Matrix Realistic, think about that. And STG stands
for like pre-graphic. Probably G. G movies are pretty much never realistic. They're never
-Gross, yeah. Basically stands for, G basically stands for gross.
-Lester's lucky day.
-Greatly distorted from reality.
-Yeah.
-Fobo.
-Elmo and Grouchland.
-Phoebe's friendly fun day. Didn't happen.
-Is it Elmo and Grouchland, G or PG?
-PG 13 is probably just happened 13 times.
-Yeah, ever. Yeah, probably around, they average it out. Probably just 13.
-NC 17, no chance this happened 17 times.
Yeah, either more or less, but not 17 17 no chance
I would say in 17 movies might be the most realistic true because a lot of times
It's just like some French girl showing up at a French guy's house, and then they put fucking fuck yeah fucking like the brown bunny
Yeah
On each other they do that mm-hmm. Yeah, can they put all sorts of plugs on each other? Oh my god?
Yeah, that's right. I patches - oh
No, yeah, the pig leg on it. Oh, you don't want to see the peg leg a peg leg on yeah
Oh, no, he put the peg leg on all what you but they're wearing clothes. Mm-hmm. Yeah, wait till you see the movie. They're not oh
Yeah, that's right. No
See an NC 17 movie. No, I don't normally normal. There's nothing going on in it. Yeah
Except for all the fun. Yeah, it's since we're not crazy except for the 17 crazy things that happen
yeah not crazy unless you think 17 assholes on the screen at the same time
are crazy because of mine we should we should watch a nc-17 movie count how
many times so I've seen what's that one movie nympho maniac nympho maniac that's
what I was your first nc-17 movie nympho maniac was the only one I've ever
watched I've seen Caligula what is nc-17 like what movies are nc-17 I've never
gone to the theater to see one dog I think I've seen man bites dog
I think yes, I've ever seen that one um oh
Bad lieutenant that was my first one. I'm on the road plans pretty scary. Yeah, what that the 90s?
Bad lieutenant oh yeah
Yeah, he smokes crack and like shows his full dick on the screen who directed that again. I think it's able Ferrara
Could be wrong. I don't know I accidentally searched NC7 movies
No children under seven can watch this movie. Yeah, that's like did you guys ever play an adult only game? Yeah, which one?
TurboTax
What was the one about the pervert
Leisure suit Larry. I think there was a leisure suit Larry. That was a oh evil dead was NC 17. Yeah, that's him
Yeah, yeah, I know I see evil was a I say a little bit the first one
I assume NC-17 was just porn, but I get like Eyes Wide Shut is NC-17. Yeah. Oh, really? Yeah, it's usually movies American Pie
What that's what it says here. No, maybe they're a good addition. Yeah. Yeah, dude unrated
My god Freddy got fingered. It says here what?
Yeah, this is the fucking poster for bad. I guess it Harvey. I tell you just have Harvey Keitel's like that
- There's no way that was the 90s.
- 92.
- Really?
- 92 Abel Ferrara.
- He looks so young.
- Well yeah, I think it was before Reservoir Dogs,
or at least after, maybe.
- It was before, or at least after.
- Could have been one of the two.
- At least it was before or after.
Definitely not at the exact same second.
- Well, I think Reservoir Dogs did come out in '92.
- Before or at least after.
- Hold on.
- Not even before or after, before or at least after.
- Or at least after, to be at the very least.
No, no, Reservoir Dogs came out in '92.
It was really- Reservoir Dogs was before, but only a month before.
Or at least after.
Or at least it was after it.
Well no, Battle of the Tennant was at least after.
Okay.
Yeah.
So wait, that's even funnier!
You're saying, "Resident Dogs- Reservoir Dogs was before."
You're not even making sense.
"Reservoir Dogs was before, or at least the other one was after."
Yeah.
That's what you were actually saying.
Just admit you just got headshotted from across a map 360 no-scope.
Just fucking admit it oh
oh
I got that in a DVD combo pack when I was when I was 12 the the only yeah
I think the only in AT-17 movies for a very long time were just ones with with you could put a cock in there
Yeah, yeah, that's yeah
Now I'll show some big heaters to noodle noodle cock 17 chunky ones, bro. Yeah
He smoked he smokes a bunch of crack in that movie. Yeah. Yeah, he's a badly
He's the fucking worst. Brother Hank, the good lieutenant. Hey some of those lieutenants walking around. I mean nowadays
He might be one of the good ones. True. That's what I'm saying. Some of the stuff that's going down in lieutenant
Well, here's the thing. This might get you on his side. He loves gambling
Yeah, let me watch a movie, let me please
All right, number six they love your sibling more than you. Not true. I'm the favorite child
I'm the favorite too because my mom lets me drunk drive her around. Yep
My mom I don't know how to drive, but that's the gauge for
Favorite child my mom and my mom one time. Let me do that and I was like I'm definitely the favorite
She would never trust my brothers with this task. Yeah drunk driving dude. That's like
That's a seer. That's like a fucking that's like a family heirloom passed down in my family. Yeah, that's like me getting a ring you know
True might be I might be the the favorite
Maybe be the favorite boy your parents don't know the answers to many of your questions. That's true as hell. Do you guys?
I realize this growing up my my dad my mom anytime you ask her anything
She has an answer and it's almost always wrong
She'll say some parents do like they won't they don't want to say I don't know they'll just say something my dad though
Would just he doesn't know any both of my parents would say I don't know and then tell me to fuck off
My mom will just make something. Well, I mean your questions are probably deserved. Yeah
It probably wasn't like why is the sky it was like yeah, like what? Yeah. Why is the Death Star so big?
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know what the Death Star. Yes
Please leave me alone. It's 3 a.m
It's 3 a.m. On Christmas Eve
There is one time I think I was showing I was watching Revenge of the Sith and thought my dad was watching it with me
but he was asleep the whole time.
And I kept turning to him to ask him stuff
and didn't realize he was asleep
until my uncle came in the room and like laughed at me.
- You thought your dad was just icing you out?
- Yeah.
- Damn.
- Well, and you thought he was answering
all your questions like this?
- And you thought, I'm gonna still do,
I'm gonna still.
- You were like, dad, what does the Wookiee language
sound like?
And you're like, not really, but thank you for trying.
I appreciate it.
Remember, Ed, you ever been to Kashyyyk?
their health isn't as good as they lead you to believe.
True, they're all dead.
That is scary to think about.
Not for me.
Especially now that my parents are getting older.
We can potentially die from anything.
My Asian parents.
Fact.
Well yeah, we could die from this person's Asian parents.
My Asian parents said the same thing.
Yeah.
And they're crazy.
Number nine, your parents hate driving.
Fact.
I don't think that's a secret.
My dad loved driving.
I think one of the things of parents is they do tell you
that they hate driving.
My dad loved driving so much because he would,
My dad would always, until maybe a couple years ago, I think his girlfriend got him to stop,
he would read a John Grisham novel while he drove.
He would literally just hold it in front of him, like one hand on the wheel, one hand
on his Diet Coke, one hand on the wheel, holding with his thumb and his pointer finger a John
Grisham novel.
I would probably do that.
If I drove, I would probably be reading and driving at the same time.
And just hit into audiobooks.
Well, it's different.
Audiobooks suck.
It's different.
Audiobooks are not very good.
No, they're good, but...
Listen, my dad's being gripped by John Grisham spy novels,
some of the most intense, well-written things
in the history of literature.
So he's not gonna let,
I mean, who's gonna read that shit, right?
Who's gonna do that justice?
- All right, number 10, last one.
Your parents get scared too.
You ever seen your parents get scared?
You ever scared your parents so hard?
- No, I think my mom,
I remember my mom,
I would always, I mean, this doesn't really count too much.
this isn't like terrified or whatever,
but I would always do a joke when I got really tall,
if we went into a room with a low ceiling,
I would turn on my mom and be like,
like, "Mom, look how high I can jump,"
and go like I was about to jump my head
right into the ceiling at full speed,
and she would always freak out every time.
- You know what?
Okay, the one time I saw my mom really--
- Or under a ceiling fan, it's a good joke.
- The one time I saw my mom really scared
is also why I'm the favorite.
I think I've told this before,
but my brother basically, we took a two by four
and we sawed it almost all the way through
and then he broke it on the back of my head
and then it was a big prank and my mom,
she thought I was dead or something for a moment.
And then my dad is like me, he gets scared by loud noises.
- Nice. - Yeah.
That's why he used to live downtown and then he moved
'cause he was like,
ambulances damn scare me too in the morning.
- I saw my dad one time,
This is like the weirdest, this is a very, I think,
life-changing moment.
Saw my dad get scared of a frog that was in a shop vac.
He knew that there was a frog in it
and then made me empty the shop vac
because he didn't want the frog to jump on him.
- Whoa, that's serious.
Oh yeah, my mom's really scared of bees too.
Which I don't fuck with bees all that much either.
- Like my dad's not like a scaredy cat at all.
Yeah, now I think about it, both my parents are just fucking pussies, dude.
Scared of everything.
My dad's scared of loud noise, my mom's scared of bugs, dude.
The two things that I'm most afraid of.
My dad's not a pussy, but my mom is afraid of fucking every--
Like, my mom, if there's a tornado warning in, like, Rochester or somewhere,
she'll send me, like, "I found out that there's a tornado warning in New York City.
You need to get inside!"
She thinks it's gonna be, like, day after tomorrow.
Just, like, giant tornado, billboards fucking smacking--
That'd be sick.
news anchors. Dude, I hope honestly, we'll leave it at this. I mean, I don't know if you guys agree,
but I do hope by the end of my lifetime I see one movie level apocalypse climate disaster.
Absolutely.
Wouldn't that be so sad?
Well, we're gonna.
All right. Subscribe to the Patreon. Sullivan Quest Part 2. Just came out for the $10 tier
patches. Worked really hard on it. It's really sick. So subscribe and give it a listen. We
- We unlocked the first part of it too.
- Pray for Microscene.
He has a disease.
- Bye.