Hey guys, it's Cameron.
So Patrick and Caleb are away this weekend and I guess that means that it's time for
me to do a solo episode.
And I wasn't really sure what to do with this.
I was thinking about it a lot and then I realized that I actually had some old stuff recorded
that I might be able to put out now.
During 2021, I actually was keeping kind of an audio diary where I would record an audio
entry of what I did that day every few days.
And I got a good amount of those lined up and kept in a folder on my computer.
So I thought maybe now that the oppression of Patrick and Caleb is gone from my life
for a short period of time, I could just put some of those out and who knows if they'll
even be interesting.
But anyway, here it goes.
Cameron's Diary.
January 1st.
Wow.
A brand new year.
fresh new blank parchment for me to scrawl my beautiful life upon.
The entirety of 2021 is before me and I for one could not be happier.
2020 was a bit weird as I'm sure that you are aware but I'm ready to take control and
make 2021 the best year ever.
But to do that, I'm going to have to make some beautiful New Year's resolutions, and I think
that my very first resolution will be to start an audio diary.
Look at that.
Number one, done.
Perfect.
This is really easy.
Number two resolution is going to be a little bit harder for me to achieve.
Resolution number two is stop declaring war on people.
I need to learn to deal with my feelings in a mature way, and if I'm angry at the cashier
at the store or my mailman or a member of my family, I need to stop writing declarations
of war and presenting them to them and telling them that I'm going to destroy them.
Resolution #3, which is one that I failed in 2020 and am thus trying again in 2021, is
to keep it real.
And Resolution #4, my fourth and final resolution, will be to live my life to the fullest.
I'm going to take as many vacations as I can, I'm going to eat as much delicious food as
I can, and I am not going to let anything stop me from enjoying my life and living dangerously
like an action movie star.
January 6th.
Well, it seems like my resolutions aren't going well because my first vacation was a complete
bust.
I took the absolute worst guided tour of the Capitol building today.
It was a complete farce.
There was people running everywhere.
I don't know how they expected us to hear a single detail of the information.
I think a person even fell asleep at one point during the tour because of the lack of information
that was being taught.
And in addition to that, when I tried to ask for Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's autograph,
she maced me in the eyes and I had to write her name down in my bitch book, which is a
list of everybody in the world that I think is bitches.
But because I had freaking mace in my eyes, I couldn't write well and I accidentally wrote
down Alito Ocoxoconus, which isn't even a real person, so now my bitch book is ruined
and I had to throw it in the trash.
January 10th.
Resolution number 4 is still giving me a lot of trouble.
I was trying to live dangerously and I ate 5 full bags of county fair caramel corn and
And I am suffering my first tummy ache of the year and folks it's really, really, really
bad and I'm thinking that I might just want to have three resolutions this year at this
point.
But I'm not the kind of guy who gives up on resolutions and I think that to remove resolution
four would also be a violation of resolution three at keeping it real.
So I'm going to persist forward and probably try to eat another bag of County Fair caramel
corn tonight.
january fifteenth uh... squirrel
got into the house today i think through the window i leave open in case fairies
are real and i had a hell of a time
trying to hunt that bugger down uh... i was trying to find my pellet gun
to shoot at it uh... but unfortunately i couldn't find a gun and could only find
the pellets
so is running around my living room when i was
throwing pellets at it with my hands 'cause i gotta say i got a pretty
mean fastball and and
little league as a kid so i i i have to imagine that throwing pellets would
would be similar turns out it wasn't at all the pellets were bouncing everywhere
and i ended up throwing a
throwing out so many of them that
when i gave up and tried to walk to the kitchen to pour myself a drink of water
i slipped and my head went through the coffee table and i was stuck upside down
in that position for about three hours
uh... i couldn't find the squirrel so i have to assume that it went back out
probably through the window in the basement that I leave open in case gnomes are real.
January 27th.
After about a week of looking I finally found my pellet gun but I used up all the pellets
by throwing them at that squirrel.
So it's pretty much useless to me now.
I was walking out back to throw out the pellet gun and the recycling, I assume it's gotta
be recyclable, when I thought about how strange it would look to my neighbors if they saw me
throwing away a gun in the bin behind my house.
So I thought better of it and brought the gun back inside and put it under one of my couch
cushions in case any more pellets crossed my path.
But then I was thinking about how it must have looked even stranger if any neighbors
were looking at me to see me carrying a gun out to the recycling bin and then decide not
to throw it out and bring it back inside.
So I dialed up my neighbors one by one on the phone and told them all that if they saw me
doing anything today they were dreaming.
February 3rd.
Well, I'm not happy to report that today I did break my second resolution of no more
declaring wars on people.
Yes, my mailman did that thing I hate again of when he drops the lid of the mailbox very
loudly after he puts the envelopes into it, and I just about lost my shit and I pulled
out a piece of printer paper and a sharpie and I wrote "Declaration of War" and then
a bunch of squiggles that looked like fine print and I marched my ass outside and I handed
him that sheet of paper and told him I was declaring war on him and he said "Again?"
and I said "Yes, again."
And he said "I thought you said you were turning over a new leaf."
And I said "Well I was but I turned it back over the other way."
And he said "I know by now that this whole war thing is a fluke, you're just a freak.
not actually gonna declare any real kind of war on me and I said just you wait mister
and I went back inside and I got the pellet gun and I showed it to him and I said this
is my war gun I'm a soldier of war and I don't think he liked that very much because he pretty
much just left without saying anything.
I really think I should have recycled that pellet gun when I originally meant to so I
might do that tomorrow.
February 10th.
Well, a few days ago I went to put the pellet gun in the recycling bin and then I thought
about how strange it would look if the neighbors saw me throwing it away.
So I brought it back inside and put it under the couch cushion.
But then I thought about how strange it would be for the neighbors to see me try to throw
it away and then think better of it and bring it back inside.
So I was about to call my neighbors and explain that they were dreaming when I realized that
I had already done all this before and forgotten.
So instead I spent a few days practicing pellet gun tricks like spinning it around and shooting
it out of my sleeve like Travis the Pickle does in one of my favorite movies Taxi Driver.
And I think I'm pretty much ready for if the mailman ever decides to deliver mail here
again.
I'm gonna scare the shit out of him and I have the perfect plan.
February 14th.
Well, the mailman took my gun.
Here's how it happened.
Basically I had a plan where I knew that the mailman would have to come to my house today
because it's February 14th, Valentine's Day, and I always get a really thoughtful Valentine's
card from Stinky Steve, the prison inmate I used to be pen pals with a few years ago.
He always writes the nicest things and he puts it in a cute little card, the kind that
plays a song when you open it.
and the year before that he got one of those cards where you can record your own audio message
and he sang an original song of his own composition called "I Hate Being In Jail"
anyway when I saw the mailman walking up with a bright hot pink envelope I knew it was my time to shine
I ran outside holding the pellet gun loaded with frozen peas of course
and I pointed it directly at his forehead and I said
"Do you feel lucky mailman? Go ahead, give me my mail
and make my day too." And he just pretty much took away the gun
he said he knew it was fake all along and that if it wasn't I would be in
big big trouble and me and Stinky Steve would be having a different kind of
Valentine's Day together
and I didn't know what that meant but I thought that was really nice
so we hugged it out and I think I'm going back to my no more war resolution
because hugging my mailman is a lot nicer than brandishing a gun at him.
At least until he bangs the lid of the mailbox too loud again.
February 28th. Met a really cool guy at the grocery store today.
He was wearing a bright red double-breasted suit and had extremely
pronounced canine teeth.
He approached me after the checkout person turned me away for being five
dollars short on my groceries.
They said I was taking too long to decide which cereal box to put back so I had to
put everything back.
I think that's fucking bullshit!
But anyway, this guy came up to me and he said he noticed my predicament and he could spot
me the five dollars.
I said, "Sure, what's the catch?"
He said, "No catch," and smiled in a really big and cool way.
Then he took out a giant scroll and a quill and he asked me to sign my full name on it.
He said all I had to do was pay him back the five dollars by the end of the month or I
I would owe him my soul or something like that.
I'm not sure if he said soul or something else.
Can't remember.
Anyway, I knew I had about 3 days to scrounge up the $5 to pay this guy back, so I smiled
and nodded and I wrote my name down on the dotted line.
The man licked his lips and handed me a $5 bill that was red instead of green, and then
I think he vanished in a giant puff of smoke, though it could have been a trick of the fluorescent
lighting or a highly developed special effect.
With the $5 bill in hand, I was ready to buy all my groceries.
It hadn't really mattered that much to me that I couldn't afford the groceries since
it was just cereal, but the extra $5 was worth it to see how angry the checkout cashier looked
when she saw me get back in line.
2021 is shaping up to be low-key dope AF.
March 5th, been feeling strangely empty lately.
March 14th, today is pie day.
I don't go in for all that math shit, so to me, today is a food holiday.
I decided to celebrate by going out to one of my favorite restaurants for dessert.
Once I was seated, I could tell the waiter was giving me the stink eye, probably because
I hadn't showered in a while and I smelled pretty stink eye.
I said "hey man, what the hell are you looking at?" and then called him "Bub" which is one
of the most cutting insults you can call a grown man.
Well, one thing led to another and I soon found myself not eating pie like I had wanted
but instead washing dishes in the back of the restaurant.
Not because I owed money for a meal or anything, but just because I felt really bad for calling
the waiter "Bub".
March 17th, that's right baby, it's St. Patrick's Day.
And I'm recording this one in the morning because you know what happens during the day
and night of St. Patrick's Day.
That's right, I shouldn't even have to say it.
Tonight for St. Patrick's Day I'm heading out and I'm drinking myself so silly that
I can't walk, speak, or breathe unassisted.
But we all know what goes down before you head to the bar on St. Patty's Day.
That's right, you gotta pregame, baby.
And I love to pregame before going to the bar by drinking a bunch of beers at my house.
But I also like to do my own special thing, where before the pregame, I will pregame that
by eating lots of pretzels to make sure that I have food in my stomach before I drink a
lot of beers.
The issue with that is that pretzels can often dry me out.
So I like to pregame my pretzel pregame by drinking a whole lot of water, also at my
house.
But, the thing about the water pregame is I usually like to add a little postgame after
the water pregame but before the pretzel pregame where I go to the bathroom because the water
makes me need to pee really bad.
The order of all the pregames can be very confusing.
Sometimes I'll accidentally do pretzel pee water or beer water pee pretzel or pretzel
pretzel pretzel and it's very difficult to get it all right before I head out to the
the bar and that's why a few years ago I hired those contractors to come in and paint a big
flow chart on the wall of my bedroom that I get to use once a year and today's finally
the exciting day I get to look at it.
That's just the magic of old Saint Patty.
March 20th, today's the Vernal Equinox so in the spirit of the pagans I sacrificed a
few Hershey bars to my stomach.
Yum!
I also took a nice walk and ate several other pieces of good food as well.
It's lucky that the length of day and night are exactly equal today because I had such
a great day that I'd like to just dream it all over again tonight and if the night were
any shorter or longer it would fit unevenly into my dream.
March 26th.
Saw some kind of specter last night.
It was billowing down the street outside of my bedroom window and it looked exactly like
a grocery bag, but I knew better.
I was terrified and quaking under my covers, but then I remembered my resolutions and decided
to take life by the horns, so I went to call the police, but unfortunately I realized I
could only remember the first three numbers of the police's phone number.
912.
In such a scary situation, my forgetfulness shook me to my core, so I decided I need to
study up.
I put on my jacket and walked all the way to the library.
It was then that I realized it was 1am and the library was closed.
However would I get in and study their phone books?
I started to break in, but then the police pulled up.
I told them I saw a specter and they were kind enough to take me home for a small fee
of two hundred and fifty dollars
man i'd love the police
april first
i am not recording
a in audio entry right now
and uh... also i'm completely
uh... mute have lost the ability to
uh... talk
uh... and
uh... i'm dead
uh... i i'd i'd
no i died yesterday
and also i'd uh... don't exist and i never was
born at all
april fools
had you going pretty good there didn't i future self listening back to these
entries
april fourth
easter
time to dig my costume out of the closet
for my annual gig as Easter Bunny who gets tied to a chair by archetypal father figure
character. I'm not exactly sure why they want me to do this every year, but the kids at
the institute for manipulating the mentally disturbed into serial killers sure seem to
enjoy the show. Big paycheck, 20 bucks.
April 11th, stepped on a banana peel today, went flying and got some insane air, grazed
my knees on the concrete too.
When I stood up, in front of me, there was another banana peel, but next to it, there
was also an orange peel.
Confronted with this Matrix Morpheus style choice, I realized that I didn't want to go
flying through the air again, so I took a big step forward onto the orange peel.
Turns out, orange peels are about 100 times as slippery as banana peels.
I skidded for about a mile before I came to a stop.
You wouldn't think an orange peel would be slippery because they don't show it in cartoons
like they do with bananas, but apparently when you step on it, you just go crazy.
I puzzled about the philosophy of my choice for a while, because it seemed to be between
stepping on a banana peel and going flying and grazing my knees, or stepping on an orange
peel and skidding a mile forward.
I couldn't figure out which one I had been supposed to choose, but then I realized, the
correct choice was to just stand there and never take a step again.
The only winning move is not to play.
April 22nd, apparently today is Earth Day.
Uh, isn't every day Earth Day?
Shat my pants today and everyone could smell.
April 30th, the end of an era.
What era you ask?
April.
Can't wait for May, very excited for 4/20.
Just counted the months in my head and realized I missed 4/20.
Guess I'll be smoking a bunch of weed on 5/20 for the 17th year in a row.
May 4th, made an unpleasant discovery today.
Turns out today on Star Wars Day, people say, "May the 4th be with you."
I always thought they were saying, "May the Force be with you," like from Star Wars, and
I thought today's date was called May 4th, but it turns out it's actually called May
4th.
I guess that makes sense because I can't think of another month that has a 4th, but I do
think today should be called May 4th because otherwise the quote doesn't make any sense.
So I've decided to write to my local representative in government, whoever that may be, to change
the name of today's date to May 4th.
I am taking out my ballpoint pen and I am writing a letter on my finest stationery.
A sticky note with a drawing of a stick figure getting fucked in the bottom right corner
from an old flipbook I made last week.
May 5th.
The disappointing revelations just keep coming.
Turns out, today is called May 5th, not Cinco de Mayo.
I wrote another letter to my representative on another sticky note, and then I wrote about
a hundred more letters, cause I really wanted to get to the bottom of the stack of sticky
notes and see the stick figure in the flip book climaxing.
May 9th.
Today is Mother's Day.
I went to the grocery store and I bought a really nice bouquet of flowers, and I put
it on the windowsill in my kitchen.
Then I took a picture of it and sent it to my mom, and also sent her a request to play
C battle over iMessage.
I hope she likes it.
May 20th.
Today is my back up 4/20 day that I always use to smoke weed when I forget about 4/20.
And man, I am hella high right now.
I can't stop thinking about some crazy ass weed shit.
For example, something I decided about a minute ago was what if a table had three legs.
I was laughing my ass off at how random and weird that thought was.
Then I thought about what if a chair had three legs.
I freaked out and I was slapping my knee from laughing so hard from being so high.
Then I thought about what if a table had two legs and if a chair also had two legs.
I was laughing so hard I damn near peed myself.
Then I did pee myself cause I couldn't stop laughing thinking about a chair and table
with two legs each.
Then I had a crazy ass high thought.
What if a table had two legs and a chair also had two legs and you combine them together
and it kinda made a really long chair with four legs.
That scared me.
There would be no more laughs today because I had a giant panic attack.
May 24th.
I was craving some freakin' coffee this morning,
so I headed to Starbucks,
where I witnessed a master at work.
I was waiting to get my drink,
and this guy headed up to the register to order.
He ordered just a plain tap water,
and when they asked him his name,
he pulled out his iPad and showed them a webpage
called List of Every Name.
After that, he just walked over to the pickup counter
took every drink and put them in a big garbage bag.
He stood there for like 15 minutes and kept doing it.
Every drink that would get made and put on the counter, he'd pick it up and put it in
his garbage bag.
And there was nothing anybody could do about it, because they all had his name on it.
After he had been doing this for a while, he took the bag outside to the parking lot
and unlocked his car.
He popped the trunk and took out a giant straw.
Then he started drinking all the drinks out of the bag with the giant straw.
I bet it tasted disgusting, but the sweet taste of a con well pulled had to have overpowered
that.
I saw the manager of the Starbucks print out a picture of him and put it up behind the
counter so they knew to keep him out of the place.
Man, I'd love to have my picture up in that hall of fame behind the counter someday.
Right between Aaron "Through" Zydarius the garbage bag genius and Marvin the bathroom
masturbator.
June 1st, it sure is starting to get warm outside.
I sweat through my shorts and then I sweat through my underpants.
Then I realized I was wearing my underpants outside of my shorts.
I can't believe I was doing this all year and nobody said anything to me.
June 7th, was out walking around the mall parking lot picking grass out of the parking
lot islands and throwing it in people's hair all day when I got really thirsty.
I headed to the vending machine to score a cool bottle of water when I realized I hadn't
brought my coins with me.
Drew up a plan for how to steal a bottle of water from the vending machine on the back
of a bald guy's head and then he turned out to be a mannequin.
So the first step of my plan, defend self from angry bald guy, was unneeded.
to the vending machine to enact my plan. I figured it must detect quarters on a weight
based system. So I reached into my pocket and pulled out enough sand to roughly equal the
weight of a quarter. Started funneling the sand into the coin slot of the vending machine,
but nothing happened except for the people behind me in line getting very very angry.
Turns out I should not have crossed out the first step of my plan after all. A very thirsty
The bald guy hit me with his belt.
June somethingth.
Forgot what day it is today.
Gonna have to get back to you on this one.
June 24th.
The last entry was on June 15th.
Well, anyway, I was looking out the window today and I saw a bunch of kids playing outside.
It reminded me of my childhood.
My favorite game to play with my friends was hide and seek.
We were all really good at hiding, so we decided to invent a new version of the game called
"Hide".
It was like hide and seek, but there was no seeker.
We would all just hide for very long periods of time.
It ended up being pretty lucky that we invented this new game, because a few months later,
creepy old Mr. Henderson invented his own new game, "Seek".
June 31st, halfway through the year and I can't fucking do this anymore.
I have not been living according to my resolutions.
Yeah, sure, I started an audio diary, that one was easy and it basically didn't count.
But I already declared war on someone in the very first month, which I wasn't supposed
to do, and I'm not certain, but I don't think I kept it very real either.
Also I've barely done anything cool this year at all.
I only took one vacation and I've just been sitting around and going to the grocery store
and other stores.
I'm not seizing life by the horns at all or living it to its fullest.
This is fucked up.
I'm not appreciating my life one bit and that needs to change today.
That's right.
Earlier today I went to a back alley and I talked to a mysterious man and yes I bought
a bomb a time bomb to be exact and I right now am drilling into my wall and I am putting
the bomb into my wall where it will tick unseen by me but I will know it's there and I will
know it is counting down the seconds until it explodes when will it explode why exactly
six months from now on New Year's Eve, the end of the year, the specter of impending doom
will force me to live my life as it should be lived.
I should appreciate every day like it could be my last.
With the knowledge that I am going to die with certainty if I don't turn off this bomb
by the end of the year, I will seize life by the horns and I will live every day like
it could be my last.
Yup, I'm jigsawing myself.
I know this is extreme, but this is the only way I can think of to really get myself to
enjoy my life and push me to my limit.
July 1st.
Hit my head pretty hard last night.
Can't remember a single thing I did all day yesterday.
All I can remember is I was looking for a Cheeto on the floor of the living room and I must
have hit my head on the coffee table when I stood back up.
Not sure why I was looking for a Cheeto, because I haven't bought Cheetos in years, but I figure
I must have been thinking maybe there's one on the ground left over from a few years ago.
Either way, just gonna sit inside today, hearing strange noises coming from the walls, but
pretty sure it's just my imagination, or my neighbors listening to a ticking clock over
their Bluetooth speakers.
July 4th.
Wow, today's my birthday, one of the most exciting days of the year.
I ate so many delicious treats today.
I had a slice of banana cake, a slice of New York baked cheesecake, a slice of chocolate
coconut cake, a slice of carrot and walnut cake, a slice of lemon yogurt cake with syrup,
a chocolate mud cupcake, a slice of flourless orange cake, a vanilla cupcake, a slice of
basic sponge cake, a slice of chocolate birthday cake, a slice of classic no-bake vanilla cheesecake,
a slice of gluten-free Persian cake, a red velvet cupcake, a slice of baked lemon cheesecake,
a slice of chocolate mud cake, a slice of hummingbird cake, a slice of Jenny's coffee
cake, a slice of baked lemon cheesecake, a slice of flourless chocolate cake, a slice
of black forest cake, a slice of layered rainbow cake, a slice of triple chocolate cheesecake,
a slice of no bake spider web cheesecake, a slice of chalk honeycomb ice cream cake, a
slice of traditional fruit cake, a slice of cinnamon tea cake, a slice of marble cake,
a slice of lemon and coconut cake, a slice of double chocolate mousse cake, a slice of
raw strawberry cheesecake, a slice of apple and strawberry crumble, a slice of gluten free
chocolate loaf, a white chocolate mud cake pop, a slice of New York cheesecake, a slice
of white chocolate mud cake, a slice of caramel mud cake, a slice of white chocolate cheesecake,
a slice of flourless orange cake, a slice of white chocolate and raspberry cake, a slice
of banana caramel cake, a slice of passion fruit cheesecake, a slice of Martha's banana
and coconut streusel coffee cake, a slice of baked caramel cheesecake, a slice of orange
and almond cake, a slice of zucchini and walnut cake, a slice of raspberry and almond cake,
and a quick mix chocolate cake.
I also got my candy shoe box out of the closet and I enjoyed a Life Saver, a Hershey's Bar,
a Hershey's Kiss, an M&M, a Pretzel M&M, a Pumpkin Spice M&M, a Skittle, a Twizzler, a
Reese's Peanut Butter Cup, a Reese's Piece, a Reese's Crispy Crunchy Bar, a Dum Dums Pop,
a Starburst, a Swedish Fish, an Airhead, a Kit Kat, an Almond Joy, a Twix Bar, a Three
Musketeers bar, a Three Musketeers mint bite, a Milky Way bar, a Milky Way midnight dark
bar, a Tootsie Roll, a Tootsie Pop, a Peanut Butter M&M, a Werther's Original, a Sour Patch
Kid, a Milk Dud, a Sweet Tart, a Nerd, a Laffy Taffy, a Gobstopper, a Mounds bar, and a Snickers
bar. That was just about one of the most delicious birthdays I ever had, and right now I'm feeling
great. July 5th. Oh my stomach. July 6th. Oh. July 7th. Ow. July 8th. Oh. July 9th. Oh.
July 10th.
Ow.
July 11th.
Ow, my stomach still hurts.
July 12th.
Ow.
July 13th.
July 14th.
Ow.
July 15th.
*weird noises*
July 16th
July 17th
Feeling a lot better today
July 18th
Ate too much popcorn
*weird noises*
August 1st
Some weird stuff happened to me last night
I walked to 7-11 to harass the cashier
and when I was done I accidentally went out a door different than the one I
usually go out of
and instead of walking the half mile home I accidentally walks 27 miles directly
into the wilderness
I had no idea where I was and it was pretty dark
and I was pretty scared but then I came across some farmland
a strange farmer in tattered clothing
beckoned me to the farmhouse so I walked over
He opened the barn door and I followed him in.
I sat down with him in there and asked if I could spend the night
in his barn because I was lost and afraid. He said I was welcome to sleep there on
a bale of hay
but I might not want to after I heard his dark secret.
I was already kind of lying down on the hay and I was very excited because it
was very comfortable.
In fact, since last night I've been looking into getting my bed replaced
with a bale of hay.
I'm trying to keep the bed frame though, because I'm worried about destroying the habitat of whatever could be living under my bed.
Anyway, I asked the farmer what his dark secret was, and he looked at me with a brooding expression and told me he was a pedophile.
I said, "Wow, yeah, you're right. I mean, I'm not a child or anything, but knowing that, I definitely don't want to stay in your barn, sir. I'm very sorry."
He said, "That's understandable. My farming partner left me for the same reason.
His name was Steve Jobs, and I always wondered what happened to him.
I told him, 'I think Steve Jobs is dead.'
And he said, 'I knew that lousy fuck would never amount to anything.'
I said, 'Anyway, sir, why are your clothes tattered?
Does that have anything to do with you being a pedophile?'
And he said, 'No, I'm actually also a werewolf.'
And I said, 'Oh, jeez, is tonight a full moon?'
And he said, "No, it's only a half moon, so I won't transform into a werewolf tonight.
Don't worry."
I said, "Well, I won't worry about that, but I kind of wish that it was a full moon tonight.
You might be the only werewolf I've ever encountered that's actually less evil during a full moon."
And then I thought about it for a second, and I asked, "Are you still a pedophile when
you're a werewolf?"
He shrugged and said, "Beats me."
So I decided against staying in the farmer's barn, and I ended up calling an Uber home.
My Uber driver's name was Babatope and his fun fact on his profile page was that he loved
to dance in public.
I tipped him a big smile.
August 8th.
Played the worst video game of all time today.
It was called Super Mario Bros.
Basically, in this boring ass game, you play as a little question mark block that doesn't
move at all, and you essentially just sit there, and then this little red guy comes
and jumps under you and turns you brown.
So boring.
I prefer this game called Sonic the Hedgehog.
Basically you play as this timer at the top of the screen that ticks down from 10 minutes
to 0 and once it gets to 0 I think you win.
It's extremely fun because you also get to look at a still image of a blue hedgehog standing
in place while you play.
August 11th.
I went to the circus today and I was expecting to have a really good time, but something
terrible happened.
During the performance, I started to feel lightheaded because of how many animals I could see, so
I went outside of the tent to get some fresh air.
As I was pacing around, I noticed a big carrot in the ground.
I thought getting some food in my stomach could be pretty good for me, so I went and pulled
it out of the ground.
I realized that it wasn't a carrot, but actually one of the steaks holding up the circus tent.
I realized this too late though, as I had already pulled up 12 more.
The tent collapsed, and its fabric blanketed everyone inside, suffocating several elephants
and several lions.
The police showed up on the scene and were trying to figure out who did it.
They almost nabbed me, but they ended up booking this guy who I guess was there to protest the
use of animals in the circus.
I thought he might have been an animal rights guy or something, but it turned out he was
protesting the use of animals because of how much he hated animals.
The police ended up picking him up because he was wearing a shirt that said "I hate elephants
and lions."
I felt pretty guilty about the wrong guy taking the fall when I got home, and I thought about
turning myself in, but I realized that if I did, they'd probably make me give the stakes
back and I had already used them to hang up a painting I bought off Etsy, a beautifully
detailed map of Hogsmeade from the Harry Potter books, the town where I had grown up in my
story where I was the son of Ron Weasley and Ron Weasley's wife.
August 21st.
Fell into a bucket of neon paint on the way to the park today.
Decided to make the most of it and stand in the middle of a four way intersection and
pretend to be a crossing guard.
Was able to cause about 17 accidents before somebody said, "Hey, that's not a crossing
guard, he's just covered in neon paint."
Not quite a personal best, but I'll take it.
When I finally got to the park, nobody would look me in the eye, because I screamed at
this guy's dog there yesterday.
August 25th.
Got stuck under my weighted blanket again today.
That's what I call my down comforter, because of all those heavy feathers inside of it.
Ended up escaping by biting a hole in the cover of the comforter and sucking out the
feathers like snake venom and spitting them out onto the floor.
Allergies are going crazy today and I'm not sure whether it's from the feathers or the
bales of hay that I replaced my bed, couch, and chairs with.
The bales of hay are nice, but they have a little more give than I'm used to and aren't
giving me the back support that I need when I lie down, so I'm thinking of replacing them
with huge granite slabs.
September 4th.
Ugh, back to school day.
This is the worst time of the year.
my son out of his box and drove him to school and dropped him off.
And then all these other parents were trying to introduce themselves to me on the schoolyard.
And it's like, "Will you guys shut up?
I don't see why we should have to be on a first name basis with each other if we're only seeing
each other once a year anyway.
Just leave me alone."
Then I drove back home and my freaking wife was yelling at me all day once I got back.
She's such a bitch, almost as much of a bitch as Alito Ocoxoconus.
Man, I worked hard today.
I deserve a vacation.
September 11th.
I feel like there's something about today that I'm supposed to know, but I can't remember.
I've been racking my brain all day, but I can't think of a single thing.
I mean, if it was a holiday, I'm sure I'd remember.
Or maybe it's just some other kind of special day.
Did something happen today?
I seriously can't remember.
I'm just sitting here and it hurts my brain how hard I'm thinking trying to remember what
happened today.
Oh well, if I can't think of it, it must not have been very important.
September 19th.
Arrrrr, it be talk like a pirate day, matey.
One of my favorite holidays.
I don't even need to check the calendar to remember this one, matey.
Only a landlubber would forget talk like a pirate day.
September 25th.
Couldn't sleep last night because of how excited I was about today.
September 25th, it's ghost hunting day.
I picked up the cake that I ordered from the bakery for today and then I hung my head and
spent a moment of silence before I ate it remembering all the people who were turned
into ghosts.
And the ghost hunters that have been lost in the line of duty.
Today has got to be one of the most important days of September.
September 28th.
I realized I was wrong about National Ghost Hunting Day being one of the most important
days in September.
It's actually today, September 28th, World Rabies Day.
Today is a day to remember and honor the victims of the rabies disease, which has a 99.9% mortality
rate.
What a tragic day.
Everybody should remember this day and should never forget the events that have transpired
on September 28th when we remember those that we lost to having too much foam in their mouths.
October 2nd.
Had to go buy a new mirror today.
The one in my bedroom is broken.
It keeps showing a horned demon behind me over my shoulder and then when I turn around, it's
not even there.
Went to Home Depot to pick up a new mirror and when the attendant guy was helping me
me get it down from the shelf, he dropped it and it shattered all over the ground.
He freaked out, saying he couldn't handle that much bad luck.
I said, "Don't worry, man.
It's only one year of bad luck."
He said, "No, if you break a mirror, it's seven years of bad luck."
I said, "No, look right here."
And I pulled out my pocket-sized copy of "A Dog's Guide to Bad Luck Curses" and showed
him it said, "If you break a mirror, it's one year of bad luck."
He said, "I'm not talking about dog years, I'm talking about human years."
I said, "How the hell was I supposed to know we were talking about human years?"
October 11th.
Today is Columbus Day.
Although I guess now, due to certain PC culture developments, people are saying it should
actually be called Indigenous Peoples Day because Columbus was actually indigenous or
something like that.
I don't really keep up with the conflict, and I'm not sure which side I'm supposed to take,
so I've been calling it "Everybody Just Stop Fighting and Hug It Out Day," which hasn't
made anybody mad out of the two homeless people that I told it to so far.
October 23rd.
Realized I don't know what I'm dressing up as for Halloween, so had to have a brainstorm
session.
Having a really hard time settling on something.
I have to strike a balance between scary and fun because I don't want to scare people too
bad, but I also want to be at least a little scary because, you know, it's Halloween.
First idea was a spider and I decided that was too scary.
Then my second idea was a caterpillar.
I thought that wasn't scary enough.
So I've been sitting here all day rubbing my temples trying to think of what's the exact
scariness level between a spider and a caterpillar and I couldn't think of anything.
Just realized just now, it's probably a bumblebee.
Going to dress as a bumblebee for Halloween.
Gonna have to go costume shopping.
October 27th, went shopping for some parts of my bumblebee costume today.
Bought a bright yellow outfit with the intention to paint black stripes onto it when I got
home.
yellow outfit in the store before I walked home to take it for a test run, but then one
of the guys whose accident I caused when I was covered in neon paint walked into the
store and he saw me wearing a yellow outfit and tackled me because he thought I was on
my way to cause more accidents as a fake crossing guard.
I tried to explain myself but he hit me in the face pretty hard so I couldn't speak for
a good 15 minutes.
Ended up returning the yellow outfit and buying a black outfit instead with the intention to
paint yellow stripes onto it when I got home.
But I didn't wear it out of the store just in case anybody thought I was an evil shadow.
Was looking for a headband with antennas on it but couldn't find them at the store so
I ended up having to settle for buying two wizard hats that I would wear on my head and
hope that they look like antennas.
Couldn't find a stinger either so I bought a third wizard hat to wear on my butt as a
stinger.
going to try to use some other wizard hats to make it look like I had six legs, but thought
better of it and decided to amend my costume to be a four-legged bumblebee.
October 31st, the scariest day of the year, Halloween.
Wish my neighbors would turn down their creepy ambient sound effects.
They're really boring this year, they just sound like this.
I really prefer those ambient Halloween soundscapes that are like clanking chains and wailing
ghosts, but that's neither here nor there.
Scared the shit out of some trick or treaters tonight with my bumblebee costume.
They got so scared they started laughing, like in a movie when somebody almost gets
hit by a car and they're so scared that the adrenaline causes them to laugh maniacally.
Didn't give out any candy to the trick or treaters this year.
really feel like digging any out of my candy shoebox. That stuff's all for me. Instead
I handed out little slips of paper that said "Imagine the delicious taste of a decadent
candy bar." Most of the kids didn't like that very much, but I could tell a few of the losers
thought it was delightfully postmodern.
November 3rd. It's starting to get cold out. I decided to take a nice long walk today before
winter really sets in.
After wandering around the park for a while, I went through a strange tunnel and found
myself before an immense castle.
A giant door was set into the wall there, guarded by two identical twins.
I walked up to them and said, "What's up?"
The first twin said, "We're the identical twin guards."
The second guard said, "Yes, we're twins, and we finish each other's sentences."
And then the first guard said, "Period."
I said, "Can I go inside this castle?
It looks pretty cool."
And the first one said, "You're going to have to solve our puzzle first.
You see, I am the brother who always tells the truth."
And the second guard said, "And I am the one who always does dares."
I said, "Well, okay, I dare you to let me into the castle."
And the second one said, "Damn."
And he opened the door for me.
And as I walked in, I turned to the first one and said, "Also, who do you have a crush
on?"
And he blushed and said, "I don't want to play anymore," and ran into the woods and hid behind
a tree.
I wandered around the inside of the castle for a while, but it was pretty boring, all
old and stone and stuff.
Eventually I came to the huge throne room.
It was beautiful.
There was a giant golden chair, and sitting in it was an old withered king, dressed in
shimmering robes and golden chain mail with an ornate crown atop his head.
He outstretched a gnarled hand towards me and beckoned me forward.
I approached the throne and knelt before him.
I accidentally knelt directly into a puddle, but I thought that if I stood up he might kill
me, so I had a really wet knee for the rest of the day.
In a quivering, reedy voice, the king told me he was king of the park and he had been
for almost 200 years, but now he was getting old and he needed an heir.
He told me I was the first worthy individual who passed the first two tests.
The first one was to even find the castle in the first place and the second was to bypass
the fearsome twin guards who guarded the door.
I asked what the third test was and he said I had to pull a sword from a stone.
He gestured to his right and I looked and there it was, a massive broadsword protruding
from a big rough boulder.
I said well here goes nothing and grabbed the hilt of the sword.
With as much strength as possible, I pulled the hilt toward me, but I forgot to brace
my foot on the rock because I was still kneeling and instead of pulling the sword out of the
stone, I ended up picking up the rock with the sword and then it flew out of my hands
like a golf club and knocked the king's head off.
So now I'm king of the park.
I brought the crown home and put it on top of my DVD player in the storage room in my
my attic.
November 8th, just realized why Stephanie Myers named her vampire series Twilight.
It's because of the similarity between the words crepuscular and corpuscular.
Crepuscular meaning of resembling or relating to Twilight, with corpuscular meaning of or
relating to a blood cell.
Very clever, Stephanie.
I love noticing little easter eggs like this, like when I realize that ATM machines have
an option to check balance so that technicians can come in and make sure that thieves aren't
able to tip them over.
November 11th, Veterans Day.
Today is a day to honor those who have fought in wars and defended our country.
A lot of people will dedicate this day to their great uncle maybe, or their grandfather, who
usually fought in one war, two at most.
But I know somebody who deserves this day way more than any of those losers.
My mailman has fought in over 50 wars against me, and now that we're in a period of truce,
I think it's time that I honor him.
So I went to the post office a few days ago to send myself a letter to make sure that
I'd see him today.
When he walked up to the house, he saw me holding something behind my back and he said, "That
better not be another lasso."
I said, "No, don't worry Mr. Mailman, this is for you."
And I showed him what was behind my back.
It was a bouquet of flowers that I presented to him.
He said, "These flowers are old and dead and dry and horrible."
And I said, "Well yeah, of course.
I bought them on May 9th, Mother's Day.
So of course they're gonna be all fucked up by now.
I can show you a really nice picture I took of them on the day that I bought them."
And then I took out my phone to look through my text conversation with my mom to find the
picture of the flowers that I sent her, but I forgot that I delete my text conversation
with my mom every single morning.
Not to hide how many times I've lost at C-Battle in a row, of course, but rather just to save
some space on my phone for my all-important apps.
Hulu, Netflix, Amazon Prime, McDonald's, Planet Fitness, Duolingo.
These are some of my favorites.
My mailman put his hands on my shoulders and said, "Son, I'm gonna be real with you.
I know we've had our differences in the past, but if the post office doesn't approve my
route change this time around, I'm going to fucking blow my brains out.
And when he said that, it affected me really deeply.
So I want to dedicate this audio diary entry to raising awareness for the lack of mental
health resources available to veterans in our country.
Veterans die every day because of no good reason, just because they're sad or something
I guess and because they have no therapist to tell them listen man
If you're gonna do it at least wait until after Christmas so your family can have fun
November 25th
Thanksgiving I know you're probably expecting me to be saying I'm super full right now
But I actually didn't get to eat anything today. Here's what happened
I headed over to my uncle's house to meet up with my whole family for Thanksgiving
It was my job there to cook the turkey, and I have to say I did a great job.
I cooked a gigantic 50 pound turkey and basted it with delicious juices and I added all the
seasonings and other ingredients that you're supposed to add when you cook a turkey for
Thanksgiving.
But then, as I walked from my uncle's kitchen, through my uncle's exhibit room, into my uncle's
dining room, I ended up tripping on a replica halberd that was lying on the floor and the
entire turkey flew off of the plate and flew into my uncle's piranha tank where it was
skeletonized in 5 seconds flat.
I put the bones on the plate and kept going into the dining room and tried to pretend
that I didn't notice anything had happened so I wouldn't have to tell anybody it was
my fault, you know, like when you throw up on the rug.
But everyone noticed and my uncle started yelling at me.
My family said it was my fault that there would be no turkey on Thanksgiving, and who
knows, maybe they were right.
My uncle got out his mind control wand, which was a stick that he had conditioned and trained
me as a child to obey any command while it was pointed at me, kind of like a dog or rat
in an experiment.
Well he pointed that wand right at me and said go the hell home so I had no choice.
But that wasn't all, as I was walking out the door he pointed at me again and said have
a bad Thanksgiving.
I thought that was a little over the top but what could I do.
Now I'm sitting here crying and it's all his fault.
November 26th, Black Friday.
to go out on the hunt for deals today for Christmas shopping but the spell that my uncle cast
on me still hadn't worn off so I couldn't leave the house.
Ended up shopping in my own pantry for Christmas gifts and things got a little aggressive toward
the end and I broke my nose.
December 1st, a meteoroid landed in my house today.
It smashed in through my wall, leaving a hole like in Looney Tunes when Bugs Bunny smashes
through the wall, except this hole was meteoroid shaped instead of Bugs Bunny shaped.
It hit me right in the face and knocked my nose back into alignment, so I was pretty happy
at first, but then I saw a mysterious green vapor rising from its surface and I thought,
this has to be bad news.
In order to protect everyone in my neighborhood from possible contamination from outer space
fumes, I took a deep breath and inhaled every last drop of the green vapor, like bong water.
I felt a strange tingling sensation spread from my lungs through the rest of my body,
and then I heard a booming voice in my head.
That said, your DNA and every aspect of your brain has been completely scanned.
Through rapid yet careful analysis of your body, we have now ascertained every strength
and weakness of the entire human race, and we will use this to subjugate you in the future.
Don't bother trying to fight back or warn anybody, because we have now cataloged every
weapon that your brain is possible of conceiving of, and none of them shall prosper against
us.
And with that, all of the green vapor flew out of my nose, like bong water, and went back
into the meteoroid, which hovered, and flew back out through my wall, leaving a second
non-Bugs Bunny shaped hole.
December 15th.
Embarrassing day today.
So I somehow accidentally signed up for a newsletter called "Brain Tumor Fan Club".
I guess it's a newsletter for people who are a fan of brain tumors.
I really don't want that kind of thing on my phone, so I've been trying to unsubscribe
from it, but every time I do, it says "Thank you for unsubscribing.
Please allow up to 3 years while we update your email preferences."
This wouldn't be too much of an issue, but a while ago I accidentally turned on that
setting for weird guys on my iPhone where whenever I get a notification my flashlight flashes
on and off a bunch of times and the phone makes a loud noise.
And it's been doing that whenever I get the email.
And for whatever reason in the past few days the Brain Tumor Fan Club has really ramped
up their correspondence.
I used to only get like one email every two weeks but I've been getting like ten or twenty
a day.
Anyway, earlier today I was riding the bus and my phone started doing the flashlight
thing and the person next to me on the bus, of course their eye was drawn to the flashlight,
they looked over at my phone and they saw I received an email that said it was from
Brain Tumor Fan Club and the subject line said, "If you are receiving this email, that
means you think brain tumors are awesome."
The guy next to me said, "What the fuck man?
during a club called the Brain Tumor Fan Club, and the entire bus started to get really mad
at me.
I was freaking out and I didn't know what to do.
So I got up and walked toward the front of the bus to get off, but right then I received
a second email from Brain Tumor Fan Club and it caused my flashlight to go on and off rapidly
again which I guess gave the bus driver a seizure or something because his limbs all
crumpled up and he started foaming at the mouth and the bus swerved off the road and
plunge deep into a snowbank.
After a few minutes of being trapped in the snow, one by one, the bus passengers started
getting rescued by drab looking women who were probably mentally disturbed, like at the beginning
of "Misery" by Stephen King.
The number of passengers in the bus dwindled as more and more got rescued, and eventually
it was only me left.
A woman wearing a vest and a plaid flannel pulled me out of the snowbank and looked me
into my eyes.
She said, "Are you writing a book?"
I said, "No."
She said, "What about making a movie?"
I said, "Also no, though I feel like I might like to someday.
I have a lot of stories trapped in this brain of mine."
And her eyes lit up and she said, "I can work with that.
I think we can make a misery situation out of this yet.
What's your preferred method of telling a narrative?"
And I said, "Well, I'm actually a podcaster."
And she shoved me back into the snow, and I had to stay and wait in there for 4 hours
until I was rescued by a passing dogsled musher.
December 24th, Christmas Eve.
I can't sleep.
I'm too excited.
I just need to see what Santa brought me.
I forgot to get a tree this year, so I'm hoping that he understands the visual language of
me putting out a potted flower on a stool in the place where I would normally put my
tree.
When I was trying to sleep earlier, I could have sworn I heard the reindeer walking across
my roof.
Well, it actually sounded more like they were walking through my walls, and instead of reindeers,
it sounded a little bit like a clock.
I'm so excited!
December 25th, Christmas morning.
That fat fuck Santa didn't come through again.
I didn't receive a single present.
You might think it's because of the whole potted flower thing, but that fucking loser hasn't
broughten me a single gift since I moved out of my moms house.
Thought it might be because maybe he still has my address listed as my moms address so
I called my mom to see if he left any gifts there for me.
She said "come on" and hung up.
I'm pissed the fuck off.
I bet she opened my damn presents and now is pretending that Santa didn't bring any there.
I bet her and Santa are in cahoots.
I would say this is the worst Christmas ever, but it actually comes in third place, after
the Christmas where I had a near death experience and the Christmas where I had two near death
experiences.
December 31st, New Years Eve.
Well, it's almost midnight and I'm just sitting here reflecting on the year I've had.
You know, even though the only resolution I really kept was keeping this audio diary,
I'm kinda happy with how the year turned out.
Even if I didn't necessarily live my life to its fullest, I still had a good time.
Maybe it's not about taking life by the horns, or going on vacation, or eating too much delicious
food.
Maybe it's just about hanging out and being an asshole to service workers and just chilling
out.
I feel like I've reached an epiphany today.
2021 may not have been perfect, but it was a good year.
Oh no, I'm missing the countdown.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
HAPP-