Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I love everything.
- All right, we're recording now.
- Oh my God, it's recording it.
- Oh my God, here it is.
Crazy.
- We've left the casino.
- Second year in a row.
Yeah, I guess you should be listening to this second.
- This is the second one.
- This is the live show after party.
- Yeah.
but we could have gone back in time and uh...
got to the uh... we could have a four-party alright hey save the improper
you on all right this is a
this is a luxury one shot at all you guys only do purely returns yeah
yet did
you think i think i can look at your fucking script right now
okay uh... i'm not comfortable doing this voice though uh... not my problem
do that role
This is right here, Branson.
You should have your wiener out.
Yeah, right.
So I'm playing the what?
And now he does.
It's a Nigerian dentist.
You guys want me to play?
No, we don't write this.
Yes, we do.
What?
It's the it's the company.
I mean, we shouldn't be talking about.
Yeah, there's only yeah.
Yeah.
Who do you guys who employs you guys secretly?
Sony Ericsson, Sony Ericsson, the Department of Sony.
Yeah, because they need more content for the Sony Ericsson.
We're sponsored by Mitchell and Ness.
Oh, really?
That's kind of tight.
That's catchy.
That's cool.
You guys get the jerseys and shit?
Yeah, he wants just a whole operation
to kind of make people buy used basketball jerseys.
Is that like, is that like they just hunt like dope white boys
and y'all just like put on for the game kind of?
Yeah, we get a big white t-shirt.
We put the, you know, the jersey right over it.
Some kind of big pants.
Wait, Andrew usually picks out our pants.
No, like, hold on.
Can I stop?
Like this is this isn't like a premise like you won.
Like you said, Branson, none of that's true.
Oh, well, that's why we're on the show is to lie to these guys.
They're so stupid. They're not going to know any better.
Yeah, we are seriously fucking stupid.
And you can say anything you want to us.
We'll pretty much believe it because it's funny.
Is that every day is like an adventure for us because we have so much money.
So it'll probably be really interesting for you guys to hear
about our very cool rich guy lives.
Yes. Tell us more about Mitchell and us.
like
little
I mean, if you like tie up a cat or a dog at a Gildan t-shirt, it's like,
I mean, it's like,
it's like a dog and a cat and a dog and a cat and a dog and a dog and a dog.
And it's like,
it's like a dog and a cat and a dog and a dog and a dog and a dog and a dog.
it's like a dog and a cat and a cat and a cat and a cat and a cat and a cat.
And it's like,
it's like a dog and a cat and a dog and a dog and a dog and a dog and a dog.
it's like a dog and a cat and a cat and a dog and a dog and a dog and a dog and a
It's like Dragon Ball Z armor basically.
Yeah, I mean if you like tie up a cat or a dog in a Gildan t-shirt, it ain't getting out.
I want to do the... what workout do you think you have to do to get...
to fit a Gildan shirt like really well for it to look good on you?
Do you think you need to be grown like a square Japanese watermelon?
Yeah, you need to be born in Gildan shirts.
An Iron Maiden style thing.
Where there's no spikes in there, it's just square.
You gotta be built like your mom.
any of you.
Uh, no.
What's the Spanish?
We don't have one mom.
Was that thing that Bugs Bunny and Gumby were always getting caught in where it like it
dresses your arms.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
No, the ones that stretch you out.
Stocks.
What's the one that stretches you out?
Oh, the rack.
The rack.
Yeah, the rack.
Yes.
I think in order to fit into a Gildan t-shirt, you would need a, a, a, a horizontal rack.
One that would stretch you from shoulder to shoulder.
Horizontal rack.
Just ask my wife.
Hey.
and
cool. Yeah, she's got nice. She's got nice. She fills out her
gildans nicely. I married her, right? I married an incredibly
beautiful, wonderful woman. Thank you. Oh yeah. She's a lot.
She is a lot though. Yeah. She is a lot. I think I've met her
before. Doesn't she she manages a cricket wireless? Yeah. Yeah.
She she fills out a polo though. I'll tell you what. He ain't
lying about that. Yeah. I mean, she works out. Yeah. Well, you
have
the
can't talk to Republicans on Obama phones. It just says this
number. The only website you can go to is LinkedIn. Yeah,
that's right. If you try to text a Republican, it says this
number is sorry. This number has become too rational.
To level headed and logical with its beliefs. What I do
when I'm headed to like the the cricket wireless or the T
mobile or the Verizon store, what have you is I go in with a
big a big thing of of hedge trimmers. These giant shears
Because if you if you can cut through that like that metal wire thing that holds the phone to the table, you're allowed to take it.
Yes, they can't stop you.
It's just the it's just that wire that stops you.
I like it.
Or if you use the wire cutters on the person working there, if you kill them, you can take their stuff, too.
That's well, they're just there to cut the dreadlocks.
We have a ballista set up for the people.
I went to way in the back.
I went into a cricket wireless to get a cell phone.
I was like, all right, I finally get one of these damn things.
Okay, and I go in there and I'm looking around my cricket wireless.
Where's Pinocchio?
Yeah.
That's right.
Jiminy cricket.
Jimmy.
Where's the stars to be to wish upon?
You know, you're talking about a different cricket.
Where are them donkeys?
I thought you're talking about the gun from Men in Black.
Oh, that's funny as hell.
Like, oh, where's Agent M?
Oh, ripped horn.
Where's the team of Indian guys?
You know, it used to be that crickets were the only thing that chirped.
Now we got these cell phones chirping everywhere I go.
That's right.
What happened to the crickets?
You know, like, yeah, I know all these cell phones.
They're crickets stillers.
I know.
I haven't seen one in about 10 years.
So that you can just can't hear whatever happened is cicadas.
Yeah, you know, it's probably been five or six years since I saw it.
We literally just had a brood come up this year.
I'm sick of everybody could walk around with these sprint next
phones chirping each other saying where you at?
On their walkie-talkie phone.
Yeah, and whatever happened to infectious diseases and viruses?
Ever since I moved into my bubble, I haven't seen a single one.
True.
I don't know.
I feel like I haven't seen them in ages.
Oh, it's so weird that you don't hear about anything like that because it doesn't exist.
It wasn't, it was a fake and it was a lie.
And that's the nurse telling you that so you can believe him.
That's right.
Andrew, you're a total Cove idiot.
the
all
at
Maybe maybe the afternoon, the late, late lunch.
Okay.
All right, even stronger.
Maybe we go the other way.
Midnight.
And he doesn't like anything.
What about all right, Patrick?
SpongeBob Ice Cream Bar.
Ooh, okay, but that's a good way to gumballs.
There's a cricket on it, though.
Okay, he doesn't like crickets.
All right.
What about gremlins?
What then?
Why would you go?
That's way scarier than midnight.
I'm sorry.
What about Oh, Patrick?
What about Cameron and Caleb?
He loves us.
He's looking at lips.
I don't think he's saying hello.
He doesn't realize he's on the call right now.
By the way, we got this is one of his educational tapes.
Patrick and Branson are the dumb guys of our podcast.
They're so fucking dumb.
They're both so stupid.
You guys probably have the you guys are probably you you guys
have coconuts.
the
and
used to said he used to ride down this big hill in his red wagon over and over.
I love my red wagon as a kid.
I went down the hill constantly.
And I like the taste of like copper for some reason.
So I would keep pennies.
You know what he likes now.
And I'd go shooting down that hill in the red wagon and be bumpy and they just
you just swallow.
I don't know what to say.
You just.
Right.
What kind of fucking family guy cutaway did you live in?
Or you're riding in a red wagon with coins in your mouth every day.
Oh, I actually swallowed it.
Oops.
I don't like it, but easy come easy go.
All those coins are still in his stomach.
If you shake them around.
Oh, look at that.
I think a piggy bank.
If you ever need a dollar on this beach again, I guess I got to eat
some of the sand to survive.
No, eating sand was different.
That was when I was smaller than that.
I was like 13 instead.
No, I was like, you know, sandbox age.
Well, coins were coins that I hung on to till I was like 24.
Two in one right now.
Look what what grade is like first open your mouth wide.
A first.
How old is first grade?
Yeah, what's the first grade?
The first age?
No, but like what year age is it?
Is that eight or two thousand four?
Hey Branson, what time?
Oh, that's what you're asking me.
How far back am I from the Eastern time zone right here in the mountain time
and
Yeah, that's minus one.
That's what Charles.
What time is it here in Mountain Standard Time?
Well, it's six o'clock where I'm at. I'm on the east.
So if you're two, it must be four.
Oh, my God, I can't believe you got it.
It only took three guesses.
That's a bingo.
I'm being put on the spot.
It is it is nice to see somebody else.
All right, Patrick, saying it to prolong.
You're also when you guys are repeating the question.
I have more time to think.
OK, but I'm not the only one who does it.
I'm following it.
You're in the eastern time zone.
It's 6 p.m.
What time is it in central time zone right now?
It's 5.
Oh, very good.
What time is it in Pacific time zone?
In Pacific time, it's three hours behind, so it would be 3 o'clock right now.
Let's fucking go, dude.
Oh my god.
100% go.
it would be is it would be you already said it was three hours
behind and then you still had to give yourself it would be
all the use in a sentence. I still got it. So it's the
dictionary defined six as three hours ahead of three camera
message rapid messaging Patrick and I'll talk the stuff.
He giving him the times.
Yeah, first behind a streak.
We can't have the dumb or dumb guy.
You know, that's embarrassing.
Well, maybe you want the dumber.
Dumb. Maybe we should.
Maybe we can have a competition here.
I used to be dumb.
All right.
Patrick Branson, Patrick and Branson.
What tastes better, pee or poop?
None.
That's not true.
One's got to taste better.
I bet you like the best.
Like equally, you love if the guy's diabetic, it's supposed to be sugary.
So I'm going with no pee or poop.
I'm gonna go with P.
I think Branson's right.
He wins. He's smarter than the fucker like speed.
Dude, we definitely have a number.
I only had two options.
He cheated.
He tried to trick question and it's how you how you separate the wheat
from the chaff and you, my friend, are chaff the weed from the weed.
The weeds from the chads.
All right, Caleb, tell me what chaff is.
Chaff is basically the shit that isn't wheat.
Everything in the world is chaff if it's not weed.
Yeah, most shit is chaff.
Pretty much. Oh, I need that sweet wheat.
Oh, yeah, I actually prefer to say that.
I prefer a lot of people who say they don't like chaff.
They've just never had good chaff.
You got to have in true.
It's true.
Nate, what's the where have you had good chaff?
What? Las Vegas. I'll go.
I mean, California, when it comes off the vine, all of chaffs.
Old stuff is pretty good, but I don't like any of their new stuff.
But I've been fucking with wheat since day one.
Yeah, we it's pretty good.
What is I actually you don't even like the week you just like the glue.
I think the wheat the wheat is the part of the wheat the chaff is the wheat
that's the part of the wheat that's not wheat they make bread out of the
wheat.
That's the force.
Can I make it through throw away the chaff?
Chaffy cereal.
It's the halfies.
Oh, yeah, so what about some chaff beer with an orange slice?
Oh that actually.
So it's like Mario Kart on the N64.
Chaff is like the Delta 8, right?
Yeah. OK, what's the Delta 8?
It's like Delta, you know, Delta 8 weed, how they have normal weed
and then they have the Delta 8 weed from gas stations.
They got new weed.
Here's a new weed that they can.
It's illegally not like the new K2.
It's legally nothing.
It's just like it might as well be just nothing.
Yummier. Yeah.
They haven't come up with a law for it.
It's a product that's a tax on dumb guys.
Pretty much.
You and Patrick would probably enjoy it.
I would.
I hate Delta 8.
And I hate weed.
Yeah, I know.
Dude, this Delta 8 virus that's going around is really fucking--
It's terrifying.
Yeah.
A new wrinkle in the wheat versus chaff debate.
It says here on the Wikipedia page, chaff should not
be confused with bran, which is finer, scaly material as far as the grain itself.
So there's wheat, and there's chaff, and there's also bran.
And that's Branson's dad.
Is that true?
Chaff or bran?
Yeah, Jeff Branson is his.
We know we're going to call him when he's old as fuck.
Raisin Bran.
Yeah, he's brand.
OK, there's also when I have a child and I just thought of that
because I had some for breakfast this morning and I was like,
Oh, I got it.
I got a joke later for for the air.
I guess they were doing raisin bread.
Good cereal for breakfast.
It's a great cereal for breakfast.
I eat raisin. I eat raisin bran this morning.
I'm a yogurt guy.
I'm a yogurt geniuses of the podcast.
I don't eat breakfast because that's insane.
I'm a steak and eggs meals in a day.
every day. Yeah, every day.
Breakfast. Prime prime ribeye.
And can we redo this?
You know what I have for breakfast every day?
Oh, here we go.
Now, you know, you probably have a glass of soy milk.
No one, you know.
Oh, well, you got the Michael Douglas.
Oh, hell no.
And we have soy flakes in a soy bowl with soy milk.
Hey, and you and you are what you eat and drink.
Yeah. And so you're basically a soy milk.
Soy. I'm a soy boy.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
You're a soy boy. I'm a bitch.
And I'm a toy boy and I'll be playing with them G.I.
Joes in the Bionicles.
Oh, I'm Bionicles.
When Andrew gets on his Obama Bionicle, he tries to text Caleb.
It doesn't let him.
That's right.
Then hit speed dial. Yeah.
Hello, this is Planned Parenthood.
Would you like to kill your child?
Yes.
Caleb, would you like for us to expand your pussy to fit more penises
that you're not married to?
Yeah.
Caleb and I are out and I'm like, we're talking to this girl and I and Caleb
comes up, he's like, you know that, you know, he's, you know, he's soy
for breakfast. I don't even have breakfast.
I just play with guys.
You ever hear of guys?
I'd be playing with my guys on top of the toy chest,
pretending it's Africa, and I'm having a good old time.
He's busy eating soy milk.
You're making them attack each other, going like, "Raaah!"
"Yaaah!"
It's pretty crazy.
Pull it out in the club.
This is my first time.
I got a truck.
I got a big yellow truck.
Yeah.
Hey, girl, are you mission control?
Sorry, I was playing pretend as an astronaut just then.
I do it pretty much all the time.
Yeah, and pretty much every girl that I talk to
when I'm playing pretend comes home with me.
So yeah, just I mean, I've been used.
I'll be rolling up to the club in my in my my fucking HES sports car.
Damn, everybody's looking at me.
Green and white, green and white, green and white, green and white.
I'm rolling up to the club with a big laser tag
target around my chest.
That's right.
The boy's got the the club on fire while everyone's watched us play duck duck goose.
Yeah, that's right.
I stay strapped up with the laser tag.
you never know who's gonna wants to take me out dude. Yeah. Yes sir. I'm 24 years deep in the
game and I haven't lost yet. We went laser tagging recently and they gave us... Yeah we played laser
tag. What were the names? They called one of us like the the eliminator or something and then
someone else was just called like the wizard. Like they gave us... Yeah there's like I remember
this one kid that got the name Twinkie and I was like oh f*cks. I'd love to be I'd love to have the
the name twinkie. I think mine was wizard. Yo yeah why do they even put like twinkie in
there? Oh fuck my name is creampie. It's like the devastator and stuff. Look at the screen
my name is lesbo. Why do I always get gay boy? I don't understand. Why do they have
a gay boy vest? Everybody else's is just their names. What's your name? Okay. I remember
these one kids we didn't know and there's like this little fat kid with like like shaved
and
just don't know what to do. They're watching fucking Inuyasha going, "Am I tripping right
now?" I saw Tim and Eric when I was nine and that shit was weird as hell. That's why you
become so funny and weird. I don't know what those guys were smoking. That's why my brain
be weird. I watched the Oblongs and I decided to look like them. It was a really smart decision
by me. Apparently the government was using squid billies to turn people into serial killers
to
- I was saying this earlier,
I think I could be a doctor really easily.
I don't think it's that hard.
I think if you think of the dumbest doctor,
I'm definitely gonna be smarter than that guy, right?
So you can do it.
- Me and Branson could be doctors.
- You guys should be doctors.
- I would have loved to have a doctor duo.
- I would be a good specialist.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're special, all right.
- I think I'd be a good surgeon.
- You know, I don't have a doctor,
so I wouldn't mind one of you guys being my doctor.
I'll be your GP.
Oh, well, I didn't know you were in the running here.
Now, you guys are going to have to prove who's the best.
I mean, who among the three of you is the best doctor?
You're very sick.
You're about to die.
All right.
How many colors of blood are there?
You need my treatment.
There's two colors of blood.
When it's on the inside, it's blue, but then when it touches oxygen, it's red.
Okay.
Well, that's not a good diagnosis of what I have, though.
What color is your blood, Charles?
It looks like it's blue right now.
Should I cut it open and see?
Yeah.
It might turn red.
might
a
invasive procedure where we open up your stomach and look what's in there to see
if you ate anything that could have caused the cut. Oh like how they do to
sharks after they catch them? Exactly. We have to cut your chest open. We need to see if there's like a fender of a car in there or maybe a Boy Scout or a
giant tire because that could be very important. Okay I was about to go with
Patrick as my doctor but I think I'm gonna switch to Cameron. I got too many
patients already I don't give a shit. Charles you're going into cardiac arrest
right now and we need to cut you open and kiss your heart.
Okay let's do it.
I don't give a shit about any of my patients.
What?
I'm already a doctor and I don't care about them.
Oh I'm glad I picked a better doctor who cares about his patients.
Well I'm pretty much addicted to drugs.
Basically I say.
And have been compared to Sherlock Holmes often.
Every time that a patient comes in I prescribe them a middle finger and I say get the fuck
out.
Why would the fuck would you do that man?
Not my problem.
I don't think he takes being a doctor very seriously.
we just became doctors he's already burnt out
yeah basically i only use this shit to uh to get pills
what should i do all my friends in here in this call right now have uh poop disease
what?
what are you talking what is poop disease and am i okay?
no you have it you have poop disease i know you know
what is it what is the symptoms of poop disease?
uh basically there's a lot of shit okay
smells really bad
sounds really immature
and you all and you all
i think poop disease should grow up
you all start eating it because the disease mess.
No way.
No way Jose.
I'm not believing this Patrick likes eating it just as much as
he likes drinking pee though.
Not true.
That was Branson that likes drinking ice.
I didn't say I like it.
But you said he likes drinking pee.
You said you preferred neither Patrick.
It means you both you like both equally.
No, that's true.
That's true.
That's what you guys do.
That's not what it meant.
That's exactly what it meant.
What is your favorite?
I don't think me and Patrick are dumb at all.
Wait, I have a question again regarding that for Patrick and Branson.
What?
Do you guys not not like eating pee and poop?
I don't not not like eating poop.
Man, I'm glad Patrick started talking first.
Well, that's a triple negative, so I think it cancels out.
And how many is a triple?
Can you repeat the question?
I don't not don't not like.
like all right I don't I don't know if he's doing good or bad.
soaking his office chair with sweat right now. I don't not not don't not not like not.
I can hear the grinding. I just want to hear the question again. Do you not not
like eating pee and poop? Do I not? Also Pat didn't say yes or no. It's a yes or no
no question. I will say don't not not not statement. Don't you
need to understand yes or no. Alright. So if he said do you
like eating poop or pee? I'd say no if she said do you not like
eating poop or pee? I'd say yes and then if he said both, then I
guess I say no again. so my answer Andrew is uh is uh is
the gentleman's no. I think uh Branson had his fingers crossed
though when he said no Branson again doing rephrasing the
question to arrive at the word no. I'm holding my question three times to say no. I'm not
looking anything up. I was holding my boys. I think we get right out. Get out of podcast
and we tour the world showing everyone these two guys. That's right. Okay. I just before
we go before you go forward with that, I just want to say I don't don't not not don't not
don't like not don't eating poop.
I've never.
Don't eating poop.
That's what you like.
I like do not eating poop.
What the hell are you?
Do you sound like a fucking no song?
You're a weirdo.
Shut up.
You're a wacko.
You stupid as hell.
So because this is a Christmas episode, which clearly a bunch
of Christmas stuff this month.
I want I don't know what's up with that.
It's Christmas.
Maybe it's because it's the season.
Because it's Christmas.
I thought today the list we could cover is the timeless nice vs. naughty list of Christmas fame.
Santa's beautiful list. I think we could discuss.
Wait, wait, Tim. How did you get the naughty nice list?
I downloaded it from santa.com. I have the secret password, which is "presents".
I shouldn't have said that. I'm going to bleep that out.
You idiot!
I hope I don't forget to bleep out the secret password to santa.com.
If he bleeps it out, it was presence.
I might bleep that out too.
I might forget.
I might go to sleep the second we press stop recording and forget.
I'm sure all these people can just go find a torrent of the list anyway.
That's true.
It's true.
So, okay.
So, what kind of, I mean, are we just winging it or do you have names that you're going
to tell us?
Name names.
Oh, I just sent you guys all the lists.
So luckily it's not just on me to read it.
Okay.
I'm seeing it.
just received a copy of Santa's list dot txt. I sent it to to
to Branson at poop eater dot co dot uk. So that's you should
get that in your email and Patrick at stupidest on the
podcast of all t. I am. Yep. And then what's that? Can you spell
that? Oh and I just got mine into awesome. Caleb has SCX dot
and I also just sent the list to the two remaining guys are
married to each other at gmail.com.
Which one was I Andrew?
Are you looking at the picture of beers that Patrick sent earlier?
Yeah. Check that out.
Guinness Peroni, Hebden sweet tiger,
sending beers, receiving beers. Sounds like naughty behavior to me.
Let's see where you two are.
Oh, Oh,
I didn't even know there was a very naughty section of the list.
And I think I should change it to like the bad list
'cause naughty, you know, a lot of people use that
to have a sexual meaning. - Naughty is sexual as hell.
- Yeah, well, it's kind of open-ended, I feel like.
I think that's what makes the list so,
so it gives it staying power.
You can argue about it forever.
- You hear a lot in videos of just British women.
I don't know, I'm not gonna say what they're doing,
but they say norty a lot.
- Norty.
What kind of videos of British women are you watching, Andrew?
- They're kind of just hanging out.
- Austin Powers.
is
Austin Powers.
Oh, oh,
OK, I got
I was happy to hear that.
I got attacked.
I got attacked by a slime.
Did you have a marble in your mouth?
He's got a lot of cool.
Oh my God. You still do it.
I did.
That was a Kennedy.
That was a Kennedy half dollar.
That's expensive.
Those are that's like an annual release coin.
That's going to take you a while to get out of there.
That's as big as a coaster.
Oh, great. Now he's eating a USB stick.
Yeah, cool.
I'm addicted to eating metal.
You always have those.
Pica.
Yeah, Pica.
Whenever they talk about like Pica, it's always like people
just eating like styrofoam or like packing peanuts or yeah,
it's it's funny.
Yeah, you like I like an Xbox controller like every day.
It's
went to the bodega earlier to get a bunch of coins to eat.
I did.
I went.
Can you break a 20?
As possible.
They need to make a toilet paper you can eat just for people with Pica.
-True. -Kids' toothpastes, yeah.
Speaking of Pica, this is actually crazy.
The first entry on the naughty list is people with Pica.
-Whoa! -Whoa!
-Everybody with Pica is actually... -Very naughty!
Very naughty, disrespectful to small objects.
Hey, people with Pica, what the hell are you thinking?
Yeah, you gotta lay off.
-Yeah. -How about you?
-How about you, Pica? -No presents.
-You're getting your own size. -That's right.
If we're talking about naughty people I think Dennis the menace would be on the naughty
Yep, he's here. Wait, Branson. I thought you got that one more shot the one year
He was on the nice list and ever since then he's been blacklisted. Yeah, here's a shit a word Jack the Ripper. Oh
Yeah, naughty naughty. Not a good ass. Do you know it says the whole the whole the Ripper family is pretty
It's funny cuz I'm on the nice list here. It says Jack the hugger
or
it's
in the movie theater. I'm ripping farts. Oh yeah? Come on dog. What are you watching?
Uh Bigg's Mama's House. Bigg's Mama House. It's me and Patrick seeing movies together. We both
have full-size popcorns and full-size sodas. We're sitting next to each other and we're just ripping
farts while we're watching Big Momma's House 2.
And we're laughing so hard they stopped the movie.
We're laughing so hard that like the laugh makes a fart come out that's just like, it's
like man you gotta go to the bathroom and check that thing.
You know but the movie's so good.
Well you guys like to go to Tyler Perry movies.
You guys like going to Tyler Perry movies and doing Mystery Science Theater 3000 in them?
weekend. Yeah, you love that. You guys reserve the front row seats way ahead of time. White
guys, white guys with beards always be farting at the screen during the movie. We got a bunch
of dogs in there with us. They're my seeing eye dogs. They're barking what's in the movie
to me. It's really dark in here so I need six dogs to see. I learned them to watch movies
like Coco the Gorilla.
They're farting too.
It smells like dog food.
Coco the Gorilla just trying to explain the movie to me and Patrick but he keeps just signing
smells bad, smells good, smells poopy, smells one berry, one banana.
And that's why you guys are laughing so hard.
You think it's the funniest movie of all time?
The characters on the screen can smell our farts.
Coco the Gorilla just keeps fucking telling us.
Branson and Patrick are so stupid.
Coco the gorilla is their social worker.
It's true.
Cocoa, Cocoa, the gorilla comes over once a week to check my fridge
and make sure it's not just candy.
Yeah, Cocoa, the gorilla has to look through my internet history
to make sure I didn't accidentally get fished.
Yeah, one plus two, one plus three, Google search one plus four.
He was trying to count to 10.
And then he skips to one plus infinity once he kind of sees where it's headed.
Coco the gorilla signing, signing to me.
You Google the word Google a lot.
You Google the word being a lot.
Coco the gorilla just signed.
You don't have to Google Gmail.
It's in the top right corner.
You know who else I'm seeing on the naughty list here is a bad guys.
Oh, well, that's a no brainer.
Controversial, I think maybe a little bit.
There's I feel like there must be at least one bad guy
who's on the nice list.
Did antiheroes make the good or the naughty list?
Let's see.
Well, we have we have Darth Vader on the nice list.
That's interesting.
Well, I wouldn't call him an antihero.
He makes a change at the end.
How about this?
Jack Sparrow.
Pretty kind and funny, but boy, he sure is.
Yeah, let's where he's a scoundrel.
Honestly, I'm going to say something now that's kind of.
I guess, you know, not
contrary, I don't know if it's controversial where I told you before.
Oh, all right. Well, I'm going to say something different then.
I'd love to share a bottle of rum with him.
Oh, yeah, he'd he'd Bogart the whole thing.
He would. Why is the room going to do that?
They call it they call it depping it when you do it with.
Yeah, well, wait, did you guys have him at Jack's?
Was Jack's fair just in the call?
Where was it? What was that?
I just sound like exactly like Captain Jack go.
I want to see him.
Oh, my God, I was missing.
I was drinking this pint of rum and it's gone.
As Captain Jack Sparrow.
Whoa, it's a Christmas miracle.
Amber Heard is a liar.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Captain, I've always wanted to ask you this.
Did you sign off on that song that the Lonely Island did about you?
Was that was that cool with you?
or do you like?
Yeah, what?
Be like them now.
Fucking whatever.
Fucker.
Michael, fucking, fucking ass.
Michael, fucking freaky weirdo.
Yeah, that guy from France who is like a pedophile.
Michael, fucking he's so drunk.
Oh, that was me.
So, okay.
Oh yeah, Michelle.
Michelle.
Yeah, sorry.
I didn't saw the sign.
French.
Should have saw the signs
that that guy was up to something bad.
Yeah.
the
are
and the nice with it list.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Pam Anderson is on the naughty list,
but her boobies, but hole in the JJ are on the nice list.
And they're seriously small.
And was that we're all pulling our pants down.
Yeah. Oh, I might end up on the naughty list after I cream on my computer screen
thinking about these different holes of this woman.
Yeah, well, yeah, but not the rest of her.
That's I don't want to see her beautiful platinum hair.
That shit looks like shit to me.
I wanna see where she shits and I wanna spit.
Oh.
You're just in general? You're just-
I'm gonna s-
I have a system with women.
The spit shit spit system.
I spit where they shit.
And they spit it out and then I split 'em in two.
Damn, you sound like a real red-blooded fuck machine, Caleb.
I'm basically addicted to sex.
All these stupid bitches I spliches. He's got these sunglasses I've seen where he cut out the eye
They're just horse blinders and I'm like why you wearing those glasses that are horse blinders. He goes it's for fuck it
I go what cuz I fuck like a dog with this thing on I can only see you know what I'm working at
That's right. I only see I it's got
Two nipples and just a pube hair
They say 2020 - they were New Year's classes that he modified genius
Yeah, everyone calls them everyone calls him Caleb spits. That's right. Could I be spitting on the shitter?
Oh, he's spitting their shit and he's spitting. It's a man. It's a man
You know, I'm an audio list is cove in 19. Yes, sir
No, I'd be having sex with one of those big plastic bibs. Like I'm eating crab
When Caleb fucks he's got a guy who doesn't speak English following around with a mop, that's right. I got
The way the way I fuck I got I got those drain holes installed on my bedroom floor like they have in gym showers, dude
It's everywhere. Yeah. Oh, yes of gym showers also on the naughty list. He
Not a very good guy. No bad bad
the
yourself if you're in the if you're in the the the Academy, you know, I guess it was no better than anybody though
And I guess he wants his credit - yeah, I'm sure somebody gets him a president
It would be awfully sad if no one got Santa president speaking. Well, I didn't get a social credit
Xi Jinping naughty list. Mmm go figure. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Unfortunately, yeah, that's it. That's an upset
This year the nice list this year, you know who's on the naughty list is Oliver twist. Maybe you should stop stealing kid
That's right. That's right. I'm asking for more all the time. You're so greedy orphans wanting more gruel
I'm sick of these I'm sick of orphans. Listen, buddy. We all want gruel
Okay, of course I want your turn yeah, I can't get enough of that shit, but come on
Stop being so greedy. He's basically the original capitalist. He just wants more more more, you know, yeah, it's true
Why'd you go complain to your pimp the artful Dodger get the fuck out of my orphanage?
Mm-hmm. I'm also seeing here. The nice list is is Oliver twists or Oliver twists assassin is on here
Oh, oh man is planning to assassinate Oliver twist and it's going well. He was presents
He was like the third boss in the last Assassin's Creed
You just walk up you walk into the back of his little head and he dies.
He was a templar.
He hit him with a stick and he goes flying.
He splats against the wall.
The game totally glitches out.
He falls into a pot of gruel and it's like poetic.
There's your more gruel.
And he does the Terminator thumb.
They call him Oliver Twist because somebody needs to straighten his ass out.
Yeah, they figured out that he was going to be the next Hitler, even though Hitler didn't exist yet.
to be the first Hitler.
So someone had to kill him before he became Hitler.
Hitler was going to be the next Oliver Twist.
Yeah, exactly.
Adoliver, Adoliver Twistler.
You guys have ever heard of Adoliver Twistler?
Oh, what about alcoholic rule?
Oliver Twisted Tea.
Oh my God.
What about Pam Anderson?
I want to see all of her tits.
All two of them.
It's only two.
I want to see those tits twisted up.
I still say all of them.
That's right.
Yeah, who else is here? Let's see. NiceList, Robert Mugabe.
Cool. Good for him. NiceList.
He's been putting in the work. Yeah.
I'm not really sure who that is, but I just read it.
He has a funny name.
I think he's responsible for some stuff that was pretty good,
but I'm not an expert, but I am willing to say that without taking any repercussions.
I don't want to speak on the issue until I've done more reading, but I'm strongly in favor
of a lot of stuff that he did. I don't know the details, so I'm not calling.
Bob Marley, that's a no-brainer, drug addict.
Yep. Naughty.
Total junkie. Very naughty, Bobby.
Naughty list. Rodney Dangerfield's wife.
All right, boys, watch this, watch this. How about you respect your husband for once
in your fucking life? You fucking ingrate. What are you doing? This man's famous.
He had dealt Rodney Dangerfield dealt with so much trauma.
Yeah, when you know, the doctor asked him for a stool sample,
a urine sample in a blood sample and he was so stupid.
He brought in his whole underwear and just gave it to the guy.
That's disgusting.
Disgusting Rodney Dangerfield on the naughty list to mean is why
should I clearly had a mental disability?
Yeah, all of America just laughed at him.
Yeah.
When he handed his underwear to his doctor, his doctor was Patrick,
and Patrick said, I like to eat all these things that are on.
No, I was not his doctor.
I said, sorry, I've already eaten.
I just had lunch.
Thank you, though.
It was it was a poop burger.
He was a pooper with a bun, but I'm CA only.
And then he said, I'm I'm so dumb.
I thought it was a regular burger.
Yeah, that's what he said.
I think I said that.
Did you really?
I heard it was an evening burger.
So you got scared?
Yeah.
And you ate it out of fear?
Oh, my God, I saw that shit burger and I got so scared.
I ate it out of pure fear.
I thought it was going to come at me.
I had to get rid of it immediately.
I couldn't stand looking at it.
So I throw it in the trash.
It's still in there.
You know, it's waiting.
Could jump out of the trash.
It's basically the trash is what pirates used to use as a fridge.
Yeah, I mean, I don't have the facts to doubt that.
I think that's true.
The naughty list here,
it says Anton Yelchin.
I mean, whoa, why?
It seems a little why?
Why put that?
It's kind of that's really a sin.
I mean, he's not alive anymore.
There's no it's crazy.
Has a photo of his dead body and his his jeep's license plates
imprinted on his forehead like the Punisher's.
Well, what a Santa.
This is the Punisher at a ring.
Yeah, I remember the classroom that he always wore.
Yeah, oh, kind of rude.
He's like, I used to play football.
Yeah. And then on the other hand, he had a ring.
He actually had
to get angry.
And also he had a lot of different.
He had the one ring on it to his photo.
The Punisher's photo of the rings, actually.
Come on. Punishers muttering.
What color you think that was?
black jet black and red.
Yeah, with a skull in it too.
Yeah, yeah, it's moving a bullet.
Bright bullets came out of it.
Probably the color of it's probably a gun.
It's probably a black gun.
Yeah, bullets.
It probably killed a guy with it by making a meat it.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, it was covered in bacteria or something.
I'm not sure though.
It says here he is on the nice list because he was avenging
his family when he killed all that makes any ways.
So that's another antihero.
It's why he says nice.
He says I punish the bad people.
The class of 1984 will be avenged.
I'm basically like all cops.
That's why they like me.
He was actually a sick guy though.
It was really, I actually saw, it was a very embarrassing moment for him.
He was trying to kill me and I pointed at his mood ring and said he was silly.
And he turned red and he walked out the door.
Well I wasn't trying to kill you, did you kill one of his family?
Well, I mean, if you look on the audio, you are going to see I'm on here for
stealing candy.
Yeah, he pointed a gun at me on at the at the women's March.
Really?
Yeah, he was there making sure he was there.
He was thinking, you know, there's gonna be riots.
These people, they don't know what they want.
Really?
I'm gonna make sure and he put the gun in his in my mouth and it says I'm about avocado
toast and they just let me keep walking down the street.
I'm like, this guy's crazy.
Well, you freaked him out because he just started sucking on his gun.
the
this
that
a
jump big.
Well, yeah, I remember that a dirt bike.
They were jumping them.
Oh, that's sick.
He was already dead.
It was pretty sick.
I was so fucked up on soju.
I don't remember a single second and at the end of a limp biscuits set when they were
doing nookie and those cops showed up and arrested Fred Durst for rocking too hard.
Yeah, well, there was one group of cops that came in and arrested him for rocking too hard
and then it's completely separate group came in and arrested him for rapping too hard.
It was crazy.
He went free because it was double jeopardy.
You can't get caught up on two cops trying to arrest you at
the same time you get to go free.
That's one part of it.
Do you remember the crazy commercials before the movement
searches like Saturday, Saturday, Saturday in Washington
D.C. Like I didn't even want to go to it, but honestly, I
just got hooked by the commercials going on.
I felt like it was huge.
If you don't come down, you're a bitch.
And like Grave Digger was supposed to be there you guys remember that it was oh, I mean it got shut down so early
So I like I mean, oh, yeah
Almost riots, but they had after parties that they had we're fucking sick. Yeah, I mean, yeah
I'm a juice world there before you know before I be
He died
Yeah, but you guys realize the reason Grave Digger didn't perform is because they had a woman driving the damn car
I gave juice for all the bag of a bag of poison.
I thought the car was a woman.
That's what it was.
Yeah, I gave him a bag of poison before.
Damn, I gave him a bag of poison.
I said, don't take this.
This will kill you.
And he was like, I know what you mean.
And then I never saw him alive again.
But I saw him dead 400 more times.
Took him a long time to bury.
Yeah, it's like a weekend at Bernie's situation where you just hanging out for did you just
blink really fast? Yeah.
Well, they kept trying to bury him, but then they just would
hit something hit another person's coffin.
They go.
Fuck.
We got to retry now.
They were trying to give it.
Yeah, they're trying to give him a burial on the plane.
That was the problem.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're trying to bury him in a trampoline graveyard
where they buried all these.
Like an elephant grave.
of two-year-old trampolines that don't fit in the new backyard when you do.
They're lower in the property value. Yeah, the thing's missing about 30 springs.
It's no good. Lost its bounce.
Gonna take 10% off. Gonna take more to repair it than the
thing's even worth in the first place. That's where the gunfight scene takes
place in Con Air, isn't it? That field full of abandoned trampolines.
They're jumping, doing flips at each other. It was pretty sick, honestly.
I really like Malcolm Gladwell's essay about that called The Death of Fun.
Oh yeah.
True.
It hits hard.
Speaking of nice lists.
Malcolm Gladwell's naughty list.
What?
Yeah.
What'd he do?
Of course.
Looked like a weird freak.
He does look like a Muppet.
Yeah, but also the Dalai Lama made the naughty list too.
Yeah, well that's true.
He looks like he's been hooked up to an IV for like two years.
Malcolm Gladwell looks like an auntie.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Dalai Lama is on the naughty list.
Because I mean, you go to fucking you.
I saw I saw a picture of him at Berghain, which you're not supposed to have
pictures of the Dalai Lama with his stupid rules.
He's some guy. He's some giggly weirdo that laughs all the time.
Yeah, relax. Great.
Hanging out with Bill Clinton.
It's important to laugh. Shut up.
Yeah, you know, he laughs because he knows all their secrets about fucking.
I fucking hate the Dalai Lama.
What a well, you know, he was that astro world.
Oh, was he?
Yeah, why do you think it went so wrong?
I know he told all those kids to rush the stage.
He's doing Titanic prayers for them, too.
He said he stood up and he said, Hey, life's too short.
Yeah, I fuck it.
It says I mean, it's here also speaking to us.
Does Travis Scott nice list?
Not his fault. He had nothing to do with it.
It was the crowd's fault.
Oh, yeah, the crowd is on.
No, never claims the crowd.
And like there's some bad crowds or some crowds, you know, that that, you know,
the
*laughter*
Yeah, I don't get it.
We are all on the naughty list.
Yeah.
Except me.
Who's like the Hitlerialge podcast?
*laughter*
Actually, we're a good podcast. We don't have one.
I'll just say Paul-mub.
Yeah, yeah, that's true actually.
Yeah.
Safe bet.
You know, I see Satan here is on the nice list though, actually.
I don't think he was responsible for everything.
Well, you realize he used to be an angel.
Yeah, that's true.
to
a fallen angel. Yeah, and nobody prayed when he needed it the most. And people don't share
photos when it says like, "Like for Jesus, ignore for Satan." Yeah. People don't share enough of
those. He had like one wing, right? And like that big sword. Yeah. I think, yeah, that's him. And
like white hair. Yeah, yeah. And he was the main villain in Final Fantasy VII. Yeah. What are you
talking about? Huh? Chilling you. Not much. I'm just hanging out. Me too. Are we recording?
Not yet. Not yet. I think we're gonna start soon. Yeah. Alright. Alright, welcome to the
second annual Riffsmith. Wait, it's a Robin Williams Riffsmith. Oh, right. I forgot about
that. Oh, oh. Let's see. Robin Williams, naughty list. He stole his talent from the world.
and uh... dane cook i think
any uh... suck the over the plot out
is your evidence you've been in the people of the earth and and and
selfishly went to live in heaven
how long i'm robin williams and stuck in a room with five gay men all
uh... no i have not one of them i'm not one of them all you have to do to be
good improv is just abuse cocaine for thirty straight years
yeah like a and big surprise it caught up with them
I don't think it did.
Hey, right?
Yeah, I think it was the movies.
He started his bicentennial man.
He started doing all those depressing movies.
No more Mork and Mindy or whatever.
No more Flubber.
Maybe if you did Flubber too.
He did Hooseline like once every four years.
That's not enough to keep you alive.
That's true.
If you have the access to be on Hooseline
and you're not using it every year, you're fucked up.
You are fucking up.
Like Colin Mochrie and Ryan Stiles
are going to live to be 200 years old.
Yeah,
Robin Williams.
He actually killed himself the day when he was recording the
voice lines for Aladdin.
He got to the scene where Jafar turns into the giant evil
genie went home and he killed himself right after that.
John, he did.
They had to get a voice.
I said you said you said the J word, you know, you don't like
the J word pet which one Jafar or giant or gene.
Oh, it's all of them.
Just not J.
It's not J.
It's not trying to the G.
No.
We gotta stop.
He's getting really he's physically getting hurt now.
He's holding up that blanket and his hands are just
trembling sucking his thumb through the blanket.
Oh my God, that's really gross.
Sucking it through the blanket.
You don't do that.
Matt.
Do you have a do you have a glory hole in your door that
you suck your own thumb through?
What is that?
Well, I don't want to suck my own thumb.
And if I put the if I put it through the hole, it's somebody else's thumb.
Yeah, because I forget where it went.
It's called your scorey hole.
Yeah, it's what I use when I get scored.
I just imagine like a rapper bragging me like she's through the blanket.
Damn, that's sick.
Isn't that a like a Hasidic Jew thing?
Don't they throw a hole in a blanket?
Now, is that a stereotype or is it true?
I don't I don't think that could be.
Does it matter?
Get a little friend.
Yeah, you know what?
I don't mean to be stereotypical, but I think Jews go to the synagogue on Saturday.
I'll say I want to be honest, but, you know, I think I get a lot of trouble
if I was ever in a situation where I was allowed to ask a Jewish man
a lot of questions about Judaism.
I don't think I'm overwhelmed.
No, I don't think they'd like a lot of my sincere earnest questions.
Might be a Frost Nixon.
I mean, that's it.
It might be a movie because my life is true.
Yeah, I guess there's life is a movie, dude.
Basically true every single day.
Just you just hang around all day, sit in your big computer chair
and get sweaty and get used to it.
And then you go to bed.
You guys think about like, man, I get to do like my dream job
with my friends like every week and I'm practically a god.
the
equipment manager for like the end of the toilers and do a little bit of heroin.
That's my I think I want to be in a Lego set, dude.
I'm moving to a Lego set. Yeah, really?
Like I'm going to be like one inch tall like pie.
That'd be cool.
Rock Raiders or some shit old school.
You get big lost in a big Tupperware forever.
Yeah, with all my home. Yeah, you just have like 12
is a homies like some some kid that looks like me or Patrick is just gonna eat your ass.
Only thing to play with is like a part of a of a control board for a Star Wars ship.
Yeah, it's a flat piece. Yo dude, this one kid left me some playdoh. That's what's up.
Dude, I'm stuck here with a girl with a ponytail and Jar Jar Binks. I'm doing pretty good.
My life a Lego set.
(laughing)
My life a Lego set for real.
Direction's been lost though.
Damn.
Sorry, did I get too personal?
Yeah, I might be missing a few pieces.
Yo, my wife
be like a Lego set cause she's got
a mini figure. She's petite as hell.
Oh.
Is that good? Okay.
And she got a cylindrical head.
With the round edges.
My girl so yellow she looks like a Simpsons.
Her boobs are drawn onto her flat body.
Frowny face.
Yeah, my girl got four holes in the back.
And holes in her feet too.
How else is she supposed to sit down?
It'd be cool to be a Lego man.
I would hate it.
It's an air on my damn head.
Come on.
Now you don't have elbows so you can't scratch your nuts.
That's right.
That's what I need to scratch my nuts.
You got to clip your beer into your hand.
Like fuck like every time I got to scratch my nuts.
That'd be great though.
Clipping your beer into hand in your hand.
You're like, Oh no, you guys already, you guys already had to do that for Patrick.
Or I'll see what you guys will be able to drink a beer.
We do Ed, we do Edward water hands with Patrick every day so that he actually
It's just easier to clip beer into your hands.
Duck taping water.
It just snaps into place Patrick, you can do it.
We did Edward Water, we tried to do Edward Water hands, he didn't understand it so we
had to change it to Patrick Water hands.
Yeah, because it's my middle name, I don't know why you guys were calling me Patrick,
or Edward.
Oh you forgot your name!
You just forgot your name Patrick.
Well yeah, you were saying my middle name and then I thought it was my first name.
Quick, Patrick, what's your social security number?
023...
There's no way he's gonna get it right.
He doesn't even know it!
I almost said the real one.
I almost said the real one and I had to stop.
We got at least two real digits there, maybe three.
Cameron had to hit the shock ankle bracelet.
I'll probably forget, if you guys ask him again, we could probably get the middle numbers
is
The first. It's easy.
That's one one one one.
So the first number.
All right. Well, OK, well, watch this.
Branson Spell, Mississippi.
In my SSI SSI PPI.
Well, did you do it wrong on purpose?
I thought it was pretty good.
That was a decent that was a decent.
Three S's in a row.
I know. That's just how I know.
I just thought I should.
MSPSISPI.
You added an extra S in there.
You said it wrong.
I can type it.
Hold on.
Patrick's laughing really hard and then he goes MIPI.
See, that's typing.
Right?
Well, now you've got it because you had like a minute to type it up.
Mipapissy.
Whatever.
I'll spell it right now.
M-I-P-P-I-D-T-I.
No, make him spell something different.
You've got T's in there.
Well, now you've got it, because you had like a minute to type that.
Mipapissy.
Whatever.
I'll spell it right now.
I got it.
I-P-P-I-T-T-I.
No, make him spell something different.
You've got cheese in there.
OK, Pat, spell or pronounce E-W-O.
Wow.
Pronounce A-W-O.
Ow.
E-W-O.
Yo.
A-W-O.
Wow.
I-W-O.
E-O.
T-W-O.
Wow.
The other Washington DC the one on the west coast the capitalizing your state, okay capital, New York is Albany
Branson we have any last-minute nice
Before we wrap this up here you have naughty list. Yep you face. Mm-hmm
Every list all naughty, all naughty, all night.
It said, but it's but it does say the fans of the podcast even more naughty.
Yeah. So kind of we're still possibly naughtiest.
Yes. Yeah. So basically, fuck all of you.
Yeah. Yeah. Basically, eat my crud.
And hey, from Potabella Lista to Episode one, Mary, Merry Christmas.
You filthy animals.
Yeah. I didn't think you guys were going to go there.
I hope you all get to did to prop your your feet up.
Eat some yuletide ham and watch when you get to watch Die Hard.
And don't forget unwrapping the damn presents on Christmas morning.
That's right.
Seriously, don't forget to do that, Branson.
Do what?
Don't forget to do what?
Open the presents.
No, if you get a puppy in there, it's gonna die if you don't unwrap it.
You have to wrap the puppy?
I already wrapped the puppy.
Alright.
Bye, everybody.
Merry Christmas.
Bye bye.
Ho ho ho ho ho.