Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughter)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- We're recording now.
- I had a pull in spring energy before this.
- Don't talk about anything except
your fucking face right now.
I know that you knew we were recording today
and you were like, I wanna have something,
I want the whole episode to be about me.
- I have a new joke.
- And you started shaving your face.
- It's not true.
I want to look like I have syphilis. I'm gonna get much I've been watching
Deadwood. You look like a guy that fucking Sherlock Holmes punches in slow
motion.
Why is that? I reuse my bit from before the I do it. You look like you're you
just got off a fucking crabbing boat. He was better the first time. Yeah, I know
He does look like a... You look like you're a Deadliest Catch.
Yeah, you look like a Deadliest Catch. I've never heard that.
We're here with Gavin Matz. What up?
Gavin Matz is with us, a beautiful, beautiful friend and stand-up comedian.
And Patrick, you know we really wanted to make the whole episode about him.
And I only have one joke for everything.
So I have to reuse it.
What possessed you to do this?
I was looking at the... I was trying to grow out the beard long and then I looked at it
and I was like, it's too big.
- And then you're like, what's the visual gag here?
- Yeah.
- But how did it make this--
- I did, I had it like Lemmy.
I had it like connected and then I fucked it up
and then just like--
- RIP.
- Yeah, exactly.
RIP Lemmy.
It was my tribute to him.
- So it's not his anymore.
- True.
- Did he kill himself?
- True, I could take it.
- Who?
- Lemmy.
- He probably killed himself with alcohol.
- Yeah.
- Lemmy.
- I feel like he, I think he overdosed.
- Alcohol's not a funny way to kill yourself.
- No.
- No, it's probably a fun way.
I find it funny. What do you think the funniest way to kill yourself is?
Funniest way to kill yourself? Probably a bunch of, probably a balloon.
Yeah. Probably heroin. No, no. You guys don't think that's funny?
I mean, I think, what's his name? The politician guy on TV. Bud Dwyer.
Bud Dwyer, that was funny. I guess it's pretty good.
Yeah. Okay, okay. What do I have about, but this is trademark. Nobody fucking
and steal okay, okay, slip my wrist in a ice bath, full shrinkage. Oh
whoever finds me there's a one last laugh
like I gave it all his diet dicks.
Yeah, that'd be a bad version of like the Whitney Houston like bathroom photos
of after you're dead. You just like your little tiny, my little
it's like the smallest pixelation.
I usually have to use this one. Yeah,
yeah, I mean, but have some respect, you know, give me a big pixel. Yeah,
one big
that goes out. It goes like over the
there's like a weird, there's weird grooves in it. Yeah, it's like it's like
it like a like a drawing of a penis, but like a black bar, it's got like two
balls. Yeah, somebody did it on the snapchat thing. Yeah,
I screen shot it. It brought it to snap chat drew it in. I'm going to be real
my my Dick's going to be pretty small even no matter where they find me. If I
die on like a tropical beach, I'm still going to have a pretty small cock.
What I think my balls yeah long as you live. Yeah, exactly how you small
little small penis, just a head. It's been so cool, but it's young hog.
I got a pig. I got the run
grow though you just got to treat them right and make sure he's nourished. Speaking of
pigs you look like you fucked them right now Tucker. You look like your dad fucked one
and you came out actually. You look like Robert Pickman right now. Robert Pigman? Pickman.
Now that's a serial killer from the Vancouver. Oh yeah you look like H.H. Holmes. No no no
this is a specific serial killer who only killed prostitutes and he fed them to pigs
pigs and he had a pig farm. Really? And they found out. They didn't call him the pig man?
They probably did. It's right there. Pig man, pig man. Fuck. Y'all need to step it up over
there. And we need to find our girls. He fed the prostitutes to pigs? The pigs are probably
so happy. Or sex workers from the downtown east side in Vancouver, where I'm from. A
Canadian serial killer yeah sorry I didn't know you had it in you sorry
about that sorry about killing all the women I guess
yeah you have a lot of hogs so it makes sense damn this gets expensive feeding
all them don't fucking come for us like that mm-hmm
you have hogs letter Kenny
my bad my bad letter Kenny what else we take back we said drive our boys damn
true little mosque on a prairie we're doing the Muslim shit early oh really
you guys were back in the Muslims early before the rest of the world was
fucking with them yeah no yes nobody was fucking with them like we were but you
guys are out there on the CBC caping for him yeah yeah on the fucking Kim's
convenience name all the Canadian corner guess
Oh corner gas oh shut up a brand right now Brent but what a crazy name one of
the best ever did one of the best ever do I look like my name is Bretton but no
you don't shut up all right stop that I thought I could get it looks like his
name is Brent but right now more like Brent butter dude come back from the
cluster also I mean it's just also like you didn't even do them right right now
like it's like a fucking it looks like I took an eraser tool to your beard like
it's not manicured on the sides yeah I think when I get home I'm gonna fix it
it's also hilarious you have orange mutton chops mm-hmm but it was like you
to lend Caleb your Waffle House hat that is true
yeah you make a lot when you're the general manager of true this Brooklyn
has actually my stepdad is general manager of a Waffle House how do you
I think I get the hat so maybe show some respect.
Like that could be my Canada, you know?
Alright, well fuck your stepdad's waffles.
I'm going to go in there and put my elbows on the table.
That's legal. It's not illegal to be...
That's manners.
Do they have manners in the waffles?
No, you can do way worse shit at a waffles.
Oh damn.
Yeah, you can cue Courtesy of the Red, White, and Blue
on the touch tunes 15 times.
Did you do that? No.
It did play when we went.
They have a setting you can do on touch tunes
the same song like twice in a row and at Waffle House they have it turned off so you
just play the same song over and over again. Speaking of the red white and blue
isn't that every flag? True. Why are you coming for America so like right off the
bat? I invite you into my home which is in America. Well the Canadian
flags that's red and white right? Yeah.
- I wish I, oh, if you don't have blue,
you're lashing out. - You need a third color.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You guys, you and the Poland flag.
- You got what, you got what, one leaf on it?
You're never gonna guess how many stars we have.
- I thought those were leafs too.
- And that's plus the stripes.
- One star, dude, we're a lone leaf.
- You're not a lone leaf. - Canada, we're Texas, bro.
- You're not Texas.
- We're bigger than it.
- That's true. - Yeah.
- That's hard to dispute.
- How many Texas's can you fit in Canada?
multiple. Okay, yeah. That's a good estimate. Close to many. Are you from the city part?
Are you city slicker or are you from that there country part? I'm a city slicker. Yeah,
you ever go out of that there country part of Canada? It scares me. Yeah? I need noise.
Oh, not enough noise out there? The hogs chomping out a prostitute's face isn't enough noise
for you? The snarling? No, man, I need noise, bro. I sleep with a sound machine. You do?
sounds just white noise dude we're just don't need noise never black noise if I
want that I'll go to a movie you never you don't ever turn on like that's good
dude that's off the bat hate America black people are loud that's a good
That's a really good start Gavin. Yeah you're crushing it. What's next?
Fuck them prostitutes. Have you always done white noise? Did you sleep with the TV on or
something? No I can't do the TV. No? No. I don't like to lose my place in the show you know.
you know what true put on the show we had Matt lock on when you came in all right
watch a mat lock and then we turned into we tuned into the to the channel that
said there was a show those it was just called rape you know there oh wow well
there's a show I can fall asleep to it's on they used to be on Bravo's called a
red shoe diaries but that's not a false see right after I fucking bust one open
yeah you don't know right she carries now all right maybe you guys are too too
too young, maybe before your time. I mean I'm not much older than you, but it was
like a show where it was like softcore porn. Oh, okay. Yeah, on Bravo.
On Bravo? Yeah. You get Hallmark. It's like an anthology series. Each episode is
different, but it's always like some like softcore porn. And then there's one
episode I jacked off. It had the scary guy from Prison Break on there. Oh, the
little guy? He's looking good. Yeah. You don't see shit though. You don't see it.
you see nipple you do see male or female both yeah
yeah I say Bravo to that I thought Bravo was like a kid like basic cable I didn't
know you could put yeah it was basically like 2 a.m. you know put nipples on 2 a.m.
baby this is Canadian Bravo that's true yeah I didn't consider that in West Coast
time mm-hmm so you're gonna shit early yeah 1130 p.m. bulls you in a nipple
that's early that's disgusting nasty that's too early way for a secret stash
in Comedy Central to be on and then you can do it there's no nipple on that
either yeah I know we didn't I don't think just that you could you could say
everything up to shit oh yeah that's a fudge or show a nipple yeah that was
huge. Yeah, that's fucking gay bullshit. They had the... Did you say that out there? I didn't
have Comedy Central growing up. No? No Comedy Central in Canada. It's called the Comedy
Network. Yeah. And it's just for last gags. Oh yeah, the little green guy? That little
green guy. He's funny. He's funny as fuck. He's funny as hell. He's cancelled. He's cancelled.
What? What did he do? He's a sex pedophile. He's a sex pedophile? He's the sexiest pedophile
all time. Oh, I just think we got to start putting categories on these pedophiles. Of
course. I just I'm tired of the of the umbrella of putting them all under the same umbrella.
Right. Yeah. So what are the different types? Sex pedophile, just a regular guy. You know,
favorite pedophile the guy who's like as 17s an adult oh isn't it actually in
Canada no no no I don't know I thought don't you isn't the isn't like the TV
rating like something 17 or no that's that's the NC 17 a 17 Peggy 17 oh yeah
yeah sixteen that's that's that's the UK that's a video game yeah that's also yeah
I'm 16 everybody loves but stuff now keep going I don't like but stuff man
you know when they pull it when you got to get your prostate out you can't get a
full erection anymore that's not true yeah it's all in the balls you idiot huh
it's in the balls, your your erections, maybe mostly in the wiener. I would say
I mean you don't my you don't get a fully hard do my. I haven't gotten a fully
hard one, then that's why I get their ball taken off. What I'd rather have
that than their prostate out really. I'm not sure
I'm making this up. Yeah, dude, I'm not. I'm not a doctor. I'm just riffing. I
know you fell asleep on the Wikipedia page for
so and I had a really beautiful to read a venture. That's like when you fall
fall asleep with a book on you and you continue to read yeah yeah yeah. Well,
you kind of dream about the exactly you're going on an adventure. Every
book is really gay. That's like
I feel like a great Tom Sawyer. I think the rest of the book is me fucking
Huck Finn,
bending him over the fence
and me yelling I'm Huck in it.
I've been falling asleep and having dreams about succession where I'm in one of the
brothers.
Yes, really?
Yeah.
That's cool.
Dude, I'm in there dominating.
Are you doing well?
Dude, the dad loves me.
Are you like an extra brother?
You're the only son I like.
I'm Caleb.
That was your impression of him?
I'm Caleb Roy.
Do that again?
You're the only son I like.
What?
That's what he sounds like.
Listen up, kid.
You're the only son I like.
He's got a transatlantic accent.
Listen up, kid.
You're the only son I like.
He's got a transatlantic accent.
accent. You're one in a million. You're one in a million. You know that accent, that transatlantic
accent, they did it because they were trying to combine British and American accents.
So it was easier to hear on the radio.
For Universal, but now they're just like, whatever, where we make the most money is China.
We'll just dub it.
So you think they should do a new one that's between American and Chinese?
Transatlantic, I don't believe in this.
no
the other i mean it's technically still we could just
combine chinese and american accents and i mean technically is still across the
atlantic
the long way you might be the biggest genius in the world but he's also
transatlantic phobic
sure he's like i hate
i hate jimmy stewart
he did not even know i don't understand it sounds like that when he was born
yeah
the put on
making that up
That's 1920s gay voice.
Definitely.
Yeah, whatever the actors are doing.
This is really still people, right?
No.
This goes to one guy in Minnesota
and he
sends us money.
Hell yeah. He sends us like $16
and a bunch of cookies that his mom
makes and they're so fucking good.
I wish that was actually true. I would love to have
a benefactor. Oh yeah.
We have a lot of benefactors.
No, I want a benefactor. I want a one rich benefactor.
I want a big Saudi prince who's obsessed with us.
Probably little, but yeah.
You guys don't have? You guys didn't get?
No. You have a benefactor?
No. I want to have a big titty lady that I leave all my money to.
What? You want to have a benefi?
Sure.
What's a benefi?
I'm guessing that's the opposite of a benefactor.
Benefactor's a guy.
If you're the benefactor.
You're thinking it's benefactress.
No. Yeah. No. A benefit? A benefit. Oh, whoa, chill. I think they're all benefactors. Yeah,
but I just need, I need somebody to be giving me money for no reason. Yeah. Take me out.
You're looking for like a sugar dad. Yeah, but I don't want to fucking kiss him. Well,
you don't have to with most of them. What? Is that true? Yeah. Some of them just walk up to me.
They're bad at conversation. Yeah. I can deal with that. It's kind of like,
they're like a lot of there's a lot of sugar daddies they're just trying to like
grind it out like a runescape just small battles in 99 99 persuasion skill no
rich guy would want little old me though I'm so ugly you don't know that I think
I think that's what they like. I said I'm so because I think kids are ugly.
Well I think if you were hot they wouldn't want to be your sugar daddy.
They'd want to fuck you. Oh true. I think they're looking for like ugly people who...
I'll financially dominate someone. Yeah. How much money do you have? Hell I could do that.
How much right now? Yeah. Like 12 grand. Can I take that? No.
Can I take that? I'm not very good at this. But did you get a boner a little bit?
I also feel like that's not a lot of money to admit that you have.
Yeah?
What are you talking about?
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
What are you talking about?
You didn't lie.
I might as well just say a number and you said the amount of money you have.
Like 12 grand.
That's so much money.
You're rich.
You have to leave.
That's a down payment on a hundred thousand dollar house.
I'm sick of having this one percenter in here.
on a hundred thousand dollar house.
You could buy a twelve thousand dollar sandwich with that.
Yeah, you could buy twelve thousand dollar anything.
I know he's taking us to Salt Bae's place after this.
True, or twelve thousand one dollar sandwiches.
Would you rather have a twelve thousand dollar sandwich or twelve thousand one dollar sandwiches
Patrick?
I'd have twelve thousand one dollar sandwiches because I could resell them for a few dollars.
I don't like the keeping the wine thing. People have a wine and they're like, "This is from
the 80s." I don't think the 80s was a great wine making decade. I feel like the expensive
stuff's older, right? It's older? It's like the 50s, right? I don't remember. They had
a big chart on the wall when I worked at the liquor store as a giant and it showed you
all the years that you're supposed to drink wine from and all the years you're not supposed
to drink it from. Yeah, because it's all crazy. This tastes good. It's from when people didn't
have rights. Well it's funny because there's like what like spots in the
middle where it's like clean white hands yeah it'll be it'll be like like oh this
is old enough that's delicious or like this is like great but then there's a
spot in between it's like this is disgusting do not drink it. Well yeah
it's like wine the wine is only really good every like six years yeah depends
on like the weather yeah it's crazy yeah all this crazy stuff like the weather
now is climate change the wine is it's all warm yeah it's getting better every
year. What if that just makes it good now? What if like climate change is like only
happening so wine can get better? I don't think that's the reason it's happening
but I do think we'll see a lot of really good things in the next couple of years.
Yeah I think food will get really good. We gotta put our heads together and invent
something. Mm-hmm yeah okay for what? Wine in a can. Need to patent something?
I'm a twenty seven year old man. I need to patent something. I need to trademark.
I mean you're talking to basically an invention master right now.
We do a lot of work with inventions.
I would say maybe like a...
I need to go back in time and invent candles.
That would be fucking killing it.
That would be good.
Even the guy who made candles didn't like get anything out of that.
He did it for the love of the game.
Yeah, well he was getting like a ton of like royalties or whatever and then someone else
invented birthday candles and that like fucked him over.
they're like this is technically different yeah yeah what about the
candle maker when like electricity started popping off he's just sitting
there like fucking bullshit I'm burning my house down it doesn't smell this is
bullshit well yeah where's the disgusting slime the last time where's
the good nobody's gonna buy this the last candle maker that's a a24 film yeah
that guy kills he's losing his mind yeah yeah I bet those first light bulbs had a
smell to it. It's Willem Dafoe. Oh my god, if you imagine the trailer he-
Oh my god. The ending shot. The music is going to the rhythm of him like chopping up candles and stuff.
And then the ending shot is he blows out a candle. He explodes. Oh my god. Yeah, yeah.
Ooh, after he explodes like some kind of like- Oh, he's a terrorist. Oh yes. He's a fucking terrorist, yes.
Everybody's like, oh we're gonna go hang out at this place with electricity.
Bro, my boy Edison's down the street right now. He's like, is he? He's trying to assassinate Edison.
yeah yeah and he's using like it be there are guns, but he's using dynamite yeah
like what he's that he invented the candle and he also invented the like the
cup on a string telephone the horse carriage yeah yeah just like every
yeah he's getting fucked bow and arrow - they're like paving the roads he's got
cobblestone. He's like no. He invents everything one day before the better thing comes up.
Yeah. I finally got my patent. Ah fuck! Yeah. On cobblestone on the road. Cobblestone's already
like been around. He didn't have the intuition or the foresight to just be like are you homesick?
Here's what Ireland smells like. He writes it on the candle. True. Well actually candles started
coming back when they started when people yeah because everyone's homesick now
yeah yeah so here's a candle company that we're all gonna get ads for now
homesick candle yeah yours smells like fish yeah yours smells like the the rust
tinge for a fishing boat so they may water they make those for theme park
rides would you say Manchester by the sea yeah they make scented candles for theme
park rides. You can get like the E.T. ride at Universal in a candle. Whoa.
And like... There's one it's a kidnapping. Yeah. Kidnapping at Small World.
He stole a child. Whoa, that's what I thought that ride was. Never been on it, but I
thought that that somebody told me once that those were like lost kids. Oh yeah.
E.T. the ride? Trapped there. No. Small World. Oh, Small World. You ever been on E.T. the ride? I've never been on Universal. Those are all children's lost souls. Yeah, yeah, they're
they're trapped. I mean that's what animatronics are in general. They're
souls trapped into a machine. I kind of believe it's true. A lot of people
died and that's why I mean you ever watch this new Nick. You ever watch
this new movie. You ever watch this new Nick Cage movie where he's he's like
a Chuckie Chucky's Wonderland. Oh yeah, he's Wonderland and then there I've
only seen the trailer, but there's a good I was like I'm not going to watch
this shit. I get it looks cool. There's just there's the one line from the
apparently the girls like he's not trapped in there with them. They're
trapped in there with him. I heard about that. So various they couldn't
they couldn't afford Nick Cage. He doesn't speak a single word in the
movie. He's he's the main character. He has no lines and then at the end
they have a needle drop of free bird, which
millions of dollars. He doesn't wait. He doesn't speak at all in the so
they could afford to get him in the movie, but they could afford to make
it. Yeah, and then they like it had to that's what people are saying like
probably money like like an insanely expensive like like it's just like they
were like finishing out the budget with like the most expensive song of all
yeah, they're like yeah, we'll get in the cage, but he won't talk that's so
sick for a speaking role crazy three birds only song Patrick listens to
you. That's a visual joke. You look a little confetti did yeah, yeah, we
paid a great yeah, my show in Portland last week. There's a guy came to the
he was a PA on pig nice and one of his jobs on the movie was every day he told
me every day he had to bring a new rotisserie chicken to Nick Cage's room
at his hotel. I was like this guy's awesome that's sick no wonder Willy's
Wonderland couldn't afford him. They didn't have fish.
- I'm doing Mr. Bean all the fucking things.
- You got full chicken wings.
- Yeah, that's why Mr. Bean never talked to you.
- He's full.
- You need a hundred more pounds for me to talk.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Can I get a hundred more pounds?
- Dude, rotisserie chicken a day,
that is a grown man's diet.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- I haven't had one in a minute.
- Dude, I'm on day--
- I'm honestly, I'm thinking maybe find a spot
that has rotisserie chicken after this.
I worked at a deli for like three months and one of my jobs was to do the
rotisserie chicken, so I was like I can never eat this again.
Everybody always says that but then they always worked at like the most delicious
place ever. Safeway. Yes, you like Safeway. People will be like oh yeah I worked at
Cold Stone I can never eat the ice cream there. It's like dude it's just I mean
like why? It's ice cream. Of course there's like huge amounts of milk and like
disgusting shit in it. It's still good. It's ice cream. The one I will say I never want to
work at McDonald's. You haven't even worked there and you're oh you're saying
because you don't want your food ruined. I do feel like if you
see the process that they make food with at McDonald's and you're like
surprised, I think you're stupid. Yeah, well I mean just like I don't
want to know how long like the chicken McNuggets sit in the little heater.
That's what I mean if you're like you should assume that it's all like three
years old and made from mold. If I see it, it ruins the magic. I'm not getting
surprised. I go search out the videos.
Every few weeks a tweet will go viral. It's like this is how
they make the food at Burger King. They take a burger out of the freezer and
people are like whoa. It's like yeah come on. It's obvious.
The Little Caesars one went viral but it's like how the fuck else do
think you get a $5 hot and ready. Yeah. They had like two like a drill that had
like a big spin thing like a big like whisk attachment. It's called hot and ready it's
not hot and ready and fresh. Yeah. Yeah exactly. It's like a hot and good. Shake things literally
you fucking idiot. Two adjectives that's all you get. Well I fell asleep watching that
McDonald's movie where the guy eats 30. Super sized meat. Yeah I fall asleep I start dreaming
I'm fucking this guy while he's housing down Big Macs.
That one is that's a movie so many so many they used to show us that in health
class. Yeah, they would show it to like probably like once every other week and
health. I go I'm gonna go get some McDonald's right now. That's exactly
what I mean. Yeah, right. Funniest thing is there's a guy who so there's a guy
who did like a rebuttal documentary that was called like super lie to me or
something and he goes to McDonald's every day, eats every meal there but loses
weight and he's like, "See, it's because I'm, you know, McDonald's is healthy but
he's eating like a salad and like a tonic water and that's it."
Every single meal and it's like, yeah, you're eating 800 calories a day, of
course you lose weight. Yeah, and he's like, "See dude, McDonald's is
fucking beast." I love when there's anything happens and then someone's like,
I'll do the other thing and then they're like defending a company.
Yeah, that's exactly what it was.
Yeah, same with Doug Benson.
Yeah, he was defending.
He was defending. He was defending McDonald's too.
I know, but then it's like, whoa, have you ever talked or listened to Doug Benson?
Right.
Shit sucks.
I'm anti-weed now.
Yeah, that is kind of how that movie makes you feel, because also it's like this guy,
his brain has been so rotted by weed that he honestly thinks that like people want to watch
just like an hour and a half of a high vaporizer and I've been on getting dug
with high I did like this like 420 show and that's like the last time I smoked
weed because I was like I can't be around this guy. You were like I hate getting dug.
I hate weed. Look at what this weed is. I hate getting dug dude. I'm never getting dug again. I got dug hard. This guy's dugging me out here.
I look like a goddamn fool.
I know a lot of people have gone on that show and had like full-blown panic attacks. They
get so fucking high.
That used to be a form of entertainment. You'd be like, you'd want to get so high that you
just like, man, I was so high.
Yeah.
That's crazy. And that was like our lives.
But that was before all weed was evil.
Monetization.
Yeah. Like every dispensary has like the most evil strain of weed of all time.
Yeah.
It's like GMO weed or some shit.
- If I buy weed, I mostly just buy it
from the gas station near me.
- Yeah, you get like a--
- 'Cause that I know is--
- You get like the Thanos Runtz pack.
- Is guaranteed to be bad weed.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You're like, I need some shake.
- Exactly.
- I can only smoke shake.
If I smoke that gas, dude, I'm like--
- I can't.
- I grew up on gas.
Like, I don't smoke that BC Bud.
I don't smoke that Seth Rogen.
- You gotta try shake, dude.
- So that's why I was like, I'm done with weed.
I smoked it all.
- You gotta try shake.
- Everyone's like, weed is crazy.
I was like it's always been crazy. No, I took like I did just hit in the bong one
time and I took I took eight t3s Tylenol with codeine and I sat in an electric
drum set for four hours just playing one with one hand my other arm was in a
sling and just playing like don't don't like I and I was laughing because I
thought it was the law and order theme song. I was like this isn't productive.
That's gonna ruin my life.
It is so awesome when you're like, when you're a kid and you're getting like just insanely high and then you sit down at like a keyboard or like a drum set or something and you just think you're Dr. Dre.
Like I feel the music dude. I understand the 808s now.
Dude I used to like, I used to get like, like one, like pretty much like one nug of weed and then like not break it up and just like smoke that through a can.
So cool dude.
That was, that was the only time I ever felt good getting high.
- Smoking through cans.
- Smoking through an apple.
- I did apple.
- Making a third bong.
- Oh dude, I did apple way too long.
- Like the Shasta Cola three liter bong.
- Yeah.
- That shit, I made so many of those.
- We used to smoke out of a guy that I knew at a hookah.
- Smoke out of a guy.
- And we would do it.
(laughing)
- With the weed in his mouth.
- No, come on, are you serious?
You think I'm sucking dick?
- That's nasty.
- No, smoking out of a hookah,
the straightest thing you can do.
- Bro, the human body doesn't even work like that.
- It doesn't, you don't even know about it.
so long for it to go yeah what do you think this is one of those bugs bunny cartoons?
well dude it goes into the belly of the cat. You let the smoke blow out of bugs bunny's cock?
it's the best way to smoke it i heard i heard that on getting dug
with hi just calling it getting dug is
dude because the name is backwards yeah he's so high he can't even spell a couple of junkies
down at the Myrtle Wyckoff stop getting dug. I was so dug dude. Me and my boy Nebby
we we rolled a bunch of joints like 30 joints and we're going to a concert so
we put them in our fucking boxers so we could sneak him in but we were real high
and then we were in line for Wiz Khalifa and we were just like let's just go and
we left. We went and ate food and and watched Looper. We scalped our tickets.
Did you forget about the weed in your underwear?
No, I smoked the rest of it.
Oh, damn. Okay. Sick.
And I'm like, that's what weed does.
Make you--
You miss out on experiences.
Yeah.
No, I would say I've never had a single good experience smoking weed.
No.
And I probably smoked weed a thousand times.
Yeah, it was bad high school weed was the only time I had a good time smoking weed.
It was the best of all time.
Yeah, when I was smoking weed during quarantine, it was all dispensary weed.
Yeah.
And it made me schizophrenic for months on end.
And I was like, what is this?
and I looked it up in the stream is called Durban poison.
I was like I can't have this anymore. Yeah, I got over. I got some real
fucked up like good weed at one point and then I was waking up and I was like
waking up like still high and then like going to my
into my bathroom and like barely being able to open my eyes in the morning
and then your eyes are like heavy yeah, yeah, horrible. The only time I'll get
back on the gas is if Seth Rogan acknowledges me this guy from the same
he doesn't support me he doesn't support you he doesn't use 12k dude come on put
it put a zero on the end of Oz bitch yeah everybody tweeted Seth Rogen yeah
said at Gavin Matt's of Oz bitch he needs it yeah he's struggling dude he needs
yeah he needs it who Seth no Gavin he needs a he needs a body said Seth was
struggling Seth is struggling. Do you see American Pickle? Dog shit. I didn't even know that
was a thing. American Pickle? You look like the American Pickle bro. Come on. How do you
not you didn't look you didn't have it taped to your mirror this morning when
you were shaving? Yeah. I did look up a photo of Lemmy because I wanted to do that.
Pretend it's two years ago when I say this joke okay? Hey Pat nice glutton
mutton chops. Oh yeah, it's pretty good right? He used to be pretty fat. Yeah. Oh, that'd
be pretty good if it were. That's a cardinal sin dude. It is one of the biggest. You're
going to get sevened. Yeah, I think that's next week. But now since now, okay, I got
that coming up next week. Just want to plug that. I'm going to be forced to have to death.
I'm going to be sevened too. I'm going to, somebody's going to cut my girl's head off
and put it in a box. Anybody I wish sometimes. That's a funny prank now. They'll be like,
remember the movie seven from seven no I was doing a seven to him oh seven oh
okay yeah it's fine then yeah we just put it back on later it's from seven and
you know that was spelled out yeah seven seven seven yeah yeah seven I've seen
seven we've all seen seven I don't know just pronouncing the title correct yeah
yeah seven in all right. We're not that we're talking about movies like
American pick. I only watch old stuff really no no that's a lie. You saw
fucking change four times.
Did my my the for a friend of mine, the shanky guy came into his work. He
works at a restaurant and my friend showed him the island boy video and I
said he was like why are you
Island boy. What do you want me to ask you for a photo? No, I'm going to show you this
beanie. You have to take stuff in your own hands. You have to make sure certain people
are aware of certain things. I just don't want you to fucking lose touch now that you're
all Hollywood. And then that guy told me that the Shang-Chi guy got canceled because he
he said like gay people are mentally disabled. He was on like an incel reddit or something.
He's on incel reddit. Really? What's his name? Similu. Yeah, he was on like some like incel.
He's a fucking legend. Leave him alone. He's young and then Chinese cultures were very
misogynist. You just said he's Canadian. Huh? You just said he's Canadian. He's Chinese
as well. You got to pick. You got to pick one. Yeah. No, you can be a couple of things. Trans
Atlantic. True. That's true. Trans and Atlantic. Wait, not the main guy, right?
Trans people came out of the Atlantic Ocean? What's up? Not the main guy from Shang-Chi,
right? Yeah, the main guy. Shang-Chi was on an incel subreddit saying gay people were like
people with Down Syndrome. Really? Yeah. I know you're not telling the truth, but I'm not gonna.
it's true. No, I'm thinking not the guy I'm thinking of the main guy.
Okay, the guy from fucking see me Lou. Okay, you got the 10 rings from his dad
in the movie. It's it's pretty good. There's some pieces. That's that's a nice story. Come on,
come on. You gotta know. I'm sorry. This I gotta see this movie again.
I kind of I should have seen it. I didn't even I honestly didn't even know it already came out.
I felt like I just there was there was some
This is very anti-Asian.
No.
I'm very pro-Asian.
To a fault actually.
Six weeks to get released.
Yeah.
Like Eternals is like oh like it's out now not really.
It's out tomorrow.
I also thought that Shang-Chi was one of the Eternals.
Shouldn't that have been out forever?
Come on.
Dumbass movie.
That's right.
Fuck you, Kingo.
You never return my calls.
Everybody online, why do you get Jack just to shoot stuff out of his fingers?
Because he's rich.
He wants to look good.
That's right.
His wife's sick.
He should have gotten ten times fatter for the role, I think.
That would have been funnier.
That would be sick.
That would be so cool.
If he was just like a bowling ball.
Honestly, dude, I bet Kumail 100%, bro.
was dude yeah. He got fucking picked out to be a monster. Yeah, that's cool. Yeah,
he was just like some nerd. That's why everybody hate you still hates nerds.
Yeah, you know that's how
nerd to job, but then everybody's like yes. Now he's a jock. We can all hate
him. You know, nerds kind of had to accept him because he's like they're
well. Yeah, shining. See, I feel like a pro jock. I feel like he just he picked
a bad point in time. Like I feel I mean, I guess I could be wrong, but I don't
see like Kingo being like the next like Iron Man really you know what I mean?
What are you talking about?
Kingo is an iconic character, Kingo.
You don't, oh fuck, you must have not seen the movie.
You saw the movie?
No.
I just love Kingo though.
Yeah, if they had Kingo in like the first Captain America movie, now that could have
been something.
I think he should be the Hulk.
Yeah, he could be the Hulk.
He would make a good Hulk.
We need a brown Hulk.
They need a new Hulk.
Well there's a she-hulk is coming out and she's black I think.
Really?
Yeah.
She's green actually.
Whoa.
When she's in Hulk form.
The first green Hulk.
I think it's racist.
You think it's racist?
I don't think black people are angry.
Well the Hulk is.
Well the thing about she-hulk is she can't go to a movie.
God damn it dude.
What is it getting to?
What?
Two times in one.
It's been fucking 25 minutes.
I'm sorry.
(laughter)
- Oh, that would be problematic.
- No, I--
- Boy, oh boy.
- I don't think--
- Well, let's get to the list.
(laughter)
- This is best places to have sex.
You like to have sex, yeah?
- Yeah.
- You strike me as a guy who likes to have sex a lot.
- Sure, I'm a sex addict.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- I used to cheat a lot.
- Nice, dude.
- No.
Edit that.
(laughing)
- He leaves in the whole thing.
Edit out that part.
- Here's the best places to have sex.
What do you prefer, ordinary or extraordinary?
Nice or wild?
- That's a good question to start out with.
- That is a good opening question.
- Probably ordinary but wild.
- True.
- No, ordinary but like the idea that it's wild.
pretending it's wild.
It's like, "WHOA!"
"I need you!"
It's like when people roleplay and they're like,
"Yeah, we're roleplaying," but then it's like, when they fuck,
it's just like missionary.
That's like 90 seconds of being like,
"I'm a baby."
Anybody that needs a roleplay,
they're always like, "We gotta spice up nothing."
And then they just like,
narrative.
What if I wore doctor clothes first?
What if I had them on first for a minute?
first for a minute. You're not you're not fucking like you were laying in bed.
Doctor is a fucking that's that guy knows everything about the human body.
He's way but doctors way better. I would not let a doctor fuck me. No dude,
he's going to he's going to feel me. Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to I'm
going to overload my body. What if it feels a lump on my nut? Well, I did
role play as a doctor once and I held an exacto knife up to
I'm going to get my Vegas nerve stimulated bro. I don't want that yeah,
that's going to I'm going to be surprised. I was a fucking doctor. I
circumcised my
number one is bed and here's the top comment. The place I had sex for the
first time.
It was in my boyfriend's house. His dad was gone for two weeks and we had sex in
his dad's king size bed. It was amazing. So I don't use someone else's bed. You
know, I seen I seen I seen a bed,
a screenshot of a bed from Facebook marketplace and it had a kennel
underneath. Whoa. Oh yeah. I'd like to have sex in that bed. Yeah. Under the bed.
I'd like to be in the kennel on my computer and not have to have sex. Yeah.
I'm just under there. I got my comic books down here. I'm reading. The door's
locked. The lock is on my side. Nobody can get in. Reinforced steel on top so I
can't even feel the squeaking. Yeah. I'm on big headphones. I'm on LiveLeak.
Yeah. First place I had sex was a couch. Shout out to my mom's apartment. Nice.
In Mayfair in Wilmington, North Carolina. That couch was so leather. It stuck on my
knees and I got a rash. Yeah. It's an old leather couch. Yeah. Was it like peeling too?
It fucked up my knees for a long time. Yeah. It was a cheetah leather couch.
Because you were on your knees the first time you got fucked?
on the couch. Yeah, I was. Yeah, I mixed it up. It was I couldn't remember who
fucks who and it was a coin flip. So, you know, yeah. Peggy, 16.
Yeah, where I really hope people are doing it. Seriously, some of these items
are insane. The beach in a pool, we are such a weird generation.
In a pool?
True.
That's true.
Sex in a pool, not good, dude.
No, well, I was trying to play and she drowned.
Yeah, that's the fear, right?
She came up, she had water in her nose.
You could put your penis on one of the hot tub jets, that's a pretty good feeling.
Yeah.
Yeah, when I was a kid, I, like, before I ever did any drugs, I used to, like, any time
I was in a hot tub, I just put my, hold my breath, just put my face in front of the jets
for a long time and I come up and it made me really dizzy and I was like, "I'm going
to do drugs in two years."
That's a good drug, yeah.
And pushing your hands onto your eyelids to see those colors.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So many things like that.
Oh, my God.
like hold your breath, take a bug, a bunch of deep breaths and then like stand up
and down really fast and you just pass out. No, I used to do that all the
addicted to that. I used to get dug on standing up. It was so cool. Yeah,
I can't really like this where I'm saying this is a common one. Yeah, the
bed. This is common. I don't understand how this could be the number one did
This is pretty boring.
Perfect. I mean, are we going...
Is this maybe the 10th?
10 to... No, this is 1.
We started with the best. Oh, shit.
Yeah. Yeah.
It says, "Perfect for being naked."
Nice place to do it. Someone just said,
"Same." Someone said, "Lie down and
make love, baby."
"Truly the best sex is in bed. There is
so much room. I have a queen-size bed,
and it's amazing how much room there is to have crazy
good sex in."
I guess I've always been any time I've been doing it. I'm like this is bad. We
need more room. I need to we need to be in a convention center right now.
Let me read that.
I especially love it when the bed makes sound. And then this one, this one too.
Oh nice. There's another good one, the final one. I don't know. One was
rocking with this comment. You just take out your clothes and kiss the bra.
Biggs just joined the show.
Yusa!
Yusa just take the clothes off and kiss the brow!
He should have been one of the eternals, honestly.
Jar Jar.
He would have crushed.
He basically was, I mean,
you add all those people up, it's Jar Jar.
Pretty much.
Can you make a Jar Jar show where he's actually a Sith Lord?
Yeah.
Number two.
Nah, not a fan, bro.
Too much water, dude.
turn the water off. If you turn the water off, it's nice.
And then you're cold, though.
But then you feel like a fucking lying down at the top.
Yeah, you feel like an idiot. You turn the- you start having sex, the water's
annoying, you turn it off, and then you're like, we're just in a room now,
and I'm a little wet.
Yeah, and then when you pee, it's like still, it doesn't get washed away with
the water.
Exactly, yeah.
When you pee at the end of the sex, it doesn't leave.
No, dude, that's squirt.
No, I'm squirting on your leg in the shower.
I don't understand the like obsession with like, oh, sexy is wet.
Yeah.
I don't like being wet.
I like dry.
I like dry pussies.
No, just like, my whole essence is wet.
Yeah.
Nobody has ever said my whole essence is wet.
No.
I swear to God, dude.
People are always saying my whole essence is wet.
People are always saying their essence is wet.
Shorty, my brain is wet right now.
I'm wet.
My essence is wet.
My fiance as of July 14th is absolutely crazy.
Oh, happy anniversary.
He is a bit more sexual than I used, than I was used to, but he helped me channel my inner crazy side.
One time he convinced me to do this even though I didn't want to.
[laughter]
Now we do it at least once a week. Love you Riley.
From Survivor 101.
Whoa.
Oh,
Stockholm
things I don't want to do
this guy's wait. I love I love him being like that. She's like, oh, he helped me
channel my inner crazy side. He did it sounds like you're a woman.
This comment is just my favorite and it's from evil angel. Whoa. Yeah, I
would never have sex with an evil angel.
So, you know, she's from the UK or China.
yeah that's a little more just those of you but color
you're looking at a color did number three is car
is fine
that they just hate
when it goes down the hill
they said the beast of my dad's a bird and wrote
he said destroy the road as it did you get the cuisine the tailpipe i was in
there alone
has never known that i can't
I was in the car alone jacking off. I got a Titanic.
Oh dude, I used to do that. I remember one time I jacked off in the 15 minutes that it
took my mom to deliver a rent check to the real estate office in my car, my mom's car.
I got roadie.
Busted in a sock.
From an old lady.
Oh.
What?
Congrats.
That's cool.
Call that American Pickle, dude.
Yeah.
Yes sir.
Gives new meaning to drive me baby.
Who's, what?
Anyone see the Doritos ad?
That's not related to like sex at all.
No, it's just like--
Dude, what's up with these ads?
The Doritos Super Bowl ad was so funny.
No, I think these car ads--
I just need to talk about it.
I was 19 and I had sex with my friend's single 47-year-old mom in my car.
Oh, this is cancer.
Then three months later--
I'm going to tears.com.
I did one of my 18-year-old classmates in the same car.
Whoa.
My husband likes to kiss me in the car, but we have never had sex in the car.
That counts.
That does count.
Kissing is sex, in the car at least.
number four is beach
uh... now i'd just love the way sand gets on you when you have sex you don't
the same as all over both of your body that is so sexy and not i would love it
i go to a private beach no kids once a week it has to expect that i will have
you
even even in the dead of winter
I've never had sex on a beach.
No, yeah.
No kids!
Yeah.
A private beach where no kids are allowed.
This is a beach just for me.
That's why we had a beach wedding.
I'll put you a fuck right there.
I like this one.
That sounds amazing.
Oh, I hope I can do that one day.
Dude, I just don't, the sand, I do feel like I would get sand all in my pubes.
Yeah.
And that's like, you know how you go to the beach one time, sand popping out of your...
I don't even like getting sand in my shoes.
- Yeah. - Dude, oh.
- Yeah.
- Sand coming out of every hair on your body for weeks.
- Oh my God.
- My mouth completely filled with sand,
stuffed with sand, can't talk, can't breathe.
- I'm on the beach, I'm having sex,
all of a sudden I'm like stuffing, fuck.
- Swallowing so much sand.
- I'm burying my head like an ostrich
while I'm having sex, dude. - Oh my God.
- I'm eating so much sand.
- It's not even awful. - It's so annoying.
- I fucking nut, I look up,
the sea gull is just staring at me.
- Exactly, yeah.
He thinks it's food 'cause he'll eat anything.
He's eating my cum.
- Yeah.
- And all of a sudden I'm worried,
a seagull baby one day and he knocks on my door. He's my dad reincarnated, he's
disappointed. Oh, he's just sitting there watching me? He's seeing my little ass dick, too?
Your performance was terrible, son. The thing, alright, the thing is, there's no, there's
really no... He's sucking my, he's eating my dicks and fry. There's really no material
difference between fucking on the beach and fucking like on a playground. Yeah.
right like this is a sandbox just saying just all the sand dude yeah and there's
like you're not in the ocean when you're like think about how much bird shit is
in the sand so much I think you're cool Bond wouldn't do this yeah and a crab
could pinch on your wiener - when you're having sex think about that be kind of
nice though I hate I hanging on the camera like
Patrick's like grabs the crab he's like I just made some money yeah cuz your face
bro yeah you honestly look so crabbish yeah I'm sorry
you're cracking off I'm evolving you need a bit of becoming a cephalopod you
look like if Wario intravenous drug use problem a cephalopods a squid I don't
know what you're trying to say you know how like people like it like like a lot
lot of animals just slowly evolve into crabs carcinoma. Yeah, carcinogens. No,
that's
speaking of cellulite. I don't like to be on the beach because then you're seeing
all that
yeah, yeah, plus bikinis. Yeah, yeah, private beach, no fat people.
That's a good idea. Yeah, so I do like looking at pictures of fucking some hot,
hot people on the beach. Yeah, you have a calendar. Check out Baywatch. I used to
I had a sports illustrated and it was ran through. Taking care of the glue coming
off holes in all the pages. Oh my god. So good. I didn't even get to my favorite one after a while.
It's been fucking amazing. I burned it up. I had a funeral for it. That smell would have been pretty
fucked up dude. It smelled like hair. Number five is on the floor. Yep.
feels so dirty and spontaneous sometimes fall on the floor from the bed.
Yes, what do you play fucking king of the hill on your bed?
It's just fuck what's wrong with I did this once on the floor.
Are you fucking playing? Can you role playing is king of the hill? Bobby
Bobby dang it. I felt the floor again.
David, Bobby, I'm gonna come Bobby.
Oh dang it.
(laughter)
Peggy?
Peggy 16.
Call back, bringing it back.
Number 6 is couch.
Caleb put this one on there.
Dude, I've fucked where both of you are sitting right now dude.
What? What the?
And you know I don't wash that shit.
That shit's expensive.
My husband came home today and I just had to have him
them and couldn't make it to the bedroom oh did it feel good damn I'm never gonna
fuck again oh did it feel good oh I just had to have them girls are after sex
after sex going oh did that feel good
that was oh wow I can jolly roll your garsh I like could be fun if you're on
one of those recliner joints. Shoot you up a little bit. But if you're on a
sectional dude all the pieces come apart. True. Number seven in a pool. I've done
this it's fun. That's mostly the pool part that's fun.
It's all the fun of sex and all the fun of a pool. You ever been in a goddamn one of those little basketball hoops?
I was jumping into the fucking pool. I'm going to ask the ball back and forth with ten friends
and all landing in a pussy.
Got one of those like flamingo like floaties around you just so you can like stay up in
the water.
Water wings.
This is some Hugh Hef shit. I will say that. This is some Hef shit.
Alright.
Dude, you know Hefner was every day in the pool. At some point the buoyancy is the only
thing that could give him an erection.
I can see you underwater.
What do you mean I can't get up?
Yeah, exactly. Check this out.
It's like a water weight.
the water way, just floating, just jumps in the water pool.
Number eight in bathroom. That's where my shit and piss lives. It makes for
easy clean up. It's even nicer if you turn off the light. What?
Bathroom with the lights off? Just pulling your whole like medicine cabinet
down. Yeah. Just destroying everything in the bathroom. Stumbling into the
shower curtain and then they think you're a ghost and they kill you. True.
I never done the bathroom. No, it doesn't seem fun and well
I may have, but I mean I'm with a girl now. I'm in a loving relationship now.
Yeah, I mean you guys met my girl. Yeah, yeah, she's cool. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
she's cool anyways, but before that
when I was just a bad guy,
there's this girl and we're like we're like making out and then we're like in
New York like walking and we're trying to find a place. It's like two AM and
and she's like I got to go to the bathroom. So she goes into this random
bar and then she texts me. She's like come here and I'm like, well,
there's something going on. Is she okay? So I go into this bar and then I go
and it's like the bathroom's like down these stairs at the back and it's like a
long hallway and then I see her like poking her head out of the bathroom and
she's like waving me and then she was wearing overalls and and she had like
and when I get to the bathroom, she has like the overalls kind of slinged off
her shoulders and she like wants me to have sex with her in the in the bathroom.
Wow, but it's like two AM at a New York bar and we weren't there, you know yeah
and it just as soon as I like get to the door, it's just like stinky. I was like
I'm not doing this. I never talked to her again.
Ruined with the smell of shit dude. Yeah, yeah, I know that would like she
thought it was gonna be like so sexy and spontaneous thing, but I was like it's
stinky. Yeah, yeah,
pooping in there. And it's late at night, you know, this bathroom's been taken care of.
People are pissing everywhere, doing cocaine. I was the previous tenant, dude. I'd be blowing
up the bar bathroom, dude. One sip of beer. The nice thing about the bathroom is you can
put the square where it belongs. Yeah. And the shower. Number nine is tent. Oh yeah, I've
I've done this, but I was role playing is unhoused.
There's one comment here from Roger McBeloney. It says, Oh yeah, in a tent in
the woods, that's hot. And then it says, definitely come to a national park.
Hey,
Roger,
alien man. Let me know if you're planning to come to a national park and
do this. This staircase that's lit up in a national park. Yeah. It's a great
campsite log cabin right about one light on I don't know who lives there though
I'm having sex in the tent next thing I know I'm camping next to the dimensional
kidnap camp next to the pit in the ground yeah I don't have giant shoes I
can kick a whole tent into it the thing about sex is that it's also so dangerous
it's true dangerous sex is the best sex dude yeah on top of a building right
next to a sign that says caution. Wet floor. And a giant vat of oil. Yeah that's good.
Yeah. Volcano. Having sex in Hawaii is a trip. Oh my god. Anytime, any given moment you could
be fucking Pompeii'd. True. Like that fucking guy who's jacking off in the Pompeii thing.
Oh my God. He touched this thing.
It's cool that he got his last.
He's the real eternal.
He's outliving all of us and he's just got his hand on his cock.
Let's be real, that guy was a prankster.
Definitely.
Because you hear an explosion in the distance,
you know, of a volcano erupting.
If you're jacking off, you stop.
If you're not jacking off, you pretend you're jacking off
because you're going to get preserved forever.
If I wake up in the morning, I'd fucking open up my shades.
His body's shards melting in front of him.
Yeah.
He's like, "I'm going to be like this."
I if I wake up, I open up my shades. First thing I see is a pumice just just
flying at me did on hand is going up my ass. Yeah, absolutely. I'm gonna pretend
that I'm marionette or that I'm self-sufficiently myself. Yeah, I've
never been able to do before. It's instantly curl into a perfect. Yeah,
perfect wheel. Yeah, yeah, yeah, like a joy to go. Yeah, they think I'm a
bowling ball. It's like I'm like how you can like like like lift a car if
if someone's in danger, yeah, it's like an instant, you know, like if you can
see a pyroclastic flow like like going coming towards you just instantly just
like yeah armadillo up
just magnetic mouth to pita and then you turn to dust. They never find your
ever find your body. It was for nothing sucking my balls and my penis is under
my chin.
What a freak yeah, the scientists like dig you out and they just throw you
away. They're like no
The Pompei jacking off guy was one thing. This is like, this is not okay. We cannot put this
in a museum. Yeah. Yeah. Science. They think I'm, they think I'm keen. In 10,000 years,
they try to Jurassic Park you and they have an exhibit full of you just like sucking your
own balls. They take me out of the amber and they think I'm going to like talk to them
I just keep sucking my own balls and not acknowledging them at all.
There's that one.
Do you speak English?
Just coming into this fucking little thing right here over and over again.
Coming into your shirt.
Wow, after all this time he's been committed to the bit.
Yeah, dude.
I still think I'm laughing with my balls in my mouth.
For him it was like five seconds.
Yeah, exactly.
though yeah whole exhibited the met yeah
self-sufficiency all right over time number 10 is outside in a rainstorm
that's like the worst shower that's why they use the weather machine for hurricane katrina
it's so hot um wet and wild i love it but no lightning
I'm not gonna get got
I don't want that. Yeah, I mean some never-ending fucking boner if I get struck by lightning. Yeah, dude, imagine just like the lightning rod
Like the like your penis gets struck by lightning immediately as soon as you pull it out then
Your superpowers you can do
Like like like palpatine
I'm shooting lightning bolts of people yeah, God damn if I could shoot
lightning bolts out of my dick,
you get a whole whole different world. I would rob a bank
yeah. That'd be a funny way to rob a bank. You are you with your dick out
yeah.
I have to do this. I'm sorry guys yeah, I swear I just going to shoot. I
swear yeah, no kids
bank that says no kids. No kids allowed. The adult only bank.
It's the only bank in the city that has no lollipops.
Yeah, what do they know of money? They don't need it. Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
You turn Richie Rich's there? Fuck!
I should have known.
God, now I'm doing something illegal. Now I gotta kill Richie Rich with my dick.
Yeah, the bank robber. It's the two worst crimes, bank robber and sex offender.
Robbers already robbing a bag was like I don't want to go to jail I can't be
showing a kid my dick dude step too far you fucking kill yourself did I get on
the street a lot dude I get a friend one one one one wrong move dude I could be
oh I that happened oh I didn't like I feel like peeing how we like cuz no
pedophiles like I really want to pee in front of a kid yeah you know like I
I don't think I should go to jail. Your nation is a victim. Let's do one of
your categories nice and your pedophile jeopardy that game that you're building.
He's running the field guide to pedophile.
You can watch him on words. Yeah, it has their different like yeah, okay,
class. The call is a little different.
Yeah, and then you have a you build in one sections like people who are
deafening up pedophiles and it's just you covering for yourself, me and my
boys. Yeah, me and all my friends. There's no earthly way. Yeah. All right.
I like that everyone, there's always a one of these. Sounds like a lot of fun.
Yeah. Yeah. That's the same person. Oh, that's so nice. I wish I had a
boyfriend. Yeah. It rains a lot where I am.
Gab, you're playing Boston this weekend, right? People should come see you.
Yeah. So this is gonna, this is gonna come out. This'll come out a week from
tomorrow. Oh, okay. Well, then I was already in Boston, but I'll be in
in Chicago on the twenty seventh at the Lincoln Lodge and then I'll be in
Atlanta after that and then also Washington D. C. But you can just like
follow me online. Yeah, so if you send me like to those two, I can put them in
the description. He has this fire ass tweet that he posted one time that said
it's Gabby Petito was a Zodiac killer. Oh, that was fire. That would we juice
that dude. That was that was a that was like front page news. Yeah, yeah, all
right. Thank you. Yeah, sometimes I have these thoughts right and then I yeah, I
need people to support me. We got you brother. All right bye bye. Thanks for having me. Of course.