Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
*laughter*
*music*
Crap monster.
*laughter*
*explosion*
Holdin' on your rope got me ten feet off the ground.
*music*
And I'm hearin' what you say but I just can't make a sound.
You tell me that you need me, then you go and cut me down
But wait, tell me that you're sorry, didn't think I'd turn around
And say that it's too late to apologize
It's too late
I apologize. It's too late. Too late. Oh. Oh. It's you. I don't know how this song goes.
Just eight, eight. I'll take a shot for you. Oh, I need you like a heart needs a beat,
But it's nothing new, yeah, yeah, I loved you with a fire red, now it's turning blue.
And you say, sorry like the angel, heaven let me think was you, but I'm afraid, it's too
It's too late to apologize.
I said it's too late to apologize.
It's too late.
It's my favorite part of the song.
think this is a part of the timberland produce song
it's too late
it's too late to apologize
there we go, we're harmonizing
it's too late
i said it's too late to apologize
yeah
No, you gotta, you gotta straight.
It's too late to apologize.
Yeah!
I'm holding on your rope, got me ten feet off the ground.
The ground!
The ground.
That was good.
That was really good. What's the next one?
What next one? We're not gonna do another one, are we?
Wait, no, click that one. Total Eclipse of the Heart.
Whoa.
You know this one?
Do you know this one?
I don't know this one.
Dude, this one always hits you hard.
Just let the lyrics wash over you on this one, okay?
So it starts off with an instrumental.
I can feel it already.
Oh, I remember this one.
I remember this one.
Wait, no, there's a bit weird.
Let's do...
Dude, I'm telling you, Total Eclipse of Heart, that's a perfect one.
No, it's my turn to pick.
You pick next.
I didn't even get to pick one. You picked that one on shuffle, but now I know which one I
want to do. Alright, well you do it. Here we go.
They're like... You ever see Transformers? I've seen Transformers, I know. I know what
this is from. This changed everything in the world of Cybertron. It's true. It actually
did the transformers didn't know what to do when they heard this one hmm they
invented a new dance called the headbang they didn't call it the robot no that
was a different dance here we go damn I like the dot dot dots here me too in
in this farewell
there's no blood
there's no ally of bob dole
because i have drawn regret
from the truth
of the past six months
so let mercy
home
and wall
uh...
wall
and we can
right
your car
so after this we have to stop the dress our world
the
car
it raised my style
well you can let you know about you know
what
uh...
where you go you go on your balcony dot is a good thing in here
well i clean your side i'm working to you on a single verse
certainty. So Linkin Park, what I've done. So let merge, come on it's the chorus.
Come and wash away. Bennington. What I've done. This is going to be the best episode we've ever done.
Transformers song. We'll defeat the Decepticons. We're Autobots. Whoa. We head bang to awesome songs.
That's really good Cameron.
Alright.
Should I pause this so we can move?
Yeah, I think we should probably...
Smell my hat real quick.
This just smells like a hat to me.
Yeah?
Yeah, I can't detect any difference in smell.
I don't know, I wore it skating yesterday.
Nothing in here smells like anything.
Or tastes like anything either.
And I've been coughing too.
Mm-hmm
We got kicked out of the karaoke bar we were in
Karaoke bar was my living room speaking of smelling. You know what I realized Caleb got really sick after he smelled your butt
Shit that's not even false that literally he smelled your button. He's been trapped at home for
Days now yeah
Huh
Yeah, interesting. He said it smelled so good. He did say it smelled really good. So I
Don't know
There's really no I wish we could you want to do you want a chair? I'm standing staying limber. Yeah
Yeah, cuz we had my energy level. We have to record in my room again
And I'm really close to this light. Yeah, and it's really a dire situation in here right now. I haven't done
No, it is is it's cuz it's the winter time now, and I'm not just wearing t-shirts
Yeah, well, you know I laundry pile looks bigger cuz it's all sweatshirts. Oh, it's also
I mean, maybe this isn't for you, but it's also right
I'm about to go home to my family and bring all my dirty laundry
Oh me too, so I'm putting your head again putting off putting off washing
Yeah, my clothes for a long time, and I got a I got a big pile mines in a hamper though
Mm-hmm my old not existing. No the hamper is over there. Oh, man. Yeah
I've overfilled the hamper.
And the thing is, I used to have two hampers,
specifically for that reason.
And then I had no, my shoe rack broke.
So now I just threw all my shoes in the other hamper.
- So you have a shoe bag.
- Yeah.
Well, I should get a laundry bag.
That's a good move.
- Yeah, a laundry bag is a great lazy guy hamper.
- Yeah.
I also don't have a trash barrel in my room.
I've just been doing a carpenter bag on the floor.
- Oh, man, yeah.
(laughing)
- It all sounds way grosser than it is.
- Dude, I have to say, having multiple trash cans,
like trash cans in different rooms is great,
'cause for example, the trash can in my computer room,
I would never use it, so I never have to empty it.
So I can throw something away in there
and just forget about it.
It doesn't exist anymore.
Exactly.
Put it in the kitchen trash, it's gonna smell, I have to empty it.
Disgusting.
Office trash might as well be a black hole.
Yeah.
Doesn't exist.
I mean, yeah, there's just clothes everywhere in my room.
Yeah.
Man, I really wish I could finish this karaoke song.
I feel like I...
Well, that's the other thing is now we're next to Neil's wall and he's probably on some
fucking call already.
He's probably been on a call the whole time.
He's probably really mad.
Oh, he's probably pissed.
probably can hear us saying that he's really mad too.
Oh no, he can't hear anything through these walls.
Oh, then we can do karaoke.
Maybe.
No, we're done with that.
Should we test it out by yelling to him?
Should we test it out by knocking on the wall?
I might test it out by running through the wall like a Looney Tunes character and see
if he notices.
Yeah, because I know he'll definitely love if I sit in my room and just keep saying his
name over and over.
He doesn't get annoyed when I do that.
No, that'll be good.
Yeah.
Let's see
It's almost Christmas. Yeah, I can't wait. Oh boy. Oh, man
I love Christmas
Now
Are you just almost New Year's I
Think you're just looking at stuff in my room to talk about we could do that. Yeah
Oh, did you see I see this framed picture?
Yeah, that's the framed photo of the Home Planet video with the Rock and Roll guy.
I like your Duran Duran poster.
No, it's an Irish flag with my family crest on it that I found in my parents basement.
Nope.
Yeah.
I'm tired of that joke. I've been tired of that joke my whole damn life.
It's not how my last name is pronounced, bitch.
Yeah, I like your Dora poster.
It's not a Dora poster. It's a Creepshow poster.
It's a Creepshow poster and it's in Japanese.
Dora n nope, what's the n mean Cameron? What are you calling her?
Naranja
Okay, does that mean orange and I think I think I think that means orange in Spanish. Yeah, I hope so
me too
Damn, I got cans everywhere. I got cans all over my table - yeah damn dude
My life is got cans and coins your those arcade tokens. Those are barcade tokens. Yo
to barcade with Robbie. Oh yeah. I bought, I never use those. Yeah. I should go though.
I should use them. You should. We should go right now and bring the recorder. Yeah. And
do karaoke. Oh dude. Me and Julio went to the fucking LAN bar cause he wanted to game
and I maybe wanted to game too but I would never choose to go to that bar if I wasn't
with him. Just saying. And all the fucking computers were reserved so we played chess
there. Oh yeah, aren't they having like there's like a...
Who is it? It's not FaZe Rug is it? I don't know there was some there were like
tournaments or something going on and they all the computers are booked but
clearly people weren't using they were clearly free computers yeah but they
gotta keep saying kept saying oh they're all reserved come on you're gonna make
us play chess? You're gonna make me trounce him in chess? That's so embarrassing for
him. You didn't play anything on the switch or the Xbox? They got
skate on the xbox we went back to my apartment and played switch at my house
okay yeah but it was so fun yeah they have the phase clan logo all over that
bar now i feel like phase clan is following me around yeah i feel like
scouting you i feel like they're gang stalking me they are yeah i feel like
they want to scout you to be the biggest phase clan member
yeah i would they're scouting me to be their new like
like uh their new crazy boy yeah their new like basement punishment boy
face glands new crazy boy. I think they want to like experiment on me.
Hmm. You want a chair? You look you you're moving. I'm gonna move I'm gonna move this
stuff and sit down on the bed. Okay. But it's all good. Don't worry about a thing.
My room seriously feels like a college dorm. That's okay. You're still in college.
I think well technically I was. That's true. Yeah. I have to I will.
- Well, I think next year--
- You should go to the new school.
- Yeah.
Well, next year, yeah, yeah,
this is like the final month that I can decide
whether or not I'm going back to Emerson.
'Cause I've been on a leave of absence.
- Yeah, for that long?
They let you go on it for that long?
- You can go on a leave of absence for two years,
and I was just like, well,
I'm just gonna let that ride out.
- Yeah, no reason not to.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So technically, I'm still an enrolled Emerson student.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - Well, no.
Well, that's how you got those glasses as you walked into the glass store and you
Detected up. He's an enrolled student of Emerson. Mm-hmm. These guys are good on me. We're getting around ease. They are good on you
They look good this fucking mic stands
Anyone wants to buy me anything off my Amazon wish list?
We could make an Amazon wish list dude, that'd be awesome for the holidays. Yeah, this room is disgusting
I got it. We don't have to talk about the room. Yeah, it's okay. No, I know I just unless you really want no
You know what? You know what? The thing is is I fucking popped an addy and fucking cleaned my room
I know it's back to this. It's back to this and literally a week. I don't believe you at all
You know what it is. I don't see anything that's moved. I oh you should have seen it dude. What's that? What's what?
That's a waterproof camera
No, what's under what's it on? What's that black box? Is that it? Oh, that's a that's a drum machine
Drum machine, I don't know you got a drum machine. Yeah, I have a Roland DDR 30. Damn. That's cool
I don't know how to use it
You should give it to me. Do you want it? No, okay
I was I was gonna I have no room for it, but I would go crazy on it. Well, it's like it's the
It's like the thing that you plug the
The drum pads into it's like a sequencer. Yeah. Well, no, it's like see all these like
look, there's the MIDI inputs here and then they have all the
like
what are these uh
yeah, okay, so our things right there and
you have to
You plug those into the drum pads for like an old Roland drum machine. Yeah
Yeah, I don't own a drum machine from the 80s.
Yeah, well you own part of one.
I do. I own probably the most important, probably the second most important part of the drum machine.
It's important to have.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking like, I was like, oh when I move here, I'm gonna like
kind of like clean it out, clean all the dust off of it and then sell it.
and uh dude it's impossible to sell music equipment it's so it sucks it's i have so much music stuff
i'm like i'll sell this but i know i tried to sell my guitar it's so fucking it's fucking
annoying as shit dude i tried to go to it all takes up so much room too i tried to go to a
pawn shop with my guitar really yeah what'd they say the guy was like well first it's missing like
like the the SG that I own is like missing like the truss rod cover. I don't know
what that means. It's like the thing that covers that thing up. Like the
like you adjust it to like fix the action and shit. Okay. It's missing that
because I bought that secondhand. That was after our first live show. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought I'm a rock star now. Yeah. I really did dude. Because I've had this guitar here since like
high school and it's like so beat up and shady like the one of the pickups
doesn't work and I'm like too lazy to fix it and I was like oh sick like I'm
gonna like you know start like it was at a time where I was like playing a guitar
a lot yeah and then I'd like stopped mm-hmm and then now I just have two
guitars and I just don't want the other one yeah but after the live show when we
We got we got pinned out. I spent most of my paycheck on that.
What's even like that much money?
I spent like 300 of the 500 we made on a guitar.
I was like yeah dude this is it I'm gonna start.
I'm gonna be live showing it up.
I'm gonna learn how to make music now.
Yeah.
And then you know.
Sucks.
Life happens.
Life gets in the way.
You had your first baby.
I don't know why I thought I was going to like, oh yeah, like this year I'm going to figure
out how to write a song.
It's really important to have like an insanely stupid creative goal that you work towards
for a year and then like completely forget about by the end of the year.
That's like super, super important.
I can't tell you how many video games I was going to make every year of my life from middle
school to freshman year of college.
The only constant in my life has been skating in that way.
In that, like, oh, you need a fucking thing like that.
But like, I don't know why the fuck I was like, I'm going to rock.
It would be really funny.
I was listening to A Loudest Sabbath at the time, too, so I bought the black SG with the
fucking...
We should start a...
It's called the...
It's a 2010 Epiphone Goth SG and it has like a cross on the 12th fret.
We should start a Doom Metal Band.
Yeah.
Maybe I keep the guitar.
And we start a Doom Metal Band and we dress up in costumes.
Yeah.
That's what I was gonna say.
It would be funny like, to not buy a guitar after the live show and be like, "Man, I'm
gonna be a rock star" and buy like a crazy outfit.
Yeah.
Like a...
Buy like a Sephiroth cosplay.
That was the Boston Live show too.
So I had to carry that, I got a gig bag for it.
It came with it free.
Oh no, no, no, I got a free t-shirt from Mr. Music in Alston.
And I carried that with me on the train from Alston.
Or no, you know what I did? I fucking, I walked to, I walked from Alston to Harvard Square
and then took the red line to Davis Square and then waited for my mom to pick me up to
go to New Hampshire. And I just, I just carried a fucking guitar around with me all day. Like
I, like, I don't know, like I fucking, maybe I should get back on Adderall cause I, my
My impulse control is so bad.
Like literally, like my fucking...
Yeah, I'm lucky that for me, my impulse control is like my fucked up like...
Like look at how much shit I've bought just because...
My impulse buy stuff, yeah, it's always like, it's always movies, which are like, there's
a pretty, there's a...
I feel like I have it on lock enough that I won't buy like an $100 movie usually, but
I've come close.
I've impulse bought $100 box sets for no reason that I don't need.
My impulse purchases are like, look at how many skateboards I own.
Yeah.
Well, one of those I found.
One of those a bodega guy gave me.
Yeah.
But like, I can't stop.
I'll just like, I'll see like somebody, I'll see like something get retweeted onto my timeline
that's like the, like the, they just did a reprint of this, like this Japanese movie
from the eighties that I watched like one time on YouTube.
YouTube and I was like I have to own this right forty dollars right now.
Dude, the fucking the Dana Carvey show on DVD. That was actually a Christmas gift. No, no,
no. You know what was the Christmas gift was the Ben Stiller show. The Dana Carvey show
on DVD was an actual purchase. Andy Milonakis show season two, complete season two. But
this was a, I bought that in high school. Yeah. Are we going to, should we go through
the DVD? Maybe. Is that how we're going to eat up this time? I guess. Yeah, I see. Like,
i've never fucking watch the ben stiller show it's really really important to own
dvds that you've never watched and never will want to shape of water
yes i think that that's a good like that movie
yeah i have a i have paranormal activity on dvd it's still in like plastic wrap
gemstone adventure series a gemstone quest with jerry sisque from jewelry
television that's really good
mhm yeah those types are important yeah
yeah i gave most of those away at the boston live show of the ones i owned
like oh yeah yeah if you know the boston live show
if you if you're a person who uh... owns one of those
good for you yeah congratulations i don't know if you're ever doing that again
you you uh...
you've really
you're really a special fan to us
not
psych
you stupid you thought it was a real deal you got to do another live show
yeah i would like to do it because i want to buy a new bass
doing a tour and buying a new guitar in every city.
Yeah.
And just like, yeah, bringing them all with you.
Yeah, like I, because I could justify that for sure.
Yeah.
I could justify that by like, well, no, this one's a 12 string.
I could be the devil on your shoulder like so easily for that.
Oh my God, dude.
Yeah.
I could, it would be so funny.
You come over the end of the tour and you have like, they're all like the exact same
model of guitar, but they like, each of them has like, you know, like, like state quarters.
Yeah.
like different pictures of stuff from like the city. Well, this one this one
my brother bought off of a friend and it has like oh watch out guitar works
right now Virginia. Oh, whoa. Oh my laundry. I first got yeah. Oh no. Yeah
on the on the back of the headstock. It says guitar works Richmond, Virginia.
Yeah. See that's why you need more. Yeah, you need so I have one from
Virginia already. Yeah. This one I got, this is my base. Did you ever have, yo, did you
ever have one of those? Probably not, but did you ever have one of those? Like it was
like a, it was like a cardboard, like board and it stood up and it had a map of the U.S.
on it and it had the coins in every state. I had one of those. I wasn't a coin collector
kid. I was not either. I only cared about that. But I remember, I remember how, how like,
Because I would you know I was I don't remember how far I got. I was probably I
didn't I definitely didn't finish it, but I got like pretty close, but I don't
even remember what I bought. It was probably just like candy or something
or one day I was like I'm going to take all the quarters and go to the corner
store. And I remember my parents being like being like what. Okay, big sorry big
news. Okay, big new. I'm sorry to interrupt your story. Yeah, it's not an
interesting story. I just got a free city bike unlock. Yo. And this is great news
considering what happened. Yeah. Talk. I'll talk my shit. Okay, so I got a free
city bike unlock. This is unrelated to what happened. I just got one because
I've been right. I decided you probably get a free one. Maybe another one. I
already got a free one. So I'm just gonna ride this one out. Unlock one and
just leave it unlocked for yeah I'm just gonna leave that shit unlocked yeah
leave it in front of like a petco or something mm-hmm let somebody leave with
their dog put the dog in the basket and just bring it in my house mm-hmm
around the living room just doing like wheelies and shit on a city like an e-bike
yeah well speaking of e-bikes so I've decided I never rode a city bike before
and then one day like there's this like skate park under the the Cusco bridge I
know how to pronounce it. It's Polish. Yeah, under the KP Bridge skate park. I wanted to
go there, but I didn't want to take the bus, so I just took a city bike there. I was riding
it there. I was like, "Holy shit, this is the best thing ever." I've lived here for, what,
since March 2021, right? I don't know. Why are you asking me? Yeah, I've lived here since
like March and decided to get into city bikes in the winter. Yeah. Like a fucking idiot.
Yeah, that's very stupid. Yeah, like I've been riding city bikes more than I ever did. Like
yeah, riding a bike in the city more than I ever did in the summer. Bikes should be
destroyed in December. Yeah, you should not. They should put all the city bikes in a pile.
I quit my job rather than having to ride a bike in December. But I've been doing that.
Yeah.
Because it's so nice and it's so convenient. But then I took an e-bike. Oh man, my mom's
gonna listen to this. But I took an e-bike from my house to go to Cooper Park. And I
was like riding around. I was just like, "Oh damn, it's like actually pretty easy to get
around cars." So I'm on an e-bike and this guy, I'm like, you know, about to get to the
skate park and then this guy doesn't use a turn signal and I start going and then
like he just decks me out with his like passenger side mirror yeah like right
next to the the doctor evil tattoo that I have on my on my left arm mm-hmm
giant bruise now cuz I just decked out his fucking mirror yeah I just destroyed
it dude yeah like it like you know like well what actually happened is he was
turning and you saw your you saw yourself in the mirror and you tried to
attack it like a parrot. I was going, "Hi! Hi! Hello! Hi little guy! Hi! Whoa! Look at
you! Look at your bike! There's a little guy! There's a little me in your car! There's a
little me in your car!" You started going way faster. Well, I don't think I would have
gotten hit if it wasn't an e-bike. Yeah? What is an e-bike? It just has like an electronic
motor. It has a motor? Yeah. So like as soon as I started pedaling, I immediately got a
bit more speed than I was used to. And then I didn't have the time to react.
And I got hit in the arm, knocked the bike over onto the sidewalk,
my board fucking flew out into the street. And the guy looks at me, he's
holding up traffic, and fucking everyone in New York, like you know, it's New York.
It's New York, baby. It's New York. Everyone's just holding down the horn at him.
Everyone's holding the horn at him. And I'm like trying to just get the bike back up
and get my board onto the bike and everyone's holding down the horn. The guy just like waits
till I look at him and just goes, "I'm sorry, man." And I just went, "Yeah, me too." And
then we just both went our separate ways. I just went to the skate park.
That's literally, that's how you should, what you should say to somebody. If you didn't
kill them, that's what you should say to somebody that you hit with your car or that you almost
hit with your car.
Every accident should just be, "I'm sorry, me too." No exchange of insurance.
that's the perfect exchange. I almost got hit by a car on my bike when I was in like probably middle
school outside a guy pulled into a CVS parking lot really fast as I was like going across the
entrance and I like I like braked really fast and I skidded and he also braked and if he had kept
going he would have hit me. It was probably my fault. Yeah but I don't know if this was my fault.
Yeah that's why I think that yours sounds like half and half. Yeah I think we're both at fault
but it actually didn't happen on a city bike it happened on my own bike.
But I went into the CVS.
I can get this unlocked for free and then never report me.
I went into the CVS and then he came into the CVS after me and he came up to me and
said you should be more careful.
It's like fuck you.
Yeah.
I know it's my fault.
Leave me alone.
Right.
I'm 13.
Dude that shit's bullshit.
Stay away from me.
Tell me you're sorry.
You almost killed me.
Passenger always has the right of way.
That's right.
The passenger has the right of way.
The passenger of the bike.
Yeah.
uh... i mean the civilian
yeah i was a billion and he was a soldier
i'm even thinking for his third service
the other night we're going to fuckin
gonna mellows and then
that car just almost hit me when we had a lot of melons
you make fun of me for that
this is my impression of you going to uh... burger king
yet there are swing by burgers later i'd call it b_k_ you'd say burger i'd say
b_k_ you know they burgers
no yeah
this is your current in the mcdonald's
yeah i think i'm assuming by mcdonald's later
all you know did you got the big in a year when though
that that's a good one
calling with his windows no not when there was no doubt that is a good it's
not sure i think i might start doing that
it's i would literally i'd be so mad at you if you could put it when he's a
I don't get why you and Caleb get so mad at me for my abbreviations.
A lot of other people use these abbreviations.
Nobody does.
Yes.
You guys are actively trying to ruin my life by making me self-conscious all the time.
Maybe.
Yeah, I stopped by the bodego.
I call it the boat.
The boat.
The bodo.
I gotta go pick up some cigs from the boat. Yeah, that one could catch on some
C's hmm Oh Oh some C's from the box a pack of C's pack of C's from the boat
pack of C's from the boat it is is I really loved that book friendle as a kid
yeah I've look at all man well I changed my life did you know there's that
there's been a friendle movie adaptation in the works for like years
They should get Tom Holland to play Friendel.
How long is it? Let's see here.
Friendel, I remember I was like, "Did they ever make a movie out of Friendel?"
Because that would be a perfect, like, that seems like the perfect movie to make a movie, right?
Yeah.
Let's see here. Friendel, film adaptation.
In 2015, they announced it. And Susan Sarandon was going to play Mrs. Laurie Granger.
She was going to play the Friendel.
and he's a serenity circus was going to play the friend
in the role of the
the mocap suit and he's just standing like straight up with
his arms at his sides.
There's recording him for like an hour.
He's still do you know, you know what actually it wouldn't be
for a friend.
Oh, it wouldn't be Andy circus.
He'll be Doug Jones.
Hmm.
He will be a much better friend older than a circus and he
circus could play an eraser and
Dude, Adventures of a Racer in Pencil.
Mm-hmm.
This is a great movie.
With Doug Jones and Andy Serkis.
I can't wait to see, like, have you ever watched the Smeagol, like, test footage?
Yeah.
Like, Smeagol audition where Andy Serkis is, like, doing that shit?
And he's like...
Okay.
That shit's crazy.
Like, seeing him outside of the Smeagol costume.
Yeah.
The costume.
Seeing him outside of that shit, that's crazy.
Yeah.
Maybe it's, okay, it's like, Doug, it's Andy Serkis, 'cause he, Andy Serkis does monkeys
really good.
Yeah.
monkey Doug Jones as a giant pencil and then maybe we could get Seth Rogan to
play an eraser Seth Rogan as all to okay starring a pencil and a monkey yeah
alright and Benedict Cumberbatch okay as a smog smoke well maybe he could play
let's see maybe he do CGI of Benedict Cumberbatch I think he only did smoke I
Rango I think they rang yeah, okay, did he did all the mocap for Rango?
Did he really and the cover badge those just used his fucking face? Yeah, that's what I say is like that. It's so funny
It's Magus the only
CGI he did it's so fucking funny. They're just like like we're really fucked up really alien motherfucker
For this role need a human argonian. Yeah, literally
Yeah
It's like they have a fucking guy who does mocap for every monster in Lord of the Rings like Andy circuit like he's right there
And they're like no we need the ugliest guy on earth. We need a dragon. We need the fucking we need literally we need a repulsive
disgusting sexually overbearing reptile
Yeah, I bet Benedict Cumberbatch has a thumb yeah, sorry sorry Andy circus, but you're too sexually warm
Yeah, we need we need a sexual winter
oppressive
Basically, we need a sexual nemesis. We need a sexual nemesis. We need icicles to be forming on on
Everybody's private areas when they when they look at this fucking dragon. Yeah, I know because people look at smiegel
And they're like damn. I want to fuck him smiegel
Probably has a big dick mm-hmm. Well. I mean you see that loincloth flapping back and that's right. He runs. Yep. Mm-hmm
Yeah, the smiegel have no dick
smiegel I
Don't know. I wonder if hobbits have big dicks or not
No, they have little ones. Well Smeagol's probably got Smeagol
Before he was corrupted was a proto hobbit. I think Smeagol fucked the ring
did yo, I did find a fan fiction one time of
Smeagol and Dobby and Yoda all having a three when I was looking for that fart episode
And I didn't read it cuz it wasn't fart themed but it's pretty good. We could read it right now
Yeah, we got what we got like 20 more minutes. Also, we do have an oh I do I do have a list
- Yeah, I think we've just--
- We could do that fan fiction instead.
- Caleb's not here to try and alpha us.
- That's right, we can just chill and talk
without being afraid.
- Being afraid of his oppressive force.
- He's so evil.
- Caleb's truly the most oppressive force in the world.
- He literally slaves us.
I think it's still in this document.
- Well, what's this list?
What do we got here for this list?
- Well, I found the fan fiction.
Alright, I guess we can read it.
It's called Rings-
It's cool that you have to get a DDoS check before you enter fanfiction.net.
It's called Rings, Socks, and Minds.
Ooh.
Um.
Oh.
Yeah, who's who?
Yeah, ring, okay.
Smeagol crept from the cave and smelled the air.
Yes, my precious.
Tonight there were no nasty orcs and goblins about.
No elves with bright eyes or men with sharp swords.
Not tonight.
Just him and the fishes of the stream.
Nice fishes swimming blindly towards him.
Tasty fishes.
he would catch them swiftly and silently.
His mind conjured images,
his fingers curling around the scales,
the helpless creatures flopping on the bank as they died.
It brought a lump to his throat and a thrill to his loins.
Gollum, Gollum.
Smeagol crawled on his stomach to the water
with no cursed white face and only the stars above.
The dark stream ran near invisible through the meadow,
but not for Smeagol, not for sharp-eyed Smeagol.
He reached his hand out,
ready to dip it into the cold, cold stream.
He jerked back as he heard a sudden click.
What, can you do the voice?
What was that my precious?
"Is that my precious?"
Someone there, some hunter more silent than he,
lurking, ready to pounce, he sniffed the air desperately.
What does Dobby sound like?
- Like a bitch.
- Dobby is lost!
Dobby is lost!
Smeagol readied himself to flee, then stop.
His night vision spotted movement not 20 yards away.
- Oh, I forgot that about Smeagol.
He's got night vision.
- Yup.
The new arrival, whatever it was, was small
and waved what looked to be a sock.
Its head was completely bald with wide,
Caleb, with wide pointed ears and massive eyes.
Its scrawny body was wrapped in a pillowcase.
strange little creature all told, Smeagol paused.
- That's what he wears?
- Yeah, he wears a pillowcase, right?
- Damn, no, I'm just thinking about Dobby now.
Thinking about what Dobby looks like.
- In all his years.
- And it makes sense that he wears a pillowcase
now that like--
- It does, yeah.
- 'Cause like a whole time I'm thinking like,
man, where'd he get that?
Why is it so, it's like so sweaty too.
- It's true.
I have some Smeagol lines for you to read here.
Starts here.
- What does it say?
- Is it here?
"Is it tasty?"
Come on, keep going.
I don't want to do that voice anymore. It hurts.
Good on Andy Serkis, because that voice sucks to do.
It's fun.
"Is it tasty, my precious? Is it crunchable?"
He licked his lips.
"Crunchable? But it might have a sword, my precious.
Long, thin, nasty sword.
Careful, careful, my precious.
Let us see, oh, let us see."
I can't do the voice very well.
And then basically they fuck yeah, yeah, this is not that good too long
I mean, yeah, this is like I can skip ahead here look get to the Yoda
I want to see what Yoda has to say this is a this is a good a good entrance for Yoda, okay?
Precious he screamed those skylight it burns us nasty Harry Potter
We hates it forever
But just as he was about to reach the cool darkness of the cave a boulder tumbled down across the entrance blocking off escape a soft
New light spread across the night smeagol looked over his shoulder fearful of what would come
stop we say yep dude if that was in a movie like the audience would stand up
and cheer yeah do they'd fuck in they go nuts that's like that's like Captain
America live that bigger reaction than Captain America lifting up Thor's hammer
okay we need to have there's a there's a conversation here that we need to do
okay it's me going Yoda are you better at smear or Yoda I can't do either I'll
I'll do, I'll try Smeagol.
- Okay. - I can just do both
and then you read the stage directions.
- Okay, here, it starts here.
(Smeagol grunting)
Said Yoda.
- So stuck we are, except for you.
- He gestured at Smeagol.
- Come you here, we command.
- Smeagol found himself helpless to resist.
He crawled slowly over to Yoda, head lowered.
He muttered as he went.
- Is that Smeagol?
- This is Yoda.
- Oh.
- If crashed and lost we are,
a cheering up we shall need.
"I'm not showing up, my precious!"
Yoda nodded.
"This sucks. This sucks. I hate you."
"This one's important."
"Mm-hmm-hmm-hmm!"
"Fancy you, we do. Horny we are!"
Smiegel blinked.
"Horny, my precious!"
"What is horny?"
He's going to this next one.
(laughter)
Wanting to put our bits in you. We are
you can skip to this line right here.
This last yoda line
wanting to put our bits in you.
Yoda's bits
said Yoda friends of Harry Potter. We are lots of snary on lonely nights. We
have read a threesome. We need
*laughter*
Smeagol tore off his loincloth and stood naked beneath the stars.
His long-forgotten phallus rose majestically.
He rubbed it, recalling the contours.
The texture, the wiry hairs.
It was a thing of beauty.
He saw Dobby had dropped his sock in pillowcase.
Yoda had discarded his robe.
Both were naked and erect as he.
Yeah.
"Dobby aims to please every friend of Harry Potter."
Read this Yoda line right here.
"Chaffed you with our meaty lightsaber, we shall!"
*laughter*
He padded it.
"Dobby has much experience! Dobby is always of service!"
He knelt and took Smeagol's phallus in his mouth.
The warmth and wetness left Smeagol gagging.
"Gollum, Gollum."
Yoda moved around behind Dobby and thrust himself into the creature's rear end.
friend. He did not even flinch his lips moved up and down the length of
smiegel his tongue so strong and flexible.
Such a tender arse of you yeah, why do they why would they put is the
author British or are they given Yoda the British accent here? I don't know
why do you say cuz yeah, do you think Yoda would say arse
hummed Yoda at last he slapped Dobby on the behind and backed away. Yeah,
is a British author. Yeah. He smacked him on the behind. Yeah. He smacked Yoda.
Yoda smacked him on the behind. That's the most disgusting part of this story.
Hmm? What's the most disgusting part? That the author's British. Oh yeah. Well yeah,
it's gross because it's Ricky Gervais. Yeah. Oh then they just fuck each other.
Yeah. It goes pretty long. Oh they talk about fanfiction. Then they do three-way
fellatio. Whoa. And then here's how it ends. So Smeagol starts sucking Yoda's
dick. Smeagol tried. He got to work keeping his teeth away from Yoda's shaft
but as Dobby brought him to ever-increasing peaks of ecstasy he lost
control. Carried away by the surging power of his own orgasm, Smeagol sunk his
teeth into the meaty member in his mouth. For a moment he tasted blood. His old
hunting instinct suddenly asserted themselves and he bit down again hard.
"Oh, bitterness you have!" Yoda cried. He pulled his bleeding phallus from Smeagol's jaws and backed away.
"Ruined we are!"
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Um...
Yoda got his bit dicked by Smeagol.
And then Yoda hits Smeagol with his staff and uh, they all run away from each other.
It's kind of a sad ending.
Yeah. I would think, I would have expected Yoda to force choke him or something.
Yeah.
This list is too long. Yeah. To do. Let's see we got what 28, 18. 18 more minutes. 18 more minutes.
Yeah. Yeah. Do you want to just sit in silence for 18 minutes? We could.
We could do karaoke again. We could do karaoke again. I wish we could have finished out the
karaoke. I think we could have done a lot more songs. Yeah. We could have. Look up,
Go on top tens, look up Yoda.
I was looking up Friendl, but nothing came up.
Best Yoda quotes. We'll do this.
"Do or do not, there is no try."
That's a classic. That's number one.
Damn, he really did that shit.
Number two, "Truly wonderful the mind of a child is."
Now hold up.
Here's the comment. "I like this one. It adds humor and shows that Yoda appreciates children."
From pedophile420.
From Rihanna410.
one oh oh you know well she's just have she's having a kid now yeah so she's
like the best parent in the world Yoda taught all those younglings mm-hmm and
you know if I'm gonna if I'm gonna look up this one's really getting me number
three size matters not look at me judge me by my size do you and the car said
that in the last story you should have that would have been a little out like a
big throbber yeah I got here's the comments getting me here this could work
from Mario after he says this uses a super mushroom laugh out loud.
Damn, you got me laughing too, bud. Yeah, that's a good one.
Damn. Oh, Yoda and Mario. Looking, found someone you have. Now, when
the fuck did he say that? Probably when someone he was found.
There's like not even that many Yoda quotes. I think Yoda would be a better-
I think they've run out. Like, there's the big Yoda quote. Yeah. The biggest Yoda quote,
or do not there is no try truly the wonder the truly wonderful the mind of a
child is that's like I don't yeah yeah that's a deep cut yeah going into the
deep cuts by number two is a bad sign I know yeah cuz then yeah this is like a
true Yoda fan I think that Yoda would be a better brother to Mario than Luigi is
oh yeah and they're both green well Mario's red no I'm saying Luigi's green
I know I don't think there would be that hard of a transition yeah I think that
they would do a lot better together. I think they would support each other more.
Yeah. Yeah. I think he would.
What? Dude, they should make a Mario game.
What's the Mario game where you have the water backpack?
Oh, that's Sunshine. That, but it's Yoda.
Yoda's on his back? Yeah.
Like when Yoda goes on Luke's back.
Yeah, but there's got to be like some kind of catalyst or whatever, like not,
which I don't think catalyst is the right word there.
Some kind of like a hindrance for Yoda, you know, because like Mario and Yoda
team up that's like too powerful of a team. Yeah, well that's why it'd be so good to go.
I guess... I think Yoda, if he's on the backpack, because
Yoda could just... Yoda could fuck up the Mushroom Kingdom with just like one force push.
That's true. I think Yoda needs to have cancer.
I think Yoda does need to have cancer. I think maybe, maybe there's some...
Malignant tumor. Yeah.
On his brain and sometimes he forgets powers. Maybe he has a brain tumor. Yeah, he forgets...
good that could be really good also he has no lightsaber okay and he's also naked
on Mario's back lightsaber to like end of the game yeah that's like the final boss
well you like lose the final boss and you're like oh it's impossible and then
he has the lightsaber remember where my lightsaber is I do yeah it was in his
pocket yeah time his skin pocket he's not wearing clothes malignant brain tumor I
I have there's a really graphic and upsetting scene.
It's like the surgery. It's like the focus to yeah, it's like the
field of flowers level in in mother three, but it's where it's
just like an interlude thing and you just like walk through but
it's you just like yeah, you just walk through you just are
watching yo's brain get cut apart.
you have to do the surgery on Yoda's brain.
Yeah, and there's like things like a mini game.
Yeah, it's like a mini game.
That's also like a big.
It's a big part of the game too because you have to do it at the
end of every level because the tumor grows.
And that's how you level up because then you can like there's
different parts of the tumor that you can cut out if you yeah,
and if you can gain a skill, but you can also lose one.
Yeah, if you if you fuck up when you're doing the surgery, he
he doesn't die, but he gets like way stupid. It's really sad yeah yeah he's
like he just goes like who are you? He says who are you the entire and then
you not remember you? I do my son you are
yeah and then the final boss is Luigi, who's really angry that Yoda replaced
him as my brother. That'd be good. Yoda Mario is a good name. Yoda Mario would
the title of the game. Yeah, Yoda Mario is malignant. I'd be the yeah, it's also a
time with the movie. Malignant. Yeah, yeah, God damn dude, Yoda with a tumor.
What if it's like Yoda and he's got like a they're going to do that in the in
tumor in his butt. I'm going to do that in episode ten. Yeah, yeah, it's got
his back. Yoda's back, but he's got a tumor. Yeah, they're going to cancer. I
have their bring. They want to bring back. They want to bring back all the
they're like
operate. I need you to do well. They want to bring back all the
like nostalgia characters, but they know people get mad like
because when they brought back Palpatine and shit so like okay,
we're going to bring them all back, but they all have cancer
in different parts of their body, so they're going to die.
They're going to be there, but they're going to be in a back
to tank. They're going to yeah, they're yeah, they're like very,
very sick. Yeah, they're going to be throwing up. They're going
to be acting like Walter. Everyone the entire
all three they're gonna mean all three movies. They're all going
we're going to die at the end of episode twelve, but we wanted them in
there. We knew you guys will be really happy to see it's like test
footage and everyone's like there's like a new gray yoda yeah, it's
just really sick. You know it's just like cannot go on. There's a
guy. There's a new Admiral Ackbar that throws up
and he holds his wife hand and he cries
(laughing)
- Darth Maul's back and he has way more bumps on his head.
- He has like one horn in the center that's just like,
it looks like a fucking like, like, geoduck.
Is that how you say it?
- I don't know.
- Geoduck?
- The clam?
- I have no idea.
- It's native to the Pacific Northwest.
- I know what you're talking about,
but I don't know how to say it.
(laughing)
like the clam that's native to the Pacific. Yeah, I think of geo dude.
Oh yeah from Pokemon, also that's a guy coming to start yeah and they'll have
cancer to
that's you they're good. That's what they do from now on to answer.
Pikachu does just like me.
That's that's how they justify they're like they're going to make like the
next like big like crossover movie. We're like okay, it's gonna be star
Star Wars and Mario and Pokemon and like there so like all these care star
trek they're all crossing through dimensions. They're crossing over into
the Star Wars universe, but because of the like the the power they have to use
the drive for their spaceships, it emits radiation and they all have horrible
answer
and they're like
to work together to destroy Palpatine junior and it's just like squirtle and
his his shell is like cracking. He's like
they have they have a like golem yeah, but like you can see like pebbles are
like falling out of his body and
have Yugi from Yu-Gi-Oh, but he's just in a hospital bed the whole movie. He's asleep.
Yeah, we got Clifford the Big Red Dog, but he's missing a leg and he also has like part
of his face is missing. And yeah, I mean, it's the only way he was able to be kept alive.
It's like the fucking, it's like the scene at the end of Endgame where all the like portals
portals open up and they're like on your left and they all come out, but
it's like they're like we need to fight Palpatine and a bunch of portals
open up and it's everyone like just falls. There's like all
like
green
the portals
gives you like cancer. It gives you cancer immediately instant cancer.
Yeah, it like accelerate.
It's like if you were able to survive with bowel cancer for 20 years.
Yeah, because it travels through time too.
And then all the characters who cross over, they still have cancer forever even in their
own movies too.
We couldn't fix it.
We couldn't fix that in the movie.
Something wrong with the character.
I don't know.
Something wrong with the character!
I don't know!
We tried to publish new Clifford picture books, but he has cancer in all the pictures!
I don't know what happened!
It went through the printer and then he lost his leg!
The artist drew him normal, and then we printed out, and he has one of those big fucked up black lumps on him like dogs can!
*laughter*
Uh, yeah.
you know and then it's like it's like they're making a sequel and they're
like we're going to cross over like even more properties like you're going to
be so surprised with like who shows up in this and they're doing like and like
you're like damn like I wish I wish I knew like who they were crossing over
like I want the spoilers. I'm so excited like it's coming out soon and you like
turn on the TV and it's like Stephen Colberry is a giant to
I was filming a movie, I can't say what movie!
[Laughter]
But I'm really excited for this to come out!
Yeah, oh man, that scene...
Retroactively, all his books on the cover is a giant, like, goiter!
[Laughter]
We have to print new editions of all his books!
Yeah, do you see the new Star Wars movie?
Yeah, I don't know. I'm not really too into it.
I mean, like, you know, it's cool to see like they brought like Yoda back and everything,
but like, he has cancer and then like, when Yoda and the guy, Maury from Tuesdays with Maury...
[laughter]
Have to fight Jango Fett.
Dude, it was so upsetting. After Superman was in the last big Star Wars crossover movie, like, there was this like...
There was this hospital ward with all these kids with terminal cancer, they wanted to meet Superman to cheer him up,
and he showed up and he keeled over and died from cancer the second he walked in the room.
Dude, that fucking final battle in the new Star Wars is crazy. Judge Judy shows up at the end.
*laughter*
Oh my god.
Yeah, I just think it's like one of those stupid fucking crossover movies.
*laughter*
It's just like, they just keep bringing like Judge Joe Brown, and like-
They only bring like circuit court DB judges.
(laughter)
- Oh man, this is gonna be the craziest crossover ever.
We got Judge Cherry, we got Cherry Springer.
- They get a new writer for all the movies
and they're doing another endgame style crossover movie
and it's like all the portals open
and it's only like anthropomorphic animal,
it's like all the Zootopia characters come through
and like Parappa the Rappa comes through,
Bugs Bunny comes through, Jessica Rabbit of course.
I guess, like like hundreds of them every of every one of the like like
anthropomorphic animals ever made and they're like
what wow it seems like like due to some strange chemical in the portals. It's
made everyone who crosses through them pregnant.
It's just three hours of the cartoon animals just becoming this. The
stomachs getting bigger and going "oh I'm so pregnant"
yeah because they're using the- they're basing all these movies off of like the
YouTube algorithm so it's all like Elsa spider-man pregnant
so it's all just shit like that it's just like yeah this is like the first movie
entirely written by the YouTube algorithm
to destroy Palpatine we have to pop every pimple on Elsa's face
we have to do a full disgusting princess makeover
Dude, do they still do those?
I don't know.
I think the algorithm's like shifted now that it's just like, well I'm sure if you look
up like baby shark pimple, something like that, like some crazy shit would show up.
Let's open an incognito window here, YouTube.
Why are you opening it incognito?
I don't want this to affect my YouTube.
That's true.
I'm a baby shark pimple.
That was fucking crazy though.
Like I know you and Pierce used to talk about it a lot, but like the...
shark trap remix. Oh dude I've heard all these. Here's an ad. Dude my nephews, oh man. Dude
I'm so fucking sick of Cocoa Melon. I gotta go home for Christmas. I haven't heard this
in two years and I'm genuinely so mad I brought it up because I literally. I won't play it.
Faster version of Baby Shark. When I lived with my parents and like my sister, they would
play this on the fucking living room TV all day.
What is that?
I don't know.
Diana, Diana E Roma.
Baby Shark, Cocoa Melon, Nursery Rhymes and Kid Songs.
You want to listen to this?
They put Baby Shark and Cocoa Melon together?
Baby Shark karaoke?
Dude, they're trying to kill me dude.
Yeah.
That's going to be the worst.
I'm going to have to go home and listen to that shit with my nephews, pretend like I
like it.
Look at this.
I've been trying to show them Mr. Bean and stuff.
Whoa.
That is a huge pimple.
That's what, yeah.
I've been trying to show my nephews like Mr. Bean.
Yeah, you got to get him started early.
Yeah, I mean Mr. Bean is like the easiest one to get kids into.
They think it's funny immediately.
Yeah, it is really a shame, his mouth cancer.
Ever since he-
I can't speak, his tongue is huge.
Ever since he appeared in Revenge of Palpatine the Third.
Episode 75.
Revenge of Palpatine the third featuring Mr. Bean featuring Mr. Bean yeah yeah
that was a huge get for them they thought they thought the Bean estate would never
allow him to appear. He did it almost immediately. Yeah he has to I mean Rowan Atkinson has to
pay for those cars yeah but you know he should you know it'd be so cool if he
did if Rowan Atkinson did a press conference that was called Mr. Bean
he's like Mr. Bean is dead. He died last night. I saw Mr. Bean. Rowan Atkinson still alive. He was hit by one of my many cars. I have one million big cars. I have one billion big cars and I hit Mr. Bean with all of them.
I can drive them normally. I don't put it I don't drive them from a chair on top of the car.
Dude, that's the crazy, like, Rowan Atkinson just owns a shit ton of Ashton Martins.
Really?
Yeah, dude, he's made, like, Mr. Bean was on, there's six episodes of Mr. Bean.
Yeah, there's very few. How many are there exactly?
Six, because it's like a BBC series.
Yeah.
I think it's six. I don't know.
I watch them shits over and over.
I mean, it's still good. I think it's, yeah, then Mr. Bean the animated series...
Fourteen.
Took off way longer.
Yeah.
But like the original series.
Yeah, there are 14 episodes of the original season.
Oh, there's 14?
Yeah.
Damn, I thought that every BBC series only had 6.
I guess you're wrong here.
Yeah.
Well, well, I'm stupid.
Man, I love Mr. Bean.
Me too.
He be making me laugh though.
My nephew's been calling him Mr. Peppermint though.
It's so funny, why?
We were watching it in the living room and then I think he was a it was is Mr.
Bean when he goes to the public pool and oh yeah and his shorts fall off yeah he
turned to me and said why did mr. peppermint do that I was like who mr.
pepper mr. peppermint is mr. beans nemesis yeah who pulls his pants off all
the time he's a ghost that follows mr. bean around and makes him do all that
fucking dumb ass shit. Yeah.
Your nephew's actually tapped into the deep Mr. Bean lore.
He can see, he sees a Mr. Bean character. Nobody else can.
He's like the sixth sense. The seventh sense is for seeing Mr. Peppermint.
Damn. Imagine how crazy Mr. Peppermint looks too.
Yeah. Probably like a ghost.
Yeah. Probably just a white sheet.
Probably a white ghost.
Yeah. Probably one big white sheet.
Yeah.
Alright.
Go subscribe to the Patreon.
Sorry.
If you love the karaoke,
we're gonna be-
We'll do it again.
Next time we'll do it for an hour.
Can we do-
It got interrupted.
Can we do karaoke on Twitch?
I don't know.
Probably now.
Yeah.
Alright.
Bye.