come back and make a mess
and we see a black
you're a scrap monster
and while
so very imminent a little hot hold on the air
the caleb couldn't figure out how to use his recorder
can you get his plan i did order
that's a whistle
That's a whistle. Do I still have my recorder from Atlantic City? No, it's in my car. Oh really? I found it the other day and then I looked at it and I was like,
I'm not gonna put that on my mouth and then you and then
And then thank god I didn't. Yeah. Yeah. I'd be having that new variant. Ooh, Petty got the Omicron.
What is it like? It's crazy. I mean, it's not crazy if you're the first one. It's a cold. It sucks.
It's nothing. I can't go out for two weeks for nothing.
I should be allowed to go to every bar in Dave and Buster's in the city?
I think you should just go out.
I mean, you can.
That's true, I can go out.
They check, they're not checking.
That's true.
They just check your vaccine card.
They don't like smell your breath to see if you have it.
Well, no, I'd feel too bad if I got anyone else sick, but...
Just do it, man.
You just said yourself it's a cold.
Just start spreading it like crazy.
It is bullshit, yeah.
Oh, I can't wait to spread it to you guys.
I think you already did.
Yeah, probably.
I'm like 90% sure that you already did.
I tried to walk around all day looking for tests.
None of them.
It shut down.
There was a line so long to get a test right now.
Yeah, dude, fucking SantaCon, dude.
SantaCon got everyone infected.
Stop!
You were at probably the fucking gay matrix party where everybody in the world caught
this.
I was at a gay matrix party.
So just admit it.
It's your fault.
There was supposed to be a pony in the living room.
Ben told me there was a pony that was supposed to be there, and then we got there and there
there's no pony.
They were literally using the pony to try and like ferment and breed the next disease inside
it.
New York City needs to be like day after tomorrow wiped off the face of the earth with a big
wave.
Absolutely, it's disgusting.
I'm so glad I'm not there right now.
I didn't catch it until Neil got it.
Liar.
That's a lie, bro.
That, no, uh-uh, because you guys know I kept testing negative.
You probably gave it to him.
No, no way.
And me, bro.
Yeah, definitely me.
If you gave it to me and you kill me, are you going to feel anything?
Yes, dude.
Are you kidding me?
What, will you feel anything if I die and it was your fault?
Don't make me think about that, man.
Oh my God, my blood is slowing down and my heart rate is reaching one.
Oh no, I have one heart rate.
That is, that literally is when COVID started.
That's what I would lie in my bed at night and I would think every night like, "Oh my
God, all my friends and family are going to be killed by me."
I'm going to kill them all.
I'm having those thoughts again.
But in a different way than you used to do that.
I'm having those thoughts again, which sucks.
It does feel like everything's just kind of slowing down to a crawl again.
I like it, dude.
Everything's going to be back open in the summer.
It's just happened like this because it's the fucking winter.
That's fine, dude.
Winter sucks.
Who cares?
Are you kidding I don't have to do stand-up for like two months. Yeah, this is gonna be great, dude
Yeah, it's gonna be awesome. We get to we get to cook up some great new podcast episodes. We're all coughing and yes
Sleezing. Yeah
Yeah, dude, I mean it's I really immediate it's funny
I'm how fast as soon as I knew that we were gonna do a zoom episode
I just slid right back into the normal routine of just like I just sat in my house all day long
Oh, me too. I started drinking at 2 p.m.
Yeah.
I did my famous, this is my famous cocktail that I invented last year.
Sure.
It's, okay, it's one part tequila, one part water.
It's really good.
I've actually, I invented a new cocktail that I've been partaking in today and yesterday
pretty heavily. It's called Cameron's Special. Not Cameron's Special, the Cameron's Special.
No.
Cameron's Special, yeah.
And it's basically you want to take water and you'll need an electric kettle. You heat
up the water with the electric kettle. You don't want it to boil.
Wow.
It's okay if it boils, but you don't really need it to boil.
That sounds awesome.
Pour the water in the mug. Get this, you're going to put in a tea bag and some honey.
You already had me on most of that.
I started throwing it in my mouth.
And you know what?
It's going to steep.
You throw the tea bag in and you lose me.
The water is enough for me.
The hot water, that's like the perfect drink maybe.
That's the difference between the Cameron Special and just the Cameron.
That and five dollars.
That's on the menu.
Yeah, yeah, I a lot more than $5 at my restaurant that I opened yesterday.
You opened a restaurant?
See this is so fucked man.
What?
I haven't seen you guys in so long.
I saw you both for like one minute the other day.
Yeah.
And now and now we're now we're we've been we've been placed on separate poles.
Yep.
This is so hard.
This is literally this this happened every winter of our lives.
Yeah, I know dude.
It's horrible.
that's true I just made that up and said it no because the first the first like
year of the podcast you guys left for LA that's true that was winter oh my god I
guess I'm so smart that I've made something up and it was true yeah winter
is so hard on us winter is one of the harshest seasons I hate the winter so
much for for I need to I need to feel you both we're a lot like we're a lot
like an old depression I don't we're a lot like crops yeah yeah I'm like an
onion because I have layers for that movie you know you honestly Pat you
might have zero
I think maybe you're right.
You might be an apple.
You might be-
I think I'm just, yeah, it's skin and then everything else.
You might, maybe, maybe not even an apple.
You might be a balloon.
Maybe like a mushroom.
Like, uh, the same all the way through.
You're just one-
A rock.
You might be the man with the least layers I've ever known in my entire life.
That's not true.
Name one of your layers.
My poetry. You don't write poetry. You are not an onion. Yes I am. And that's no slight on you.
You have no idea how deep I can be. Okay here, say something profound right now.
What if, what if I died right now? That's not profound. That's not profound at all.
I said that four minutes ago. You're not dead, you're just out of the
the fucking screen. Wait is he dead? Hey Pat are you okay? Pat seriously I need you to say
you're okay right now. Hey Pat. Pat? Pat! Oh he's moving! He's drinking water! A ghost.
He didn't- you don't become a gho- how fast do you think you become a ghost? I'm convulsing!
I'm convulsing from my covid symptoms. Instantly you think? Definitely. What? You think it has to
like load it's just a ghost it flies okay I'm back alive by the way it doesn't
shoot out of you flies out like a like an automatic pitching machine there's
got to be some transition where you're just like in your body but it's dead and
you're like that's dying fuck I'm dead the second your ghost shoots out of you
like a bullet all right where does it shoot out from your mouth that just isn't
true it would break your teeth okay your heart it would break your heart and put
a hole in your body through it doesn't break things you know it breaks my heart
what all the pain in the world okay you earned you just earned your first layer
you're now a rock in a bag you're now an onion that you open one layer of rock
inside and you've ruined dinner so thanks a lot.
Yeah when I when I found out um that my roommate tested positive
I was at the I was at the skate park and there was just like
this COVID truther pro skater there this guy Bobby Pulio.
He sounds awesome. Yeah he's actually sick um
but I told my friends I was like hey I gotta go my roommate tested positive and
and he went, "Oh, hell yeah, get some!"
I was like, did he just tell me to go get COVID?
I think I did it for him.
I think I got--
- That guy's a beast.
- Yeah, I think I got COVID for Bobby Puglio.
- Yeah, he sounds beasted.
- Did I ever show, he, somehow his name got sold
to some like Chinese company,
and now there's like a shit ton of bootlegs,
that like bootleg children's skateboards
that have his full name on them.
It's like a picture of like a shark.
That's really cool.
That's sick.
I wish that would happen to me.
That's actually fucking cool.
Dude, I wish too.
To become famous in China, dude.
Yeah.
Oh, right?
I'd like to, you know, I haven't Googled it.
I haven't looked into anything.
I'd like to think I already am.
Yeah, you might be.
I won't really know until I head over there in about 10 years to make my new life.
But I'd like to think that people are going to know me when I step off the plane.
But I really want to do one of those, you know those like...
Like imagine this, I'm sending the link right here, imagine this but it just says your name
on it.
Okay, let's see this here.
Let me see.
I'm going to look at this.
Okay.
Yeah, that would be really sick.
That's really cool.
Yeah.
It looks, it's, you know what, I'll say this much, it looks like that's the name of the
shark.
Right.
Which is a high compliment.
I would also love to have a shark named after me.
Exactly.
fine with me being famous in China or having a shark named after me that's
about it so tight you know if anybody is a marine biologist at the highest level
and is in charge of what's the name a shark can you please yeah you know
person you can there's like they have shark trackers that are like the Santa
tracker where you can just see where I look at it every day to make sure
they're not anywhere near that's what my dad does that would be so scary to open
shark tracker as a lark. Oh this is cool. It's next door. It's in your house. Yeah, it's in
your kitchen. He literally does that though. He opens up and sees how many sharks are in Cape Cod.
The thing is I think that like a shark is so powerful I feel like if I walked into my bathroom
and there's a shark in my bathtub it might win. You know what I mean? Duh. But like it's not like
Like it's in like just the smallest amount of water, but I still feel like it would win.
Yeah, but then it I guess we'd both die probably if it got out of the bath.
Yeah, if I had a shark in my in my bathroom, I'd feed it some chum.
You don't have to what is chum?
Dead fish.
Hold on.
It is.
Yeah, plankton was wrong.
No for for putting that in his no restaurant.
What is chum then?
a friend or companion. Alright, you know what, you've bested me. That's right. You just got
mentally chest. I don't know if Bobby Pui is a COVID-struther, but still a sick guy.
That's right, you just got mentally challenged. I just mentally challenged you in one. Oh,
you know what I watched last night that I haven't watched in so long? I watched Wild
and out oh dude did you watch the Andy Milonakis episode okay that was on for
15 years and I watched one episode I forgot that it's been on for 15 years
no it was not the no it was the Amber Rose episode oh okay but that they are
so bad at rapping on that show you need you need to audition dude I need to do
that the entire time I was losing it I was like bro put me in coach yeah oh my
God, I in we got to get you on that would be so soon. I'll be crushing it, bro. Yeah. Oh my god
I was like thinking of I was like doctoring all the verses of there as they were as they were spitting them, dude
Yeah, I'm so hip hop. It's it's crazy. You are pretty hip hop, dude
I would I would honestly I would beast on Nick Cannon. Yeah
Yeah
Never mind bang him. No, so he said no
Too far and you just make fun of his his kid that just died. Oh, I forgot he has a doodoo
Sorry, I'm just thinking
Have you seen that like it was like article
It's the article. It's the photo or it's like photo of the dead kid
And as Nick Cannon loses five-year-old child and it's like a photo of like Nick Cannon post it up somewhere
It's so fucking funny.
Yeah, no, that is a funny photo.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, no, it's really funny when a five-year-old child does.
No, he's five months old.
Yeah, that's even funnier.
Yeah, and you know what's even funnier?
The brain tumor exploding his head.
Yeah, sure, Pat.
That's great.
Yeah, that's right.
His brain drowning in his own blood.
Yeah, that's really, really funny.
Oh, awesome.
I'm so congested, I can't hear you guys making fun of me.
It's so great.
It looks like when you crack an egg and there's two yolks in there.
I'm sorry, I can't hear you guys.
Pat, what's wrong with you?
Talking about this stuff.
No, it was really funny when his
pieces of his brain fell out of his ears like spaghetti.
It was hilarious
when his kid's head blew up
like a water balloon you leave on the faucet too long.
That was great.
I'm just saying.
And it was really funny when Nick Cannon rapped about it.
I'm saying it would be funny to go into that
and then try to make
actual beef.
You wanted to make actual
beef going into the wild and out meat.
What is wrong with you Pat?
What is your problem?
You're gonna make beef patties out of a child's brain?
No.
First of all, it wouldn't taste good because of the tumor.
And because he was stupid.
You fucking...
You're disgusting.
I just got bad news.
You're so...
I got I have Delta too and I spread it to you too. That's tight. Listen. I don't care. Just shut up
I'm not saying that it's funny
That this is true
but if you ate
If you ate Nick Cannon's baby's brains out of his head
You'd become stupider instead of smarter because of how dumb this baby was are you are you doing a wild and out right now?
Well, oh my god
drop the beat
(beatboxing)
- It's a double beat special at Wild 'N Out.
- Why aren't you doing anything?
- I'm just listening to the beats.
- Have you never seen Wild 'N Out, Cameron?
- I just like the beats.
But they're just fun beats.
I'm just dancing.
- You're supposed to sing.
You're supposed to do, I forget what the game is.
- I'm gonna get up to the mic at the Wild 'N Out.
some guys are gonna call me bald and ugly or whatever and then I go oh so I'm
pretty much the best singer in the world
and then I show them a one hair one long hair that I grow like a like a pad you
You audition wearing like a wig.
Honestly, if I go to Wild 'N Out, I'm wearing a full like, like, uh, Spirit Halloween Gene
Simmons outfit.
I'm gonna wear the Gene Simmons hair, I'm gonna have the like shitty like fake leather entire
suit and brown shoes with the black leather.
Oh, did I ever...
That would be so tight, dude.
Do you guys ever see, I was Gene Simmons for Halloween when I was 11.
Did I ever show you guys that?
Oh yeah, I've seen that picture.
Yeah.
Gene Simmons or Zero Suit Gene Simmons?
I was Gene Simmons, but like the only thing my mom, my mom bought an Afro wig
and she did my makeup, she did the Gene Simmons makeup really good,
but that was the only good part of the costume. She got me an Afro.
The black diamonds are way too big.
And I wore an Afro.
I wore an afro wig that she was like, "Oh, I'll just like put a ponytail in it."
Because see that's how he like used it, but it's like you can't fucking do that.
So I'm just in Gene Simmons makeup with an afro wig and I'm wearing a cape and I'm wearing
like my school clothes under it. That's pretty cool. That is sick.
What's the best Halloween costume you guys ever did?
Skeleton. You guys want to see it? Hot Rod. When I was like 11.
You want to see my really cool skeleton costume? I've seen this. It's on your fridge, right?
Senior year of high school. Huh?
Haven't I seen it? Oh it is on my fridge. I'm gonna pull it up anyway. This is the best
Halloween costume. I'll never top this in my life. You'll never top this in your life.
I'm gonna top you so hard. You're not gonna top me. Oh my god. I'm on another level.
I'm on the second story. I can't find it. You guys can imagine how cool it is. I'm trying to
think of the good ones I had. I was, I was, uh, I've talked about this. I was a Rastafarian
Kung Fu Master. I was a werewolf. I was a doubly offensive costume. I wore the Jamaican cap
with the fake dreadlocks and also a ge. That's pretty cool. That looks sick, Kim. And a ge.
It's so cool. That is pretty fucking cool. What else was there for Halloween? That's
the one that stuck in my head the most, I think. I wore a white t-shirt one year and
I wrote the F word on it.
No.
Which one?
Not, not, no I wrote like the and then parenthesis F word meaning fuck and then I didn't think
about it because I was like oh I'm going as the word fuck but like I'm going as the F
word and then I like didn't realize I was just yeah, yeah just going around with a shirt
that says F-A-G-I-T on it.
Yeah and and basically an arrow pointing at your head.
Yeah.
yeah yeah yeah yeah and arrow pointing out of your head that's how that's how
they used to mug people in the medieval times. They'd step out of a dark alley an elf with a
giant longbow. Avast ye. Yeah I would say it is yeah halt. I have to download this file now.
Honestly you're right mugging was probably so easy to get away from.
Well, mugging was probably easier back then because it was all swords.
Mugging was not profitable until like, like fucking 40 years ago.
The thing about, the thing about fucking mugging is like, like highway men in the West, it used
to be that, that you could mug somebody who was in a car.
Like they were like riding a horse and carriage and you walk up to them and say, "Stop, I'm
gonna steal from you."
And they'd be like, "Okay."
Yeah, 'cause like you can easily kill my car.
That's the tough part.
If you have a mortal car, that's how you came up with normal cars.
It's so funny to imagine like you're in your car nowadays and a guy comes up to you wearing
like a Zorro mask and is like, "I'm gonna rob you!"
And he's running perfectly at pace with your car at 60 miles an hour.
It's like a self-driving Tesla and he's like walking up to you.
Yeah, exactly.
That's why they need to put a machine gun in new cars.
That's the thing that's the thing if your car is self-driving no reason you couldn't put
a fucking a minigun.
Yeah they need the Breaking Bad gun and all Teslas.
That would be that I mean that's I bet that's why they explode is it's that's a weaponry
thing.
It's probably programmed to just if they see somebody wearing white and black stripes nearby
they instantly blow up in case you have any gold bars.
Yeah. I'm imagining like a nightclub where the it says dress code like no like
large t-shirts no gang colors no black and white stripes and a small black mask
that covers just your eyes. No giant bags with dollar signs on them. Yeah. No snapping as you walk.
yeah is that a thing in the north where they they make it to cat burglars yeah
no that clubs you can't wear like a big white t-shirt in them um I don't know I
have I've never been clubbing before in my life every like bar in the south has
a sign that yeah I think no no like no Jordan yeah no phones that are on oh
No backwards hats.
No in-your-face attitudes.
No political lyricism.
No hollering "eh, bay, bay" in this club.
It's kind of fucking hilarious.
Every bar in my hometown has some sign like that.
The place we went to in Atlantic City, when we stayed there, what was that, the Dome or
something it was called?
Yeah, Pool After Dark.
Pool After Dark, that's right.
I was nervous because I went in there, I was in the all white suit.
Yeah, I knew you were in the all white club.
I was in it, that's not true.
That was not all white.
Why did you say that, Pat?
Did you ignore the other people?
I don't have that bad of brain fear.
You can't manipulate me like this.
I'm going to manipulate you so hard.
I think that you're probably going to end up with long COVID.
No, that's not real.
Yeah, yeah, I bet it's not.
That's not real.
You're going to get it, dude.
Long COVID's not real.
You're going to be like this forever.
COVID isn't real, but long COVID is real.
Oh, what, how I'm already, how I already am?
What are you talking about?
Tomorrow, tomorrow, I'm going to bank on this.
you're gonna wake up and you're gonna feel just a little bit weird and you're gonna feel like that
for the rest of your life. Long COVID is so funny because it's like my 60. I've had so many beers
today already I'm obviously gonna feel weird tomorrow. Long COVID is like my 60 year old
dad got COVID and once he got better he breathes heavily when he walks up the stairs. Right. I
think he has a permanent syndrome. Which you long COVID. Yes. Yup. Yup. I think I almost certainly
have it. I'm not saying, GBO's leaving tomorrow, I'm not saying bye tonight I don't think,
cause I'm worried that I have short-covid. Now I think I do, now that what Pat told me
about that it's just a cold I think I do probably. And I think I probably gave it to a thousand
people. You need to go upstairs, you need to lick all your mom's food. I gave it to
so many people in Dunkin Donuts this morning. You need to lick every fucking glass in the
pantry. There was a homeless guy in Dunkin Donuts this morning who straight up had vampire
fangs you can't just had he just had he he had two really long teeth that were
that were if you're in Dunkin Donuts I didn't get it in Dunkin Donuts no you
can't sell you fucking asshole no that's what I'm saying you don't worry about
that because you if you go in there you're not giving it to anybody you
can't catch it in there it's a safe zone it's true yeah it's like a spawn zone
yeah do the Dunkin's in in mass still have a lot of the ones that I used to go
to had that Duncan like branded ATMs in them. I think so. I don't know because I always got
that cash on me. Damn. But where do you get it from? My mom. My mummy. I got it from me
mummy. I got the cash from me mummy. It's kind of, Duncan should just open a bank man.
Yeah, dude. That would be sick. I would switch over immediately.
I would literally, I would read any of the-
If I could have a fucking debit card that just looked like a Dunkin' gift card.
They have to have a Dunkin' credit card, right?
I might actually try and order a Dunkin' Donuts picture.
You can put anything on your credit card, yeah.
Yeah, I might try and do that.
Um, 'cause dude, it's the best.
Dude, you know what'd be sick?
What? Wait.
So the Dunkin' Donuts bank, right, it gives you 10% cash back
on Dunkin Donuts.
Okay, here's my idea.
It gives you 20% cash back on Dunkin Donuts.
That's a way better idea.
100% cash back and I'm not going any lower.
110% cash back.
Yeah, 300% cash back on Dunkin Donuts purchases.
Bro, holy shit dude.
What?
Dunkin Donuts has a black card.
No way.
It's a special gift card that they give to celebrities.
Oh, you know who got one of those for sure?
BJ Novak it says.
Ben Affleck probably.
I was just about to say BJ Novak.
Dude, the second paragraph here is "Celebrities like BJ Novak" shows off their top tier
Dunkin Donuts status.
Can we try and get one of these?
Dude, I feel like it's a must, right?
We're all locked.
I want one so bad.
Now that I know this exists, I'm not gonna rest.
What fucking podcast reps Boston more than us?
True.
Literally, we're the only ones.
Yeah.
Fuck all this Barstool shit.
No, Dave Portnoy, you don't rep Boston.
do that's right I'm starting a second beef yeah unless you guys want to buy it as
you don't have to be a celebrity to get a Duncan black card Duncan superfans have
been awarded the card for other things including becoming the 1 millionth
member and Duncan's loyalty program and simply being a frequent visitor at the
chain so if we can be like if we can okay I'll be the two millionth member
Pat can be the three millionth and I'll be the four millionth and we'll each get
it
to
out
me do my intro and make it a Christmas the tune that's what I'm gonna do make
you wait okay hey guys it's Christmas week and we're so excited to do to
Christmas themed episodes for Christmas week that's right it's Christmas week
Week and today's the first day of Christmas Week here at Podcast
About List. So why don't we jump on right into it with the first list of
Christmas Week for on the first day of Christmas Week, Wednesday the 22nd.
From the top tens.com this is by user Moldy Sock. This list for the first
week of christmas week is called most embarrassing presents to get for
christmas
that's right
mhm
you didn't sing it
most embarrassing presents to get for christmas
number one is underwear
i have a... i need more underwear so bad
if anyone wants to send me one thousand pairs of
beautiful expensive underwear
nobody wants to do that
if anyone does
there's going to be bad stipulations to that agreement
maybe like a three hundred pound sugar mama
from
what?
from the south
what is it? what are you saying? i'm trying to recruit a sugar mama right now
for christmas. it sounds like you're trying to recruit tyler perry
to send you a good bunch of the under and it sounds like you're giving away my
fucking play head
do you guys have an i have an art that always gives me underwear
it's not as i guess i don't know what i was going to say another
well here we are let me let's read the car with the comments have to say about
or cuz i think they would disagree with you here about it being the best gift
there's the top comment
if i had a pair i say i won't wear it so my parents say i have to
that i will poor we in them to not wear them and they will take them away but
then they make me wear a nappy. But I think that is better than some underwear.
I think this guy might have the worst life ever.
Yeah.
That's a horrible situation to be in.
Dude, I haven't done any laundry and I'm down to my last pair of underwear.
Yeah.
And I don't know if I can go and do my laundry.
You know that, you're going to be in your house for the next two weeks. Just wear sweatpants.
Yeah, I know, but my, yeah, that's true.
You don't have to wear underwear.
You know what I don't own?
Nobody's going to be doing, nobody's doing a nappy check on you.
You know what I don't own is sweatpants.
Well, you gotta order some brother. Yeah, I know I literally right now never never bought a pair of sweatpants
That's why I don't like sweatpants, dude
You're better where if I wear sweatpants or pajama pants, I can't like I look I mean
Well, I leave your house. Yeah, that's the fucking point. I won't leave my bed
That's fine. You haven't there's nothing you you're you have your bed in your computer for the next two weeks. Yeah, that's true
God damn it dude. I already want to kill myself. You should play it then. You should play Fortnite with me.
It's fine just do it. It'll be over really fast.
It'll hurt really really bad, and then you'll be... It'll hurt forever.
It'll hurt, but you'll be stuck in that as a loop forever.
That's how, it's the moment of the amount of pain you're in when you die is how much pain you're in. It's your punishment for sinning.
Yeah, that's what they don't tell you.
That's what I get this one's a script so okay Patrick you'll play boy
Caleb you can play behind boy
Pause and I'll play everyone we are we already what I you want to be everyone too late. Oh god back to school day
I'm going to take off my pants so you could see my door underwears. No takes off pants ah
You want to see Dora stickers on my butt?
We already see it. That's behind a boy. Yeah, that's from Jay's top ten list. It's a pretty good script, man
There's a pretty good. I think I'd like to I'd like to option this
Yeah, I think a 24 could do something really beautiful with this. Oh, oh my god. Can you imagine?
Yeah, I don't mean they'd call it behind boy, and it would it would make so much money
I already think of a theme Michael Michael chick-list plays behind boy. Yeah
People yeah, Ari Ari Aster directs uh-huh right it's called back to school day
It's called boy boy boy is played by Steve Carell
Yeah
Yeah, that's pretty good and people people what if his dramatic roles?
People will be like the trailer now branded razor scooters, and yeah, yeah
24 movie the the the trailer would have no no
Voice over at all the the boy pulling down his pants would be like rhythmic to the music
They go like play play that they play that children's choir version of creep, right?
Uh-huh, and then fucking the guy from the Naked Brothers band would say you want to see my Dora stickers on my butt
And it would go ding
ding
We already see it
Damn
Fine boy. Oh my god
That'd be really cool. That'd also be a great movie.
That would be a good movie. This next one would be a good movie too.
What are you supposed to say in front of everyone when presented with a pink Lacey number from
your uncle Cecil? Well, they are not actually my size, unk, but thanks anyway. Awkward!
Haha.
I love calling my uncle unk.
Oh dude. I didn't get to say that enough as a child.
Bro, I won't get to see- bro, if- if COVID shuts me down, locks me down,
fucking anchors me, I won't get to see Matt.
Oh, dog.
For Christmas.
Damn.
I'll miss him coming up to me on- on the 1st of January saying,
"Haven't seen you since next year."
Last year.
Since next year.
He always messes it up the first time.
Damn.
Someone I know recently got SpongeBob underwear.
Seriously, he just ran a mile after that.
If you got that Spongebob underwear, you know you gonna get clowned at the playground whenever on underwear day.
Yeah.
*slurp*
This comment...
*laughs*
This comment's really good.
"You call that bad? How about Fishing for Floaters poo fishing game?"
*laughs*
Is that a real thing?
I have no idea.
Is that a real game?
*cough*
I hope that's not a real game.
I think you should check-
Oh, that's a real game.
Yeah.
Fishing for Floaters.
Wait, there's-
What?
It's a- it's a little, uh...
Yeah, dude, it's turds you put in a bathtub.
Oh, man, they're making dookie games now?
They did make a dookie game.
Back in my day, dookie was something you just left on the ground.
Now it's a whole game?
Dookie was something you throw out of your window.
That's disgusting.
When you're done with it.
Back in my day, it was something you let roll down your leg in the grocery store.
in my day you your mom got mad if you had dookie in the bathtub now you get a prize
Now she buys it?
Now she buys it for you? What kind of bullshit is this?
Now you get it on Christmas?
I do remember I have a very clear memory of when I was like three or four maybe
and my younger brother's like was he's like two I guess my mom put us in the
bathtub at the same time and I took a dookie in and then blamed it on him
because he couldn't speak English oh my god yeah I've never there's a floating
poop and I was like what the hell Levi you farted shit in the bathtub man. I've never pooped in a tub.
Me neither. I would highly recommend it. It immediately cleans your ass. Does it
feel like like a home birth if you know what that feels like? I would say it
It feels exactly like the other water births that I've done.
Yeah?
That's good.
You ever taken a doo-doo in the ocean?
No.
No, my cousin did that once.
Not in the ocean.
If you do that, it'll attract a fish.
My cousin was told to go to the bathroom and then she dropped a trowel and just like started
pooping onto the water.
I'd be afraid I'd attract a great brown shark.
Yeah.
Me too.
It smells it.
It smells it. There's dookie in this water.
Yeah.
Comes up, starts eating my butt out of the floating.
The poop shark, dude.
Yeah.
Pretty scary.
The dookie eel.
Remember that shark from Zoobooks? The Zoobooks commercial?
It's the shark that like stays flat on the ground.
Remember Super Mario Land?
I don't know what Zoobooks is.
It's like a shark that like sits in the sand and like...
Remember colored ketchup?
Fuck you.
Shut up.
Yeah.
It's a shark with like a big mouth and it just like inhales fish into its body.
Remember riding our bikes?
Can you play that Uncle Adams song?
Uncle Adams.
Go to the last comment on underwear. I have some exciting news.
Oh my god, another script?
It's a sequel.
Holy shit.
To Behind Boy.
To Behind Boy, the hit A24 film?
There's four parts in this. Me, everyone, boy, and Jacob.
Well, I was just gonna say, imagine that Zubook shark inhaling your dookie out of your butt for you.
Come on.
That's nasty.
Alright.
Okay, if I have to, I'll play me. I guess.
Okay.
Caleb, you wanted to be everyone so bad, you'll be everyone this time.
I guess I'll be boy and Jacob.
You'll be boy and Jacob.
I'm going to take off my pants so you could see my Donkey Kong underwear.
No!
Too bad, takes off pants.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on. There's a...
Sorry, this person, whoever wrote this...
You're supposed to say "cut".
Yeah, cut, there's a dire need of a script supervisor here.
Halfway through the script,
me changes to boy.
It's two different characters.
I don't think that's two different characters.
You don't think two different characters can have Donkey Kong stickers on their butt?
No.
Okay, can we take this from the top, please? We need to get this...
It doesn't make sense.
listen we've been shooting all day okay we are hemorrhaging money we it's cost so
much fucking money to have Michael chiklis on set okay we cannot do another
take of the studio okayed this a sequel to the palm door winning behind boy all
right all right the sequel to behind boy Jacob it's it's called shot of a
called a couple of people
yeah it's gotta be taken to the tagline is this time it's donkey kong
yeah i think it was a little bit they get a comedian to play a serious role here
they get him gaffigan plays jacob
okay are you know i'll keep that in mind for the line reading
okay
and action
i'm going to take off my pants so you could see my donkey kong underwear
to bad
takes off pants
the hell
which one it's a boy
your boy
tied to it seriously it makes more sense of you read that line
there's two clearly it's different is a difference between me and boy here
because i will be probably everyone to the boys probably everyone is such a
everyone kind of includes a lot of people okay
so yeah this line you're having trouble with that you don't really more
it is it makes a lot of stuff from the top of the house and i just maybe i just
I fuck card no craft services for you today I'm going to take off my pants so
you could see my Donkey Kong underwear
no too bad takes off pants what the hell you want to see my Donkey Kong stickers
on my butt we already see it see it makes more sense Kim it makes more sense
if you read the donkey i didn't write the fucking script our job is to do what the
director and writer want us to do okay
look all right i'm just saying
dot my my order we got the terry okay
and i can't i can't go against mister aster he's sorry a stare ever heard of
them
that i'm just a really he told me me and boy are two different characters okay i'm
not going to go against him i'm not putting my neck out on that shopping
block you can if you want
I just don't understand this.
But I'm not going to be responsible for that.
I don't understand.
Also, you need to gain 500 pounds for this role.
Yeah.
I'm already halfway there.
You need to gain, no, you need even more.
Yeah?
I need you to get, Ari, sorry, Ari needs you to get really humongously fat for this role
right now.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Well, that's all we can ask, right?
Number two, a sex education book.
quick how cool would that be to get cast in something where they're like we want
to pay you ten million dollars yeah to eat every everything you've ever wanted
that would be sick first for a month you to eat butter we need you to eat butter
we need you to eat milkshakes with with olive oil in them that'd be so
incredible that would be tight I need to become a character actor yeah yeah be
funny to get to for them to like hire you to play a fat guy and you're like okay
we're just gonna give you a fat suit and like prosthetics and stuff and you'd be
like no I want to bulk up for this like I want to do it method I want to be real
and you just die yeah whenever like fucking Christian Bale talks about like
for the machinists he like a can of tuna and an apple and that was all he ate
every day for like months yeah like how I couldn't I would die yeah I don't have
an actor's soul. These people are unkillable. Also Lady Gaga did the female version she
gained 15 pounds. How did that not kill her? Christian Bale is British so he has Oliver
Twist DNA in him. That's true, yeah. He can sit there and ask for more but he's not getting
it. Lady Gaga, that bitch ate Oliver Twist. She ate her cheese twist. She looks fat as
shit in this new movie. You better not say that. That's so wrong. I'm just saying. You
better not say that. She's more like, she's more like Lady Big Big. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
up
world
she she is so happy
okay number two
a sex education book the top comment
no kid should be knowing that kind of stuff
that can lead to the big addicted to it they can cause harm to them
did you have a really i was just say that look
that uh... your parents gave you that made you know where does no my parents
just uh... let me do whatever i wanted on the computer
really i mean i definitely are yet that but the but the point i got the book i
already knew how long do you mean a book that had a i'd think i knew it's ex-
was from friends
and then yeah mom gave me a bit units it's ahead like fucking for actual
photos of chickens having sex
Whoa yeah so now I like I got there was a chap it was like there was a chapter
that was about like girls or whatever like awesome but yeah like you say the
PDF well that was it was like and and I like obviously I got the book and that
was the first thing I looked at I just opened after skip to girls yeah the
literally the first line of that chapter was like you probably just open this book
to this page right?
*laughter*
Go to the table of contents
Birds, bees, love
I guess I'll go back to the beginning
Pussy
Chapter 6, Pussy
I was ready
I think I asked my parents
like when are we like as a joke
like oh when are we gonna have the talk
and uh
my dad was like
I know damn well you already know
about that shit and just did not did not want to talk to me about it. Swag.
Here's another comment. I'm under 13 and was once a Nicki Minaj fan. Do not get me
started. Facts. Me too. I'll hear about sex from an Anaconda video. Pat's
responding right now saying OMG me too. OMG me too. Hit me on telegram. I'm gonna
to leave the call. You can't leave the call. I'm leaving the call. Nope, you're not allowed.
Oh, number three is coal. Wait, hold on, look at the last comment on that last one. Wow,
look at all the pictures. That's disgusting. Did you guys have sex ed in like school? Yeah,
we did and they had like, you know how they have the anonymous question box? Yeah. Yeah,
They got we had a different kind of box in my sex head.
Yeah, yeah, the teachers, the anonymous teachers box.
Dan.
Yeah, there's a you put your hand in hole.
You put your hand in like the dune box.
I honestly I remember I remember I'm sure everybody holding a different kind of needle at her throat.
If you know what I'm talking about.
Yes, sir.
I come to bar baby.
And one prick from this you die instantly.
I'm sure every person who's a boy in middle school can relate to this but I really heard
that we were doing sex ed and I was 40% sure that it was gonna, they were gonna pair us
off and let us have sex with our crushes.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
I did not think that.
Now it's time for a live instruction.
That's right, yeah. Now it's time for Lisa Anne, your sex ed teacher, to come in and fart
on your stuff.
Can all the ugly girls please leave the room for this next lesson?
Just the girls!
Yeah, I...
All the guys that could stand.
Ugly men, you're awesome. Ladies, you might have to work.
We know that you're good in your heart.
We have an odd number, so there might need to be some trios.
Yeah, well, you guys are going on it. You guys are going on a field trip to the McDonald's
to learn how it's run. Yeah, on a field trip to Macy's, you guys are going to get to hang
up behind the counter and see you know, sex ed should have been sex ed should have been
everybody in the class loading up into a magic school bus and then just going into one kid's
dick yeah that would be funny that would have been what they did in the show just
ruin his life yeah yeah everybody in the class saw the inside of his penis
yeah and the outside oh yeah I'll be farting so much in there yeah I love to
just destroy his penis with my fart I'll be doing graffiti and farting and yeah I
would not I would not lick the inside of the wall I don't want to know what that
taste like? I would taste the wall and see what it tastes like. Brandon's fucking... Brandon's
dick? I would call out sick that day I ain't going in no man's penis. And I may have a
disposable camera with me but it's staying in my pocket. I might accidentally go off but I don't
know how to stop it from making a flash so that's not my fault. Yeah that's right.
Yeah. And I might and I might and I might try and put an Xbox controller in my
underwear and have and have my friend hit me and halo a bunch of times so I've been
there but it's cuz it's funny that's right no that's right I might have
somebody take off my shields and halo so that I get that rumble as a joke so it
sounds like I'm farting yeah yeah and I might carve my name in a heart plus
Brandon's name on the walls of his penis like an old oak tree but it's just as a
a joke. And I definitely won't be skateboarding around it. I'm not gonna grind on his fucking
urethra if that's what you're asking. No, definitely not. That doesn't even make sense. Yeah, it's
not gonna play Superman. It's not gonna play Goldfinger's Superman. It's not gonna play...
I'm doing a loop-de-loop around a vein. It's not gonna play "If I Go Crazy Then Will You
still call me Superman hmm that's a good song damn yes sir
go crazy then will you superman they had the anonymous question box in my sex ed
class and they got rid of it because there's one kid in my class who kept
asking questions like if I accidentally leave cum on the toilet seat will it get
my mom pregnant? It's a very romantic question. It's also a valid question.
Asking it over and over is the funniest part. It's just like having like some kind of toilet
baby. Well also how bad does your mom have to be?
That kid was probably having literally a month long panic attack.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh absolutely.
How bad does your mom have to be at sitting on the fucking toilet that she slushes her
pussy on the fucking...
The whole, the whole seat gets up there?
She's gotta be doing that on purpose, man.
Yeah.
There's no way, she saw it and she was like, "Hmm, maybe that's Ashton Kutcher's."
Number three is coal.
Yeah, embarrassing for sure.
Yeah, I would hate to get coal.
Oh, I would hate to get coal fuel on my trains.
Here's what I would do. Okay, you guys, Kim, you be my brother, okay? It was good for Christmas.
Okay, I've just opened my present and I pull out a chunk of coal. It's coal.
Serves you right.
Serves me right? What do you mean? I asked for coal. I love coal and I asked for it for
Christmas. And see, that's how you keep it from being embarrassing.
Oh, okay. I get it now. I get the scenario. Okay, it took me a second there. That's a thinker.
Yeah, it is a thinker. Yeah. There's a little bit of a twist. Yeah, it does have a twist
on the Christmas format. Yeah. Yeah. I ask for coal every year so that when I'm naughty,
I don't even know. Yeah, I'm saying it's like, I've been saving it up. You've been naughty
on coal, you're getting your new, you're getting a brand new RC car. Oh, shit. I hate RC cars.
Yeah, and you'll probably hate that it looks like a shark and it can go in water or land.
Are you ser-
*laughter*
Oh, that's my least favorite feature!
And you'll probably be livid that it can fly with a helicopter rotor.
You have to be kidding me. Wait, is it sold separately or did I get it too?
And you're gonna hate the fact that-
You're gonna hate this tri-phibian car with batteries included.
Yeah, and you're gonna hate-
You're gonna hate that it's got a picture of Thanos on it.
you're gonna hate that the house
uh...
all i just wanted call for christmas
yeah and that's how you teach a kid a lesson
safety channel as intended
number four is the other end
here's a comment
for positron wild hog
a complimentary gift i'm certain
well positron one auction
mom and uh...
said but i mean intellectual comment there
Well he's an intellectual.
Yeah.
Uh, number five, Justin Bieber's CD.
Wow, just what I wanted.
I'll play it once and throw it into the fireplace to show it how much I love it.
Canadians make terrible music, someone says.
That ain't true.
I prefer dubstep anyway.
That's what someone says.
Yeah.
Facts.
Y'all heard scary sprites and freaky...
Oh my god.
Scary sprites and freakier sprites.
Yeah, scary sprites and sprites with evil red eyes. That's a really scary song.
Mostly the title. The drop is crazy. The part when it goes,
the part, the part when it, when it goes like this, right before it gets really loud.
That part's, that's my favorite part. When it goes, the part right after the
but before the wow where it goes the best part
yeah that's what it's like this
yeah or sometimes it's like this
we will really i don't like the sound wall wall wall wall wall wall i don't
like that
wall bullshit dubstep should just be the part where it's like
oh yeah i like the beginning when it's are you waiting for for cinema
that parts that's the best part of the song my favorite part of dj
sets is when my favorite song gets quieter. Yeah, and then my second favorite song. And
then it sounds like a like Bowser's making a noise. Yeah. I love DJs, but I hate that
scratching. Yeah, knock it off with that scratching. You're ruining the disc. I didn't buy this,
I didn't come here to listen to my favorite songs be scratched and disrespected. That's
I came here to, here's what honestly the perfect DJ literally walks up to the
computer a MacBook Pro that has the rap caviar playlist from Spotify loaded on it
and you know what he does he presses spacebar and he plays it all the way
through because you know that rap caviar shit gives me more, that rap caviar shit
fire as hell, it gets me more turnt than anything. That's right hey DJs if you
You better stop scratching.
If I wanted to hear, if I wanted to hear wiki wiki wiki, I'd read out my Google Chrome tabs
at 3am.
Am I right guys?
Yes sir.
Oh my fucking god.
Pretty good right?
Holy shit.
Would that roast a DJ if I told that to him?
Hey DJs, if I wanted to hear Scratch, I would, I would uh.
I'd go to my middle school computer class.
That's what I was gonna say.
That's right.
Yeah.
Got to it first.
I was gonna fucking, god damn it man.
Took you so long.
like a couple seconds to load yeah no you think you're so cool rubbing on those
records why you try with a DVD huh yep yeah that's not gonna work out for you
fucking idiot halfway through my favorite movie right the Wachowski speed racer
halfway through that all of a sudden we're back at the beginning for no
reason I'd fucking kill your ass yeah you'd be the worst projectionist of all
time yeah hey you want to turn some tables how about you turn that table
away from me yourself that's right that's right you piece of shit if I
want yeah yeah hey hey yeah you're on the ones and twos well that's what I call
being on the toilet so you're you have a stupid job bitch
because you go you know one and two and you're on that that toilet yeah yeah why
Why don't you, why don't you get, you're leaning over that machine, why don't you go slave
over some real machines at a factory?
Learn a thing or two about a trade.
You're sitting there on your laptop, why don't you sit on top of Santa's lap and wish for
a new job?
Bang!
That's right.
Yeah.
Yup.
Sick.
Sick ass people.
You crush them bro.
With disgusting lives.
You know who's cool though?
Horrible habits.
What?
Who's cool?
the guy who does the the DJ is like drop Alex yeah that's a cool guy that is a
cool that's the only cool DJ yeah if you have a cool DJ drop you can you can live
everybody else get the fuck out of here yeah which way would you guys go with if
you had a DJ drop shit you're gonna add you're gonna get gunshots to a song I
I wish I would come to you add gunshots to you
Yeah, and a bomb dropping and also I'm gonna reverse your entire life until you're a baby again
But what if I came into your life and I started skipping around
Huh, you wouldn't write that at all. Oh all of a sudden you're taking your first steps. Oh, you're taking your last breath
No, I'm messing you up with another guy. Yeah, that's right. You guys are becoming one your DNA is combining. Oh, yeah
Hey, how about you meet Steve? This is Steve. You know what Steve does that's right data entry
Yeah, now he's stuck to your fucking face. You have the same body now
You're trying to you're trying to press different buttons on your MPC. Hey, you know what up. What's coming up?
Files that's right that and that is how you make the songs feel when you mix up without me by Halsey with
yellow submarine uh-huh fucking idiot
why don't you put your headphones all the way on?
You can't hear shit when you do that.
- What, he got one ear?
Only idiots have one ear.
- What, are you gonna walk around with pants
with only one leg, that's what you look like?
- And here's another thing,
here's another thing about Steve, he's a wimp.
- Yep, and you're attached to a wimp now, so great job.
- Yeah, great, oh, good for you and your career.
You got, you got, you got--
- A DJ combined with a wimp sounds like just a DJ to me.
i don't see any changes
get him yeah i wish i was in the room so i could high five you
you think you're you think you're so tough just cuz you stand on a platform
above the whole crowd if you're on the ground they'd rip you apart
they would tear you apart day of the dead stay dry and quarter you
you'd be sitting there saying choke on them you're a test to be flying out
you know why women are jumping up on people's shoulders they're trying to kill you man
they don't like you ok they're screaming because they hate you so much
their boobs have lasers in them and they're aimed right at your face so don't
blink
but pretty much d_j_'s are dog shit
yeah they suck
yeah number six a baby nappy d_j_'s are dog shit there's a mean bastard named
bobby van poppen from team galaxy and that's his main present
don't know what that means
number seven i know exactly what that means a baby show dvd facts
yep that is embarrassing a baby show dvd number 10 is condoms well you guys ever watched oh
i guess have you ever washed a condom and reused it yeah of course yeah uh i found it
i forgot about this is one of my favorite ones on here um number 11 is book on weight
loss and this is such a good comment this is the last comment on book on weight loss
Do they even make these? It's kinda obvious on how to lose weight.
*laughter*
Facts. Facts.
Also, fat people can't read.
What's the point of these fucking books, man?
Yeah.
Pretty famously, I would say.
Number 14, ticket to fat camp.
If you're overweight, you're more likely going to get this.
True. That's a good point.
Fat camp still exists.
Number 15.
like he's been there and he forgot number 15 a dead bird i will put you in jail if you do that
number 18 is tampons the top comment is from xx society's underscore biggest underscore rebel
and it's well thanks for reminding me about my useless uterus that serves me no purpose
other than to cause me unnecessary pain every month as a child-free female."
Wow.
Damn, society's biggest rebel.
Truly, truly the biggest rebel.
Holy shit.
Society's biggest rebel is one of the coolest.
Yeah.
And with the double X on his bookends.
That's pretty good.
That is a crazy ass.
Oh God.
Oh God, and in front of my brother.
Dot, dot, dot.
I hate these, somebody says.
If you need them, then this is something nice.
Number 20, a nightlight.
I love nightlights because I'm scared of the dark.
I left that comment.
Number 29 is poop and the only comment is, "I know someone who eats this."
[Laughter]
Number 35, kisses from granny.
The only comment, "You have to directly get this."
It's true though.
That is so true.
A box of food.
Why would that be bad?
Gummy bear.
What?
That's an awesome gift.
Yeah.
A stone.
Well, what if it's the sorcerers?
A lemon with Anne's smiley face.
Okay.
Pink bunny suit.
That's cool.
That, that is, that's ripping off from a Christmas tale.
Tubby custard making Christmas.
A Christmas travel.
And number 69, the last on the list, fundies.
is that yeah fundies but it doesn't sound like a very good thing to you for
Christmas that sounds like fun undies that dear listeners wraps up the first
day of Christmas week on podcast about list the thrilling new feature that
we're not being paid to premiere this week and also it wraps up the first two
in the in the behind boy saga yes yeah which we will be finishing next week
okay bye