come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
you're a scrap monster
yeah okay
there's a sparrow at the window i can feel you both again
yeah i know
and i'm feeling you both again
we're back
unbelievable all crazy
i never thought it would happen again i do i can i can i can see you guys i can
feel you guys I can hear you but I can't smell or taste you. Well that's the
problem because you've had your tongue and your nose all up in me all day long
yeah so you might want to get that checked out. I'm used to it. Yeah. But you still remember what I
smell and taste like. Oh I wrote it down. Okay then we're fine. Yeah good. That's what you were
writing in the terminal before the episode. Yeah I was writing in the terminal.
Yeah. Yeah what you have is terminal. I do. Yeah. Sorry to announce this on the show.
leukemia. You would never get leukemia. No. You're not like, I feel
like you're not big enough. Well I have it. Honestly, I don't mean to say it a bad way,
you're not big enough of a talent to die of cancer. Does that make sense?
Look at my diet. People who get cancer die. No, no, fuck you, I'm gonna get cancer.
No, you know what? No, shut up. Prove me wrong. You know who had cancer? My grandpa.
Really? He must have been a great man. I think so.
Was he like a great writer or something?
I feel like you have to be really
No! He wasn't a great writer or something.
He was my grandpa.
to
Yeah. He did.
He worked at Polaroid.
He was the CEO of Polaroid.
I think you're like high school car crash talented.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. I did get in the art show in 5th grade.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Oh yeah.
school you would die in a car crash everybody be like hey wow he could have
he could have made it long enough to get cancer yeah but he died what's the yeah
well so what age bracket is cancer or what's how I bracket are we talking age
or talent it's a mixture okay well I want you to lay out the whole the cancer
sometimes grass cancer from the ages of one to five that just means that you
were basically just nothing and like nobody ever yeah you were a white blood
So yeah, you are a white blood cell that for like you might as well never even been born if you get cancer when you're a baby
Like that's like a huge waste of like hospital bills and all that
dot you're just like feeding the
fucking medical industrial
Feeding like in League of Legends. Yeah
Yeah, I quit yeah
system. There's no point in fucking yeah. Just stay in limbo. Just stay. Don't go through
the big door. We don't need you on this plane of existence. If I got diagnosed like next
week. That'd be funny. What do you mean? It'd be so funny. It'd be funny but like. And then
I would say ten to twenty five, that's the real like lost talent year. Years. You know
what I mean? Ten? Well there's some talent. Have you ever seen, what's that fucking. Look
up America's Got Talent. That Asian fellow with the violin. Who's that? Yo-Yo Ma. He's
not ten years old. He's still ten. Wait, is he actually ten years old? Yeah, he's been
ten a little while. I didn't know that. No, I think he was really good at ten. Like, I
feel like that's when prodigies get cancer. You know what I mean? It's like ten to twenty.
We'll say twenty, right? And then you have the post-college years, the twenties where
everybody makes their masterpiece. And then I feel like in your thirties, if you die of
cancer in your 30s that means that you you were you were stopped from making
from being really truly great. Does that make sense? Yeah like Robin Williams.
Yeah like Robin Williams. Yeah. Who died of cancer. Yeah. Cancer of the mind. Yeah.
And then if you die again I would say... Cancer of the soul. Yeah. Yeah. And then if you
die of cancer late in life you're just like... You're someone's grandma. Yeah. You
have a grandma kind of thing to you you know what your talent was fudge if you're
old you got grandma that's right your talent is making a really amazing
Thanksgiving pie uh-huh yeah yeah the sweet potato with the marshmallows in it
yeah yeah I know your son has had that as a kid yeah dude I made it for
Thanksgiving I know he did fucking I know I know your southern Baptist ass
good wasn't Baptist yeah you were was evangelical Oh evangelical were you
baptized yes and what do you mean oh were you bet everybody gets closed eyes
case closed it's not bad every everyone gets baptized Catholics get baptized
around we should make our own kind of bad did I say this on the podcast what to
say what it is for us to know like an evil Shabbos boy that like baptizes
Jewish people why do you have to be a Shabbos boy that could just be like a
Jack the Ripper, Jack the Dripper. Yeah. Right? Well I was thinking it was because
you know like they can't like during uh was it the Shabbos? I don't know. Whenever
they need a Shabbos Goi. The Sabbath yeah. When they can't like. That's a
cushy gig. They can't turn the lights on or anything you know so it's just like oh
no no no like he's like pushing like you know it's like oh it's so dark in my
place and he's like oh no trust me trust me there's no, there's nothing there. And he just trips him into a
a kiddie pool you my friend have a dark and twisted mind I don't think so I
think Shabbos go I think would be a really good job yeah I mean yeah I'm
only saying that you know what and let it out there is the exception get it
what if you get what if you're what if you're going for a Jewish guy who has
like a robotic leg and you have to like yeah you have to like take care of it if
If you got a robotic leg, do you have to take it off?
Dude, prosthetic, can you imagine like smelling somebody's prosthetic hole?
Did I ever tell you?
Fuck.
Oh, wait.
Speaking of...
Did you?
Yeah.
What?
So...
You smelled someone's fucking leg hole?
So, well not like the stoma, but like...
No, the like hole that their leg goes in?
So there is a Christmas tradition in my family...
To smell grandpa's leg?
So my mom's grandpa had diabetes and got his leg chopped off and had a prosthetic leg.
And then when he passed away, my family at our family Christmas party put a wreath in
it in the leg and wrapped it in tinsel and shit.
And it was tradition for us to take photos with my great grandpa's prosthetic leg.
There's a photo of me fucking crying next to it.
That's like true detective shit.
Yeah, I know.
What the fuck?
That's fucking crazy.
There's a photo of me just straight up crying next to it because I thought it was weird.
Do you remember the whiff?
No, not really.
Can you imagine that?
Are they plastic?
Is it plastic?
One day that smell is going to hit me again.
I don't like rubber and stuff.
Well, I mean, this was like in the 70s.
So that thing must have been made out of pure oil.
It was a different guy's leg.
(laughter)
- They could only do swaps.
- The different guys' leg that they put
like a piece of rebar in.
- Yeah, yeah.
It was the, yeah, it was the guy
who couldn't afford the medical bills leg.
It was two guys who lost their leg.
- Yeah.
- It was a Chinese guy's leg with a,
like the marking of like a train wheel on it.
He just put it on his grandpa.
- It's like that fucking, holy shit,
what was that show called?
- The leg show.
- SpongeBob.
No, all right, well I'll just explain the premise of the show and then somebody who remembers it
can reach out to me later. It's like a guy, they had Lego sets of it and you could like,
he could replace his limbs, that was like his power.
Inspector Gadget?
No, no, no, no, no. It was like, it wasn't called like Max Steel. I remember Max Steel,
Max Steel was a different Lego thing.
We need to have like a theme song for the segment of the show that is us trying to guess what
Patrick's talking about. Yeah. That would be a good thing to have on hand whenever.
Yeah, a soundboard. It's a Lego set and they have like this. If we get
space, office space, we got to get a physical soundboard. Yeah. Yeah, a huge one.
Yeah, they fly around in a blue sphere. Effects pedals. Mm-hmm. See, he's still going.
We're talking about... Yeah, so if you remember that, just hit me up.
About a blue sphere man. A blue sphere and a guy who can change his limbs.
- That's called the Earth, Patrick.
- Yeah.
- And there's Legos.
There's a Lego tie-in.
- There was a Lego set.
- There's a TV show.
I think it was on,
I think it was on ABC Family.
I think it was on WBZ Kids.
- It was on my ceiling at night when I closed my eyes.
- What if I, yeah.
'Cause what if I just made this shit up and it didn't exist?
- I wouldn't put it past you.
- But I remember the Lego set.
- It would be funny to have like
a creepypasta candle cove situation
where you're like watching static every day,
like a creepy kid,
but then it's just like, yeah, like,
I invented a new superhero.
And he's awesome.
- The other day I was, I made myself laugh.
I should have texted you this.
I made myself laugh thinking about like,
you bringing a girl home.
- Me?
- Right, yeah, and like, everything,
stuff's getting hot and heavy, right?
Right, like really hot and heavy,
and you guys are like making out in your room.
- You were thinking about this in your live range?
- You were thinking about me having sex.
- No, you were having, this was a separate scenario,
and then later you thought of something that you could--
- I thought of something funny that I could add to it.
So I imagine you, I'm not going to waste a thought, I have so few of them.
There's nothing better than laughing after you jack off.
But you, you're hooking up with someone right?
And then you like, let's say you're making out right?
Listen, you pull their, listen dude I'm trying to get you horny.
You pull their pants down right?
you know and then they're they're laid down on your bed right there about to
get their fucking shit sucked on right and then they look up thinking of and
then they look up at the ceiling of your room and you have those glow in the dark
stars there is a there is like a crazy frog stuffed animal that hangs on my wall
I think the glow-in-the-dark stars are way better my room is already way worse
you should do the glow-in-the-dark stars. You've seen my room I looks like yeah I've been in that
situation it looks like Pee-wee's Playhouse you've taken me home I have
yeah yeah you unbutton I got those H&M pants with ten buttons on the fucking
zipper. It takes you ten minutes to get my cock and balls out right and as you're doing that I'm just looking up at those stars
stars yeah and it spells Pat you've spelled Patrick with these it says good
night. Patrick
in glow the dark star oh yeah I need more shit like that in my house. I need to get
I need to get funny stuff on the old silly shit on your walls. He's like
deflated birthday balloons like taped by the string to the ceiling like hanging
not even a joke had that in my room had that in my room when I was like 18 I had
a deflated birthday here's a frame sock like the first dollar at a restaurant
they're like what's that it's my some other paper I have I on my wall I have a
drawing you gave me at Moo Yaw's yeah the first week we met that's cute and
then for me you just got my cum on your sheets I think a little bitch I have a
drawing that was in the whole she
Wall my first night with Caleb
Single dot
Like one of those things where it's like I like strings with like clothespins as much up with a bunch of Polaroids and it's just
Come just all over your face
very slightly different angles just like a hundred like a 360 thing cuz I was
doing like a 3d study yeah can I recreate the camera rig that they they used in
the matrix to make the camera spin around where it's a bunch of still photos
at 360 degrees we need to you and me need to hook up we need some way to meet us
getting back in the room together has made you way too sexual we need to tell
we need to get we need something tumultuous our friendship is too good
these days I need to fuck it up by you me have it's a yeah that'll be there'll be
a good way to have any cas yeah we I mean the first couple years of the show we
had struggles did we you guys were in LA yeah then Kovu that wasn't a struggle
that's fun dude it's fun you guys had a good time in LA the Sun shining on my
back hell yeah yeah didn't have credible what do you mean surfing bikini model
is a guy's bananas every day there's a friggin Boston by myself I was in
friggin Boston was a friggin Boston I had a work at wife alive but yeah you guys
were in New York and I was in Boston yeah so now Kate we need to go somewhere
that Caleb can't go me and Kayla we're gonna go to we're gonna go to Acapulco on
our honeymoon we're going on a vacation. I'm gonna listen to me I'm gonna I'm
gonna edge you until you're so full of cum you float like the Goodyear balloon.
Blip. That's what's gonna happen. Yeah no listen Patrick we needed move somewhere
that Caleb can't move for a long time. Yeah cuz we went on we went on vacation.
We wanted a short vacation that was too short that didn't that didn't measure up.
Why don't you plug your ears plug your ears we're going to a castle in Europe
We're gonna move into a castle
Little do you know?
And I just heard that you guys are going to the halo
The ring without me and you guys know that's my yeah, you should move there. You should look for yeah
Every day plug my ears
Why is he plugging his ears? I don't know you guys are gonna plan something - no we were in LA
It's the lat Caleb has to be a band both you plug your ears, okay?
I can't, I'm wearing headphones.
Okay, well just turn off your ears.
I'll close my eyes.
Okay, close your eyes.
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go to the grocery store by myself.
Okay, you can open them.
Okay, speaking of closing your eyes, do you guys want your Christmas presents?
Oh yeah.
Oh, right now.
I forgot mine.
I guess I have to give mine on the next.
We've been talking about Christmas presents for so many episodes.
Yeah, oh, so okay, well let's tell, Caleb, tell us, tell them what you got us.
I got Cameron Ruth Bader Ginsburg Funko Pop. It's awesome. Yep, and I got Patrick a
shirt with a dabbing unicorn and it says "Fighting HIV/AIDS is my superpower. What
is yours?" Mm-hmm. And I wore that in a bar for a couple minutes.
When I first gave it to you, you seemed so embarrassed. He was so shy. I was like, "Put it on."
You were like, "No." He literally balled it up. There were three people like looking.
wearing the same shirt.
(laughter)
Wearing the same shirt, just looking at you.
- Well that bar was like kind of packed
and there was three people looking directly at me
and I was just like--
- Did they seem like they had AIDS?
- Yes.
(laughter)
He balled up the shirt--
- Three very skinny people--
- And he pushed it into a corner.
- With IV drips sitting at the bar.
- I saw their lesions.
- What do you, what they would like if you wore that shirt.
You're saying you're fighting and it's not that you,
you don't say, it doesn't say I'm fighting for.
You fight against.
- I guess that's true.
- Yeah.
you they are you actually disappointed them by not putting it all i did put it
on later you looked at
well you had a certain set i hate i hate aids and you looked in the eyes of three
people with aids and you bought up the certain you should have to do it
slap them with it
yeah yeah you think i i think fighting aids means fighting people with a
yeah i had a t-shirt canada shot at the who wants their present first
me
you're kidding
okay with you said which one you think is better first okay wait let's just
both close our eyes and you both give it to both of us. I'm gonna give Patrick his first.
Come on. Pat, close your eyes. Keep your eyes closed. Oh, keep them closed. Don't open them.
I'm gonna do the... Hold out your hand. Hold out your hand. Oh my god. Okay, open.
Wow! Read it. My nephew has the same one. Read it. What is it? Tell people what it is. Read it.
This is the chat and count emoji phone.
From?
From LeapFrog.
I'm so fucking jealous.
Read some of the, read the blurbs on there.
Play games and watch cute videos starring Scout.
*Gasp*
Add emojis just like a real phone.
Just like a real phone.
50+ activities and phrases and songs.
Wow!
It's pretty exciting, right?
Champ, plug it in.
(laughs)
- Hi, this is Scout.
Let's talk on the phone.
- Talk to--
- Talk to Scout.
- Talk to Scout, I wanna hear what Scout has to say.
- One.
One.
(phone rings)
- Hello, police?
My friend just got me the greatest gift of all time.
(laughs)
- I need a friendship ambulance.
I have too much love in my heart.
- Oh, geez, I'm having a heart attack
'cause I love this.
- It's full of love.
My heart's attacking me with love right now.
That's very sweet Cameron.
Yeah, I thought he would love that.
Was that on your list Pat?
Yes.
Yeah?
Who are you calling?
My mom.
Hi, let's count to ten.
Whoa.
Scout is with your mom right now?
Scout, what are you doing with my mom?
Two, three, four.
Scout is counting.
Scout, Scout is counting with my mom. What are you doing with his mom? Does my dad know?
Does my dad know you're counting with my mom? He's counting strokes. I can't do this anymore.
This is fucked up. I'm sorry dude. I'm sorry. I thought this was a great gift and now I
find out that Scout and my mom. And now it's all public too. Yeah exactly.
And we can't edit that out. We can't edit it. This is going live to tape. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm fuck my turn your turn close your eyes
Okay open oh
My god open it up new fashion weaving cap
Invisible nylon hair nets with elastic easy to apply size control makes one size fit most hairstyles
Put that on open that up put it on you should have have Jana style it for you
Whoa, wait, it's a wig!
Yeah.
Oh my god!
It's beautiful too.
It's platinum blonde!
Holy!
Oh my god.
I've been needing one of these for so long.
Put it on, put it on.
Dude, this thing is like high quality too.
This is a good wig.
Yeah, that looks... damn.
This is like a hundred dollar wig you got me.
Yeah, no.
Was it?
No.
I wish.
Just say yes.
Yes.
$50,000 whoa you look like inu yasha
Yeah, dude you gotta get that style
Wait wait limit block one. I like that move your head oh
My god, that's amazing. I look in the mirror. Holy dude Wow
Literally look like an anime
(laughing)
- It's kinda hard to-- - It's so crazy.
- I can barely see it.
I really gotta cut it, but I do love it.
Thank you so much.
- Dude, you straight up.
(laughing)
Say something evil. - Why you crushed it.
- Say something evil. - Blocking your eyes.
- Say something evil.
Do I look like a--
- You kinda look like-- - A big sword?
- You kinda look like-- - You look like a--
- Malfoy's dad.
(laughing)
Lucius.
- Should I grow my hair back out?
- The way that you're playing--
- Lucius Malfoy.
I can't see.
You just instantly, you put that on you literally instantly started acting like a girl.
Wait I need to get a hat, hold on.
Yo what's up, what's up with Scout?
I want to see the emojis.
Let me see.
Let me see that shit.
Woah.
Damn, woah it's got a whole screen and shit.
this is great not really a lot of choices between the emojis there's over 50
activities I got I got my hair over 50 activities holy crap you have to wear
this everywhere I'm going to I'll wear it out you should cut it into like a bob
or something I feel like I like the link the length is good it's like really I
I think you have to style it a little bit though.
I think you got to maybe.
I think maybe it's...
I can't wait for Patrick to be giving me back shots and pull on this and take it off my head.
It's also...
It's a good color.
You're never going to outgrow the Trixie Mattel allegations.
Yeah.
It's a good color.
You can dye it whatever color you want.
True.
Oh my God.
What should I go?
We should have a wig dyeing episode.
I think it's really funny.
It's just like plain white.
But like blondes do have more fun.
people you could always diet blunder near
here
thank you very much and you're well and what did you get us patrick that you
brought with you
i'd forgot mine
great you for got yours okay great you literally for god i know i know
that you guys are a lot of them
i spent a lot of time i guess the attunement
whenever whenever patrick is i think it is shit together yeah
you know you're my i'm i was it because it right now and then go to my house and
and then I can give it to you.
- I bet you haven't even bought them.
- What are you talking about?
- That's what I bet.
I bet you haven't even put in the thought
to get your best friend's anything.
- I got you stuff.
- Like what?
- He got you like five things, Caleb.
- I didn't get you five things.
- Like every day we hung out.
- I kept buying him one of these.
- Every time I saw him, he'd be like,
"Look, this is what I'm getting for Caleb.
"It'll be something different."
And he'd be like, "No, I changed my mind."
So you have a lot of gifts coming to you.
- I kept buying him stuff and then realizing I liked it.
So that means that you got me something good at least at first and then you got me something
stupid that you don't want.
No.
In the end.
No, because I want to keep the thing I got you still.
Really?
The thing I got you now is actually really fucking sick.
God, dude.
We were supposed to get, I hope it's another wig.
That wig is shedding.
Yeah, I've definitely ruined my...
And Cameron, I got you...
I gave you an anti-girlfriend gift.
I got you something...
Yeah.
Well, I don't need a girlfriend.
I'm my own girlfriend now.
That's true.
I got Cameron something...
I'm so damn pretty.
something that it will complete something else for him. The first half of his penis?
No you remember what I got him. I've been waiting for something like that for a long time. A second penis
half? Yeah. Oh my god. That'd be nice because you have that kind of blank space between
you're playing your balls and it's in your plane. Your tip floats like Rayman's dick. You just have a
floating Rayman penis tip. It's floating but when it's not when it's not there it's plain. Do you
I think Rayman just has you know you know like I think Rayman just puts his whole
body up in there. Do you think he's very small? Do you think he even has a ball sack or do you
have two floating balls? No. He's not wearing well oh right cuz he's wearing
clothes. Yeah. Do you know do you know when you dress up as Captain Hook? Yeah.
The hook that you hold like a thing inside and it's like a it has a hook and
you like hold the thing inside? You need a small one of those that your P-hole can
hold on to. Uh-huh. Oh. And get a hook on the end and then you can use it to carry stuff.
I just the Prince Albert at that you know yeah, we will kind no, but you just
hold it yeah, but you could get more guys yeah, you know, you could carry a
small bag of groceries. I don't know if you guys relate to this. I whenever I
bring groceries back from the car, I'm like I gotta get them all in one trip,
you know, but then if I could I can't look at you because I'm too gorgeous.
Look at me eyes. Do I like a slut?
Do I like it's like like retraining my brain? It's me. It's making new neural
connections that aren't supposed to be there.
It's retraining my brain.
You're going to take this off and like kill yourself immediately?
Do you guys think I look better with this?
You look, you look, wait let me get a glamour video here.
Whoa.
Dude, toss it around.
Let me see.
Wow.
Get some, get some slow-mo shots here.
Oh my god.
He does make me act like a girl.
Let me, let me slow-mo it.
Hold on.
right go horrible job I have only been a girl for 10 minutes okay and you're
already you're criticizing me yeah how about you try to be a guy can't believe
it damn I'm gonna crack your it now I'm definitely having sex with you
no chance I'm not gonna fuck you crazy news for your wife you're gonna get
crazy nudes in your life from my phone okay I'm not even hairs I'm gonna be in
it the hair is not gonna be in it gonna be my body my beautiful naked body maybe
you'll get a strand poking out of the top of the frame yeah I can live with that
so did anybody give me like a dress I thought you already had one or a thog
what's it called fog fog the thing that weird underwear girls yeah Oh Oh
Thog that's a thing. What are they called? He heals he heals. He heals he heals. I
Don't know. I need a lipstick
Don't need a ball of lipstick need some lipstick. But what you need to carry the lipstick in is your purse
I need to get it. I need to get a pruce. Yeah. Yeah, what other shit do I need? I might need a
Jewelry, I need some jewelry. Yeah, I need something clanging on my neck right now. Definitely. That'd be crazy if you got like
you know, there's like a
What are they called?
Brass?
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
I kind of look like a Bratz doll right now with my banging body.
You do.
Yeah.
I look fine.
Some make up.
Yep.
Here, ask me a question.
Any question.
I just imagine a kid getting a Bratz doll that looks exactly like Caleb.
With a trucker hat.
Just crying.
With his fucking hair.
Just fucking crying.
Because it's so beautiful.
We should pay a company like a million dollars to make an action figure of this look.
Alright, ask me any question. What's your favorite color?
I don't know. Oh my god.
Did that turn you on? Oh my god.
I'm gonna flood.
Oh my god, I'm gonna surge. I'm gonna do the flood Super Mario Sunshine.
when you do the rocket nozzle from the world
christ all go
last
well uh... now i need to see the big
girl versions
the very
everyone i mean a lot of people have seen the girl versions of me
you know you know everybody walk by on the street somebody posted that photo
the face of the mail up
beautiful as hell
you seen that one me with the bangs
every time i use face at the most of the make me grow i look like a fucking
bitch
yeah i'll excel route
are you slay that i look like
if i if i saw the face that version of me
in line like in front of me i would leave yeah i would not want to hear them
order
at the register will you just have yet you you it works i would i have i have
a very face i have a version of me i have the mail and i don't
i have the the mail version of resting base phase but like not the mail for
like I just have resting bitch face but like on a guy. But you cover it with a beard now
but if you got if the beard leaves the beard and mustache is gone then it's
full bitch. Yeah you just look like a stupid sexy bitch. Yeah yeah yeah I mean I
look girl version of me look fine as hell. You got a resting friendly face. I'll make
her my damn wife. You would not want to marry a woman who looked just like you
actually maybe you would maybe you would actually. I wouldn't want to marry a girl
looks just like me. Bald. Two Patricks. Two Patricks raising a family of other people
who look exactly like me. No. Patricks, the scientists finally create like, like, like
asexual reproduction for humans, like cloning. And, and they, they tested on Patrick and
just like a full family of cloned Patricks. It's like fucking duplicity. They just keep
getting dumber and dumber duplicity that's what it'd be called
no that was it multiplicity or duplicity that movie you know I don't know what
you're talking about but I don't know yeah oh I'm thinking I'm getting you
know what I'm doing like it bond girl a little bit you could oh my god yeah
Katya James Bond you're Katya extremely pussy yeah Katya stinky
Katya wet pussy. Yeah, Katya stinky vagina.
Nadia. Katya borette vagine.
Nadia vagina.
These are drag names. Yeah. These are just...
I know, fuck, we've unlocked something crazy in this episode.
I like when drag names are like, they have poop in them.
Yeah. That's funny to me. Petunia fart. Yeah, Petunia fart.
Petunia fart. Yeah. Scooby dooby dooky.
what about Lucifer poop ah yeah I can't I can't get loose of her poop because I
love it so much can't shake loose of her poop Dana poop I like her poop diamond
that might be good what about some fruit Lucy fruits good what about like so I
I can't think of a good last name for this, but first name Poopa.
Poop-a-lot.
Poop-a-lot of stuff.
The Knights of the Brown Table at Poop-a-lot.
The Wipes of the Brown.
No, stop.
The Shitter.
Fuck.
No, and it wouldn't be King Sharthur.
It wouldn't be King Sharthur.
And what are the knights names?
Lisa Newcar.
Knight.
Who's one of the knights?
I'm trying to think.
There's Lancelot, there's Galahad, there's Turdcivil.
How about Sir Turdcivil?
God I had a big shit.
That one doesn't work.
Golly I had a shit.
Golly I had a shit in my pants.
At the brown table with Sir Shartfur.
The wizard Turdlin.
Oh, the smelly grail.
[Laughter]
The smelly grail.
The smelly grail. That's pretty, you know, it's pretty easy for me. I'm a professional comedian.
The smelly grail. It's not that hard. Yeah. But I think this is going to be a new era for me.
Yeah.
I got to say, I'm not sure we're ever going to record with me not wearing this again.
Yeah. I feel like the guy who invented the atom bomb right now.
right now. Do I look like Lady Gaga? This is what I'm talking about. I just became
death. I need to put on... I just changed the world in an irreversible way. You Oppenheimer'd
my head. I'm going to put on sunglasses and I'm going to look good. Dude, if you had this
outfit and you put on sunglasses and you just went into a CVS, like 20 people would ask
you for an autograph. Yeah, they'd just think I was famous. The Bud Light hat, sunglasses
in that hair, people would be like swarming you.
Put me in a big shirt, I'm fucking Ariana Grande.
Big ass hoodie going over my thumbs.
Oh my God, lollipop?
Yeah, that's right.
Lollipop, tiny little tricycle, I'm Ariana Grande.
Spiral, tiny little tricycle, spiral makeup on your cheek.
Like Tessa hair back here.
Oh yeah.
You go like, ho, ho, ho, ho, he, he, he, he.
That's right.
That could be a really good look for you.
They're gonna ask me for an autograph.
You should play the Jigsaw puppet in the next Saw movie.
That would actually be huge for you.
Why would I-- I don't look anything like him.
You look exactly like him.
Really?
Yeah.
I think I have similar facial structure to Billy.
Definitely.
You have big red spirals on your face.
Oh, you put those on just now.
Yeah, with my lipstick, okay? It was here.
Oh yeah, we got the lipstick, we got the purse.
I got a whole makeup do-it-yourself outfit.
Yeah.
Carrie thing from Mary Kate.
You look like a princess.
You think so?
Would you look at me-- would you guys rescue me?
From what? That's important.
Bowser.
Bowser?
I'd complete one world but if it was a year in another castle situation I'm not
moving I'm not going to the desert maybe Lemmy. Lemmy? Yeah. What's that?
What are you saying? One of Bowser's kids. What about Bowser Jr. Lemmy one of
those guys I'd rescue you from them. Oh okay. I'm saying I'd fight like one boss
like I'm and I'm definitely not hitting the desert. Ludwig? Definitely not water
world. Yeah that's one of Bowser's kids. Why not water world? That's the best song.
Let's list them. That's what the podcast is about.
That is true. I think that I could be kind of a third Mario princess next to Daisy.
You'd be the fourth. Princess Luna. Princess Rozo.
Princess Lunala.
She's not a princess. For you to be a princess you have to be caught by Bowser.
That bitch is a god. She's like a space god.
You could be Wario's girlfriend.
you mean it yeah. Thank you. Winsett's Weech.
(Laughter)
Yeah.
They should have Winsett's Weech. Yeah, why not?
They should have every-
She would look more Italian than Mario does.
Okay, wait. This would actually be a great game. I'm pitching this to Nintendo right now.
Yeah. Wario, like, gets a big machine and he starts a converter and he puts everybody through.
And so Mario has to change everyone back and it's like Woshi and Wonky Wong
long yeah and wowser and winces wheat and everybody turns wario style and it
could be called mario vs. wario the game because there will be a movie that
comes out before it and the game is a game version of the movie it's a tie-in
movie disappointing exactly or aragon to find out that you were
can you imagine how upsetting that would be to find out that you're someone's
Wario. You just see a better looking version of yourself, skinnier, everyone loves.
That happens to me every day.
But you don't meet fucking Matric all the time.
True.
They have to have the exact same name.
The thing about Wario and Mario is if it weren't for their outfits and they ran into each other,
they might think that they're like cousins I feel like.
True.
It's the outfits that makes them enemies.
And also the upside down.
Like if you walked into a CVS with your sunglasses and your Bud Light hat and you saw somebody
hat with an upside down Bud Light logo. Yeah. Named Daleb. Yeah. A Coors Light hat and a brown
wig. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Even that you would see him be like, "Whoa, that's crazy!" But like
an upside down version. Yeah, I guess it does have to be Bud Right. What? Because you know
like the Waluigi, the L goes upside down. But everything would go upside down. Fuck
fuck right
wasn't all going upside down turn into an hour
look at it is one of the hand right now
she flip it upside down
becomes an hour
i don't think that he comes in our thinking it becomes a i guess maybe like
a lower it becomes a really possible i would i never again hangman
up to an element of cancer
yeah you know heard that
to bring a little family
you're really mad cuz i'm i'd did the word in my made up language with its own
alphabet
Yeah, you didn't guess a Durthon. I'm also drawing the guy exactly like my dad.
It's all done in Sigillium, that fucking language Bam Margera made up like two months ago.
Yeah, actually yeah. Look at that, it's the fucking Plan B logo!
You didn't guess square.
Yeah, they have every letter except one. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so today we have a list. We have a list. Top ten things humans do that aliens would find most weird.
Do I look like a kind of like if they did me look like you look like that would be the roach you look like the
Alien Android thing from near automata you look like the like Oh Oh to be no
Yeah, no, you look like the bed that villains look like me where they called. I forget their names
To be to be here's my thing bitch put some pants on you
you need to be way more goth if you're gonna look like to be you look like that you look like the
android things. I got a fucking briefcase full of goth shit in my bedroom buddy. Test me.
You're not wearing it, you don't look like 2B. Plus, if you were 2B I'd be able to move
my vision to look up your ass right now. And your ass is firmly on the chair. That's a really
good point. Who's, what is this? 2B? I'm thinking of- They made like the most sexual video game
character of all time. Yeah, literally the most- Yeah, she's just wearing a thog and
that's it. Yup. And that camera goes everywhere. I was thinking about the gorillas character.
Oh no 2d 2b should be wearing is 2d swario hey get rid of this thog I'd like to
see most these women wearing a thod mm-hmm the horn is a death what's the
horn is it that thing that's like it was wiper was wearing oh my god Viper Viper
was wearing a yeah tightening it so hard that he like couldn't breathe he had
nightmares in the world. I'm like ascending and he just kept making it
tighter and putting more on and he called it the hornets of death. The thawed.
The thawed. Damn. The hornets of death. So cool dude. That was so sick. The hornets of death. Number one, applaud. That's a thing that humans do
that aliens would find most weird. I never really thought about it before but
applauding is actually really weird. Why do we smack our palms together to show
appreciation uh whatever whatever it's got whatever it's right
clap at magic tricks yeah monkeys do clap that's a good point but they also go
which I don't do yeah you do name one time I've ever done that you just did
that right now I'm gonna take the wig off I go I go
what I go whoa was I'm cool happens in the Marvel movie you do you don't watch
Marvel movies. Oh I clap. Marvel movies are cultural slurry. Anybody else?
Yep. Anybody else? I disagree. It's a baby entertainment. Anybody else? I disagree.
Anybody else? I think it's the greatest movies. Except for Half a Star out of a hundred.
Anybody else agree? I think they're the greatest movies. The compositions
are flat. You? And the CGI. Anybody else? If you don't like Eternals, analyze that. I like to
call it a turtles because it's a big turtle at the end of the movie sorry for
the spoilers the movie it turtles if it's gonna have a turtle in this movie
is so idiotic that I don't even know where to begin and yes Kumail rides the
turtle yeah okay he's got a turtle as a steed yeah this is gonna be called a
turtles fucking stupid movie oh it's just like it's that movie immature
juvenile childish try it they tried to mature the formula with the end but
ultimately it was just so star dress the Avengers they should have called it
cringers the way that I a cringe I winced the Hulk turned it green my god
I'm at comics he's not green and that disgusting fucking junkie waste oid
Go on
Playing that one character Robert Downey jr.. Yeah, yeah, oh well. I I do agree with you on that
He is human we do need subhuman. Oh my God
He needs it. He needs a life-support suit to even be on set
Yeah, looks like a robot that thing probably probably fucking takes his pee out of his penis and puts it back into his mouth
Yeah, he said it's his fools him to think he's they're feeding him oxygen like he's Frank Booth and he's acting like Frank
He breezy I heard content. I heard he tried to drug a piece of shit tried to smoke this tesseract on set
Yeah, I already smoked cigarettes on set how does that to have some that he endangered?
his fellow cast members
It's true by creating a portal to Thanos. Yep. He went on SNL cuz he thought it went meant suboxone
narcotics narcotics and light okay and
And laxatives that's how much the drug addict is
He'll take a laxative cuz he just gives a pill. Yep fucking pill head piece of shit
Yeah, and another thing Paris Hilton newsflash. You're a whore
Okay
You dress like a complete slut so and you and you
Wear some underwear when you get out of the limo
You fucking whores. Oh bozo slut. Oh, he's a crap
Lindsay Lohan
Lindsay job get your shit together. It's your shit. Okay. I love you in the Disney originals
such as Freaky Friday, but I don't want to see your damn snatch on my
ears. And you know who else? You're doing fine. You know who else? Taylor Swift.
You stop whoring it up in movies like the Lorax, okay? You're rearranging the
chemistry in my brain. You are a slut. To get a big bouncing boner when I read Dr.
Seuss books. Dude it's so sick that for like Perez Hilton's whole thing
for like years was just like drawing on like pictures of Britney Spears being
like "DIE SLUT!" Yeah it's cool he was right. She should have died. I wish they used
Spears on her. Yeah and here's the other thing. Hey Perez Hilton how about me and you go to
of Hilton yeah I show you my present whoa that's a bit of a wordplay situation and
another looks like shit there's a starlet there's a starlet from 2008
Caleb Pitts hey Carmen Electra stop wearing that damn wig you look like the
most sexual girl who ever lived you piece of shit you look like Paris Hilton
and Nicole Richie and it's basically Mary Magdalene and Jojo Siwa.
No, that's a kid. Don't act like she's a kid. That's a kid. She's like 20, she's like your age.
No she's not. Swear to God she is. Look it up. I don't want to, no, I don't want to look it up.
Look up Jojo Siwa on Cameron's computer. Look up Jojo Siwa age right now. Do not do that.
no
and here's another thing
and scarlett johansson
while you go get lobotomized so that you talk in movies i can just look at you
that's right
how much you get comply dot they put your brain into a thousand robot body so
there's more of you for being movies because i love you so much better but
instead of brains it's just one boob
it's not a star in the head
and then the arms are boobs
And the legs are boobs and the feet are...
- They're the same. - Here's an idea.
What if we turned Jennifer...
Jennifer Lopez, if you're gonna be such a whore,
we might as well turn you into a boob monster,
you fucking stupid bitch.
Right?
If you're gonna be out there showing Pitbull your asshole
on a music video,
I might as well have a boob version of you in my house.
Salma Hayek,
why don't you stop slutting it up on TV
and finally adopt me?
That's right, Salma Hayek.
Salma Hayek, you are disrespecting Frida Kahlo by being a whorish bitch.
You need to settle down and be happy as your child.
Stop posting these pictures on Instagram and make me an instant dinner.
I'm hungry.
Oh my god.
I need an instant gram of dinner.
I have a small appetite.
One gram of chicken.
One gram.
One gram mashed potatoes.
one gram of peas and one gram of gravy and that's all I need and then you need
to take me to work cuz I'm an adult child and I go to work talk and make me a
ham hock you bitch
somebody is imagine a yes somebody's like how did you stop posting on Twitter
and make me the make me awesome dinner that's right people celebrity slut to
they need to become their mom.
You need to be my wholesome mother.
- Like 2008 tabloid guy, his only gripe
is that they're not his mom.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Britney Spears--
- You are showing way too much skin.
You need to tuck me in.
- Britney Spears, you're saying about toxic.
Listen, mom, I got sick, I can't go to school,
and you're staying home from work.
(laughing)
That's right.
- Gwen Stefani, no, we're not cool.
I need to be tucked in.
Yeah, hella good, I need hella food, I'm so hungry, I'm your baby. Yep, hey,
Rihanna, stop singing Ponda Replay, we gotta get on the freeway, I'm late for
soccer practice.
Hey, Justin Bieber's wife.
Tell your dad to stop killing people. You're clinging to Justin Bieber,
meanwhile, I got a fever. Yeah, and I'm sick. And I'm sick and you made me
make a noodle soup. Yep. I need a rectal thermometer. I don't like it in my mouth.
I would do anything to get rectally thermomated by a starlet. It would be incredible. Hey,
Carmen Electra, how about you go to the car man and make it electric. Yep. Dude, we got
to save the environment, mom. Hey, Caleb, you're so obsessed with starlets. Meanwhile,
I got scarlet fever. I'm very ill. I'm praying for you. Does anybody care how ill I am? Does
anyone care if I would die? Would you care if I died? Number two, walk a pet dog. Walk
a pet dog. Yeah. They'd probably walk a pet blorbazoid and we'd just tell them, oh no
it's like a blorbazoid, you walk it. They'd go oh, yeah. Did you have to teach them how
to pee on newspaper yeah yeah yeah it's like yeah yeah my blurb I have to I go
through with like six holograms a week with my blurb azoid yeah yeah he won't
stop peeing on his whole holograms damn yeah I and then and then and they're
like oh and let me guess when he the newspaper you would tell the Daily
Meteoroid right yes yes yes we all hate that galaxy-wide we hate the Daily
Meteoroid that is a rag I don't know so happened yet but there is a meteoroid
that is supposed to hit today. I read it in the Daily Meteoroid.
That's really bad news. Did it say what planet?
Earth.
But I just got this hair.
I know.
It's like the worst news ever.
And you know what? The worst part is?
Imagine that my hair grew back.
Oh, what's the worst part? He's pointing at me when he said, "Do you know what the worst part is?" What is it?
Cameron's the worst part?
It can go through walls.
It can go through walls?
The Meteoroid?
Directly?
That sucks.
Directly.
Alright, but I'm saving them on the second story, right?
Don't tell me it's gonna be a direct hit
What okay? What if I wear?
Anti-meteorite, I think you wear a cone
a cone like a dog I
Can do that?
How are you?
Do a spare cone? Yeah, I mean get a dog
Yeah, I could go for a cone
This very instant. Oh, I can either be Coney Island dog or more corn dog your pick
I got I got cone dogs in the freezer at home. Hmm
Number three, have sex.
Yeah, and there's one comment here. It's shaped like a what now?
Depend on the alien civilization, that is true. Yeah, I mean if they have you know if they got a
You know their own kind of Sasha Gray character Sasha Green
porn star you know I feel like they'll understand well there are there is also
gray aliens she needs to be my mom maybe she is an alien Sasha Green needs to take
care of Sasha Gray I think I would pop out of that thing just fine and I need
you to be my mom I think I would fly out of your huge hole Sasha Gray you're
going on entourage mm-hmm I need a I need a mom massage I need a mom
massage massage number four is dance now dude have you seen the fucking Eiffel 65
music video I'd say dancing is like probably the universal yeah which to
really they don't do they they know that those blues we say go dabba dee dabba die
I mean one of these yeah they do that we do one of those shuffle in that little
dish then the blue aliens and the blue video going yeah yeah that's a good
dance yeah I think aliens my whip and nana - they got spaceships they got ahead
they must call them whips yes that's them practicing they have to call them
with that's the practicing hitting the lever for hyperspace yep and the nana is
the name of their alien race mm-hmm that's they say nana when they wave
their hand because they're saying hello. They go like that. I would have...
And they have the lasso dance because that's how they abduct people. When you swing the
lasso around a girl that you'd love to pull. True. Just like Cotton Eye Joe. Oh my god,
they have to have Cotton Eye Joe on their planet. I fucking hope they have Cotton Eye
Joe, Jesus Christ. It's a whole planet of Cotton Eye Joe. They probably have technology eye
cotton eyed Joe
on obtainium I Joe. They probably say they probably think I know exactly where
you came from and I know exactly where the trajectory of where you're going to
go. They're looking they're looking exactly where you're looking from an
observation on UPC. They're looking from an observation deck on like a
spaceship looking at Earth's like should we make contact yet? No, they're still
too primitive. They're still on cotton. I Joe
have three I'd Joe they probably do number five watch TV yeah a group of
humans watching a group of humans in a box aliens would not have TV that's a
human that's a surely human about no the we're the only people to watch TV humans
are the only people people in the galaxy watch TV I have that a good authority
from the Federation yeah are you in touch with the Federation often yep I
I knew he was a gray.
I'm not a gray, I'm just an excited ambassador between our two cultures.
Do I look like a gray in this wig?
You look more like a...
I knew this guy.
I knew he got probed for sure.
Perhaps one of the lower forms of a reptoid.
You really think I have a rept- I'm exhibiting reptoid stuff?
Well you ain't no Anunnaki.
No.
I could be Naki.
You, you, you know what, you're a uh, a fuckin, oh what are they called?
I'm gonna change my name to Anunnaki.
There is a type of alien that you look like, a Pleiadian I think.
Let me pull this up.
You look exactly like a Pleiadian.
Next time we record with Matt, I'm going to wear this wig and not acknowledge it at all.
Check this out.
See if I can find him out.
That green guy from Star Wars.
Oh wow, yeah.
You literally are a Pleiadian.
Totally a Pleiadian.
Yeah, they're like the, yeah look.
Look at that.
That's you, dude.
It's not Jarl Poof.
You don't look like Jarl Poof right now.
Shut up. Number six, speak different languages. Dude, Sephiroth. You're a Sephiroth too.
You have Oporhynxis's hair and Sephiroth. Can you guys just stop talking about my beauty for one moment?
No, it's really hard when you're playing with your hair like that. I'm thumping.
If alien civilizations developed like ours, we'll probably have a lot more in common with them than we think.
My thumping thing. Number seven, believe in God. This is probably the most weird thing they could think.
aliens all have the exact same religions that we do
yeah well they only have christianity no they all have the same ones
no they're far enough in a civilization they eliminated every other
uh... religion no it's just the true one
it's exactly the same everywhere
i don't think so it's true
trust me i got i got an info pamphlet
on it when i was in the federation office do you have it with you? yeah let me pull it up
actually does have a picture does have the pimp here are read out to you
voted best family magic show
ron's i want to have to hold up here you have another have another one
have you ever fed a giraffe have you ever smelled their grassy breath
these are memories that will last i think that's a good sign for a template
that's better in a federation is like that's a very absent area need a
leaders yet after a period of time premium giraffe encounter our most
exclusive excursion only for people who really love giraffe. I think that might
is four guests maximum so that means there are four religions maximum. I think that
might be a giraffe thing. What? I think that might be it for a giraffe park. Yeah
for Giraffia the giraffe planet. I don't think there is a giraffe planet. I don't
think you're part of the Federation. I was shutting it off. You weren't doing
anything you're pretending number eight eat use eating use a eating utensils use
a eating utensils they're probably wondering why we look like we're not
trying to kill our food when it's already dead that's true as hell yeah
damn I never thought of it that way it's funny as hell though a spork oh hell no
that shit's random nah a spork eating cheese now check this out check this out
What about a spife?
What's a spife?
Pie.
Sorry.
Sorry, I got distracted just now.
What about a gnorc or a noon?
Well, a spife and a noon are the same.
What about a knop stick?
A spop stick.
A spork stick.
That could be good.
What about spongs?
Spongs could be really useful.
What about a knife chilla?
on
perfect one a spevery thing whoa wow that's making me thirsty for a
neverage right now what's a neverage? It's a beverage with knives in it
okay really sharp and hard to drink but I love it. You're drinking out of my nup. But I'm
addicted to it because it has forcatine in it. You're gonna get a nup of spotter.
Number nine listen to music okay again like aliens have hip-hop. Aliens listen to
Skrillex, okay? Scary Monsters and Freaky Aliens.
They listen to this shit.
They call it "Normal Things" and "Nice Sprites".
Yeah, exactly.
Normal Things and Other Normal Things.
And Other Normal Stuff.
Normal Things and Nice Sprites.
Skrillex is alien language for John.
Yeah, so he's completely normal in space.
In space.
That's like the alphabet to them.
That's like the normalist song.
You know that Polish joke where it's like
the eye doctor says the it's like like it says like all the letters and it says I
know the guy that's what they think about when they see Skrillex mm-hmm they know
Skrillex that caveman doctor and he's like I doctor you know yeah it's pretty
good and the eye chart just has like what does it have on it a picture of an
antelope yeah or the guy looks covers I looks like a spear oh my friend we need
to kill you we are gonna have to put rocks on your face spear they have an
event we're gonna have to replace your eyes with rocks we will be eating you my
friend I'm gonna prescribe barbecue sauce all over your body and to hang in front
of a fire pit for three to four hours because we're gonna village is gonna
have to eat you buddy you're in no condition to to hunt for mud we have to
be our food.
Yep, we're the mud eaters.
Yep.
Unless somebody has bad vision, then we're the you eaters.
I'm sure we're going to have very successful descendants from thousands of years from now.
We will not be a forgotten tribe of cavemen that died out immediately because we only
ate mud and guys who thought antelope was spear.
Yeah, listen, a bird told me mud is the best thing a person can eat, okay?
So we're doing it.
Mud is so much easier to domesticate than a deer or a dog, too.
- Yeah, yeah, true. - Plus, you can turn mud.
- We got into the Neolithic age,
like thousands and thousands of years before other people,
'cause mud stays inside the fences easy.
- Yeah, also, make your mud-- - You can turn mud
into any animal you think of. - Make your mud work for you.
- Yeah. - You know what I mean?
If you need to put something in it, it's gonna stay.
It's mud, you know?
- We don't need fire, wheel.
Mud can do all these things. - You don't even need clothes.
You just put mud on your damn body.
- You just make a mud fire. - That's right.
- Also, you make a mud fire, it's not very hot,
but it works.
You can, instead of a wheel,
well, you just slide through the mud everywhere,
twice as fast as a wheel.
Yeah, of course we'll make a mud fire.
What else are we going to burn?
Rocks?
Yeah, that's right.
Those don't burn.
You can't burn a rock.
What are you, stupid?
Of course the mud fire.
What are you, a fucking idiot?
That's what you use for fire.
Fucking dumbass.
Number 10, drive.
They fly, though.
Yeah, that's a good point.
They might say, like, I think your spaceship's broken.
Yeah.
It's rolling on the ground.
Your spaceship is a lowrider.
Yeah.
They might think we're all swaggy.
They would think we're swaggy.
Yeah, because we have a low rider spaceships. Yeah
Number 11 take a selfie. We must be some ugly-ass aliens right now
I'm looking good, and I want to take a selfie of my right. Yeah, it's like
I just need to make sure I look like myself. I mean what the heck I love taking selfies by the way selfies fun
I just love sitting there taking selfies. Do you delete them or leave them on your camera roll?
I leave them on whoever's phone it is that I'm taking the photos. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, sometimes I take a selfie and immediately delete it just to see what's up
Yeah, phone just to see if it were just to see what's going on
I like to sometimes I'll be sitting down on my couch and it's like 1 a.m. And I'm like
Watching TV. I'm like I bet I look really tired right now. I want to see how tired I look I take a selfie
I'm like, mm-hmm. Why did I do that? I don't need this on my phone. It is
To be like sitting down sometimes you'll be like I'm gonna take a photo of myself without moving my face at all or yeah
No, I love doing that. Yeah to see how fucked up. It's always horrible. It's always really
Yeah
One time I like that. I checked my bald spot once that's never a good move
No, it's never good check my bald spot in the mirror and then like saw
my face in the
I was like
Yeah, one of the best man is at his lowest
You're trying to take a picture of like the back of your head or something
Yeah
and you like you take like three and they're all completely miss and you just like take a bit like a blurry picture of
your shoulder on the other side of the room I always keep those those are nice
that is good those are a good photo to have in your camera roll yeah yeah let's
see let's finish out this list what do we got here we don't have to finish we got
cry call aliens aliens true that's actually the smartest one swim pray kiss
they kiss they get away morning master bait whoa master bait use money knock
have a gunfight use computers yeah I know take me to your dealer son that's
they be saying one shot and they'll understand yep uh-huh one shot one shot
what's up and heroin one shot of high shop get arrested murder they would
understand my work so much work so much watch porn work so much they wonder why
humans like to watch other humans reproduce sounds strange if you put it
like that it's simply a scientific I don't use a toilet these aliens nasty as
a laugh engage in war laugh use the middle finger floss again dancing
universal language mm-hmm all right bye everybody