come here come here come here let me see your butt
crap monster and we lost our zoom license yeah yeah the last episode I
don't know Kayla we didn't tell you about this oh yeah I mean I did literally
didn't tell us that we lost the zoom license until the middle of the episode
when I just said like five minutes left in your in your meeting yeah and we are
to like cut it together. It was maybe the worst episode we've ever done. Well this is good.
At least this is the last time we have to do one on here because I'm getting over my COVID
and you guys are probably both completely negative, right? Yeah, I would definitely. Feeling 100%?
Yeah, I definitely don't have any COVID at all in my body. Yeah, you guys have been like
staying inside, you know? Taking care of yourselves. I've been ordering grocery deliveries so only
people that don't matter get exposed. You guys definitely didn't go to one of the biggest
COVID hotspots in the fucking world and hang out with a bunch of Uber Eats drivers, right?
No, no, no, I don't even know what you would be talking about. Yeah, that wouldn't make any sense.
Yeah, I mean, even if I did, I'm safe for three months, I think. My scientist friend told me that
if you get COVID. Patrick was fucking going around, he was saying like, no, I actually can't get COVID
for three months. And we were like, oh, really? And he was like, yeah, this guy I know who's a
scientist told me. No, it's not a guy. What do you mean you don't have a scientist? I have a scientist friend. Who?
Dr. Lisa Bobby. No. You don't know a Lisa Bobby?
Yes, I do. No, you don't. You don't know Lisa Bobby. I know Lisa Bobby. No, you don't. Uh-huh. No.
What is she assigned? What's her field of study? COVID-19, actually. Where'd you go to school?
Uh, Traeger University.
Traeger University, okay. Like the smoker?
Yes.
Okay, gotcha.
They specialize.
What do they specialize in?
In, um, you know, the thermometers that can detect whether or not you have a fever for COVID.
Meat thermometers for people?
Yes. You put it right in your butt and it uh...
Come on, man.
What? Where else is it gonna go?
Your mouth. Your mouth.
Your mouth or ear.
Have you guys ever had to take a thermometer in your butt?
Well, I didn't have to, but I did.
Not have to, I guess.
I didn't have to, I did it by choice.
Why?
Accuracy.
He's lying.
It is more accurate, supposedly.
Yeah, but the problem is it's like one of those like forehead read ones.
You shot a laser into your asshole.
Yeah.
It's like, it's one of those ones that's like a...
It's like on an iPad.
There you go.
There's the camera on it.
You're supposed to line up your face with it.
Yeah, no way those work.
How was Florida?
Oh, dude, it was amazing.
It was swagged out.
It was a YouTube Red original?
Uh-huh, dude.
That's fucking sick, man.
Dude, it was a 2B original that we did.
Damn.
Yeah, we stayed in an econo-lodge.
You stayed in one?
And the door never opened, dude.
You stayed in an econo lodge with no door?
We stayed in an econo lodge and the door never opened.
Did I say stayed in?
Yeah, you did.
I like that you said "and the door never opened" like that would make any sense to anyone besides
me.
Dude, the door to the hotel room was fucked up and you had to like try and open it like
a hundred times.
Yeah, it's an econo lodge, man.
Yeah, but you know the door never opened.
I slept in my clothes both nights.
We stayed in there and the door never opened.
I just love my little kid friend.
He literally is fucking the second day.
He woke me up at like 7 a.m. because he just woke up and he's like, well, it's time to be
awake now.
Oh, there's fucking six years old.
Such a nightmare.
That's like I feel so bad for fucking Neil having to live next to him.
Just hit your just knock on his door.
If he wakes up too early, just sitting in the doorway.
I open my eyes now.
Hey, Neil, I threw up.
What am I supposed to do?
I have done that before.
I know you have I knocked on this door to ask him if a sweater looked weird on me
Just interrupting all his meetings at his fucking work shit
To be like should I should I checkerboard my shoelaces? Is that still cool?
I'm actually gonna do that now. We need to bring that back. Yeah, it was so cool. Oh, man
I'm just people did cool shit with their with their shoelaces man doing straight laces
Yeah, straight laces were straight laces on the etnies dude. Yeah
She was she knew I got a cartoon character. Uh-huh unbelievably cool dude. I have a next I have the next big thing, huh?
barbed wire shoelace
That's cool. That's pretty cool. I am you have to tie them with gloves
I've just tied my shoelaces together and I hop around that's it's a good. Yeah, what up?
It's pretty much the new, it's Matt Brick outside and this is the new vibe.
When I tied my shoes earlier that shit was a Shutter Original.
Check out my shoes, they're tied together bro.
I tied both my shoes together.
What are those shoes that don't have laces?
Slip-ons.
The slip-ons.
You know those slip-ons that people always wear?
Vans slip-ons.
Yeah, those ones.
I'm drilling lace holes in those.
That's smart.
That's gonna be my big fashion thing.
There used to be a...
Also, I'm cutting a tongue into them, too.
I'm making them look exactly like a normal shoe.
Well, the whole shoe is a tongue.
No, I'm making them into a normal shoe.
Think about that in my laboratory.
I'm covering my body in laces like I'm going to be a mummy.
Yeah.
I'm waiting for lunch and I was laughing so hard.
Imagining going into a restaurant and being like, "Yeah, I'm actually a food scientist,
so I'm going to study this food to make sure that it's good."
it's way too hot first of all.
And second of all, the whole vibe is off in here,
so I'm gonna need to teleport your restaurant back into my food laboratory
and do a few updates.
We were at some, we were at some like
fucking, what was that place called?
Dude, Pat literally saw a restaurant across the street called Love Child
and was like, "Let's go there."
Love Child.
It said it had Cubanos.
I wanted a Cubano in Tampa. I heard that that's where you go.
For Cubanos.
But it was not an authentic Cuban place. It was not owned by like a five foot tall. You mean I Tico
Authentico it was not authentic. Oh, it was very trendy. It was a good cue. It was a good it was good lunch
But it was good food. Yeah
But it was
We got dude they had a vending machine that had a tamagotchi in there. Why yeah
I say a vending machine like for zines and stuff. Yeah
But yeah, they we got what was it like yucca fries or something and it came out. I was like sauce
Oh, yeah, I like picked up the fry. I was joking it back going like
And like the waitress like oh, yeah
Dude, you did that like three times three separate times Cameron like said something and the waitress was like right behind him
He didn't know and like the fucking like you saying like I'm a food scientist
She popped up right then was like is this everything good over here?
Tell me I missed this trip man because of some fucking stupid
Stupid virus that brought me to the very doesn't very nice of my world of my life brought me to my very knees
Mm-hmm. I was sitting here her very knees. I have very knees and it brought me to them
I was sitting though. I was in my room Jana still is testing negative
So I've just been sitting in this room for nine days just by myself.
It's been so awesome, dude.
It smells like it's unbelievable how much this room smells like a fart.
Are you getting meals under the door?
No.
No, she sucks at cooking, man.
I just make the food while she's at work, man.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I make the worst food ever and I just go back into my room.
I've just been making like lentils and shit. I'm just sitting in the room just fucking farting. Oh, did you miss her?
Oh, man, you missed Applebee's you miss Tampa Apple. You got you guys you guys know how much I love Applebee's dude. I got
Before yeah, even possible Cameron's first Applebee's trip. You missed it
The inaugural I was a two waitresses walk directly into each other
I missed that cuz that like I ate I got the ribs Applebee's and immediately had to shit so bad
I like dude that that fuck that trip fucked my gut up the ribs made you shit
you think is the barbecue sauce no we got Waffle House in the morning he's oh
yeah I don't make you shit yeah no I forgot about it I almost got it I said I
said uh let me get like double hash browns everything on it and then the I
thought she said do you want to leave everything on it yeah I said well almost
Almost, almost. I got sausage gravy. I almost got sausage gravy and chewy.
Can I get a hamburger with mostly everything on it?
Most of the stuff on it. I didn't want to sit there and go chopped, fucking smothered, covered, and peppered.
That's like the whole reason why they named it Fun Shit, so that it doesn't feel like a chore.
Sure, you can say smothered, covered, chopped, peppered, and uh, staked?
What's the other one?
I don't know.
Ah, fuck.
Fuck.
But I almost got sausage gravy and chili on it until the other waitress came over and
was like, "Are you sure you want chili on it?"
And I was like, "No, absolutely not.
I could not handle that."
I thought she said chili and I thought that she meant like, I thought she meant chili peppers.
I thought you meant like chilies.
She thought they had chili peppers at Waffle House?
Yes, I thought they had like poblanos.
Poblano chili at Waffle House?
No.
Well, they have jalapenos.
Yeah.
Last time I was at Waffle House was around Christmas and I went with Noah and Noah started
um, Noah like went to the bathroom and then all these people there, it was like just two
groups of people there and all these people just started yelling, it was like three in
the morning. We started yelling through the bathroom door that they could hear him
shitting. It was like, "Oh I hear you shitting in there! That's nasty as hell!
Oooo-wee! Oooo-wee!" And we just sat there, we just did nothing. We just didn't even talk to them.
We were just letting Noah get destroyed through a bathroom door while he dropped a
nasty waffle. That was shit. He didn't even eat anything. He just went into shit.
He brought that from home. Yeah, no it was pretty fucked up. Yeah. Dude, our Uber driver made fun of
us for going to Waffle House. What the fuck? Yeah. I knew if you were there. Yeah, if you're
from out of town, you probably, you didn't even, you didn't know better than to go to
Waffle House. You told them we liked Waffle House and you didn't talk to us. I like Waffle
House. I'd try to go here and there. He's a fucking idiot, man. And then he just like
didn't talk for the rest of the drive. Because I fucking showed him up with my intellectuality.
What was it like to destroy him in his own car? We rated it one star and didn't tip. That's
right I don't tip these people anyway I'm I'm trying I mean it's European hey
here's a crazy job crazy shit was down there every fucking uber driver asked us
to give them five stars yeah every time we would get out of a ride that I when
that's saying this but it's because everyone owns their owns a car and drunk
drives yeah oh like there's no reason to call it that was the strangest I that
was so strange to me but I guess it's normal I don't know what part of Florida
you guys in? Here in Tampa. Oh, Tampa sucks. Yeah. It's horrible. Tampa's the worst. It's
the worst place ever. Yeah, it's pretty bad. Oh, shout out to uh, shout out to Shooter.
Shout out to our boy. No. Yeah. This podcast isn't for shout outs, Pat.
Yeah. I just wanted to. You can start your own fucking podcast or you can say your friend's name.
If Pat did a spin-off podcast, it would be an hour of him shouting people out and saying thank you to
people I'm thanking him for showing us a lot of thank you saying hello yeah he's
doing oh yeah my mom but that guy Greg yeah good to meet you man you should be
doing that no but for real shut up Vladimir yeah Vladimir you were low-key
here's one of our drivers and he's cool you guys later in a minute here you got
mad at me or something I'm at it you could haven't seen you in so long I need
to ring your neck. When I see you, I'm going to ring your fucking neck.
Oh, I did. Speaking of Lyft drivers, we did see a really good Lyft driver fun fact.
Oh, yeah.
Our Lyft driver, Hoy, his fun fact was, "I can and will dance in public."
Whoa, that is good.
It's a good one.
Remember that guy that we asked him if he liked chocolate? His fun fact said he loved
--
His fun fact was, yeah, he liked savory snacks instead of sweet snacks or something like
that.
and we were like, "Ah man."
You know, "Hey, settle a debate for us.
We're having this debate.
Which one's better?
Savor snacks or sweet snacks?"
(laughing)
It's like 3.30 in the morning.
Getting into a Lyft and he's like, "Uh."
- Yeah, and I'm just being like, "Yeah,
well I like pretzels, but like,
I don't like Hershey's chocolate bars."
- I just don't get it.
How do people like sweet snacks?
Savor snacks are definitely better.
- It's the worst getting into like Ubers
with you guys sometimes.
- Why?
so like you just you want you'd rather just look at the ground yes no dude i'm the i'd rather look
at the ground give them a nice tip and say thank you if i was literally there to be the ant under
your magnifying glass dude you should be eliminating him from existence they have to listen to whatever
you say you remember that dude there was one time we were i was just me and caleb in a car
And the Lyft driver honked at the guy in front of him, and Caleb was just like, "Is that your enemy?"
And then for the rest of the ride, you kept saying like, "Yeah, I'm thinking about getting a nemesis
and an enemy. I'm thinking about, I'm finally gonna get a nemesis." And then you kept asking me,
you kept asking me who my nemesis was, and I didn't want to answer you, and I felt so uncomfortable in
in the car. You're shy. I am. That's what's great about riding. In the car I'm shy. Dude,
I'm shy as fuck but not in lifts baby. The great thing about a lift driver is it's like
having, like riding in a lift with Patrick is like having two lift drivers. It's like
two people who just anything that you say to them they're just gonna be like, "Mm-hmm.
Oh yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah." They just won't talk to you at all. Except yeah, except every once
in a while they'll say something like, "Oh, you know there were like a hundred murders
here?"
Yeah.
It's like, "Yeah, out of nowhere."
I like to bring that up.
It's gotta be a hundred and one.
How would you fucking pedal to the metal, you slow motherfucker?
That's right.
Yeah.
If I wanted to go this slow, I would have got a city bike, pal.
When I was a kid, whenever we'd go to the airport, my dad knew this taxi driver that
he would call.
you'd always call the same guy
and he drove a minivan
and uh... he had a little members little screens that uh... was like like
portable dvd players if you would have their cars on the back of the year
as they had a little wheel that you could you played with
no i wish
he had a lot of what i have those in this
he had was portable dvd players
that he would set on the console
and he would watch the final fantasy movies while he was driving
that's the sickest shit ever that's there's only two there's only two final
fantasy movies he would rotate between the two and literally every time we took
this car he's watching one of the final fantasy movies the they should put in
lifts like in a like in a student driver car how you have a second steering wheel
and a second brake yeah so you can you can just do no they should they should
put a little steering wheel in the back so you can pretend like you're driving
driving too. That's for you. Yeah. I'm actually driving a little, a little horn that I can
press. You should be able to hawk the horn whenever you want. Oh, there should be, there
should be a button in the back of the lift. You pay, you pay a little bit extra. There's
a button in the back and you can just hold down the horn. That's what the, that, yeah,
that's what the fucking, the like lift or like Uber subscription or whatever is where
you can, you know, you can like get like a premium version of it. They should add so many
more options. You should be able to call a cash cab also for an airfee. You should be
able to drop you should be able to drop like spike strips on the ground behind it too.
Yes.
Oh dude.
You know what sucks is when you-
Batmobile Nitro also?
You know what sucks is when you get, you're in like a, you have the subscription, you
get in an Uber XL and then the person behind you is in an Uber Black and he throws a blue
shell at you.
That shit sucks.
Is it Uber Black?
Is that the, like the Bentleys and stuff?
I don't think they have Bentleys.
I think it's like they get like a black Escalade. I don't think they have like Rolls Royces.
I think it's like I think they get like a like an Audi sometimes. I think you're wrong. There
should also be Uber hang gliders and you can like get if you're in a building you want
to get to the next building. You should be able to Uber shoes that you can walk in and
then drop off. Yeah. When you don't need them anymore. Oh dude like the inspector gadget
shoes yeah like the big ones no actually no big normal stilts that you can just
throw out the city i don't think those are street legal
hmm i don't think you can have giant stilts on the street i think you need to
be you need to have a license or a permit
to be on stilts that's not true yeah that's not true at
all that no there's no way that if you walk down
if you like walked around brooklyn with stilts on
the police are gonna stop i mean they tell you to stop but i don't think that
they're going to stop you because you don't have a license i think they're
going to stop you because you're walking around still
are you talking like walking in the bike lane on stilts or walking on the
sidewalk walking anywhere on stilts you're not they're not they're gonna i
agree that they're gonna stop you but i don't think that there's i don't think
that there's a something you can show them that would get them to not stop you
the only thing that's gonna stop you is a guy with an android phone going
Oh, only in New York!
What the fuck?
That would be good to be con- I mean, I feel like there is a whole-
'Cause there- okay, so there's the guy who rides around Manhattan with the basketball on his head.
Oh, I love him.
Oh, he's the best.
Multiple times, he goes "Baaaaah!"
Yeah, he has-
I got it!
He's got a horn, I love him dude.
He says "I got it."
Uh-huh.
And there's- who else is there?
It might just be that guy.
Oh, Tweek Season.
Who's Tweek Season?
Donald Trump.
There's Donald Trump.
Who's Tweek Season?
- Is SpeakSeason's the guy on TikTok
who walks around and finds weird shit and makes fun of it?
- I don't know that dude.
- Oh dude, if I ever ended up in one of those,
I'd kill myself.
- But there's a good, there's definitely a hole to be filled
for maybe like a bald white guy on 10 foot stilts.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Or a unicycle.
- Oh, oh, here's what you can do.
Okay, so you get like 10 foot stilts
and like an Uncle Sam costume.
- Yeah, that'd be huge.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
and you know i a big and big hands to like big uh... like foam fingers
but they have a lot of start a parade
yes you'd all my god i'm so fucking glad u_s_ i was trying to sneak it into this
conversation
you know we can walk around and i think that you know two-person llama costume
because of a sort of weekly marching band for a hit
yeah i'm not
that the route is is every single street we go like we snaked out we just
surround every block in brooklyn so we know everybody just really more out there
twenty four-hour parade
and we get these people are used to like
despacito blasting out of a car
when speeds by they're not used to it
yeah you know
the song is a very by the way very slow parade
yes it was like a very old to bus and all to the wheelchair parade
all to you
people in your chairs playing to boost down a fucking myrtle broadway
and just see what happens.
The worst cyclists in the world too.
Because what are these cops going to do?
Stop a bunch of young people in wheelchairs trying to express themselves?
That's a bad look for the NYPD.
I think more likely they just keep, that wheelchair parade just keeps going until they get fucking
blasted by an escalade one day.
They get all the way to the Brooklyn Bridge one day and out of nowhere, big ol' caddy.
honk and escalate just destroys them. An escalate with 50 more tuba players hanging off the side.
We can do a faster parade than you! We can get a way faster parade down this street!
After a while of the parade, the cops are going to be like, "Okay, you guys are going to have
to have a parade license to do this." And then, one tuba player on every train car on
every train. Oh my god. 24/7 until they let us do the parade again. Do you guys want to
maybe a flash mob kind of improv everywhere type thing I yes I was
thinking about that I've been doing them I've been doing them by myself we can do
like a three person flash the first guy to ever see a flash mob like I literally
probably would have killed myself just I would have thought it was I would have
been so scared yeah I would have been like I would be like these people
there's some kind of infection yeah these people have been are being
controlled I literally never trust reality again yeah if I saw a flash mob
I'd feel I'd feel so left out. Yeah. I oh my god are you kidding me?
A flash mob should I just based on the name of flash home should be like a
million women just showing their boobs to I think that's what it used to be.
That can't be true. And then PC culture ruined it. Really? Mm-hmm.
There's another L for PC culture man. Yeah. Yeah. Well cuz it was I think it
wasn't it a flash mob because it was the no pants subway ride
you know i'm gonna be real with you i haven't done
all that much research. you're cutting in and out. yeah your shit is fucked up
my shit's fucked up
what the fuck
it's fine on my end
what's wrong with you? dude turn your video off
okay
uh... we gotta use that audio
I'm now the extra work
I'm a normal now
He's sitting there going
Shit, my...
*laughter*
*imitates sound*
I sounded normal over here
Oh man
Of course you did, you're talking out loud
My ears sound fine, I mean I'm just, I'm not talking any differently over here
Yeah
But yeah, I don't know all that much about flash mobs, Pat
I haven't done, I guess, as much research as you have
Into the art
I know
Well you seem to know the origin
I know the no pants subway ride.
You scrolled down to the early.
Everyone knows the no pants subway ride.
That's because you googled no pants subway ride
will I get arrested.
Well one day I've lost my pants.
It's not hard to fucking you know.
It's not hard to what?
It's not hard to lose your pants sometimes.
It's not hard to expose yourself.
It's not hard to go swimming.
Go swimming in the east river.
Oh what's this?
It's 3.15pm on a weekday.
I'm gonna lose my pants. Oh, there they go. Oh, there they go. And I'm on the subway. Oh,
SMH. Oh, I'm off the subway. I hope I don't take an especially winding route home today
that surrounds several very crowded restaurants and dare I say playgrounds? No. I couldn't.
day I get shit for being myself like like you know like an exhibitionist and
pretend that you lost your pants and our traders tried to get home like in a
giant spiral like around your house
yeah oh dear, oh dear, I had my GPS in my pants and I'm completely lost
I had a piece of paper with my address on them in my pants and now I can't find
them
I forget my home oh dear, they're in your hand
oh they're in my hand the whole time like a remote
oh god this is embarrassing oh there he goes again
what the fuck's wrong with your shit dude, god damn it dude
I can hear myself. I'm gonna ruin the episode regardless.
Don't test me.
You're not gonna do shit. I will. You won't do shit. You're a coward.
I'm not a coward. You're the cowardly lion.
What was that?
Would a coward make that noise?
What was that, a whisper?
Did that scare you?
No, that only works in person.
Fuck, I miss you guys.
Damn it, I hate this.
It does suck.
All right, so today we got a...
We have, I mean, as...
Which one should we do first?
I think the odd one.
All right.
Wait, which one's that?
They're both sent in the chat.
I'll send it to you.
Wait, are these made by...
Yeah, they're made by the same guy.
Perfect.
do
I was naive and kind of lame when I first joined this site.
I've changed.
Facts.
I can relate to that 100%.
I joined summer 2018, early gen 19 if we still use that terminology.
I like to write.
Check out my stuff here.
I'm mostly inactive, only occasionally logging in to comment and check out my stuff.
I'm one of many who left a sinking ship that is this site due to admin's pointless changes
and needlessly strict personality.
And can I please change my name to Second World or A'Shy?
It's probably not that hard to add that feature.
facts. So the description to top 10 things that writers do that are seen as odd. Sometimes
when writing a story things go well, other times things go wrong. What you can always
count on though are things that some might think are strange. Yeah. Wow. That is so nice
to get. I've definitely had that experience. I mean like I would say that all three of us
are writers right? We're working on different. Definitely. I mean I have a novella in the
works that I've been kind of talking to people about, shopping around. I'm working on, I'm
working yeah well you set yours yeah go ahead well it's seven pages long mm-hmm
because it's a novella you know it's not like technically that as long as like a
normal novel and it's actually about a giant a great white whale but I've been
working seven pages well yeah I feel like I mean that honestly sounds I can
imagine some of the scenes in that being painterly I mean like I guess for me the
most important thing is like concisicity and in my writing and like it being
like easy to understand for like a more broader like general audience.
Yeah, I'm actually kind of on the other end of the spectrum because I've been working on
this like it's kind of like a multi-format piece like I would say it bridges the gap between
a screenplay and a poem and it's about 792 pages at the moment but I'm trying to kind
of you know thread in different influences like you know plays definitely novellas like
yours, like spreadsheets, pencil drawing, and just kind of as many different mixed media as I can add.
And I think that it will kind of like bridge, you know, a lot of experiences throughout the
universe and help people understand what it's like to read a 800-page piece of paper.
That's cool. I love that kind of multimedia, like David Foster W. style thing. You know what I mean?
Definitely. Yeah. It's also very like House of My Leaves, you know?
Yeah. One thing that I've been looking into recently is like edible pages. Like once you
you read the page you can actually eat it with your mouth.
Oh yeah, destructibility. That's actually big in my work.
Yeah, like because I feel like everything is just, everything is so like, like
ephemerality it has. Ephemerality, you know what I mean? So like I need to, I'm
getting super into like things that are ephemeral.
Yeah, and I feel like... Have you read, have you, have you read any No David?
No, have you read... No David's huge in the destructibility scene. I would
Did he write Gaunche's Bluff?
No.
Who?
That was me.
That was, uh, nuh uh.
That wasn't you, that was Slic3r.
I wrote the sequel.
I just write to my pen pal.
Really?
Well, I'm not anymore, he was in prison.
Pistolaries.
He passed away a couple days ago.
Love Pistolaries.
So, as writers, like, I think we can all probably relate to this, like, we might not be the same
as other people in a kind of way.
Definitely odd and strange in the perception of, like, society at large.
Like, to a normal person, like, have you ever thought of the fact that maybe, like, the
blue that you see is different from the blue that I see as, like, a writer?
Yes!
Yeah, so that's most, that's a huge part of what my book is about.
It could be B-L-O-O.
Exactly.
So, number one, they see their characters as real people but confined within the walls of the mind
and page. So, I mean, I think every writer in the whole, in the damn world could probably relate to
this one. I relate to this comment right here. It says, "Because I am a man who makes tainted
mistakes that I highly regret so much that I want to forget my illusion mindset, which I'm not
delusional anymore, but a man who hates Jeffrey, a teen who is struggling, his anger issues, and
mostly of all I believe that I don't like hate that I like all of the people
around me but my anger encrypted of who I am and it's not my fault I have anger
issues I don't know if I've been abused or not I didn't respond because I was
busy what well sorry actually he or Siri actually responds here he says all right
we get it now can we end this petty conflict while you let it reach a
conclusion like again kind of writerly you know no conflict yeah exactly one of
the biggest hammers in a writer's toolbox.
Exactly. It's all hammers, they're just different sizes.
It's 100% hammers, because we're nailing the words onto the page.
Much like the nails were thrusted through the hands of Christ.
Who?
Christ.
Okay, well I got a book recommendation for you, my good friend.
And it's actually the Holy Bible.
The New Testament, specifically. You can ignore the Old Testament.
Oh, I only read the Old One.
What?
Yeah.
Uh, number two, they find that their world and characters are quite prominent in their
dreams.
You sound...
Your audio's going, uh...
Dude, what's going on with your Wi-Fi?
My Wi-Fi is normal.
No, it's not.
What?
It's normal now.
You sound like a robot.
I just re- I've just recently made the switch to AOL and, uh...
Really?
Yeah, I might be running out of the disk space, actually.
That's probably... it could be your typewriter.
Well...
Oh yeah, you have one of those fucking typewriters that connects to the internet.
Yeah.
Okay, well somebody else can use the microphone.
It's like when you turn the microphone on.
Sure.
They find that their world and characters are quite prominent in their dreams.
Oh yeah, like I have this character I've been writing about, Dracula.
Right.
He keeps showing up in my dreams.
He's like, "Aaah!"
And I'm like, "Aaah!"
And then I wake up.
I've actually been working on a short piece that's been infecting my dreams lately.
It's called "A Missive for a Matriarch" and it's actually about Patrick's mom.
And I've actually been dreaming about it twice a night.
She got you guys Christmas presents and you still make fun of her on here?
I didn't make fun of anything, my dear friend.
You guys disgust me.
How could I make light of such a beautiful maiden such as your mother?
She is the one who makes light.
brings light into this world. Like you. I have to add that line. One second guys. I
dream about my stories all the time. Usually it ends up being me and my
friends with the personalities of the characters that are most like us.
Sometimes I dream about my characters. They can wake me up in an ungodly hour.
And I have to write the dream in my journal there and then or I fear of
losing a potentially good piece forever. I mean who hasn't had that moment as a
a writer. Waking up, you're in a cold sweat, you're so possessed by the spirit of the dream
that you just had that you have to run to your typewriter and you have to write about
having a fart power at your middle school.
Yeah, you write, you get to the typewriter, you sit there, you write down, "I was naked
at school and there was a test that day and all my teeth fell out."
Oh how deliciously lowbrow.
What? I actually love indulging in that kind of
lowbrow pulpy if you will kind of writing.
I sit down at the typewriter some days and I think
let me allow myself to play in the mud today.
What would a moron write? What would an absolute moron write?
Oh I have an idea and then you go.
and then you just let it run free like a hog across the countryside.
You should write that down.
Number three, they're able to tell what another writer was feeling when writing a story.
Definitely.
I mean, that is so, to me, that's like huge. It's like, because I'm also, I'm a writer/empath.
That's what my LinkedIn says.
Bibliopath.
Yeah, exactly. So I feel kind of exactly what like, for example, like, when I read Huck Finn,
I feel racist. Yeah, you know what I mean? Yeah, definitely. When I've been reading this list,
I mean, I can tell that this person was sophisticated. And yet odd. When I read Mark
Fisher I feel dead it's really I mean like I it's an incredible power it's
crazy you say that too because when I read when I read Shakespeare I also feel
dead and David Foster Wallace too and when I've read David Foster Wallace I
feel dead interestingly interestingly when I read the lyrics to Tupac's music
I feel vibrant and full of life and I feel Cuban
This entry comes from when I was reading wings of fire book 5
It was around then that I truly saw myself as a writer and all of a sudden I saw past the page and into what?
The author felt while writing it's kind of like empathy
I was able to understand what they felt but not through reading expression and vocal tone
Rather, it was through how happy or dark the book was.
When any book I read from then on got sad, for example, I remembered losing one of my
own characters and could tell that they too were sad while writing the scene.
See my list entry for how characters can seem like real people for a basic explanation for
why the writer was sad.
Ugh.
I hate losing my characters, but at the same time, I gotta say, kill your darlings.
Your darlings need to die.
Yup.
They need to die.
Yeah, like the first step to any book like Clementine
Clementine I mean
Darling, I'm in the ground. He should have died. Yes. He should have been he should have been excised
He should have even have been should have been gutted like a pig in the first page or two
Absolutely would have been a much about making the bar feel a rare book
and
Cut out those unnecessary descriptors. It's Harold in the crayon if you please
That's right. We can see that the crayon is purple. There are pictures in the book exactly show don't tell mm-hmm. I can also Harold
Drew Harold removed the crayon across the page and it shines purpley
much better
And also there should be more that's a much better title - they're basically only have pictures on every other page
There should be one on every single page. Definitely
It's all about showing and maybe just call the pictures worth a thousand words, you know
That's a lot more words you can fit on a page. So you can write a thousand, you can write a
thousand word book with one picture, they say. They do say that. Number four, they write at odd hours.
Guilty. As charged. That's actually really good. That could actually be a good line of dialogue.
If you want to steal that, I wouldn't mind. I'm all for other writers borrowing my strokes of
of ingenuity. If inspiration hits and I get a eureka moment at 513 a.m. I can't
help but go with it. I read it all times. Mainly though I like to set a time to
sit down and write. Usually around 7 a.m. We all know 513 a.m. Writers are all too
familiar with 513 a.m. They call it the writer's hour for a reason. 513 a.m.
Here's the problem I have with eureka moments. So I I'll wake up maybe like I
know like 4 36 a.m. I'll get up I have a eureka moment I go to the bathroom have a
eureka moment and then it's done and then I go back to bed see you need to
snatch that inspiration from the heavens and actually write it's hard it's paper
it's hard to find time to have a eureka moment when you have roommates that's
also so it is absolutely and and you know I've had roommates who complain they say
Caleb at 430 in the morning last night, you know, I have work at 6, I can't just hear you
in your room going "Eureka!" over and over again, you know what I mean? Like, I see the
glow of the giant blue exclamation point above your head coming out from under the door,
like it's actually, it's pretty disruptive. And I say, "Uh, well here's an idea, go fuck
yourself."
That's right.
You say that?
Yeah, because art, I don't care if people get hurt while I'm trying to create art.
Imagine the clatter of my typewriter keys is the is the pattering of rain against your window
and let it lull you into a dreamless sleep where you hopefully stay forever my friend.
Yeah I would never say that to my roommate.
Imagine the sound of my Razor Black Widow Ultimate Mechanical Keyboard with Cherry MX
keys.
Like imagine that the switches that I'm hitting that sound oh so loud.
Imagine they're gunshots in war-torn Syria and you have to sleep one last night because
you never know which one will be your last. Wow. That's right. Oh, how I would love to
rent a cabin in Syria and stay for a month to complete my novel. Now that would bring
delightful inspiration to my writing. Amazing. I've looked for Airbnbs in Aleppo, but they're
actually very expensive. I went to, see I went to an Airbnb one time and I went looked
at the spice cabinet and they had Aleppo in there. See now that's something you could
write about you know to us people in the west Aleppo is a spice to the people in
the Far East which is what I call Syria Aleppo is actually a city. Is that what
it's from? So that's what we in writing in English in language call a dichotomy.
Yes. See I'm learning a lot here as a mentally challenged man I don't I'm not
a very skilled writer and that is a unique perspective to write from.
I guess that is true.
Tell your story.
Hey, don't doubt it's not mentally challenged, it's mentally invalid.
Patrick, I just I want you to sit down and I want you to write your story.
I want to see your franchise launch.
I want to see your first novel.
See when I was in...
Patty Doren and the and the push or pull door.
When I was in school...
The mystery of the push door.
When I was in school, we had a...
And the answer to the mystery is printed upside down at the bottom of every page.
Patrick approached the target.
It was red like an apple.
There was a ball outside that was round like a ball.
He looked...
And it bounced like a ball bouncing.
He investigated the door.
The answer to whether it was push or pull was apparent, but it was facing the wrong way
for the people leaving the store.
Therefore impossible to decipher.
Patrick tried to leave the store.
Upon trying to leave the store, Patrick discovered it was closed.
The outside was closed and he couldn't go through.
And then a hundred pages later, Patrick realizes, in fact, that it was the open sign, the back
of the open sign on the door.
Wow.
Moving.
See, I thought that the sign said nope.
Number five, they look at the small unneeded details in everything.
Oh.
See, that's, I mean, leave it to me to notice a molecule, ladies and gentlemen.
Absolutely.
Because I actually do notice molecules on almost everything that I eat.
I do.
I can tell you just this morning, I saw it when my girlfriend was getting ready for work,
I looked at her and I told her, "Did you do something different with your dust?"
Hmm, I can actually tell that the hairs on your body have grown.
I saw some molecules in my bathroom this morning.
I left some molecules on the seat and I immediately wiped them off.
Every writer's bane.
What did you...
Wait, Patrick, you're almost there.
What did you wipe them off like?
as if they were like a maid
that's that's
all right getting their you're getting there
i wipe them off like my family's made should have
yes
much better now we're talking
now you're going to see us we'll make a writer of you yet my friend see this is as somebody
who's a part of your
uh... the caleb and cameron writing school
an academy rather
the caleb and cameron writing academy i'm learning
I'm learning so much and my parents are paying so much for me to learn.
Caleb and Cameron's Learnatorium for Languatology.
And graffiti.
And hip hop.
Because the two are so connected.
Can we talk about that for a second?
I mean hip hop is what?
Without hip hop there would be no Moby Dick.
There would be no William Shakespeare.
No, James Joyce.
Moby Dick, by the way, is one of the most fantastic authors I've ever read.
If you have not read his works, you have to check them out.
I urge you to pick up something of his.
Also support your local library.
Okay?
Support it.
Go in there, rent out one of the computers.
It's $2 an hour and play Fortnite.
You can also use the library computers to look up recipes and other different types
of ways to make napalm.
And you can look that up in the library and they can't,
you can't get in trouble for it at the library
because it's public.
- Yeah, anything you look up, it's completely untraceable.
You're never gonna know it was you.
- I mean, unless somebody looks over your shoulder,
not your problem.
You can torrent things at the library.
You can look up how to make bombs.
You can type in ascendants that I can't say,
but you can type it in on the library and it's fine.
I have to say I respect the library as a place of learning but I haven't been able to go
in there since they started they added DVDs to their offerings it fills me with unspeakable
rage.
I haven't been able to go in there since they banned me from going in there.
How did they ban you from going in there or why?
It's not important okay I'm showing not telling I'll leave it at that.
template oh ha ah ah gassed ah ah zoons ah gadzooks this is the truth to me oh
a lot right if this is not me reality as a template you know I look at I look at
a bus and I think hmm maybe I put a bus in my story I put a big yellow bus into
story next time definitely I also I I wrote an example of this that people is a
fun fact about one of my works is my everybody might remember my the period
piece I wrote about yeah first female serial killer which was actually called
period piece it was a bit of a bit of a wordplay a bit of a wordplay yes because
It was based on my wife. I actually used that as a template to create this
curdled woman. Yeah. I never read that. Blackened soul. I just learned how to
read. I'm glad you didn't read that because you were a character in there
too, my friend. Was I really? Every writer puts their friends into their
works and let me tell you it's not always what they want to read. Of course.
I mean I have you you're in my book as a as a character named sir poop poops Lee I
Have a very interesting that he said
Is that okay? Well you can language listen what language is that in and what does it translate to?
Listen pal you can pick up a copy of my book at your local Barnes and Noble all right and don't go
Getting it from any archive org because and how did I get to archive org?
Well, you probably can't get to archive.org because me and Cameron are in the process
of suing them into oblivion.
Oh, really?
Where they're hopefully going to shut down, yes, because it is an evil...
I mean, information should be anything but free, right?
Definitely.
You should be working to earn information.
What is knowledge but currency?
I agree with this.
There's so much information I just don't care to pay for and I don't want to pay for.
There's so many things that I could have learned and I just didn't want to pay for it.
I'd rather go and buy extravagant meals.
You my friend should be on the gallows.
Why?
What is a gallow?
Ah, to be so ignorant.
Pick up a thesaurus for once in your life, my friend.
What is that?
Pick up a dictionary for once in your life.
He probably thinks it's an ancient reptile.
From where?
Some primeval beast.
Probably crossed his mind.
*laughs*
Oh, the imbecility-ness.
My friend, my friend, you, my friend would be the leader in a cuckistocracy.
I know what caca is.
I'm sure you do.
Because it drips from your ears when you think too hard.
*laughs*
Oh, the delicious hilarity of the situation at hand.
7. They push on, despite knowing that their project may not be excellent.
to this. No. You're a bit of a quitter. No, no. I've just never written anything that I
would deem subpar. I'm sorry I have a higher standard for it. Have you ever thought about
how you actually want to be under par? And that the word subpar actually makes no sense.
This is actually something I meditated on during one of my retreats. Where have you
you
this I can relate to. I've been working on my book about a bug for... I've been writing it,
rewriting it. It's a tough nut to crack. Actually, this isn't... if you wouldn't mind,
I can read a passage from one of my horror novels. I would adore to do such a thing.
The Beast of the Bloody Land that actually demonstrates this point.
Ah yes, go on.
I rewrote stuff quite a bit for this book.
Let me read this passage right here.
The Beast of the Bloody Land was very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very,
very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very,
very scary and I really that were very
a-ha a-ha I mean I think I speak for myself
Patrick the audience when I say bone-chilling my friend rocked me to my
core
my very essence was harmed by that story and that's only two pages of it
wow scared me a number eight the
they remake the same thing many times only to get it right once
I mean, again...
I mean, this goes double for people who write cookbooks.
And cookbooks is... some people say that cookbooks are a lower form of literature. I disagree.
I think that... I don't know if you've read Binging with Babish. He's one of my favorite authors recently.
I mean, he's just... the way that he puts together ingredients, it's almost poetic.
Mm-hmm and ingredients are the words are the words of food
Exactly, and the way that he somehow ties these ingredients to
Television movies video game. I mean, it's it's it's truly an amazing piece of work another very underrated
form of writing along with cookbooks is
the nutrition fact
Yes, no, that's so that's where that is where words in science come together. Yes
normally I would say science and literature completely uncompatible I
would say a match made in heaven but considering we're dealing with science
I'd have to say a match made in a beautiful laboratory mm-hmm a match made
by Stephen Hawking in heaven mm-hmm or hell much like the mouth that's a story
hook much like the matches made between Jeffrey Epstein and Stephen Hawking were
they fucking with each other they were on they went to an island
Stephen Hawking wasn't he was they did a split he was on the island there's no
way yeah look at no actually what spinning and that would be kind of
great escape park on the island for yeah they were spinning him around like the
Fresh Prince intro. That is pretty fucking cool man. He was on the halfpipe. Mm-hmm.
But we digress. But back to the important stuff. Number 10, they write
characters that are totally unlike them. Mm-hmm. I agree. I mean I yeah I mean I've
I've been writing books about mostly people with huge lion's mane hairdos, dreadlocks,
afros, you know, none of which I hold on my head.
I wrote a story, or at least I attempted to write a story.
It was difficult due to how similar the character was to myself.
Sometimes the mirror is ungodly.
Yes, especially when I wake up in the morning.
I can't even look in there. I look at that mirror, I just want to headbutt it.
Well, that's, I mean, a writer's pain is where you get your inspiration from.
from. Absolutely. Yeah well anyway I tried to write a story about a guy who was six
feet tall and I got so upset just imagining a world. It was too close to you. Because it's
too it's too. The concept was too big for you to grapple with I understand.
It was a high concept. It disgusted me that somebody could be that tall
tall and I forgot what I said at the beginning of this.
I forgot.
Wait, hold on.
Here, let me read a comment here.
It was actually, it was actually easier to write a story about a guy who was six feet
tall than it was.
God damn it.
So that my friend, you should have utilized a first and final draft.
Yeah.
A bit of writer lingo that you may not be familiar with, but I urge you to check out ask.com
to discover it.
One of the writers greatest tools.
Similar to askjeeves.com?
Ask Jeeves, any writer who uses Ask Jeeves should be excommunicated, uh, for writing culture.
And here's the thing, what's, it's so frustrating is back in the day if you wanted to learn
something, right, you would, you would crack open a book, right? Right. Crack open an encyclopedia
and you'd learn about it. Nowadays, these kids have Ask Jeeves in their pocket, right? It's true.
They're asking Jeeves every damn question.
Whatever happened to the beauty of mystery?
Now ask Jeeves.
Well Jeeves got all the answers.
I have half a mind to put out a hit on this Jeeves fella.
Hold on I've got to write that down.
Now that's a story.
Jeeves has to be one of the smartest people in the world.
This fucking guy knows everything.
Also for a butler, pretty impressive.
Here's a comment here.
It's fun writing characters that differ completely from your own character.
I love writing in the viewpoint and voice of rather bolshy, loud, and arrogant males, or
cunning and manipulative females.
It's just fun experimenting with different styles and viewpoints and seeing how far you
can stretch your imagination.
It's a most satisfactory feeling when you feel you've accomplished it.
Oh, how I despise bolshy males.
Cunning and manipulative females, hey, what are you, writing a story about every woman?
Come on.
Authors Bane, my friend.
The author's bane is a woman.
The woman is like, I think it was Mark Twain who said-
The woman is like the whiteout to your writing progress.
The woman is the whole of the world.
I think Mark Twain said.
Here's another comment from Max Aurelius.
How is this unusual? And then he amended it.
Edit. Again a year later.
I kind of think the comment I made was unnecessary and kind of hypocritical of me
critical of me considering I was and still am an avid writer.
Now here's a man who can recognize his mistakes.
Evolution, you know what I mean?
That's a huge part of the writer's...
Evolution is a huge part.
I mean, it's like an orphanage, right?
You take all your budding story ideas, you throw them into a pool together, you see who
sinks and who swims.
It's only the survivor you wish to adopt and raise into a fully-fledged adult with a beginning,
middle, and end.
Real quick, let's do this other list by...
Really?
Yeah, we can run through this.
We've got three and a half minutes.
Hey, that's okay with me.
Top 10 things writers are sick of hearing.
So number one is put me in the story.
I mean, I think we've all struggled with this.
I'm rageful just hearing that.
Yes.
I'm full of vengeful hate.
I'm full of chips.
I'm so full.
Maybe I will put you in the story.
As a toilet.
I'm going to name the toilet in the story after you.
Are you happy now mom?
Megalomaniacal sex criminal.
Or maybe even one of the dookies that my main character takes and puts inside of the toilet that's also named after you.
You fucking asshat for an ass.
You ass clown.
Oh yeah, and good luck trying to debate a writer.
Oh, our insults are on another level.
I will tear you to shreds, you shit fucker.
Linguistic shreds, you farting shit fat ass.
You dookie rat.
You smelly smucker.
You sharder of a shit.
You, you, you imbecile.
You dumb poop. Did you hear that one? Did you hear that? I learned that just now. You crap shit.
You are a shit. What's this? A shit from a crap's ass. Yes. Talking dookie about
about a shitter again. My friend, it seems all five senses rather than just one are
registering the smell of a fart in your presence.
Hmm I fart in your general direction.
Monty Python.
Monty Python also one of the greatest writers of our generation.
Yeah, his movies were so crazy.
Check out his graphic novelization of the Book of Mormon.
Oh, wrong one.
Yeah, you were thinking of Terry Gilliam.
I was thinking of South and Park.
Now tell me that you guys have never heard this before.
Writer's block doesn't matter.
Just keep going.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I wish the writer's block was physical so I could bash my parents over the head with
it when they bring this up at dinner.
I wish that it was a wooden block that I could stand on to reach things that were taller than
me in the pantry.
See, now I wish it was more like a question mark block and I could just keep hitting it
until money comes out to fund my various novels and projects.
What's this, a coin shiny in gold as the surface of the sun?
Finding funding as an author is one of the greatest
banes of my existence and one of the author's banes as well. I mean,
one of my last books I wrote had a massive spaceflight sequence spanning almost 30 pages,
and it cost upwards of $30 million to put that to the page.
Wow. Wow.
because I needed to I as every writer does I needed to compose CGI footage video
footage of the scene so I could describe it and put it to the page how am I
supposed to describe something that I can't see I can't I can't I can't walk
outside and and and look at a spaceship shooting a laser that's why that's why
until I got a budget my lab my first 20 books were all about homeless people
asking me for money because that's what happens when I go outside that's what I
see in my life. Wow. And we can end on... And that's truly something that I don't
experience but I mean hearing it from you... And we can end on this.
This is... I will say I didn't know where I was going until I got the 30 million dollars.
This is... you must be a terrible speller. Okay. Right? Yeah. Been there. Okay.
Maybe the word flop has a curly bracket in it, okay?
Did you never consider that, right?
And then here's the comment,
"Oh, come on, we writers do go back over and fix spelling
"into not that big of a deal."
And that's from I love to read and write.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- I mean.
- I love to read and write.
I'm actually very upset that this person
has this username on this website
'cause that's my username on every other social media,
but I had to be I love to write to on the top tens because of this freak you should
you should message them oh I already have times graphically threateningly to the
point where I'm in big trouble often copied never replicated okay and I would
like to bid our audience a great adieu oh I do and once I once I find out what
That means I can say it too.
Au revoir.
Then I do this again when I find out.
And let me and let me just say the end.
Wow.