Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughter)
(music)
You're a crap monster.
(laughter)
(explosion)
Alright, yeah, my mom got you guys a present.
No she didn't, I don't believe you.
Look right here.
I got her a present.
That's just a white piece of paper.
That's a package.
My mom handed this to me and said...
And I got her a package.
It says...
I'm looking here, it says...
I got her a package.
It says, I'm looking here, it says St. Pete Warehouse.
I gave her my Peter St. Lee.
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
She saw me ware a house.
Let me open this up here.
I housed my wares in your mom.
Yep.
She opened up my package too.
Hold on, hold on.
Yep.
I'll open this up so you can, or take it out of the package.
unpacked me my mom got you beer koozies I taped your mom up I was I'm ignoring I
don't care what is it what is it my mom got you beer koozies that say why does
it burn when I pee nice it should say why does it burn when I pee inside of
Patrick's mom we can add that part in I can when I pee inside Pat's mom you know
it makes sense cuz the lady's are like a toilet the label says right here to burn
pee that's your mom's name - she signed it yeah I know - - barn to barn - that's
That's my neighbor here.
How was your Christmas guys?
Mine was incredible.
I'm back in the south.
Based on your background, you're as small as an ant.
Yeah, right now.
Oh, my background?
You're a blade of grass.
Sorry, I'm actually, I'm on the links right now.
I'm back to golfing.
No.
So, yeah.
I don't believe you.
I decided to become a golf ball.
(laughing)
- Oh dude, you're living out Uncle Matt's TV show idea.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You're doing the Meisner thing.
You're trying to method act.
- Well yeah, he wants to have me star.
I did see Matt the other day, he's doing well.
He sends his regards.
- Nice.
- He laced me up with an Apple gift card, $25.
- Oh!
- Thank you, Matt.
That was huge.
- Hell yeah, dude.
- I'm gonna buy, what can you even buy?
Yeah, you can have it.
I have no idea what to use it on.
- Really?
- You can use an Apple gift card on.
- I already, I set premium.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's actually, I think that's what I did last year
when he gave me the same gift, actually.
- Yeah, that's what I would do if I got it.
If I got that.
- I gave him an Amazon gift card.
- Whoa.
- It was also $25.
He just gave me a worst $25.
No, not equivalent.
- Equivalent.
- I can only buy digital goods.
This guy could buy whey protein if he wanted to.
No no no no no you could buy a phone charger.
What I don't...
Okay.
You probably...
You could buy a phone charger with the name of a song.
Hey nowadays at $25 you probably couldn't buy a phone charger.
Those damn things are about $100 now due to inflation.
These days, $25 bucks, what does that get you?
What is that gonna get you a McChicken?
What's that gonna get you?
A gumball these days?
Yeah.
Hey.
$25 for a fucking gumball?
When I was a kid $25 would get me two and a half albums on iTunes.
Now you can barely get one song.
You have to buy the first 10 seconds of the song.
For 25 bucks I could have sex with Pat's mom 50 times.
That doesn't make sense.
Yeah it does.
And nowadays it's only 25 times.
It costs one dollar.
To have sex.
She bought you these wonderful gifts, you two, and you're treating her like this.
I'm treating her like a-- She likes it.
She'll never listen to this.
Oh wait, she listens to every episode.
Oh shit, I forgot.
How's y'all's Christmas's been?
It's been... I mean, I didn't get to go home for Christmas.
I'm the only one of us who didn't get to go home for Christmas.
And whose fault is that?
That's right.
50 gay guys in Manhattan that you hang out with.
Yeah.
Yeah, you deserved it.
I honestly... yeah.
I don't believe that I don't believe that there's that people should like
Moralize about like about like oh, I should have been more careful about Kovat except for Patrick. Yeah, it's no
It is literally 50 gay Grinches ruined Christmas for about 4,000 people in New York
50 gay Grinches hanging out it
Are you kidding me? The gay guys I hang out with love Christmas.
Yeah, well, they shouldn't have ruined it then. They loved it so much,
they should have stayed home and watched The Matrix like me.
Yep. True.
Yep. I did not stay home to watch The Matrix. I went to IMAX.
Damn! Because I could.
That's pretty cool. Baller.
I couldn't. Baller alert.
I'm not sacrificing that ticket. No way.
Yeah, I'm finally back home. I beat COVID.
Nice. How was it?
What was your highest high and your lowest low?
Rosenthorne for COVID.
Basically, I'm not afraid of it anymore.
You guys know how scared I was of it.
Because it damaged that part of your brain that experiences fear.
It damaged fear in my brain.
I've been afraid of a lot of things.
As soon as the Atlantic publishes a new article about it.
Yeah.
We'll see the name of the new variant, you'll be afraid of it again, don't worry.
Hey, what if it ever happened to me when I saw-
Omicron is so easy.
When I first saw Omicron I was like, "Oh, here it is."
You guys should get it.
But then, I'm gonna get it.
Yeah, you guys should totally get it.
I'm definitely gonna get it.
You think there's a difference?
Anyway, we're literally all gonna get it.
Now that Christmas is over, I don't give a fuck if I get it anymore.
Yeah.
That's fine.
That's fine by me.
I'm gonna be out and about every single day.
You can come hang out with me.
My cousin is coming to visit.
Oh, swag.
Okay.
So, I'm gonna be probably giving it to him or getting it from him.
Um, yeah, now it's gonna be a good time.
When that cousin comes up, you know you gotta link up.
What?
And that's facts.
When that cousin comes up, you know you gotta link up.
That actually is.
That is actually so true.
That's so, that's low-key facts right there.
You have a, that's a Christmas vibe.
Uh huh.
That's a whole Christmas vibe.
No cap.
When you link with that cousin, you know how that is too.
When you link with that cousin, you know you got grandparents involved.
When you link with that cousin and you go on that Thanksgiving walk?
my cousin link my reaction be like the Thanksgiving walk when you when you both
split a Gatorade blue laser blue color submarine sandwiches with my cousin
before Thanksgiving so we don't have appetite so we don't know eat the gross
food my mom makes.
Changing my gifts to my cousin before Christmas?
Eating like Shaggy and Scooby with my cousin before Thanksgiving?
so we don't have that thanksgiving fullness I hate that
drinking a toilet with my cousin before Thanksgiving so I don't have to eat my
grandma's damn ass food me and my cousin throwing up after Thanksgiving so we
don't have to keep the turkey in our body and fall asleep I love eating
turkey but I hate poopooing it and me and my cousin feel similarly about this
issue so basically me and him split a pound of sugar-free jelly beans before
for
robot dance at Thanksgiving with your cousin?
When you flatten out the tips of your fingers and your cousin's fingers to make them more alien-like?
When you put your fingers in- when you do Spock hands with your hand and you do-
your cousin do Spock hands with his hands and you put them together and you look inside and it's a vagina
and you show your grandma?
Experimenting with my cousin before Thanksgiving in the woods?
Seeing whose pee smells worse, me or my cousins in the woods?
Doing a science experience with my cousin?
Science experience?
Yeah, I had a science experience with my cousins.
Chasing my cousins through the woods.
Making mud pies with my cousin in the kitchen.
Bringing in mud from outside and bringing it into the kitchen and making mud pies in
the sink.
Feeding grandma our new potion recipe at Thanksgiving.
Yeah, it's leaves and dirt and water.
Yeah, Mark brought his potions again.
I don't know what to...
Like a grown man.
Greetings!
a
wearing a big green robe. Yeah, cool man. Yeah, that's our cousin Mark. He does like potions.
He does basically, he's the potions master of the family. He calls it, he calls it's potionry.
He got into like, like over the pandemic, he got into like warlockery. Yeah. Pretty
much. Yeah. He rolls his eyes. He's like, I'm not a warlock. Okay. I'm a potions master.
I'm a potions fucking family. I hate this gay ass family. My gay ass family call me a warlock
when I'm clearly going to wizard school.
- Yeah.
- Shit's-- - Ugh!
- When I'm like way more into wizardry.
- My fucking uncle is gonna go on his rant again
about how warlocks are trying to halt the rotation
of the earth to bring an infinite winter.
It's like, God, dude.
- What is the difference between--
- We literally just do rituals.
- A warlock and a wizard.
- A warlark.
- I think a warlock is evil and an accent's just cool.
- Your southern accent?
- Yeah, I'm back in the south,
So I'm a southern accent to coming out.
- Hi, me, it's from south.
I'm from south.
- I've been riding around in my slab.
- What?
- Basically drinking lean in my slab.
- Your slab? - My slab.
- What's your slab?
- Big ass fucking box Chevy with fucking huge rims
and a stencil on the rear window with a dead kid.
- Yeah, that's cool.
- With angel wings.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- Rest in peace, Miguel.
Yeah, 1999 to 1999.
(laughter)
Yeah, I've been riding around in that car pretty much.
Yeah, listening to the Boatwork Doll Season of Cereal really loud.
That'd be so funny to get, like, an in-memoriam thing on the back of your car,
are
piece Caleb turbo pit 1997 1997 to 2000 XX you have you have like a like half
robot face and it says forgotten but not gone behind you when you least expect it
yeah I need it I need it we need to I need to put my car we should I want to
be an ice man so bad yeah like Oatsy the Iceman like freeze I want to freeze and
then be like unfrozen oh yeah in the future yeah no that you want to be
American pickled is that in but in an ice America's America what's what's you
never saw American pickle on a plane no oh no it's a bit of movie where Seth
Rogen is the he's a guy in the 1800s and then he becomes a pickle and then they
They un- they un-nickle him and he's hanging out with himself, but now.
That sounds cool.
I'm glad you brought this up.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's really bad.
It's terrible.
Maybe if he wasn't smoking so much he wouldn't have written that fucking shit.
To unfreeze me after like thousands of years and like, they've like eradicated the common
cold and I like destroy the human race because I'd have some sickness that they don't have
an amenity to anymore.
more. Yeah, the sniffles. The sniffles plague destroys all of us. They cut me out of the
ice and somehow everyone on the earth catches depression and they all kill themselves. Yeah
because you're so damn ugly. Damn, I will be ugly after thousands of years in the ice.
Hey I'm not even taking that as an insult. I'd probably break a leg or a razor. You get
freezer burn on your shit yeah I look like a damn hot dog mm-hmm you wouldn't
look like an American hot dog I'd look like an American hot dog you're claiming
that we ever heard American hot dog about you coming out looking like a dog
yeah I don't ever put hot dogs in the freezer dog huh yeah I ate some freezer
hot dogs this week yeah yeah you ever put hot dogs in the freezer what doesn't
no reserve them they already preserved with nitrates I know I don't know why
You don't have to put it in a freezer.
Speaking of dumbass shit, I literally also ate freezer hot dogs this week.
Are you saying you ate them cold out of the freezer?
No, just in the freezer.
They were in the freezer and then I cooked them.
I thawed them and cooked them.
You thought I was eating them like a popsicle?
Well, I don't know why else you would put a hot dog in the freezer.
To preserve it.
You could probably room them in the fridge.
Hot dogs you can keep out on the counter.
Yeah, you can, yeah.
They're fully cooked.
You don't have to put them anywhere.
Yeah.
But, did you, what, you guys get,
or Cameron, did you get potatoes at Christmas?
No.
Instead of coal?
My, fuck.
Do you, I--
No, I just got coal.
I just got coal before as a joke.
Yeah, it's a funny joke.
One time my, well that's the thing,
it's like, that's so, like, I don't know
if it was just like my grandparents
trying to cut costs or something by putting potatoes in the stocking instead of coal.
But what my parents would do is we get stocking stuff that would be like a bunch of like tiny
like random toys and stuff and then we would just get we've literally got the same like
not the same items but the same exact things in my stocking like every year for my entire
life.
They would just like because I would open them up and then they just put them in the attic
and then give them again the next year.
Yeah, that's smart.
system.
Yeah, because you always forget about it by the next year.
My mom has multiple times just wrapped up shit that I left here last year.
Yeah, that's a good move.
You forget about it and you're like, "Oh, thank you."
Right?
I actually do want this because it's something that I have.
And then I just forget it again.
Yeah, it's perfect.
It doesn't happen with me.
It's very clever.
I remember all my stuff.
No, you don't.
I'm a hoarder.
You don't remember a single thing.
I haven't seen you becoming a hoarder.
Did you guys ever see that one video that lady-
If I live with a girl I would be the worst hoarder of all time.
Literally everyone in my family, every old person in my family lives in like, hoarder palaces now.
Did you guys ever see that episode of Hoarders?
Where the lady, she like, she eats food in her bathroom.
And she gets pieces of poop from her toilet.
Like little specks of poop that fly everywhere and she like puts them on her food and she eats
Like we talk like we talked about eating poop on this show so much
I don't know why that just grossed me out
It's so disgusting cuz it's like also I'm watching hoarders to see like how many like game cubes that they have in their basement
And then they just ten minutes in there's a woman just eating her
(laughing)
- They don't even blur it out.
Exactly.
Well, 'cause I guess she hoards,
oh yeah, she hoards her poop.
Yeah, I forgot, that's a big part of it.
She hoards her poop.
- Well, but how does the poop get into the food?
You said it flies everywhere.
- I don't remember.
I think she like puts it on the food,
if I remember correctly.
She like scrapes it up and like it gets on her food.
- My aunt just hoards DVDs.
- Well, she's better than this lady.
(laughing)
- That's my great aunt.
- She's a lot better.
- Yeah.
- But yeah, she like eats specks of,
like she it's like she's like it's like a lowry's she likes my recent
so don't want to
let me really had to be set to resend it actually split the group
you cannot put the place of coupon
you know i don't know you know you know there's a little bit of gumbo
you get the flexible but the government will be able to find you don't want to
or in june
he and the pool
my uh... it might be a good on a cracker
my eccentric grandfather when i was growing up he started he's a big order
and one of the things that he ordered he started
collecting and gathering and hoarding as when i was uh...
growing up was he started
uh... hoarding collecting importing these
uh... engine powered
pogo sticks called hopper odds
that it was a that's so sick diesel-powered
well
yet i can add a run those
i read i don't think it a they're like very dangerous
yeah i think you know you've been fucked up
like use them or anything i think he just thought they were going to like
either be worth something or that he was going to be a little like
build something using them personally i have no idea what the end the ultimate
jumper
but he like bought a bunch of them
and i was planning to build the ultimate jumper i mean he's gonna do it
probably probably what
yeah he's not school is hard to do
like the whole town
the whole town coming there's a big event called the ultimate jumper
and it's him just at the police operas like a really good idea together and i
think it was a legs
he's just like you let it be a decent gentleman
but any flies into space yeah all hell no everybody's doubting and they need
any flies past the atmosphere because he's laughing about partner
you know
go feels bomb gardener on the one bomb gardener no red bull
new year sheesh he's uh... he's crazy
uh... he when
when uh... was in high school my high school girlfriend met him and she played
the french horn and that came up in conversation somehow and he was like
of you play the french horn
you need this record and he gave her a record
that was like
uh... it was like a uh... uh...
brass orchestra but they were playing inst instruments made out of bicycle
tires
while it's like jam you need to check this out
here was a business fire was a really good it by why
you know that i don't live it
no let me see if i want to find it
that sucks bicycle music
my uh... my uncle rick one time got my brother a brick for christmas yes sick
israeli marine brick nope nope this is for a two thousand four he'd wrapped up
he wrapped up he was in a full break a person all the idea for the supreme brick
from him. From Rick yeah dude Rick was a pioneer he also one time he also one
time gave him a when he gave him I think the next year a broken softball bat
and he was like I broke this in my softball league. He wants him to have it
he wants him to have a piece of history. He's just giving him trash every year.
That was a different thing.
- What?
- I was thinking about something from earlier.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't, hey, don't press him.
- I think I told you.
- All right, I'm not gonna press him on whatever this is.
- I told my nephew that a poop guy got arrested.
There's a poop guy going to jail.
- Oh, I remember that, yeah.
- I told my nephew there's a poop guy going to jail
and then he asked me, does he have a heart
that pumps poop instead of blood?
- It's a really good question.
is a good question. That is, I mean, that child's gonna grow up and be a genius.
Hey, speaking of that, today's list, top 10 most annoying things little kids do. I'm just
kidding, that was annoying. That was funny and cute and adorable.
I know, but he's been, yesterday I was trying to watch Spy Kids and the whole time, like
I was trying to watch Spy Kids with him and the whole time they're like, "Uncle Pat, is
that the Spy Kid? Uncle Pat, is that the Spy Kid? Are those helicopters carrying the Spy
kids which ones are the spy kids? It's two, three minutes into the movie and they can't
fucking stop asking me which ones are the spy kids.
They learn from the best. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't imagine just like how annoying those
kids are going to be when they get older under your tutelage.
Me? Yeah.
Not my tutelage. You're gonna tutelage all over him.
No. No.
Yeah.
This is from, this is "Things Little Kids Do. My Niece and Nephew Always Want to Bother Me When They Come Over."
This is the top ten most annoying things little kids do.
Yeah.
This, number one is from user Patrick. It says "Run Away."
Okay.
No, it's not.
Okay, then what is it?
Prove you can read.
Number one is they see you doing something and ask you to play with them.
That literally, that happened before this.
That literally happened right before this.
Did the kids want to, they wanted a podcast?
Yeah.
Willie was in here.
picked up the microphone and asked me if he could try it.
And I told him--
- Dude, that's a dark path.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Save him, save his soul.
- I know, dude, if he started a podcast,
wouldn't he be good? - Probably wouldn't be
very good, he's at least four years old.
- No, he's five, he's this many.
- Oh, it might be pretty good then.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Otis is this many now. - That many.
- Oh, really?
How many are you, Pat?
- I'm, no wait.
- 45. - 45.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
- 455.
- No, hold on, sorry, I missed up counting.
Okay, so it's--
- Or 14.
- He missed up.
You're five, you're five!
- You're five!
- Five, five, five, five, four.
- I'm four fives and a four.
- Yeah, Patrick, Patrick going up to a kid
and be like, "Hey, I'm five."
I'm this many.
- I'm this many.
- No, we're just like the bouncer.
He looks at your ID, he like, he flexes, he says "How old are you?"
I'm this many.
One, two, three, four.
Four.
Oh that's cool, I'm this many.
The bouncers like 60, he's 60 years old, he has to sit there doing 10, 6 times.
Have a good night.
And a half.
He holds up half a finger at the end.
I'm 21 and three quarters.
I'm twenty one and three quarters.
It is so fucked up when if you're an adult and you ask how old somebody is and they're
like, "Well my birthday is next month."
And it's like, who fucking cares?
It doesn't matter.
You're the age you are.
Don't try and get cute with me.
Or I'll kill you.
I hate cute shit.
Absolutely.
I like ugly fucked up cool stuff like Ghost Rider.
Yeah.
And Bugs Bunny.
bugs bunny whose head got chopped off
come on that's an american institution
yeah what the hell Cameron next thing you know you're gonna be telling me
you're gonna be telling me squidward is doing a suicide
you're gonna wanna look something up you wouldn't believe some of the things i've seen about
cartoons being killed
yeah
you wouldn't believe some of the fan theories that i have in my twisted brain
you wouldn't believe some of the dark ideas i have about what kind of blood comes out of different
characters
yeah i guess i mean i hear it's i heard a song the other day
about how well having a gun
my fan theories that on the jury are brothers and that's why they fight so
much
or that my theory theories that they're married
that's what it might so much areas of kitten theory
yes it is a small cat
it's true is
yeah their status was that brothers
known their blood brothers their blood brothers
their brothers by blood they did it
but they don't know that he's actually real brothers idea is that bugs bunnies
stay being funny as hell in the episodes hold that that is that the ratio
uh... we share that theory
we have a theory
i have a theory that uh...
sylvester as a speech impediment
one of my family and i'm going to laugh at one of my series i developed as i
think spongebob isn't in real life under the ocean i think he's a cartoon that
does
I think that's a fool's theory.
I think Spongebob has no holes and he has black spots.
Yeah.
Yeah, like a cheetah.
That's a really good theory.
And Patrick, I don't, Patrick is a girl.
One of my fan theories is that Patrick's actually in purgatory and all his characters in his
life are in his imagination.
Which one?
theory that christian ramsey is really cheap
christian crab that he's really he's really really cheap any of the money
my all my theory about christy the crab is his redness actually comes from
blood because of the how much he kills
you think he is a little bit also is a murder
yeah yeah also my theories is that the seven deadly sins are in sponge bob
yeah my theory is that squidward actually has a depression
gay yellow
yet yet uh... girl who
crazy
squirrel
stealing the crown word stealing the crown from king neptune lankton
uh... and what that
because he works at the restaurant
all he does work at a rest yet hamburger
hamburgers the seventh deadly sin
uh...
so this is under the cd something as you play with them this happened a few
minutes ago my brother asked me to play with them and i said no so he stole my
books and hit them and when he gave them back after a long time
he said if i would play with him and i said no and then he started crying in my
mom had to get involved of course and uh...
that's a sounds like a nerd here's a second nerd and uh... the
kid is actually
a bully and i'm on the bum on
the bully side pro-bully i'm actually i hear a little comment here
if it's against a nerd but if you're bullying a jock that's not cool
you don't know what's going on at their home that's making them act that way
their dad could be putting out cigarettes on them
so true i dread the day where either caleb
or nate or alfie comes over to our house
ten times worse when i have friends over it went like this friends and i play
minecraft together alfie
cory why don't you play with me if you don't mom will make you lucas one of my
friends. Aw, that's annoying. Alfie. And I want Lucas to play with me too. Lucas. Whaaat?
Reluctantly plays with Alfie. See what I mean? It is never a good experience.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, dude, when you get Caleb and Nate together, so annoying.
I'll admit, as Caleb is an annoying kid name. Yeah.
And here's a reply to that comment from the same user, from Alfie, one of my not-cringe
comments back in the day I am proud in memoriam of their old posts here's a
good one doesn't this happen in Jeff the killers
backstory says xx severed humanity xx I think it does Jeff the killer got
annoyed why do you think what do you think made him start killing true I guess
That's a good point. I love this if it is with my little brother
My seven-year-old brother is the opposite very big introvert wouldn't ask me for anything unless necessary and kind of mature past his age
Unlike my nine-year-old sister
Little kids want to play with me because I look like an eight-year-old
roll. That's a comment from Andy Bilinakis. Yeah, there's a lot of scripts on this one.
Too many scripts for my taste. This one's very long too. The one at the very bottom, yeah.
you want to read it? You know what? Sure. Do you want to be me or kid? Or six year old?
I think six year old might be kid. Yeah, I want to be. You'll see if we read the script.
Just choose six year old for now. I'll be six year old. Alright, I'll be me. Walks in
the kitchen. Do I have to be kid? No, you don't. Just wait. Let's play. I hate being
six-year-old okay restart go ahead okay walks in the kitchen let's play brothers
and sisters the brother has to act like a girl the brother has to play with dolls
can I have that thing over there to play with no I got it for my birthday and it
will break I won't break it thinks she said you won't break it I said you won't
break it fine I'll be the ugly Elsa doll doesn't look like Elsa you have it but
But don't break it.
I said it's fine.
Okay, Pat, this is where you come in.
Okay, by the way, now the six-year-old will be called kid.
That's a stage direction.
Have it!
I said I'm fine.
Let's play!
I don't want to play.
You're mean!
What?
I just didn't want to play.
I hate this game.
Second scenario.
I sit down next to my laptop, and guess what?
Thanks for helping me.
I was using my dolls to make a movie on your laptop.
You know you can't do that!
Oh wait, I gotta expand this.
Can you be the mom? Elsa is the mom!
Come on!
After a bit of normality.
Pretend the mom fainted.
Thinks no, I'm bored this little kid.
I'm gonna also be the little sister with the big sister.
Please, I won't have anything to play with.
Oh, this is you, Pat. Kid's mom.
What is going on?
I'm playing and he wants to be the little sister, but I am.
You should not be playing together!
Decide what you are going to play!
There we go, I found the voice.
I want to play Roblox on your laptop.
I want to go on my laptop.
You're not sharing.
I am, I let you on the laptop to play earlier.
Give it to me.
And my dad said you can't use it.
I've suffered getting told of by my parents just to let you on it.
Fine, I'll play on the Nintendo Switch.
Finally.
I convinced the kid to leave me alone, but she kept asking me to do stuff.
And she said I have to help her.
She calls my name and tells me cool stuff that she made and did in Minecraft.
That was a beautiful story.
Wow.
I mean, it had a big plot twist in the middle too.
Yeah.
A huge plot twist.
The 6 year old will now be called Kid.
I think when that, if you can do this in post, put the song from Fight Club in there.
It's kind of a split personality thing.
Pretty cool.
number two they force you to watch annoying little kids shows with them
true yeah this is facts this is facts my brother is 13 and watches My Little Pony
he makes me watch it and I hate it I'm 11 I'm sick of it my cousins forced me to
watch Disney jr. with them a few years ago at least I don't have to and that's
from Panthers for the win Patriots for the lose
no as kayla on the patriot bro keep pounding
they'll lose
like lazytown for example
true uh... i would not watch
let's say together okay
i would not want to watch one
i would if you can you give me one million dollars
missus with a great jets
that was amazing my sister makes be watched at the peak and then they reply
that's a good and that's the issue
okay wait is a script here on the second day of our well here we go okay so
are you a direction skin
okay i i will be albion reprise my role as little kid your typecast
And then Cam, you also just sign me as "me".
I'm always playing "me".
I wish I could play against...
We're looking for kind of a "me" type.
Yeah.
Alright.
Here's a tip to prevent a little kid forcing you to watch what you don't like to watch.
Plan A.
Let's watch Teletubbies.
"Uh, let's watch F-Zero GP Legend Anime, the super cool futuristic race car packed with exciting racing and light comedy."
"No, Teletubbies."
"I'll give you Candy and Disney Channel, all set of Barbie dolls and Teletubbies if you watch F-Zero GP Legend Anime."
Plan B.
Trick the little kid by disguising F-Zero GP Legend Anime DVD as a Teletubbies DVD.
Plan C.
scared a little kid with the monster mass
if you try to change the paper no one's
and i'm not going to ask
plenty scare the kid with a chucky doll
while i think i had a little word with the monster mass because it got a lot
stir massed with a lot of the master mask
uh... do you know when you know as a kid
you didn't you didn't take the
the chicken out of the freezer that fridge to thaw
your dad's coming home with a monster mass
that is a pull up with the monster massing
if you have you know you find that the chickens ninety finds that the chickens
not the odd
that's right you know you we are a great up late at night under covers playing
in ten dodi s you dad's footsteps you better you better show that the s
between your mattress in the wall 'cause he sees you
he's gonna leave and let me tell you the most i come back into the room
the monster's coming and i'm throwing my my game boy s_p_ in my butt cheeks
Wait now that storm.
Yep.
That's how much it's gonna fit.
And don't even think about trying to explain it away by saying you were playing Big Brain Academy.
It's not gonna work.
Yeah.
No.
That's not homework.
It's still a game.
It doesn't count as studying.
It's still fun.
What's the one that Penn Jillette was in?
You're playing with too much fun!
That's what your dad's gonna say.
The Penn Jillette game?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think he was Big Brain.
Right?
I don't know.
Oh wait, no.
It was Magic Simulator for Detective DS.
- Yeah, magic fat guy thing.
- Yeah.
- For DS.
- Libertarian, pendulet, libertarianism is magic.
- Libertarian, atheist, fat guy, magic thing.
Little no talking friend for DS.
Do you think he found--
- Little no talking friend.
- Do you think he found Teller in like a tree trunk?
- Yeah.
Teller, this guy ain't telling me anything.
That's the thing about this guy. How do you even learn magic?
Both of them look very fucked up.
He can't talk or read.
You ever see that Run DMC music video they're in?
No.
You're thinking of Aerosmith, Walk This Way.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Number three, they whine for their parents
because you got mad at them.
True.
A twelve year old is not a little kid.
My cousins scream a lot.
I tell them to shut up.
They cry for my relatives and I end up getting in trouble.
Need I say more?
Here's a comment from Dogs Unleashed.
There was some...
[Laughter]
That's such a good username.
There was some kid at a party and we were arguing
over who was going to hit the pinata.
Long story short, I didn't
get to hit the pinata.
Damn. That's so fucked.
All you
people are sick talking about your siblings like
that. They might never see you again in their life,
even in the biggest events, sickos.
goes these people that put stories in here I have to say this to you those
younger kids are bitches yo that's pretty harsh there's a lot of scripts here man
there's way too many scripts what is it's gotten into these people they heard our
last episode and there they yeah they realized that we're really we're
scouting screenplays from the top tens true sensitive gangster productions is
gonna have all of these movies made by 2022.
- Yeah, doing that thing, what was it?
- By the end of 2022. - Where N24 posted that thing
where they're making like a movie,
like a Travis Scott movie or something.
And they like posted just a picture of a screenplay
that said, "By Travis Scott."
We were just posting like 20 pictures a day
of just stacks of paper that say like,
like, yeah, like--
- "By Dogs Unleashed."
- Yeah, "By Dogs Unleashed," "By XX Severed Humanity."
(laughing)
cousin mistake by cut dogs unleashed. They're like yeah like 500 page scripts like like
bound. Oh yeah yeah we'd do them we'd do a big A-list celebs too. Oh yeah yeah we get
Javier Bardem to play the cousin. Yeah who's gonna play who's gonna play. Andy Serkis is
the piñata. Cameron has to play me. I'm always me. Yeah I know. Little kids. I'm straight
I'm straight up just like me.
I feel like I was born to play that role.
I think little kid and six year old are gonna be like, like that duo of roles is gonna be like the next like Joker kind of thing.
Where you have different, where James Bond, you know.
There's like a rotation every couple years.
Yeah, it's like a prestige role.
People wanna play.
Yeah, people are gonna be looking.
You know, why can't we have, why can't we have a female cousin?
That's right.
like a bunch of think pieces huge news Idris Elba will be playing six-year-old
in the cousin mistake saga yeah yeah number four yeah they get you in trouble
for something they did so in roblox she was in my account and guess what she was
online dating on my account and she tries to seem grown up but in reality she's
being stupid. That's so funny getting really mad at your sibling for getting
like groomed on your account. I remember my friend of mine got in trouble because he was dating a girl.
I think Patrick froze look at his beautiful expression. Who froze me or them? He's stuck. He looks so cute I'm
I'm gonna take a screenshot.
- Now he's gray.
- Oh no, he came back.
- Am I back?
- Oh, dude, my internet sucks here.
- That gave me time to reflect on the story
I was about to tell and I've decided to not tell it.
- Yeah?
- Yep, nope, that is, I saved, I dodged a bullet there.
- Maybe I need like a timeout type thing
so I can decide whether or not I'll take the next story.
- I should be able to give you timeouts like a coach.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I think that's a pretty good idea.
- I've experienced this a lot, so much pain in life.
I hope my parents die because I literally don't need them long story, but I don't
need them and the reply is I hope this comment haunts you for the rest of your
life for wishing death on your parents. They may be annoying, but there's still
the reasons you're alive. What did you guys read this one? We don't
Christmas 2015 my cousin hit me with an iPad then she told me I was being
annoying to her. I told them that I didn't do anything guess who they
believed that's right my cousin. Here's another here's a short but sweet comment
This defines my cousins.
*snort*
This is a very cousin-heavy episode.
Listen to this one.
Yes, my neighbor got me in trouble because she threw a water bottle on the ground.
It wasn't even a big deal, but now her parents hate me.
And every time she sees me, she beams like a sun and does cartwheels as if that's a show-off thing.
Whilst I'm skating and doing cool tricks.
So who's the show-off now, you little brat?
F you, Michaela. You are the reason your parents are divorced.
divorce. I hate when people do cartwheels as if that's some kind of show-off thing.
Me too. Make a go in and make grounded video of your cousin to teach her a
lesson. Imagine like your family court you're like being
asked like which one, which parent you want to stay with and you just bust
out a fat cartwheel. Yeah, just in your car wheel as if that's a show-off thing.
Who's the show-off now, Michaela?
The judge is like, well, Michaela did an amazing show-off trick and I cannot-
OBJECTION! A cartwheel is a show-off thing!
Overruled! Michaela, your parents are forced to get back together!
Your Honor, a cartwheel is clearly a show-off thing.
Number six.
Wait, one more. Oh, you got another.
One kid broke my dad's laptop by dropping it down the stairs and blamed me for it.
I was so grounded.
Then they caught him on the surveillance video the next day and ungrounded me right away
and apologized for not believing me and they called his parents.
He was grounded.
Having a surveillance video in your house to catch kids breaking laptops.
When I was a kid, my dad had one of those air freshener things you plug into the wall.
But I thought that it was a security camera.
mhm inside i would like act really weird in this one part
house
i would like never like
if i would like uh... wake up ur like in the middle of the night
i would like to avoid uh... an airway because i think it's a security camera
it's pretty cool right
number uh... five they never shut up
this is much like sonic boom rise of lyric where instead of awesome music you
get to listen to the four main characters not shutting up
true yep lots of long comments on this list yeah it seems like this one brought
out a lot of a lot of anger in people definitely happened to me once when I
was 13 once in the car by five-year-old cousin asked 5,000 questions about a
horse it was so annoying yeah the question my brother talks about
dinosaurs all day every day that sounds like a blessing like a cool kid yeah
dude I just got a field guide this is so true come over and look at it it's so
awesome well we should go look for dinosaurs this is so true the little
ones are louder than the rocket launches true that is facts a few minutes ago my
thorat hurted because of screaming my ass off at my four-year-old brother my
My thorat.
My thorac-
Did you read this one?
They sure haven't brought it into the house.
My thorax.
My brother slapped me in the thorax.
[Laughter]
Uh, number six.
They ask you to do ridiculous things for them.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, once my mom would force me to make videos of myself singing terribly to random songs
just to entertain my cousins while they were eating dinner.
This one.
Hi, I'm twelve.
My nephew always asks, "Would you choose a hanger over me?" and "Will you let me in your
room if someone busted up in the house and would you let someone kill me i'd be
like yes i would let someone kill you and he'd be like i know that's not true
and then i'd be like that why you ask you'd be like i don't know
the cover players
could you please cut the i'd be like and he'd be like
that's a cool way to talk
there's one that's it's so pretty being twelve and having a nephew in your
nephew's asking you guys we would you would you let me dot
I would say yes.
Would you care if I even died?
Yeah.
Would you care?
Would you even give a 4 year old, would you even give a shit if I died?
That's such a good thing for like a little kid to be obsessed with asking.
By the world, make me fly, eat an entire school lunch without throwing up.
By the world, make me fly.
When my 9 year old cousin was younger she forced me to wipe her butt for her after she used
the restroom.
She was like 3 or 4 at the time.
I'm never wiping anyone's butt but my own.
And I barely do that.
If I ever have a kid, I'm gonna get a robot to do it.
Hopefully they'll have those by then.
I don't want to ever...
Or a maid.
a maid yeah just a wiping maid a wife maid.
Maid wiping only?
Yeah a wiping only maid there's a different maid to clean and the wipe maid gets paid
less because she only does one thing.
Exactly yeah it doesn't matter how hard the job is.
I guess I could pay you more if you wanted to wipe me and my wife too.
Yeah if you want to get really deep when you wipe I'll pay you extra.
If you want to wipe a little bit of the poop out of the inside of my butt.
And then like a month later being like, "Hey, do you still have that poop you wiped off me
a month ago?
I need a stool sample."
And then six months in you go to the National Enquirer like a tabloid and you break a story
that's like you on the front page like, "My maid won't stop wiping my butt."
You get her just like, "Can we put her in jail?"
Number seven, they never leave you alone.
It's so true.
I'll play with you, says Anonymous.
That's creepy.
Yeah, I'll say.
This one, all the comments here are too long.
Yeah, how about some one word comments?
Hey, wait, here's a--
I'm never gonna play with you, so go away.
Here's a script, a very short script on the last page
can reprise my role as a little kid sure and cam you'd be big kid please okay
okay hey sissy shut up lol see that one doesn't have as much going on no in it
as some of the other scripts you really know much at all no I don't I'm not even
really sure what the that one's gonna be hard to that's gonna be it's an
unadaptable yeah absolutely script as some might say yeah but they hey they
said that about Dune and look how that went. True. That's true. Yeah. We could be seeing
a Denis Villeneuve little kid, sissy big kid movie pretty soon. We could. Yeah, you never
know. Number eight, when you ask for something, your parent says no, but when the little kid
asks for the exact same thing, they get it immediately. How come when I ask for a diaper,
I don't get one, but when this kid does, he gets a diaper? It's so messed up what they
do the definition of my annoying nephew if our world depends on the youth of
today I can see the earth lasting another 20 years that makes sense because then
they won't be young anymore yeah true to the be new kids yeah this one also has
no good comments wait wait me can I have a YouTube account I'm 26 mom no me why
not my cousin has one she's nine I show my mom my cousin's YouTube account mom I
I said no is no, okay?
Why is a nine-year-old allowed to have a YouTube account,
but not a 26-year-old?
That makes no sense at all.
- That's so true.
- The reply, your mom has no right to stop you
creating a YouTube channel, computer fan zero.
(laughing)
That's the first ever computer fan, guys.
- Yeah.
- Came before computer fan one, yeah.
- That's actually, that's a very adaptable screenplay.
- That is a really good screenplay.
- Kind of a controlling mother, controlling a 26-year-old,
not letting him have a YouTube account? I feel like this could be Tom Holland's
chance to break out of the MCU. Playing 26 year old. Yeah. Yeah. He'd be so good as 26
year old. Number 9. Probably the best. They stare at you. I sometimes have to wear an eye
patch because I just had a surgery on my eye and we went out to eat. This rude little kid
kept staring at me because I was wearing that. Then she loudly asked her mom, "Mommy, why
Why did that girl paint over her eye?
Mind your own business, you brat!
That's so rude.
That poor kid just wanted to know what was going on.
Years ago, I was at Ocean City, Maryland, and I was playing Final Furlong at one of the
arcades and a baby was staring at me.
Also years ago, I was at Wildwood, New Jersey, riding a coin-operated horse at Ed's Funcade,
and a toddler was staring at me.
I was a teenager at the time, and I was just being random and having fun.
My sister always stares at me for like 10 minutes before she goes to bed. Don't underscore blank
7. That's the that's she doesn't blink. That's what he's trying to say with his username.
Yeah, this is this comment. I think we can all relate to here this summer in 2019. We
went to India for five weeks, which I don't enjoy and we met my three-year-old twin cousins
who were fine two years ago but turned super obnoxious, and I was watching YouTube on their
TV and mom made me stop and I got into an argument because I was dying of boredom and depression
due to the fact that there was pretty much nothing fun to do on India trips except watching
TV and my cousins were staring at me.
I was so mad that day.
How is there nothing fun to do on India trips?
I know!
There's so many big restaurants you could go to.
There's those really curvy boats.
Yummy Sea Strike.
Tandoori Strike.
You gotta hit Tandoori Stop when you're in town.
Absolutely.
Every single time, bro.
The number four combo?
I don't know, I like Yummy C Tummy better.
Yummy C Tummy's probably one of the best ones there.
Plus they have Mr. Beast Burger.
Oh, true.
Yeah.
Dude, they have Mr. Beast, but they have like, it's cool because they have like, you know,
items that you wouldn't get in the States.
Like you can't get like the Mr. Beast Paneer sandwich.
True.
That is true.
Nice.
Yeah.
anonymous commenter says I stare at them
yep all right number 10 they act spoiled no comment truth and we can just go
through the mmm the contenders this one's actually true number 11 they asked you
to play annoying songs do what is up with kids in these fucking annoying yes the
most annoying world yeah I like that as a kid did I know I was I was into the
classics like twinkle twinkle a.c. well I was like I mean maybe I must have been
annoying people when I was asking them to play like Beethoven and Japan and stuff
you know I was asking them to play mmm 4433 by John Cage yeah what that that
song that song I mean look I'm singing it right now no no you wrong for that
That's too short. That was you're sing to by John Cage
That's a
Kill the song the photo is the is the gummy bear song and naked gummy bear with a stub singing in a high-pitched voice
He might taste gross, but I want to eat him anyway, so he dies
I don't know that must have been in the German version. He had a stub yeah
It's kind of disgusting to gummy meow
12 they report everything you do. Yeah kids are tattletales period they are
Number 13 they hog all of the attention. Yeah, that's so funny being like a 26 year old guy
And just being like my fucking my little cousins like getting so much more attention than me plus. They're allowed on YouTube
Yeah, number 14 is they sing songs over and over again, and here's a comment if you thought that's bad
I once saw two kids doing the whip nay-nay dance while waiting at the cinema lobby
This is why I am pro-choice now and that abortion should be legal worldwide
The whip and the nae-nae do those are some of the coolest dances ever well you have a problem with those
There's a comment here that says I saw a little girl with a shirt saying I know all the lyrics of frozen
And I will sing them to you
That is unbelievable we they now the kids now the
There the kids are doing the whip and the nene
But we used to eat the chips that were Lays Lays. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah
Nowadays kids are doing the whip and the nene back in my day used to get the school on horse using the whip and the hey
Hey, yeah. Yeah, that is that is really true
Yeah
Back in my day
Now we do the whip and the nay nay back in the 1800s we used to be on ships and say nay nay
Mm-hmm
Yep, yeah, I mean hey now kids used to do the whip and the nay nay
But now a few years later kids nowadays are just crips and don't want to play play
True true and on the streets of LA that you know a lane will get you will get slice laid
By the crips yeah
Growing up yeah back in the nowadays kids doing the whip in the nae nae growing up. I had uncle chip who was gay gay
We used to do the whip in it no never mind never mind the kids now do the whip of the nae nae mm-hmm
This might be the hardest one yet
No, this is here's like kids nowadays their idea their idea of a good is a good summer is
is doing the whip and the nay nay,
but back when I was a kid,
I'd rather have a trip or a vacay-cay.
- That's right.
(laughing)
Nowadays these kids just wanna do a Fortnite dance.
I wanna go on a food tour, use a fork and knife in France.
- Yes sir.
- Try a Michelin star restaurant in France.
- Kids nowadays are too focused on learning the floss dance.
I'm trying to stack my paper so I can buy some Hugo Boss pants.
Yeah.
That's right.
Yep.
I heard that.
Definitely.
What else do kids like these days?
Uh.
Jujubes.
TikTok.
Jujubes, sock hops, playing jacks.
Nowadays kids are doing TikTok.
When I was their age, I was, uh, I was jelking with hair ties to get a thick cock.
(laughing)
- Yep.
- That's pretty good.
- Yeah.
- Yes sir.
Back in my day, we didn't have TikTok.
- Mm-hmm, what'd you have, brother?
What'd you have?
- What did you have?
- I don't remember.
(laughing)
I don't remember, guys, fuck.
Um, I remember I sang the La Cucaracha song too many times to my older sister.
Yeah.
La Cucaracha, that's a damn annoying song.
Yeah, that's a good song.
Yeah, if you hate Mexico, me, I love it.
It's a catchy ass song.
I repped it.
It is catchy.
I sang that song a lot as a kid.
Number 16, they follow you wherever you go.
Mm-hmm.
I am from Somalia.
Who wrote that shit, the damn Pied Piper?
Come on now.
That's right.
right yeah I am from Somalia yes number 18 they ask are we there yet I don't know
does it look like we're there no then stop asking this is why your kid should
play with Google Maps I've been using it since I was 7 number 21 app number 21
they act like teens if I had a sister in order for me to shut them up I'd head to
my drum set and play a Neil Peart style solo. Wait, oh, that'd just make them scream louder.
Here's a script here Cameron and Caleb can do. On what? On they act like teens. I think
Caleb you should be playing Gretchen. Yeah I play me. Caleb's definitely a Gretchen type.
How am I a Gretchen type? Okay whatever. What are you doing? Playing Bloodborne and ignores
if you don't tell me what you were doing I'm telling mom set up you're not my
parent we're gonna have this everywhere by next year it's gonna be huge in China
we're gonna have to remove a lot of references so that it plays actually what
I want the I would really like the Wachowski sisters to adapt this one here
okay 23 they spit at your face if they can't beat you up here's what I this is
This is the Matrix 5, okay?
Okay.
Yes.
My five-year-old cousin once tried to hit me, so I grabbed her wrist stop.
She tried to hit me again with her other hand, so I grabbed it too.
When she realized she couldn't move, both of us can't since I'm holding her hands with both of mine,
she spat straight at my face.
It was a big saliva that landed between my eyes, so my reaction is violent.
Since then, she would spit at me when she is angry or just want to piss me off.
In other words, she spits every time she wants.
She loves my reaction.
It is gross. I hate it.
I can already imagine that, uh...
I can see that as a monologue.
I can imagine the 8 bullet time. Yeah, going into spit time.
That's cool as fuck, dude. Oh my god.
That would be sick. And it's just like the rain scenes from The Matrix where all the spit is just suspended.
Oh my god.
Hello, Cousin Anderson.
Cousin Anderson! Cousin Anderson!
Cousin's like you are a disease. You're a virus.
I finally watched one and two. I gotta still see three.
You'd never see what's wrong. I never finished the matrix. That's why you do. That's why you're not as conscious as me
You're Cameron. Yeah. Well, I never watched literally the best my grandpa's favorite movie
Your grandpa's favorite movie. Oh, yeah, he was driven to insanity by the Matrix. You told me that's pretty cool
I think it'll be that week will be driven to insanity by the Matrix
Yeah, I almost was driven insane by how good the action was. Yeah, I mean I was going crazy
I was nearly driven to Lawrence Fishburne in that movie. I was nearly driven to Kung Fu
I was nearly driven to FYE to buy the box set
Damn
All right
Subscribe to the patreon
No, I actually do that and the twitch which is nothing not and
For a libs home address all right