(upbeat music)
- Order, order, order in the court.
Welcome, dearly beloved.
We are gathered here today.
for the trial of the people versus Patrick Doran in the case of the heinous
and horrible and inhuman kidnapping of beautiful jungles group we need a by it
we need a daughter order without a bias order order my my client order I haven't
even finished sorry the thing you'll have time for opening so I have to start
now I have to start over dearly beloved we are gathered here today in the
horrible terrible no good crime of the abuse kidnapping and possibly sexually
motivated. We are now adding that to the list of crimes. Is sexual assault and
no and no yeah we're adding. It's not being added. You can't you know where you're
being tried for I'm not sure you're gonna be found guilty. Okay opening
the
I think it's a coin flip, right? Yeah, it's definitely a coin flip. You guys want to flip this hammer? Yeah
Uh, I don't have a coin
Uh, anyone have a coin?
I don't have a coin. Okay. Well, okay, I guess we're using a starbucks lid. Okay, this is gonna make a coin
Heads is heads is first. I want tails is when it's under right? Yeah, I want tails
So how this is right here. This is this tails right now tails right now. Yeah, okay
This is this is to win you get to choose first or second, right? Yeah, sure
Okay, I'm gonna flip it. Okay. This is what the judge does in a case. He's the one
who flips the coin. It was heads. All right. I want first. All right. I want to
come at you with the strong arm of the law right now. The long strong arm of the
law. Your Honor and people of the jury including Alex Forrest and Jungel Skog.
I would like to establish today that there is beyond reasonable, beyond the
possibility of reasonable doubt that one Patrick Edward Doran violated New York
City's first-degree kidnapping penal law code 135.25 which states
kidnapping in the first degree essentially amounts to the broad crime
of kidnapping in the second degree with one of a few aggravating factors which
also serve to narrow the kinds of circumstances where the crime is charged
by police departments. Kidnapping in the first degree is an A1 felony
punishable by life in prison. Do you understand me? This sounds serious Mr. Doran. He spent all
Saturday writing this. There's no way I'm gonna win. A person, a person can and I
believe this day will be charged with kidnapping in the first degree when they
commit the crime of kidnapping in the second degree in that they abduct the
person or junglescook and either when their intent is the whole is to hold the
person for ransom or compel someone to do or not to do something what might be
called traditional kidnapping or when the victim is held for more than 12 hours
with intent to inflict injury on them sexually abuse them advance some other
felony or terrorize the victim or another person and your honor I'm here
today to prove that Patrick Edward Doran used his his captivity of Jungelskoog
to inflict terror on the employees of this office building. With his penis.
And also he stuck his penis in Jungelskoog. I did not stick my penis in Jungelskoog.
So let's start with the facts okay? Let's start with the facts. Order!
What did we get out of here?
Jungelskoog... I'm gonna give you guys a quick glimpse into
the jungles Cougar's life youngle skug was born sometime on Saturday or Friday what
day do we go Friday Friday sometime on Friday March the 11th okay sustained
sustained he was born on Thursday Thursday it was Thursday and we he came
back there's a new home at approximately 4 p.m. and he found his resting spot so I
want to put you I want to put you into a place in time 4 p.m. on a Thursday okay
young go skook young go skook the the young brand new to the world young go
Scoog is introduced to his new home. He's hanging on a set of Christmas lights
looking, I mean, dare I say adorable. Any objections? No, I didn't think so,
adorable. So what is the last thing that he thinks in that moment? "I'm going
to get kidnapped and sexually assaulted by one of my dads." Can we agree on that?
any objections he was not thinking that that was the last thing on his young
monkey mind and can we stop saying that I sexually assaulted the monk we can
stop objection no grounds for such a claim for which claim sexual assault
well you guys you have to work on you to prove that because that's how it works
because I said he sexually still assaulted youngle skug and so we're
need listen buddy that is slandered look up slander lock your slander and we will
counter sue that's why we'll have another yeah that's okay so today two
days three days sorry three days after you uncle skoog is brought into this
world who comes into the office but Patrick one of his dad's Patrick Dorn
the defendant and what does he do while he's here but viciously and violently
sexually assaulting I don't like this anymore you're going too far with it and
okay fine maybe he didn't sexually assault him okay but I'll say this much
down. Yeah, it's kidnapping. This is simple robbery. Okay, well,
I'll robbery child robbery. Okay, kidnapping is actually technically
young. Young uncle Scoob was here. He was sitting on our equipment
rack where we went. You went right to that. What you went right
to sexual assault and it was about kidnapping. I've I kind of
I got lost and I'm doing a kind of a dramatic lawyer thing. He's
trying to scare the people who choose if you listen it whether or not I can prove
that Patrick Edward Doran Doran sexually so why do you keep saying my last name
wrong door I'm friends for three years whether I can prove that that it doesn't
matter if I can prove that today okay we're not think we're not gonna talk
about that anymore today okay that's a that's a day where that's day two of the
trial that's a conversation for another day but not today so young girl skook is
sitting on the equipment rack Patrick comes in and we can prove by the way
ladies and gentlemen that Patrick did in fact come to the office do we have do
we have evidence for that - let me tell you what I actually do have evidence let
me see this and I can not only the judge of I can prove that Patrick is Joe
hasn't said a thing on a cross-examine I thought we'll get to evidence later but
okay ladies and gentlemen the point is please wrap it up Patrick Edward
please wrap it up. I'm wrapping up Patrick Edward Doran Doran didn't did
did in fact come in on Sunday, March the thirteenth grab young school from the
equipment rack grabbed leading what the word grabbed is no
overturned.
It makes rules. He's making a an accusation that is it's an it's opening
statement. He did, but how did okay, we said we're not doing evidence yet, so
can say whatever he wants that's right placed him in a box at the end of the
other end of the office wrapped him in a green screen cloth and left a menacing
note that read and I'd like to just finish my my opening statements with this
the haunting chilling note that he read or that he wrote which is I mean it's
really it's terrifying if you're sensitive to things like this you may
want to cover your eyes. Junglescoog is gone. Sad face, sad face. Do not look for
him. He does not want to be found. Now look look at young Junglescoog and tell
me that this face wouldn't want to be found. Your Honor, I yield my time.
Okay. I close my statement. All right. Mr. Gleason, representing Patrick
Doran. You gotta hold the mic closer to your face. I am Joe Gleason, I'm representing Patrick
Doran, who I know to be a very kind and sweet and generous man. Yesterday at 830
p.m. Sunday, Patrick Doran arrived in the office ready to get some work done at
his new setup desk monitor. It's an exciting time to be Patrick Doran. That
sounds fun. He walks in with his bag of Burger King and he is repulsed and
astonished by this haunting chilling note that the prosecution just read. Before
even sending any evidence he said "who did it? It wasn't me."
Patrick knows the manner in which his closest friends treat him, antagonize him,
and berate him regardless of any evidence in any way shape or form. He sends a
picture of the sign which does read "Jungle Skoog is gone.
Sad face, sad face. Do not look for him. He does not want to be found." That is met
yet with a response by our current judge who said you will never get away with this.
Which I think throws this whole trial into green.
If you can find another judge in 30 seconds then we'll switch him out.
You have to give it to Alex.
He's not trained to be a judge.
I've actually trained a lot of time at judge school.
He's done bias training.
yeah i'm willing to forgive and forget i'm willing to trust cameron on this
thank you i'm not willing to forgive and forget anything today okay i'll prove it
i'll prove it to you
uh... patrick responded with i'm being frightened
i'm serious
patrick has maintained his innocence from the very beginning of this entire
unjust much like oj simpson
innocent
i'm proven by a court of law to be innocent
i'm not saying
i said w_t_f_ with a crying sad face
cameron said why are you in the office them patrick said i'm working on my
power point
i'm working on my power point for uh... show them to be on at life world on the
seventeenth
uh... there's tickets online objection
objection to the same love sustained
they can't do that
court
what it all boils down to is that patrick is being blamed
for reporting a crime
you mentioned jungle skus fathers you mentioned
at two points
at many points
you mentioned on the school's scoops fathers
jungle school is a very unorthodox
kind of parents situation his five different fathers
and this is all being pinned on one of the five
and i would say that patrick doran should not be on trial
we should be having an open-ended discussion on which one of us
all of whom have access to this office
could have come in in the time frame before 830 and since Thursday, whatever, Thursday
at 8 430. Patrick Doran is not on trial. The office is on trial.
Well, that's not true. It's the people versus Patrick Doran.
Or I'm saying shouldn't be on trial. Also, I would just like to kibosh any SA claims that
have been heinously levied. I dropped it, okay? I got a little bit excited.
You seem really fixated on this. I'm not. Caleb is. I haven't talked about it since I said I wasn't going to.
Jungle Skoog is just like us. He has two eyes, he has a nose, a mouth, he has two arms and two feet.
But he has no butthole and that drove our defendant insane.
[Laughter]
I would like to point out to the jury and to the prosecution that Jungle Skoog has no holes.
he has no holes that have been made
since his birth he is he looks exactly the same
and if anything he was he was swaddled
in a little blanket as if he's a small little baby Patrick Doran
is one of the kindest sweetest man I know what is it smell like
smells like a
penis objection
what are you talking about?
(laughter)
sounds like a penis
ok so what happens after the opening statements
I'd like to call to the stand Patrick Doran
ok
(laughter)
that's a gavel
yup
that's a gavel and an egg carton for the people listening at home
ok
here you can take this mic
Hi Patrick.
Hi.
So Patrick--
It's my old roommate.
Hi.
We used to be roommates but now we're not.
Patrick what were you doing yesterday?
Yesterday--
How did you let your day begin?
My day began, I woke up, I was with my girlfriend and then I walked her to the train.
What time is that train?
At 12.
12 noon.
Proceed what happened next okay, then I went back home and I took a shower. Do
you have proof perhaps pictures of you in the shower? I have a picture. I do I
do I have a picture of me after the shower because I was going to wear a
crazy outfit.
I have a photo picture. Can we have a photo of the crazy outfit? Can we see
the crazy outfit here? Yes,
is there a time stamp with there's a time stamp on the crazy outfit?
It is at exactly 1 p.m. I wore a shirt a sweater that says golf on it with real
tree pants and I sent a picture of that to my girlfriend and I asked does this
go?
Continue. It did it go? She said I looked handsome enough that she didn't care.
I did not wear the outfit I switched because I felt that it looked it was too
much so Patrick is Patrick is under the impression that wearing a fun you know
exciting outfit is too much business for just a normal day let alone a kidnapping
and a crime and I had plans to go skateboarding which again there are
receipts there are pictures
if you have a look at the door he loves to skateboard
he's a he's great at it he's the best reporter i know
we've established that he already commits crimes on a daily basis objections
skateboarding is in the olympics
skateboarding school yeah in china
well and there are a couple of people who have a skateboard
objection racist
I... yes.
Patrick Doran is guilty of...
Yes!
Reporting a crime.
What the fuck? Patrick Doran was just reporting a crime and we also have
a statement from Patrick
that goes through his day. I said this, I said it already, I said the same thing.
Okay, he said the same thing.
Yeah. Okay.
So I went, wait, I left out, so I went,
I did that.
You left out when you kidnapped Rumpelstiltskin.
No, I went to, I have an actual receipt of a purchase that I made.
I bought new trucks.
Let's see it.
I have, well, there's a, it's right there.
Okay, well that's not a receipt.
That's a skateboard.
Okay.
I'll pull up my Discover Card account.
And can you read the card number out to the, for the...
I'd like to be in cross-examination when you get a chance.
I think you can cross-examine Patrick as much as you want, but I think that you will have
to find him.
Okay, it has a transaction date.
He is kind.
He is sweet of heart.
And he doesn't want to hurt anyone.
Okay.
Patrick, how are you today?
I'm good.
Yeah?
I'd be better if I wasn't being framed.
You got a smile on your face?
I'd be better if I wasn't being framed by my closest friends.
closest. I'm gonna ask the questions okay and you're gonna answer them. That's how
this works. All right. Would you say hmm if you could describe your Sunday
afternoon with one emoji what would it be?
Can I look through the emojis? Nope. Nope.
Probably just the the one that's like this. Which one is that? I can't see your
your mind can't see your straight the straight line on okay the gym face
emojis yes the gym so a day where you kidnap someone is a normal day for you
you're the judge and you're not allowed to order order you're not allowed to
speak or listen I'm the one who tells you you're not allowed to speak you're
not allowed to speak for the rest of the cross-examination oh that fucks me up
okay okay so you said the gym face one okay and where where does Jim Halpert
work. I order you to speak the office mmm Thunder Mifflin gotcha so what I have so
far from what you've said it just this short time that I've had you is you've
mentioned emojis and you've mentioned the office you were leading as in that
objection leading is completely fine and you do it all the time I'm looking up
the rules of court right now there are some courts that let you lead and some
that don't and we're the one that lets you lead. And I'd like to ask you... It's just
based on the court. I'd like to ask you a few more questions here Patrick. What
time did you arrive at the office on March 13th? 8.30. 8.30. Gotcha. So 8.30 is
when you say you arrived. Around 8.30. Around 8.30. Okay so now anywhere between
between 825 to 830. Okay, all right, so you're changing the time a lot, which is
which is perfectly fine if you're a huge liar, like I wouldn't do it, but if you
want to that's fine. By almost five times. No, here's my big question. The photo
composition of the photo that you took of the ransom note, we'll call it a
Ransom Note for now, is so kind of perfect. It follows every compositional rule of
photography, rule of thirds, background foreground, you even added a little flare
of your Burger King bag in the back. Okay? So my question is, if you, if any
reasonable person arrived, excuse me, if any reasonable person arrived at the
office and saw the horror that Patrick witnessed on that day, allegedly, that he
alleges he witnessed and did not cause, would you be able to even take one
second of a break from crying your eyes out-- nope-- to take a perfect photo like
that? Because I'm gonna speak for myself and I think the rest of the office when I
say no. No. I would be losing my mind, it would look like a still from
Cloverfield there's no possible way that I can take such a perfect photo.
You can't say anything to him.
He took time to put the Burger King bag down behind the sign.
That's a good point.
And you did not, and you, listen, I'd like to make one more point.
Before even looking for Junglescoog and worrying about his well-being,
you were taking photos and messaging the group chat to establish your innocence
innocence before you even looked for him.
Your instinct was to protect yourself before your child.
- He's not my kid.
- Whoa!
- I don't care if you move to the dock.
- Can everyone gasp for a sound bite?
(gasps)
- What did you just say?
- What did he say?
- I've played the fifth.
default himself and i missed it
that's what we need to cross examinations
patrick
i'd like to ask a question or questions yeah
first of all i would like to point out so jungle skunk
the the branson note was found by patrick at eight twenty seven p_m_
which is in line with when he arrived in the office
it takes you it takes him two minutes to walk from the door to the table
statement
and said to you said arrived at twenty four
i spent spent the first couple seconds looking for jungle skunk
and then i i took the picture because i knew i was immediately being framed
and jungle school was found by patrick
i might add
amir nineteen minutes later
uh...
it's a lot of that
and that's what i think that i have to do that
Mr. Doran, were any of those 19 minutes spent consuming Burger King?
Yes they were. Yes they were. I had a Whopper with fries and a small onion ring
and a Dr. Pepper. So again you're worrying about yourself before
Yunglescoop. Because I knew I was being framed and I knew that he was okay. So your
proverbial kind of last meal you're enjoying. I knew that he was okay. Why did you know he
was okay is it because because one of you was because you were the architect of
his fate no because I was being framed I'd like to call to the stand one an
expert witness just one just one okay and that would be truthologist Cameron
better here Alex you have to be the judge now can you slide this around hi there
okay we have a new we have a substitute judge judge how are you your honor I'm
good I had a heavy night last night judging a lot of cases but I don't think
it should interfere with my judging I agree thank you for that hero guilty
- Cameron, oh. (laughing)
Mr. Cameron Fetter, how are you today?
- I'm doing well. - Okay.
- I'm hungering for vengeance. (laughing)
- And Cameron, how long have you studied
the art of truthology?
- Practically my entire life.
- Okay, as if you can't remember a day
when you weren't a truthologist.
- Basically. - Okay.
And just looking at Patrick, could you do,
I'm not sure if you do this. Could you do a quick truth analysis of just kind of
his body and his body language and kind of give me a percentage point? Okay, so
for the audience he does have his hands behind his back. He kind of a
Matthew McConaughey pose. So there are several key points of truthology
that are kind of tenets of the study that let you know whether or
not somebody is telling the truth and one big point that we always
look for is smiling too damn much and he's got a little bit of a smirk here as
we can see so that's that's one point of of the liar of of liar dumb. He does
look disgusting. He's smiling a little more here. Another another sign that we
look for in liars is earring on the right side and he does possess this
trait right now, which is the second major point that we as truthologists
look like and something that we see with liars a lot too is that they after they
lie they attempt to hide themselves away and they try to but to become elusive
and as you can see he is wearing camouflage on his shirt, which is a
hallmark of trying to hide or disappear after you've been discovered or caught
in a lie. So those are three main points and it only takes half a point to be
deemed a liar under truthology. So he is really six times a liar. Yeah, oh my
goodness, okay on based on hard science. So now quick question about yesterday
So you were obviously involved in the group chat.
Oh yeah.
You know, and we commissioned you to do a truthology review on a video that Patrick made where he
professes his innocence.
Yes.
Okay, and could you very quickly recite what you said in response to that video?
Okay, let me, I have to find it.
One second.
video is way too long we're not watching it guilty okay and then could you very
quickly for for for reference I also made a video professing my innocence
because it was a lot of accusations being levied at the time you tell me
what you said about my video yeah I said I just analyzed that video and it has a
truth reading of over 100 points hashtag where's Patrick's video hashtag guilty
yeah okay you said it has over 100 points you said it only needs six to be a liar
truthology is not real objection truth all I've studied truthology for over 20
years and this clown probably been a lawyer for what five minutes wants to
tell me it's not real if truthology so fake who invented it not true
it was John truth.
Okay, and
can I submit evidence to while I'm not the judge. I really want to submit
a piece of evidence.
Listen, this is huge. Actually, it's a huge breakthrough the case. We're
having a piece of evidence submitted live. Okay, by our truthologist. So
Patrick here, give me this Patrick. Do you remember making this post on
March 12th,
at 2 42 p.m. on are you at lunch enjoyer on Twitter yes do you remember making
this post quote jungle skug will go missing end quote no hit can you
refresh the page I'm actually I've already archived the page so if you've
deleted it that does nothing for your case and actually we're gonna include
that that includes a charge of tampering with evidence hmm it does yes hmm so do
you don't remember making this post I remember all of the posts I make online
are done in a character okay all right with that in mind let's go through some
of these no no no no no no if you insist that that day that this is all a
character let's check this out it's actually it's all me it's 100% real it's
all you and it's 100% real so you so including including the the the jungles
post no that was done facetiously on this same on this same facetious means just
kidding
Patrick a tweet from Patrick's Twitter account yesterday yeah I got a BAFTA big
ass fucking Toyota Avalon I just I'm trying to can we quickly just give a
a rating of this post. I'm gonna give a round of applause for this post. I mean this has got to be one of the best posts of all time.
I think it's funny. That's a funny tweet. It's timely. The BAFTA Awards happened.
He doesn't have a Toyota Avalon. He doesn't have a car. Patrick does not have a driver's license.
So I think this just goes to show that Patrick is tweeting
in said character, not tweeting the truth. He is not, you know, his retweets are not necessarily endorsements.
So if you have, if you tweet in this kind of character as you say it, we'll call it
we'll call it an alternate personality almost. Do you ever find yourself losing
time to this alternate personality? Maybe becoming him kind of a la Jekyll and
Hyde? No. Okay. So there's no possibility that this character took over your psyche
as you entered the office that day filled you with so much non-sexual rage that
you snatched Junglescoog, wrapped him up in a green thing, and put him in a box.
I'm actually also a snatchologist and Patrick's fingers actually have the
perfect articulation for snatching. Patrick does love to talk
about his his his large hands he I don't love to talk about my large he brings it
up all the time I was like a girl does at a bar I'm hearing in sizes I told you
yes I did compare hand sizes with you both of you and how many times I would
say three or four times in the past couple months and what I've noticed is
that you have very large kind of snatchy grabby hands you're you're just a grabby
guy his hands his hands he has bigger hands and then either either me or Caleb
look my hands don't even fit around him I'd like to ask for a hand comparison
between the five of us okay are you sure Joe oh wow Patrick's hands are
approximately the same size as mine which is and he's and he's six five yeah
I have the hands of a six foot five man bigger than mine snatch ability snatch
ability. Yep. Okay, continue the test. Let's go. Oh, no. Alex is bigger. No. No, they're
not. They're the same. Alex has bigger hands. I have longer fingers. Okay, but I can't,
my, I can't. I'd like to call Alex to the stand. I'd like to, I can't lift him up. I'd
like to call, I'd like to call Alex to the stand. Let's all call Alex to the stand. You
You are no longer the judge.
Okay, I'm back to being the judge.
I'm being examined?
Yeah, you, yeah.
Okay.
Fine.
Alex, Alex.
Hit me, hit me with it.
Alex, you have the biggest hands in the office.
Thank you.
Would you say that this helps you with snatching things?
Um, no, because I, I, while my hands are big, they're not very agile.
Look how long it takes me to lift this, lift up Jungle Scoog.
Okay, you've been holding Jungle Scoog this entire time.
It's 'cause...
Once I have him, I can kinda do whatever I want, but like I...
You can do whatever you want?
Whatever I want in a...
Alex, where were you yesterday?
Where were you yesterday?
Yesterday I was at work. I worked a double.
And then I arrived home at approximately night at 8.30 and I...
Okay, so you arrived home at 8.30...
Wait, no, no.
Patrick found...
Sorry, I'm...
And you live 10 minutes away from here.
Shut up.
You have any proof?
Yes, I do.
I can show you.
I arrived home on the train.
I went to Queen Restaurant and I bought a chicken shawarma and I have the email or I have the
text and order confirmation from this restaurant.
It was sent.
That's so far from our place.
I was coming back on the train and I stopped.
I got off.
Or coming back from here.
Which one was it?
Coming back from work.
I work.
You work in an office, no?
No, my other job I work at.
I was I was your other I got a I got a text at I had sex 715 that my order was
ready we'll be ready at 730 and I went and I got my order and then I went back
to the apartment took a shower I believe at about your painting a very wide open
window. No, no, no. I have an alibi. Let's see. At 843...
Oh. So I went home at 843. I received a text from our roommate Neil Linsky. He
said, "Anyone home?" I said, "I am home." Patrick said, "I am at the office." And that
was at 845. So there's no way I could have done it. And I'm too slow. I can't
pick things up. I would like to... Next question please. You've given us...
You get off of work around 6, right? 7. I got off work at 7 and I arrived
home at 7.45. Alex, I have seen you leave work a lot. Let the record show I
recently got in trouble at work because I don't stay late enough. So now I have
to stay an extra 30 minutes. The record will show that. Thank you. So I stayed
late at work. So yes you may have seen me leaving work earlier but I
don't leave them see okay all I'm trying to say in this analysis of Alex is that
if you put schedules enough schedules together enough anyone could have come
into this office kidnap jungle school including Patrick including Patrick what
yes I'm saying anyone hypothetically could have come in with the same amount
of evidence that we are throwing towards Patrick I would like to I think you're
right Joe I think you're right anybody hypothetically could do this but it is a
matter of motive what did what have we illustrated what is Patrick illustrated
about himself time after time when I got my dog okay mm-hmm what did he say he
said he's getting more attention than me he said he was jealous mm-hmm jealous
jealous my dog was getting more attention than him that the dog is now the
recipient of belly rubs and tummy scratches from me from me and cam from me
was what he was complaining about he doesn't care about your belly well
that's that you know that hurts my feelings but it's okay but what and what
did he say what what what refrain did he echo once more when we got going to
kidnap and molest your dog.
(laughter)
If my memory serves me correctly, I think...
The judge was joking on that one.
That was a joke.
Strike that from the record.
I'd like to ask the judge to not make jokes.
Well, it seems you don't really have the authority to ask the judge to do anything.
I have the authority to ask.
I asked the defense to go outside.
(laughter)
The door locks. I can't do that.
Oh, listen.
Perjury.
And I would like to say that he said almost the exact same thing
when we got Jungelskoog, that he was jealous that Jungelskoog was getting the attention.
If you remember correctly...
The judge remembers that correctly.
And if you remember correctly, judge, the first time that he saw Jungelskoog,
he grabbed him and would not let him go as you and me chased him around the office.
I believe that we have audio evidence of that occurring.
Yes, we do. It's on an episode.
We tried to free him from Patrick's...
But that is on the premium feed.
Patrick's touchy-feely clutches and he was running around the office with
Jungleskoog. Okay, so we've established that you have a you have a pattern, a
history of Jungleskoog abuse. If we're talking about if we're talking about a
period of or a pattern of Jungleskoog abuse I would like to highlight
immediately bringing Jungleskoog back from IKEA, our beautiful Judge Cameron
proceeded to put him in every doorway and shut repeatedly we put him in a closet
he liked it we put him in multiple closets shutting the door we put him in
drawers oh did I hear the word we here interesting party to this but Cameron
so you did this also refused to let me hold jungle school that's not true you
hold you several times you seem I have also also I hung him up on the lights
first with you instructing me how to do so if you remember correctly and it was
after that I hung him up on the lights that you took him and you it seems like
I was why I was here has participated in jungle skook abuse no what I was doing
was not abuse I was propping him up in doorways very cutely and what Joe was
doing was rubbing him in the corners of the ceiling and getting spider webs and
bugs all over him objective I did not rub him I tried to hang him because he
has a velcro feet and you try to hang him interesting no no okay
thereby murdering him I would like to call to the stand the prosecution Joe
Gleason objection you can't object you know come on come to the I just have a
couple of questions ask okay call him to the stand and then give him jungle skoog
and then see what his eyes look like okay all right well thank you for thank you
for giving it up out loud so that he knows exactly what to not do that is
great Joe Gleason we hold on to him for a second so I just like to see okay Patrick
immediately violently reached for him so you look very at home with the uncle
scoog in your hands I love jungle school of course who doesn't can you tell me so
when I came in today I young go scoog was recovered right he had already been
unrecovered and we we I basically took the ransom note and I rearranged the
letters to be a little bit sweeter so tell me what could you read this for me
yes it says jungle skug is fine winky face tongue-out face tunes are good he
do want to be found so he do want to be found I think we think we all agree
that's a very sweet kind of nice message that I left right you do want to tell me
This is kind of what I want to focus on here. These two, you mentioned them, the
the emojis, okay? So these were at one point a double sad face emoji in the
original Ransom Note. I believe a double crying face. Okay, so you know the
specifics. Would you consider yourself an emoji user? I'd say I use my fair share
of emojis. Gotcha, because I would like to bring to the attention of the court, back
to the group chat okay in the first two messages that Joe Gleason says in
response to the photo okay the photo is it the photo is sent by Patrick right of
the note Cameron says you will never get away with this
Patrick says I'm being framed I'm serious Joe Gleason says WTF sad eyes
emoji and let me tell you what it gets even worse for one Joe Gleason Cameron
no but I just I just I'd like to pique the interest of the court on this on this
one possible suspect not even a suspect yeah I just want to I kind of just want
to bring this up Cameron says why are you in the office then Patrick says I'm
working on my PowerPoint for my show on the I'm gonna show you know plug
sustains no plugs Patrick no plugs mr. Doran Pam Cameron says you have the
motive means and no alibi and here comes Joe poor young sad face emoji - sad
face emoji emojis - two messages I dented you you you often find yourself
using emojis how about so often that in the two messages after we get the first
piece of evidence both of them contain emojis almost as if you're seeding as if
you're leaving a breadcrumb trail directly to yourself
Joe I would like to know what you were up to yesterday so my friend was in town
at my house at my new apartment okay in the morning I friend or accomplice friend
friend does not know of Jungle Skoog.
I would like to say that earlier when we were discussing going into this court case.
Hold on, hold on.
Let him finish this.
Okay, okay, sorry.
I drove my friend to his home in upstate New York, going out of my way.
What time?
Let me see.
I have a, I think middle of the day, about three.
Two to three.
And three around the time where I was in Midtown.
And would your friend corroborate this?
Yeah, I have a...
Would you mind giving him a phone call?
I have a...
You know, he works.
But I do have a receipt for a gas station.
He works in upstate New York?
Yeah, he lives there.
I have a receipt of $35.93 at the Millwood Market gas station, the Exxon.
Wait, is that right?
These gas prices are crazy.
$35 to fill up a...
probably buying black trash bags and gloves and then I was driving back here
to New York to go back to my house and when you say here you mean the office
well so I was driving I I had to head to poop and my house is about ten minutes
from here. So I decided to stop through here.
What? I decided to poop here because there's the squatty potty and... At what time?
At what time were you here using the squatty potty? I texted Kara.
you're burying yourself right now. I texted Kara and said I just went to the
office to take a poop. Gonna drive back home in a few minutes. What time? I don't know.
At 530. At 530 when I was on I there's there is photographic evidence I can
prove this I was with my friend Blaine. So at 530 there was what was you what was
young school doing at this time while you're proving he was here we played
you play
at five oh six i have a way with his permission yes jungles jungles good and i
i would say have the strongest relationship
in the office i think i was going to die let's ask you know
yet
dot but the culture of the school to the stand
he's nodding
(laughter)
leading the witness
Joe is nodding his head
he's playing with his head
he's puppeteering him
(laughter)
Jungle Skook just shook his head
so I guess Joe has nothing to do with
ok so let's ask Jungle Skook some yes or no questions
ok
Jungle Skook
Jungle Skook are you
who's your
the question I can ask him one time I'm also a lawyer he know you hold the
phone up to him jungle skunk yeah am I your best friend am I your best friend
in the office he's shaking his head he's nodding his head I'd like to I'd like to
shaking his head no let the record show he's not in his he's not you can't
affect the record I'm the judge and I'm the only one who can change the record I
would like to say he is nodding his head okay but you know we don't know how
truthful he's being he's right now okay wait he's rubbing jungle skunk is
rubbing his armpits and his privates well he's a monkey that's the kind of thing
that they do that's perfectly normal like behavior play games like so you say
so jungle skunk did Joe in fact come to the office yesterday yes and were you
playing yes and at any point did you feel in danger when Joe was in the office and
that's a no are you sure yes yes that's a yes so that's what the game they played
was what with he can't speak can't speak okay he's he's they played way they
played the waving game hi hi Joe hi Joe hi yeah we kind of played wave we played
some hide-and-seek we played some running around did you just say that you played
hide-and-seek yeah I'd like to call another surprise witness to the stand
okay ladies and gentlemen of the court please welcome crazy frog who was here
and saw everything okay okay Patrick you you speak crazy frog yes yes okay and
would you mind being his translator here in the court okay crazy frog how are you
today and what does that mean that means I'm doing very well actually I just I
I just bought a new home.
- Oh, that's great.
- Congratulations, Crazy Frog.
- Where were you on Sunday, March the 13th?
(laughing)
- Jungle Scoog!
- Jungle Scoog, no!
- Stop, Baylet.
- Jungle Scoog, stop it!
- Baylet, get him.
- Stop!
- Keep these two away from each other.
(laughing)
- Jungle Scoog, let the record show,
Jungle Scoog just tried to kill.
- It's just an attack.
(laughing)
joe is grabbed trying to grab the on the school trying to see a little bit of a
right out of my arms is is clear i let the record show i i separated crazy
frog in the most critical you're going to do it
you know
it's always joe do you just leave it like that don't wait like that
no that's that's not the list i i i think i was just trying to point a crazy
for always pointing always he can't move it is a great thing i have a dozen of
articulated fingers no no joke and I physically cannot you say you're in the
penalty box it's crazy frog is he ready to talk you said yes crazy frog were you
at the office on Sunday March 13th that also means yes okay yeah it's like you
know if many crazy frog has many different words for yes okay
Yunglescoot took the gavel and he's bashed Crazy Frog in the head.
He's bleeding all over the place.
Bling!
What does that mean?
We have to operate on Crazy Frog.
We have to operate on him.
Oh my god.
He said, he said, well he said, "Thank god I'm wearing this helmet."
Why would Yunglescoot do this?
He's shrugging.
Younglskug, you, you, oh no! He can't even stay, stay up, he's dead.
Crazy Frog, is he? He's alive. Okay, he looks dead. He's, he's, okay. Yeah.
Alright, Younglskug, stop, Younglskug, stop. I, you are being restrained. He's trying to
grab the hammer again. Okay, Younglskug, you're gonna have another trial later, I think,
because you just did a way worse crime.
okay so crazy frog I just have one question for you okay who did you see
kidnap you uncle skook yesterday afternoon Bing and Patrick what does
that say that says he says I don't know I looked it up I thought that being means
me what I just looked at well yeah I've just studied a lot of linguistics I'm a
linguist ologist wait crazy frog crazy for you saying this to cover things up
so you can still hang out at the office why would we you're gonna get crazy frog
I want you to know we're going to sentence you to death if you are the one
who kidnapped you uncle skook and what does that mean Patrick that's another I
don't know ladies and gentlemen I my hands are tied I think that at this
point I think that all we can do is closing statements some deliberation and
than the verdict I think that's basically all we do. That will take up about nine minutes.
We also didn't get, hold on, Joe clearly was here playing hide and seek with Jungle Scoog.
And tell me, do you remember, give him the microphone, give him the microphone. Joe,
do you remember where the last hiding place that you and Uncle Scoog had was?
i do remember i would also first before i answer the old no okay no no no let me
answer the question before i answer no as a judge you can't you're a witness
right now before i answer the question i would like the record to show
that patrick offered me the herman miller chair if i can prove beyond a
reasonable doubt that he did not do the crime of putting jungle yet you pay you
pay your lawyer that's normal
but if you're his lawyer right
i saw that the thing you can't you can't get bribed your low he's he pays you to
to help prove the case. That's my payment for proving him, his innocence.
Yeah, so answer the question. I came here, the little board said, "Mmm poop"
I believe. "Mmm poop" Wait, actually it did not. It said, at the
time it said, "Mmm ooo pee pee." "Mmm ooo pee pee" which was a variant of
"Mmm poop" before. Yeah, okay.
I saw that the boards were still in, the boards with all the little letters were still there.
I had to take a poop as I previously stated.
I like to play around with jungle skunk.
I think he has a funny face.
It's a very funny object.
Yes, it's a very funny.
It really looks good no matter what he always looks like he's giving whatever emotion you
need him to be giving.
He's happy.
He's scared.
He's sad.
He's excited.
He looks he looks rageful right now.
He looks murderous.
I came to the office.
I'm
Alright, so what's your point here?
Give us, put us through this whole rigmarole, Joe.
Just spit it out.
What is your point?
- I did it.
(gasps)
I was playing with Jungle Skoog.
- Did you do this for the Herman Miller?
- Yeah.
Well, you know, you didn't--
- I mean, I did it now,
I defended you for the Herman Miller.
- I need a microphone.
- Cameron's been talking.
I'm holding a microphone.
- No, no, no, earlier, when you didn't have one,
you were saying stuff.
- Yeah.
can you hear me screaming probably faintly yeah it's like court flavor.
You know if you yell stuff yeah, it's like sounds like there's a big court
with people you know that you mean there is a big court with people. Oh
yeah, it sounds like it because it is yeah exactly, but it sounds to me like
now as the judge as a judge, I'm an expert on deals and rules and it sounds
to me like Patrick promised the Herman Miller to Joe. If Joe was able to
successfully defend Patrick and this actually does count as a bribe now and I
would like to make one I would like to ask one question how can we know that
you are not just taking the fall so that you can get the Herman Miller at this
point please speak into the microphone because if you're taking the fall to do
it that I don't think that's successful because then that leaves the case open
ended do you have any hard enough Patrick did not go to IKEA with us Patrick was
here yes waiting for the optimum man Patrick does not know where the little
fits like letters are to put on the jungle school he does not know which
cabinet those are in Patrick also not very good at spelling we can say that
too Patrick does not know the spelling of jungle scog scoog potentially it is a
it is a strange swedish spelling
uh... i don't know that he knows it
uh...
you
don't you're hurt you're hurting your case i think it's also on this also on
the tag it is on the tag
uh...
he did and what was your motive
he didn't do it he says he's taking the floor i thought it would be kind of
funny
i think jungle school looks funny in the little green blankets while like a
little baby
and i kinda wanted some
some fun excitement. I was like whoever's gonna find this is gonna be kind of
funny.
So you did this all just for entertainment value. I did it for fun. I
think jungle school had a good time as we kind of he had a good time jungle
school is a you think you showed jungle school a good you gave him a real good
time. I'm
I'm like a
I'm not an evil person.
It's very kind of Machiavellian of you to do all this just for a chair.
Well that was...
It's like you set up the entire thing.
I did the original thing for fun because I thought it was kind of fun to change the board
and you know have some office drama as we enter this new office phase of our lives.
Which I think is a nice thing.
I think we all appreciate it that we're having fun talking about this fun thing.
Jungle Skooge I would like to point out is a stuffed animal.
does not have a traditional brown you
jack time from the court
okay I love jungle skunk
I love playing games with them I love having fun with them I did not do
anything sinister with him
I'm Patrick I understood Patrick
would likely get you know like
whoever came and found it would probably
blame Patrick because that's I mean I wouldn't personally
But you too, I think, definitely would blame Patrick.
You wouldn't blame Patrick when he tweeted the day before "Jungleskoog will go missing"?
Well, I wouldn't blame Patrick because I did it.
You didn't do it. It was Patrick.
I fully take the blame. I did do it. I did take a poop here.
And I'm sorry for any hardship that it's caused.
Mainly Patrick, who had to go through the brunt of being, you know, guilty before proven innocent or whatever.
I think it was funny. I think it was a fun time and I have the I get the chair and
will you submit to me taking a black light to jungle squeeze body
yeah I yeah I stand by stand by I would never ever ever do anything to physically
harm jungle school and you also stood by well Patrick physically harmed young
school Patrick and I were not here at the same time I cannot speak to any of
those. Patrick could have done something. Patrick probably did it after Joe
faked it. Patrick probably saw that Junglescoog had been missing,
realized he was being framed and decided I might as well attack him and touch him
all over. No. Well I have the chance. That's not what happened. You saw Junglescoog, you
found him and you were so excited you kind of you couldn't control yourself. No.
you saw him restrained by a green blanket no said you're mine out loud I did not
say that and you gnashed your teeth and licked your lips I and you put and you
took you used the green blanket as a green screen on photo booth and put a
roller coaster behind him and scared him I did do that but these other claims
about gnashing my teeth I would like not true I would like to take it whoa he's
He's, oh my god, he's holding Crazy Frog hostage.
He's holding him hostage.
- Yungleskug, no.
- No.
- Why do you hate Crazy Frog?
- Oh my god.
Whoa!
He put him in Phil's crate.
- Oh, now the ravenous monster that lives in that crate
is gonna eat him.
All right, that's fine.
I don't really like Crazy Frog,
but I would like to take this to a vote.
- Yeah, well, it's a jury.
- A jury, a vote, Joe to vote a jury.
- Yeah.
- We're basically in this--
jury yeah us five are the members of the jury okay we'll just start we'll just go
clockwise from the judge here just who's getting the blame it I don't care who
did it anymore yeah okay I would as one last piece of evidence I would like to
say that Joe told me he did it ten minutes before and I heard Joe say that
(laughing)
- I heard Joe say that.
- His entire thing was just for fun.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Caleb said, "Yeah, we got the wifi."
I was like, "Oh yeah, I saw."
And then I realized, "Oh wait, how do I see it?"
- He gave himself up, yeah.
- I pretty quickly gave myself up.
- And then you started laughing really hard.
- Yeah, 'cause I did that.
- And I heard all of this before we started,
and I told you guys I heard it.
And then Joe said, "Why are you so quick to blame me?"
- All right, what's your vote, Caleb?
my vote knowing what I know it's got to be Patrick definitely Alex I think Joe
guilty of hiding jungle suit Patrick Patrick guilty of hating jungle scoot
daddy being jealous - yeah yes all right Patrick your vote I don't I don't
remember after I ate the Burger King I don't remember what happened you blacked
blacked out I blacked out after I ate Burger King I don't know what happened
okay so that's a vote for Patrick. Okay so that's two votes for Patrick. Two for Patrick, one for Joe.
Yep. All right Joe what's your vote? I'm gonna vote for myself I desperately want
this chair and I did do it. Okay so that's two votes for Patrick and two for
for Joe and now I'm the tiebreaker. You're the what one two three four. I
voted for Patrick. I voted for me too.
Alright, you so not only am I the tiebreaker, but my vote actually counts
100 times as much because I'm the judge and you have to come up with the
punishment as well. Yeah,
and I am going to vote
for Patrick because I believe that he did it and Joe is lying to get his
hands on a really nice really low chair. Maybe his punishment is that he has to
give Joe the chair
that is one part with one part of the punishment. I sentence Patrick to
payment of a fine to Joe of one fucked up Herman Miller chair that the it's
broken that one both the chairs to give Joe both your chairs and you have to
sit on the floor and one hundred years in the dog crate. I will not be going in the
dog crate.
Court is now adjourned. Do you guys want to go get pizza? Yeah, let's go get some
lunch. I'd love to. Yeah, we'll get a drink or something. Bye! All right, well,
Patrick, you have to go in the crate. Oh, wait, we have to plug the tour.
Swagpoop.com/shows. A pod about list on Patreon if you want to hear the first
part of this. The first part? The first part of this, where I said that I was
to capture jungle jungle scoop oh yeah true there's basically all we talked
about last episode yeah that's why this was specific this is really bad for him
well you should subscribe to the patreon yeah all right bye everybody I'm good
definitely oh wait also go check out home play oh yeah home planet dot-com
Bye.