Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- All right.
- Let's unlock a premium.
- Yeah, let's just unlock an episode instead of doing this.
- All right, bye.
- Bye bye.
- Bye.
- This has been a little intro to the unlocked episode,
which will start now.
- Now.
- Sorry, I'm new, so.
- Yeah, this is, Caleb's not here today.
Caleb's very, very sick.
He has a new type of COVID where his butt can't breathe
because his underwear is too tight.
- He was in Boston and he ate like the shell of a coin.
- Yeah, like a two week old lobster roll.
- Oh yeah, dude, I love this.
This is so good. - That's your Caleb voice?
- Oh yeah, man, I love eating lobster rolls.
My name is Caleb.
- Yeah, we got patches with us.
That's a really funny...
My name's Caleb.
How y'all doing? It's me, Caleb Pitts.
It's me, Caleb.
I'm Caleb.
It's me, Caleb Pitts.
Now, I just love having diarrhea and not recording.
Oh, it's my favorite.
I love eating doo-doo.
I got diarrhea, you know how?
Eating my own poop.
I'll be pooping from the front and throwing up from the back.
Everything's all backwards where I'm from.
I live in a swimming pool. I live in a swimming pool and I'm not allowed to go in because I have active diarrhea.
My landlord makes me sit outside.
Yeah, my Caleb voice is, it's just if you live below like the 40th latitude to me.
Yeah.
You just immediately...
Of course.
[Caleb makes weird noises]
Does that sound good or bad?
Deep throat voice.
Yeah, you immediately sound like you suck pee pee.
You got a dick in your whatever.
You got a pee pee in your mouth.
Yep.
Pee pee in your mouth.
I was also in Boston over the weekend.
I didn't get to go.
While I was waiting, while me and my girlfriend were waiting for the Amtrak in South Station,
we were sitting down at like a table by the like Obonpan.
And the what?
The Obonpan.
Obonpan.
Are you familiar?
Obonpain?
know you mean a bond payment.
I forgot it's Boston yeah I'll bomb
pain yeah you can't call you can't speak
French sitting next to a like a middle
age couple who's on like a date yeah
like a station that's probably so
there's nothing there yeah dude it's so
so look at they were having a yeah they
were having a conversation this was like
one of the my the best Boston guys ever
yeah so on a date in South Station you
have to imagine it was his idea because the woman seemed pretty normal, but he
was like terminally Boston and it was at one point. They know me at the tavern in
the square. Yeah, exactly. At one point she was like she said something about
like having epilepsy and he was like epilepsy what's that? What's epilepsy?
And she was like well I haven't had a seizure in a long time but epilepsy is
like when you have seizures and he's like oh a seizure so what do you see a
vision of something I see you over there I love you like ask who like talk like
that where where they're like when they ask questions it's always at you yeah
it's like it's like see just what are you doing yeah I don't what did I do I
I don't think you can. Why are you mad at me? I can't control that about myself.
He was so fucking good. Then they were talking about like religion and stuff and of course
you're saying like, "Yeah, I was raised super Catholic. I'm super Catholic."
And then she started like saying something about the Bible. I don't remember how they
got on the topic. She's something about like healing lepers being in the Bible or something,
right? And he's like, "Oh, I don't know about any of that stuff. I just have an adventure book."
That's so fucking sick. Oh my God.
So cool, dude. He also told me that he got into Harvard on a full scholarship for sports.
What?
Yeah. Oh my God.
No.
That's what he said.
Big Papi signed my adventure Bible. You want to take a look at that?
He was so fucking sick, dude.
I also like the idea of you at this, with your girlfriend, just listening to this conversation.
You're back completely away from her and just like, it's like, no, this is sort of
of what I'm doing here right now.
- It was literally so--
- You're like you have a newspaper,
like you're spying on the date.
- It was even more awkward than that
'cause we were sitting, like me and my girlfriend
were sitting across from each other at the table
and then on the chair next to us,
they were sitting across from each other.
- Oh yeah.
- So we were not talking at all
'cause we were both just listening intently
to this conversation going on.
- Of course, of course.
- So we were just looking at each other
and every once in a while just looking at the people
and looking back at each other.
Yeah, and kind of like, yeah,
like peeking out from behind the luggage
be like oh my god. At one point she also started talking, they had a crazy
conversation, it was a crazy date conversation. I wonder if they met at South Station,
I wonder if this is like an internet thing. I couldn't tell if they were like
went there on a date or if they like met and like he started like he crawled out
from underneath South Station. At some point, at one point she also started
talking about Anne Frank's diary and how like it was like edited out that she was
gay or whatever. Oh yeah. And the guy got really quiet. He was just like, "Oh, a lot of things
I want to say about that but I'm not going to say them." He was jumping to interrupt
her to say his thing and now he's just like, "Hmm." Oh, yeah, that's gross. Dude, I wish
that that couple would win. She was like, "Portuguese?" Anything to change the topic.
yeah who's that bless him who's that yeah who's that and she has seizures yeah who
is that who is that who's that maybe that's why I just didn't know who she
was or he like it is like oh and Frick Oh and friend line one of my
delightful I blind one oh the one who picked up the ice the underground
railroad. He's just like sitting here. Did I go to school with her? Do we both know her?
Oh yeah, Anne Frank. Oh, Sister Anne Frank. Sister Anne Frank, yeah. She hit me with a
Arula great ass.
Not no offense.
She's a whack my fucking hands with Arula.
That's so I would we've definitely talked about it
before.
It's so funny that like every fucking townie in Boston has
some story about just like, oh, yeah, the harshest abuse ever
fucking.
Yeah, like ever fucking like done to a child by just some
it's always like it's all they always want to us.
They're always went to a school that's called like, yeah,
like like Our Lady of the Afflicted by the Faith. Yeah. They were like
like they're the nun like sliced them with razor blades or something and
they're like, "Yeah, but it was fine because we pranked her back." Yeah, we put a thumbtack under her chair.
Yeah, we covered the chalk in paint so it didn't show colors on the blackboard.
It's, it's, there, there was like a, I forgot, like a little while ago there was
like this massive article just about like a about like nuns this like one
there's like this massive article they made a movie about it. Huge ass article.
yeah apparently a bunch of Catholic priests yeah doing something weird they
made they made a game about it too I think Jackbox made a game about it. Yeah what was it called?
Spotlight the game.
Spotlight.
But it was a story about these nuns, just like it opens with like, I never finished it, I
was like, "This is too fucking long," but it opens with like, Sister Mary Margaret Mathis,
you know, like tosses the child out of the window and like, it's talking about from the
perspective of somebody else seeing a child fly out of a nunnery or like some fucking
school and then like just seeing like a nun in the window and like a nun not
like just moving out of the way it's just like yeah like a horror movie John
wick is - is - like us as mrs. trunchbull is - a nun that's like that's there like
success when I like a recut yeah where she just like it's like it's like
Pinterest is all just pictures of the choky yeah it's like it's like Matilda
recut but then like the other scenes like anything that happens to like a kid
is like some scene from like funny games or something yeah it's just like yeah
yeah get him again tie him again I'm again yeah feed him the cake yeah it's
crazy they made that kid eat so much food yeah damn that honestly they should
have done that to Bruce yeah that was fucked up what they did to him that cake
looks so fucking good though I really did oh my god I think I think about that
cake every time that I like that's probably the best of cake has ever
looked yeah movie that's but that's I hate cake that's the best of cake has
ever looked. Every time I see a cake I want to eat that cake. I have to imagine
I'm eating that cake to eat the cake. You walk into a bakery and just have like an
episode. That's a beautiful metaphor for porn addiction.
Yeah every time I have sex I just hope it's that cake. I was hoping it was Miss Trunchful.
know that cake is a lie? Wait is it actually? Did you know that that cake is a lie? I never
played Portal which is a huge blind spot for me. I heard they actually killed all the kids
on Matilda's set. They did. The real daddy kid that died on Matilda's set. I heard they
actually threw that kid out the window by her pigtails. No shit. Yeah. I heard it was
actually a really fucked up set. You know that's because the kids don't have unions.
They don't have kid unions. It's a problem. Man hold on going back that cake in Portal
also looked at the table to look at it
as the best the case is that we're going to rank we're talking about case
right now what other case are there are many wedding cakes are really good the
wedding cake with a little bit i think i would in case i i think i was always
looked at what i think i was a little bit of a
the
your and i don't like the post-it notes
i hate the whole thing
well i got his wife and i hope you get it
is walking you walking into McDonald's and looking up the menu and starting to
cry because you think you have to eat everything
looking at the McDonald's menu and being like a twelve course meal.
This is all this is all prefix right, yeah,
gonna be like okay yeah all right here's my money okay okay yeah just go to it
how much does it cost to buy the whole McDonald's menu hmm I'm sure that I could
find that on Google right yeah that's so well I mean I'm sure it's like more we
can find we could we can stop the episode and then do the man do that do
that and then come back and try to record after doing that yeah we eat the
whole McDonald's menu we bring the whole McDonald's challenge yeah yeah I feel
like I feel like if I was ever I feel like I would fast for a week to do that
to eat the whole McDonald well no because if you fast for a week your stomach is
gonna get smaller okay so in in May 2017 the answer was a hundred and ninety four
dollars and ninety cents that's fucking Biden's inflation yeah go on how much is
is it now? I don't know. That's just the most that's way less
than I thought it would be $194.
Buying the whole McDonald's menu would cost like $2,000.
I don't know.
We're forgetting.
Yeah, that's a small medium and large.
You get every size of everything.
We're also forgetting the Golden McNuggets.
Those are really expensive.
go to the McDonald's and say, I want the golden McNuggets. And
then the guy has to like go to the back and talk to the
manager. Then the manager has to like go to the vault and
unlock. Yeah, yeah. Well, I heard you can only get those in
Dubai. Yeah, it's true. That's one of those international.
Yeah, that's what I mean. There's a lot of articles where
Steve Harvey is just like when I go to Dubai, I'm always eating
the golden McNugget.
Just be like that's maybe you see that might be Steve Harvitt's
favorite Dubai meal may shock you. That's one of the funniest foods to be like to
have gold in it I think. Yeah. It's like yeah like have like a really rich person
gold like a little yeah big nugget. Yeah. It's like a golden nugget. Like the salt
bae. Yeah they're always getting like tomahawk steaks and like create like
luxurious stuff. I would love to be a salt bae guy but for McDonald's. Yeah. Like
like cooking McDonald's. You see me in the back and I'm doing some great shit. You're like
Squeeze it you you're holding like the sweet and sour package. Yeah
You're so you're so like sweaty and gross from working in the kitchen you can see the sauce is a different color when it leaves your
It just smells by that area I keep doing that keep squeezing the shit I like
The idea of like of like like gently putting salt on and you're like you're wearing a long-sleeve shirt
You do it and it runs down the sleeve and then like filters
Assistance assistance
We drain it out of there put it on the prize. Oh my god. We would kill opening a salt-based style restaurant
Like doing like opening like a
Chick-fil-a or something I feel like I feel like really easy to make a shit ton of money opening chick-fil-a
Chick-fil-a will know chick-fil-a is cheap to open, but then they take a bunch of your
Write like 10 essays yeah, but I think it's only like how much you'd love a thousand bucks. Yeah, okay?
Yeah, yeah, it'll write like all this stuff like oh
I just writing like your whole chick-fil-a essay like yeah, I would bend down and I would suck
Yeah, I would let Christ fuck fuck me. I would let Christ pipe me down
I would let Christ bust it. Why I would let I would let Christ squirt his hot nut into my
One chick-fil-a, I would let him breathe right into my prostate
Shit I would let Christ use his magic ET finger
Making me nut 1000 nuts. Oh my god leaders of not Christ turn my come in the wine
Oh my god, I would be I would be fucking his renaissance. Halo - yeah, I'm a woman by the way. This is not gay
I'm a woman in this scenario. Not I'm not not trans. I'm not I'm just an actual is a woman
I'm not trans. I'm a woman in this scenario
Yeah, I I think I'm not gay either. Yeah, this is the most this is the most
heterosexual Christ sexual
I'm writing like a letter to Chick-fil-a and just title it titling it if I were a woman
Yeah
Fine let me and let me tell you chick-fil-a. I would be letting the Lord give me a different type of my pleasure. Mm-hmm
No, I know that this is a scenario where I was a sighted female at birth
which that means and they just
explain everything and realizing you're writing to Chick-fil-a and being like,
but I don't agree with any of that. Yeah, but that stuff not for me.
I made that up. The footnotes are going to cover this. Yeah,
yeah. You'll see. All the footnotes are like, but straight up, I think this is bad.
I mean, footnotes that are like, I will let Christ fill me with his nut and then like a
little one and you like flip to the end of it and it says like, the nut will be hot.
I would let Jesus Christ go fucking buck wild on my ass and it's like, "My ass will be good.
My ass will be hot.
It will be sexy."
My ass is a woman's ass and my name is Jeanette.
Yeah, my name is Jeanette.
Yeah, like a footnote after that being like, "Jeanette is 5'4", 36, 24, 36, blonde, beautiful."
Yeah.
This is all written from the perspective of Jeanette. Yeah, yeah, oh man. Yeah, I'd
love to write a Joycean essay. Tight hold the exact size of Jesus's cock. Here's a
picture. It fits like a sweater on a snake. That would be so funny if like, oh man,
and just like having a,
well have you seen those Chick-fil-A commercials now
where they have like the,
like it's like how great their service is?
- I've never seen a commercial.
- I think I've seen one.
I think I saw one Chick-fil-A commercial recently
but it was in Spanish.
It came on Hulu.
- Yeah, I haven't like seen commercials in a while.
- Yeah, I saw, I think I saw them on Hulu.
- You gotta tap into Hulu.
- Should I check this shit out?
- Hulu, that shit will blow your mind.
- Yeah.
- Well, Hulu, I didn't used to have Hulu with ads
but then they made it more expensive
So now you always have ads.
Yeah.
But what's the Chick-fil-A commercial?
There's like these Chick-fil-A commercials
where they're like, all they talk about
is just how great their service is.
So it's just like this one.
Oh, you know what it was?
It was like a commercial where it's like
a woman who had recorded this like employee
and it was like the singing Chick-fil-A employee
or some shit.
And it's like, I think, honestly,
I think it was just a show that Chick-fil-A hires gay people.
- Right, yeah.
- It was like, it's just like a crazy PR move for them.
- That's funny they have like a
don't ask, don't tell thing with that too.
They're never gonna say it, but it's like, look.
- We know, we know Travis is our fabulous employee.
- Yeah, right, yeah.
Yeah, we know he's wonderful, we know he's on fleek.
(laughing)
Like can you guys cut us a fucking--
- A message from the CEO.
Look at this thing we brought in.
Can you give us a break?
And because we love him so much,
we are letting him wear this beautiful
fabulous badge all the time
whenever he works at our store.
The most fabulous
employee at Chick-fil-A.
We are giving him the privilege
of being constantly
identified. Just like
the idea of Chick-fil-A.
Just the idea of Chick-fil-A.
Just like being like, okay, we'll let
this person good we're just gonna okay yeah this is a pink triangle bed people
who are serving we have another thing for that yeah we are so excited to debut
our fleek badge program. When you work at Cracker Barrel you get a you get you like
stars. Do they do that? Yeah I was only a one star I didn't work there too long but
there's like you know you get like you get stars like you're a general. Yeah
yeah that thing that's like such an ingenious way to break people's morale
down. Oh no no the Cracker Barrel kitchen is the saddest place in the world. Yeah no it's
but you see that when you see that like at grocery stores too where you'll see
like an old person walking around with like a 12 year like it says their name
and then 12 years basket yeah it's so it's so nasty it's oh yeah it's so
ingenious well yeah cuz yeah it does this like it does this because because
there's the way that people people for not great reasons think of you as scum
if you work there yeah and then then it's like you should be proud of how
long you've worked at this place. It's such a smart move.
It's genius. I'm going to do that. We should do that. Yeah. I'm going to do that for my
neighbors. You flip next door to me. You could do that to me and Jubio for how long we've
been working with you guys. It's true.
You have one more star than Jubio. I know. I order over him every day.
You just say, "Oh yeah, they're paying for my vacation."
(laughing)
- And then once both of you guys level up,
we'll need to hire a third person.
- Absolutely.
- I can't remember what the fucking,
the stars meant at Cracker Barrel though.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause it was like--
- You had one star, did that just--
- That's 'cause I just started working there.
Actually, I never got my star,
'cause you're supposed to get an apron that has the star.
- You were zero stars.
- I think I quit before that happened.
- You were zero stars, wow.
- Dude, I was a dishwasher too,
they were putting me on,
I had to do lunch rushes and shit,
Like there was one time I came in and there was like six bus tubs
lining on like lined up on the floor and someone's like, Oh,
thank God you're here. Yeah. Oh, cool. I'm going to quit.
If you ask me, nobody working at Cracker Barrel should have any stars.
It should be everyone's zero.
Every time you put the fight that broke out in the kitchen. I don't know.
Yeah. There's like a fat bald guy fought a guy.
Well what that's come on.
- You copped out so hard there.
- I copped out hard 'cause then I realized
that the story wasn't that interesting.
- That sounds cool.
- What was the fight about?
- The fight happened during the breakfast rush.
- Okay, so we had a fist fight.
- Yeah, it was a fist fight during the breakfast rush.
- What was it over?
Was it over a girl?
- I don't remember, I just saw one guy,
the shortest guy in the kitchen,
fighting the biggest guy in the kitchen,
who was bald and had little black holes for teeth.
- So they were trying to reenact the biblical myth.
- Yeah.
and he screamed like you do again you fatball fuck I'll fucking kill you and I
think I was imagining I'm imagining the little guy just running back and forth
like the giant boss fight in Resident Evil 4 running through his legs and
trying to stun him he can climb up his body yeah yeah yeah the problem was that
that the big guy found his weak spot.
So he was trying to find his,
he was like, I'm gonna find your weak spot now.
- Yeah, his prostate, they were doing crazy things.
- Yo, that's a perfect spot to hit during a fight.
If you can get your fist up your opponent's butt
and hit him right in the prostate.
- Will not shrink. - Glowing red.
Glowing red boss weak spot.
- Once you're above a certain height and a certain weight,
you get a glowing red thing on your back
that's your weak spot.
Like that's how we evolve.
It's like, okay, you're too big,
need to have a weak spot. So that's what happens. So that big guy probably had one.
My only other co-worker there, that day at least, was a 65-year-old man named Buster.
Whoa.
There was four people working at Cracker Barrel that day?
Yeah.
Like, oh, it was just me and him at a working dish.
Okay. You were just like, yeah, there was four of us. Nobody was serving.
No, you know what I mean.
The only other person in the dish pit.
Alright, cool.
I think I've talked about Buster on here before.
First day I was working there
it was my birthday.
My 19th birthday.
No. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It doesn't matter. It was my birthday.
He was teaching me how to take the
trash out.
Oh, did you have trouble with that beforehand?
Before Buster showed you how to do it?
Yeah.
ever done it before.
Yeah, right.
It was his first time.
Well, no, he was telling me how to like, because there's like some system where you like, he's
like, "You gotta tie the bags like this."
And he's putting the bag, like he empties one out and then he's like putting another
one in and he's like, "See, you put it on like this.
Kind of like putting on a rubber.
Hey, this trash can's almost as big as me.
I wish I was that big."
You're just not responding, yeah.
I actually don't wish I was that big. He like fucking went through the thought
process of like, "Oh what if I had a penis that was the size of like a trash barrel
that is meant to hold like probably a ton of grits?"
Like an actual ton of grits. How is putting a trash bag on anything...
You put it in.
I was he may well, what if like he's the only like guy in the
world that use dental dams?
The guy's name was Buster. Yeah, like he had some money, rolled
his own cigarettes and kept them in an old Winston box. And I
don't know how long he had that Winston box, though. Oh, yeah,
that's true. I guess that is pretty crazy. Yeah. But it's
still cool, though. Yeah, it's cool to be that dirty. I hope.
yeah yeah I when I'm old dirty old guys kick ass oh they so I hope I just get you
close to you I smell weird yeah yeah sound memes are amazing if you're a
dirty old guy I want to sound like a lawnmower when I'm I've had 65 I've had
that like the type of when I worked at the liquor store I see you would see a
bunch of the type of old guy who would hand me like money that was literally
covered like in dirt.
(laughing)
As if he was like storing it like underground
before he walked into the store.
- Yeah, it's so cool.
- It's so sick.
- Yeah, there's just like a, there's like some step,
there's like, I guess what it is is that we haven't
figured out that guys when they're older than 35
or something, you just start to produce dirt
and grime and like--
- You do.
- Like it's a like pig--
- You don't have that step in your like hygiene,
it's just gonna grow.
Yeah, I have no choice. There's something it's either that or you do something like you have some crazy private secret
If you're like a well manicured man in his 40s, oh, yeah
Killed a guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like it's like why isn't your dirt sack working? What did you do your dirt go? Yeah
Where's your dirt?
Like the cleanest man
Yeah, no just someone unlike like someone walking out of like sacks fit that yeah
It's like being like give me show me your dirt show me your dirt show me your dirt
I know where your dirt is let me see your dirt
Come on. See you dirt cuz I know come here come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Yeah
Amen, yeah, and he opens his mouth. It's all in his mouth. Oh
My apologies no worries enjoy your time at sacks
- Max Fifth Ave.
(laughing)
I'll be here all night.
- You know what it is?
It's also, I think, the amount of dirt you have
is the amount, like the amount of dirt you produce as a man
is also, it's like correlated with the,
what's the word I'm looking for?
Like your willingness to wear
your favorite sports team's pajamas out to get coffee.
I'm looking for exactly what word you what quality you mean yes yeah yeah that's a
hundred percent it though yeah that's another that's another sick Boston thing
that's all yeah favorite bus and I did the Duncan the Duncan ruins pajama
pajamas pajama yeah so they sick dude sweatshirt no no no the Celtics like
slippers or something yeah actually no Celtics no yeah no Celtics gear at all
but like Patriot sweatshirt, Red Sox hat.
- Pat's sweatshirt for sure.
Yeah, the Bruins pajama pants are my favorite though.
Those are the best. - Adidas Kobe 2 samples.
- I might get myself a pair of Bruins pajama pants.
I love seeing those around.
- Oh dude. - They're so sick.
- Yeah, the Bruins have the best logo for pajama pants.
- Oh, absolutely.
Best logo in colors.
- I'm outing myself as a fucking scrub.
What's a Bruins logo?
- The Bruins logo, it's either a bear
or a bee that has black and gold.
- Oh, that's cool. - Black, white, and gold.
- It's either a bear or a bee.
- Yeah.
- It's usually a bee, the ones that I'm thinking of.
- That's interesting, so they're just kind of like
any bee animal will do.
- No, a bee, like the letter.
- Oh, I'm...
(laughing)
- You thought it was a fucking bee?
- I don't know.
- I have to find the specific pants.
- Those are the ones, right there.
- With the fucking...
the ones that those dreadful all of those are actually never mind
but these are these are the idea of these ones that are there were a little go and
i think it's really important to have a room for the bumblebee
there's a lot of my mind there's no bumblebee on the brew is that is not a
man
this isn't that the perfect logo for any of the other hand yes he has a brutal
though the bruins logos all so sick it's just a
fucking uh... it's so sick because i have to go more
Oh yeah, I never even thought about that.
Oh dude, look at this family.
This is going up with the episode.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh man.
That's going to be my family.
We gotta get-
When I grow up?
We gotta get Bruins pajama pants.
It's like of course they have four kids.
Like they can't fucking help themselves.
I know.
Literally my family.
Yeah.
100%.
That looks like my family.
Yeah, it's like there's a latent gene in the Irish.
It's like there's still a famine.
Like we have to.
We have to produce as many fucking kids as we can.
It's not even like a Catholic thing anymore.
It's just like something stuck.
We think this works.
Just in case a comedy writer eats two of your kids.
[Laughter]
Yeah, this is a new problem.
Irish Catholics keep producing kids because all the Harvard people are going out at night and stealing their kids.
It's those two groups both have ancestral genetic memory of a modest proposal.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
And they just...
The incestual...
The Harvard kids can't stop doing satire of eating babies and placenta and doing...
And doing those things, actually.
Doing blood rituals.
Doing those, yeah, whatever that stuff is.
And the Irish people just love popping them out and fucking.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
I don't even like anything.
And not being able to eat.
Yeah.
And dying.
And smelling like shit.
And living in Shrek's house.
And fucking Shrek.
Yeah, in the mud bath. Yeah, and there's bubbles whenever they thrust. Yeah
There's a footnote and it says yeah, and the bubbles they're stinky
Those are stinky bubbles
man, okay, I would love to yeah, you're like I I thought that I guess a kid I
Thought that farting in the bathtub. I think it was just we do that every time. Yeah. Yeah, it's done it before
I've seen that happen.
- Has it really, like, but like legit,
like, you know what I mean?
Like real--
- I saw a bubble come up to the surface and pop.
- That's awesome, man.
Did it smell?
Did you like smell it?
- It was the worst smelling fart I've ever had.
So I thought that if you fart in the bathtub,
it makes it smell more.
- I know why you thought that.
I can't get mad at you.
- Yeah, no, I--
- 'Cause you're like, oh dude,
it's gonna travel through the water and then blow up.
Like, you just had, yeah, it's like, no,
all that just gets absorbed.
Yeah.
the stink the stink air comes like combines with the filth of your day.
Yeah and then it goes up.
It's carrying your dirt.
You know what I thought about being like a scientist?
Yes.
You know what's so funny?
The stink air, my hypothesis is that the stink air combines with the filth of the day.
When I was like ten years old, I thought I could be a doctor when I was older.
I was like, I'm going to like, you know, I'm going to dick around as like a kid.
And then one day, I'll just sort of sort this shit out.
Yeah.
My, my sixth grade teacher, we had to do a, uh, he was like my sixth grade social
studies teacher made us do the vision boards.
Oh, miss do vision boards.
And on my vision board, it said, I'm going to be a doctor.
That's so admirable.
I feel like every kid that wants to be like an astronaut or like a doctor or an inventor
or something is like, "Well, I better get going now.
I better make an invention.
I better start practicing going to space because I'm going to do that."
But yeah, you just want to be a doctor.
You're like, "Yeah, I'll do that later."
That's fine.
That seems like a thing that happens with time.
That's how you become a dentist is just like, "Yeah, I don't know.
I could be a doctor."
Which is what you are now.
Yeah.
A dentist is a doctor with no will.
It is a doctor who just like was too fucking who's boring want to party
more yeah,
you don't want to party with a dentist. You're a dentist in that they bring
you into dental school to punish the
like this guy's getting too cocky. You're like the choky of the dental
world. They have to operate on my shitty ass fucking yeah, British teeth,
British teeth quarter British I'm not I'm not claiming that mm-hmm okay we got a
list today this is sent in by our boy Charlie by Charlie thank you Charlie
most controversial go listen to that I've been on it I've been on it twice
Cameron this is I went on it one time Cameron went on at one time I went on it
twice I don't know maybe it's cuz like I'm a better guest yeah or maybe because
I'm just like a 10 times the guest that Cameron is.
Maybe because you're so stupid it takes you two episodes to say what I could say in one.
You had to stop in the middle.
25 things parents should never say to their kids.
This is from bestlifeonline.com.
Think twice before saying things to your kids that you'll wind up regretting.
I don't subscribe to that.
I think that you should say whatever to your kid whenever.
- Oh my god, I was having a real conversation
about this the other day.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, that like that--
- Number one is, hold on, you keep going.
(laughing)
Sorry, sorry, no, I'm just--
- No, you couldn't, what it was,
this camera was in front of me,
so you're like, Patches isn't here.
- Yeah, no, I have no object for him.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah, that's my bad.
- Oh no, it's very--
- I genuinely like--
I thought the Bruins had two animals as their logo.
(laughing)
I can't come back from that.
- I genuinely did not mean to interrupt you there,
sorry man. - Oh, that's fine.
No, I was talking about how just like,
I was like, how do you, 'cause you see,
it's like you don't wanna be a shitty parent,
but you're like, man, kids are sometimes just fucking,
genuinely unreasonable.
Like what am I supposed to do except be like, fuck you.
(laughing)
Like either like--
Sometimes they kill yourself. They just want some
You know like a parrot I don't like that color shirt yeah fucking kill yourself
Our parents are not supposed to say that
Number one like I got told this all the time as a kid. Yeah, well it was
It's fair for you.
I want to read the opening paragraph.
That is true.
No, the opening paragraph is boring.
Is it boring?
You don't know what you're talking about.
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
Let's do this.
Number one.
This is number one.
You're so dramatic.
Yeah, I got told that a lot, but I would freak out over tiny things.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I still do.
Yeah, you definitely do.
I do too, and I was definitely told many times, "You're being dramatic."
Yeah.
If we go to like a bar or something and I think that the vibe is corny, I'm like, I'm not
going there ever again.
I will never step foot in there ever again.
That's the last you'll see of me.
The last you'll see of me, McFerrin's.
I didn't like that like Modellos were $2 more than like a different place.
I'm like, well, see you never.
a nice life! I must be gone now, ta-ta! And I won't tip! And then you just spit in their
face. Yeah. Yeah. Now I feel like, I feel like with when, when you tell a kid you're
being dramatic, you're just making sure they understand that like, you know, there's times
to be dramatic, there's times to be comedic. Yeah, no, you should absolutely tell your
kid when they're being dramatic, like when they're telling you way too enthusiastically
about their favorite Pokemon.
- Yeah.
- Like shut up, you're so dramatic.
- You're so dramatic.
- Just say you like it.
- Yeah, why are you like--
- I don't care.
- Yeah, I don't care, like I don't--
- It's a kid's show, I don't care, I'm a grown up.
- Why would I be interested in that?
- Yeah, I don't even know what that is.
- Yeah.
- Is that a Pokeman?
Did you guys get that growing up?
- Pokemans, yeah.
- Oh man.
- Yeah.
- I never, I don't think I ever got like,
'cause I was thinking about like the shit
like when you're a kid where you're just like,
that's not how you say that!
I don't think I ever did that with Pokemans, but I definitely did that with
like, like I feel like, I feel like my parents would like if I was playing like
this is so bad, playing like a like a Final Fantasy game. Yeah, like they'd be
like, what is that? What does that say? Like Sephiroth? And I'm like, that's
Sephiroth! I definitely did that to adults a time with like Godzilla type
stuff. Oh yeah, yeah. I'd be like, no, it's Badara and it's the evil Mothra. Yeah,
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's, yeah.
(imitates gun)
(laughter)
- I did, like, the complete opposite, I think.
I was watching Revenge of the--
- You're the parent.
- Yeah, I'm my dad's dad.
- You're the kid.
- No, I was like, I guess it's not the complete opposite.
But like, I did something, like,
I was watching Revenge of the Sith with my dad,
and I had the visual dictionary,
and I was telling him what the names of--
- What's the visual dictionary?
I'm sorry, you don't know the visual dictionary?
Damn, all the--
- Oh, you missed out then.
- All the-- - This is like a
New England thing. - The kids whose houses
you hated going to had those.
- Yeah, really? - Star Wars visual dictionary.
- That was not the only thing you could do
at their house. - Yeah.
- What is the visual dictionary?
- It's so cool. - It just has like
the names of blasters and shit.
- It's a bunch of pictures of all the Star Wars stuff
and it has like just, it's like an encyclopedia.
- Yeah. - Oh.
- But it's like all the pictures and stuff.
- Made by the DK, whatever the fucking--
- It's so cool, dude.
- Oh, that sounds sick.
- Oh yeah, they're so sick.
All of those--
all the kids you hated had that. Yeah, all the all the rich kids who are super
annoying. Yeah, you go to their house and they be like, I just want to read your
book. Yeah, I had a friend growing up. I didn't hate him, but like he had like
the full it was the full encyclopedia of like everything from like the like
beginning of like from like EU to like before I got retcon I used to fucking
read that shit all the time. But the one time I was watching Revenge of the Sith
with my dad and like show like and that's Plokoon and Plokoon is a
Keldor and like saying like that and realize like my uncle Paul came
downstairs and like it's like dude your dad's asleep.
I think though I remember I think probably the worst of that type of
thing that I did.
I was thinking about Godzilla stuff specifically as I was a kid who
like if someone says something about Godzilla breathing fire, I'd be
like, no, he has atomic breath.
Oh man, it's different. Yeah, I doesn't breathe fire. I would he doesn't I was
right. I know it's so what it's so unimportant that you're right about that
man. I got upset. I will never be your dad. I'm gonna get so mad at you.
Number two is you're selfish again. I got your kid. They're selfish. Yeah, it's
a works. It does work. They've got these works. Oh yeah, they do exactly what you
want them to do when you say that. Yeah, exactly. You're only
thinking about yourself. How come you don't think of me constantly?
Exactly. How to make me feel good. Yeah, I want to watch TV. I don't want to
pick you up from school every fucking day. You can't get home on your own.
That's so gay. Yeah, what's wrong with you? You're six. You can walk home. It's really not
hard. Hey, hey, hey, give me a refresher. Hey kid, kiddo, kiddo, kiddo. How long ago
did you did you learn to walk? It's been what about like five years now right?
Okay. Oh that's I was just trying to do the math because it seems like I guess
if I was if I was able to do something for five years I would just do it. Oh you
want me to pick you up from first grade? Okay let me ask you a question did you
do my laundry? Did you give me a back rub? Yeah oh you think gas is free huh?
Okay, well you want me to tell about you up. Yeah, how about this? Yeah? Yeah, smell that
Take a big whiff of that dad ever fart in your face since they smell that my dad never farted in my face
Not in my face, but definitely pull my finger was - yeah, really my dad finger dad
I mean my dad just let some rip dude. That's sick
I hang out with my dad
And he just fucking like he like I think we were we were walking we were hanging out around here
We're walking to a bar one time. It was like mm-hmm outside
and he's just walking, just blasting heaters.
And it's like, "Man, I should not be able to smell these outside."
Yeah.
Only, yeah.
That's dangerous.
Yeah.
It's dangerous.
Number three.
You don't feel that way.
The picture of this is so funny, too, because it's a kid who's clearly hurt.
Yeah.
You're so sick.
You're not hurt.
Yeah.
You don't feel it.
That is actually, this is the first one that I actually think you should say to your kids.
This is the first one.
Literally, the first example is like, even the belief to be less than completely true,
your kid saying, "I hate you" to you.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
No, if your kid says, "I hate you," you say, "Well, I hate you too."
Yeah.
Yeah, you just say it right back.
"I hate you, bitch."
Yeah.
"I hated you first."
"I hated you, bitch."
"I hated you, mommy and daddy."
"I hated you, but more than you were even bored."
Yeah.
"I knew this would come."
Yeah, you don't feel that that is actually that's one of the funniest
evil thing.
Yeah, that is such a funny thing to say, especially to a child who's
like just sort of figuring out how like these things like cause and
effect and all these things and to be like no, no, no, no, no, no,
no trust your gut here.
Yeah, I know not even that just like no, you're wrong.
Yeah, no, no, no, sorry.
It's like I'm hurt.
It's like interesting.
Let's look at that from a different angle.
- Yeah, I do like that one, I think that's a good one.
- Number four is I wish you'd never been born.
(laughing)
- Why isn't that one number one?
That's like-- - Oh my God.
- No, that's-- - It's so crazy.
- No, that one's okay. - You know what it is?
- In the right context, that one's okay.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like, okay, if you're in a scenario
where it's you and your kid, and your kid is like,
if your kid wasn't born, you know,
you wouldn't have to get drafted to go to Ukraine, right?
then that would be an okay time to say it, I feel like.
- Well yeah, so we're not supposed to say,
"I wish you'd never been born."
What if my kid just killed everyone else in my family?
- Yeah, right.
- And went on a killing spree and killed 5,000 people?
I'm not supposed to say,
"I wish you'd never been born" to them?
- I'm gonna say it.
- I'm gonna say that,
and I'm also gonna say, "You don't feel that way, too."
And you're dramatic.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, that's the most dramatic shit you can do.
- My kid goes on a 5,000 person killing spree,
I know 25 things I'm going to say to him right off the bat.
Yeah, exactly. My kid goes paddock mode.
[laughter]
I like the last sentence here. It's like, "When you're feeling frustrated enough to say something
this hurtful, simply remove yourself from the situation until you've cooled down enough
to respond in a more level-headed manner."
Just like, imagine a parent who's so angry at their kid. How angry? I guess it's like
you have to be I guess completely fucked but it's like being like like I'm really
frustrated like that word is so like I'm so frustrated I'm gonna tell you I wish
you were never born like that that that makes a lot of sense yeah like after
he's not cleaned his room yeah yeah yeah it's like okay before I go in there and
say I wish you were never you never existed and you're a little fucking shit
yeah you or like being like really pissed off and being about to say that
and then be like okay wait I'm gonna leave the room I'm gonna cool down
- Yeah, coming back in and saying,
I wish you'd never been born, wait, shit.
(laughing)
- It's like, yeah, when I--
- I was supposed to think of a new thing to say
when I was in the other room.
- Instead I said that really calm.
- I still had that loaded up.
- Saying it calmer than you've ever said it before.
- More sincerely with more honest emotion.
- Number five, why can't you be more like your sibling?
- Oh, that happens all the time, that's fine.
- That's fine too.
Usually when that's, one sibling's evil,
the other one's good.
there's no one and then i said i don't got that one sibling
howie i mean
and i don't want to know that that war
and sibling and i want to go settling
the other side warren i don't know what i have a lot of a number six years to be
here
my mom said that i had a good time the problem is a by the way that my brain is
wired i will say this to my child five thousand times yeah with like without
meaning because that's just like I just say you're an idiot yeah I say oh you're
stupid yeah you're stupid you're stupid you're stupid I have to hear that like
train that up in the next ten years yeah because I will be saying that a hundred
times a day oh yeah absolutely and I'll be doing the post that this guy's doing
this pose with that caption so funny yeah dad taking a knee like like brow
now furrowed pointing his finger really sturdily in your face. You're stupid.
You are stupid. He said the number seven you're the man of the house. This is
this is this is the one well you can't you shouldn't this is one you
shouldn't say because it's not true. Yeah, all the other ones that stuff
it's like could be damaging. This is just it's false. You can say this on
opposite day, maybe but you shouldn't be saying this because you don't want to
be a liar. How do you how when did you guys first know you were the man of the
house. When did you guys first know about this?
I'm not the man of the house, even in my apartment.
No? You don't think so? I think you are.
I think I knew when I was in high school and I had a girlfriend and I did well on a test.
And then I kind of went home and I told my dad, "Get out." I said, "You gotta go. I had
the two and a half good things today. I need you to get out of here. Yeah, he left right
after that.
This one says, "This puts too much pressure on the child to fulfill a role he cannot and
should not yet have. It's the equivalent of a chef going on break and telling the dishwasher,
'You're cooking now.'"
Which, as we went over, dishwashers only have one star, so how are they going to start cooking?
Well, you get more stars.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I've been there a child getting like your work is permanent psychological
damage because his dad told him like I'm going to take a nap. You're the dad
while I'm asleep.
Oh my
how to do taxis.
And then get it like he's asleep. The dad's asleep like sit like four hours
just like I'm taking a nap before a big flight or something. And then like he
already has the whole house like the family audited
like this is obviously a chef should tell the dishwasher to cook but that's not
like a terrible thing to do a little like i got a break
like close to come break it right now
yeah right yeah i think it's a good idea to be like a little being like you you
can't go on break like you know i think you will never take a break well well
being a father's a twenty four-hour job and so is being a chef a chef should
never have to leave work never sleep they shouldn't
They don't.
Look what happened to Anthony Bourdain because he slept.
He did a bunch of, he did cocaine and drank beer all the time.
And he slept a lot.
Yeah, no, that's what happened to him.
Absolutely.
Number eight, no dessert until you finish dinner.
Shut the fuck up.
Fuck you.
This article was written by a kid.
This article was written by a 13 year old.
No dessert until you finish dinner.
(laughter)
- Listen to this.
- Yeah, I'm gonna listen to this.
- Enforcing the clean plate club rule at your house
can have serious ramifications in terms of your kids'
autonomy and eating habits.
- Oh my God.
- Oh my God, that's so funny.
- Sounds like someone's pissed off
they never made the clean plate club.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my little hummingbird stomach,
I can't eat one whole rib.
- Oh my God, I remember joining the clean plate club
and just like, oh my God,
and watching everyone else in my family not join in
and feeling so fucking good about it.
You get benefits when you join.
Immediately.
Immediately you get benefits.
Sky miles.
Oh yeah.
The dining club.
Amtrak points.
It's all just clean plates.
Yeah.
This is the thing on.
Okay, but to be fair on this one, the parent scientists need to recognize that children
have been telling you all for years about the dessert and dinner stomachs.
They're separate stomachs.
True.
That's true.
They've been new.
I want to read this quote because of who this person is,
what their title is.
"You're already having difficulty getting your child
to eat their food, and this actually increases
your child's perceived threat and creates
an increased power differential,"
explains registered play therapist, Rees.
(laughing)
So it's like, oh, are you just a gamer?
Like, what are you describing here?
- Yeah, this lady-- - Wait, okay, wait,
listen to this last sentence.
Instead, Reese recommends telling children that they can choose to have dessert if they choose to finish their food first.
That's psychotic.
That's the same thing!
Yeah, there's no difference there.
You're fucking stupid.
I think when you do that, you're just fucking with your kid.
Yeah.
You're just like, "Oh yeah, it's all a matter of choice."
Yeah, exactly.
That's a, "I don't know, can you?"
Oh yeah, yeah.
That's treating your kid like a computer.
Where it's like, if you don't have the exact right words, it's gonna malfunction.
It's like, "Shut the fuck up."
- If I tell my kid to eat the vegetables
that I know are good for them before they have the candy.
- Nah, but candy's better.
- I mean, candy--
(laughing)
- Nah, but candy better though.
- I mean, it's just, it's true.
It's a thing.
- Number nine, hurry up.
- This is insane.
- This is the list, I hate this list.
- Yeah, Jesus Christ.
- The phrase creates more stress and anxiety in children
who are most, I'm doing Caleb again,
who are most likely already doing their best
to find their shoes to get out the door.
- Yeah, this was written by--
I'm telling my kid hurry up constantly.
Oh yeah.
Just everything, doesn't matter, even if they're on time.
Hurry up, let's go, come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Snapping in their face.
Makes it more punctual.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's good, I mean it's training.
He doesn't have to, you know, never has to say hurry up to as a German kid.
They're famously very punctual.
I also like it's like, but telling them to hurry up isn't actually going to motivate
them.
It's not about that, I'm trying to hurt them.
(laughing)
- Fucking stupid.
- Yeah.
- It's not about motivating.
- I didn't even, I didn't want to bring them
to this dinner anyway.
- Oh my God.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- That actually does, like I think about like, I do.
- I would like to get Apple Dippers though.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Like it would be, I think it'd be fun to be a parent,
but I don't know how I feel about like,
bringing a child with you to places.
Just sounds.
- Yeah.
- I think it can be really fun probably,
'cause it's probably fun to watch a child
just make a mockery of any situation
and be kind of blameless in that, right?
Like if I show up to dinner and I, you know--
- I don't wanna wear my shirt anymore.
- Yeah, right.
- The collar hurts on my shirt,
I don't wanna wear it anymore.
- The waiter's Chinese.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's like--
- Gosh, geez.
- Oh, yeah.
I gotta remove him from the situation.
- Sorry my husband gets like that.
(laughing)
Yeah, no, he's in his terrible 32s.
Yeah, he was told hurry up too much as a child.
Yeah, yeah.
He was told to hurry up too much, you know.
Yeah, the terrible 32s.
Number 10, what did you do to yourself?
What do you mean? What did you fucking, like, what did you do?
Let's find out what they mean, Halle.
While you might not be a fan of your kid's new hair color or nose ring,
when you start a conversation with an accusatory question like this,
you're shutting down communication right off the bat.
Your child will constantly feel judged and not good enough.
They shouldn't do stuff to themselves then.
Right?
You walk in, you walk in, your kid has cut, I've done this before, I've cut like, I cut
like up and around on my hair, like when I was in the third grade, and like there's a
family photo where, I mean it was taken on like an old cell phone so you can't really
see it, but like I have just like one giant chunk missing from my hair.
You just like created a like a, sort of like a puzzle piece.
Yeah.
I think I tried to I think I saw like a dude with like
Sounds like you're trying to make yourself
It sounds like you were trying to do Trunks hair
Yeah I think so
The thing is if parents don't want kids to give themselves
fucked up haircuts and stuff they need to stop putting it in movies
because it looks so fun in movies
Yeah it's true
They do it's in every movie ever
Think the utility of what did you do to yourself is like to let them know
you did this to yourself
Yeah
You need to understand that
did this to yourself is worse than what did you do to yourself. This is a kid coming home
with a triangular ring, a triangular nose ring or something, you know. And you just don't
even say it, you just say, "You did this to yourself."
Number 11, stop crying.
How are they going to know to stop?
How are they going to stop?
This is very obvious.
Yep.
Just tell them to stop.
Okay, here. Yeah, let me predict what this is going to say.
Cut the waterworks.
licensed crayon therapist
Buddha, who even knows what liberal name is freak has says
that instead of telling your line instead of this, instead of
telling instead of saying stop crying to your children, which
creates a threatening power attack.
You should
try triangle triangle square combo.
Actually, you should actually use the empowering phrase start
laughing.
(laughter)
- Start laughing.
- Yeah, Diesel Antwerp, a child psychologist,
says instead of telling your child to put away your toys,
which is a--
- Which could actually mutate them.
- You should say,
you should say,
like use your mind and your body to move yourself slowly over to the
block. Just take like as long as possible to articulate this. I don't
understand why you can't say stop crying.
Child linguist Nick Cannon says that you should never say clean up
your room. Instead, you should always use the empowering phrase.
Shit.
I ran a zero. I'm getting zeros on these two. Yeah, the the
license license child scientist,
Dr. Evil.
It's okay to say stop crying to your child as long as you also
sometimes say it when they're not crying.
(laughter)
- You have to balance it out, he says.
Number 12, don't be a baby.
What if they're being a baby?
- Yeah, that's kinda obvious.
- Yeah, number 13, you're the best at that?
- Child videographer Mace Windu
(laughter)
claims that saying--
- Child videographer.
- Saying the phrase--
- Child videographer Mace Windu.
(laughter)
Saying the phrase "good job" makes a child act stupid later in life.
And instead you should say "fuck you" to your kid.
Infant gymnast Boba Fett claims that tickling your child can actually rupture their soul
and cause them to explode into hell.
You're the best at that. If my fucking parents said I was good at anything, I wouldn't be
here.
Yeah, you need to say your kids are the best.
Yeah.
14, you were an accident.
My mom did tell me that.
Yeah.
You just seem fine.
No, I mean, yeah, I'm like, I know that I was, but like, that's okay. I mean, it's not
like you can't tell like I'm like my sister was born two years two years
before my brother yeah my younger brother is two years younger than me right I'm
13 months away from my brother right my brother's birthday is 13 months from
mine yeah I it's nobody wants that it's very clear who in the family was the one
that was like ah well let's try this let's try this out let's take this for a
spin yeah yeah licensed child biologist Charmander actually thinks that you
should specifically tell your child that they were on purpose no matter what
provide beautiful details for the scene John you were on purpose mm-hmm number
15 you're okay we covered that kind of yeah I think so yeah what is it wait
what is this telling kids that something does not hurt when it does challenges
their reality says Nance.
Who's Nance?
Wait hold on. Enhance.
Nance?
Enhance Nance.
You wouldn't want to challenge their reality.
License Nance.
License child
License child predator Mr. Nance
says that parents should actually not
teach their children about stranger days.
It forces them
Forces them into a state of just distrusting everyone who comes to their door and offers them treats and fun time
Child psychologist Jimmy Savile
Says that he'll fix it. Yeah
What's lightning around these why can't you do anything? Right? What's wrong with you?
Mm-hmm. I don't believe you. That one's okay to say there's nothing to be afraid of
This is just shut up. There's a lot to be missing their feelings. You're trying to comfort them
Number 20, you're lazy.
Mm-hmm.
What if a kid's fucking lazy?
Remember I told you guys--
I was.
When I was a kid, I went to see the Star Wars movies when they were released in theaters.
Yeah.
And I was really afraid of Darth Vader, so my dad told me that he just had a cold,
and that's why he was breathing like that.
And so I just thought for too long that he had a cold.
Then someone was like, "That's not why Darth Vader--"
He's in that suit, because--
I was like, "Yeah, he's got the flu."
Yeah, it's gonna weaken. Yeah, right. He's Darth. Yeah, that's why number 21. You have to give them a hug or kiss
Yeah, it really depends who you're talking about I guess we also address this earlier yeah number 22 your friends don't do that
Yeah, me and my friends are gonna we're gonna play some online games your friends don't do that
They don't play that game. Yeah
Every night my friends are gonna play Halo 3 your friends don't fucking play Halo 3 do they think Halo 3 sucks
Your friends hate I wouldn't do that if I were I wouldn't do that if I were you that's very funny
That is such a sick thing to say that's yeah, that's like a villain
I'll be back
Never asked never tell your child. Do you feel lucky punk? Yeah?
Number 24, you should have done better.
You should have done better.
It's the second to last one here.
And then the last one is you should be ashamed.
What if you caught your...
We all get dead silent because we're all raised Catholic.
Yeah.
Got upset.
I know.
That actually happened.
Shut up.
Shut up, Liz.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's it.
I think that's it, right?
Dang.
by
Tickets to the live show which patches will be
DMing in Brooklyn on the 31st at Union March at Union Hall
I'll put the link in the description and also subscribe to the patreon at $10 because we do a bunch of D&D episodes that patches
Does and he gets money from that and they're really fun and you'll like them and there's a bunch of them now
So there's a big backlog. Yeah, like what like four campaigns 400 I think yeah, I think there's 400
It's not like fraud or false advertising.
- No, why would it be?
- Yeah.
- There's 400 episodes if you split them up into
- Not, you don't have to do,
I've been trying to explain to you,
you don't have to do anything.
If you just count them the way I count them,
where you count them all until you reach 400.
(laughing)
- You have 400 episodes.
- You do the skip a few method,
one, two, skip a few, 99, 400.
- I think we have like 50.
- Yeah, at least over a thousand seconds.
- Yeah, right.
- Of content.
All right, bye.
- Bye.