Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Hey, guys, hey.
- Oh, what's up, buddy?
I really like this new setup of you all the way over there.
- Yeah.
- It shows that you're separate from me and Cameron,
maybe a little worse, like Robin from Howard Stern.
- Or from Batman.
- Yeah.
- Robin from Howard Stern sat away?
- They segregated her?
- They did, yeah.
- What?
You ever watch the video versions of Stern?
Where it's like him, it'll be him,
and then like Gary, Gary, Gary, Beetlejuice.
- Gary De La Ba-tay?
- Gary De La Ba-tay, yeah.
It'll be him, Baba Booey.
- Baba Booey is Gary De La Ba-tay.
- No, I'm thinking of Gary, Gary De La Retard.
- No, that's Eric.
- No, Gary the Retard.
- I thought it was Eric the Retard.
- No, Gary's the one who has no teeth.
- No, Gary's the one with the big teeth, Baba Booey.
Gary has no teeth who am I thinking of I don't know I'm thinking of Baba boo Gary's
the one I'm thinking of Gary the snail from Spongebob Gary's the one who does
this the the game show with beat where they both know that red that's Eric the
retarding it's Gary the retail hold on let me google this could be wrong let me
go to my it's Gary the snail still I'm standing by that Eric the red was an
explorer yeah I loved when when when Howard Stern made leaf Ericsson ride the
Sibbian oh oh it's I'm thinking of I'm thinking of high-pitched Eric mm-hmm
Eric the actor okay then there's Fred the elephant boy Lenny Teixtra Gary yeah
- Yeah, okay, Gary the retard, yeah.
- And Gary's from Oregon.
He lives in Oregon.
He says in that video, he says,
I have to, he says it just like this,
I have to fly back to Oregon tomorrow.
(laughing)
He says it just like that.
- That's so cool.
- Yeah, he's a great guy.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You know him?
- Yeah.
- You guys like hang out?
- Mm-hmm, I go to Oregon with him.
- Nice. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- You go down on his Oregon with him.
- I didn't know Tan Mom was one of the Whack Pack members.
- Tan Mom? - Yeah.
- Really?
mom yeah I remember her the tannest mom of all time she's like this table yeah
pretty much a mahogany woman yeah I um I got I got oh yeah I got attacked yeah
you tell your story and I have a question about it
it's a story dude some some fucking Antifa soldier through a through a
Heineken bottle through my so my window yeah you're getting too close to the
truth car window right yeah here's what I'm thinking of you've parked the car
near the office before right yep do you think maybe this could be the work of
the beautiful invader who's seen you walking from the car to the office and
follow the car at the office no it happened outside my house maybe he
walked he fought maybe also apparently happened broad day did really yeah broad
day didn't you not know hey that's good that's good that's good at night the
invaders getting beauty sleep true I thought that it was during that it
happened like a couple days ago during the night and I just didn't see it till I
I went to move my car, but apparently,
the old baby girl was walking the dog yesterday morning,
and she made specific note of the fact
that there was not a hole in the car window
when she walked by. - Wow, interesting.
- And then when I went out at about 4.30--
- She specifically noted that,
'cause I think that that would maybe make her the culprit.
- Yeah. - No, I don't know.
She, I was like-- - I think we might have
to put her on investigation. - She texted you.
- She said, yeah, she texted me--
- She texted you three hours before--
- At 8.30. - There is no hole
in the car window. - There's not a single hole
in the car window, especially not from a beer.
And then she came back, she's burping up bubbles,
you know, she's got snot bubbles,
she's swaying left to right.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Seeing pink elephants who were spurting water
out of their mouths.
- Yeah.
- But I don't think it was her.
- I think the trunk of an elephant
should be the mouth, not the nose.
- I think the trunk of the car is where you get beer,
not the window.
- Here's my question, why do you call it a trunk
on an elephant when it's in the front,
when you call the trunk of a car is in the back of the car?
- Yeah.
- Unless it's a Lamborghini. - That's the back of the elephant.
- Yeah. - Unless it's a Lambo.
Maybe all along that was the back of the elephant and the front is the butt.
That's my question and my problem as well.
Maybe the tail is the real trunk.
I don't really care. I'm just really-- I'm just hurt, man.
I'm hurt and I need to see a pair of humongous boobs.
- Well, what? - Yeah, I need to see a pair of boobs.
That's not gonna fix your problem, man.
- I need to see a pair of boobs. - You need to go to therapy.
No, I don't think so. I need to see a pair of boobs that are so big that they smell bad.
bad. You need to go to therapy and I have just the solution for you. I need a pair of boobs.
With betterhelp.com. No, a pair of boobs that smell really bad because they're so big that
they smell bad. You know what I mean? Betterhelp.com. Like a fat guy's belly button. You can get
a therapist with big sweater boobs. Like you lift up the big boobs and you're just like
"Ugh, ugh." Get back here. Get back. Stop rolling away. Speaking of websites like betterhelp.com,
of some really huge news. And then you do this like under the boobs right and
there's like tons of just dead skin that gets all over your face. Jesus Christ man.
It's been just so long. Why are you doing this? Yeah what's wrong with you today?
He is really loopy his car was broken into. Did I not just tell you what's fucking wrong with me today?
Did they take anything from your car? Yeah was there anything stolen out of the car?
No but they. Did you check your CDs? I did not check my CDs. They took one kind of beer
bottle size shape of glass for my window yeah it sucks dude the worst part is the
whole fucking cars filled it's like covered in beer no we didn't take your
beer gave me beer yeah but it's like the the beer dried and all the glass stuck
to it so it's like it's like a nightmare like I know the glass like I can't clean
it up you know shop vac huh you know the shop vac I think I am a millionaire my
dad has one. He's a millionaire. That's true. Yeah. My dad is a millionaire. He's a
millionaire. Yeah. No I don't have a shop vac. I have a... I do have a dog. I'm thinking just letting him
kind of... lap everything up, all the glass and stuff. My dad's only a
millionaire because of the NFT he sold. Yeah. You guys see that? I think I
should send it to you guys. Isn't your dad's Goatse? Yeah. He's selling an NFT.
goatsies he minted goatsie mm-hmm that's smart dude that is smart can I share the
exciting website news now oh yeah oh yeah yeah this is huge if you check out our
website at swag poop calm you'll notice that several very fun games have been
added that you can play let me actually let me read out the games that are now
and there are more to come so don't don't think that this is it but right
now right now I mean you have access to for free it doesn't cost any
money to play no ad free as well should be putting this behind a paywall haunted
house hidden objects game a bunny solitaire squirrel bubble shooter that
one's really fun squirrel bubble shooter is really good Christmas mystery this is
the one I've been really on to Kings gold is is is my second favorite Kings gold
Kings gold very solid is really yeah I do like Kings gold a lot yeah but squirrel
bubble shooters definitely the best one more more to come keep your eyes peeled
and when it asks you if you want to accept cookies
to read and share your data with advertisers, click yes.
- I would say that's a strong yes,
because that supports us.
- That comes from our website, so it's safe.
And I'm not embedding these games from any website
that would do anything nefarious with your data.
- No.
- Definitely not.
So you should definitely accept the cookies.
- And even then, a website like that--
- And if you already accepted the cookies
without reading what it was for, you should not be worried.
- Yeah.
And even then a website like that, that would host games like this for free, would never
take your data and do anything bad with it.
No, and it wouldn't hack our website either.
No, it would not.
And it won't, it definitely, yeah, it won't be an issue if we ever added any e-commerce
to our website and it won't take any credit card data from our database or anything like
that.
Definitely not.
Yeah, I can't see that happening.
No, that makes no sense.
Yeah.
Kingsgold, Squirrel Bubble Shooter, Squirrel Bubble Shooter, Kingsgold, those two, check
them out.
I got I was good world bubble shooter for like an hour less and I got to level 26
before I got I think I got to level 11 oh you're not a you're not a pro I guess
I'm not Christmas mysteries a lot of good I mean that is that one of the
hidden objects ones yeah yeah I like really why would you hide presents so
you can find them why you hiding them presents I want to see the presents I
I want it every day is a present yeah what I call it that's what I call it no
every day is every day is a gift and that's what I call it the present and
then the past every day is a present that's why I wrap the past is you passed
it past is the past is you're in the future because you're for her no the
future is called that because it futures it's future yeah yeah future it's
future to happen soon yeah it's just future to happen mm-hmm and what's it
What's it called when you go sideways in time?
- Dimension, parallel dimension.
- Dimension, yeah.
I shudder at dimension of this bullshit.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Can I say it again?
- He forgot dimension, how to pronounce it.
- I shudder at dimension of this bullshit.
- Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- The very mention of the third dimension.
- Yeah.
- I wish we could go back one dimension.
- I'm sick of this.
- I wanna be 2D.
- I'm sick of this 3D shit.
so skinny I like to unfold us and get us back to 2d yeah definitely like our
forefathers yeah our two fathers are two yeah yeah they only see they only call
they call them that because they only had two names and this - bullshit yeah
their p parents are having now when you see a kid with a hyphenated name you
know you know they got a crazy ass home life yep yep you know his parents are
either lesbians or you know that you know in algebra uh-huh why the hell
- How the hell would you do that to a child?
- If I was a teacher and I got my like,
my like attendance roster at the beginning of the year,
and I saw a kid with a hyphenated last name, I would quit.
(laughing)
- Definitely.
- Yeah, I have no chance, I'm trying to teach one of those.
- That kid ain't bringing you no apples.
- No.
- No, he's bringing you apples,
but check it out, there's a worm in 'em.
- Can you imagine how good that's gotta feel
when you just get yourself real hungry as a teacher,
so you can eat some apples when you get there?
- Yeah, but what if the kid's bringing a Red Delicious?
- Who cares, you're a teacher.
- Dude, a Red Delicious apple on a teacher's salary,
I think that's a delicacy actually.
- Yeah, maybe.
No, honey crisp, that's gotta be.
If a kid brings in a honey crisp.
- Oh my God.
- Straight A's dude.
- That was like, I mean.
- A pink delicious.
- You know, nowadays though, with today's society,
kids stop bringing in apples.
Nowadays they bring in Starbucks
and Dunkin Donuts gift cards.
- Yep.
Nowadays kids bring in their Apple iPhones
and film you when you're bending over in class.
- Yep, yeah.
They used to bring in apples.
- Now they bring in their Apple iPhones
and film you calling one of the students a freak.
- Posted on an Apple location called hotteacher.com.
(laughing)
- Yeah, the kids are there trying to fool you
by drinking I-beer in class.
They're making me all pissed off.
Hey, you can't drink the--
- It says you gotta be 21 to download that app.
- You can't be 18 plus and downloading that app.
- No.
- I teach kids with GEDs, or trying to get GEDs.
- That's another app I teach.
- Yeah.
I don't know what it does teaches you what teaches you how to rap. I don't
know about you guys. Well, when I'm in school, I see the teacher right on the
chalkboard. I want to talk because I'm bored. Yeah, yeah, and they're calling
them smart boards. What's not making me any smarter and the boards white and I'm
white and I'm bored
white board. I'm white and I'm bored.
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh that she's writing on the whiteboard with a marker.
Yeah, I'd like to put down a marker on this school with that. I would like to
blow up yeah yeah, because I had to read ten books and I I my name is Ben took
I to read ten books, but but Ben took them and I I look thin yeah. They got me
reading bell hooks in this class. The bell just went off and I have to go
play hooky for my next class. Yep, you know I'm a senior in high school. They
they want me they want me to buy text books. I'd rather buy sex and fuck
that's
yeah, I'm over there in home ec because my home's heck my dad's real. He's
abusive. Oh my God, I'm so sorry. My hat my home is complete. Heck they want me
to run around in gym class and said I'm running away from my dad, whose name is
Jim class.
I'm Darrell class.
My dad is my story.
Yeah. Yeah, my name's Math Class. Yeah. They got me in wood shop. Yeah, I would shop for
new school clothes if my dad didn't make me wear his hand-me-downs. Yep. And his name
is Math Class. No, his name is Jim Class. And then when I get home, he brings his hand
down yep yeah yeah science class my dad's violent ass just beat the shit out of me
yeah social studies class yeah my sister is named social studies class yeah yeah
US history yeah a my dad be saying app and then his story is they just drop a
put drum set upstairs? I think so, I think they dropped an entire drum set. But the point
is, lunch, my dad lunched over the dinner table to beat my fucking stupid ass at dinner, because
I mouthed off. My dad, Jim Klass, he lunched over the dinner table. His middle name is
Shorts. And I've recessed into my mind to escape my physical heck, my home heck. And
to me that's psychology.
- Mm-hmm.
- AP psychology.
- That's right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep, algebra.
Who's Al?
(laughing)
Who's Algebra?
- Art class, yeah, that's my uncle's name.
(laughing)
- Biology class, that's my aunt.
My dad's gym class, I'm Darryl class.
- Oh, you want me to go to the guidance counselor?
Well, actually, I dance when my dad tries to pounce on me.
(laughing)
- Got me a medal shot.
Yeah, the only fucking medal I could get
is one I shopped for.
- Yeah, my dad--
- Can't even win at baseball,
'cause my dad hits me too much.
- My dad shot a piece of metal out of his gun.
And he shot me in the head.
Daryl Class.
- Damn.
And now I'm--
- And now I'm back.
- The story of Daryl Class.
- And now I'm a ghost.
- You mean Ghost Class?
- Yeah, yeah, Ghost 101.
That's my class, I teach.
- Yep.
- Yeah, teacher.
Hogwarts. We've talked about that before right? Like at Hogwarts like these kids
are like completely stupid about everything except pointing their wands
right? Like they don't know how to spell or read. There's an SNL sketch. Is it? No wait
that's High School Musical. Oh. They have Troy Bolton come back. Why are you
I'm remembering SNL sketches. Zach Efron's in it and he looks very cute.
I'm at school. They're making me study calculus. I wish I was a gladiator
named Maximus so I could defeat my dad.
Yeah, with a spear and a net.
A net? Yeah, she's in my class.
And she's a girl that makes the cootie catchers.
who do you get yours yet that's what my dad is when he's down at the damn gold
club
uh... the cuchi catches the courier injuries put his finger in all those
women in the champagne room
yeah what's a terrible thing really i think there is a lot of champagne room
i'd rather be in the shampoo room i'm so dirty i think that that doesn't let me
shower
champagne reminds had enough pain in my room
from my dad
by dutch my dad's sham l belts
my dad sham on
- Shimona.
- Shimona Payne.
That's my mom's name.
- My name is Daryl Class Payne.
- Shimona Payne is what those kids were saying
after they were at Neverland Ranch.
- Yep, Shimona Payne.
What's another school thing?
- Well, we have to, if we wanna do this, it was--
- Kindergarten. - Desk and chairs.
I got, I got--
- Chesley Hares.
- Lesson.
- I went through puberty.
- I went through puberty, I have Chesley Hares now.
So what about that?
Hannah that's my crush at school. My dad crushes me after school.
Driver's Ed, yeah my dad's designated driver's name is Ed. He can't go anywhere without having
six beers. Gym class. Driver's Ed, my brother Kyle is dead because my dad hit him so hard that he
died with one punch. He killed my son or my dad or my brother. All of them. He killed all of them.
He's the worst guy ever.
All right, today we have a very special episode.
A special where we're--
We're doing an advice column.
We're jumping out of the--
The lists to give you the advice that all of you
sent into our email address,
pod@castaboutlist@gmail.com.
Pod@castaboutatlist@gmail.com.
Yeah, it's an extra @ email address
that has multiple ats.
Yeah.
we want to we want to jump right into this maybe yeah. I think we should just start
with the first question from a listener. I love to jump right into this. Yeah let
me let me see here now some of these also have just just answers attached to them
already. Yeah we don't know why. Yeah don't know what's somebody replied to
the email thread. Yeah here's our first question can humans become demons?
Here's the answer that's already attached here. To be a demon you will have to spend
several hundred and thousands of years in hell as Lucifer's foot soldier gaining
his trust doing his dirty work and building a demonic reputation this often
means quote accidental mass murdering such as 9/11 Hurricane Katrina and more
Wow it's pretty good that one it's making Caleb cry
Okay, so this question is should teenage boys eat their come
So there's two there's two answers here, and I'll give my answer first mm-hmm no mm-hmm, okay
Neil sterling who lives in the United Kingdom says yes, not only is it good for you, but it's fun to produce it and then
Somebody else says most definitely you should eat you come every time it's possible in fact a teenage boy should go
out of his way to find all the people they can and drink their cum as well. It
is growing years and eating a lot of cum will help your dick grow long and hard
so find all the people you can to suck them off and drink their cum and that
person's name is Master.
But you guys ever get some cum in your mouth? Yeah. It's not, it tastes like
orange juice? Depends on the day. It tastes like fire. Did you eat a bunch of ribs or
something? I did, yeah I did. It tastes like salt. Yeah. If you eat a bunch of pineapples it
tastes like a tropical delight. Yeah I think I did, I tried the pineapple thing
for a little bit in high school. Nobody was like eating my cum, but I was like
I was like maybe I just want to make sure if it ever comes. In the situation that someone
wants to eat my cum suddenly. I want to be prepared. Yeah, so I was eating a lot of
fruits and stuff. That's what the Pina Colada song's about. And I wish that I'd
gotten, I wish that that's when I'd gotten cum in my mouth. Yeah. But I got, I
think I got cum in my mouth at a time when I was mostly eating like ciabatta
bread and Cheerios. Oh man. And so it was really, it was real dusty. Yeah. Yeah, kind of
tasted like an attic. Yeah, do you, do your cum taste like kashi and it's like
damn. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, it's got some crunch to it. Yeah. Yeah. That's why I
Mills loves this shit. It's like the gojo soap. Yeah, exactly. It's exactly like gojo soap.
had the pumice stones. It definitely had stones in it. That is the worst soap of all time.
It's horrible. You just fucked it up. The one office thing you did, you just fucked it up
so bad. I bought a one gallon thing of soap that has pumice stones in it. The nastiest
soap ever. And he bought quarter ply toilet paper. Yeah, one roll. Yeah, one roll of quarter
ply toilet paper. I didn't buy that. I didn't buy the toilet paper. You did. No I didn't.
read your Joe and Alex. Just answer your question. All right here's a question
doesn't say who it's from but this is a it has seven answers it says I think my
aunt has a crush on me what do I do? And Janet Maker PhD of educational
psychology says just make sure you do nothing to encourage her you might start
talking about your girlfriend or boyfriend make sure you're never alone
with her if she invites you anywhere say no in fact if you think she might invite
you prepare a list of excuses in advance what are the signs of an aunt crush she
says I have a crush on you mmm she says I have a crush on somebody in the family
but I can't tell you who my husband so there's this guy so I'm talking I've
been thinking I've been talking to this guy but talk to this guy he's a little
Thanksgiving update I've been talking this guy's a little bit younger than me
And he loves Spitfire wheels. He loves getting his cheeks pinched. He loves
cheeks pinching and he loves getting a Spitfire shirt for Christmas which may or
may not be happening. He's great with my son. He's really good. Being at Thanksgiving and
getting a note handed to you from your grandfather who's sitting next to
you yes like do you like me ever be a great yeah yeah you just look at you
pass it on yeah pass it on it's supposed to go to your grandmother do you like me
why in yes how did you see me yeah my my advice for this one is you have to leave
your family permanently yeah your family permanently that means that you were no
longer a part of the family and then your aunt. And then you can fuck your aunt. So I think what you should do is
probably... kill your aunt. You become your own uncle at that point. What? If you get involved with your aunt.
I guess so. But I would say that this situation probably is an
aunt by marriage. Okay. Because I don't, you know, aunt by marriage, pretty hot.
hot, you know, like that's fine, you know, like you can you can pursue that. Do you
think that's like a like because they have all the stepbrother stuff on the
internet now, all the pornography. I don't even know what you're looking at. You're
looking at the stepbrother stuff, not the stepsister stuff. It keeps popping up.
The pause it keeps popping
Do you think there's like so it's like the stepbrother stepsister stuff there's all this stepdog stuff
You think that there's like some videos that are like aunt by marriage
My marriage stuck in dishwasher. Definitely. Yeah
I'm by marriage, hand stuck in garbage disposal.
Please don't turn on the garbage disposal.
I want to see it stuck in the dishwasher one where she's like a perfect cube.
You know what I mean?
Like she's all mangled and like her...
Like a plate.
She looks like the beginning of it follows where the knees like bent back.
When you put like a water bottle on the bottom rack and like the lid like melts and like yeah.
Yeah, she's all melt, half her face is melted off.
Yeah, that'd be so hot. Here's a here's a question from one of our listeners sent
this in. How can I punish my slave online and here's an answer attached here from
Utah father's rights helping dads win custody a slave with a clueless master
is punishment enough. How do you think he lost his kid? Just telling his kid he's
Is this slave his whole life?
I would like to--
You are my child's slave.
Here's one.
This is from somebody-- this is from our listener, LicketySquirtingSplits.
This is, "How was the taste when you first sucked and licked a pussy?"
And Michelle Morgan said, "She tasted so good I couldn't stop.
It was my mom."
Oh dear.
And as for my answer, I'd like to say that I've never and will never do that. That's
disgusting.
Yeah.
Put somebody's thing in my mouth.
No way.
Eww.
Yeah. A penis or a vagina?
Just anything.
Yeah, I'd have to say, I mean, either way.
I'd be sitting in the bathroom immediately after going, "Eww."
I'd wash my mouth.
That was soap, if I heard.
I'd have to. I'd put Listerine in my mouth.
A penis or a vagina.
And Listerine really hurts.
Yeah.
But I'd put it in my mouth for maybe four or five seconds.
- I do Listerine mixed with hydrogen peroxide.
- I do Listerine mixed with the hot sauce.
- I do nail polish remover mixed with Styrofoam.
Put that in my mouth.
- Um, and here's another one from the same guy.
This is, he just replied to the same email
so that he could, he wanted to get two for one.
- Yeah.
- He said, "Have you ever fucked teen pussy?"
And this person says, "My cousin brother
"has fucked his teen sister's pussy."
(laughing)
and Don Spencer who lives in West Virginia says,
when I was young, I did my neighbor's daughter.
It was mutual and good.
And-- - I love our fans.
- Yeah, and our fan Jignesh Sharma says,
yes, my own sister's pussy.
It feels so awesome.
- Here's a, here's one here.
This is kind of a prequel one.
Prequel question from a fan.
How can I tell my aunt that I have sexual feelings for her?
here's a celebrity guest answer from John Wilson who says this is how it went
this is how I went about it my aunt and I have had a close relationship for a
long time I stayed with her like I was her son through the years as I grew
older we could talk about anything and we did some of our best conversations
would be when the Sun when she's untanned by the pool I would stare at my
aunt's hot body and imagine her naked. One day I couldn't help myself so I asked
if I could rub lotion on her. With no hesitation she said hell yeah. I missed
some spots plus I'd love to be rubbed on. I thought I was dreaming when she said
that. Sweet this works for both of us because I wanted to rub all over your
sexy body. She didn't say anything so I apologize for saying that. So she rolled
over so I could start with her backside. My dick was semi-hard as I made my way
up her thick with two C's. We need to imagine what he's what he'd be filming
with all this. So thick with two C's. He's just filming random women on the street.
Thick with two C's maybe like a tree trunk. You know. Continue. It was time to
make my move so I pulled my dick out of the side of my short. Okay so that's a guy
getting off the subway yeah yeah as I moved it got so hard her tan line on her
ass was covered by the bottom she was wearing with both hands just grabbing
her so much I asked if I could pull them off her hips come up and I quickly had
them off I asked if it bothered her by what I said but not shocked her there I
was had her legs spread wide with one oh geez actually this is like this is just
10-minute video of a guy like trying to put clothes on a mannequin yeah that's
what plays yeah tell me the dirty detail this is clearly somebody like I from
reading this I think that people use this our fans use this website our fans
use this website to ask these questions and then calm gmail.com and then get
prompts from other or get get a get erotica written by other users so they
use these questions as prompts to to garner and then people were emailing
there okay yeah that makes sense this one is there's a it says is this one ends
with can you keep it between us nephew but there's also another one here from
Musa Dick Khan Moosa dick Moosa dick Khan he was a former ex-team leader from
2010 to 2013 he says you need to go closely and hang out with her be
friendly with her in conversation check whether she taking interest in you know
her level of comfort and attachment in your company once you enjoying in your
company slightly move for body touch a close and nearly once attempt your what's
accept your touch gently kiss her and on hand and hug her she'll need privacy and
confidentiality in such relation with you ensure complete privacy to her and
move forward for sexual romantic intimacy intimacy during sex respect
her twice on every step of sexual embassy. This will take you to long sexual
relations with her. You said embassy and then you said intimacy. I'm reading
what's written. Okay, I believe you Cameron you had one yeah, so it is a lot
of these I think are our fans kind of you know trying to get erotica written
like this one here. What is sex like with a female bodybuilder and this is
was answered by by one of our fans, John Willie. This is about he answered the
last question.
This is about me and my wife, who is a tall and very strong and dominating
professional social media, female body builder and I'm a normal skinny and
short guy working in software services industry. We got married in September
twenty twenty one after dating for over twenty four months and I can't read
this whole thing because he literally he wrote a twenty six item list of what
happens when they have sex and each item is like multiple paragraphs long, but he
does include the statistics, the vital statistics of both his wife and him.
So his wife is five foot five feet, nine inches, one hundred and five
kilograms, breast, forty nine inches, triple D's, biceps, nineteen inches,
waist, thirty seven inches, thighs, thirty inches, biceps, calves, twenty
four inches, shirt slash bra size, triple XL, body type, strong, athletic
and muscular. And then his stats are five feet, four inches, weight, fifty
six kilograms chest, thirty four inches biceps, thirteen inches waist, twenty
eight inches thighs, eighteen inches calves, fourteen inches shirt slash
vest size, extra small body type, weak lean and thin. Does he does he list her
does he list her at or anything does he yeah? I would like to see my eyes are
smaller than her biceps. My face is twenty percent smaller than her boob.
This is her ass is bigger than my back. Her thighs are bigger than my waist and
as big as my chest. Her side body thickness from back armpits to boobs is
as big as my front body with shoulder to shoulder with so she can hide me behind
her even horizontally apart from being obviously able to hide me behind her
vertically and then yeah it's a 26 and then it at the end it's a attached like
super dark blurry picture of it just look it's just two naked bodies, but only
like the shoulders. Oh we looking at this it's like it's a it's a oh my god.
Yeah, that looks like a fuck her. It's crazy. She's built dude that looks like
it was a it looks like it's a I it's it's nuts but anyway so we have a lot of fans
who are trying to write this erotica stuff but we also have some more some
fans that are a little more philosophical and are just looking for a
serious answer to the to like you know a deep philosophical question like this
fan who's sent in why are my nuts can we pause for a second I have to go to the
bathroom so bad and and as we were saying listen this one this is a pretty good
question this this is a woman who's having some marital issues she said how
would I make my husband happy in bed he complains I have a big pussy and he
doesn't enjoy sex with me so it's a lot of people in this thread who are just
kind of it's not your fault it's not your fault right but your gum out huh
Spit your gum out. Yeah now he's the villain. It's not your fault. Oh, it's not your fault. Your husband's a jerk and then this guy
Usman Fia
He's yeah friend of the show. He says I sex with you
Accolade is that he knows English
So that's pretty impressive. I have another I haven't I have a an advice question here from a fan of the show
I think this one is specifically for Caleb. This is an advice question that I'm here to answer. Yeah that asks
What is size of your boob? Can I see it?
My boob. Yeah, I don't know. I'm trying what what's my measured one?
So like I could be an a cup. I tried to get my
My sternum bone fitted for a bra
Yeah, I have pectus carinatum. I don't know how to say it the one where it pokes out instead it goes in
Oh, yeah
Yeah bird chest and when I was 13 it poked out a lot more and as a gag
Me and my friends made they were like, oh, what are they like, you know with the odds remember that game?
Yeah, I lost I had to go into Victoria's Secret and get it fitted damn asked to get it fitted and they said no
They said no, they won't they said they wouldn't say no
They said they would not fit my they would not check my my size
That's terrible. Yeah different time. Yep
So it would probably one of the most embarrassing moments of my life talking to a Victoria's Secret employee like
Victoria's Secret model because it's all models who was yeah a Victoria's Secret angel
I had to walk up to yep and ask well you was wearing the angel wings
She's only in she's six. Will you put some tape measure around my 13 year old chest? Yeah
and she said no no I will not beat you yep and my friends were like well at
least you did it that's right anybody have one or just I yeah sure my son's
dick gets boner on seeing me is it good Brandon DeVos I have a question for
Cameron tell him it's normal and teach him how to take care of it specifically
for Cameron from a fan. Uh-huh. What happens if I put liquid meth in my
vagina? And somebody named Carissa Gardner, former addict of several drugs for over a decade,
says first off what's the point of meth mixed with water? Secondly I will only
allow pure organic grapeseed or coconut oil in my vagina because I fear infection.
It would destroy your pH balance. Yeah I only I only allow I only allow
purists is weird. I only allow pure coconut oil in girls vaginas as well.
Absolutely. Yeah. That's a big rule for me. Yeah. That's the only thing that's
going in there. Definitely. Nothing else. Yeah. Why is it's kind of weird that
women's thingies have a scientific element. Yeah. Well it's because it's an
open hole. Guys thingies don't have that. Yeah. There's nothing alchemical about my
penis. Yeah. But the girls are trying to put the right mixture of salt. It's
It's basically a hot dog. It's basically a Petri dish. Yeah. Their thing. You guys
haven't have never... because I'm... this has got me thinking about the pH balance of
my butthole right now. The pH balance of my butthole is all the way negative. Yeah.
It's fully... The pH balance of my butthole... the pH stands for penis hole. Okay, what's the
balance yeah what do you balance in there how are you balance are you
balancing it in your butt what's the number is that a sick I don't know which
one is with me neither I think acidic is the the most medium my damn buttholes
acidic the way that I twirl my fucking butt pubes that's right
you know you know I got them curly bouncy little things what are they called
tendrils
things that come off of the city guys heads yeah I suppose the city close well
I'll be rubbing sheets all over it. Whoa! Stop look! That's crazy! That is a fan named
Adam Schlong sent in a uh... Adam Schlong certified HEO and avid
extreme outdoorsman
uh... sent a photo of somebody injecting meth into a vagina
I bet that feels really good though. Yeah probably
He also posted a picture of
of him uh... his penis next to a butt
and it's a little
uh...
uh... what's the last picture
uh... it's important that the newspapers
do you know who's
it's also good
it probably was really bad for a second
there's a new card burns there's a color of the city of the needle in the
team here
there's a car nearer tristan constantine this is damn you to have my attention
how the hell you get open those veins i would love to see that in video hell i
well, I would pay money to see them from the beginning to where I both come.
Here's another question from a fan. This is a this is another thought provoking
one. What if I pull my wiener through my balls and call it a donut
and this has no answer? So I'm going to need you guys to answer. I like the
template of of feather in my hat and call it macaroni.
Yeah, I like it. I like what if I like how open ended what if yeah, so what if
I think maybe you might change the world my young friend.
Yeah.
Here's an idea so powerful.
It's gonna, it's Steve Jobs level powerful.
That idea will cure your cancer.
What if I pulled my wiener through my balls and I called it a donut?
The I-donut.
Yeah.
It's mine.
And one more thing.
What if I put my wiener through my balls and I called it a donut?
Everyone at the keynote is just clapping.
Tim Cook is like comes out and yeah they get Johnny Ives in the fucking I heard
that was first we started with a wiener right I heard that was what killed him he
put it making the donut the donut the doughnut he thought the doughnut next up
is the doughnut here another Johnny Ives is just just there's like just perfect
close-up shots of just like a ball sack and then the dick just like flies
underneath it slow motion yeah this is an urgent question this one just came into
into the inbox. This is really important, so I need you guys to answer really fast.
My wife keeps sucking my thing every two days. What do I do hit her?
You said answer real? I don't know gave her my credit card damn
damn
right.
Here's an answer from Oliver pick up composer, twenty fourteen to present as a
sick ass fucking name. You should go to the police immediately. Why you ask
because if you refer to your penis as your thing, then you are clearly not an
adult, far too young to have a wife. Ergo, she is sexually assaulting a minor.
Not good. Hey, here's my impression of that fucking guy. Ergo, bitch. Ergo,
ergo's up my ass. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, she blows into my ass. This is a,
I found an interesting, somebody made an email group on the, yeah, and it's
called Farts, and the description is, "I'm looking for more teens into fart
and as one member it's KJ Copperhead and this person made two posts
one is I'm looking for a M or F who gets turned on by pooping forts and then and
their second post or email is I'm looking for someone who has attracted
the forts please get back with me who thinks sports are sexy please text me
fort so somebody wants to just like get a potential partner over get a bunch of
pillows make a fort yeah or it's a fortnight player maybe I don't think I
think it maybe is about farts no I think it's ports it would say farts if it was
about that's a good point yeah I actually also have found an email an
email group that a fan has made called peeing pants lovers and here's a comment
there's a question from a fan that's in the peeing pants lovers group that's
is asking is it okay for me to wet my shorts if I really can't hold it in any
longer and they've attached a lot of picture.
That's good or the answer has the answer says yes. I think it is okay. I'm
waiting for my diapers to come so I thought I would put on a pair of my
training pants and a pair of shorts and wet a little well. I failed I'm soaked,
but it felt great and there's a lot of pictures here. If you guys want to check
him out this person has a really cool body type.
Holy shit me
look at that back he looks like like Joaquin yeah yeah he looks exactly like
Joaquin in the Joker. It looks exactly like him dude. I have a question here from a fan
we need to be answering these questions by the way. We're jumping over so
answer this is it okay to piss yeah of course of course it's okay of course if
you can't hold it in who's gonna fuck it's nice your own penis at your own
shorts. If you can hold it in sometimes that's okay too yeah just let it go
here's one that that needs to be answered urgently no one someone they this fan
prefers to remain anonymous okay they sent in this question why does my uncle
dig in his ass and smell it simple answer because it's just feels right
yeah there's a there's an answer here from Clint Carl for retired former
retired entrepreneur which means he's an entrepreneur he's former
- He's literally retired.
- Yeah, so now he's back in the game.
They pulled him right when he thought he was out.
- Yeah, this must have pulled him out of the game
'cause this was in, he was 1983 to 2009.
- Oh wow.
- He's a former retired entrepreneur, he said,
because he has a deep-seated anal retentive needs
that were never met as a one-month-old baby.
(laughing)
'Cause caregivers most likely,
products of their own parents'
depressive drug-ridden environment,
had a comorbid poly drug and substance abuse
and undiagnosed mental health disorders.
They were never brought out
in his part of the family's lineage
and it began a self-perpetuating generation
and cycle of maladaptive behaviors,
thus leading each new offspring to be neglected
and not properly potty trained
and rarely had his diapers changed.
So when he grew up and landed in a foster care family,
they actually cared for him
and helped the boy overcome his anxiety
he became unable he became able to handle the stress of life I could find a
part-time job utilize newfound ways of self-care and could afford underwear and
habits begin to change his ass digging habit and smelling it was likely a
remnant of his early memories of anything anymore than the first sentence
of this yeah here's the thing big guy it smells good your butt smells good
everybody knows your butt smells hopefully you're not calling him
scratch and sift no seriously maybe his anus is itching and he needs to check
and see if his butt stinks who doesn't like to smell their own but it's cool to
do everyone loves their own yes smell here's an important question from a
listener that we need an answer to no answers yet can bread oil regrow my
thing I think it can I'm guessing that they meant to say beard oil so by
oil. I mean a hair that they have they may be I'm reading. I think they need to
retire. I think they're talking about bread oil and I think they're talking
about their downstairs thing yeah,
a lot of it rolled in the store and I think they're trying to might be a
little yeah, my right. I was the oil that they give you when the ed like a
restaurant to dip bread. It's got balsamic vinegar and oregano yeah, that
might work. I want to this is from truth finder. I want to sit on my
boyfriend's face and fart on it. How do I approach this?" And then here's just one
answer. Somebody did this, or somebody has a good strategy. "Sit on his
face while he's eating your pussy. When you get ready to come, let it rip. That
way you can say, 'He did such a good job eating your small pussy that you blew
him a kiss.' It always works for my wife when she farts while I'm eating her
your pussy. I blew you a can you imagine that just like getting farted on your
chin.
Well,
I have an important question from
a fan, a mother actually a fan of the show and a mother. Wow, then maybe you
can shed some light on Patrick. This motherly fan asks us, why does my son
keep my undies in a box?
You have any insight on this one?
No, I don't.
It's because your son's a freak.
Your son's a weird freak.
Maybe, I mean maybe the son's putting the undies in the box to protect them from
the underwear perverts.
From the underwear fairy.
From underwear perverts.
Oh, I was thinking of a magical creature.
Like Spongebob and Mr. Krabs.
This may be a question that the son asked.
That woman's son, our fan, I think they asked, "Can you tell me why haters take so much pleasure
in hurting people?"
I fucking hate haters, dude.
I actually love haters.
I hate haters, but I love my haters.
I love my haters.
I have a shirt from DGK that says this.
It says, "I love haters because they motivate me to be a better person and basically do
do all awesome, do incredibly dope shit,
kick incredibly dope shit.
- Do you kick dope shit to your haters
and they get mad icy at it?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Do you know what I hate more than haters?
- Suck MCs?
- Suck MCs and herbs.
- Oh, dude.
- I hate herbs.
- Oh, dude, the only time I want a herb is 11 of them.
- That's right.
- 11 of them on a--
- And maybe some spices, brother.
- Uh-huh, 11 herbs and spices in my damn--
- But I hate them herby-ass haters.
- Uh-huh.
(laughing)
I saw a picture of this one.
Oh my god, I did not open the answers to this question.
He's crying.
He's crying!
This fan made Cameron cry.
This is a question from a fan that I picked because the question is "How can I make someone to be my slave?"
Holy fuck.
There's an answer!
Dude, what the fuck.
Kimberly
You need to find a person like me and if I am as you desire then I submit to your training and allowing myself to be
Brainwashed until all I am and will ever be as a slave. Good luck in your search
Then it's a picture of the penguin from
Exactly like the penguin she has black lips uncle fester in a way
Wish both of them all the best of luck. Can you get can you give me?
I think I think the office needs a slave. I think we should hire her as a slave. Okay, Kimberly
Well, I do I do actually have some if you if we're looking for a slave. I have some good news from uh, oh really
I have a question here that that um that might be relevant. Is it true? This is from a fan even
it's very it's very nice of the fans to kind of predict that we might be looking
for a slave is it true that if you tell someone be my slave they become your
slave right away as if it were a magic incantation be my slave Oh be my slave
be my slave be my slave we had a great slave off
so we all are each other so how does this work then we can't boss each other
around it is guys George Sawyer says this is sorrows George Sawyer says this is
complete nonsense it is not true at all if it were that easy there would be
armies of slaves out there that's what well Jory he's using one George source
is using a fake name so that people don't know that it's him and - he's only
saying that so people don't know catch onto his mind control well that's what
he that's what he does with everyone yeah he makes everyone his slave and he
He doesn't want a secret to get out. Is it rude that my boyfriend put his naked
ball sack on my head while I was sitting down and not looking?
No. It's certainly rude.
It's not rude. It's certainly rude, but it's not unwelcome.
And Steve says, "People are getting so offended now."
I have a ball sack related question for the fan.
I got quite a couple ball sack ones. Let me throw this one in there real quick
quick and then we can maybe do a
ball sack lightning around.
There's this thing on my nuts that
is blue and is like going into the
nut sack, but I can't get it out.
It's kind of sticking out. What is
this and is it bad?
This is blue. It's blue. Blue is
that's the scariest color for
something to be absolutely growing
out of your necrosis of your balls.
That's yeah. This person says what
should I do with my ball sack smells
like salt and vinegar and and Marco
says make a salad lol oh make a salad with here's one I'm not gonna get into the
answers but this is good for I think for us mm-hmm what changed in your life
after becoming a martial artist just the way people looked at me I would say it
saved my life yeah yeah yeah because I would say health what was I would say
personally I have heart failure idiopathic dilated cardiomyopathy plus
an extreme number of irregular heartbeats as you guys know yeah this
diagnosis means I have a life expectancy of six to eight years and the diagnosis
was made 18 years ago when I was six years old yeah I take the pills that are
prescribed and I have a pacemaker and I and I practice Tai Chi basically every
day I'm convinced that a large number amount of credit goes to Tai Chi for
keeping me alive I doubt that I will ever get into a fight because who would
want to pick a fight with a gray-haired overweight person who is obviously over
75 that's me but I'm winning the fight for my life good for you man thank you I
I actually think becoming a martial artist actually changed my mental health.
You might think it was for the better, but it actually changed it for the
worst because now I walk around and I see everybody on the street and I think
I can kill this person with a single punch and it makes me depressed and
anxious. Think about my power. That's a good point. Yeah. I just use it
for chopping wood.
Just you know if I don't have an axe handy. Going up to the cabin and just
smashing your head against logs and then like getting a concussion
hallucinating that you've chopped all the wood.
I uh this next question from a fan um it was answer um let me let me just get
into it let me just say it um i want to have sex with my maid but i'm
scared i'm young and muscular will my maid agree should i start masturbating
or flashing my dick in front of her and there was an answer here from Daniel but
he deleted it. Daniel got in trouble. So that led me to find a man
named Steel Rod, it says related answers Steel Rod and he's created a
judgment-free space for anybody of age called pick/tips for jerk-off
fantasies Desi plus Bollywood and there's three questions in here there's
none of them are answered. This is a fan of the show, Steel Rod. I didn't
come for the last nine days can anyone help me come with their pics or DMs?
And which of these non-Indian celebs turns you on the most? This real quick I
just I want to read this one this is from an anonymous fan they say can I
I open my ball sack like a bag of chips
and then someone responds. It depends and that answer is from
spider man.
I have a question here. Is it possible to get a girlfriend using magic? Yes,
yes, I would say yes, there I have a few answers here. This one is from
Joshua George, which I think great man. This sounds like this might be his
personal story of his life, but he says learn magic get guda at it go to an
orphanage put on show ask the sweet old lady running the orphanage to be your
girlfriend. Yep, wow yeah, and I have another answer here. That's more of like
life wisdom from dress swami vaidya nathan chandra sikar born in Tamil Nadu
and worked in many places all over India. So experienced knows a lot about
about life experience. Don't use magic use logic magic will mislead you to
that the GF is out of this world and disappoint you.
Logic will make you accept her as she is,
as no one is perfect.
Magic will jack your expectations sky high,
only to bring you down to earth later in a crash.
Logic will keep you grounded and stable.
- Damn.
- Logic is basically a kind of magic.
- Logic is like better than magic, I think.
- All right.
You're thinking logically.
- How can I get a blowjob from my mum?
(laughing)
And Nicola Green, who's--
- A fan of the show.
- Accolade is a mom of two, says,
"Now it's wrong with a blowjob."
(laughing)
And then related question,
this one doesn't have any answers, but it's for you guys.
If your son said he was feeling stressed out
and then took out his penis and asked you to suck it,
would you?
- No.
- But he's stressed.
(laughing)
But he's really stressed.
He's like--
- Not until he gets his chores done.
Okay, all right, all right, listen.
Your son, picture this, your son straight A's
his entire life, right?
You've been putting him in special schools,
like he's straight A's at like--
- So my special son is stressed.
- He's special, but he gets straight A's, right?
And he comes to you and he gets an A minus, right?
And he's about to break down
when he hands you the report card,
and he's like, "Dad."
- Dad. - Dad.
Dad! Dad! Dad!
The reason why...
Dad's failing in school, Dad.
The reason why he's so stressed...
Son, I'll suck your dick.
Welp, Bobby.
Goddammit, Bobby, get that dick over here.
Dang it, Bobby, pull out your penis and let me suck it.
So yeah, that's an answer then.
It's a yes.
So yeah, if your son's stressed out enough...
If your son is Bobby Hill and you're Hank Hill...
Yeah.
...it's a good group.
You might be a redneck.
yeah i think it's a good reason the yeah
uh... here's a question from uh... so this is from a fan who i think started
to write
one question then realized how it had sounded and kind of uh...
changed courses in the middle of it but i think we all know what's really going
on here but this is from uh... a fan of the show
i need some dark and torturous commands to have my slave do in this new story
i'm writing to someone who can't please help with fresh ideas
what is
there's an all-new
and what is what does it look like to suck a penis well i think i like this
and it's just a a woman who has a uh... so that's a that's a part of the
yeah yeah
sucking a penis
uh... this person says what would you do if someone walked up to you touch your
private parts below your pants and walked away
and pre a matthew has a phd from bangalore university says he would be
sorry he ever did such a thing to me
kind of a samurai answer. Yeah here's a question here from a fan I've just
talked about Steel Rod. Steel Rod well this is a question submit there's a
question from a fan Harley Quinn FC which I can only imagine stands for
football club. You have to. Harley Quinn football club how could I seduce my maid
slash servant to have sex with me and I didn't realize Steel Rod's accolade is
is that they fapped a ton and they say that i picked up her phone once and saw
she had porn in one of the chrome tabs, asked her about it and the rest is
history.
This is the last one that i had in my section of the inbox. Okay, the advice
column. This is a fan who wrote in and asked what is it like to have sex with
you and somebody's already answered. Barnard Handel, oh
has answered, whose accolades professional guy
as answer is laying for that. I mean yeah, that name is a bar, a guy,
sex with me is great. I give you toe curling orgasm with my massive shlong
and then I deposit ample quality quantity of hot spooge onto your body,
where is ever thou like it's
pretty good. Yeah, I just got one more sure I have one more after this,
- Nicola Bjork, I'm 15 years old and I just cummed.
(laughing)
- Is there a question mark after that?
It's just a statement?
- No, it's just a statement.
- It's a statement.
- Okay. - That's great.
- So this question was sent in,
but I think there's a question,
another question under it to kind of like,
I think they kind of regretted saying this.
This question is from an anonymous fan. They said, "What is the most
inappropriate thing a cousin has done to you?" So they start to try to start the
question here, get the conversation going, start the discourse. And then an ad by
the penny hoarder immediately under that says, "What are the biggest money secrets
that rich people keep from us?"
[Laughter]
The trick is to start a podcast. You make a lot of money. You make a million dollars.
dollars. Most inappropriate thing a cousin did, won't say. No thank you.
Yep. Alright. Thank you guys for sending in all the questions. We love you guys.
Go to some family therapy sessions, a lot of you, definitely. And we have to announce,
oh yeah, we're adding another show in Los Angeles, an all ages show to our tour. And
all of the people and a show in San Francisco. I don't remember the dates,
but they'll be on the website along with tons of really fun game. Well with lots
of HTML 5 games swag poop.com slash shows swag poop.com slash haunted - house swag
poop.com slash squirrel - bubble - shooter yeah swag poop.com slash Kings -
gold check all that out yeah Christmas - mystery so the the all-ages show it
will be at the El Cid in Los Angeles on May 20th
and the San Francisco show,
don't know if that's all ages,
that will be on May 22nd at Amado's.
- Amado's, sick.
All right, see you there.
- Bye. - Bye.