come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
you're a scrap monster
beef and dosing
we got a big deal
i thought we should run
you already said i thought the kills and you know it's a repulsor
what are you guys doing to a listing
what reuben
what is that we've ever just one
This is not gonna help me understand it better.
- Galbata dee vodern.
- Gakana, got that one?
- Gakana, Gakana!
(singing in foreign language)
- Is that how the song goes?
I don't remember it doing that.
(singing in foreign language)
(singing)
Is that really how the song-
Wait, you just said turkey sandwich, that's a real word.
(singing)
Have I been wrong about what I thought was called Twinkle Twinkle Little Star?
What's it called?
(singing)
Gherban turkey sandwich gobo wandia wow my life is my my life is different
Sorry, we've been listening to a lot of seagross. Hmm. Who is seagross? It's um they sing that song spread your love and fly
They sing that song twinkle twinkle little star. Yeah. Oh really?
Damn, I'm sure that's not how you say that fucking band's name, and they're gonna damn little made of it's so they have a made-up
Language a band that sings entirely in a made-up language
What yeah?
I've never heard one of their songs though.
Really?
I just know that about them.
I've heard that name, I've heard Seeger Rose before.
I've heard their name before, I think they probably like...
I thought it was Sugar Ross.
They probably like performed at like Boston Calling or something.
That's the type of place that I would have seen their name.
Dude, that's like one of those...
I didn't know they had a made up language though.
That's one of those like millennial bands that like everyone in like a dude who's probably
like 32 now and he was like our age was like I just saw them it's like one of
the greatest shows you'll ever go to. Yeah I is they they they they I feel
like they're in the same category in my brain as a band like and I don't know if
I'm pronouncing this right Toro y Moi. Toro y Moi is very different.
I love Toro y Moi. It might just be because they have weird names. Yeah yeah. But in my brain it's like oh
those are the same band. In my brain both of those bands are centered
around banjos no torui was like like they were like the the start of the chill
wave thing I gotta check out reacting Benjamin they weird as hell
yeah dude they weird as shit she don't know when she need Darwin she don't
think it Japanese band they are yeah yeah she need Owen and fucking yeah
yeah what's that other band oh oh oh my god oh my god cred yeah yeah yeah oh my
God that song it's been a wheel a that's not that's not it is good
there's dying Ned kicks out they're actually really good yeah hey where are
they sweet I'm bad didn't but it didn't a bunch of bands do a similar version of
their of their songs for the city Perry did yeah Katy Perry did it so did my
hot and cold. Mike Posner. Oh yeah. You mean Katy Perai? Yeah. And Mickey Posner.
Posner. Mickey Posner. Mickey Posner. Yeah. I bet Mike Posner is like huge in some
like like like you know how like the Bloodhound gang is really big in Russia.
I didn't know that. Yeah I bet he's huge in Sim City. He is huge in Sim City yeah. Did you uh did you know
that Mike Mike Posner when he did his one song and then he got real rich. He did
another way to get took a pill in Ibiza. He but after I took a pill in Ibiza
after that or before that he went he walked across the entire country like
Forrest Gump. Really? Yeah he went full Gump. Damn. Why? Yeah he just was like I
I'm I need to be I need to do something awesome. So it's funny that that is like
he did it cuz he's like in there like Zen Buddhism stuff and he's like let's yeah
and then he was like I'm gonna take a pill with the Vichy yeah which by the
way pretty bad taste to put out a song after a Vichy died of that was before
was it no it's after no it was before it had to be after did it before he died in
like 2015 that's I took a pill in Ibiza 2014 no Vichy died in 2016 cuz I do as
it was I swear the first casualty of the Trump I'm gonna go I took a bill in his
- If BeTha came out like two years ago.
- No.
You're just like, literally,
I looked at a picture of myself from seventh grade
and saw the time stamp in the corner was 2010,
and I got so freaked out.
- 2016, I took a pill in a BeTha.
- Then Avicii must have died 2018.
- Let's see.
- No, I think it was 2016, wasn't it?
- Avicii, Swedish DJ, born 1989, died 2018.
I bet you feel stupid as hell.
- I just said that.
- Whoa. - What?
I said 2018. No you didn't. You were right. No you, no yeah I was right. Oh my god. No not you.
Yeah I was right. Not you. Because it was, it was that, it was that, it was June and it was like
Chester Bennington and Avicii. Yeah yeah I remember everyone. Chester Bennington, I feel like Chester
Bennington died ten years ago. No. Really? That wound is still fresh. Damn. It's still a very fresh
wound. Yeah. Not for me. Yeah. I'm glad you know. You know who killed him. You know, you know Avicii
and Chester Bennington are jamming together in hell right now. That's right. You know Chester.
Rockers go to hell yeah when Chester Bennington died he turned into liquid
metal like really bad like really 2000 cc yeah he went down a shower during it
went down like a like a snake like a snake yeah I heard he died exactly like
his death in in saw seven where all his skin got ripped off in a car oh yeah I
heard that he was in saw seven yeah he's cool dude he is all his skin gets ripped
ripped off and he screams he goes like like his like his Lincoln Park scream.
Oh my freaking skin! It's peeled from my bones!
He literally does like just his singing, he just like he's like like pull his
skin is getting peeled off he goes like. I can't stand Lincoln Park I hate
screamo stuff. Really? Yeah. I hate screamo and I hate emo because it's gay.
I mean something about emo. Something about gay having guys having long hair.
Screamo is basically about who can be screaming about having a pussy the best.
You're so stupid, because when it comes to Screamo, some artists like Chester
Bennington, they may have the screams of a devil, but they have the singing of an
angel. I don't even care. And the rapping of a gangster.
Linkin Park was, Mike Shinoda was basically the biggest thug on earth.
Pretty much, if you ask me. Why is he not in prison for being such a gangster thug, dude?
Did you see him? You should have heard his side project. Oh yeah, there's a lot of
song about being in prison for a large population of people being in prison for
being gangsta thugs. Yeah. And he named his song after- he named his
band after making a fort with children. What was he on? Styles of Beyond?
No, Fort Minor. Fort Minor. Yeah, he also named a song after what my
grandma can't do anymore. Remember the name. I forgot that was him. I thought that
song was called 10% look for a split second I was like that's what it's called
yeah I know those songs were swag was it am I misremembering this is there a
Linkin Park music video where they're in a giant sink no okay you're thinking of
Gnarls Barkley you know Gnarls Barkley gone daddy gone where there bugs I'm
your thing of the movie flushed away
very specific memory of a Lincoln Park music video where they're in a giant
like bathroom sink and they're all really small and they're singing like
the truth you can't I think I think you're thinking it was supposed to look
like like a ruin an ancient ruin maybe I thought that it was yeah I don't know
you thought it was insane yeah cuz I mean that early 2000 CG yeah I was all
they do have a but yeah I feel like they're probably a three different music
videos where they look like they're in a sing. Yeah. The thing about Linkin Park
that sets them apart from other bands is most other bands will be too scared to
perform for Transformers. Yeah, they actually. Dude, their songs in
Transformers are so sick. Dude, going to see the new Transformers
movie every year on my birthday and be like damn what Linkin Park song are they
gonna put in next. The first Transformers, the first time I ever had caffeine. Yeah. I stayed up
to go see it at midnight. Dude, those movies are so good. And then I sat, I had a
small Red Bull and then I sat in my bed until 8 in the morning just like shaking
my legs like that. I had a time, my dad took me out of school one day and took
me to this like skate demo outside of Snowboard Jones in Manchester and I had
my first Red Bull there and my dad is like yeah it won't kill you. I was nine
years old had my first Red Bull. I was so annoying for the rest of the day.
Honestly now that I'm thinking about it I think that maybe that Red Bull ruined my
my life. Me too dude. I'm like that Red Bull, maybe one of the extreme sports
for
my first Red Bull until probably like three years ago. Really, I was always a
I feel like I got I never I didn't I don't think I had I was in the cafe, but
I never I never drank energy drinks until I met you. Yeah, only coffee. Yeah
damn yeah. I mean I still don't drink. I don't I didn't doesn't I'd maybe had
ten energy drinks in my life. I could probably still yeah. I was probably
- I'm still gonna count on two hands
how many energy drinks I've had in my life, yeah.
- I've had a lot now.
- I didn't get into energy drinks
until I transferred into Emerson.
I was like, I wouldn't drink coffee,
I was on Adderall anyway, so I figured I don't need this.
- That's the thing too, yeah.
- It's like I was on Adderall too.
- I feel like an energy drink probably would've killed me.
- When I was like 16, when I was like 16 or 17,
I would like, I wasn't, I was like somebody
who like tried to be, like I was like,
yeah, I would smoke cigarettes, but I was like,
energy drinks, that shit's so bad for you.
And then like, once I turned like 19, 18, 19,
I was like, everything that I like did in high school
was like, yeah, fuck it, like I don't care anymore,
like I'll just like drink like two Monsters a day.
- Yeah. - Yeah, I was--
- Dude, I was, like it's documented on this show,
Like I was up to like two monster zeroes a day.
- That's not that crazy.
I feel like you used to drink a bang, right?
- Yeah, well there was that week where I was drinking rain
and I would just have panic attacks.
- Yeah, that's too much.
That's too much stuff.
- Too much too fast 'cause I fucking chug every,
like look at how gone this coffee is already.
- That coffee's gone as hell.
- Yeah, you're supposed to drink a coffee
throughout the day.
You're not supposed to like--
- That's not true.
- You're lying.
- Yeah, I am?
- You're, stop lying to me.
- I thought you were supposed to drink it
throughout the day. - You're supposed to
drink it in the morning. - Fuck no.
- Yeah.
- I had a really, this morning I woke up
and I had a cup of coffee and I was like,
it like made a noted difference in my day.
Which I haven't had that in a while.
- Yeah. - Like a cup of coffee
I'm like, whoa.
- I love chugging a mug of hot coffee.
- Dude, just drink. - It's the best.
- Taking one sip of it. - And just feel,
just the worst feeling of your life for one hour.
- You can feel just a pump shotgun of shit
just like in your ass.
- That's what I, yeah. - Just like, yeah.
- And it's just fully loaded. - It's so sick, dude.
- You walk into the bathroom.
boom it I mean it's literally a second yeah it's a five second scatter shot yeah
all over the toilet every cleaned out yeah but the toilet isn't and there's
just a black like there's a little one a little black spot above the that one
spot where the water doesn't hit yeah basin mm-hmm
y'all don't get your toilet it gets on the bottom of the scene you know that's
how explosive - it's on the bottom of the seat yeah dude I'll pull the seat up to
go pee and there will be like a ring of my shit all the way around ever looked
at the bottom of the toilet. I mean, I live with three men.
That's true. So you always keep the seat down.
Yeah. That makes sense. Yeah.
So what's the thing girls get mad at?
If you leave the seat up. If you flush because they want to look at it.
Yeah, they want to inspect your bed. They get mad if you flush.
They can tell by your poop if you're cheating on them. They can.
It has your wedding ring in it.
You're like, "Oh my god, a hot girl!" And you ate your wedding ring.
Oh, I think you're getting fingered by a guy joke.
I would never do that.
That's gay.
It's like when witches in medieval times could read animals' intestines to tell the future.
A girl can read a poop to tell the past.
All women are witches.
That's actually true.
These are the daughters of the witches.
I don't think they're witches.
I think they're queens.
Yeah, evil queens.
Yeah, these are the daughters of the witches that we couldn't burn.
So let's finish the job.
you know what I'm saying? You know here's something I was thinking about the
other day. You know so you know snow white, so you know the story, you know
how like the evil queen yeah, the evil queen has like a magic mirror and every
day she goes to the magic mirror and she's like who's the fairest of all
who's the most beautiful woman in the land and I'm familiar yeah, the magic
mirror says it's you and what
one day snow white turned eighteen
- That's a good point. - The magic mirror changed its answer.
- Yeah, well let's be real. - What was the difference on that day?
Was it her eighteenth birthday? That was the only explanation I could think of.
Did she do her hair a slightly different way that day?
- I mean, let's be completely- - And that just gave her the leg up.
What is the real practical difference to this mirror?
The mirror's never gonna fuck her.
- Yeah. - It doesn't care.
- Also, it's medieval times. - Unless you know it's magic.
- It's medieval times. - Unless you know it knows objectively.
- She must have turned like thirteen, actually. - Yeah.
- That's true. - It's way worse.
- That mirror. - And the mirror's probably like a demon, so-
the mirror and the mirror was you know the mirror like checking in every day
that's the thing the Queen goes up to the mirror every day and acid and it's like
scan the case also fairing every pussy in the world
fairest the fairest so through the whitest is the yeah yeah who's the white
is no way to fair if I'm going by rhythm game standards should be who's the who's
the perfect of them all yeah we need black as night the new Disney Princess yeah
what's no pitch black yeah like blackface version of snow white they're like yeah
got like a really bad snow black. I think it was called coal black. I was gonna say
that
I said that's probably better than what I was gonna say. I was thinking cold black.
Why do you have the why do you have an inside the knowledge of race parities
princess ologist really? I just you know ever since I was a kid. I thought
princesses are beautiful. So no I just read it. I just tried to research
- Which princesses are mighty fair?
- Which princesses are problematic?
Which ones have done certain things?
- I'm glad I didn't go to Disney as a kid,
speaking of princesses. - Me too, yeah.
- Glad I didn't go, 'cause if I saw the Disney princesses
at like age three or four-- - Oh, you could not
hold me back.
- No, no, I probably would've turned out
like a much gayer child.
- I would've knocked him with a tree branch
and put him in a bag. - It was funny to go to--
- I would've been there. - What's the one in Florida?
- I would've asked my mom if I could land there.
- I don't even know. - It's probably Disney World
or something. - It's Disney World?
I went to go into that the first time last year. I mean like this sucks ass
Like rock I've been wanting to make a Disney and Universal trip as a grown man, dude
It's so sick. I'm so
Good. I want to see dude. I don't give a I like roller coasters
I want dark right the mummy right VelociCoaster will blow your mind
I want to get in a room and be and be transported you got to go you got to go on the mummy ride
I want to go so mummy ride Gringotts the spider-man dark ride spider-man dude really good
But I'm telling you a velocicoaster
Do we got again?
You can go
No, that's universal, okay, that's the one with the loss of clear and universal and I agree it's motorbike adventure do that one fuck
I've always wanted to be on his back. You're not on his back. You're on his bike
So yeah, you're all you get it on my bike you get to choose if you're on a motorcycle
Motorbike motor back adventure or in the sidecar you would be in the sidecar. Why would I be?
What's there about is I'm loyal like a dog. Yes. Yes, I would
Your brain goes to what cousin it's I guard dog you watch too many cartoons. I mean have you ever seen a real sidecar?
Yeah, yeah
I don't think so
No dogs with goggles
I honestly think I still think sidecars are for dogs.
Why would you want to be embarrassed if you were if you were a human relating in a sidecar
and dogs?
It does make the riding the motorcycle way easier.
Yeah you can't fall over and if you do like a training wheel.
You just land on your damn dog.
Yeah.
It's a fucker.
Right.
That's a good point.
I almost got Phil a backpack to put him in.
- Yeah.
- But I was like, dude.
- Dude, you're becoming way worse than I am with pets.
- I know, man.
I'm gonna be like, it sucks, bro.
I got boots, he got boots, man.
- You got your dog boots?
- Dude, he hurts his paw.
- You have to get your dog boots.
- He hurts his paws when he--
- That's a normal thing to get a dog.
- You know, he came back from a walk.
- In the city, in New York, yeah.
- In general.
- 'Cause there's a needle on the ground.
- 'Cause salt hurts their feet in the winter.
- He came back from a walk a couple days ago,
and I wipe his paws when we get inside and I was I wiped on a saw blood
immediately. I was like we're going right now. We're getting him boots and now I
and I got a booze. He has does he does he walk funny with the boots on you? I'm
going to show you a video. I mean I was it was two at straight hours of me
losing my mind walking around. He walks like yeah, it is to these flapping his
shit. That's how I walk when I put shoes on me too. Yeah, it's not natural dude.
You know what I you know what I realize I haven't done in a while is put my
bare feet on like grass. Yeah. I feel like I need to do that. No, it feels really good.
That feels so good. This is very specific to my childhood. My room in the basement had
a popcorn wall, you know, like the popcorn ceiling, like the little, like with the spackle
on it. I would like rub my foot on that. Like it was a pumice stone, dude. I'd sit on the
opposite wall and just rub my foot on it. Oh yeah. God damn, that's disgusting. It felt
so good in your fucking cat comes and licks it ah no no because it was it was
on the stairs so no one could really like I would mom comes and licks it my mom
would not come in like it she did did she cleaned it off oh god you're just
rubbing your dead fucking foot skin dude I remember felt so good I remember my
better felt really good yeah dude I remember my dad at one time I touched his
heel changed my life oh do you feel now oh my god it is my dad's heel is a is a
is volcanic yeah see ever see like I remember angle I feel like I have a
similar like seeing well like just my dad's like toenail and it's being like
yeah whoa like my dad's toe is like is like bright and yellow like when they're
they're like corrugated - dude just realizing like your dad's like not
taking care of his damn feet yeah well the two there are two epiphany the first
one is like when you're yeah you see your dad's toenail for the first time one
is when you see your dad naked in the shower.
- And the second one is when he smells butt.
- And then the second one is like 10 years later
you realize, oh shit, wait, that means my toenail's
gonna be like that too.
- Yeah, and now my toes look exactly like that,
I'm not gonna lie. - Yeah, it's crazy.
- My toes look pretty, I take good care of my feet.
- Do you guys remember-- - I don't,
I spit all over my feet of poop and pee all over them.
- Do you guys remember when your dad,
he would bend over to take the trash out
and you'd sniff his butt?
(laughing)
Do you guys remember that?
- No.
- Yeah.
- You guys remember sneaking a little peek?
- Uh-huh.
- That your dad smelled.
Hey dad, take credit cards, 'cause my nose is a credit card,
and then you slide your nose up his butt crack.
Yeah, like a credit card.
Like a credit card would?
Yeah.
It takes chip.
(laughing)
Yep.
Yes.
All right, so we gotta talk about the news, man,
the big news that happened the other day
that everybody's talking about.
Oh, everybody wants it.
Everybody wants to hear our take on this issue.
Everybody wants to hear about what we think
about Trump getting a hole in one.
- Yeah, that was pretty big news.
- I think it's awesome and I'm really happy for him.
- I think it's cool, yeah.
He obviously practiced a lot.
- Did you see the video of him walking up
to get the ball out of the hole?
- No. - No.
- It's so cool. - I actually didn't see this.
- Trump got a hole in one.
- You show me the video. - I didn't see it either.
- Dude, I'll find it, yeah.
It's like-- - I really wanna see this.
- Dude, he walks up and he's just like--
- At Trump Links?
- No, it was at a Trump golf course.
It's the only place he goes. - Yeah, Trump Links.
- No, it wasn't that one.
He has like fucking 50 of them.
Wow, that's so cool. He should be president.
He honestly, I watched this and I was like, we have to get him back, dude.
I hope he runs again.
He's like, it definitely recharged him.
Yeah.
Like doing this, you know.
Oh, fuck.
He should, dude, he should play Frolf.
Did I not like it, bro? Oh, God.
Dude, Trump should play Frolf.
True.
He should be, Trump should be an unlockable character in Ribbit King Plus 2 if they ever make it.
I would love to see Trump playing mini golf and getting really confused.
Oh, yeah.
Hitting the golf ball into the windmill over and over and over and over and over and over.
What is this? I can't even get into it.
It's broken. The windmill's broken.
The windmill is broken? I can't...
The golf course is broken. I can't open it.
He walks... That's a good impression.
You look like Gilbert. I know.
I can't open up the windmill!
Folks, you're not going to believe this. The ball did a loop-de-loop.
The ball went around the loop-de-loop.
Is that... that's not real...
That's John Daly.
It's there.
He picks it up.
you know everybody comes walking out of the way.
I got a picture with you sir.
Just the fattest guys in the biggest polos of all time.
It's so funny that he says it's there because you can tell he's just losing
object permanence. He just doesn't, he wasn't sure it was going to be there.
It's there. He didn't even hit a ball. Yeah. I uh, uh, dude, hole in one.
I mean, as a golfer dude, that's, that's insane. That's like, I mean like you can
do a lot of presidents have a lot of achievements, a hole in one.
He might be the first president to ever have a hole-in-one.
Yeah, that's true.
Hole-in-one is like most...
Well, that's not true.
Who has a hole-in-one?
Obama.
Does he?
Yeah, was that wedding?
That's right.
He's standing up to salute me right now.
He's saluting me.
(humming)
Take your hat off.
- Yeah.
- That's a hero.
That's a hero.
- I took Obama.
Obama, if you listen to this,
your playlist last year sucked.
- Yep.
- Obama may have got a--
- I don't think you even listen to all the,
who has time to listen to 30 songs in a year?
- Obama may have got a hole in one,
but I heard Bill Clinton put his one in a hole.
- Yes, sir.
(laughing)
- Yep.
- Uh-huh.
- We have a take no prisoners attitude.
- I want a cigar.
- Yeah, hey.
- Did he really put a cigar in her thing?
- Yeah, and it was on fire and she exploded.
- She smoked it through her thing.
- Yeah, just take a dynamite.
She just was so stupid, she thought it was a cigar.
- She's not stupid.
- Monica Lewinsky?
- I'm a huge Monica defender, dude.
- Yeah, I bet you wanna defend her.
- I love her, dude.
- I wanna defund her.
- No.
- Defund Monica Lewinsky.
- I'm gonna give her as many funds as I can.
- I'm trying to keep her from ever getting a fund again.
- Monica, if you're listening to this, open invitation.
You can come on the show whenever you want.
- I'm trying to defund her.
one-on-one interview me and Monica Woods. I know where that's going. Do you do you
like me? Yeah, you just act like she's like trying to fuck you the whole time.
You're like a very serious woman. Yeah, yeah, you're like are we doing this or
what? Listen, the cameras, they're just for show. They're off. Dude, she's
sick though. She's got like, she's got a lot of good jokes about what
happened really yeah also very good what kind of jokes yeah what you do about
being about being taken advantage of like Bill Clinton she's like um yeah
that happened yeah that's not bad that's not bad at all yeah yeah maybe we should
have her on we should I mean I we got to get Trump on we got to get
that'd be so good that would be awesome the trip I mean Trump went on some other
Trump went on some stupid podcast, some like video podcast. Yeah.
The fucking, like the alt-right Mr. Beast. Yeah we could get the Nard Boys or
something. We could get that dude. Is it the Nard Boys? I have no idea. I don't know what
you're talking about. We're like the alt-right what? We're the alt-right
Chapo. Yeah we're like, exactly. So we could get Trump. Yeah if we just told him
maybe we could convince them like this is an interview about your golf
performance. Dude we're a golf podcast. Yeah we could be like yeah. Do you think they paid
Trump though? I think they probably paid for his appearance. No. No. He doesn't do, he
doesn't care. He's not like that. He's literally the richest man in the world.
There's more money than anybody on earth. I mean he just like he knows what's up like he
understands the community. He does everything for the culture. Yeah it's not
- It's not about money, he knows that.
- That's true, he loves the culture.
- He loves the culture, yeah, the community.
- Have you seen, there's not a lot of photos of it,
'cause he's always in a suit, he's always bossed up,
but when he's in his plain clothes,
like him going to the store, he's in full Ame Leon door.
But when he's at the club, when he's in the bape hoodie--
- He turns up. - Oh my God.
- He's got the full zip.
- Stewie pajama pants.
Trump in the bait putty in the Stewie pajama pants.
He takes a lot of inspiration from Luke Blauvod.
And the Teva sandals.
(laughing)
He had, there was like--
And the cowboy hat.
The cat underneath, 360 waves.
Perfectly lavish, 360 waves.
Dude, did you see that picture of him in 7-Eleven
with the astronaut space suit on?
Yeah, dude.
That was so sick, dude.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's funny, but it's also like fire.
low-key lurking the Kanye to the forums. He's on the clothing. He was apparently
gonna be one of the members of Brockhampton but they just moved forward
without him because he didn't want to move to LA. You see when he went to the
Grammys and he was dressed as a perfect cube. Mm-hmm. So sick. Gold cube. Yeah.
And people were like who's that? People thought it was CeeLo Green. Yeah.
Yeah. Dude I mean and speaking of like outfits he wore when he I I don't know if
you guys saw this but this is like I mean it's a little different but he was using
in the Bruno Mars skin in Fortnite.
- He was.
- He was like, he was headshotting fools left and right.
- Yeah, he was actually kind of sick with the sticks.
- Yeah.
- Do you guys remember when he was,
he was like, had that pro smash career for a minute?
- Oh my God.
- He went to Evo?
- Damn, I forgot about that.
- People forget that about Trump.
- Yeah.
- People forget about Trump too.
He had like a guest trick in the Illegal Civ 2.
he did a south flip down Wilshire and he also had a speed run of Civ 5 that was
there was a world record was in mr. show him and fucking Maynard dude he was in
fucking Pucifer and mr. show oh yeah no it's Trump did a south flip down
Hollywood high really it was yeah that's crazy people forget that about him yeah
do you ever when he was on Broadway mm-hmm he played Harry Potter that was
like Harry Potter and the cursed child touching ass performance I know yeah it
that was magical to the curse. I did yeah when he did that whole thing at the end
about being the cursed child. Oh my God, I was like do he actually believes he's
him for a second there yeah, like this guy is like mind. This is like the
actor of our generation yeah, yeah, I mean he's just like done everything like
I just I don't I saw him ever up one hundred times outside my apartment. Do
you remember when he saw a real back flip remember when he did the robot yeah
remember when he was a row and out and everybody came on wild and out was so
he was he did not get kicked out of the classroom was Nick Cannon tossed his
hair Nick Cannon did toss his hair but he was like so cool about it yeah dude you
know is actually like crazy though it was like one of the feel like one of the
first times in history and when did this when he made that crab leg aspic on
chopped junior that was like that just like that was because the game he made
so he made it so like the crab legs hurt we're sticking out of the aspic yeah so
it's like it looked like a jello crab or like an alien yeah yeah and he called it
he called it Trump's alien delight.
(laughing)
- And he won.
- Yeah, he won the whole thing.
- It was pretty damn impressive, dude.
- It was nuts.
- I mean, he did the whole,
he ran the whole spectrum of food competition shows, okay?
- Definitely.
- On Triple G, let's be real, he crushed it, okay?
If one, it was him against Kenji in the final,
and then he, you know, he kinda,
I think he had the better dish.
I think they just gave it to Kenji
'cause he had a book coming out.
- That's true, yeah.
- You know, if I'm being real.
He was on, I mean, he was on Iron Chef,
You know, but who beats Bobby Flay?
- Right.
- Nobody, except Trump.
- He was also--
- He made ice spaghetti.
(laughing)
- Yeah, dude, so it was crazy 'cause it's like,
you think he wouldn't have enough time
to put the spaghetti in the ice cube trays
with the ice, but like, his whole thing was,
he already had the spaghetti pre-cooked
and then he put it in the ice cube trays,
put the water on it, and then just--
- Blast freezer.
- Stood there with his arms crossed
while it froze in the freezer.
is really remember when he was a contestant on the bachelorette and he
won and then he's like i didn't even like you anyway i was just pretending
said marty marty happily married to malani a you know yeah yet but he did
where fake mustache all times and no one knew it was him yeah
he was he said his name was donald scrum
dot said everyone's like you don't normally say your last name on this
because i don't think
and i think we use donald i different but he kept saying i'm donald scrum
Yeah, you know what I want so badly dude. I want I want like a
Curb with him. Oh my god, wouldn't that be so
They do right yeah, they did no
Enthusiasm with with Larry David no, I'm thinking about the one with Anthony and a maniacs. No, I want a real one
I want actual Donald Trump. Yeah to do curb that would be sick. He's so sick. That would be really good
Maybe I'll just start doing curb. Yeah. Yeah.
You throw that at me. I don't know. Who cares? Cue the music.
I'm the main character. You can't throw stuff. I'm doing curb now. No,
you're not doing curb. I'm doing curb. Larry! Larry I'm stuck!
Both my friends think they're doing curb. Oh, I'm Jeff Garland now.
I'm Jeff Garland now.
Fine, I'll be Leon.
I'm stuck in the dishwasher, Larry!
What?
He's doing this thing, I'm like...
I don't know, do I fuck him?
I don't know!
How do you get stuck in a dishwasher?
I don't know, Larry!
I'm stuck in a dishwasher, though!
How stuck are you, though?
Oh, that'd be so funny.
Larry the Kerbal Guy.
Larry the Kerbal Guy?
- You know the aliens that make spaceships?
- Yeah.
- Larry the Kerbal.
- Larry the Kerbal guy walking up to his stepmom
who's stuck in the dryer.
How stuck are you?
- I'll just, I'll just--
- Your big boobs are stuck in the dryer.
- I'll just pull you out, I'll just pull you out.
- I'll just pull you, I can't, no, I have to go to the,
yeah, I gotta go do the thing.
Yeah, no, at the jewelry store, I gotta go get the jewels.
- Come on, Larry, I'm stuck.
- No, no, no, I'll call, I'll call, I'll call.
I'll give him a call.
and he leaves and then leon and then he's like what
yeah what did you she was stuck in a dryer. Why did you fuck her listen larry
I love the eats all day all day and all night. I've only started watching it and
it's so funny. I only watch episodes if my roommates are watching them. You
should watch every episode that has anything before leon take it or leave it.
they replace his wife with Leon it's like the biggest upgrade ever man
I got I think I got through the first season and then just forgot to finish it
but the first season of every show sucks man
mmm that episode with the jewelry store and Richard Lewis is good yeah it's all
it's all very funny yeah I never see actually the whole show is good it's all
very fun the whole first season was so good it's all very funny listen mm-hmm
what's the list today what time to react
we have to start the list are people complaining about us not doing shut up
we'll just we'll just well if they do they can suck our pricks man yeah I
don't give a fuck top ten top ten gayest nerds number one you yep and I don't
give a fuck about anything and number number nine through ten is also you and
And then, yeah, and it's fine if number 11's one of us.
- But number two, gayest nerd, Adolf Hitler.
- Come on.
Why'd you say nine through 10?
- Nine through 10, 'cause I meant to say nine through two,
and then I said nine through 10.
- So this person is one, and then also nine and 10?
- Yeah, then there's a few other people in the middle.
- Give me two through eight, who do we got?
We said Hitler's number two.
- Oh my God, Ned Schneebly.
- I fucking hate Ned Schneebly, dude.
Get out of my damn way.
I stepped in a puddle it's none of your fucking business yeah Ned Schneebly your
damn nerd. Then after that, he used to be the bass player. I thought Ned Schneebly was the guy in Groundhog Day.
After Ned Schneebly, Ned Schneebly. You gotta shut up about rock and roll pal.
Yeah it's not cool anymore. The only thing worse than a nerd is Dewey Finn.
Ned Schneebly slash Dewey Finn. Yeah the only thing worse than a nerd. Number three is Lawrence or number four
is Lawrence on the piano oh my god that kid he says you're a fat loser and you
have body odor you know I really don't he transforms so that's one thing about him
he becomes cool at the end yeah he's like he becomes like Ray Manzarek after
yeah a liar what's Miranda Cosgrove's characters name you're a joke you're the
worst teacher I've ever had that yeah and then she sings and he says shut up
you bitch yeah that's awesome he tells her that she's a groupie yep
*Groupie noises*
You're a groupie slut!
The legend of the groupie slut!
You're gonna suck dick!
You're ten!
You're a little child slut!
*Groupie noises*
It is funny that he-
Rikki dikki dikki you suck dick you're four!
It is funny that he did go into that school
You're a groupie!
It's so funny that he went into that school
and called two like nine year old girls groupies
nine-year-old girls
Listen you're going to suck their dicks man. You know you're a preschool whore
You them junior bacon chi you're gonna suck they're gonna suck their D's I'm gonna be I'm gonna be eating the junior bacon chi
You're gonna be sucking their
You stupid slut come here see that drummer boy sucks dick you're groupie
Hey, well, he's not supposed to be the good guy. It's true. No, you're not supposed to idolize
Yeah, if you miss a point by idolizing do we fit the principal dude? She's so
on it's crazy dude that's the hottest a woman's ever been no not true do you see
that you seen the new Batman she no I was in that I was in that theater sprung
caught me on a peewee Herman charge don't do that yeah he's yeah say say
Kony 2012 instead. What? The Kony 2012 guy had the same thing. Yeah. No, it wasn't in a movie theater.
It wasn't in a movie theater, but come on, put some respect. I'm outside, I'm looking at the poster, I see
Batman, I see Catwoman, I see my thing, I see my hand, I don't know what happened after that, I blacked out.
That's right. That's what I like to hear. My peewee squirming. It's funny that...
The Batman, Batman five stars, this movie got my peewee squirming.
the uh it's sad that he he kept getting in trouble for sex stuff after that yeah he had like a child
porn charge and his excuse was like i bought tens of millions of pieces of porn in bulk and yeah
odds are some of them were child porn because he said he bought like 1930s like kitsch art
yeah kids no no it's not kids art it's kitsch art yeah yeah paul it's shame though paul rubens
very funny guy. I don't think so. Peewee Herman, even funnier. I find that peewee
humor immature. Peewee human? I mean, we've been talking a while, but don't you hate it how
nowadays like everything's kind of being destroyed by peewee culture? I feel like
everything's so small now. Peewee culture keeps trying to make the
day every every piece of furniture talk to you. All these smartphones and all
Smart TVs and smart fridges and stuff I bet Peewee would like sitting on the couch and he sits on a human tongue
Uh-huh. Yep. Yeah
Even the Globes are talking, you know, I don't want that bullshit. Mm-hmm. Don't tell me about shit globe. Fuck you bitch-ass. Fuck you
Bitch, fuck you. Yeah. Yeah. Hey keep fucking you you stupid bitch glow
You're gonna be a child slut
Such an awesome movie. You are my slave you you're basically gonna be a
lazy slave. You are my slaves.
I feel like there's like a that's like like that's a very in a in a alternate
universe. That's very not very far away from school of rocky. He goes in there
and he's just all right. You are all gonna be my slave for three months.
You're gonna be my slaves, okay?
You're gonna be pressing license plates.
Awesome.
- You're gonna be making me shirts.
- You, we're doing school. - Not to sell for me to wear.
- We're doing school of prison.
We're all gonna be different prisons.
I'm gonna be the warden, man, okay?
You can't talk back to me.
You, you're gonna be the guy who has a cell phone
in his ass, and we're all gonna fuck this one.
- And yeah, that's Lil Wayne, it's 2008.
- That's Lil, you're gonna be, you,
this is the drummer kid or the piano kid you're you're little you're little Wayne
man you're wheezy man and the F is for Renzi that's right I love I love I love
Jables dude he's so sick I would be nowhere without him look at me I school
of rock is such a good I listened to a tenacious D song the other day yeah and
was like Kickapoo this funny as hell dude fucking sick kick who is my favorite
song in that movie tenacious D is sick dude the dragons balls are blazing into
his cave I watch that movie like a year ago - it's so great it's perfect meatloaf
as his dad yeah foo panda I didn't see that what panda he's not one he's kung
fu panda Angelina Jolie is the snake woman yeah what's his name that movie
shu mu his name is foo panda kung fu panda no he has a name that's shu mu more shu
no the more shoe shower shooter what's his name name is the more shoe shopkeeper
his name is not lame oil is his name Derek or is it Chinese kung fu panda
this is oh oh yeah oh yeah yeah okay so the list today that is a Chinese goose
yeah do we do the list it today what what time are we at people are really
gonna want to listen to this list okay okay we really need to get to it we're
hopping into this one this is the top 10 greatest internet memes so he has a
Chinese goose dad right yeah that's a Chinese goose who makes ramen I think
yeah right and who there was someone I was talking with someone recently
there's somebody in that movie who there's one Oh Kevin Spacey the dad the
dad is the guy who voices though like the master the like kung-fu master I
know but the dad is voiced by the guy in in Big Trouble Little China which one the
dad no which guy in the big trouble the China guy I'm looking at he's little
China okay yeah I'm looking up the cast list for a kung fu panda here okay oh
it's Dustin Hoffman is the master really the turtle or the red panda yeah
it's not been Hoffman doing like an Asian voice no no he's doing himself I
I just remember I was like what else is Dustin has Dustin Hoffman been it cuz I
was like the only things I can think of Dustin Hoffman being in our Rain Man and
the Graduate. And yep David Cross is the monkey. No it's Jackie Chan is the monkey.
Jackie Chan is master monkey. David Cross is the snake. David Cross is the snake.
Lu Sing Liu is master viper. David Cross is the snake. James Hong is in that. Which one is David Cross?
Crane. Crane. Oh my god. David Cross is the manager. Ian McShane as Tai Lung. Wow.
Wow, that's one of the next level. Oh my God, Randall duck cam as
who way
who weighs a master who way that's the turtle.
Yep, I never seen this James Hong as Mr. Ping James Hong is a he's
James Hong rocks. Yeah, that's what I'm thinking of. I think
Daniel was really good saying getty getty want to know Bay.
He's not in this movie. I'm just I thought it would be getty what
to know Bay. Oh my God,
the karate teacher in UHF and he plays long dong in 16 candles.
Yeah, the stupid you are so stupid guy.
Yeah.
He's awesome dude.
Dude, he's so funny.
Fucking love that guy.
I love that guy.
People don't talk about this performance from Kung Fu Panda that much, but Stephen Kieran
as Gong Pig/Grateful Bunny was actually like next.
Fire.
Like it was flames.
Yeah, it was.
My nephew got into, I don't know how he found out about 16 candles, he's five years old,
he called me the other day and said...
- You should be watching Five Candles.
- Yeah, he should be, that's way too many candles
for him to be watching.
He called me the other day and just said,
"Donger needs food."
And I was like, "Oh, geez."
- Yeah, that's not a good movie for a child to watch.
- No, I don't know how he, I think maybe my dad
said it in front of him or something, but he...
- My son just turned five, we're watching 16 Candles,
Breakfast at Tiffany's, and Team America.
(laughing)
but just the Kim Jong-un part.
We're getting him prepped.
Yeah.
That's crazy. That's a crazy move.
Number one is Rick Roll.
Yeah.
He called me, so he called me and then
he'll call me and then do that and then
"No, this is Patrick" now.
He does "No, this is Patrick" to you?
What the fuck, man?
He calls me and says "Is this the Krusty Krab?"
You need to kill this kid.
Do you say "No, this is Patrick"?
(laughing)
- Here's a better question, dude.
Why does your nephew have a direct line to you, bro?
- My sister's phone.
- You should just never answer.
- Yeah.
- There's nothing important that this kid's gonna tell you.
- It's not true.
- What has he ever told you that changed your day?
- He got a new Lego set.
- And you thought about that later?
- That is pretty big.
- He got the Batman Lego set.
- Nice.
- I was with my family this weekend.
My cousin Jeffrey, he picked up the Catwoman
and looked at me and said,
"You gonna put this in a jar or something?"
and I said, "Whoa."
- That's pretty funny.
- That's a good joke, but don't say it
in front of these damn kids.
- If I was a kid and I got a Batman Lego set,
I would eat all the villains so they couldn't kill Batman.
Those villains are small.
- Yeah, listen, I'm a monster compared to you.
- You know the--
- The Joker has no, I can't do anything to him.
- I will chew you up.
- You know the fucking, it's like, oh, no,
like ages three plus, we don't want younger kids
to take a choke on these, right?
My little brother, when he was like three years old,
his whole thing, he would eat every fucking tiny action figure
that we had.
We had Star Wars micro machines.
He would eat the fucking things.
- He was gulping?
- He would eat all the like figures.
Like there's a tiny Chewbacca that came with this,
the fucking, I think it was the Endor one.
He fucking ate it.
I remember him taking it out of my hand and swallowing it.
- I think that you were an immoral child
if you were not eating the evil toys in your collection.
- One time my little brother, he--
He was eating the good guys, dude.
My youngest brother.
He was going to grow up to be a dark overlord.
He walked into the living room, like crying his eyes out, and he was like,
"What?" He was like, "I put a Lego or there's a Lego in my nose." And I was
like, "No, there's not." And I looked up with a flashlight and like an inch
into his nasal cavity, there was like a little red Lego. Like I have no idea
how he got up there. And I took him to two different doctors and they finally
like, when he had to like stick a balloon in his nose and inflate it from
the other side to pull it out and he hated it. He was like four and he was
like okay, I'm going to do this for my family. He said that out loud and then
he did it and then when we finally got the leg out, we were like why did you do
this and he was like oh, I didn't even do this. The dog did it. The dog put the
leg
and he maintains his day. He's like a teenager now and he's like yep, the dog
put the leg
so cool did yeah. Number two is doge. I think this is the dog that did it. He
does look a little bit suspicious.
- Yeah.
- Did you guys ever put anything up your nose?
- No, but I did.
I swallowed, I was like laying on my back.
- You can say that.
- Yeah, I've put some things in there.
I was laying on my back when I was five.
- Tissue, finger.
- And I put a Lego in my mouth and it like went down.
(laughing)
And I got up and I like looked at my parents
and I just went (slurping)
and it was the first time I ever had the Heimlich done on me.
- The first time?
You had multiple Heimlichs?
- I've never had the Heimlich done on me.
- I've never even.
I come close to choking every once in a while. I'm eating this because I
thought the Heimlich and CPR were interchangeable. Oh, that's bad yeah.
Yeah, I yeah, I'll eat. I eat sometimes I'll eat too fast and it'll be like one
second where it's like well. I can't breathe or swallow I'm dead and then
it's fine every time, but I've it's it's happened enough times that I'm getting
registered to get really scared when I eat.
I try not to eat a little chew your food better. I don't know something. I just
I never learned my little I never learned. I don't problem with that in
preschool. Yeah, yeah, my parents tell me you have to chew your food more.
You're going to say no. I'd be like
why would you want to chew your food? It's a good point. Do I want to taste
that bullshit? Get it get it out of my mouth. Get it in my book. My tongue's in
there. My stomach that's where the flavor gets. That's what the flavor gets
process. I never learned how to chew my food is
you're on a day with a girl. So one thing about me is
so cool. My little brother choked on water one time and we told that happens
to me. I told him yeah. Oh yeah, that was like the kitchen table, like
and we're like what are you doing? I just drink water.
That is it was choking on the water. Oh, I mean yeah, just eat something. I
Yeah, yeah, if you're drinking water you got to eat something a set. Otherwise you'll die
It's true number three Chuck Norris jokes. Hell. Yeah, shit is funny as hell man. What's your favorite?
to me to me
Tom Brady is like Chuck Norris
That's the dip. Yeah, here's my Chuck Norris joke one time Tom Brady and Chuck Norris were playing football Chuck Norris one
That's actually really good. Yeah one time Chuck Norris and Michael Jordan were playing basketball and Michael
George our truck Michael Jordan lost Chuck Norris one. Mm-hmm. Yep one time Andre Agassi and
Chuck Norris were doing what Andre Agassi does
Yeah
And Chuck Norris won it one time one time Robert De Niro and Chuck Norris were acting and Chuck Norris was better at it
Then you're a De Niro Chuck Norris and Chuck Norris killed Darth Vader. Yeah
Yeah, basically if you use
Yeah, Chuck Norris is made out of Nokia phones. Basically Chuck Norris did better
did better karate than Jackie Chan the other day. Yeah. Chuck Norris beat Jackie Chan.
Yeah. Yeah and Chuck Norris did that for real. Chuck Norris counted to zero.
Chuck yeah yeah did you know Chuck Norris counted to zero? Chuck Norris flew higher than a bird
yeah Chuck Norris flew on a plane once Chuck Norris yeah without the plane yeah
with the plane yeah and he said because he sat first class because he's so rich
Chuck Norris is more awesome than Superman
yeah so these are pretty much my joke thank you everybody
Thank you Comedy Store, it's been amazing. This is what Kramer said at the Laugh
Factory was gonna be before he got rudely interrupted. Yeah, it's amazing to be here at the Comedy
Store. So amazing, I'd love to be here. Chuck Norris is here tonight. Yeah, he's here all
around us. Hey, listen, I'm good at comedy but not nearly as good as Chuck Norris.
Is that Mark Norman? Yeah, they got the Chuck Norris guy. Yeah, you see Chuck Norris is here.
yeah yeah we're here at Chuck Norris yeah yeah yeah yeah number four is it's over
9000 yeah it's over 9000 it's over Chuck Norris's bank yeah that's how much Chuck
Norris weighs in stone 9000 yeah Chuck Norris weighs 9000 pounds or over I
I should say. Yeah. Yeah, Chuck Norris weighs 9,000 pounds. He's a ball of spaghetti. Yeah,
Chuck Norris is as big as a house. Yeah. Yep. And he has a support beam, like a house. Chuck
Norris has a stronger smell than anything on earth. Yeah, Chuck Norris has a load-bearing
pole. His penis is load-bearing. Mm-hmm. Yep. Because he has to lean on it because he's so
old. He's not over 9,000 years old. He has a load-blasting penis. I can't bear how many
many loads of sucked out of that thing that's right and it gave me so many
calories. I became as big as a bear. I'm strong, but I don't need but I can't be
Chuck Norris. Nope, but you can load me into a truck. I heard apparently Chuck
Norris fought Godzilla and apparently neither one of them one because Chuck
Norris is Godzilla. That's how big and strong Chuck Norris got in a truck
floored it and ate a puck for his dinner
because he went and played hockey yeah and he used his mouth as a goal,
because he's so big yeah Chuck Norris said fuck Norbit because he hate that
movie yep. He got confused. He thought it was all different actors. He said he
wanted to meet the entire cast and when one guy came out, he got one of those
and then he did karate to him better than Jackie Chan.
One of those pictures of like a celebrity with like the news thing and
it's like Chuck Norris got confused at Norbit
up number five is we are number one what's that one that's the one where
they did the dance from oh that's lazy's town yeah yeah yeah it's cool that that
show looked like scary it was cool look it looked like a Robert Rodriguez I
thought yeah I think that's a cool-ass show I've never seen it but I know I
used to watch that shit when I was like a kid I don't think I came out well
after we that was when I was they came out on a seven I watch it when I was
2007 I don't think that's true yeah it is I think this was like a like 2011 no
pretty sure no LazyTown came out like 2004 and it was came out first in
Sweden or some shit I have no he's always right about this kind of thing I
learned from the ended right now 2004 dude what is wrong with you bro August
16th I'm gonna stop trying to you're always right about stuff like that every
single time and it was it was from it's from Iceland Iceland that's what it is
same thing they all come from damn Viking sperm Norris is even colder than
Iceland yeah he's colder than green oh he actually named guys like green I
learned something really cool yesterday did you know that people used to believe
that that that sperms can had a tiny guy inside them and that's how babies were
born showed me the diet I showed you a diagram of this but so it goes it's
that's deeper than that right. So they believe that that's a sperm had a tiny
guy inside that would grow into the child, but then like philosophers were
like well, then doesn't that mean that every like the guy inside the sperm
also has a sperm inside him that has a guy inside it and a sperm inside that
guy that has a guy to infinity and then the the the science the people who
believe this who are called spermists were like yes, that's that's true.
that's how it is and the
they disproved it because they're like well, then why were they? Why how come
sometimes babies look like their mothers and the the sperm is or is like I don't
know
sperm is as what they call me down a damn glory hole. What's up your yeah? I'm
sucking all them off. I would have ate the comments. It doesn't taste like
anybody to me. This doesn't taste like chicken. This doesn't taste like
buddy I've ever ate. This doesn't taste very small. This doesn't taste, I've eaten a small
guy before. This tastes pretty substantial I would say. What do you guys think it's like
to be sperm? I remember. What was it like? I remember everything. Have you ever seen?
Do you guys think that you guys were like popular as sperm? Yeah probably. I mean that's
That's the thing about all of us were the most popular sperm.
No, I feel like we were the, I was, I don't know, maybe you guys speak for yourselves,
I was like an underdog.
Yeah, because you were pathetic and lame.
No, listen, they doubted me, and I showed them.
I guess you reached it to the top, man.
In sperm high school, I was like the...
Which one were you?
I was the jock.
Really?
I was the jock and I was the prom king.
I was the prom king.
I mean, I'm high school.
That's cool.
I was the principal, but that's cool too.
Wow.
I was sperm.
entire sperm school basically sperm Hitler you guys think in our in our
sperm lives we all knew each other.
We had to have right.
Yeah, do you think it's the same load do you guys think when twins or sperms
there they like are like in their like boyfriend and girlfriend yeah they got
to be right yeah boyfriend girlfriend sperms like why are they seeing why
they holding hands yeah seen look who's talking of course he's talking to seen
of the intro of that movie the intro that movie where it's all the sperms run into
the damn egg yeah I saw that when I was six and I my mom did not explain what
that was to me you know you're running their stork hey you know what other
movie has that that is a seed of Chucky really have they have a bunch of doll
sperms running into a doll egg they showed Chucky jacking off in that movie
to Chuckie I mean he raw dogs right yeah they show us each one of Chuckie's
catchphrases you know like you get the laugh you get the like want to play and
then the third one is I don't use condoms. I hate condoms. I hate the feeling of condoms. I'm already rubber. He's not rubber.
Why do you say that? Chuck he's rubber. His arms are rubber. He's plastic. He doesn't like
condoms because he's allergic to latex. Watch Child's Play. Watch the intro of
Child's Play 2 again. No. I have to use a sheepskin condom. I'm allergic to latex. I'm already made out of it.
He's not made of latex look at child's play to the he's made of wood brother
Though he's not fully wood. He's not wood
He's made of horse teeth nah. Yeah, you know yes me the kids made a pure evil. Yeah, he's a kid
Yeah, he's a child's play you when I was rewatching child's play. It's so funny in that movie
They like they tried the whole time in that movie
They try to do the like the whole game of like oh is the little kid crazy, or is the doll actually alive?
but the first scene in the movie is literally like is literally Brad
Durif like calling a lightning bolt down from the sky of being like does saying a
magic spell to become a toy and go to a toy's body and then the whole are like
who knows is the toys the doll is so funny dude good movie was it child's
plate is it two or three we're like it's the intro where they're like scraping
that I think it's three where they're scraping like the the the char off of the
dolls face and she was the one where they go where he goes to military school no
threes military school three is not to us he was the one where he's in the family
and the dad's played by the the redheaded pedophile yeah yeah Tim Burton and he's
also in and he's in a Phantom of the Paradise why does Chuckie have all these
scars on his face huh why is Chuckie have all these scars on cuz the child's play
three he falls into a fan blade three it was the three is three the military
school and also the amusement park. Or is two the factory? Two is the factory and
that's when he gets melted down into plastic and then like his blood gets
into the vat of latex. Those movies are so good. It's crazy. Every one of those
movies is good. That shouldn't be true. How did he reach the kitchen counter to
grab the knife? He climbed up on the stool. Okay and how does he use the
bathroom? He doesn't have to. He uses diapers. Yeah. That's kind of
embarrassing well that's also a telltale sign of a serial killer was it how does I
haven't seen I haven't seen child's play four and five that's realizing they
also Jennifer Tilly comes back to life Jennifer Tilly is for his bride of
Chucky yeah and if I watch that at a bar with Neil actually five is seed of
Chucky that's my Glenn and Glenda yeah yeah and then oh have you seen the new
series where he's like I gotta yeah yeah I'm binary that's I mean that's
That's literally already what it is in Seed of Chucky.
Chucky is a non-binary kid in the fifth one.
Yeah.
And then there's...
But then they split them into twins.
...Curse of Chucky and Cult of Chucky.
At the end of Seed of Chucky, they split them into twins.
Dude, I don't remember.
I don't think so.
Yeah, that's because the concept of non-binary in movies in '03 was just so foreign that
they were like, "Well, they can't be a boy and a girl."
I don't remember that.
They have to split up into...
I think you invented that in your brain because you don't...
No, the final scene of the movie.
...you think you can't understand non-binary kids.
The final scene of the movie, it's Jennifer Tilly at Glenn and Glenda's birthday party.
I don't remember.
And then Chucky comes back at the end.
No.
Like a screamer ending.
Don't tell me Chucky comes back at the end.
Dude, Curse of Chucky and Cult of Chucky are the ones where they have Brad Dourif's daughter
as the main character.
Oh really?
Yeah, and those ones are really good.
And then they're in an insane asylum.
The remake I thought was fine too.
Really?
Yeah, I didn't hate it.
the one where Chucky says that's a game you can only play when you're high. Is
that the remake? I've never seen a single that's the no that's that's I got them
all on DVD. If you want to come over and watch them all in a row, really want to
watch child's play. Great dude, very scared the shit out of me when I was a
kid because the fucking the kid who jumps on the grenade that the best part of
child's play three is that is one of my favorite like like side characters in a
horror movie ever where it's like in said in military school and there's like a
characters just like an evil barber who's just never explained any dislist like he
just like sneaks up on kids and it's like i'm gonna cut your hair.
I remember really vividly he like there's a scene where he like really
violently cuts one of the kids hair and then he goes presto your bald.
That's not very and that's just like one of the things like oh yeah, there's an
evil bar at the military school like that dude. It's so funny like like
Military school is like the most evil place a kid can go in movies. Did you guys ever know when I went to military school?
No, I I knew someone who wanted to but who didn't I knew this one kid
He was he was literally he was too cool and he they sent him to a military school. Yeah, his name was Dylan
He was fucking awesome, dude
He's the coolest kid I ever met and his parents were like we're like you're too you're too fucking cool
He used to snort pixie sticks. Oh, you would pull it in one rip dude
Damn. And they were like, "You have to go to military school," and then he got really
good at soccer. That's tight. Yeah, so it's really upsetting to talk about.
Yeah, but like, you know, as a kid the scariest thing you can go to is the
military school and then, you know, when you're when you're grown up they expect
you to go into this damn draft to fight for Zelensky. Fuck you, Zelensky, you little bitch.
Here's my fear about going to a military school. What if I become like the perfect human weapon?
Yeah, exactly. You know, and I'm responsible for thousands of civilian casualties.
and I'm the perfect human weapon,
and I have to go over and fight for this
Funko Pop president of Ukraine?
Fuck that shit.
- What if during a hazing ritual,
I discover a taste for blood?
- Yeah.
- All of a sudden, I'm in Aleppo,
and I'm chopping children's heads off.
- Yeah.
- It's like, I don't want that.
- They call me the butcher of Syria.
- Exactly, just because I went to military school,
because I played too much video games.
- What if I'm the first soldier who fights in space,
and they call me the Hound of the Stars,
and I spread hatred through the galaxy?
Yeah, that happens. Yeah, that's what they're exploring that in the new Buzz Lightyear
What if I put what if I put every single one of my victims into a big like?
Trailer that I pull behind my spaceship and the scent of death. Yeah, it's the entire galaxy
Yeah, what if I accidentally become an overlord that would fucking suck dude?
What if I get some military school for growing horns and tusks like I went to the dark side and code if I start wearing
Like like World of Warcraft armor with the giant shoulder Paul good
exactly did and I have like spikes on my back that like have like human heads
and like small animals and stuff on hills and shit yeah. I have my articles
over what if my name change changes into crendor the hateful it's all because I
pretended to I smoked a piece of rolled up printer paper and my grass yeah. My
parents got scared and they sent me to to to do those account on the scourge of
the universe. I didn't that great. I became a scourge and awesome. So when do
feel like it called me dirty becoming a scourge it all started with my parents
with military school actually yeah I listened to live it leads by the who and
then I tried to smoke numbers paper number six is troll face number seven is
mama Luigi number eight is Pepe the frog number nine is Sanic number ten is this
is Sparta go buy tickets to the whole hour without talking about the list
Sparta yeah we spent a lot of time yeah on those swag poop comm slash shows
shows, please buy tickets and you won't regret it unless you do.
Yeah, high ticket warning Fort Worth.
Please buy tickets for Fort Worth.
There's a lot of tickets left.
Low ticket warning DC, Chicago.
I don't know.
Normal tickets warning everything else.
Austin.
You know what, actually now that I say it, now that I think about it, I just
actually got an email that says there's a low ticket warning for every show and
if you want tickets you've got to buy them now.
And those shows are at...
And also I'm also seeing them again. I got a long now. I got another email just
now that says that if you want to buy one ticket you have to buy two because now
two tickets counts as one. Yeah and I and it could go up again two could mean four
very soon so you better rate the gas is going up you're gonna want to buy more
tickets than you thought. Yeah. Also bring your friends. Bring your mom. Bring your
mom. We'll bless her and yeah. You could also bring like you're trying to go into
like an HOV lane, you could bring a dummy.
- Yeah, that's fine. - And sit it next to you.
That's okay.
- But you have to pay for their ticket.
- Yes. - Yes.
Okay, bye everybody. - Bye.