come back and make a bet
and we see a black
you've been crap monster
the
the well we started i press start on the record is a lot of work in clock
it is a sixty two hundred six thousand two hundred okay so that's how the
Okay, four. Okay, great. I was beeping every time.
Why did I do that? Yeah!
Alright, now we're counting up. Alright, that makes sense. Yeah. That's pretty good.
Counting up is better than counting down. Yeah, I agree.
We got a clock so we can know when the episode should stop.
Does that make you feel pressured though? Does that not?
Definitely. If it's counting up, it doesn't. If it was counting down, it definitely would.
I think it's if he makes me feel pressure because it's red yeah, a red number
it's very intimidating directly across from me like yeah, it's like I have a
right number right here, too. I have two numbers to look at now that's too many
bread is this one around not for me. Yeah, it is red check it out. There's a
red circle next to it too. That's probably the scariest red shape. Big
trouble does this beep once it hits the time again. We'll see it probably
the episode will and I just like I could be every minute is would be very funny
if it reaches an hour to make some really loud beep
and we just end it immediately.
No matter what we're doing.
- I think that's what we do.
I think that's what we do.
- Oh, that's interesting.
- Whenever the beep goes off,
the episode's ended. - Oh, I actually have to go.
- Yeah.
- You should hook up the whole,
we should hook up all the electricity in the office
to the clock.
(laughing)
And set it for like nine hours every day.
- And the sprinklers turn on.
- And so we don't overwork ourselves.
- It locks the door, you get locked in.
(laughing)
You're not out by the time it ends.
- Can you guys believe we're one month into the office?
- Yeah.
- It's crazy.
I mean either me either we have seven keys yeah yeah what are they gonna change
the locks don't think so crazy they probably forgot we're down here we're so
quiet no way no way no how they forgot we're down here that lady has my phone
number now she called me at 2 in the morning oh yes she did then she's a
scholar 2 in the morning I think to confirm that it was my phone number but I
I also think...
I don't think that's why she got it.
She told me she put two sevens at the last two digits on my show.
She had like a... how many numbers are usually in a phone number?
Nine.
No. Ten.
So she added... so she had a phone number for me that was like 13 numbers.
And was like... she couldn't get...
Well that's your extension.
She couldn't get rid of the other two numbers because she was wearing mittens.
yes i don't know what you do with the flip phone
can get rid of the other two numbers
and uh... at two in the morning
i don't know she called me it to me because you're doing the men's team
one of those
she wanted you
and she's usually come over how about their
needs to hear it
maybe
on their matter
we have a whole plot with us today
joanne alexander okay
uh...
you know it was a real bird
sorry to upset you
that was a little more importantly than home planet
patrick is trying a new monster you know
and i found this at the dollar tree and not only that the unscathed he uncovered
oh yeah i don't know if there is a mystery monster mystery has been a
did you guys did you tell you guys about i have anything about that so i was
sitting here i was sitting here i was looking at this can this is a
is a monster lewis hamilton who i learned from the can risk is a formula
one driver yeah I don't do that I don't know sort of the LeBron James of
Formula One so he's LeBron James of driving a car in a straight line so fast
yeah so like yeah he's more of like a show for the reptilian invader was China
I believe yeah yeah China Chinatown he's doing he's doing sharp turns though yeah
I don't know what Formula One is.
But anyway, it's the first Formula.
I can break it down.
It's a scientific term.
Is Formula One the long skinny cars?
With big wheels.
That's like Monaco.
That's an Ironman 2.
Formula One, is that the one where the car looks like a shark?
Or is that Hot Wheels?
Is it the one where the car goes in a giant loop?
All the way up and down like Sonic?
Is that the one where Bowser is driving one of them?
No.
No, is that the one where you sometimes like some of the tracks you fly out of a
shark's mouth or like a yeah, yeah, yeah, is that is that the one is that the
one Mario drives them or crash bandicoot dress them is it's more of like a human
being thing, but it's a Mario and their heads and their heads are just like a
normal heads or what size their heads are really big or I would say their heads
are probably small. If we're looking at the crash bandicoot, that's the one with
sweet tooth, the clown unfamiliar with sweet to really is it he could be. I
- I don't know it well enough.
- Super Bombad F1.
- Is it what?
- Yeah, are there Gungans involved?
- Yeah.
- Do the cars travel?
- I'm pretty much like, I know Lewis Hamilton
and then like everyone else I don't really know.
- Is that where the carts like bump into each other
and they have the big pole that hits the ceiling?
- I think they do bump into each other.
I don't know about the poles.
- Is that the one where it's like a boat
and it's Leonardo DiCaprio's on the boat and he dies?
- That one's good, I've seen that one.
I've played that one before.
That's my favorite one to play.
- I love playing that one.
Is that the one with John Lovitz and Mr. Bean and they're like trying to get the money at
the end of the movie?
Oh, you know, Vince Vallu is in that too.
Vince Vallu.
And Whoopi Goldberg.
And Whoopi, yeah.
I mean, dude, I'm not trying to...
It could be any of this.
Is that the one with Louis Hamilton?
I only know Louis Hamilton and I know one other guy.
So you're sure it's not the one with Tobey Maguire, Andrew Garfield, and Tom Holland and
they team up to fight the ultimate villains?
Okay, okay, we all know that one.
I think they probably show up at some point, but...
Is that... have you drank in any of it?
Yeah, I drank half the can already.
What taste would you flavor it as?
- Okay, so I, so--
- Car.
(laughing)
- Car, this tastes like jet, this tastes like oil.
But I was sitting here and then I saw
that there was a label underneath the,
there was like a plastic wrapped label,
so I took a pair of scissors and I cut the can open.
And this is all in German.
- And the label on top was in English.
- The label on top was in English
and it said copyright 2021.
So they either had old cans--
- Yeah, what's the copyright on the German one?
- The German one?
- 1939.
(laughing)
- It got sent over in operation paper.
- The German one is,
- They wouldn't have it.
- 2017.
- Really?
- Whoa.
- So this is a vintage.
- Can I see it?
- So they are ripping you off.
- You should go demand your dollar back.
- It was only a dollar 25.
- But you're putting it in your body,
even though you just said it's from 2017.
- No, it's 'cause it's a vintage.
taste. I also have monster juiced ripper up there. Can you believe he just drank that?
I can't believe, I can't fathom drinking monster energy in general. It's pretty good. You should
grow up. Ugh. It does smell like gas, like it's like incredibly potent. Give it back,
you don't respect it. Wait, I just wanna. You're gonna put a dent in the can. When your
four time F1 world champion Lewis Hamilton, life moves at 15,000 RPM and 200 miles per
- Sounds like a nightmare.
(laughing)
- Sounds like hell, bro.
- I don't want to do that.
- Is it date itself?
- Kill me!
- 15,000 times per minute.
(screaming)
- Does it date itself on the can at all?
- He's probably won more than four times.
- Drank by President George Bush.
- I have the new label.
- A man who exists.
- So they could have just had old cans
and then just printed new labels on them.
- I think that's clearly what happened.
- Light, crisp, and refreshing with a fast finish.
- It gets you out front and pulling away.
- Damn, that sounds sexy.
- Yeah, I'm out front.
- It's got like a texture to it too.
It's got me pulling away.
- Yeah, see, they put the fucking,
the best thing about every monster can is the texture,
and they put that label on it.
- That's the best thing about monster cans?
- That's why I get it.
- It's how tactile it is.
- It's like ribbed.
- Yeah, it's got grip.
- Whoa, it does, yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's the best thing about every monster can.
- This'll never slip out of your hand.
- Is the grip?
- Yeah, the grip is the best thing about monster cans.
- Are they all gripped?
- Yeah, they are gripped.
When did that happen?
All the zeros and stuff.
Yeah.
All the monster zero?
But not the normal one.
What's a grain?
Monster juice is not a grip.
Monster zero, you're so thin that you don't even have those.
Monster juice is not, does not have a grip.
Is monster juice normal?
The monster zero has a grip.
What's monster juice?
Because that's when they take the sugar out, they put it on the outside of the can.
Yeah.
And that's like the grain.
Crystallizes, yeah.
But what is monster juice?
Monster juice is...
You don't want to know.
Monster juice.
Have you ever had the tea, the rehab?
the black they change it to monster recover it's no longer monster rehab
that's monsters pretty good you can't even call it drink rehab anymore
PCS JWS yeah even though it was a rehab thanks so thanks Obama thanks a lot
Obama yes shallow Obama this blue-haired Obama
God this blue hair asymmetrical hair
coat Obama's right.
He got blue hair.
Yeah.
It's the news tomorrow Obama got blue hair.
How angry like.
I did it for Marge Simpson.
I wanted to be Marge for Halloween.
I love Marge Simpson.
Marge Simpson.
She's the mom of fellow Americans.
On the Simpsons.
It's like on 60 Minutes.
So he's like why did you choose?
President Obama, what drove you there? He could rock a cool March hair cut. I think
if Obama dressed up as Marge that would probably trigger a successful January 6th. I think
the government would end. He's not even there but people would be so mad. Just seeing that
on Twitter or something. I would have gotten a call from my grandpa and he'd be in a Mad
max convoy headed to the fucking capital. He's got like a red leather jacket. Yeah. And he's
like yep Caleb this is what I'm doing now. We're going up Barack Obama. I'm FaceTiming
you because it's the last time I'm gonna see you. They're just going up there they don't
want to hurt him they just want to look at him and drool because he looks so hot as Marge.
I feel like politically it might be a smart move though. To marge it up. Just throw a curveball
like. Well yeah like hey. Like why did he do that? Yeah try to get Tucker Carlson to
make some excuse why this is a bad thing.
It seems like all he did was grow his hair long.
Tucker's ratings after Marge Obama...
They'd be crazy.
They'd be, "Hey, excellent."
It seems like...
Obama wants to turn his hair blue.
Why?
It seems like Obama is spending more time dying his hair
than he is even playing golf these days.
[laughter]
He's trying to become
Marge Simpson. Why?
because liberals are stuck in a fantasy land like a cartoon. They're trying to become cartoons.
What's next? He's gonna turn his skin yellow, maybe. Like Marge.
What's next? Bo Obama. Santa's little helper.
[laughter]
Kinda.
Dude, that'd be so crazy. Tucker getting mad at Marge Obama.
Yeah, that'd probably change the world for everyone.
You know who they would have on to talk about that?
You know the Obamas are a little bit The Simpsons though.
Mike Huckabee.
questions though. Yeah. They have a mom, dad, dog, Bart, Lisa, Maggie. They're funny as
hell. Yeah. You know how Obama's always going like. He drinks Dove beer. What's he in charge
of? Nuclear bullshit at one point. What's he love? TV? He loves watching TV. And he's
It kind of makes perfect sense. Biden is Katie's friend with Krusty. Who's Biden in the Simpsons?
Milhouse. Biden's Milhouse. Or Milhouse's dad. Huh? Milhouse's dad. No, because who's, no
Biden's like. No, I think Hunter Biden is Milhouse and then Kirk Van Houten is Joe Biden.
Who's um. Or maybe it's the other way around. Oh, Biden has a dead, Biden's Flanders. True.
Oh, there we go. There we go. Dead wife, two sons. Obama and Biden were always like
grrr. Yeah, they hated each other. You know why? Because Obama hated Joe Biden.
Biden was such a nerd. Yeah. The way that like liberal couples are nowadays,
it's kind of like Obama would be Marge and Michelle Obama would be Homer.
Yep, that's probably true. Probably. I thought that was under the assumption.
That's what it was. That's what it definitely is. Yeah. Michelle Obama, I
mean, she's got Homer's arms. Remember that? Everybody was like, her arms are
muscular yeah I do remember yeah remember she took all the good snacks out
of school I'm gonna talk about this again it was fucked up miss school lunch I
didn't see that much of a difference yeah you were going to friggin
Empire State fucking lobster mac and cheese every day for lunch
caviar that's what Joby like yeah did I wish did I even have it that good
check believe it believe it or not bro caviar sucks
I'm not the first time okay we also have our first time we both had caviar at the
same time and we ate it warm at a like someone's birthday and it been sitting
out for like three hours have yours we don't know how long it's fancy no it
tastes like salt yeah just a little exploding you you're good you got fooled
you basically you fell for caviar yeah like really easily it's like it's like
- Yeah, literally, yeah.
- It's the impers new clothes.
- Really, really rich people.
- And I fell hard.
- Really, really rich people invented caviar
to prank normal rich people and be like,
oh no, yeah, that's super good and cool to eat.
- Yeah.
- It's the same, it's the dude.
- I'm saying purely based off taste, it's like a fun thing.
- I mean, what was the human mouth feel?
- That's the same thing with lobster.
Lobster's a bug.
- Lobster is good.
- I mean, it's good, but you're falling for it.
- You're betraying New England by it.
- No, I like lobster, but you have to admit,
it's a bug that lives on the bottom of the ocean.
- Chicken's just a bird.
yes feed and dinosaurs were birds yes would you know what you eat
caterpillar mac and cheese yes depends what kind of do we would you eat a
spider roll I posit you this did good chef Gordon Ramsay make it oh fuck
no then probably not
a caterpillar mac and cheese
I pretty much eat a beef wellington
and caterpillar meat
I'm on the Gordon Ramsey
Wellington an entire be fun to every single day.
The only meal I have won't do hundreds of dollars of pastry.
Yeah, your meal prep days insane.
Yeah, just rolling everything you donkey.
I'm yelling at myself.
I think good.
Oh fucking shit.
Fuck me.
You've done fuck me.
This isn't love.
- Oh, fuck me. - It's a caterpillar.
(laughing)
- Did you think I wouldn't tell the difference?
- Oh, fuck me, mate.
They sold, look at this.
They sold me a bunch of chrysalises.
- The caterpillars have too many legs.
- Would you guys--
- These are centipedes, fuck.
- Fuck me. - Are you guys gonna eat
all the bugs?
All the different bugs that we're gonna have
to eat pretty soon?
- Yeah.
- We're gonna have to eat a lot of bugs.
- Cicadas. - Yeah.
- Just 'cause like protein stuff?
- Yeah.
- What are you talking about? - We're running out of chicken.
No. Joe Biden just said, "I just got a Google alert because I have a Google alert for chicken."
Joe Biden just said we're running out of chicken. He did an entire press conference just to say we're
running out of chicken. You know what else? People are freaking out about us running out
of chicken. Everyone forgets. He also said two sentences later, "And we're running out of sauce,
too." No. Not sauce. We're running out of chicken and sauce. You have a Google alert for chicken,
Joe from surf's up. Yeah, chicken Joe sauce. Have you guys ever eaten?
Someday they're gonna make it bro. Google it for like hamburger.
I want to know. Yeah. I mean,
sending that and immediately getting like 10 million emails.
Perfect. I got a reading list. You turn it on in your phone. Just explode.
Have you guys ever eaten one of those spicy crickets or something?
Yeah.
I ate a ranch cricket.
I think I ate a chocolate cricket one time.
I feel like that one is probably the easiest.
I've eaten like eight spiders in my sleep every year though.
Eight spiders?
As a rule?
Yeah.
On average or eight?
On average.
Some years it will be five.
Some years it will be eleven.
I wonder if those are the better years when you eat more spiders.
Definitely.
You take their energy.
Yeah, it's protein that you don't know you have.
What if, well it's on average, so what if you live like a hundred years but you eat 800 spiders
in one year?
I mean, I think, yeah.
You just get it out of the way.
As a newborn, you're just like, I can't do it.
Well, you would have averaged, you would have made it eight.
You do that to like, as many spiders as possible.
You just do that to your baby, like your parent.
Yeah.
Because then you just, first year, spider gumbo for my kids.
It makes the rest of his life so easy.
Yeah, you know, and the spiders do this, and then the spiders just learn that it's a good
thing.
And then you just do it like, you know, you're like, I'm going to do it like, I'm going to
- Crawling out of his body every day.
- You just do that to your baby, like your parent.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause then you just first year.
- It makes the rest of his life so easy.
- Yeah, you know?
- And the spiders do this,
and then the spiders just learn
that it's a good mouth to go into.
- And then see all the others.
- But yeah, it's just 100 spiders a night, forever.
- When the kid is like 12,
he's just like at school vomiting up like a termite.
- The thing about eating spiders
is it may be like a little bit of extra protein,
but I also think if you eat an entire animal whole,
you get it's like life force and so yeah you get it.
I agree.
This is like that's the difference with the heads on them.
I don't like I've had it.
I've been thinking about this every day since you had the head of the
shrimp.
Well, no, it's a place that serves head to place and they serve head
on shrimp, which is my my guess.
So good.
The eyeballs like explode in your mouth so bad.
They taste really good to you want something to explode.
Do you eat the do you eat the poop line too?
I think they probably devane it or whatever.
Well, if they don't take off the head, why would they take one off?
- Well, also shrimp poop is not poop.
Like it's like-- - Yeah, yeah, it's true.
- It's all dirt. - It's all shrimp poop.
- Yeah, dog poop isn't human poop either.
I'll eat that.
- No, but dogs are eating meat.
Shrimp are just absorbing-- - Dirt.
- Particles that fly through.
- It's still-- - It's still poop.
- Particles is a lot different from food.
(laughing)
- Like, I'd let a shrimp like poop in my mouth.
'Cause it's not the same-- - Why?
Why would you let-- - I'm saying--
- Like for free? - You don't have to.
You can just not.
- If I had a choice between doing it and not doing it,
I would let it do it.
- You have a shrimp poop in your mouth.
- Well what is it?
- For what reason?
You're choosing to eat poop.
- I'm just saying I would do that
over any other animal's poop.
- Yeah, good point.
You have to pick one animal.
- If you have to pick one animal,
at gunpoint, it's your life or you eat this animal's poop.
- That's not what you said though.
You just said, "I would eat this animal's poop."
- No, I know, but I'm saying that I don't care.
What I should say is I don't care if I eat a shrimp's poop.
- You don't care about eating poop.
I don't either. I've eaten a shrimp before. I would like to not eat poop.
Any poop that's brown or white. I'm against brown or what about green bird
poop. Green counts as a subsect of brown. I think usually that you're
that's not the size of the car. But in poop, if you see a green poop, it's
yeah, that's in the goods in the normal mammal poop family. Okay, so if you
it's okay, so okay, so if you saw an animal and it pooped just like it poop
like diarrhea, the folds of diarrhea, it looks like you're like you're folding
over his chocolate. - What is it, gelato?
- Yeah, and it's red.
You're eating that? (laughing)
- No, no, no, so I mean--
- You're not saying he's just gonna go eat it,
no matter what he eats. - You said anything
but brown or white.
- He can't stop himself, I mean it's hard,
but he can stop himself from eating shit.
- Hold it back!
- I would eat like a sea creature's poop,
if he's probably not. (laughing)
- Yeah. - That's probably
not that bad. - Would you eat the green stuff
in a lobster? - No, no, no, no, no.
- Would you rather be like-- - No, because they're--
- No, they're like sharks will poop and it's like--
What they're eating is like moldy barn, that's like a cloud of like, that's a cloud of other
animals poop that they're eating.
That's like a gross, that's a, like, that's a, it's poop, that's not what this scene is.
I would eat a fly's poop if I had to eat one single poop.
A fly?
A fly.
Yeah, but that's real poop, bro, you're crazy, bro.
No, I bet I wouldn't even, I bet I wouldn't even notice it.
Would you rather eat a fly's poop or like see your mom naked?
See my mom naked?
Really?
Dude, yeah, she's hot.
I do fly poop every day.
No, I would...
Every fucking day, dude.
Every fucking day.
I just eat the fly poop every day.
You need like a fish oil supplement.
Well, you need to do it every day to stave off seeing your mom.
If you skip even one day...
Nope, not today, mom.
Sorry.
Come on.
You're squeezing the fly.
Please, please.
Come on.
You paper duck.
Well...
Oh, fuck.
Dude, you hear the shower turn off.
Oh my God.
I gotta do it.
don't think flies poop. I'm sure flies poop. Where does it go then? They spit out stuff
that dissolves their food and then they suck it up. Yeah, but no, but poop, they still
have to get nutrients, right? But where do they poop? I've never seen a fly poop. I'm
guessing at a time. Can we google fly poop microstoop? Yes, I have. When they rub their
hands that's them spitting out gunk. Have you seen, were you here when I looked up flies
having sex have you seen that no so funny it's just like I looked up superfly
having said here's a picture of fruit fly poop fruit fly excrement on food
contains pheromones that entice other flies to join that looks like a berry so
they eat their own eat that they poop over they poop on I thought that was
fruit fly poop under a magnifying so fruit flies poop on something and all the
other fruit flies smell the poop and are like that means that's good if you I'm
I'm gonna go see that if you eat fruit you're eating fly poop
No, if I fly poop you can wash it if you eat fruit from like a bodega
That's why you don't eat the fruit before you were you you're getting an apple on the way to like
I'm not gonna get sick from it. So yeah, there's a mental thing of like, oh, yeah, this is gross. This had dirt on it
I'm on my body. I feel like sick from so much dirt in my life. Yeah, I feel like bacteria
there's a lot of people right there now housefly poop you to the point most dirt
is pretty clean
yes in quotes let's see if it is here
also sitting it's sitting i feel like you know very well all along
i feel like a little
all along i don't know what the public's alive it's really good you eat that
all
okay
all that way really that is that is not a whole shoots out of the cool and then
and he drops a smudge bomb. So you would
that's called do it. Yeah, it's just like super super. I guess I suppose
not huge.
It's like the size of a card. Yeah, it's the biggest poop we've ever seen
in a bad scenario to eat a fly. Yeah, why not?
So you'd eat you'd eat fly you'd eat flyer shrimp poop. No problem, but it
would take a bad situation to eat a fly.
No, no, I'd eat it take a bad situation to eat
if prepared nicely at a restaurant, I don't care.
- A fly?
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, if it was like in his soup,
if it was in his soup, he'd eat it.
- It's the same thing with a spider.
- Spending like $25 at like a bistro to get a fly.
- If you took a tarantula and you like grilled it
and seasoned it and stuff like that,
I would probably enjoy it.
- I think that like any, I feel like most--
- Spider on nachos.
(laughing)
I would love that.
- Most animals, if it's like prepared and like,
it's not like poison, I would probably eat it
if it got put in front of me.
- I don't know what the head on shrimp is.
It's really fucking good.
- I did not find it very good.
- You gotta take me to this place, I gotta eat it.
- The shell is too thick and it feels like
you're eating a coin.
- What?
- Yeah.
- That's where they got the head on shrimp?
- Fuck, dude, I almost got the shrimps,
but I was like, I feel like everyone would yell at me.
- It's so good.
People were yelling at you a lot that day.
- They were.
- I don't know why.
- I was hungover.
- People are too hard on you, Pat.
- Yep.
- You get yelled at though, there you go.
- I get yelled at for, I don't know.
you remember what I did. Just being yourself. Just goofing around. Probably. That's all
I was doing. Messed up bro. What was that crap? SHUT UP! I believe you got the chicken sandwich.
I got the chicken and the potatoes with that sauce. Which is good. That sauce was good
as hell. I did not like the sauce for some reason. You didn't? It really looked like
I tried it multiple times. It did. The sauce is very brown.
The peanut one. No, he got the normal ones.
Oh yeah. I got the normal potatoes and then I tried them and I was like,
damn, they're good.
And I got the, Oh, Oh. And then I ate the garnish on that drink.
Ew. Is there anything more delicious than garnish?
Garnish is so good. I get so hungry for micro greens.
Dude, dude, like kale used to just be a garnish.
And then people started eating then these damn hipsters started eating.
Oh my God, don't get me started on these fucking freaks.
I mean, most garnish is just like the top of a vegetable that they cut off, right?
Yeah, I wish most hipsters were vegetables that would get cut off from their damn parents.
Yeah, what's up?
Throw them in a stew, cook them up.
Yeah, I want to throw them in a passion pit.
I would eat a hipster's poop.
Yeah, would you eat a hipster's poop?
Depends.
Yeah, they're just drinking coffee.
Yeah, cheers.
No food in there.
It's the black brick.
It's just...
Caffeine bomb.
That'd be awesome.
I want to throw these.
- The hipsters' poops probably freakin' plaid anyway.
- I wanna throw these hipsters into a passion pit
and then hit 'em with an iron
until their blood flows like wine.
- Yup, yup. - I don't understand
the reference. - Yeah, I would like
to be a vampire for a weekend
and bite some of these hipsters.
(laughing)
- Yup. - I hope they get--
- I'd like to take my mom's Ford
and drive it into their son's.
- I would like to lay down on a mat and kill myself.
(laughing)
- I want to squish them between two doors
at the cinema club.
that their arcade on fire yeah that's true yeah I hope I send them to Nirvana
stir ass nirvana Jackson them I hate hipsters so much I saw one the other day
yeah where on the street I saw your money I saw a guy on the street today
homeless person. He's a hipster. He smells soap. He's a fucking hipster. I saw a hipster on the train.
Oh, he's too cool. I saw a hipster on a train. He's walking around with his, he's got a little cup and he's
shaking coins in him. It's like, hey, I don't want to hear your song. Yeah. I don't want to hear this
song. This is bullshit, man. Yeah. Kick the coins out of his fucking hands. I mean, you know in like five years
they're going to be bragging like I was dressing in cardboard before it was cool. That's right.
It's so fucking annoying. On the way to the office today, I saw a guy, he's standing in the middle of
the road and he was dancing and he was wearing a paper bag on his head with like the handles
over his ears.
Fucking hipster bitch.
Hipster.
Yeah, it was pretty cool.
He was doing that before.
He was dancing.
He was doing music?
No, he was just dancing.
He was kind of doing like a hip thrust dance.
Oh, you remember that guy who would wear all white in front of the, what building was that?
And he would dance?
In front of the gates of heaven.
Yeah.
By the Boylston street stop, that building, like that Tremont intersection.
I saw, did I ever tell you, I saw that guy, he was like all white, he had a white cane,
He was just walking in the traffic on the Tremont and Boylston thing and just like twirling
his cane around and just looking at cars going like, "Hmm?"
And then someone started recording him like there and he like ran over them and was like,
"Stop fucking doing that!"
That's so funny.
Yeah, it's like you're doing that.
This is for people who are here.
This is in the moment.
You know, it's like a concert.
You shouldn't be just holding your phone up.
Yeah, exactly.
Experience it.
I always saw that guy and I was like, he could never eat like a hot dog.
It would like ruin his entire outfit.
He was in like a white suit?
He was a full white t-shirt, white pants, white shoes, white hat.
Yeah, he had like a white bowler hat too.
White skin?
Black skin.
Black as night.
Africa black, dude.
Darkest depths of Africa, bro.
Yeah, yeah, but the white shirt was immaculate.
It was crazy.
He would stand out in front of that building that played the radio.
And he would like dance to the music?
He would stand there and just dance to the radio.
He was cool.
Oh, oh wait.
I kind of did.
It was like the worst song ever played.
He was like, oh my God.
I remember that guy.
That was me.
He had some good tunes.
He never, I never saw him in Sebulba interact.
I miss the vagrant street people of Boston, Massachusetts.
You do better than the ones here.
The ones here are sad.
They are way better than these ones.
They are sad.
These freaking losers.
They don't do any like dances.
None of them have it.
I don't like on the line. None of them, none of them here have any character.
Yeah, yeah, you're the guy. I feel like I'm watching a TV show. Remember the
guy who would have a he would have a cardboard throne and sit on his throne.
Do you guys remember sadly chatter, but I remember smiling smiling. That's the
one. Yeah, there's a girl made a go fund me for like this amazing homeless man.
It's amazing.
It's like he's like the nicest guy in the world. We call him smiley because he
such a bright smile it looks like he's going to learn his name and it got
this is my race like ten thousand dollars or whatever for him and then they found
out like through they never knew his name and then they found out once they found
out his name he's like a registered sex offender
yeah it was like at the house and I did give back the go fund me you guys
remember he has remember the ghoul oh yeah they got with the burned face I
don't know if I called him the ghoul I think about it I didn't call on the ghoul
I didn't call him the ghoul either I just made that over the guy with the guy with
the leg somebody called him somebody called him because you're taking stock of
these well he looks like the ghouls from Fallout.
I vaguely remember.
Yeah they called him the ghoul because of that.
Who called him the ghoul?
You?
A couple people I know.
The guy with the leg, remember him?
The guy with the leg, it was itching his leg?
Yeah.
And I was like stop itching your damn leg.
And he showed it to me and it was like, it was like necrosis.
- So sick.
- It was so, I mean, he's a man.
- Yeah.
- What are you guys, family?
- That was nice.
(laughing)
- Remember we used to make 'em fight?
- We made a bracket.
(laughing)
- Remember that hill that we'd be like,
okay, you gotta roll all the way down,
I'll feed you a beer.
- Remember when we took them to Niagara Falls
and we made 'em go over in a barrel?
- Yep.
- Oh, dude, you remember when they,
the three-on-one basketball game?
- That was awesome.
- You guys against him.
- No, no, we had three of them play.
the
it's a little bit of a basketball by of course i don't know what versus three
homeless guys
it's one of the
the i don't know what the other day i was a little for the fact that you can
get it
is just like a mega godzilla is like a shooting like a little bit
basketball by basketball by
and power is powered by a fourth homeless guy inside can you buy me some
food he eats microchips okay activating slam dunk as the craziest game of our
hard time and then we self instructed him. Yeah, three other guys. Yeah, we
self instructed him on the. They found they found his self destruct the button
and that's how they won. Yeah, self destruct. They just stuck their finger up
his butt.
And he it's just that like a public court and they're like three guys
waiting for next. This is yeah, it was at a catholic school. He's playing
against like two like twelve year olds.
basketball but go play those kids he has his own basketball it's a cube it's a
robot yeah it doesn't go into it's a very well he is like it's made at a
stake yeah yeah it would be fun to play chess with a bunch of homeless guys
they're good human human human chest yeah no not this one not the you like wizard
chess yeah yeah oh yeah yeah fight oh wow that'd be cool yeah they probably fight
over who gets to be like the king in the ponds and so that'd be the first chess
man yeah is decided who does that you have to start with a really wide pool
yeah yeah it's gonna whittle then we just narrow him down then at a certain point
it just becomes Red Rover. That's a fun-ass game.
That game rocks. What's that, send someone right over?
We see it so hurt playing games.
It's like, I mean it's fun because it's an excuse.
What is the function of the gate? How do you do it?
You hurt people. You hurt people.
You stand in line and you hold hands and make a wall and you run across the field and try to like
break through the wall. Oh yeah.
It's so sick. It's just an excuse to like hurt people.
Yeah. That's why it's fun.
Cops and Robbers Wall Ball Challenge.
Manhunt.
Challenge?
Manhattan was legit.
You pick it up and you say challenge, you have to throw it.
Running around and hitting your friends. That was a fun one too.
In kindergarten, the girls played kissy girls.
Holy shit.
Whoa.
Oh my god.
We should bring that back.
Yeah, can we play that right now?
They tried to kiss the boys. Never got me.
Nice.
I used to play this game.
You won.
I won. I've been winning every day since.
Bird golf.
Yeah.
So you try to hit a bird with a golf ball.
golf ball. Yeah.
Yeah. Throwing rocks at the teacher's car in the parking lot in the back of the playground.
Every time I was like nine years old, I went to my friend's house and we tried to record
ourselves doing jackass. Oh yeah. And we recorded just straight up just me throwing a nine volt
battery at his garage door. And we were like, warning, these stunts are performed by professionals.
We used to do that shit too. I remember I would, well, my brother.
I thought the battery was going to explode. My brother would just make me do shit. You
you just make me hurt myself on my balls and then he would film it for his
jackass thing and one of them I like it was like January 1st and I jumped into
the ocean and it was like so cold and there's the entire thing because I just
jumped into cold water and he's like whoa jackass awesome. I had to feel good
as a little kid being like your brother. Yeah cool good job buddy. Yeah and then
I remember this is not for jackass. We used to make homemade stink bombs at a
dog poop yeah, we should throw him at my friend a little bit one of the best
jackass stunts. Hey, hi, I'm Cameron and this is running as fast as I can. It's
cool because I don't have a golf cart. I wanted one so bad. I know me and my
brother, we would look at golf carts online all day. That's like a beach
thing. I feel like is people drive golf carts around. Yeah, like some yeah. If
you live on like like there's like an island in North Carolina, you're not
allowed to have a car. You can only have a golf cart. Oh yeah, yeah, fucking I
I think like Myrtle Beach is kind of like that a little bit.
- Yeah, there's parts of it
where you can only have a golf cart.
- It's cool. - That'd be so fucking cool
to have a golf cart. - That would be so sick.
- You don't use your car at all,
everything's so close. - I want one here.
I want a golf cart. - My neighbor,
my neighbor Justin. - Just go to the front.
- Oh my God. - It'd be perfect, dude.
- Yeah. - That would be cool.
- My neighbor Justin had a go-cart,
which is the sickest shit. - Whoa.
- Yeah, I don't know how the fuck,
like he had a go-cart and like he was like the--
- My neighbor Mario had a go-cart.
(laughing)
My neighbor had a hovercraft.
My neighbor Dr. Einstein had a hovercraft.
Dr. Zingbop.
I don't know how it worked at all.
Zingbop!
Dr. Zingbop's hovercraft.
He always wanted to test his crazy inventions.
There's this crazy one where my neighbor growing up wanted me to drive his car to the past,
to the future, back to the future.
Oh my god.
Shut up.
So crazy.
Did you guys see Cowboys?
know that you did but you only did it twice. If you had done it again you would have sung
Cowboys. He doesn't fuck his mom in the movie. Yeah he does. Remember he starts to disappear.
You didn't see the director's cut. It's like Blade Runner. Yeah. The final cut. It's like
Blade Runner where the original cut had a narration and it's just Michael J. Fox like
"Whoa, this is heavy. I'm about to have sex with my own mom. Her boobs are amazing. Crap."
"Oh crap." "Oh crap." "No going back now. Here I go."
"Yahoo!" "Yippee!"
That's what I always, that's what I say out loud when I do the deed.
you do well with your mom? When I post that shit, when Joe has sex with his mom he says yahoo. Wahoo!
That's not true, I don't do that. I would never. Well what do you do then? What do you do?
[Laughter]
And he goes [mimics Joe's sex sounds]
He goes, "Ow!" [mimics Joe's sex sounds]
I'm a step man!
It's actually not funny because like I love my mom and I'd like... Yeah you love your mom like a lot, right?
I would, like it's not even funny to joke about because I wouldn't ever even think about doing something so
disgusting and so
gross as
saying yeah, it's my friends to even suggest that feels like a personal insult to me as a person and a personal insult to the
Years that we've known each other. Would you rather eat a stranger's poop or your mom's?
I'd probably go
Stranger really? Yeah, I need my mom. It's it's just it's just the mom's poop is gonna be like comfortable though
It's it's it coming out on a plate or is it moms poop was a home cooked home cooked mom's poop or five-star
Michelin poop five star Michelin poop every day. That's -
If you gave like
You gave like if you did like I don't trust my mom to prepare like a chop style thing
Where it's like you have to create the best meal you can with poop in it. That'd be a really good cookie
I think we should get a touch of like Netflix or Hulu or something.
That's a channel choice but it's gotta be a mammal.
I put my...
That's a cutthroat kitchen.
I know, yeah, that'd be great.
I shaved flakes of poop like in the middle of a bowl.
He's giving people like nerds and like skittles,
being like, "Oh, you gotta do this."
And also...
The curtain goes up and he's shitting.
Well, that's what would happen.
I'd be trying to make like a poop souffle or something
and it would deflate and at the end
end I would be panic. I just put it into like the blast freezer and just make
poop ice cream in like two minutes. I think you probably want to kind of
reduce it down and make like a sauce. No, because that's gonna make it more more
like concentrated. And then you're just gonna add a bunch of like, I already had
you're gonna add a bunch of like sweet and savory to just like push it out. I feel like you have to go with an extreme temperature if you're serving poop. You're so lucky.
That's what Cameron said, the flash freezer. But then I just I wouldn't want
want any poop texture to still exist within the dish.
You dehydrate the poop and shave it like a truffle.
I just want it to be the least amount of poop on it.
For me, most.
I'm just rolling it in bread crumbs, that's it.
Deep fry it.
I mean honestly, if you went flat enough, I feel like you could probably do something
interesting with it.
This is poop in the air fryer.
Have you guys ever seen the episode of Hoarders where the lady, she puts poop on her food?
you know, horders about that, though it's pretty awesome. You get all over her
house, like flakes of poo, and then she like slates sprinkles it on her. How
are the flakes like dried flakes from like the toilet bowl? They're like
goes over the toilet bowl and scoops it out. I don't think they show that, but
they do show like the charts on her food. I just do it. That's not actually
poop, because she can't be yeah. No, that shows someone eating poop on
Yeah, you can. You can definitely show that. You can show it to everyone on television.
I think they can fake that because they're like, "Oh, this would be funny."
You can't show Two Girls One Cup because it's too sexual.
But if someone ate it...
Because it's actually kind of hot.
Yeah, you could show one guy one cup.
Yeah, you could show Dave England eating a poop.
Yeah, definitely.
But you couldn't show Two Girls One Cup.
Well, you could show Two Girls One Cup, period, but I don't think...
You could show Two Girls One Cup.
You could show that to you right now.
You can show it on HBO. Two kids one TV.
really like to watch it for the first time, like three years ago, and I
almost I like wanted to vomit. It's so fun to girls one cup because the
funnest part of it is that they're pretending to like it yeah, which is
like it. I think one of them died after I don't know one of the women
died. That's certainly like a two dozen eight and I got married. No, she
got attacked by aliens.
They fell in love.
I heard it was the first
That was the first date.
That's how they got engaged.
She pooped the ring out.
Yeah.
It's a great story of meeting.
She pooped the ring out and turned to her and said, "Will you marry me?"
She pooped the ring out, then the other one ate it, and then she pooped the ring out with
the poop.
Yeah.
And then gave it to her.
She threw it up.
She threw the ring out.
Do you think you could poop the ring onto the finger if you stick the finger in the butt
hole?
No, because the poop would push it out.
The poop is solid.
Okay, guys, listen.
It's a soft poop.
This is way too much poop talk.
We already talked about this.
stick the finger on the butt of it.
The poop would push it out.
The poop is solid.
Okay guys, listen.
It's a soft poop.
This is way too much poop talk.
We have to stop.
We have to go to the list.
Would you rather drink carbonated pee or eat pee ice cream?
Well, it would be pee sorbet.
Would it be airy in it?
Because it's yellow and stuff?
Yeah.
Pee ice cream, it's just like pee and it tastes like pee.
I guess like pee snow cone maybe.
I did that in Czech.
Wait, what's the first one?
Yeah.
carbonated pea soda. I feel like carbonated pea actually. Pea soda?
Carbonated pea goes down easier.
But then you're going to burp and taste it again.
Oh, true. I go ice cream. I love ice cream.
I'd go carbonated pea.
You would?
Cause I could convince myself that that's like a broth.
What is in here?
Carbonated?
I could convince, I could drink pea if I convinced myself it was chicken broth.
I don't think you could do that.
That would take a really...
That's so pun- I'm sorry, I just like smelled the monster.
He opened a Pringles can.
I opened the Pringles because I was like, "Why is this so heavy?"
And it has Patrick's monster in it and then I just got like a whiff of the monster mixed
with the chili.
Oh, chili lime scorch and Pringles.
It just smells so gross.
Patrick's chip corner.
Pretty good chip.
I don't like Patrick's chip corner.
You really like flavors and stuff.
What?
You look like a- What?
You like like a new flavor.
You're a sucker for like a new brand.
he's the modern man did he only eat things that are bright red and drinks
things that taste like and you have a four monster cans plus one is one of
those is a Pringles can.
Why do you do that though?
You imagine I've ever seen him eat like a fruit. I was just saying the same
thing with Alex. I've never seen him eat like a salad. I'm allergic to most
raw vegetables and how are you? How does God make you allergic to fruit and not
- How is this even possible that that is better in your--
- I'm alert, dude, I can't, if I eat a raw carrot,
my lip will swell up.
I can't do, like--
- That's why nobody's asking you to eat a raw carrot.
- Remember when you came into my work and you were like,
"Can I get something for free?"
And I was like, "Yeah, you can have any,
"pick like a juice, like a Natalie's juice."
- Those are like eight bucks.
- They're eight bucks, but I just gave it to you
and then you drank it and then you immediately
had an allergic reaction to the drink
and then you had to go home.
(laughing)
- Ew, that's so--
- Your face just got like--
- It was so gross.
Your face just got really puffy.
There was carrot juice in it.
You didn't think to check it?
So funny.
I've done that so many times, I forget to ask for no guacamole on al pastor tacos.
Every time.
I've seen that first hand.
Yeah.
This magic bean is so specific about what kind of tacos he does.
Well al pastor is like best with guac.
I wish I could eat guac dude.
I don't every Mexican food in the world. What they put guac on everything.
No, they don't. They do. No, they don't put it on beer. I think what you're
saying is that with al pastor guacamole is so good. Someone who finally
understands me on here. Is that true? Is an al pastor the pineapple one?
Yeah, I don't think they usually put guac on that. They do every place I
and al pastor that's because they look like this guy's probably allergic to
let's see we're gonna make this guy blow up we want to do a mr. Korea so to him we
want to turn this guy to the human pufferfish yeah I'm not allergic to
really anything yeah yeah you're probably such a great you're probably
allergic to death I probably would not have a great reaction to that yeah yeah
I'm also a zero. Allergic. I'm a zero. I'm a zero. I'm pretty much a zero though. Although
I would at birthdays in like elementary school I would eat the rice cakes sometimes. Tastes
better than a cake. That's for the kids who are allergic. Yeah if you're allergic you
usually bring in a stash for birthday celebrations. Rice cakes. Do you guys not do that? For the
nerds. That wasn't a universal school thing? No. None of my school. We didn't know. We
- We didn't bring in cupcakes.
- We didn't go to freaking Joni Mitchell High School.
- You didn't bring in cupcakes on your birthday or whatever?
- We don't know.
- Like donuts, munchkins?
- I had a summer birthday.
- We brought in dirt and pennies.
We need that.
- Damn, that was so bad.
- We're so poor.
- Yeah, we bought in tuppence.
- Yeah.
(blows raspberry)
- Tuppence.
- I went to school in a chimney.
- We bought in tuppence, dog.
- I just thought this was--
- It's the fucking tuppence.
- Yeah, did you ever watch Matilda?
- Yeah.
- So that school, that wasn't my school,
but inside the chokie that was my school.
It was like a school within a school.
- Have you ever watched Matilda?
- No.
(laughing)
- What's up?
- Huh?
(laughing)
- My cousin is in Matilda.
- Yo, what the fuck?
- My life was like Matilda since Mrs. Trunchbull.
(laughing)
- We talked about this one time
and I've thought about it maybe like just everyday since
is that that chocolate cake in Matilda,
I wanna eat that so bad.
- Oh my God.
- It grossed me out, bro.
I thought when she says I put blood and sweat into it,
I thought when I was a kid--
I don't like it's a blood cake. Are you kidding me? That is probably trunchbull
sweat. Oh my God. You want that bull crap dude that no it's not miss
trunchbull. I want her to sweat me by my damn pigtails. It's the cafeteria.
The lunch lady's sweat. Oh then never mind. Miss trunchbull. But that
chocolate cake looks so good. What's the miss day? What's the ones thing?
Miss honey. Miss honey. Miss honey. Miss honey. Miss honey. Miss honey.
It just makes you want to like.
Yep. That movie makes you want to like your teachers. It's a good. They did
a good job with you want to like miss trunchbull. No, I would say that movie
makes me want to have magic powers
teachers
levitate
the cake look at bat and I like teachers.
The cake looks so good. I thought the cake look terrible. Yeah, I want to see
like a
cake looks so good. I thought they're like well, okay, the kids with the kid
is ugly and fat, but the cake looks really good. I wanted it to be a milk
bar cake.
I thought when they eat the TV dinners in that movie,
I always thought that looked really good.
- Oh, the carriage in that movie looked good.
- I did wanna eat the TV dinners too.
- The TV dinner in Matilda,
I always thought that looked good when I was a kid.
- Their house is nice.
- I would love to eat Danny DeVito.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, roast him on a spit.
- He honestly would be a delicious celebrity.
- He would, he's probably one of the tastiest.
- Putting him on a shwarm of spit and shaving him.
- Imagine like lamb and beef gyro mix,
Danny DeVito, Andy Milonakis.
Oh my goodness.
You know, I mean I think that Andy Malinakis is probably full of some weird stuff.
Because he's Greek?
No.
Just like, I don't know.
He'd be the perfect one to be half Euro.
I feel like I would not want to eat Danny DeVito because I don't want to cut out, cut
down on the rest of his body of work.
I feel like if I...
Bruce Valanche.
Imagine how much more you would enjoy watching his movies and TV shows if you knew he was
inside you.
At least until you pooped him out.
That's not really how I look at stuff.
You don't look at stuff like that?
Preston Lacey.
Why are you trying to eat like big fat?
I heard they're going to do that in Jackass Pot.
Preston Lacey would have like...
Can they all eat Preston Lacey?
It's like the scene in Day of the Dead.
Preston Lacey would be too raw.
That'd be a tough butcher job, Preston Lacey.
You want like 15% fat.
I think Jack Black would be pretty good.
Jack Black would be tasty.
No.
Yeah.
You guys are making too...
I feel like you're making like 50/50 fat.
Probably.
Have you ever seen a Wagyu?
I've never seen a Wagyu.
Jack Black would be tasty.
No.
Yeah.
You guys are picking too--
like, I feel like you're picking 50/50.
Probably.
Have you ever seen a wagyu beef cow?
A wagyu?
Yeah, they're fat as well.
But I feel like you want someone--
100% wagyu beef.
Jack Black is made of wagyu beef.
You know, like the prefectures in Japan, where the people live
to like 120, because they have a very specific diet of rice
and fish.
And I feel like you want someone--
So OK, I would just eat those Japanese people.
I'm just saying like you want like a grass-fed cow.
The equivalent of a grass-fed cow.
So like a vegetarian or vegan person.
No.
Or a big fat person with lots of meat.
You want a big fat.
You want somebody full of fat.
Are you gonna eat a whole person in one go?
I mean, if you're eating...
Well, not in one go.
It's meal prep.
I'd have like my freezer in the basement.
That would be like, I'd like write "Preston" on the lid and I'd just have that for a month.
How long are you planning on eating?
Is this not one, this is forever?
You're trying to like sustain your...
It's however long it takes me to eat him.
I mean then I'm gonna next alarm you don't know you get one cow you have a
big freezer you probably yeah you probably would try to be trying to
UberEATS Jack Black yeah you try to get the ultimate Jack Black burger that now
that's a there's an app idea and UberEATS where you can order different
celebrities yeah like all of them are just like they're all a satellite
kitchens anyway true so if you're getting Jack Black you could be getting a
Jack Black impersonator I just don't know if I could really come around on
murdering a human being for this. You wouldn't be murdering them, you'd just be eating them.
You're following just like a serial killer kills these people just by chance.
It's the same thing with like a restaurant where I don't want to see the cow that I'm eating.
Also you can't, for whatever reason, even though it is
blackjack black, you're like, "I ate it." Even though it is blackjack.
You can't identify the body. Well probably nobody can.
I don't have like the head with the apple.
- Well yeah.
- Well you also, it's like,
I know you don't wanna see the cow
before you eat it or whatever,
but I feel like seeing the celebrity
before you eat them is different
'cause you see them, like it's like awesome
when you see them.
- They have a good life.
- Like when you see the cow, it's like sad.
- Oh, yeah.
- You're not taking a photo with the cow with droopy eyes.
Like.
(laughing)
- But if I like watch School of Rock,
I'm like, oh, I'm excited to eat this guy.
- Taking a selfie with Jack Black
before he like goes into the slaughterhouse.
(laughing)
- Before they just put the bolt in his head.
- He's just jet blacked out.
(laughing)
- He's still rock and roll.
- He's skadoosh.
(laughing)
- As you like turn up.
- Watch out!
- That's what they do.
- That's pretty hot, dude.
That's hot.
- They shoot the bolt into his head.
He just goes, watch out!
- Ow!
(laughing)
- What's that bolt, Crest?
- He goes like just completely rigid.
can do it around like a piece of wood.
Well, we kill Jack Black. It's so quiet. Now we can finally think
everyone. Oh my God, I've got the best all the cure for cancer. Oh my
God, all carbon emissions halt in the world. Everyone builds
futuristic because he's walking around doing funny for it. Yeah,
he was in like the psychic energy of the human race. He was did yeah the guy who
was supposed to cure cancer got distracted by kick a poo. Yeah
Patrick starts wearing button down shirts.
I don't know what happened. You're a lawyer.
Oh, good evening. Everybody gets British
only American accent.
He's like he's like a an emissary of the devil. He's put here to like
inhibit the potential of humanity.
He is, dude. His fucking rock crap is fucking driving me crazy.
Yeah, tribute devil thing.
Yeah. Remember, Paul F. Tompkins is the devil in the movie.
Yep. Is he?
I think so.
And then we ought to eat him too.
Paul F. Tompkins turns into the devil once he gets the pick of destiny.
So, okay, we should just eat everybody that's in the Tenacious D movie.
Dave Grohl.
Yeah, he's still-- I thought the-- no, the other one died.
Yeah, well, Dave Grohl will soon.
Did we already talk about this, how Dave Grohl denied AIDS?
No.
I think you said it was cool.
Like he thought it was cool.
He thought it was cool to be like AIDS isn't real for like 15 years.
Wow.
Pretty crazy.
Damn.
It's just like how can you feel so strongly about it that you're going to take that stance?
Yeah, they were like doing benefit concerts to like benefit the idea that AIDS did not
exist.
Just to make the AIDS people spend more money on it.
That's not a benefit concert, that's a drawback concert.
Yeah, they were like, it was like a...
like vacuum to suck up the money. Red Cross. He's cool though. Dave Grohl. It's sad they
made the devil movie right as the guy went to hell. I think they invited it on themselves
by courting the devil. It is bro. It's like the Pulcher guys. They made a movie about
the devils. They made a movie where they're recording their new haunted house. Studio
666. Yeah you didn't see the trailer for it? It was on a few movies. It was on ahead of
have a few big movies. I feel like it was on B. Flick. So it is in theaters. I
got about B. Flick. What's B. Flick? Lady on Fortnight told us to check out B.
Flick. See, we just told you. We're like, Oh, you have to go see Morbius in
the theater. It's going to blow your mind. And she's like, I don't really
watch movies in the theater. I usually watch them on B. Flick.
She's like B. Flick. It's got all the movies.
And then her husband is like some like, yeah, some fake streaming service that
couldn't find called Beeflix or if you just think Netflix is called Beeflix.
What did that guy say at the zoo?
What was his company called?
Oh I can't remember.
Yeah, he was like.
Yeah, there was a guy who was talking to us.
We're trying to do the thing with Alex with the face paint.
And there's just a guy who came up to us and he was like, "Have you guys heard of like
Capture Reimagine?"
And I was just like, "Oh, I don't know.
I don't know if I've heard of it."
He's like, "No, no, no.
Tell me.
Have you heard of it?"
Have you heard of it?
Yes or no.
It sounds like something I might have heard of
and he's like, that's 'cause it doesn't exist yet.
It's my idea.
(laughing)
Is that out yet?
He's like, ah, is that out yet?
Yeah, it doesn't exist yet.
It's in my head.
It might be on technology,
but you know, I don't really like technology.
It's in my head.
(laughing)
- That's pretty good.
- We talked about this for like 30 minutes.
- That's a really good gutch.
- It's so well done.
- We have it, you filmed the whole thing.
- Yeah, I have it.
It's a video.
It's just a 30 minute video of a tiger.
- Really?
- I've gotta release that.
guys voice to allow you have to really yeah we could it's funny I just want to
lay it was so fucking annoying I was like Alex was wearing like shorts and a
tiger shirt and it was like 30 degrees out of why we just tell him to leave I
was I thought he was gonna go it's a new show I really give it a much he's gonna
sing joke you could have made him sing probably be flex be flex captured
reimagined on beef licks calm this is new it's not dude don't even that is so we
got that for Caleb and he doesn't like it what is what do you notice about this
this giant thing there's a dragon elephant gecko what look at the middle
people who are these two characters
fucking Lincoln's
that on his desk.
They got me some Japanese thing and put it on my desk and it's huge is giant
it's like
and it's just a giant fucking breath of the wild.
It's not a poster.
It's like it's like wood.
Yeah,
it's like a wait, wait, hold on, pull it down. Yeah, just move it. The painting
down.
Let's move it out of the way. Something behind it. Flip it. No. What is it
behind it?
Okay, that's a picture of me.
It's a cool picture. I drew of Caleb. That's nice. Tansom. This fight is it
like that? I don't know. It makes no sense. It doesn't. Oh, you broke. You
Broke it you bought it you got a yet to use. Yeah, it was a hundred dollars. Hang it up over there now
We're gonna put this in your in your on your curtain over there this we should just pop the fucking snow
That stays in there. That's a nice wooden frame. We just
Breath of the wild you are insane if you think we're getting rid of that you are psycho if you hate Lincoln
I don't think I don't think either of you guys would stop me from I would I would stop you just bite him
I would slap you silly
It would hurt my feelings to see any one of us hurt like physically hurt another that's not hurt
It's okay
Like can you imagine what it would be?
What would you feel if you saw like if you guys walked in you saw me like hit Alex really hard?
In the face by one of our good friends who twice Neil
Punched you in the face twice
Twice like genuinely punched you in the face. I don't want to get into that story, but whoa
Yeah, I
Watched you throw Alex against the ground very violently like a nose gentle that was not gentle
Yeah, it was you were really grabbing him. Yeah, actually no he didn't the first the first thing he tried to choke me
You remember that we were at a party and he tried to Homer Bart you did try to Homer Bart me
And then the second one was a
Not a very touchy group of friends though. Yeah, no, I feel like like Noah was just here
I realize whenever me and Noah are hanging out. We like push him around all the time. Yeah. Yeah, and we touch each other
Don't like that. Yeah, I feel like I've given you a hug like twice and anytime I do it I'm like
We pushed each other around alone when he was in town was Jubio. Oh, yeah
He's another guy who if he's here, I'll just try to push him over for no reason.
Because he's so tall.
He looks like he'd be real easy to push over because his head is so big and full of liquid.
He has a hydrocephaly.
My head is full of Haritos.
It is, dude. It's bubbling. You can hear it in his ears if you get close enough.
It's true. It's tamarind Haritos.
If he goes past like a 45 degree angle, just all the liquid just pours out of his ears.
Yeah.
yeah there's a guy in school who used to like fight with his friends the
principal yeah the principal
morning announcements. If you excuse me, my friend,
nice try, Derek. Derek dress up as a ninja. Try to attack me. I was doing
the word of the day is
word of the day.
I went to the word high school. I went to word high school on
Sesame Street. It's in ninth grade. He's in a college prep class. The word of the
day is banana. No, they would have a word of the day at my high school and it would be like
hope or inspire or something like that. Every day they would end up. You could have just
cycled back and forth. Today is inspire. Today's word is creativity. They used to play music
on the announcements in the morning. It was pretty tight. I went to old fashioned school
where they just announced stuff on the damn announcements. Am I right? Kids nowadays want
to play music, do words of the day. I don't know what this bull crap is. You had a PA
system in every room that played it yes we didn't we didn't have that they we
used to tell the janitor to come get kids to like go to the principal's office
yeah yeah the janitor would like knock on door be like fuck mr. wolf wants to see
this one mr. wolf
what big what big eyes you have mr. it's probably a good prank to do on your
principal speaking of the word of the day you guys should go check out the
word of the week. Yes, sir on patreon.com/home planet. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
what's every week? People what's on offer here? You know, look out for what
can they find? It's gonna be an episode every week. Yeah, of what? Of ten
minutes stuff, you know, sketches, variety, talking, just kind of us
putting together just a general vibe of like good fun. Would you say it's a
variety show called the home planet show? I would say it's a variety show
called the home planet show. Would you say that people could expect to
encounter a white thug on this kind of show? I would say perhaps. Probably in the
future. Perhaps. Given a word like because we don't really find the word of the
weeks come to us it's not we don't choose them so if there's an appropriate
one maybe. Thug. White. The week is white. White. White dash thug. I don't know Patrick can do a cartwheel. Perhaps. Would you say you could do a cartwheel?
- I'm asking you.
- No, say no.
- I would say no.
- I would say probably not, but I'm open to being wrong.
- You should come on the show, do a curse.
- So you guys are also posting video breakdowns.
- Video breakdowns.
- When you talk about a one minute video for two hours.
- I'm in one of them.
- We indulge in talking about things.
- And then you have old videos.
- Which are terrible videos from four years ago.
- Where a lot of us are doing a lot of embarrassing things.
- A lot of embarrassing things.
- Whoa.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
- So it's over.
- We're done.
- That's really, that scared me.
- All right.
- That's too loud.
- Yeah, go check out Home Planet.
- And check us out on tour.
Yeah, swagpoop.com/shows.
Okay, bye. - Bye.