Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
(imitating guitar)
- You can't go back to the--
- No, 'cause when the guitar starts,
like that's when the fucking,
they're still doing the,
(imitating guitar)
They're still doing that and that.
I don't think so. They are. I think you have the Halo some wrong song song wrong.
No. Yeah. They they it goes over it. It's like an accent or whatever. I'm gonna go
over you and I dunk on you. You did. I'm gonna I'm gonna get some hops. I'm gonna
accidentally drink soap this morning. You drank soap? Mm-hmm. Why? I didn't clean
out a cup enough. I'm so not used to having a dishwasher. He saw the blue color.
He's like oh Mountain Dew. I saw the soap and I was like that could just be because I was
putting the cold brew in and I was like oh that could just be like a head yeah and
then I I mixed it with the milk then took one sip and immediately was just like oh
fuck spit it out you can have soap yeah it's normal yeah I know but my tummy
hurts now and I need you guys to rub that's just that's the coffee that's not
and I need you guys to rub me soap doesn't so makes your mouth I need you
to rub me soap has no effect on the stomach I'm a scientist I've researched
this and I need a rubbing a lot of different ways and soap debate
practically disappears by the time listen to the stomach it's not about it's
not about what you're talking about it's about my belly and how I need it rubbed
and I'm scientifically saying that's false I just polished facts are not
stealing yeah just a pinch of pussy I just polished off so I gotta buy the we
gotta buy the I think that that is a good first first mini fridge item yes we
get like a 64 pack of Pussy Energy. The same one Jack got with the
shirts. I think that's a good choice. I've never had it.
I wish you had. Wait there's at least one sip left in that. Yeah,
yeah, get that sip. Drink it like a genie. It's a genie flavor. Something might
come out. That was way too small a sip to tell anything about what this is. Nope, you
got it it feels like we're ordering a prickling my tongue well it's prickly
pear flavored so that makes perfect sense mm-hmm I think it's it's really
terribly area sparkling passion fruit and lychee flavored wrong that's way off
produced in the Netherlands mm-hmm you know same place as a Red Bull is that
true do they have like a Swedish zero grams of salt they do have a spring
though it's the friggin the way I jump around and bounce after I drink a little
- You're also bringing your stuff, that damn Red Bull.
- Yup.
- That's right.
- I was buying, I put on a bad pair of underwear today.
It's like, you know when you like put on a pair
of underwear and you're like,
"Oh, I gotta throw it out." - A rotten pair, oh my God.
The ones that have holes,
just your balls just pop out of the bottom of them.
- I had a pair of boxers where the elastic
has completely deteriorated and it makes that crunch sound.
And I was-- - Ugh.
- Yeah. - Okay, that's not--
- Yeah, I don't know about-- - No, no, that's--
- You've been nutting on those.
- No, it's not a nutting.
It's the elastic. - It is a nut.
the band has like completely deteriorated. You've been completely
nutting on to the thing. I can go get it for you it's in the trash right now it's in the
trash in the office. I'm gonna shatter the waistband when they do the math and break
your bed. Because I bought the underwear on the way here. I bought a new pack of underwear.
And you swapped? Yeah I swapped out here. You are a monster. Can we have a no shitty
underwear in the- It's not- I didn't shit in there. You literally said it was covered
with dried shit and that's why it's so dry that you shatter it you ate granola
bars into it and that's why it's crunchy. It does sound it sounds like uh when you
pull it it sounds like styrofoam. It probably tastes like styrofoam too.
It's that's so gross. Yeah. It cracks like a like a salt field.
Yeah pretty much. That looks bad. I bought I bought underwear on the way here
and I was in the store and uh there's like a little. Is there an
- Is there a Thunders outlet around here?
- No, I went to a place called Jimmy Jazz.
I bought some Nike dry fit underwears.
- Damn.
- These things are nice as hell.
- That's sick.
- Yeah, but watched a kid just get smacked
in the face by his mom.
- You said that, what did he do though?
- He was sitting there and he was just moving around
and she said, "Stop moving."
And then he just got the shit smacked out of him.
- I mean, to me, that's a clear cut case.
- Yeah.
- Hey buddy, you moved.
- She said if you don't stop moving right now,
I'm gonna smack the shit out of you harder when we leave.
- So she gave him a warning. - When we leave the store.
- Yeah, she gave him a warning, that's right.
- And then the kid said to the mom, the kid said,
"We're not in a store, we're in a shoes store."
And I was like, "Oh, you are buying yourself."
He bought himself six more slaps.
- Oh my, I would've knocked his teeth out.
- Yeah.
- I can't believe that, dude.
- Yeah, crazy. - We're in a shoe store?
not in a store. We're in a shoes store. What a fucking brat. What
didn't you should have gotten some licks in dude? I honestly
I turned and I was like oh no dude. Hey, you need some help
over here. Yeah. Yeah. That kid's that kid's going to be in
a coffin to destroy him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hold on one second
man. It's a good idea. I did you should be able to phone a
friend to hit your kid. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like I mean,
because then it's not if I were that if I were that mom, I
I'll be ackley I'd be I'd be dragging him from the the sneaker section of the
dress shoes section, because I'm dressing him for the cough and
that's right yeah, yeah, I'm getting fucking from aldehyde injected into his
skin, make him puff up a little bit yeah, yeah, give him a fake eye do that
was I mean I haven't seen a good good old fashioned. You should be able to
hire a hit man to punch your kid in the face, like you should like as a guy
walks up to your kid and just smacks him and goes, "That's for misbehaving at home."
And then you can be like, "What in the world?"
"I'll have to chase you away around this corner."
I guess that'll happen every time that you misbehave from now on.
And then the kid will be like, "Oh, I'm gonna get him."
"But it's not my mom or dad's fault."
"Yeah, well that wouldn't make any sense."
"I'm not gonna get a complex about this."
"She tried to chase him."
"It's a crazy bald guy."
"She chased him away around the corner with money and then he was gone."
hit your kid too much, they get too talented like Michael Jackson. I don't
want that bullshit. I don't need that life. Yeah, I know, but then they get too talented, but then they develop weird crap.
Exactly, and also, you know, the worst thing... Here's the only reason not
hit your kid, okay? It'll make them too talented at something, and then
eventually they'll become super famous and write a memoir where they talk
non-stop about how you hit them. And then they tell some weird
things like, "Yeah, my dad used to eat peanuts with the shell on." Yeah, they
definitely they'd latch on to something yeah. It's like man my dad was so my dad
was so weird growing up he would hit me and he would eat peanuts with the shell
on yeah. I don't need some kids on my fucking business. No way. Yeah no fuck
that. My dad used to put peanuts in the microwave and eat them. Well that's just
boiled. That's bold. No my dad didn't do that. I'm just saying this is a thing.
I'm saying that's what they would say in the memoir. That's what they would say in the memoir.
They would ruin your life. Yeah. You'd be in like a nursing home and they'd start to shun you.
because oh here comes mr. shell yeah mr. shells yeah mr. shells a better name
than Shelly unless it's mom who does it maybe they call you like mr. peanut like
after mr. peanut that was that's a pretty obvious name yeah why you wish it
but like you know mr. shell mr. shell mr. shells better than mr. peanut yeah what
mr. what as an insult mr. peanuts a distinguished man
Mr. Peanut's so rich, nothing embarrassing about that.
Mr. Peanut, also, you call someone Mr. Peanut and they're like, "Mr. Peanut, how's that an insult?"
Mr. Peanut, you call someone Mr. Shell and they go, "Oh, he probably eats peanuts with a shell on."
Or he might eat shell.
Or he eats shell turtles, that guy.
That's from Mr. Peanut, so we know this has to do with peanuts, not like eggshells or something.
Immediately they're like, "Well, that's a... Yeah, that makes sense."
If they just called you Shell, they might get confused.
Exactly.
The Mr. helps a lot.
Mr. Yeah. It's kind of like a signifier. It's like a peanut-based insult.
Exactly. Yeah. You can't go anything other than Mr. though. Monsignor? No. Nope. Monsignor
show? Then it's a snail thing. Yeah. Are you guys on high alert? Oh yeah. So what DefCon
are we at? First of all, can we get a DefCon thing? Yeah. Oh, that's a good idea. Yeah.
Like a sliding scale. I would say we're 10 minutes to midnight. We're in, we haven't,
We got an office.
Yeah.
We're in an hour recording in our office.
We're here.
We rented this office and then after we moved all of our expensive cool stuff in here, we're
like you know dusting our hands off long hard days working on walking out.
I move my whole computer in here.
We meet the superintendent of the building.
She's an old Italian lady.
Well, she's Italian, Dominican and Puerto Rican.
Okay so Italian.
Triple threat.
Yeah.
with the she made me she made me like she made me know she was like like I'm like
first two sentences she was like um I'm not gonna say her name it's funny that
she does have the accent of mixing all three of those yeah yeah oh she thought
I was Italian - she looked at me and went oh yeah you were Russian Ukraine and I
said no I'm Italian she said oh Italiano yeah yeah and then she looked at you and
she said what are you she said oh she said Italian I said no she said German
and I said no I said just a bunch of stuff she's like oh yeah but we walked
out and we don't like you and like just like all people love me that's not that's
not a fact that's completely our boy Phil called you lame run whoa that I do
remember that he called you he hasn't stopped thinking about it I didn't I
didn't hear that I actually didn't think you've been thinking about that a lot
- What happened to you?
- He got you so good.
He got you so fucking good.
- No, I'm an old soul.
- You're an old soul.
- I'm an old soul.
- No way.
- Old people see me and they know I'm wise beyond my years.
- Old people see you and they look at you--
- They can have a conversation on the--
- They look at you and think you're on their level
and that's why they don't like you.
- The thing is, I have inherited the worst old person traits
from my grandparents.
Like I--
- Stomach problems?
- Still, yeah, stomach problems, sure.
- You got that smell.
- No, just like--
- You got that weird smell.
you know, just like like like hoarder, like just picks up like like books out
of the trash and brings them home. Like I'm going to read this and like that
that kind of like just telling telling people in a love yeah being like, oh,
did you ever hear about this this this thing that happened in the one thousand
and fifty yeah horrible horrible terrible. Yeah, really annoying to find
a deal. I was saying I would love to fast forward to be seventy years old,
because I think I'll be a really, really good seven year old. I'm a really
annoying twenty something year. Yeah, we hate you be the perfect grandpa of all
time. You would get so good. That's what I'm saying, right? And like this long hair
could be really wispy, right? And gray. You'd be so good at metal detecting.
Dude, I would be so good. That's what I'm saying. Yeah. You need to get into
that stuff, bird watching. Anyway, the... Anyway, yeah. So this lady, she's
talking to us, she's so excited, we're renting the place and she's like,
"Oh." And just so you know,
you'll see walking up and down this block, there's a beautiful 31 year old
white man. That's what she said. Yeah, those exact words and he is the
police description. He used to he used to live in this apartment. He used to
live here and he fell in love with the place, but then he lost the apartment
and now he tries to get back in because he loves it so much. So he broke that
window right there and he went in a broken. He went in there a few weeks
ago. He just he loves the place. He's beautiful by the way. Yeah, beautiful
and she's also like he's so she clever like
like he's a velociraptor. He's so smart that he figured out the
combination to the bill and we're just in a oh
great great news. Yeah, that's cool. That's really good.
So she's like we put a security camera down there and
like that's going to help us. He just he loves the apartment so
much he's trying to get back in. He just loves it. No, he has to
get home. He needs to go home. If he pays us rent,
I mean I'm done now with that's what I was sounds like we should if he shows up
if he's like trying to break in with a we'll give you a tour bro like you hang
out whenever if you really need to hang out that bad yeah just he's really that
beautiful also yeah if you're good look like we could probably use a like a good
looking guy in the crew like a really good looking guy yeah also he used to be
a construction worker he could help us set some stuff yeah also he used to be a
construction worker, but now he's into drugs. We could get some drugs. I love
drug like drugs. I love doing drugs. It's not pressed with fent yeah, and he
probably wouldn't he wouldn't have drugs that are pressed with friend fent
though. I don't know you would have drugs pressed with friend. Yeah, yeah,
after he's done with us friendship. That's right. He could live under the
stairs there, but so we're pretty much calling him the lovely invader, the
beautiful invader. Yeah, we have to deal with the beautiful invader now. Yeah,
the little the craziest part of it is like is not to me and some strangler
the home body is she told us this whole story about how he so he walks out. He
runs up and down. She said she also said she said oh the other day he was
running up and down trying to get in, but he saw me and he left
running up and down. She's so powerful. He ran by and tried to get in, but he
saw her and he was out of the he's trying to displace enough air that it
just pushes the doors open. Yeah, it's by fast running around the building and
trying to create a tornado. He's building up speed so that he can just run
through phase through the can try to dive kick through the way. Yeah, he's
running around to he's trying to run fast enough to spin Earth's rotation
backwards, so we can go back back in time to win. Yeah, he's trying to
Superman. Yeah, that's a really yeah. What what I the whole thing of the what
it felt like a though like a cruel joke is that he like he got into the unit
directly next to our like he tries to get he's not going to get in don't worry,
but by the way he broke the window right next to your window and he went in
there. Also, he must be a thin man because I was a small hole tiny tiny
drugs and he's good looking yeah yeah and thirty one. I bet he's white. I bet
he's shredded dude definitely. I bet he's like I can't stop writing. It just
like him yeah perfect. I want to I want to I want to show him. Can you imagine
that he can he can have a better life. Can you imagine his cum gutters? Oh, this is
his V. I bet he's so cut, dude. What if we see him? And he's got to have a small
cock to fit in that thing, too. Yeah, definitely. No, that was a tiny hole.
It's not a power thing, either. Maybe he can like squeeze his body like an
octopus. See, that really didn't look like a human-sized hole. Also, it was a very small hole and also there was
there was jagged glass pointing, like, surrounding the hole. Yeah.
and so he might be cut up to to have to nurse back to he literally is like a
dark souls NPCs, probably covered in scars and he he's chasing some long lost
like sorrowful spirit of his like past dwelling yeah yeah and he's called the
beautiful invader and then i heard i the when i was trying to figure out
something and i went into the lobby of the apartment building the other day and
i heard from the apartment that she pointed to is like that's where he lived.
I heard that one Spanish song is like
so maybe he's just trying to get back into the party. Oh true. Maybe he's got
a non stop party. I was up there. She also another detail. She told us that I
forgot about until the other day is that she after she said after he lost the
apartment, his roommate left to oh yeah. He probably doesn't even realize his
roommates gone. He's probably going to get back into the apartment teamed up.
They might have a team rocket kind of thing. Oh shit. The thing is we either
have a nemesis or a best friend and either way i'm like really happy about it.
Yeah, like it's cool. It's a big it's nice to finally have like a villain.
Dude, i've never had an actual like i've never had like it like an other world
really like a slasher villain. Yeah, it's fucking sick dude. We have to
defend ourselves. We've been talking about it just being five nights at
freddy's every time we're at the office. That's cool dude like i want that so
badly yeah playing like like maybe one and also the best part is he cuts the
power. Oh shit, well, I got the power and then we just start yeah, it's all dark
start hearing change just drag
down the hallway
be cool. So there's a grumble yeah.
Oh my God, that would be so sick open the door. He has one huge arm. Yeah,
yeah, I like it like a like a like a left for dead. Yeah, I'm the Popeye no
or like no, I mean pop. Maybe his roommate could be Popeye. Okay, so it's
charger it's the charger and pop I and then like which one I'm more scared of
maybe it's like a boss fight where like we had been like eating spinach so we
have to like hit the Popeye guy before he gets to the spinach we were eating or
else he'll get more we need you know we could we could poison the spinach by
putting soap in it you know we need to keep it around here some red barrels
yeah that we know that makes that makes the fight way harder if you're standing
right barrels at him though what if he uses a chain spinning attack and he
blows up all the red barrels at once. I'm not going to pretend that I know the game
faq on this guy. Well, red barrels respawn if they're needed. Exactly, yeah. And also,
you don't need to keep little floating cross. Little floating plus sign. Get some health.
Those will be good. Yeah, they're expensive, man. Little green floating holographic plus
sign. Barbarian, rogue, wizard. Okay, can I have a bow and arrow? What did I say you
another rogue. You can be a ranger archer yeah or yeah, thank I was going to say I
think if we keep some chew jellies around, if we keep those in a bottle, we
can bring them to the hag and then she'll turn them into potions. If we get
some room we oh we got to get we got to turn this into a crafting table. Yeah,
oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, because we're going to need to upgrade our stuff. You
know once we get the bone arrow and the sword in the
chain mail yeah, we're going to need and I'll probably buy the scar. This is I'm
- We're supposed to go to Medieval Times soon.
- You're supposed to?
- Yeah. - You have an appointment?
- I do.
- You have a portal opening soon?
- Yeah, my girlfriend has tickets to Medieval Times.
- Oh, we're gonna need a portal.
- Yeah, we definitely need a portal.
- We're gonna need a portal to our home.
- Yeah.
- Also, we're gonna need to invite,
maybe invite some other players.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, to defend our--
- Oh my God, we could do a raid.
What if he, what if--
- He's doing a raid.
- No, yeah, no, what if we're like,
we go home for the night, we come back in the morning,
he's in here, he's like terraformed it
and we like his layer and we have to do a raid we have to recruit the other people
from the apartments and stuff he terraforms our office into his plate do
so once we do when we kill when we defeat him it goes back to normal yeah
okay I was gonna say it mad or we have to use a converter shard that's true but
all of our stuff would be repurposed into new things right so it'd be like so like
this would probably be like this would be like a drug table the computer would be
like drugs.
The computer would have the Silk Road OS on it. That skateboard would probably be
a pile of drugs, too. It'd probably be a giant pile of crack. Yeah. Yeah. Alex
told me my room looks like a crack den. Your room? Yeah. He, Alex has never met
anybody who's ever done crack.
That is so funny. Your room is, like, full of, like, British comedy DVDs and
the beds on the floor. The beds on the floor right now, 'cause the bed frame
broke in the move.
- Okay.
- That's why it's on the floor.
- I guess, it's not even your bed,
it's a mattress on the ground.
- Yeah.
- You don't have a bed.
- No.
- You're a bedless man.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, what's that like?
- Dude, it's been crazy.
- It's crazy, it's insane.
- It's like I moved--
- It's so hard to fall onto a mattress on the ground.
- Yeah.
- When you are really tired from a long day's work.
- 'Cause it's a bigger fall. - I love falling onto my bed.
- It's a what?
- It's a, you know, it's not like--
- Yeah, you gotta have a comfy mattress.
- Yeah, you go down, like if you go all the way down.
- Did either of you do that mattress scam?
- No.
- The purple mattress thing?
- What is it?
- You could, it is a, anybody can do this, I think.
- Yeah, there's someone like Chloe.
- A million people in New York did it.
You just order a purple mattress,
or maybe it doesn't work anymore 'cause,
but when like lockdown was real serious,
they wouldn't take returns on mattresses.
- 'Cause it would cost more money for them
to get the mattress back.
- And then clean it and everything.
- So you would, so you--
- You say it doesn't fold out correct.
- I think I know where this is going.
- So you just order it and then you say--
- You buy the mattress, you kill the delivery man.
(laughing)
- And then it's like, good luck trying to bring this back,
you fucking asshole. - Exactly, yeah.
- But yeah, you would just order it
and then you would say like, it's too weird.
- Yeah. - And then they would--
- It didn't fold correctly. - It's like a $2,000 mattress.
- I mean, that's a scam, that's not just mattresses,
that's a lot of-- - Nope, that's a lot of stuff.
- Well, but mattress-- - Frequently, yeah.
- It has to be something where they won't take returns.
Here's a crazy fact, maybe it's why, they know, Purple Mattress, big Mormon company, owned
by the Mormons.
Those stupid idiots.
Those stupid freaks.
I love Mormons actually.
You can do that on Amazon too though.
Really?
You get free shit?
Yeah, so you can get free shit, you can say it's stolen, but also you can also just like
if it's a thing that you only need to like, like if it's not something you need permanently,
it's just something you, like say you order like, this is a dumb example, like scissors
or something.
Oh that's so fucking stupid dude.
that's a use in return of all. Oh, you idiot, why would you say that
returning eight dollars scissors, not scissors? Obviously, but you know what I
mean you can just return. You can open stuff and return it to it's a scam
ordering scissors and using them to cut one thing. Yeah, you're only going to
need them one time right.
That's what else you need them for sharp. Yeah, they had the the sharp it
was facing the wrong way. They sharp the wrong side of the so yeah, you could
order a full set of silverware, eat a bunch of meals and then return them.
That's a really good idea. It's a scam, but then what about the next time you
need to eat? Well, you do it again or you can just return a year's worth of
food. That's the best part about the scam is they don't get mad at you
because they still get the stuff back. It's true and you can do it all the
food. Leave all the food on it. Well, yeah, I mean it's not your job. I don't
want to clean. Well, that's you. You order dishes and then you get them all
dirty, but I don't want to do the damn dishes. So then you return them.
exactly. It's really smart or you can order food on Amazon like groceries
right and then, but then you eat you listen, you eat all that you eat all the
groceries. Then you go to another grocery store,
you buy the same groceries and you say you're returning those great and you
just little. They know it's completely different. Groceries are doing that
forever. Exactly yeah, and then you and then you're basic, you're saving a lot
of money. Every time thirty dollars, depending on yeah, well, no, because you
So if you buy the groceries expensive from Amazon and then you buy them cheap
from somewhere else, you return them, you make that's called a profit.
Exactly, it's a profit deal. That's how businesses are run. Yeah, profit and we
have a business. We need to start getting into drop shipping or something.
Yeah, while we have a space or maybe like scams or maybe we or maybe robbery.
Yeah, we should rob something or somebody and then we plan it all here.
- Yeah.
- Oh, 'cause then we can buy a whiteboard to plan it?
- Listen, it's subterranean.
This could be a crime den.
- This could be a really good crime den.
- I can't wait.
- Yeah.
- Let's soap start--
- We need to hire a kingpin.
- We're gonna need--
- Because let's be honest, I mean--
- None of us have--
- We're all criminals, but none of us have the build
that's required for a kingpin. - We have kingpin attributes.
I'm bald.
- Yeah.
- You're square.
I'm clever. - Square?
- You're just boxy.
- That's true.
- But we need to double your width.
- Exactly, yeah.
- If I got any wider with my shoulders and my belly.
- You see, that's why we need--
- I'm all torso, baby.
I'm built like a widow.
- That's why we need to get some cloning pods
or genetic modification stuff,
'cause if we combined all three of us--
- Oh, I should get into synthol.
- The combined width of all of us
would definitely be wide enough for a kingpin.
- I should get into synthol injections.
- Oh, yeah, that'd be good.
- Do you get my arms huge?
- Yeah.
- You could be the muscle.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- You can be the muscle we call you the saline.
- I'm the muscle but like I'm, no I'm not working out.
- That's the funniest thing about the Synthol thing
is like you don't get any strength from it.
- Yeah, it's so funny.
- It looks so strong and then, or not even,
you just look like a mutant.
- You look like you were in the microwave,
like you look like a hot dog in the microwave.
- Yeah, it looks, yeah the weird bubbles and stuff.
Yeah, it's cool.
- But you know, that's what I should do.
I should get into Synthol,
I'll get some BK Bold shit going with me.
- If you run at someone with giant balls like that,
they're gonna cower immediately.
- You could do that.
I think I might get a beak.
- A beak?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I think that might be really scary.
- You should get like a pelican beak.
- Yeah.
- It has a pocket.
- Really?
I was thinking maybe like a toucan beak.
- Oh, that would be so beautiful on you.
- That'd be really beautiful.
- Okay, well I don't really want it to be beautiful.
I'm kind of more looking to be intimidating.
you would need the other bird of paradise that you need like a plume okay I don't
want a plume because I'm not trying to be beautiful I'm trying to be scared so you
want to look like a like a car okay so what's a scary maybe a chicken's beak
could be possible speak no the area's thing about a condor is the fact that
they're like the wing that they're bald yeah maybe I'll get no beak and I'll
just get wings wings and black wings how do you fight with wings look at Sephiroth
my feet maybe I could kick oh we're gonna need claws on your feet and I could just
get like that. You know what we should do? You know what we should all do?
That's true. But he has arms. The sword is the scary part. I wouldn't have arms. I would be
turning my arms into wings. Here's what we do, okay? We all get an
extra... we all get an extra...
The two winged angel. They call him the two winged angel. He's the scariest villain.
(laughter)
- They call him the one haloed angel.
- That's the scariest part about him.
- I think the simplest way, the simplest body mod
we could do to make us all seem scarier
is get an extra toe right here like a dog.
- That could be brilliant.
- An extra toe halfway up our calves.
- I have an even simpler idea.
We could just get our eyebrows slanted so we look angry.
- Yeah.
- Oh that's good.
- Like henchmen.
- I got pretty good eyebrows for that already.
- I think that, no but it's not.
- That sucked.
- You have made-- - Might make a perfect M.
- That was a really--
- That, are you--
- No, that doesn't make you look angry.
What are you talking about? - M stands for mad.
- You look like a baby. - Oh, okay.
But you're not like,
this is not anything.
- That's a baby pooping diaper face.
- You do look like you're shitting yourself.
You look like you're doing like the,
no.
You do look like, just with the face,
you look like you're pretending to be an old Mexican guy.
(laughing)
- Chingate puto.
Yeah, exactly.
No, yeah, but I'm saying we need our eyebrows need to be rotated at a 45 degree angle.
They need to be slanted down.
No, that's your, you're raising them up, you're slanting them the wrong way.
Yeah, like that.
Exactly, like that but more.
That's not bad.
That's getting there.
Yeah.
Now imagine how scary if you saw that running at you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Out of a crime den.
Cherry on top, cherry on top.
Oh.
Oh, you know what we could all get is a rattler.
Oh shit.
Would we need to get a tail installed or what would we put the rattler on?
These are our penises.
Yeah.
Oh true.
It's like a little extra length and it's ribbed.
Yeah.
Oh for my pleasure.
And we gotta start, I'm telling you now, strongest thing we could do is start hissing.
You sound like a tornado siren.
Yeah, I know.
- Tornado siren.
- Yeah, I know, I'm adding scarier things to it.
- We could get a--
- What's scarier than being in a tornado?
- This, boom!
(yells)
Also, century gun.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Century gun?
- Century.
- Century egg.
- Century egg gun.
- Century gun.
Century eggs are probably pretty hard,
it would hurt if it shot out of a gun.
- Yeah, it's probably--
- And they smell.
- Really hard.
- Yeah. - They smell good.
- They probably smell--
- They don't smell good.
- Those don't actually take 100 years, do they?
- No. - Yes, they do.
- They don't. - They don't.
I think I take like a couple months
100 months it's called the century egg so yeah, but it's cuz it doesn't say I know I
I can tell you that it doesn't take a hundred years because I
Googled literally probably like 20 times does a century egg take a hundred years because I forget every time well
Then that means I can sue you can't sue China. Yes. I would love this is how we take them down
Finally you look badass right now. Yeah, do we all look we all look like some badass Don's
Why are you not letting Cameron use this chair right now? No, you can take it
Why are you letting me yelled at me when I tried to sit in?
Oh, yeah
This chairs and he yelled at me when I tried to sit in either of them
No, I yelled at you and tried to sit in this one
The only time that you should look at your ass to see if you have two chairs is just make sure that you have two
So your neighbor can have one for his ass and guess he yelled at me before
in this chair too because it squeaks. You're allowed to literally can't sit in
any chair at all. Whenever you want.
It's not what you said before. You're putting on airs because we're recording
and you don't want, you don't want the fight to be air, but I'm, I'm, I'm
making it public. You better fuck. No, everyone, everyone harassed Patrick about
this. No.
Take him down. Don't take him. Once and for all. You need to be taken down a
peg. You need to be taken down one. I can't move this chair. I can't move this
hair up or down at all. Look, it doesn't go up anymore. When I had to move it--
You will never fix that.
I will.
You will never in a million years fix that.
You will not.
Because I mean, I'm going to make money if I fix it.
What?
Because then I can flip it.
Is there money stuck in there?
Fuck you, dude. Thank you for giving me this chair.
The guy who you scammed for a free chair?
I didn't scam him. He was giving it to me.
You scammed him. You're a scammer.
Thank you, Will.
- Thank you.
- Getting free shit from him.
- All right, so here's a list for today.
Top 10 questions to ask male top tenners.
So this is kind of a top 10 community.
- We're three male top tenners in a major way.
I would say we're the three most high profile.
- Probably the most male, yeah, the most high profile.
- Most high T.
- Well, definitely high T.
- I'm losing my hair.
He has none, but you have beautiful girl locks.
- I do.
- So what's up with that?
- What's up with it?
- Girl.
Girl, girl, you guys are proving you're a man right now. Prove your chest. We
show me your balls and your penis. How do you get your testosterone tested?
Why? We should do, we should. What are we the fuck, we're the try guys now? I'm
not going to do that bullshit. We should get our testosterone tested and then
whoever has the most. If you're worried about it, go ahead. Whoever has the
most is the alpha of the show. No, you will never be the alpha of the show.
Even if you, it doesn't matter how hot you are. You have dangerous levels of
testosterone, you literally will never be the alpha.
- Well, we'll see.
- You will always be the omega.
- We'll see.
- That's cool, right?
Omega, you like that.
Oh, it sounds cool, right?
- We will see when we get tested.
- Omega's the best one, right?
- Oh yeah.
- Omega's cool.
- Google right now how to get your testosterone test.
- What do you mean, why would we Google that?
Right now, on the show?
- I'm the alpha.
Google the testosterone test.
- No, no, I don't think we will.
use your phone if you'd like little guy go ahead little boy. Why are you sitting so
low? You look really short. It's the chair! How about you roll your shoulders back.
You literally look like a slug. I don't look like a slug. Get off your phone.
Testosterone. You started this trying to alpha dog me and Cameron, the two
co alpha dogs same day testosterone check results you heading king Roman testosterone
what the fucking box cutter on me I didn't pull it on you you just open right
now which one eating ones open it back up bitch let's go no I don't need I don't
need to do this we're gonna sword fight live okay that's gonna snap off you know
But you believe me you fucking idiot. Yeah, you got so worried non-alpha. Yeah, Omega Omega dog
Omega dog
I can get an Everly well testosterone test for $50
That's a bad
That's a bad thing to be sitting on your you can buy it at CVS for
6179 imagine like you take it at Walmart for fun. You take a girl home. She sees that on your dresser. Yeah
God, oh, I thought it was a Colbert test. I'm sorry. That was a $50
Test goes down one
If you search that on your phone
I think it adds you to a list where you will be like the first person they test the remote control on the microchip for
The vaccine on yeah, yeah, they're gonna they're gonna explode your head first. Yeah, if you do anything like that you get
You also get ads before it forever. I get ads for dog DNA tests cuz I mentioned at one time
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah, we talked about it in the yeah, I keep getting dog DNA tests
Yeah
Fuckers you should test because I swear to God he's part German Shepherd. I'd be cool. We'll be cool getting huge
It's so scary. I know he's
Dude, I hope he grows too big. So awesome
I hope he stays just same like low to the ground but gets like
Like like you stretched him like you open him up in Microsoft Paint and just yeah, like yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right
All right now first question. Are you homosexual bisexual or transgender
hole is a hole
hole? It's a hole. Okay, then why don't you fuck an animal? If you think a hole
is a hole,
they call me an animal in the bed. It go. What's up? No, no, if you honestly
think is a hole is a hole. I dare you to fuck a chicken.
dare me I double oh I would hate that I double dog dare you to I would hate
that here's a comment oh boy I would hate that so much I have ascended above
the need for sexuality and that's a comment from Freddie Mercury fart Queen
Freddie Mercury Freddie Mercury for the Queen he did not ascend above sexual
urges I'm a nothing I am completely gay pressure hammer one I am NOT trans buyer
gay I'm heterosexual to be honest I added this I'm straight as a stick are
you though straight straight I know that's from read that name which one oh I
I can't see from over here. What does that say? Does that say PM?
Oh, that's PFTT. Okay.
You gotta move the laptop closer to me.
Okay. This is why we need a super extra large 50-inch TV.
If you have a 70-inch TV...
Then, first of all, congratulations. Second of all, can we have it?
It's ours now.
Question.
You don't ask if we can have it. It's ours now.
No, you gotta negotiate. See, this is a classic Omega Dog mistake that you're making right now.
you got to negotiate and then you tricked him into buying something out
of duct tape, maybe and then like a wallet trading it yeah duct tape
wallet. That's a that we need to go to tape wall tape wallets with the spit
fire logo on yes, so bad. It'll be sick number two question. Are you sexist?
Yes, here's the time. I would say definitely not and I'm honestly proud
of being socially acceptable to everyone, whether they're lgbtq or
anything like that. I don't judge unless you are either a hate sloths be have
murdered people see are a certain person called called Donald Trump D R
rapist or E are sexist or F are gay
the F stand for
never mind
no and I don't think anyone here really is Feminazis are quick to call men
sexist for the dumbest reasons. That's facts kind of I like talking to girls a
lot more than boys in some cases. So if that counts then yeah, did you did you
see the video where it's like it's like a hundred women with their tits out in
Paris yeah and they're sitting they have the Ukraine flag painted and it's like
stop the invasion of Ukraine once Mike's gone crazy keep someone has a crazy Mike
how's that mine probably Patrick's I was stuck under the chair I mean sorry
probably Omega dogs but the video is so funny cuz they're like they have on
their on their tits it's written like it's like a feminist against like Putin
I think it's so cool that they're like that's good yeah he's gonna be like
showing their tits in Paris. I will have to go see the women in Paris and we will
have a long talk with them. I will I will have to see them. I will have to see them in person.
I will have to I will do I need to understand their points. I will have to walk up and down
little rose and look at all of their boobs to make me finally decide no more war.
Women really think that boobs are gonna work against Putin. That's happened before.
Remember there's that picture of some girl. Yeah the white lady. Who's like shows her tits to Putin.
She's like frowns up. Oh that's because to Putin. I thought you meant the lady at the
fucking Chazz or whatever that like sat down with her damn pussy out at the police.
Her snatch. Yeah. Well it's because Putin has been known on occasion
on several occasions to be gay with Donald Trump.
- No. - And a gay guy who sees
boobs will become enraged.
- That's true.
That's a, actually, they're--
- It's like a thorn in a giant's foot.
They become, they chimp out.
- I didn't even think about that.
- They go crazy. - When a gay man sees
a boob in person, there's like a foam--
- That's what he's thinking. - Coming out of their ears.
They're whistling like a train.
- They say, "Why you little," like Homer Simpson.
- Yeah. - Chase the women around.
- Yeah, so that's what they're trying to get him
so angry that he kills himself.
yeah, because he's watching that video and the guy goes to his head loads like
scanners yeah, that would be the best like like somebody committing suicide,
because they're so angry is so funny. It's getting so mad yeah that they just
jump out the window. It's happened not even yeah. They love the way that's
not just like getting so mad and just just charges just smashing out the
window. I do want to jump out of a window. It would be sick. It'd be so I
- he was like a parachute you know it would be really disappointing I'm gonna
jump out of the window and the glass shatters in a way that it kills you
before you true oh yeah I met a guy who jumped out of a window and I he was like
on crutches did he live he lived yeah I wanted to ask him so bad if it was fun
but I feel like that was like yeah I didn't want to ask that's not hey it was
he sensitive I think it was a sensitive subject jumped out of the fucking window
- Yeah, nobody pushed him out of the window.
He did it on purpose.
That's, what an idiot.
- That's true, yeah.
- What am I, what's he doing?
- He didn't win an idiot, he survived.
- Oh, he's a god.
- There was a--
- Probably had a great time, too.
- There's like a--
- Not that you would know.
- It's like a tower of terror.
- I guess he's all sensitive about it.
- Well, what if I had asked him and he said no?
That would be really, like I wouldn't want to--
- Yeah, you don't want to do that.
- That would be more of a bummer.
- Yeah, that's secret knowledge.
That's not for us.
see that would be if you ask somebody if you ask them that instead of getting
mad, you're just like no
that's like that would break my heart. People they say that like if you like a
third degree burn actually feels like really good or something they say yeah
says that like if you if you burn all over your body, it feels really good.
The heat miser said that
it burns off all your
the heat miser said that
heat miser came into my elementary school. The presentation
fire safety. It was the devil, the decree, the degrees of burn is how good
they feel.
If you feel it, if you go, if you're trying to run away from a fire and you
hold your hand to the door and it's hot, that means it's a fun room. Now that I
think about it, that probably definitely is a little kid myth. Yeah, I just
know what a I've never heard first degree. First degree is the worst first
degree. Second is the best second yeah and there is the one with the treasure
chest. Yep, yep, absolutely yep.
yeah number three are your fingers large yeah are your fingers look at my shit
dude who is it my fingers are small here hand sizes no wait
you definitely yeah yeah you have I have I have we've done this oh we have done
this before yeah you Omega dog Wow whoa that's why we're that's why we're in
love we have the no no no your hands aren't lined up Kayla move your hand
down it has to be palm to palm. They have palm to palm. Dude they're literally exactly the
same. Caleb no no no no Caleb has smallest hands. No dude I don't care. You're trying
to tear us down because you're Omega Dog. You know who else has small hands? Literally
the biggest alpha of all time Donald Trump. Facts. Literally alpha dogged everybody in
the nation. Yeah who do I get John Kerry? Yeah fucking pussy. Frankenstein looking motherfucker.
I wish he got a second purple heart for dying. Yeah. Who John Kerry? I wish he got a yeah
today is a purple heart. Yeah guys with big hands. You know what you should get
that checked out
guys with big hands. They play piano and that's female. You guys with little
hands. They can only can only hold like hammer. She only thing I can yeah a
hammer a drill a hamburger, which is a combination of a drill and a hammer.
Yeah, only cool things. I wish I got like you know, I wish I wish I had like
a tiger mom who made me play piano as a kid. I would love to everybody wishes
that dude. I wish I learned P. I wish I could play that's really that's probably
the most that's probably the most common thought in the history of the human
races. I wish someone forced me to play piano and I was a kid. I got forced to
play piano. I suck at I did too and I stopped. I didn't yeah. I kept doing I
started playing. I taught myself. I you really think you really think that
that somebody could have forced you to play piano as a kid forced me to play
piano. I feel like there's no way I tried to get me to play hockey too and I
didn't want exactly would have gotten stuck in the you think that like oh
there's I wouldn't have like I forcing me to learn hockey didn't work but piano
like that would have been the thing well I would have been stationary what are
you talking about yeah you that's true yeah well well then I would have seen
like a video of little Richard and I was like you can move while you play the
piano you were like Jerry Lee Lewis who's that play the piano with your feet
who's the from the wild thorn berries squidward I don't know I never watched
that show yeah what's his name much nature is his name
no Darwin's the monkey futter it was futter water the monkey baby
futter thornberry it's cool today what's his name thing his name is it's like
It's like they they like a doctor what is like part of the family his name's like Lyle
It's probably closer to Lyle than thing
Nigel's the dad the mom and I don't think he speaks
I remember you remember those funny-ass pictures where they put Nigel Thornberry on people's faces. Oh, oh my god
No, it's funny. We never saw those now just the room very like brother you are
You know that tonight if you're if you're feeling down
Any night in the future could open up your Google Chrome put your cursor in the URL bar
And I want you to go to know your meme comm slash Nigel - thornberry, okay. I'll have to check it out. They're gonna
Don yeah, see that's not was Donnie thing
His voice by flea. Did you know that?
He was he was yelled by flea. Yeah, yeah
It would be funny if his uh he only spoken slap bass that have been way better that would not make any fucking sense
you're you you're a fucking idiot don't have an imaginative mind number four do
you play video games no yeah yes Sam a bit of a video game player definitely
eight games now Omega games now Omega Omega you don't know what it's like to
fail your enemy in battle that's why the one of the skills of an alpha is putting
yourself in the shoes of others and understanding what it's like to lead the
pack yeah so when I play for example an RTS like Starcraft yep I become the
leader of the zerg and I know what's right for my people.
That's what makes me an alpha.
You play Starcraft and you're like, "I don't understand.
I'm this little guy in this unit.
I can't."
Yeah, I'm that little grunt who dies instantly.
Yeah, that's me.
It's like, no, you're supposed to be...
When I play Animal Crossing, I become a deer with a fancy suit on.
I just look at all the zergs dying and stuff and I just get sad because they have families
too.
Omega.
Omega, dog.
Yeah, alphas are about commanding the pack, but they hate families.
we don't have anything to do with family. We would literally kill every family in America
instantly with one button. I hate families. The family unit, I think the family unit should
be a one by one cube that I compact them into in a machine. That's what the family unit
should be. A foot by a foot by a foot. I'm more interested in the family eunuch. That's
right. I'm going to be castrating every last one of them so they can't reproduce. No families
left. That's right. Fuck. And the girls. Yep. That you hate. I'm taking one cool guy from
from each family and I'm making the biggest pack the world has ever seen.
That's right and all the girls. I think we're doing female female castration,
which I'm pretty sure is when you put a cork up there.
She like a bottle of wine when they you get home in the family eunuch hasn't
taken the chicken out of the fridge to defrost.
It's his job. Yeah, my God, you got one job.
Take the other.
I did I yeah when I was in I was at the store the other day and I saw mom beat
the shit out of her eunuch.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
Yeah,
she was like she was like saying a jaunty diddy right now remember we used to be
able to he's like
I wish I had a hunchback - oh yeah dude the hunchback I mean your church who
gets so clean every family should I'd use that hunchback like a lunch every
family should have a eunuch a hunchback a mutant and a slave yeah yeah that's
the real family unit yeah yeah that's right and they all live in the basement.
They party yeah they're having more fun than their owners definitely they
basically
all of them are slaves. They live like the Gorgons and small soldiers. Well
actually no the hunchback owes them a
life or death favor. He has a he has a he's a servant yeah. Oh and like a genie
or like a bound spirit. Yeah, okay.
does your does your hunchback be reanimating people? No, he's not unless
you're a man. I just family okay, no yeah, the hunchback doesn't do that on on
his own mad. So that's something he does. My side is American family. Sorry
yeah yeah
number five. Do you go to the gym? Hell no, the notes are my gym. Here's a
comment. No, these are perverted true facts. The gym is low key. Perverted is
- I'm gonna pervert it.
Here's a comment.
- There's nothing stopping someone
from smelling the machine after you use it.
- Me, that's my job.
- Your job is to smell the machines after people use them?
- Well, yeah, I get all the stench out
and then they can go in.
Like if a girl with a big ass does a bench press
and gets up off the bench.
- A bench press?
Oh, bench.
- Then I go and I smell the--
- You have to suck it all up.
- Yeah, I gotta suck up all the stench
so fucking Stanley doesn't smell it.
- Yeah, or--
- He's the gym smeller.
- Stanley Sniffer, the gym smeller, sucks.
I have a similar job, but instead of sucking up all the smell, they want me
to mask the smell, so I have to rub the smelliest part of my body all over the
machine after. Which is? When I'm done. My thing.
He's got patchouli on his thing. Yeah. I musk it up beforehand. I forgot your
thing has mushrooms growing off of it and stuff. Yeah. It's like, yeah, you
know, they say like... Your grandparents ever say you're growing potatoes behind
your ears? Yeah. Yeah. I got a... Growing potatoes behind my face. I got a
wood knot in my balls. You never heard that before? If you have dirt behind
ears. Old people say you're growing potatoes behind your ears. They're not,
they don't have very good eyes. Yeah, they can barely see anything.
And also they're from back in time when like
Jack and the Beanstalk was like real. Yeah, exactly. Jack and the Beanstalk was
like... They lived through this shit. My great-grandpa like hung out with them
actually. Yeah, apparently he was like way different. My grandpa would always talk about like
turning the TV on and seeing the giant falling from the beans. Yeah, I mean
here's a TV on the radio in the magic TV. Yeah, I mean the portal of the mirror
magic mirror. Yeah, I mean his window. He lived there. They used to call it. I mean
it's called PTSD now where they used to call it being shock. Yeah, my grandpa was
actually a prisoner of jar. He was stuck in one of the the Giants jars. Damn, are
Are you serious? Yeah, yeah, he's from crazy. That's crazy. I would love to sit
on it. He would bang on the jar.
And people people make jokes now, but like if you do, if you live through it,
if you say fee five foe, from near an old person, some of them still just get
flashbacks. Ptsd sit there and just go like yeah, no, it's really it's scary
because it's really yeah, yeah, we tried to bring my grandpa to the Redwoods,
the great redwoods. He's trying to convulse. He thought they were bean
- Beanstalks.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it was like,
- It's good. - Not again, not again.
- It's like, you know, I mean,
it's good they got rid of beanstalks
that go to Giants' castles.
- Definitely. - But like,
- The thing is, and now people wanna be like,
"Oh, well if we don't have the beanstalks,
"we're being isolationists."
- I mean, yeah, it is kind of,
- There's a clear-- - The shit that's going on
with Giants right now is kind of our country's fault,
I feel like.
- Oh, absolutely. - I mean, I don't really
wanna get into it, honestly.
- I mean, yeah, but you have to--
- I don't wanna alienate anybody who's listening.
people know I'm like a libertarian.
So I just don't think that we should be involved
with giants, but whatever.
- People know I'm like a pescatarian.
- Yeah, and I'm also,
people know I'm a Rastafarian.
(laughing)
- Well yeah, that's my whole problem is I'm a Rastafarian.
I try to promote one love.
- People know I'm like a cafeteria,
so I only eat cafeteria food.
- Food from a cafeteria.
- Yeah.
- I'm a cafeteria and my diet is all appetizer samplers
and it's just like--
yeah, just like tiny pieces of orange chicken. Yeah, my every every
cafeteria and know the excitement when you wake up and you see it's pizza day.
Yeah, my diet is tiny piece of cafeteria, orange chicken and then doing
the backwards man back over to there and pretending to be another guy and
grabbing another definitely yeah and then trying to put it into the back of
my head where I drew a mouth. Oh dude, but it doesn't taste very good in the
back of my head. The day
fucking I mean pizza day is probably one of the best holidays Charlie's a great
cafeteria food oh yeah I can't come into work today I have a religious holiday
it's it's French toast sticks day yeah you should be able to claim one of the
lunch ladies has a crush on me so she gives me five is there a way to claim to
to like schedule your year where you convert to every religion in time to
have every high holiday Ali I don't I think you can just do that I don't think
you need to schedule anything. I don't I think that no, I think I guess you kind of
have to soft seed it. You have to be like when the holidays coming you're like I
don't know guys. I feel like
I feel like I might be becoming a Muslim right now. I just don't I don't know. I've
just been fucking with the Quran. I feel like you can kind of only do that for one
year before they catch on. One year of you just being like an indecisive guy, but
then like also every Christmas you just go back to Christianity. You're like I
need a full. Well, then maybe the next year like well, I finally decided I'm
just going to do them all that could work because then I mean you have that you
have you're like well I like I have proof I tried them all I like them all
it's like I'm just doing this great kind of a very soft cult yeah like just a
religion that takes off every religious holiday yeah that is a good idea I mean
you could technically and and it also is like is what are they fucking called it
can we take off Halloween Joe was witness and that take our Halloween and
we can take off our birthdays. Okay. Yeah. And we can take off our clothes. So it's reverse, it's like a reverse
Jehovah's Witness so it's like somebody's never even seen Jehovah. But also Jehovah's Witness just for
birthdays. Yeah. Yeah. Well they don't celebrate. Exactly, you can't, you don't
celebrate your birthday but if you go into work people are gonna be giving you
a cake. People are gonna be saying happy birthday. Guess who's going to hell now?
You. So you got to stay home. Yeah. True. Yeah. There was a, I knew a kid who was a
Jehovah's Witness. He stayed home on Halloween every year. I knew a kid, he had a
stinky butt. I'm serious. He would like smell up the entire school with his butt.
That's part of being a Jehovah's Witness. Can't wipe. Cannot wash your
ass. Can't wipe, can't wash your ass. You gotta stay the way God made you.
Yeah, you can't use a washcloth. Mm-hmm. Fucked up. Mm-hmm. Number six. You could use a stick with a
sponge on it though. Are you a... number six, are you a virgin? Nope. Yep. Nope. Nope.
- Nope. - Nope.
- I pretty much had sex a hundred times.
- I can't say.
- I had sex when I was nine.
- I don't want to answer the question.
- Bad, bad dude.
(laughing)
- Okay, alpha.
- That's alpha.
That is alpha dude.
(laughing)
- Teacher.
- That's the funniest shit.
I totally talked about it before,
just like old men on Facebook where it's like,
when's the first, like in those horny groups,
where they're like,
when's the first time you had sex?
- Five years old, I fucked my janitor.
I my babysitter let me eat her pussy when I was nine yeah that's like it's it's an
obvious lie but it's like you realize you're just saying you got molested so
funny claimed in like second grade that every day when we had nap time he was
fucking this one girl yeah he's like we fuck every single day we just go into
the corner we fuck and I never stayed awake long enough to try and get a look
ship, though yeah, yeah, it was jessie
here's the biggest fan of the show. It's cool. This is a good question number
seven favorite female user. My favorite female user was britney murphy female
user. I'd have to say myself. Whoa, I'll be using these females hit it and quit
it. What's up boys fact come on come on. Yep, this is just I mean the comment
section here. The comment section here is literally just a list of of user
Yeah, I'm except for this comment from Pokemon fan 10 that says I'm not gonna say anything yet. Yeah, let's go
I'm not gonna let these women take you down. Don't let these women discourage you that's right. Don't let these females. Just yeah
He said yeah, yeah, it's literally there. They're listing there are people who list like ten of them in one comment
by age
What that last one? What was why do you care? Oh?
Jen what is that listen by age?
13 to 16. No, that's you back to Omega. You just got down downgraded.
He's got demoted Omega. We'll say Omega pedophile remember. Okay.
We'll just say that we'll just call you the Omega pedophile of the office.
That's like a like a Metal Gear Solid boss.
You put up a clone the one clone that they don't talk about of like solid
snake and he's can we put up a one?
this is a pedophile snake snake. You're gonna have to be careful going around
there. They there's a ray that turns you into a child as soon as you walk into
this building. Yeah, he has like a cut scene where it's just like flipping
around a lollipop in his hands like it's like a full minute. He's dressed up like
Donald Duck Omega pedophile. He's like walking around. He dresses and talks
exactly like Donald Duck.
Hello Snooks!
*snort*
Donald Duck is a really funny costume for a pedophile to wear.
Yeah, what do you- I'm just gonna wear kids in.
Yeah, I don't wear pants. It's part of the costume.
No, it's the little hat is getting me.
I'm a kid too.
Yeah, it's just a sailor's outfit with no pants on.
Yeah.
Did you guys ever meet like an adult who-
Did you guys ever meet Donald Duck?
Yeah.
Did you guys ever know like an adult who would do the Donald Duck voice to kids?
My papa.
My dad does it to my name.
That would scare me.
If strangers did a Donald Duck voice to me when I was a little kid,
it was my grandpa.
Where is it coming from?
What is it's like?
It's just like a loud,
violent voice.
Spit out Donald Duck right now.
I my grandpa,
he just like scaring me when I was a kid,
so he would do the Donald Duck thing and then he had dentures.
You just shoot his dentures out and they would hit me in the face.
But like the hit me in the forehead.
It's so scary.
It's scared the fuck out of the like the pizza place near my
my house growing up where we go like a little dog beats. There was like it yeah.
It was like an old Italian guy who like who ran it or whatever and whenever he
saw me he would do the Donald Duck voice. We was like not good at it, so it just
be like hello Cameron. It just feel like we'd like go in and he'd see me and
expect
like I'm right. It would just be him just like it like making a scary hissing
noise.
I'll be like
yeah, that's a scary voice. If you don't have it down, you know well,
Favorite band? Shinedown. I'm a guy. I'm a male user.
"All you'll ever be is a faded memory of a boy"
Shinedown, sick.
"I just saw Haley's come as she went"
You know that Shinedown song from...
I saw them live.
Really?
2013.
Then you heard Bully?
Of course, dude.
Dude, that song is...
They had a guy open for them who just had a 50-piece drum set.
And he was just...
Doing one man...
Doing a white man group.
that song "Bully" was in one of the NHL, I think it was NHL 12, I think, NHL 13, one of
them, and it's so funny to have like an anti-bullying song in a fucking game
where like one of the, like you just, like one of the options is fighting another
player. What are people saying their favorite band is? Well my username is
Bon Jovi 117, so do you expect me to say Maroon 5, Bon Jovi 17? Oh yo, we got to go
to the Bon Jovi rest stop. I'm down. You know that in New Jersey there's
like a rest stop that is Bon Jovi like it's a tribute to Bon Jovi. It's named
after Bon Jovi and is Bon Jovi themed. That's sick dude. New Jersey is like...
New Jersey sucks. New Jersey is one of the sickest places on earth. You are
from the worst state in the Union. What? New Hampshire? Yeah. It's not the worst. It is
the worst state in the union. You're wrong I'm sorry. I'm right you don't even have
like cool western stuff like we had the old man of the mountain.
No New Hampshire is not. Old man of the mountain. I've been to more states than any of you
guys I've trekked around this entire country. It doesn't matter. Yeah but New Jersey's sick
because it's just stupid they got medieval times they have the Bon Jovi
rest stop. That's literally a intersection in America. Hold on.
There's a new mall there. Okay. It's like one of the it's I think it beats I think
it beats there's an indoor amusement park at this mall we talked about this the the
the ski slopes burned down no I don't think we do yeah they this is a
different burn down this is different mall nope that's the mall I'm thinking
but anyway on the 1st of April 1st and 2nd at then it's the don't go there on
the first of it guess who's getting do not leave your house on the first of it
it's gonna be it's gonna get well I don't want to scare anybody but that is
it's a prime time for Russia to
course yeah, Russia's pranks. Well, just a normal believe it. How many text for
how many forwarded text you're going to get that day about about you hear you
hear an air raid siren. Yeah, yeah, sure this time yeah, you know exactly and
then also even if the if the bomb in the bunker all day, the bomb hit somewhere
that you're not you're going to be like well. As if that was a fool exactly I
got fooled again. Okay, so on Friday, April first and Saturday, April second at
American Dream Mall in New Jersey. DJ Pauly D, Nickelodeon Universe,
(laughter)
- Okay. - Municipal Park Takeover.
- Okay, I will go there. - We gotta go to this.
- Yeah, okay, fine. - We're gonna do a meet and greet.
- April 2nd, though. - Alright, yeah, we're not going on the 1st.
- We're going on April 2nd if the world's still fucking here.
- Yeah. - At the American Dream Mall in East Rutherford, New Jersey,
at the Pauly D Show. - They have an Americone Dream Mall?
- Yep, named. - Damn.
- Alright, number nine, what kind of list do you make?
I would say that I might actually have the most diverse range of lists whether
it's a unique miscellaneous one animal people movies companies products or
sports I have a featured list in almost every category so I don't think I
straighted one side only I'm bookmarking this person's profile it's not working
mostly music all sorts actually we should we should start making more lists
I think yeah we need to contribute a little bit we're just we're just we're
just taking we're not even a yeah yeah not even giving back number ten are you
gay last one
here's a cut though the last comment on here is no ugh I know what this list is
for I am 100% heteronormative I am leaning towards a gay but I am a chill
bisexual.
That's a good comment, Pat.
Thank you.
Alright.
Go buy tickets to our tour.
Oh yeah.
SwagPoop.com/shows.
We're going to Philadelphia, Washington DC, Richmond, Atlanta, Austin, Fort Worth, then
Austin, then LA, Los Angeles, then Chicago in May.
dates and the ticket links and everything swag poop dot com slash shows
buy the tickets come see us it's the swag 19 super spreader experience
bye!
featuring peash campion peash?
peash campion