Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
Okay, now hold your--
- No, hold it to your mouth.
- Pick your arm up.
- Oh, wow.
- Hold the microphone to your mouth.
- Caleb, lift your arm.
- Meh.
- Okay, now move it this way.
- You know what, he's sitting in my spot.
- Now move your hand towards your chest.
Now put it onto the microphone.
Put your hand onto the microphone.
Get your hand on the microphone.
Put the microphone in your hand.
I'm missing.
Try again, okay, grab.
I'm slipped.
Nope, put it, get your hand back up.
Get your hand on the mic.
Nope, grab, nope, up, up, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is this it?
No, I'm gonna go home.
I slipped my hands.
Yeah, we're leaving.
I'm not looking at you anymore.
Do you guys even care?
Just ignore him, he just wants attention.
I don't even want attention.
He just wants negative attention.
I am so fucked up that he does,
I mean, it sucks that we have to do this at his house.
I know.
it's yes
like why the fuck do we even it's irritating i mean you should on your
house but i know it's a he said he's making makes it up about my house
because he doesn't like it is too cool i don't not like your house nobody can
hear you
yankee
did you turn me off nobody did you know you do you know the way so far
i didn't you turn yourself off yes you did
i just don't i didn't pick up the mike we can hear you it's supposed to be a
new invention and you guys don't know you it's not an it's not a lot of
It's a lack of invention.
This is a super invention at the same time.
Pick your mic up.
Okay.
You are, hold it normal.
Hold it to your mouth.
To your mouth.
You can't even hear you.
Yeah, this is, yeah, this is good.
No, this is terrible.
This is way better than this.
Are you kidding me?
Pick it up and hold it to your mouth.
God damn it.
Take off your clothes.
No.
No, I'm too pretty for this.
Take off your clothes.
No, I chose this outfit to be pretty today.
I'm not going to.
- My chains are in the other room.
- Put on your shackles.
Go get your shackles.
- I don't.
- Get the shackles.
- Okay.
- Go get the dungeon key.
- I don't know where it is.
- Get to find the dungeon key.
- He's sitting in the spot.
It's all fucked up today because he's got a bunch of
like little trinkets out on the floor.
He's got all these glasses.
- I got a car just dropped these off.
I don't know.
- A car dropped these off.
- It's just all my fragile trinkets.
- I don't believe that a car came and dropped off
bunch of glassware. A hundred fragile trinkets? And he put them all across my floor. He didn't put them all across the floor.
This is your, this is your wife's trinkets. I'm building a Rube Goldberg machine. Caleb went on
Facebook marketplace and searched 100 most fragile trinkets available. Yeah, and someone dropped
them off in a car. What is that a snake charmer basket? I'm thinking of getting into snake charming.
- No, you're not.
- I am.
- You're not.
You're not getting into Snake Charmin.
- I have a flute on the way.
- I don't believe you at all.
- A big long wooden flute.
And a very funny hat.
- Yeah?
- Yep, and a sleeveless shirt.
- What about the snake?
- What?
- Is the snake in the--
- No, that's how, you summon the snake with the flute.
- Is the snake in the apartment right now?
- It's not a snake, you're not a snake maker.
- Okay, I had the snake and it was in there.
- Oh, rats.
no snakes
uh... do you know
guys is a
uh... unless he's like
disney to camouflage yes yeah power fine
he's probably in their states to camouflage yet it did i really good like
coming out of style came from the worker basket pattern yet and worth
he's in that
basket yeah guys fun
you receive uh...
who is it that
there's like a world record relate these women's
date in a room with eight hundred eighty eight snakes or something
what see what i spot these these lounging like i do in
unjust up
was elected to get it really like to be dominated you get the spot you're being
a you're being cuckolded
you know what you want to do a single thing that you're sitting there
i want to look at my phone
exact c how to ruin the episode yet
do you are you do you're feeling a sudden urge to go on on the pop
I want to buy the biggest pants in America right now.
Yeah.
For $80.
I want to buy the biggest, stupidest pants.
I want to pay $800 for them.
Yeah, and say, "Sorry guys, I can't go out to lunch for another two weeks."
Yep.
Oh, guys, I ran out of money.
I bought a $4 million sock.
I just...
I went on desocks.com and I bought a hundred pairs of vintage socks.
The one thing I will say...
Vintage socks from the 2000s.
With a bunch of holes in them.
Really big baggy socks.
baggy socks. Really big baggy like JNCO style socks. Denim socks.
That are just like they spill over out of your shoes. Oh they fold. Oh do you see that guy
the guy that wears crown royal bags and socks? I did see that, that's sick. That is cool.
I feel like I saw that guy I thought that guy should be wearing those with
with flip-flops or Crocs. You need to be showing those off. Those are beasts.
there that's like if they just see the like cinch right like that yeah they're
gonna be like those are yes I mean like that's like a nice that's like a subtle
swag thing but when you know when you're doing that that can't be subtle no that's
got to be you need to see the crown royal logo yeah that's important definitely I
mean like you got it it's you show it off you know exactly yeah I mean you're
either you should I feel like I feel like what I would do is I would get a
bunch of crown royal and I would take a bunch of the bags and I would stitch
them together into those five toe shoe things. Oh shit. The like water shoes? No the shoes
that like that people use to run marathons in the woods. Yeah with your foot. Yeah the
water resistant toe things. Are they water resistant? Fuck yeah. They might want to be.
Different route. I want to feel every mud puddle I step in. Completely different route.
I'd go like those Balenciaga sock shoes. I had some. Put a sole on them. I bought some
fakes of those for four dollars at a goodwill one time and I was like I don't know why. I
never gonna wear those but I just had those for like a year and a half. I might
make a cloak. You still have them? No I got rid of them. Damn. They were so stupid. I know,
it's stupid I would have worn them. They're like the ugliest shoes ever. Yeah.
I might make like a like a perfect cosplay of the Resident Evil 4 merchant
out of the the crown royal bag. That would be sick. A cloak with like those, yeah exact.
Crown Royal. I don't have any. I just have the bags. I drank all of it. And you can't buy the bags
because they're my clothes. I still sell guns just like the guy in the game. There should be more
like merchants in video games should sell just like normal shit. Yeah. You know, things you
don't need for anything. I love that. That's the best part of it. That's one of the best parts of
like Skyrim is when you like sell a guy like a piece of bread and then you come back later and
and he said he'll sell it back.
- Yeah, selling it for like 10 times the price.
- Yeah, you're like, well, I guess I have to--
- I wanna play that guy.
I don't wanna play my guy.
My guy's getting fucking scammed every single time.
- They should make a game where you're just a merchant
in like Skyrim or something.
- That would be so sick.
- You're just a merchant in a small like fucking place.
- And all the adventurers come by
and they have to pay your prices.
And you can do that thing where like,
you know, you have like a bunch of items
that are like 100 gold, 200 gold,
and then be like, and I have the ultimate sword
and it's 10,000 gold and everyone saves up for it
and then it's just a normal sword.
- It sucks.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Well, actually, how would that work?
'Cause like, you know, like--
- Oh, you wanna sell it back to me?
20 GP.
- Yep.
- How does that, 'cause you gotta have like a guy,
you gotta have a buyer, right?
- Yeah, it's an NPC.
- So the buyer just shows up.
So it's kinda like a fallout shelter type of game.
- A non-player character.
- That's facts.
- Not balling out.
- No balling, no balling at all.
- Don't kick him.
- Don't kick me.
You're in the perfect spot to kick.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That's why I hate this.
You hate sitting in a chair.
You're getting reminded of school right now.
You're balancing your thing so precariously,
your phone so precariously on the edge of your knee,
I can't help but try and kick it off.
You can help it.
You are doing like a seal routine.
A seal?
Yeah, you know?
I'm singing Kiss from a Rose.
Hell no, ball on the nose type seal.
Who the fuck is that?
Seal?
I don't know who that is.
I'm a virgin.
Yeah, I only care about Navy SEALs.
Yeah.
And what they do for our country.
There's so much I can show you, so much you can take.
Listen, pal.
You be kidding.
It'd probably take two to three Navy SEALs to chop that guy's fucking head off.
He got fucked up shit on his face.
Yeah, he'll have a lot of fucked up shit on his face when I'm done with him.
He had like a thing as a kid.
It's like a scar from like a...
What?
Yeah.
It looks like you fell into a George Foreman grill.
You don't have to feel bad for people with scars.
that's just a normal. You definitely don't need to feel bad for steel. He overcame scars and had such a beautiful voice.
Scars are nothing. He's like fucking, he's like a perfect skin. You have a person with scars. He's so hot.
If you have like, if you have like no eye or like you're a mutant, then you have to feel bad for them.
But a scar is fine. That makes you cooler. I don't know what you're talking about. If you have either one or three
something that you should have two of yeah that is a like a story that I want
it's crazy that Chris Morris was able to be so funny when his face was so red see
red face he was able to overcome the now that's not you know he just needed to
smoke a little weed mmm that's the truth he's had anxiety yeah it's funny that
people do you ever think about like like the fact that people smoke weed to like
quell their anxiety it's crazy yeah hilarious imagine - when I smoke weed I
I turn into the monkey kid from the Thornberrys,
like every single time.
(laughing)
(gurgling)
Swinging from a chandelier I don't have.
- That's me on soda.
- You do not get hype on soda.
- I do.
- No, you don't. - No, you don't.
- You get hyphy.
- No, you don't.
- You definitely don't get hyphy on soda, buddy.
- I get hyphy as hell.
- You don't drink even, no, you--
- I get, I drink--
- You don't even get hyper on three energy drinks.
- I do.
- No, you get tired on three energy drinks.
- You get hyper, you know what?
your biggest drug is like the TV being off that's what makes you hyper you walk
around going like oh we're doing this true talking to yourself talking way too
much that's true you're the type of kid I bet that you drink a cream soda and you
go like well I'm the caffeine I'm really feeling the caffeine in this cream
don't get so stupid you are what do you like cream no then how about yellow I
get one it's iced iced but yeah you put cream so shut up you put cream soda over
ice? No. I put ice cream in it. Well, okay, hold on. If it's cream soda with like a little
bit of ice cream in it. That's not, that's a float. Yeah, if it's a cream soda float.
Okay, so you like a cream, so why do you not like cream soda? I don't like, you know what
it is? I drank too much, it's one of those things, drank too much of it as a kid then
threw up because I drank too much of it and now I associate the taste with puke. Oh, I've
been there. Yeah. I've had that with collards. I had that with hot dogs for a while as a kid.
collards oh okay I ate too many collards I said he had that with collars I was like
what the fuck are you eating his own shirt collar I think I think you're the
weird one you are the weird one I ate so many collards and I was a kid I like
projectile vomited all over a train to Busch Gardens that's so sweat I was like
I'm never I'm never eating that shit again I still eat it though but I just I
I think I like puke cheese poofs another wolf cheese poofs poofs poofs what
Poops I say cheese poofs wise positive South Park
What really said yeah, where he says the seasons the cheesy poofs jingle never seen that never heard of South Park
I've been doing a rewatch if we I wish had a friend who had never ever heard of South Park's actually do
You can pretty much
I've seen like one South Park episode. Caleb is so funny, he says the craziest things.
He keeps saying respect my authority, he keeps saying he's doing Hanky the Christmas Pooh.
He made up this character the other day, Timmy, and it's one of the funniest things I've ever
heard. Been doing a South Park re-watch, been re-watching all the early seasons.
- What?
- Yeah.
- What the hell?
- You must be crazy.
- It's actually, it actually holds up
a lot better than I thought.
- I'd like to hold it up in the sun
and let it get sunburnt.
That's how seriously I hate this crappy show.
(laughing)
- I'd like to hold Mr. Hankey up to the sun
and dry him out and throw him in a car.
- I'll say it.
No, I like South Park.
- Yeah.
I like when they do celebrity...
They won so hard getting people to buy into that art style and get to just pump out episodes.
And now they're doing the Circle Show, right?
They're doing a show about guys who were made of circles.
What is it?
It looks like South Park.
I don't know, some circle thing.
It's called the Circle Show?
It's like doing a South Park show about being...
It's called Circle Circle Dot Dot and it's a Jamie Kennedy...
It's an expansion of a Jamie Kennedy bit.
It's going to be really good.
It's just circle, circle, dot, dot for 30 minutes.
I think we can make a really good show called The Circles Show.
Who do you think's doing?
I think we should.
Okay, you have to move beyond characters who are made out of circles.
I think our characters are circles.
Square show?
No.
You would do a square show.
The triangle show.
My circle show is going to beat all your shows in ratings.
I'd do a tetrahedron.
Pac-Man's going to be in my show.
Oh yeah, okay.
a good point. If you could have a show, which show would be better? A show of all
circular characters? Or a show of all square characters? If you could use every square or circle.
Circle characters, Pac-Man, Voltorb from Pokemon, Kirby, Jigglypuff, Square, SpongeBob.
A couple of Pokemon. I think Square might have it actually.
You get, let's see, Mrs. Puff when she's puffed up. True, she's circular.
are
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
circle. Okay, yeah. The entire army of the Gungans under their big force field. They all
count. All the Star Wars planets. R2D2's head, if you mirror it. Okay, so now, oh BB-8. BB-8.
BB-8. Okay, now let's think about squares. Minecraft. Well, Minecraft's not a square.
Minecraft's blocks. There's a Minecraft. No, no, it can't be, because then we could have
characters made out of circles for the circle one they have to be completely a
square oh shit well then squares my so squares
Bob the board you really just have sponge Bob yeah board cube the plank from
Ed and Eddie plank oh that's a rectangle are we counting right yeah otherwise
there's nothing four-sided sharp sharp corners sharp shapes yeah yeah sharp
shapes I believe who table II what's that towel we table you could be tally
- Towel-y. - Towel-y.
- Yeah. - Towel-y, yeah.
- See, they're kinda losing, man.
- There's not very much.
A computer.
- I guess a computer that has a hard drive
with every single character on it.
- Okay, yeah, but that computer's on the earth,
which is a circle. - Thwomp.
- Thwomp, very good. - Thwomp is really good.
- And the other kind of thwomp that falls flat.
- Oh, yeah. - The one that looks
like a door. - The flatterer.
- The flatterer.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Oh, yeah, I mean, you've got the flatterer.
- Obviously the flatterer,
but that was should've been the first one we said.
is a kind of genius kind of we do consider ourselves a debate show yeah
you know I think we're in the debate section on maybe 8-bit Mickey Mouse Oh
any 8-bit any 8-bit yeah any 8-bit one big character yeah an 8-bit character
that's on a 2x2 pixel screen mm-hmm mr. game and watch mr. game and watch on a
2x2 screen mr. gay man maybe oh okay Wally Wally Wally is all the characters
from LazyTown if you put them through a trash compactor.
True.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah.
No, but I do think Circles will probably still win.
Circles win.
What about Triangles?
Anybody?
I can't even think of a god damn triangle character.
Triangle Bob.
Triangle Pants.
That's nothing.
That's just nothing.
Triangle Bob, Triangle Pants.
Yeah, that's one of those-
You're just saying fucking nothing.
That's one of those like-
Dr. Pyramid.
That's one of those like Spongebob shows that they greenlit immediately after Steven Hillenburg
died that he was like, "I will never make Triangle Bob."
(laughter)
- It is funny that they did have a show.
- Oh yeah, he died and then they immediately
made the package show.
- They had like a live, like a big red button.
- They had like five shows going on.
- And just aired them in a block.
- Yeah.
- I was like, this one's about the sand.
- Teenage Squidward!
- Yeah.
- They're all, it's so funny.
- Yeah, and they have like young SpongeBob now.
And it's like animated.
- It violates the canon.
- Hey, yeah, here's a thought.
SpongeBob was already young, you fucking idiot.
That's why he's so joyful and full of life.
Yeah, it's why he's jovial.
Is he supposed to be 30, Spongebob?
I think he's supposed to be 76.
He should talk more about how much he hates his 30s.
Yeah, he should.
I don't think he knows how old he is.
He should be like, "I'm 30 and that's still young."
"I'm 30 years young."
He should be like, "I'm just a kid, 30 years old."
I think that would do a lot for a lot of sad,
lonely sacks of fucking shit.
Spongebob can't be that old.
If Spongebob was born in the 40s, they would have put an ice pick in his head.
Nah.
been like Rosemary Kennedy yeah he would have been done for yeah who'd been
sitting there just all day I like water you would have you guys ever met a
lobotomized person no I mean you know I want to so bad I just fully believe I
want to see if I can tell you know what I mean yeah I want to see if I'd be like
well yeah they're sitting there like do that
lobotomies don't do that to people like if they're done right yeah it
just like takes out like part of that personality now a double part of your
brain yeah like a non-aggressive or something if they fuck it up you're full
drooly yeah but if they do it well it's beautiful if they do it well it's it's
the the a it's an art form yeah I think I can get one I think I'd be good you
getting lobotomized wouldn't change anything no you'd see you would power
through cuz I think that all of your brain they'd open your skull of me like
that's odd somebody's already been here they just try to lobotomize Patrick they
keep just missing because there's so much air they'd like take the saw to like cut
open his head and it would be like a beer can that you shake it up and just go like
like a shit ton of air. They just keep trying to hit the spot that you're supposed to hit and it just keeps going.
Yeah you'd be like you'd be like tickling and giggling the entire time. I'd wake up in the middle of it and just go
"Hoo hoo hoo!"
I come out talking like Mickey Mouse or some shit.
Yeah.
That would happen to me.
Man, I can't get it. There's so many trinkets here.
There's a little cow.
Don't look at the trinkets.
I don't know what's there, man.
It's not my shit.
It's got an angel horn.
Yeah, I believe in Christianity, man.
What's angel horn mean?
Those things that are on their back that make them fly, dude.
You fucking idiot.
Yeah, they got devil horns that make you sink into the ground.
Does it mean a halo?
That's an angel's horn.
is
and put it on right now.
I can't, I don't have one.
Oh, he can't put on the hat.
Okay, you put on the top hat.
Where's your top hat?
It's on right now.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Liar.
Okay, my halo's on right now.
It's on.
C2 versus 1, it's on.
My halo's on right now.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
No, you don't have one on.
My 5,000 friends on my phone just said it's on.
You don't have--
Look at these notifications.
What app?
Instagram, Twitter, Messages.
There's 5,000?
Yeah, 5,000--
Each?
No, between them.
but not between them come on. How many from each app then that adds up to
1000, 1000, 3000. Can you double check that Pat? Is that how looking and it's
not true. You're not looking at all my phone. I'm looking to it's not true.
Phone is face up. My phone is face down. See my halo is hanging on the corner of
my girlfriend's four post bed. Wow. Did you guys see the halo show trailer? No,
does it look cool? It looks really bad, but I didn't watch the trailer.
Dude, I'll watch it.
I watched two seconds of the trailer with the sound off and went, "No."
I'm a halo fucking...
I saw the picture of Cortana and I was like...
It looks like a...
It looks like a girl into blue.
She's not blue.
They did not make her blue.
They made her look like shit.
It looks like the CW superhero shows.
Yeah.
Oh my, I gotta look at this.
The effect's really fucked up.
Yeah, let's watch it right now.
I gotta look at this.
All right, we're done watching it.
Cortana, beautiful body.
Okay, we just finished watching it and it looks immense.
It looks incredible.
like a victory against the monolithic quips of the Marvel Empire. Oh dude, if
they fucking they're going to do some Marvel shit yeah, oh yeah, oh she's blue
yeah purple hi, I'm Mrs. Chief yeah, that's right yep, if they did halo today
yeah, hi, I'm Mrs. Chief and I have chronic back pain, you probably do that
that's right yeah, they put me in this suit to make my back pain worse yeah,
Yeah, and you know now it is about how funny it is to struggle the grant the
grants.
You'll aliens and we definitely don't eat their meat man.
Say that again the grunts.
Yeah, be called grunts anymore.
They'd be called genders.
Yep.
That's right.
Yeah, elites would probably be called the Commons.
Yeah, because they can't even be the elites are probably be sure to be this
time.
Yep, true.
Yeah, the Spartans.
I hope they don't make the Spartans normie.
That's one of my only that's a big deal breaker for me.
no normie spartans i hate normie i would break shit in my house oh absolutely
they'll probably make some kind of like gayish alien yeah yeah yeah which is fun
all the elites are girls and all their mouths look like vaginas and they have full-on kiss
yeah yeah gay rights and the flood they'll probably probably the flood they wouldn't
couldn't even make that joke like they did in the original.
- Flood would probably be somebody's name.
- Yeah, exactly.
Flood is probably someone's name now.
- Yeah.
- And it's probably somebody with short hair.
- Uh-huh.
- You know, some kind of--
- Oh yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
- Girl kind of thing.
- Mm-hmm.
I heard Master Chief wears earrings.
- I heard Master Chief is called,
is called Female Masturbation Is Okay
and You Won't Go to Hell.
- Yeah.
- That's his full, her full name in the show.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's what they're doing now, to Halo.
Yep, you're gonna do the same shit they did to the Matrix.
Yeah.
Okay, the Matrix used to be about bullets.
The Matrix is about guys' bullets.
It was literally about two--
And now it's about cutting guys' bullets off.
It was about a white cop and a black cop,
and they would go into a computer and they'd kill 500 people.
And it was fucking sick.
Now it's about fucking being some kind of a gay thing.
I don't know.
I don't know, I didn't watch it.
So they got that guy from How I Met Your Mother in there.
And you know what?
Now they turned it to How I Met Your Father to get him a boyfriend.
That's right.
If things had okay, I did watch that and they know what they and they called it and they called it how I met your father
It was on tinder slash bumble. Mm-hmm. That's the title now. I watched dating apps nowadays
It's just like you go on there and it's like what is that FOMO for sure? Yeah. Yeah people are like look
I'm looking for a she/her. What does that mean? Yeah, that's right
Looking for I don't even know what that means. Yeah, she hers
this dating scene makes me wish I was in a she/her.
Exactly. They're like, "I'm looking for a she/her." I'm like, "I'm looking for he-man.
I'm Skeletor." That's right. What's up? If I'm on these apps, I'm looking,
I'm, I say I'm more, I'm interested in finding a holy
Jesus, kind of Christ. Yeah. I need to, I need to see Christ. Yeah. Also, I watched
the new Matrix and I did watch the Neil Patrick Harris thing and I was like, you
know who would crush this role if this came out directly after the third
one Sean William Scott oh yeah Sean William Scott yeah would have been
turning I mean Neil Patrick Harris was gay he's not gay enough you know it was
so sick that they made the villain just a super a super annoying gay guy yeah it
is so tight yeah actually I did I did really yeah I'm watching I'm watching
it three times that's right have you seen Southland tales no I haven't seen
Stifler's so good in that dude.
Well, let's put some respect on Sean William Scott's name.
You already called him Stifler.
I was saying it as a bit, but he called him Stifler for real.
Oh really?
You ever seen Role Models?
Yes.
There's some serious boobs in that movie.
There's boobs in that movie.
I watched it with my friend's sister man.
David Wayne.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is that the girl's name with the boobs out?
No, David Wayne is Bruce's dad.
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
from Batman is there any kind of any info yeah what's the joke here yeah let's
boobs in Batman what boobs whose boobs poison ivy poison ivy doesn't have boobs
it's all plants doesn't count that doesn't count that counts no dude the
watch that lizard the blue bitch from x-men those aren't boobs yes they are
they're not blue they're from a man is not boobs no they're not yes they are
she's made out of fucking goo she's not made out of goo so you think I'm Cortana
doesn't have Cortana of course not you're a liar you're a liar
can you know I talked about Cortana games a hundred times go ahead and try to
nutty try to nut on the I haven't I did and it was easy you didn't do that it
was quite easy nope yeah I did it was hard cuz they would go I was hard yeah
you were I bet cuz you there was not boobs because of your gay self get down
with your gay self. Get down. Anyway I heard they're changing it to boy Tana and he's
pink. Boy Tana and Mrs. Chief. Yep. Yeah I already said Mrs. Chief like a while ago.
So I've already said that earlier. Yeah she's probably gonna be some kind of
nurse now instead of a machine. Yeah and the characters will be nerds as well.
they'll probably like math and science now and there's probably gonna be way less
fingering in this version of Halo too yeah probably gonna cut out all the
fingering scenes I miss the fingering in Halo I would honestly I'm not kidding
they feel like it would feel really good to fuck one of those little flood bugs
yeah you know those little face sucker fuckers I want to fuck her that sucker
what about that alien for the the stomach puncher from alien actually a grunt oh
yeah squish all throat from how you're feeling about grave mine the disgusting
huge thing yeah I think you would like great that's like a tentacle porn thing
I don't really get that what about um for the the bat thing and the stomach of the
worm in episode 5 is that thing in the stomach of the war that thing refresh my
memory here it goes on to the window and it's suction cups what were they on
Falcon that's when they're from the worm yeah and there's a bat uh-huh okay I'm
I'm gonna search Star Wars Worm Bat.
I'm gonna see if I can see this thing.
- I don't remember this at all.
- 'Cause I don't remember it.
- There's a bat that attacks Chewbacca.
- No, no!
But they get saved, right?
- You gotta watch to find out.
- Is it a Minoc?
- Yes, the Minoc.
- Oh, okay, I know that.
- I can't believe that, those are in caves.
- Yeah, they're in caves in KOTOR.
- That is a very funny, you know it from the name,
but not from the exact description of what it is.
I knew it was in Force Caves and Kotor.
I don't watch any of the Star Wars movies, I only play the games.
I might have seen them but I don't know.
Oh, they got Kotor on the Switch now, did you know that?
I have Kotor on my phone and my computer.
I might play Kotor for the first time then.
Yeah?
You better, it's really good.
Oh dude, it's great.
Yeah, it's really fun.
It used to take hours.
This thing's pretty cool.
It's good.
I like the Minoc.
Yeah, Minoc is cool.
I'm a fan of it.
It's got a big suction cup face.
Oh yeah, we have a list today.
Oh yeah.
What time is it?
547.
- I have 47 to do.
- What?
You have something to do?
- You can't have anything to do.
- Who are you meeting? - Okay, now it's 5/48.
NBC.
- Really?
Oh, really?
- Yeah. - What are you meeting about?
- Well, it's not that NBC.
- Which NBC is it?
What does it stand for?
- Non, nonsense,
nonsense broadcasting corp.
- Nonsense, the comedian in New Orleans, Louisiana?
- Yeah, he's starting a streaming service.
- Oh, shit.
- Uh-huh.
- Is that doing hood pizza delivery?
Yeah, actually that's, yeah, they would.
You know Hood Pizza Delivery?
Uh-huh.
By No Nonsense Entertainment?
I'm gonna be in Hood Pizza Delivery.
Oh, you're gonna be in the sequel?
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna be the white nerd.
The reboot?
Oh shit, they put a white nerd in it?
They put a white nerd in it.
That's what I said, when I saw the first one,
I was like, I need a goofy-ass white nerd in this.
Who doesn't understand what's going on.
They need a character who's typing
on his mechanical keyboard in the background,
who looks really swag.
Everybody go choose No Nonsense Entertainment,
Hood Pizza Delivery.
I think you're gonna have a really good time.
Yeah.
list of the top 10 tips for trolling online this is a master class today this
is we're gonna take you fool yes school I hate this list actually I need a go no
wait did you see what he just did there wait you actually hate this list why are
you making this goofy ass face where you look absolutely stupid to the burn what
trollery is this what is wrong with you been trolled nah take it back nah back
Back in my day, getting trolled meant that you were a giant club that just bashes you
against a rock from a green-- Well, it used to be getting trolled was they make you take
photos of yourself in a dress and they send them to your school.
But now, trolling is as easy as pie.
Yeah.
It's true.
What's your best-- Guys, what's your best and biggest troll?
Oh, okay.
So get this, right?
Yep.
So you remember Bitly?
Yeah, bit.ly.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
some water while I explain this story. You can shrink any link with bit.ly.
Yeah. And uh, and sent my teacher an email. Guess what the link actually was?
Oh no. It was Rick Roll. No it wasn't. Mm-hmm. No it wasn't. Yep. Okay you have to stop.
I Rick rolled my teacher.
(laughing)
Right now you did?
Nope. I did a couple weeks ago.
I can't go to jail today.
Yeah, my best troll was probably
one time I tagged somebody.
You tagged somebody?
I tagged someone and killed them.
Attacked or tagged?
Yeah, I went werewolf.
He's trolling me right now.
You're getting trolled.
And werewolves are actually good.
God yeah guys. I think he is fucking good to drink yeah. Yeah, they just I think I
think they change speed of poop and poop to pee yeah. Do you hear about that?
Okay, can we not have a Mexican okay guys before we get before we get too
deep into trolling each other? I'm going to start the list. Okay, the top ten
tips for trolling online, but I don't want to start the list. Here's the
description trolling is like a sport. You must learn it well to win it. Here are
some suggestions number one claim that evil things are fine.
Yeah, that sucks hitler actually had b-boy. So it was fine. He was no
don't say claim evil things had b-boy swag. Yeah, you're out fine.
Hitler was fine. Hey, the devil's fine by me fine. I don't care if he
tortures my entire uncle's a guys stubbing your toe. It's fine. It's
fine to stub your toe on the coffee table. Yeah. Yeah, it's fine.
actually. Pretty much okay with LGBTness these days. Pretty much it's fine. It's fine with
me. It's fine to be LGBTQ. It's fine. Yeah, no, it's fine. Yeah, no, it's okay. It doesn't
upset my uncles or me. Me and my uncles, we actually think it's fine and we watch it on
TV every day. Yeah. Certain channels that I only watch. We're co-authoring a book about
it. I think MSNBC isn't pushing any kind of thing. Yeah. And actually, I like getting vaccinated.
Yeah. I'm wearing a max. Mm-hmm. Oh, and the booster is fine. The booster is fine and it
didn't give any single person in my in my entire family autism. Yeah. Yep.
Seriously. I think the download port on the back of the newscaster's heads are
fine. It's fine, dude. Yeah. It's okay for a newscaster's eyes to blink sideways. I
think it's great. I think it's fine and normal when their eyes turn gray because
they blinked them too slow and you see their true eyelid. Yep, and when a
politician becomes a reptilian on screen, it's okay. You know what guys? I'm gonna
I'm just gonna come on and say it. I think unchained slave trauma based mind control programming is fine. Mm-hmm fine, dude, sir
I think the monarch program is fine. I think sir. Just fine and dandy sir is good
They should be colliding more crap together. Yeah and trying to create dimensional black hole and guess what?
I love I love their statue of Shiva - yeah, I'm by me. I think rituals are fine. The Denver Airport is beautiful
I think it's that horse. It's cool. I think I think it's fine to be born on Halloween
fine,
normal
forever. You're not a son of Lucifer weird. It's okay to get
double the candy. I was telling you guys about this, but I've
been reading this like this book about this conspiracy theory
book and like this guy is like really obsessed with Satanism
and he keeps saying stuff. We're like talk about a cult. They
like killed like fifteen people or something and then like his
big like clincher is like and did I mention the leader of the
cult's wedding was on Halloween day and that's like the proof oh my god I knew
kids weren't allowed Noah wasn't allowed to celebrate Halloween grown up was
really his witness no it's just normal normal I knew erect kind of only kid I
knew who wasn't allowed to celebrate holidays was Jehovah's Witness and he
got to get school off for they only had a holiday not do Halloween I think okay
everything else was pretty fun well Jehovah's Witnesses don't celebrate
Christmas or don't even do their birthdays Brian. Yeah yeah that's fucked
up. Yeah to take that away from a child. A birthday is the most sacred day. To take that away from a
26 year old woman. Yeah leave her alone.
That's one of the most violent things you can do. Yeah. She would have got a Fitbit. Yeah. When else
you supposed to get presents in? Do they just not do presents or do they do
presents like. They don't do presents at all. It kind of sounds sick to spread Christmas and
Halloween and birthday presents and cheer around the entire year. Yeah. And
just do presents every single day. Are you doing a troll right now? No, I
seriously think that'd be normal. Yeah, so I mean that would be a good troll on
some Jehovah's Witnesses. Number two troll technique, side with the minority.
Yeah, I think minorities are okay. And I'm not trolling at all. No, here listen,
here's the description, here's the explanation from the person who wrote
that was okay find videos with topics that many people feel very strongly about
like religion and choose to side with the minority whether you truly feel that way
or not defend your opinion like it's your newborn child using as much
completely incorrect information as possible make sure you bash the opposing
view as much as possible no how about I don't yeah I don't think I will yeah I
actually hate trolling yeah trolling is actually fine now trolling is not fine
I'm
think just say come on one for fine zero for bad I think it's bad okay you are in
a tricky situation now I don't think trolling exists I think there's no such
thing he's the most deft troll I've ever seen I don't think abortion exists I've
never way you could do that to a no such thing I think okay it's not good or bad
because it doesn't exist and they show you a video you say okay I think that
exists but I don't think it's called abortion it's called something else
that's I don't know what and I don't know what it's called but it's good
whatever it is it's something I was a good or bad that's just a normal
procedure that's a video of a surgery okay if we're gonna make if you guys
really wanted to be a dentist you know who should decide this a police officer
that's who should decide if it's good or bad this is I don't know yeah okay
someone else is like yeah and you're like no no no actually not no I actually I
don't think police officers exist either they defunded them a long time ago I
seriously think abortions just fine and dandy and you should be able to cut up a
kid and I think it's dandy but not fine whatever I think if a kid I think you
should be able to just you should be able to make a fucking a smoothie out of it
an unborn child. I mean I hear that's how they make Play-Doh,
sticky enough. I'm not okay. Hey guys, I'm not okay with abortion,
unless you torture the child first.
I think we should have abortion up to age 70.
Yep. You should be allowed to to sell the unborn fetus at Costco in a
chicken bake. Yep, and hey why stop there? Let's kill
the mom too. Let's kill everybody. I don't think abortion's okay, but if I
were a baby, I would be okay with getting aborted.
Yeah, me personally, I wouldn't care. I'm like cool with it. I would be cool with it for me, but
yeah, can't make that choice for anyone. It wouldn't be a problem for me to get aborted.
I think you can, I think abortion is okay as long as you use time travel to make sure that the baby
was going to be bad. Yeah, exactly. If you, and also we should do testing to see if the kid has
like ADHD or dyslexia and then you should be able to abort them. Yeah, definitely. This child's going
to be born with dyscalculia and you have the option to either abort or have the child. Yep.
I think that abortion is not okay and instead we should be sending all of the
fetuses that have these brain things to Mars and let them figure something out
up there. Yeah, how about you evolve you fucking piece of scum shit. If you
get rid of the baby you can put in the ocean. I think you should be able
to abort any fetus as long as it doesn't have a tail. If it has a tail we need to
see what happens. You need to see what it grows into. Dude, I wish I had a tail.
tail so that I want to tell red with so yeah what kind of Taylor we took cuz okay
my tail so my tail loadout is a lion's tail just a tail with like a big tuft of
hair at the end mine would be basically it's like a tail but then at the end
there's like a truck perfect kind of triangle spike yeah yeah I think exactly
like like nightcrawlers tail like being able to use it like with swords and
stuff like I'm put wrap my yeah and a sword you want to be knife crawler who's
night crawler blue blue guy you did what
yes I did okay number three trolling strategy call alternative music
listeners stereotypical oh that's a rather normal stereotypical
that's too far for me as an alternative music listen so you like you like pop
music like Radiohead? Wow, okay. That's messed up of you to say. You know I'm a
huge OneRepublic fan. Yeah, wait, okay, so you like normal pop music like 30
Seconds to Mars that is completely normal and not avant-garde whatsoever?
That's so stereotypical of you. Yeah, interesting. I prefer that. Yeah, you
know you should find an alternative to that music that you're listening to which
is so normal. I prefer indie music, yeah, like Justin Bieber and Chris Brown. Yeah.
also a Chris Brown did yeah I listen to indie music indie music at all including
rap and country. Indie music at all. Yep don't matter. Indie of it. Indie of it. I like all of it. I like it all though. I hate all of it. I don't like indie music. Yeah I wish music would just hurry up and indie.
Mm-hmm the Andy the
is he
The Andy okay of music I get it. Yeah, you get it. I didn't get it first number four be exceptionally vulgar
Fuck you. Yo, bitch. I think that's fun. Fuck you bitch
Stereotypically normal, and I think it's fine. How normal it is and I'm I also I think you should be aborted
I think okay, so abortion is abortion is completely normal fucking shit
I'm gonna be so fucked. There's tons of fucking...
The guy's the president's shit fart, he could be gay as a dick and I wouldn't give a flying fuck over here.
My fucking president is jizz.
[Laughter]
He's a damn jizz.
Yeah, so the...
A fucking fart shit crab pooper is normal.
Yeah, you know it's nothing is more normal than a shipment that's on fire. Yeah, yeah, and it's slimy damn it
How the hell my president? Yeah?
I think I think this bastard is fine. Mm-hmm
And and this crappy bastard and my print and there's a and there's a g's cum shot. Yeah
Yeah, I mean oh definitely yeah, I think yeah, and I think you guys I think I think are
dildos yeah i think i think uh and i don't actually think that you're a serious cobswallop i think my
my spunk stain is normal yeah i think it's fine for me to spank all over my face whatever hey
i'll spunk on my mom i think i'm gonna sit upside down and spunk on my face my spunk splutes
splatters uh sperm flying jizz cum shot blast of white sauce jello cube i'm gonna make splatoon
for jizz. I want to be a jizz slave badly. I need to be one like yesterday. Being a jizz
slave is fine. I want to be a jizz slave for a liberal Democrat. I want to really badly.
I really like liberal Democrats and everything they stand for. Clap on those cum chains.
Yeah I'm putting them on because I like to be a little shit fart. I want to be in the
fucking milking machine. I want to work for a Mexican version Nancy Pelosi and I want her
smell her butt. Yep, they're basically making me like the uh...
fuck, what was the Teletubbies guy? I think it's normal to fuck a pile of pee.
I want to go into a Christian church and I want to play Diablo 3 in there. Yep.
And I want to run around top down view and I want to be shooting fire and flames. That's too much.
I'm going to be a human vacuum at Ed Buck's house.
I want to be a victim of Ed Buck very badly.
Really, really badly I want to be the victim. Yep, they're going to take a picture of me asleep on the floor.
the floor. I think Bowser's a fucking good guy and shit.
Uh huh. Yep. And it's okay if he fucks Peach's pussy.
Yep. It's fine. Peach had a bunch of fucking kids from Giz.
I think he's fine if he blasts fire red sperm, which like Cheeto dust sauce style.
I agree with socialist democrats that animals and humans can procreate. And I think that
when the baby is born though, we should abort it.
Yep. Or maybe keep the baby and then abort it later.
Yep, I think that I think it's good to put a baby in the fucking wood chipper. Yeah
Yeah, speak on it. I think it's good to have fucking sex in the oven and you burn it out
I think it's normal to watch fucking pooping on TV
TV and shit I saw I saw fucking damn crap on TV, and I liked it, and I think it's cool
I think there's nothing funny about wipeout
(laughter)
- I don't think fat people getting hit with big red balls
is humorous in the slightest.
- Yep, to me it's America's Saddest Home Videos.
- And actually I would prefer to watch CNN,
the communist news network, it was not what I call it.
- I think fucking creepy crawly bugs are cool.
(laughter)
- I think Slenderman is a good guy.
What are you looking for, it's right here.
- I dropped a cap.
- It's right here.
- Oh, okay.
- You really thought it was that important to--
- Freddy Krueger's skin is normal.
He looks good. He looks really good.
Freddy Krueger's hand is small.
Freddy Krueger's hand is small and normal.
Mm-hmm.
I think short guys and tall girls should date.
I fucking like Freddy Krueger's fingernails.
Yeah, I like 'em.
Yeah, I think his fingernails are good.
I don't think they should cook the sushi.
I think it's good to stay raw.
I think they should keep all the sushi raw.
And the worst part is probably the spicy mayo.
Yeah, I actually love picking my ingredients one by one at Chipotle.
And ketchup is good on steak.
Mm-hmm.
No, ketchup is not good on steak is what you meant to say.
Yes, it's true.
And it's just complete crap.
And you know what I really like?
You should always use A1 on a steak.
And I really like rare.
And it should always be...
I like rare steak.
No, seriously.
It should always be rare.
I don't think it should be rare.
Or you should never use A1 on steak and it should always be rare.
I think falling down a manhole getting fucked by the fucking Ninja Turtles is normal.
Yep.
I think fucking becoming a weed junkie and getting addicted to pot and popcorn is good.
I think it's normal to walk around with fucking crutches a wheelchair is better
than legs I really fucking think that shit I think it's fucking normal to walk
around with four robot legs like a spider no I seriously think Terry Shivo
at a soul. No. Yeah, I don't think she was as useless and devoid of a human soul as a
lunchbox. I don't think she might as well have been a Lego. I think that she was a real person.
I think Jeb Bush was wrong to do that fucking shit. Yeah. And also I, I mean I just... And
sagging your pants is good. Sagging your pants? Yeah, I like to see some cruddy money underwear.
I'd like to see money print underwear sagging over the jeans. I think that's good.
Okay? And I really like rap and I think that it's good. And country?
Rap and country. Don't even get me started on how much I love that fucking ass shit. It makes perfect sense.
I think that more songs should be about money and clothes and what kind of hose
that the person has. Mm-hmm. Seriously. And ladies should be pimps too. And I think
Euphoria is a great show and I don't think it's in for the show Humongous Perfect Breasts on TV.
that the ICU at the hospital is not might as well be the Sahara Desert in terms of
human spirit and I'm okay that euphoria is an Israeli sigh up it's okay with me
it's cool actually I think Israel should be 50 times the size it should be we
should swap Israel and Russia mm-hmm Texas and Israel should we should swap
Israel and the moon mm-hmm they should get the whole moon yeah we should put I
Mean we should send Israel to the moon
What's that number five is be creative which I think hey, I think we already just covered that yeah
We mix all okay
I loved I love to paint fucking pictures of a rats come
I actually hate to paint pictures of what happened to me as a kid. I just imagined a
liberal unicorn
Yeah, I think fucking rap music about sex is cool. Yep
And I think it's great to be a female rapper. Yeah
That's right. Yeah, I think they bring a unique perspective. Yeah. No, I think a female
Waiter is a good idea. Yeah, I don't everything. Yep
I don't think a female rapper would fall over if they tried to put on a chain and it's good that women work in
Drive-thrus and I think that guys can be nurses. I do think that women should not have to wear high heels all the time
I mean, I think straight guys are nurses. I
Do not think that women should have to choose between either high heels or roller skates
Or lying down I don't think it's wrong to see a woman's hair
I think it's completely moral for a woman to show off her disgusting sluttish hair.
No, I think that's normal. Yeah, and it's normal for women not to shave their arms.
Yeah. Yep. It's actually good that they don't shave their arms. Yeah. And it
doesn't gross me out when they don't shave their arms. Mm-hmm. They should have
arms that look like... And a woman's ankle should be more than one inch in circumference. Yeah, a
woman's forearm should look exactly like the halal cart guys. I
I think it's fine if a woman weighs over 70 pounds.
[laughter]
I think that's perfectly A-OK.
Mm-hmm.
Yep. And she's seriously deserving of a husband.
And it's not good that we forced women to eat nothing but sugar cubes.
Yeah, that's not good.
It's not good.
It's not good to make your wife eat cotton rounds.
I don't think...
[laughter]
To fill her up.
Cotton rounds and sugar cubes.
I don't think... I do not think that I should get free season tickets to the woman reserve.
and Cameron should not suck my penis tonight
it's about trolling not hypnosis yeah I seriously know the difference I guess
trolling is a form of hypnosis I guess we discover that number six is multiple
accounts Oh I'm Patrick and I think abortion is okay I'm Cameron and I think
think that birds are real. Well yeah I'm I'm Patrick and I think that they should
lower the the distance requirement from a hundred feet to fifty feet when it
comes to playgrounds and they should let me let me buy binoculars again.
He's getting background check like he's buying an AR-15.
right and what's answer what will you be using this fishing rod for fishing?
Yes,
but also buying a candy bar and
oh wait. He likes he's a he's a granny guy now. Hi it's me Cameron and oh yeah
he likes great. He's a granny guy. Hi it's me Cameron. Let me know when you
when you go from seventeen to eighteen.
Let me know come on to put a joke in
yeah
is
that was good
sorry patrick
i tried my best
that was not your best at all had my best we've we spent a record yet but i
would like to know that i are comments camera pretty much
just a pet of we're not even a pet of large i think it's a
you gave up
yeah i did need gave me a spent the last like twenty minutes just
screaming it just shit
my uh... i'm shutting down i got a
what how long i'm really a little bit like this on this next yet no it's like
at a point number seven
humor helps trolling
uh... that could have been that could have been a year
i don't mean you know if i don't mean you know that i have a lot of it so good
about only noon
You should have noon, man.
Yeah, man, if I nooned that shit,
shit would have been traded.
Traded from Drain.
I hate when--
(laughing)
Traded from Drain.
I think Patrick's okay.
I actually hate when cowboy duels are at noon.
Huh?
Me too.
It's okay, it's actually good to have a stroke mid-episode.
It's good for you.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think that we should--
It's good to have only function of one arm after.
I think it's good to eat a vegetable and it's not vegetables weren't invented 40
years ago.
Vegetables don't have things called micro worms in them that go in your stomach
and eat your shit.
I think fluoride is seriously making the insides and my brain
I think 90% of diseases are real.
I didn't fart.
He didn't fart again. I didn't do a double back-to-back fart
with a fart sandwich of me talking. Okay now number eight this is another tough one for us
don't become a trollie. That's
Hard for me, I guess
Trolly
Trolly trolly sour worms pretty good. So on rare occasion she worms on rare occasions
The troll will become a trolly if signs of this occur abandon all hope for that trolling attempt
Unless you think you are smart enough to get yourself out of it and emerge on top once more, but you most likely are not
It's true
Okay, the next one actually we could put into practice really easily number nine say no you to every argument whoa
Pretty you should say no you know you know you I think it's fine
That is gonna be really bad if we keep doing yeah, that was gonna
That was we I just don't we got a huge bullet. That was great. I have like five minutes left
No you
Number ten easy for Caleb become a grammar Nazi Oh a grammar Nazi yeah
He's a grandma. You want to become a grandma not see no no no no and you what no cuz you want to get you want
To get 50 grandmas in a shower together with you. That's what I said. No you did your grandma
Not see the way you're hiding your grandma from me no
You see my you've met my grandma
Yes, I have
It's fine
Okay, you fuck my banana. I don't care. I give a fuck dude
got shingles what yeah I got it hey do you know you know you have a grandma I
don't have a great that's why you like them so yeah because you don't have one
it's like people who are only children who are like to a grandma tinder date
with a bottle of wine and a feather duster you showing up to funerals he's
she's like but is she like she was a lot who was her who was like leisure suit
Larry just like come here up. He doesn't know yeah people die showing up to
funerals and being like did she have a Facebook account she have a public
friends list she have an alive beautiful twin who was her best friend who was
closest in age to her and who's closing age but still a little bit older yeah and
now sad and unstable. I don't know what's worse you guys calling me a pedophile or you guys
calling me a tomb raider. I think definitely pedophile is worse you should be glad. Yeah.
There's nothing illegal about fucking an old nasty granny and letting her boobies sag in
your mouth but that one doesn't sexually arouse you actually so you don't like it. Yeah. I
I don't think there's anything wrong with fucking a gram.
You know what you and I would actually hate?
It would be fine.
Okay.
Actually it would be fine if you said it.
Said what?
That I'm normal.
Oh it would be fine?
Okay we're doing the trolling so it would be fine.
It would suck if you said I was fine.
Okay well you're seriously normal.
For normality.
You're seriously fit for normality.
I fucking love normality.
You know what I honestly believe? I do think that it's worse for a
like a young woman to fuck an old guy
than for a young guy to fuck a really old nasty granny.
Yeah? Yeah. It feels like the man is getting taken advantage of
but that old bitch knows what she's doing. She's been there before.
Do you know what I mean? No.
You don't agree? I think it's wrong both ways.
The idea of an old penis going into a young vagina
is so much more like like my thing is fine if they're doing it in the same
room. I think old vaginas look.
I think probably an old woman's vagina looks if it's a swarm or if it's a
swap. I think it's okay.
Well, that's okay.
But if they're unconnected incidents, yeah incidents,
I was like man of a higher rate of dementia.
Yeah.
So a lot of these old guys, they don't even know they're having sex with
a beautiful.
And there's a higher rate of uh...
Yeah it was just after their fortune and their veiny old cock.
The higher rate of dust too.
They got a much higher rate of dust.
Yeah that's right.
Yeah.
And a higher rate of money.
Oh yeah.
I mean you know it's called the blowjob because you're doing two things.
You're blowing the damn dust off and sucking on that thing.
That's right.
Yeah.
Whisping away the cobwebs with your tongue.
like you're making it's like yeah he's old man can't fuck yeah I can it's crazy
like there it's crazy that there's just like an age where you're just like I
can't fucking do it anymore I can't have sex yeah I think it's like 24 yeah
pretty close to five yeah you're just like this sucks I never want to do this
again yeah I hope I hope I never have to take funny pills that make my penis
bigger dude oh yeah those old men are basically living hell every day old men
need to be liberated yeah we need to let old men walk around nude that's why old
men get into like crazy shit oh yeah that's why they get in RC planes yeah
cuz like you can't have the option to jack off uh-huh yeah I thought of like
because if you start a heart attack if you're that old and you jack your shit
off or you can't even like you you litter there guys who when you get too old all
you can do is move your balls around and hope that you come yeah can you imagine
that hell yeah sitting there squirting out of your fucking loose penis man just
pushing your balls around and the foreskins dry already it's it's sagging
it's sagging like like way it's a good yeah you're trying to think about like
it's like so like if you like it's kind of like I was saying like that's kind of
like being on like adderall or something but when you're on adderall you still
you'll jack off for two hours and it'll be still be fun. Yeah exactly this is like
it's a chore to sit there and like you have to come up with techniques where
maybe you make you make a hole with your fingers it's like a little smaller than
your balls and maybe you push them through that one at a time so they pop
real hard. Plus you got a punch on your balls like Fonzie on a fucking jukebox. You do.
You gotta elbow your balls. Elbow straight down your nuts just to make sure that it's still
work you guys know there's electricity in your balls yeah yep what kind static
like heart electricity oh okay yeah and she rolls you if they're but they're
hairy enough no yeah I mean I'm sorry I'm creating a serious nuclear winter oh
yeah no they'd rub it you know if I walk fast enough on the ground yeah rub my
you drag your paws across the rug fast yeah I drag those things around it looks
I'll shoot a lightning bolt. Do you see how funny it is that like God put your dick and
balls in the place on your body that is like always going to become the smelliest
stinkiest most disgusting thing? Why is that bro? Why couldn't they put your
he put your balls right here or some shit? Because it smells awesome. But like why would
they why would your balls go in a place where they're just like dark and squished between your legs and shit?
The balls should be on each leg. Completely covered in hair. The balls should be in each leg because I
I mean the ball should literally be like hidden inside of a bone.
Yeah.
I don't ever need to touch my balls.
Yeah, they should be.
Balls should be on each side, each side next to the, like, you know, like maybe, maybe it's
like the balls are on top, like hidden inside of your body, right?
Yeah.
Balls are hidden on top and then it goes down in one big, so it's two tubes connecting both
the balls and then they go down and then they connect.
So it's like, kind of like a...
That's pretty smart actually.
Yeah, so it's like two...
What is going, what happened?
There's something going on outside, I don't want to worry about it.
You looked so scared just now.
Yeah, I thought a bat got in here.
You think that's what a bat sounds like?
I thought a big bat got in here.
Oh, alright, well, that's all. That's that.
I don't think that would have been a big bat.
Bye everybody.