Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- This is seriously not how I wanted to spin my story today.
- You were the one who started this conversation.
- I didn't want to have to do this to you.
- I have a spicy mouth right now.
- I have the highest quality sperms in the group.
- I didn't want to do this today, but Patrick.
- I ate a gyro and now my mouth is all spicy.
- Patrick.
- What are you doing in here?
Get out.
- Get out.
- Leave.
- Get out now.
- We need to hear about this.
- You need paper towels, you need to get out.
- Okay, back to the matter of fact at hand.
- My sperms are masterpiece quality.
- My sperms are shit.
- No.
- My sperms look like--
- You're not in the competition for a reason.
We know you have shit sperms, okay?
- You're third place sperms.
My sperms are bronze.
- I have divine--
My sperms, this is what--
When my sperms hit your tongue, you'll go,
"Oh, that's divine."
- No. - Yep.
- My sperms get in the mouth like pop rocks.
- My sperms are so strong.
When they hit your tongue, they weigh it down.
Your tongue just droops out of your mouth.
It unrolls on the ground.
My sperms will make your mouth go numb.
I'm not kidding.
My sperms, same exact shape as shit.
Shit has all sorts of shapes.
My sperms have arms and legs.
My sperms can speak English.
Not very well.
My sperms can speak five different languages.
Including spermies.
You do not have polyglot sperms.
My sperms only speak Esperanto.
Yeah, that's great.
And Klingon.
Awesome.
My sperms are nerds.
Great.
actually celebrate Festivus instead of normal Christian shit. Yeah, oh yeah, look
at look at my sperms under a microscope you'll see they're all wearing
colanders. My sperms are so strong that they force their way out of my
pee hole when I'm not even touching my thing. They just crawl out and they go
around and they look for people to go in. Okay, so you have you have sperms that
force their way into people. They don't force their way in. You just said that. No,
they don't. I said they look around for people to get in. It's not something
thing that I can control their too strong control your sperm. I can't
he has uncontrolled one is going up your leg right now a sperm, not my problem.
My butthole has been her medically sealed. It's not going for your butthole
yeah, he's butthole. You got hermit crabs in it and they seal it for him.
No, they hold it closed with with their picture. Their pictures, their
pictures, my sperms, a pinchers, my sperms like a straight to dvd. Your
Your sperms look like season three.
- Yup.
- And that's from the song.
- Your sperms got the HIV.
- My sperm got HIV.
Your sperm look like a DVD.
My sperm smell like a cage fight.
Your sperms look like stage fright.
My sperm Gary Coleman.
Your sperm Gary Showman, Gary Goleman.
(laughing)
- Gary Goleman?
them funny ass sperms. Hairy old man. My sperms, hairy old man. Your sperms sound like Gary
Goldman. Gary Goldman. Dude, it's time we let the world know. You gotta let your girl go.
P-A-L is the best in the business. Hell yeah, we got sperms like Jesus. Yep. Yep. Uh huh.
Okay, so we got a new song basically that's on our recording to do this. So we're going
the aqua fina route which in a couple years is not gonna be good
which poor coffee onto your phone. I didn't pour coffee. It came off the lid you fucking moron. You picked it up and you poured it on.
You have the mind of a monkey. We're going the aqua fina route which means you know we're
doing like a you know they we do a song parody of my dick we're doing a parody of
a parody of my dick and then in an interview years down the line one of us
is gonna get very flustered about a racial question mm-hmm and plus you're
doing that new movie Patrick from the Ghetto. Yeah mm-hmm.
Awkwafina is Patrick from the Ghetto. I know we've definitely talked about it
before but funniest career path is is yeah doing being the being gangsta
Awkwafina and then doing the like doing the sad a24 movies and then the dividing
line is that you were a Skeksis in Dark Crystal. She was a Skeksis? Dude she was
one of she was like wasn't the Gourmand but she was like one of them. It's so it's
That's that's so funny that that's like that's like the metamorphosis phase.
That's the that's the in between of those two is yeah going. Yeah being a
skekis being a skeksis do that's my favorite movie. She's not in the movie.
She's in the show dark Chris that movie's sick. It's your favorite movie.
It's like my all-time favorite movie. It's a really good movie. I love I love
puppets. Probably Mickey blue eyes. Yeah, Frank Sinatra. No Hugh Grant.
Hugh Grant.
Hugh Grant and James Caan.
Hugh Grant is the one, he got caught with a sex worker.
And then Jay Leno was like, "What the hell were you thinking you stupid idiot?
You stupid bitch.
What the hell is wrong with you, you big tooth fuck?"
I don't remember this story.
And that's not what Jay Leno says.
He doesn't curse like that on TV.
Yeah he does.
He doesn't swear.
Jay Leno swears like a sailor.
He's polite.
No he's polite.
Jay Leno's like, "What are you looking at this fucking fat piece of shit on my couch?"
He doesn't do that.
Where are you from?
The toilet?
What are you gay?
He didn't say that.
Are you gay?
You're gay from the toilet.
He didn't say that.
Now, now, now let me.
Who did he say that to?
Who was on the couch when he said that?
He said that to Dame Judi Dench.
He did?
Yes.
Oh my god.
Jay Leno had Dame Judi Dench on the couch and he said, "Let me turn around.
Let me see if."
Does he know or does he not know that she is an international treasure?
He doesn't know.
Does he know that she's my treasure?
All he cares about is...
Does he know that he is...
if she had four wheels in an engine he would care about my god yeah this guy
uh... he says the total i would do anything to bolt a steering wheel to the
back of her head on the on j_e_ you're just a little real jay leno right now
what kind of sure you were
what kind of sure my word and i'm sure that a pants
none of your business or ok
was turnaround let me see a book
or
people building
that was a little bit that was it was a drug and it was one of his cars and
cars
big car little stick
driving stick
i'm driving to take to the right group
i'm jay leno and i'm going to sit in a car over the uh...
i'm not going to work hard for a restaurant was he going to make
uh... notes
but i think it had a big impact that didn't seem to use it for her
make-up
well-suited and i think that it may not be a and i thought i had
I'd like to drink it down.
Mm-hmm.
McDonald's.
20-piece nuggets and a soda, yeah.
I'd like to drink it now.
Yo, Mick, they came around looking for you the other day.
Oh, boy.
They came looking for me, Ronald McDonald.
Let them know, Ron.
McDonald's.
Restaurant that's named after my name.
I am a fucking clown.
[LAUGHTER]
And then you know there's the Espanola version.
uh-huh mcdonald's chocolate chips and pancakes for breakfast
it's in English in this in the in the Spanish version but they talk like
everything say that's sweet breakfast yeah oh they breakfast at McDonald's
chocolate chip pancakes at McDonald's you know it makes Arnold's in in Mexico
and Spain yeah okay guess what you guys actually get the hot cakes fucking
idiots so yeah they're actually hot cakes and I'm pancakes oh no you're
think of a different restaurant. Oh yeah, you're right. I'm thinking of IHOP.
IHOP, so fucking shit man. Terrible, one of the worst restaurants ever.
The worst restaurant ever. Literally the only time it's excusable to go there is if it's
4am. And even then, even then. What? You go to McDonald's after your theater. Oh my god,
after your musical. Uh huh. I was never in theater but I went to IHOP. My bad. I went
to IHOP one night-- Take it back. I take it back. I went to IHOP one night after a
musical had like been let out and that was like one of the worst things. Is that
a tradition? Mm-hmm. Theater kids go to IHOP after and then they go to each other's
houses and they all have freaky sex. I would have been an amazing theater kid, dude. I would have been perfect.
Dude, we went to a theater college. My mom tried to get me to go to 50 different times and I was like, "What? You want me to dress up and be gay on stage? Hell no."
I was like I probably would have been a superstar if I did that dude I was almost
if I if I had seen cannibal the musical when I was younger that would have done
them theaters actually kind of cool yeah you man oh fuck if I was a theater dad
be fucking crazy I would be the worst person that would be fucking insane yeah
thank God I wanted to be cool yeah I'm dude that's all setting to think about
me in a theater meet me like the Sun will come out you really want to cut the
acting bug just you think oh crap you think you'd play yeah we should raise
the money on like go fund me or some shit so we can do like a stage production of
Annie where I play and it literally it doesn't take any money to do a stage
space production the budget of a gee-haw the budget of a play is just for the
the director's bail yeah for one of the actors do you get a little it's free
what do you think that we could how much you think it costs to rent out Madison
Square Garden for a night like ten bucks yeah if it's if it's like a night
where nothing's happening I bet it's if it's ten thousand dollars should we
should do it we should do it I think carmine was pretty cheap into Carnegie
it's gotta be Madison Square Garden. Dude, Madison Square Garden would be so fucking funny.
Yeah. We just have like that it's completely empty. Two rows of people.
Like there's 150 people there and we're just doing also like the same volume on the speakers
as if like Kevin Hart's doing like a packed fucking stadium. Dude, that's so fun. That's
crazy. Doesn't it? Getting it like pro shot, like getting like all the cameras that like fly in.
Yeah. Have the fire. Yeah. I've never thought about that, like how weird that
Dane Cook special is where he's playing TD Garden.
Where he's in the...
Yeah, TD Garden.
Yeah.
Where he...
What is that?
Vicious Circle.
Because he's on...
Because the stage is a circle.
Theater in a round.
Yeah, the theater, that's a circle.
Is this supposed to be Dane Cook?
This is the vicious circle that I'm in.
It's in the BK Lounge.
The terrible...
That's a good Dane Cook.
That's a really bad Dane Cook.
No.
Back me up.
I don't know what Dane Cook sounds like.
Fuck!
No, that was not...
I got a boost of energy all of a sudden.
You did.
I think it's because you zipped your jacket up.
What?
You're gonna scream?
We just gotta power through sounds here.
Yeah, you can't.
Because there's so many of them.
You, I, literally, I am mentally incapable of not get it, like, that, there it is again.
I think there is a, I think there is a fight.
I think they're watching videos in this part of the office.
Right.
I'm gonna get you, I'm gonna get you headphones to just play white noise all the time.
Yeah.
Maybe I should be the one wearing the headphones.
No, you should be wearing earplugs.
Yeah.
I just never hear a thing you guys are saying.
Do you guys do that?
I've become an earplugs at concerts, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have too.
They just prick my ears, man.
I like going to a comedy show that has earplugs available.
That's hilarious.
Like at Union Hall where you can buy them and then buying the earplugs and putting them
in.
Just in the middle, yeah.
Sitting front row.
If somebody goes too loud a laugh and just shaking it, ugh.
putting the earplugs in. It does the thing that sucks is it real like I remember
when I would go to like loud shows or whatever as a kid my parents would
always tell me like you have to put your plugs in because like you're gonna lose
your hearing and it sounds you're still gonna hear it it sounds the same or
whatever it does it sounds like shit with your plugs in. It does sound so bad. It's horrible it's it's like so
much less enjoyable. I just don't care. Yeah. Well that's you got to get close to
the stage. I just rather not be at a concert than be at one with earplugs.
I don't like live music as much as I used to.
I don't go to concerts that much.
Yeah, I know, me neither.
I haven't been going to stuff because it's like, yeah.
Remember when we saw Have a Nice Life?
Yeah, that was sick.
Yeah, and it was like, I mean, what was it?
That was, what's that place?
Great Scott.
Great Scott, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good venue.
Yeah, but it was like punishingly loud.
Yeah, it was sick.
That was like the first time I ever did consider buying it, but it was like, that show was
at like one in the morning.
Yeah, it was like, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know.
Punishingly loud yeah, that was sick. That was like the first time I ever did consider buying it
But it was like that show was that like 1 in the morning. Yeah, that was weird
I hate when you're at a show like that you go outside to smoke a cigarette
And then everybody everybody's talks at such a loud volume because they're all fucked up in the ears
Yeah
Hey, can I bum a cig up you?
Let me get a cig!
You smoking Camel Blue?
Oh dude, love it!
The show is awesome!
It's not a guy from the show, it's just a guy who walks up to you on Instagram.
Hey!
Can I have one?
What's up?
What's that?
I learned to speak from a bird!
What's that in your mouth?
You wanna buy a taffy?
You sound like the taffy salesman.
Peanut brittle?
Can I interest you in a gumdrop?
Here's a CD!
It's me and my friends, we're in a barbershop quartet!
listen to it. But it ain't free though. You listen to it. Hello. Hello. It's getting louder. Do you want to buy toffee and sweets?
You want to come to my house? We are the four sweet boys. We can't hang out in my house. We can sit in my car.
The four sweet boys from Dorchester. We need to become a... And we're a barbershop quartet. We need to start doing
Candy Grounds. And that's their only original song and then all the other songs are E40 songs.
Yeah.
I like butt meat.
Put that pussy on me.
Let's fuck.
That song's so good.
Best song ever made, dude.
Let's fuck.
E40 Gangsta Boo.
You want this dick?
Yeah, I want that dick.
What?
We gender swapping.
I got him to say it.
Yeah, I want that dick.
I'm gonna get it.
I'm finna get it.
I like dick meat.
I like ball stink. I like nut stink. He's got me blocked on Twitter, man. What? He has had
me blocked on Twitter since I was like 17. What did you do? I don't remember. You did
something. I don't remember. You wrote an article called like the E40. E40 actually
doesn't like butt meat. What E40's butt smells like, an investigation. I would investigate
yeah yeah probably smells like enormous yeah 40s day yeah 40 pound but yeah you
know he has I got a 40 pound boy he has he has he has wine he has like his own
vineyard Oh Earl Stevens Reserve and I he's got Santana DVS guess it makes you
wanna have sex he I got a bottle of his wine and it's like it's like supposed to
be like a red wine like a Pinot Grigio or whatever and it literally tastes like
lemonade it's like it's sparkling it's like soda yes fucking delicious I bet
that's so good it's so good like a wine bottle yeah but it's like wine is one of
those things where I feel like if I drank enough of it I would start to like it
but I don't why would I want to drink enough wine I'd get addicted to it I
probably like get really drunk if I drank enough wine I don't like it's the
same thing as like like growing up and drinking tasting coffee and being like
"Bleh!"
Yeah.
And now it's like, "Oh, I like it."
Or beer, dude.
My dad used to give me sips of beer every day.
I hated beer until I was like 14.
Yeah, same.
And I was at a party.
I did not like beer for a very long time.
I was at a party.
It was all they had.
And then I just kind of like, I looked at it and I was like, "Hmm, well."
And then like took a big, I think I chugged the can.
Because I was like, "Oh, if I just chug it, then it'll go down faster."
What's the first drink you ever had?
I think mine was Mike's Hard.
Pineapple soda and vodka.
Mine was vodka.
I don't remember what was mixed in,
but there was something mixed in.
- Mine was Mike's heart when I was like
something pretty young. - Crazy like soda.
- It was just something from a convenience store.
- And then I remember being like,
oh, that's awesome, I like drinking.
And then like the next week, I filled a Solo cup,
I like raided my parents' liquor cabinet,
filled a Solo cup with half vodka, half Hennessy.
I was like, that's a mixed drink.
- Yeah. - And I just, it was awful.
- I would drink straight vodka too
when I was starting to drink.
- My uncle-- - It's cool.
- My dad's uncle, so my great uncle,
- Donald, no, Dennis, I don't know if it doesn't matter.
- Donald Dennis Draco.
- My uncle Denise.
- My uncle Draco.
- My uncle Denise, he came over one Christmas
and left like a handle,
like this had to be like $100 worth of Bacardi.
Like it was like the biggest handle
I think I've ever seen in my life of Bacardi.
And he left it, my parents hid it under the kitchen sink.
And me and my like two brothers would like sneak,
drinks we would make ourselves like mixed drinks and then just use the computer
you know like we would do like you know we didn't have cars or anything. You're just drinking to sit in your house.
Yes when you're like 14. Which I would never do now. Yeah no oh no believe me I would not have
two beers and fall asleep around the TV. I hate drinking and just sitting in my house watching TV.
But we would all like sneak drinks and then like not together so none of it we
didn't organize this at all so each time someone would sneak we would fill it up
with water. So by the end, we just had a Bacardi thing full of water.
Yeah, I got in trouble for... I didn't fill it up with water, but I got in trouble.
My mom got mad at me because the vodka was gone and stuff. Yeah, it's
bad. Because you're also a little too young to get away
with that. Yeah, yeah. Where it's like, "Oh my god, my son drank half a bottle of
vodka." I went to this kid that I didn't... I stopped really
hanging out with him after this happened.
But we were at his house, I went to his house after school
and we like drank some of his parents vodka
and we're sitting in the kitchen and then like cleaned it up
but then like some of the vodka spilled
onto a paper towel roll and then he picked up
the paper towel roll and just lit it on fire.
So the whole thing of paper, like it lit on fire
and then it's like two minutes at like, not even,
like he was just sitting there standing
with the thing on fire and then his mom walked in the back door and looked at
him and it's like what the fuck are you doing and then me and my other friend
just bolted out of his house and I don't really I never really. I've never had
one of those drinks where they set the top on fire. Oh, I want to have a
flaming most so bad to just get your mouth flaming hurt your mouth drinking
it. I think you maybe would flaming. What's the one where you where you you
drink it and then you light the like trail into the cup and it like dynamite
dynamite. Yeah, what's the one where you only drink a little bit of it and then
you put like a cloth into it and you shake it up, you light it on top and you
soda, you throw it at a Coca Cola, a British guy's car. Molotov cocktail.
Yeah, that's what it is. Yeah. No, but I've never, I've always wanted to have
one of those drinks, they light on fire. I'm not a fan, I don't want my food to
be on fire, I'll say it. Then you've never had baked Alaska. Yeah, somebody
never had baked Alaska. What's baked Alaska? Oh, nothing. Remember that Betty
- It's like a rocker cake commercial with the molds.
It's like the three-tier mold system.
- I do not want to eat a moldy cake.
- Oh, hell no.
- No.
- But it's like the mold thing where it's like,
"You can make ice cream cake.
"You can even make baked Alaska."
That's how I found out about baked Alaska
and I wanted my mom to make that so bad.
- They catch on fire a cake.
- A catch on fire cake.
- It's a cake on fire.
- It's an ice cream cake and it catches the top on fire.
Yeah, candles if you're fucking stupid.
This is an ancient Inuit tradition.
would make an ice cream cake, they'd cover it in vodka, and then they'd catch it on fire.
Yeah. I wanna eat fried ice cream so bad. Fried ice cream is so good. We used to make
fried ice cream when I was a kid, but it was just corn, you just put it in corn
flakes. What? You just roll around a ball of ice cream into corn flakes. I wanna eat the fried
ice cream from Whippersnappers in Londonderry, New Hampshire right now. How
do you fry ice cream? How does that make any goddamn sense? It's great, it's so good, you fry it.
that doesn't help me what's she I mean I don't know I ate it I didn't make it
here's how you make fried ice cream you go to a restaurant that has it and you
say can I get the fried ice cream yeah they bring it to you how do you guys
feel about one Oh flan funny ass name for it it is pretty fun I'll have the I'll
have the pocket flan that's right remember that movie Envy Jack Black Ben
Stiller Christopher Walken let's do Jack black again we can't do it three weeks
in a row to candy three Jack black that's a good movie we can't do three black
jacks or Jack blacks I why do I always say black Jack I don't know it's so hard
to do for you ever seen that movie up envy no so the movie where Jack black
invents a cream that vaporizes dog poo envy and he becomes a millionaire I'm
envious of Jack black getting on the visa being a rock band yeah I think we
need to be in a right now rock and roll we didn't play rock and roll we need to
we just start the band and say we're taking rock and roll back to its roots
yeah and then we do like covers of splish-splash yeah oh my god around the
clock we have to we have to do yeah just play like splish-splash jingle bell rock
yeah it's so fun like 50s rock music is so bad yeah it's so fucking fun it's
like this is like this is satanic yeah this is the devil this is what this is
what like inspired every every like documentary it's like like Black
Sabbath and they're like we were inspired heavily by by little Richard yeah yeah
war pigs and then you see like it's footage of little Richard and he's like
to be fair if I Richard is sick though I don't I shouldn't I if I walked if I
walked into my my kids room and he was just listening to Splish Splash I would
think he was possessed yeah it's the same it's like it's the same it's like it's
like tiptoe through the tulips yeah scary yeah it's just a little too
bad
the bong and listen to split mom it's just what it's come on said other little
Richard song no no is this Rudy he's a king right little Richard he's no he's
very little. He's a tiny little Richard. He's a little piano and he sits on it and he goes
"Whaaaaaa!" You know that song where he goes "Whaaaaaa!" You're being too loud today. Yeah.
You're so loud today. I don't know why. I don't know either. You know what it is? I
just got a bed frame. I'm sleeping better. Nice. I slept pretty good myself last night.
Yeah. I did not sleep good. I finally got a bed frame in my new place. Wayfair, there's
there's a kid in it yeah, which did you you're the michael from wayfair what the
hell is a bed yeah. What the hell there's no damn kid in this. I'm sending it back
yeah. That was the funniest conspiracy. That was the telltale one was when was
when I saw the the the bed frame that's that was called Luke Skywalker. I was
like I know they're sending me Luke's yeah Luke's in here. John's all the other
ones that come you know
grown woman. Hey, how you doing? You want to buy me cigarettes? I don't know how old I am.
You've been sitting in a cabinet for fucking 20 years? Yeah, they fed me beans most of my life.
What do you guys think happened with her? I think a lot of the consensus by like women with
bangs is that Burke Ramsey did it. And that's a professional wrestler? Burke
Mark Ramsey is like the brother. I think that the whole family did it and they
were alien robots. The little, the like young brother? The older brother. But
he's still young, right? I don't know. How old was he? People think that he was
like a psycho and then he killed John Bonnet and then the parents covered it
up. In that book I read, they said that the parents- They never found her bones
or anything, right? The parents did it because they were like, they were like
connected to the CIA or something. Yeah. Yeah. I personally think that she was a
vampire. Mm-Hmm. I see they thought she ran Z. Yeah, there's no way yeah, she's
actually a mummy.
Scary mz. Yeah, yeah, and she was not dead. She was actually beginning her
life. I think it's a honey. I shrunk the kid situation. Yeah, do you think they
shrank her? I think they shrank her and she's been living with ants and little
tiny pieces of doesn't be crazy. If it's like
John Bonet just grew up to be Amanda Seyfried or something
I feel like that's like a fantasy you're having.
No.
Wouldn't it be crazy if she grew up being a manatee breed?
No, it's like crazy she's like-
I grew up to be Justin Long.
It's a little too specific.
Yeah.
Wouldn't it be crazy if, I don't know, I was married to Nelly Furtado?
That would be- I would not marry her.
She has a whole song about her being a promiscuous girl.
But she also has a song where she's like a bird.
That doesn't balance promiscuity in a marriage.
You would-
She also has a song about being a man eater.
Yeah, she's a man eating bird. I would-
Look out, Haji Beats.
your other son, right? I am a man eating bird. You know that Haji beats is
married to Nelly Furtado. They have a kid really yep. Wow congrats. Yeah, I'd
like to smell her stodgy feet.
I would actually yeah, I bet she wears wooden sandals and I'd just love to
peel them off and yeah that hey that child I'd hate to say that she's
probably going to have an odd future.
That's right,
probably go up to be a rescue a scroll
the that shows that we're gonna grow up into a long
you won't give a fuck
man the trust and wolfgang
and you're calling out with uh... at at a camp flocked out of all of my bed last
night with my nightmare
yeah
it's not a prior right now i had a dream about that i had a dream but trunkett
i have a full
hoping that i have a look at that
i think that i have a good
I had a dream that I was the cockroach from Yonkers.
I got eaten.
I got eaten by this gay guy.
And you screamed in your pants.
Yeah?
Mhm.
You did when you got eaten.
You made scream out your thing.
Do you guys remember how awesome it was when Tyler the Creator ate a bug?
I know.
It was like, "I'm a freaking sweet bug eater.
I'm a guy who eats a bug.
I'm a hot eating, drinking, blood eater."
I thought it was really gross when Tyler the Creator ate the bug.
I was happy that he knew he did was right and he hung himself right after that's
right. That's what he did was wrong. I a guy who eats a bug. I'm a free
you
I'm just the guy who died and hung himself because I ate a bug again.
That's
you know that's why he hangs himself in the video, because
the bug he still had the bug taste in his mouth, couldn't get rid of it.
Rather die than have a bug in that video dude. I saw when I saw that so
13. Oh my God, changed my life. Yeah, me too. I was eating bugs left and right.
I wanted to buy that stupid Odd Future Cloud button down, remember that? As soon as Earl
got out of, as soon as Earl got out of bad kid school. That, that. It was so fun, people
were like, "Free Earl!" We have to save him from high school. Yeah. His mom sent him to
like a, a. His mom sent, yeah, because he made 50,000 songs about rape by the time he
was 13. Yeah. I would have done the same thing, dude. Me too. I would have been like, "Get
the fuck out of here, dude. You're not living next to these kids, dude." She was just being
responsible parent probably can you imagine if you're a bit it was a
knowing Tyler the Creator yeah like from a play date he's eating bugs in your
living room feeling not did you're going to be a school bro yeah but it was
annoying like having to go to oh I don't know Samoa I was probably beautiful
tropical paradise yeah he went to surf Academy no I had to buy the surf all day
I'm so awful yeah I didn't do luaus oh my god he came after way better it was swaggy
he was like he was asleep the whole time yeah yeah what's that they literally had
a song called a par yeah hey that's on staples that song pretty good that song
is pretty good pretty sick that's how I found out about Vince Staples and then
he kind of that's how I found out about sexual assault it is so fun I again is
probably some people a bunch of people talk about it's very funny to imagine
somebody who's a big fan of like Earl Sweatshirt and Tyler the Creator right
now to like be like I'm gonna listen their old stuff yeah yeah that's what
happened like all like the tik-tok kids are yeah Tyler the creators old stuff
they're like he's gonna do eat and what he took off all of her limbs and then
fucked her dead body well now it is songs are like I kissed a guy and I
I liked it. I'm a gay monster. Yeah, he's the guy and I don't know if I'm gay.
Yeah, and he dresses up like Elton John outside my window. I haven't heard a
teller the creator. So I know he fell. He fell off when he stopped. Yeah, I
fell off of my bed the other night. Really? Yeah, I had a nightmare for real
for real for real. Well, the nightmare wasn't real. It was a night. This is
new music. Good. I don't know. I don't think so. I don't listen. I listen to I
I listen to the one what was it the I listen to wolf in high school when the
like the one that he's like hyping up for years and then I heard that and I
was like damn this. Yeah, I was not as good as the other stuff. I yeah, I
listen to like Igor when it came out and I was like like cherry bomb was
already bad. I think to that one was not great, which one is one he started
hanging out with
ASAP rocky all the time and they like started like they're like driving a lot
cars together. Oh, and then you know they're going to make like a sap Wang or
something. I don't even remember. Yeah, he wants some Wang ASAP. These yes, dude
bastards. That was my shit bastard dude bastard song VCR was tight that song
bastard personally. I prefer slick. This is what the devil plays before he goes
to sleep once upon a time not long ago when people wear pajamas in them.
That song is in Tony Hawk's proving ground. That's Lincoln Park jay-z
collision course. Now that's real rap. Yeah, you know what the real rap is boom
- Mhmm.
- And none of this hippity hoppity shit.
- Yeah.
- Just rap.
- Uh huh.
- Yeah.
- Just with the backpack on, talking about ASAP Rock.
- 'Cause it's not about--
- No jumper cables.
- It's not about guns or sex or any of that stuff.
It's about crawling in my skin.
- Yep.
- ASAP Rock.
- He doesn't say no jumper cables and no jumper cables.
- And I just found a frog and it was on a log.
- I saw a frog that was weird.
- I just saw a weird frog and it had a beard.
- I saw a frog that was weird and it had a beard.
and it had a beard. - And John Darnell
is gonna sing the chorus. - I hung out with it
for seven years, okay.
- I have bugs in my basement!
(laughing)
- I saw a frog that was weird, it had a beard,
and I became a beard. - And I just went home
and my dog had a bone.
- What's that song called?
The fucking Mountain Goats ASAP Rock song.
- I don't know.
- Fuck.
- That one album we did with-- - We don't need no
(mumbles)
- That album we did with Tobacco.
- All this is so many rap guys who were like,
I'm gonna be the guy with the funny voice.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Danny Brown.
- The king, the king dude, he's like the best.
- I love Billy Brown.
- The best ever.
Remember when a lady sucked his penis when he was on stage?
- Yeah.
- And remember like, what's her name, Kitty Pride?
- A thing that was like, that was actually not very cool.
And you see the video and he's like pointing at her head
like, yeah!
(laughing)
He's like, she's like, that's my friend.
And actually he hated that and it ruined his relationship.
And in the video, the girl starts sucking his dick
and he's just pointing at her head like, oh yeah, fuck yeah!
So cool, dude.
He's the man. He had the funniest tweet I think I've ever seen where it was like, "Grand Theft
Auto Ballad of Gay Tony, what am I going to do commissions for a peep?"
Awesome.
Yeah.
He's cool, dude.
I love that he's just super into persona. That's so funny.
He is?
He's obsessed with persona. He's the best.
We need to collab with more rap.
Oh, yeah, well do you guys think that we could get signed to rime sayers? I think we get fools going
Why haven't we been signed yet makes no sense bro? We're underground legends already. I just remembered
Huh, I won't say it what okay. It's a burn on Caleb. It's a burn on me. Oh
No, it's a picture of you from like high school
I used to love a track dude
I have some pretty bad
photos of me from in high school but yeah man that like yeah i know exactly what kind of kid you were
dude i was home school dude i didn't have i had you guys all had a leg up in this world yeah i
had to crawl from the bottom dude that's true i i had no standards of what was cool i was like
fucking i was listening to pete holmes bro yeah yeah my favorite rapper pete holmes bro he was
he's fire yeah dude have you heard t.j miller's rap album yeah he made a whole fucking rap oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
them. I was just with the shit. I was just re watching that clip for you
remember in Cloverfield when they're there in the I saw I saw a dinosaur
outside when they're in the hospital area and now the girls like I don't
feel good and they take her behind a curtain. She explodes that scene. I was
re watching this because I remember that scene that's getting scared me so
bad when I first saw it and I just re watched it this morning because I was
like oh that was cool and it's so funny that it's like she's was like like
like blood is squirting out of her. It's just teaching me to be like oh my
God, oh my God, what's going on?
it's
so fucking funny dude. The fact that like they hired the most annoying guy in the
world to be the one who talks over the entire movie. Well, that's that's the
guy who would have the can yeah, no it works. I hate him yeah, that's the guy
who would have the camcorder yeah, yeah, because he's just he's so it's so funny
on knowing he isn't that because the for the whole beginning of that movie is him
was going to people be like say something to the camera and they're like
will you shut the fuck up like we only we leave me alone. It's perfect, it's so
good people don't walk around with cameras like they used to I'll say that
honestly world everyone's got a damn phone that's right iPhones the new
cameras the world the world is pretty much streamed online every day there's no
such thing as privacy anymore and we live in a digital hell world where
basically you can download pictures of Carmen Electra's pussy and boobs at your
fingertip I'd like to have both of my love yeah I know my finger to those are
her pussy are just perfectly small enough that they fit. Really? Yeah they do.
You would like to have 1990s Carmen Electra have sex with you? No I want to
have 2090s Carmen Electra have sex with me.
Yeah. Bones? Old-ass bones. Yeah. Just fucking dry bones. No meat on them, been picked clean by a vulture.
She died on Route 66. A turkey vulture picked her entire bones clean
and I'm there and listen it's Mad Max style. I gotta get it where I can. It's
either me fucking dusting lizards or this pile of bones. I'm choosing the bones my
friend. One eyeball in there. I would choose a lizard. Nah. You would rather fuck a lizard than bones?
Tribute to the movie Grind. I don't know what that means. Yeah I don't either. There's a
scene in Grind where a lizard goes into his pants. I would put a lizard on my dick
like when you'd make a lizard earring. Yeah. Yeah. He gets the lizard in
his pants he goes like "I just got violated by lizards dude!"
Pretty good scene.
Look up grind lizard.
Okay yeah I'm doing it right now.
Just kidding I'm re-upping my subscription to keeps instead.
You take keeps?
No dude that would be crazy.
That would be so funny.
I've been taking keeps for four years.
Yeah.
No.
Dude my mom got me that for Christmas one year.
That's disrespectful.
My mom got me hymns.
She got me minoxidil.
still she didn't get me the finasteride she I did have like hair gummies though
like hair don't he's made a finasteride gummies I'm just gonna let it's funny a
grown man eating gummies to prevent hair loss yeah you have you have hair loss
because you've had to know he was in your life and they're like well we got to
feed him gummies he was eight when he got the finasteride yeah yeah I'm just
let myself go bald I'm gonna have my mad scientist hair I don't care I had
scientists here is fucking if you shave your head I'm growing mine out yeah yeah
that'd be so funny I think I honestly think it might look pretty cool yeah I
do a Walton Goggins thing you could do a wall dude it's so tight that's what I'm
saying you got crazy teeth though you like established yourself as a bald guy
now I know dude it kind of stinks yeah like if I go back I'm like fuck I'm like
losing myself yeah I love being a bald guy you know it's so fun it's so nice
- Nice, bro.
- Shaving all your hair off is so therapeutic.
- It's great, dude.
I literally have a reverse Samson effect,
where if I don't shave my head for a couple days,
I feel like shit.
And then if I keep it clean, though,
oh my God.
- Dude, when I was in high school,
I shaved my head at least once a year.
Like, Bic razored.
- Like, Bic razored, wow.
- Yeah.
- Bic razored.
- Dude, you realize I do that every morning, bro?
Why don't you talk to me?
- No, my head, like, I need to have hair,
because my head is like a--
- You have those lumps on the back?
- That plus I have a perfect circle head.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, you look like a bowling ball.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You've seen me bald before.
- No, I haven't, but I'm imagining it right now.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I have a bunch of like red circles and bumps on my head.
- I have like an almond shaped head.
- I have a bunch of red circles and purple lumps.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I have spikes on my head.
- I had a fucking dream last night that I had no more hair
and then the top of my head was all zits and pus and cysts.
- Cysts too, really?
- In addition to the zits and the pus?
- Yeah.
- No way.
- God damn that's disgusting.
- I tried to look up--
- Zits and pus on hair, my dream.
- A dream, yeah, like one of those dream analyzer things
and I realized, oh yeah, I'm literally having a stress
dream about getting a zit on my head.
I know myself well enough that I would be so neurotic.
Yeah, if you have to look up what a dream means, it doesn't mean anything
exactly. Yeah, it's all either. It's either yeah, you have a dream that you
have a dream where your boss says you didn't do your work right or you a
dream where you are a dinosaur. Yeah, yeah, I don't think dreams mean
anything. Yeah, the older I get, I don't think that, but then it will be
like I will have a dream where it's like where I have a dream where it's
like I need to do something and then I wake up and like oh, I forgot to do
thing yeah like I've fought Megatron and I wake up with a puddle of nuts I'm like
what does this mean that means you have to fight Megatron that means I have to
fight Megatron and when I do it's gonna be so awesome that I get hands-free nut
oh my god I forgot to fuck the the I forgot to fuck the grandma from yes man
oh no I bet she I bet she go crazy though she goes crazy in the movie dude
and she takes her dentures out and starts
*galloping*
she starts galloping
she turns into a horse
she starts galloping and then she puts ketchup on a hot dog
and she farts
and that hot dog does not agree with her stomach
*galloping*
*farting*
*laughing*
and that's sucking dick
and then she sucks Jim Carrey's dick
there's a deleted scene where
she's dressed up like a horse
Yes, man, it is not a good movie movie change. That was my first date really.
I've definitely said this before recently. My dad was like we have to
watch yes, man. I never see it before I watch it like why did you say we have to
watch this? I watch a change my life. I did yes man for seven days yeah
afterwards and it made my life suck. Yeah, yeah, I went on it. I went on my
first ever date my first girlfriend in sixth grade and when I was in sixth
grade don't make that joke and then I ate all of the popcorn before the movie
that she bought. She bought the popcorn and then I looked at her and I said, oh
I'm sorry I didn't think you wanted that to the thing about you. I was nervous.
The thing about yes man is that it doesn't be doing yes man doesn't actually
help you because you need to already have a life where people are like asking
like do you want this gold bar? Do you want to go on vacation and in real
life? A yes man is just like will you do this? Can you do this and you say
yeah, there's no you have to already be asked, especially if you like rear in
somebody and they're like hey buddy suck my dick. Oh fuck. Oh yes, well
they're not asking you have to say will you suck my will you suck my dick? Oh
shit yeah, I guess I will he saves louise guzman or yeah when they say
what do you suck my dick buddy? Can you ask just ask ask it come on make it a
- Make it a question, make it a question, make it a question.
- Oh, I guess I'm a yes man,
I gotta suck this guy's cock on the highway.
- Oh, great, I gotta get out of my car,
go to this truck stop, and I gotta just,
I gotta just wait for people to ask me some questions.
- Yep, but hey, I'm a yes man, I gotta do it.
- That's what they're called.
- They are.
- On the lot, yes man.
- Yeah, lot yes man.
- Lot yes man.
Remember that video where it was like,
what I eat in a day as a disabled glory hole worker?
You guys watched that one?
making the rounds. Chili. Is it a video you made? No. Chili. How did you make the video?
Breakfast chili, lunch chili, dinner chili. Beans and chili. Black bean chili. What does
it mean, what do they mean glory hole worker? You don't pay somebody. I don't know. I think
they drilled a hole in their house or something. My ear just started ringing, do you think
I'm gonna die? Yeah probably easily. Your ear is ringing because someone's talking about
you. Really? Yeah that's what that means. Cause he just, we're talking about the disabled glory
whole world talking about chili. That's probably what it is. I'm so hungry. My
ears started thinking about chili. Yeah, no, but like how do you I don't I don't
understand you turn glory hole sucking and fucking into. We just put a slot
under it for money. Yeah, it's simple quarter card, a card, like a dollar in
the hole. It's like one of the four quarter things for a pool table, right
where you suck you do that and then and then you pull out the lips show up.
Yeah, yeah, that's perfect. And it makes the same as like a pool table. Yeah,
- That goes gung, gung, gung, gung, bang.
- You guys remember that movie Be Cool?
- No. - Yeah.
- Or Get Shorty? - Get Shorty and Be Cool.
- His name was Chilly Palmer.
- What?
- John Travolta's name in that movie is Chilly Palmer.
- That one girl's name is Kiki Palmer.
- I would love to have some chili in my palms right now.
- I think Chilly Palmer is Kiki Palmer's dad.
- The Kiki, the...
- It is the same, like two--
- Make sure for Capsaicin, Capsaicin.
- Capsa, Pesacin.
- Capsaicin, Capsaicin.
I forgot how to say my cousin one time distilled pure capsaicin extract and put
it in my chili really and I like could I like ruin my life I think yeah like
since then I've not had a normal shit really yeah my cousin Nick I've not been
having good shits lately I just want to let you guys know my farts in this
office have not been good yeah my farts here have literally smelled like I'm my
my stomach is decaying. I love that, dude. I love smelly, stinky shits and farting.
I hate it. I hate everything about poop. I hate pooping. I especially hate wiping.
He likes it. This door to this bathroom being back here is like, every time it
opens, it's like unsealing a sarcophagus. It smells disgusting in there. It smells
like a mummy in here. It's literally every, all of our poops mixed together.
it's not only the smell to the density of the air and there is different yeah
because also when somebody it'll be like someone takes a really smelly shit and
then then lights three candles and closes the door and you walk in and it's
like ten degrees warmer in there and it's like it's like a poop fog. All the
oxygen is burned yeah yeah it's amazing can't breathe when you're going perfect
yeah. I love it. What we need also is a bathtub in there. Oh my God to put a
bad chemical shower in here for the experiments. I'm about to do on Cameron.
You will not experiment on me. I am an experimenter. You could not even create a hypothesis about
me.
You're not going to experiment on me.
Oh, I couldn't create a hypothesis.
No, you're not going to give me a soda.
All right.
You're not going to give me a sparkling water that tastes like CBD.
You know what? We have to do a list. It's a normal episode. Let's do a list of all your
best inventions.
This is not a normal. There's not enough time for this to be a normal episode.
Yeah, we have 15 minutes.
I can't reveal my best inventions because they're not patented. People will steal them. So I'll
do some mediocre ones.
Okay.
patented invention. Cure to hunger, cure to bad smell. Cure to bad smell is your
third one. Yeah, well that's just one of my mediocre ones. I got a patented
invention. Okay. A what? Being a little rat that does a chef. What? Yep. I don't
get it. You'll have to say it all over again. Being friends with the king of
queens. You have to start over. You have to say the thing again, because I don't
know you have a what invention Pat on did oh okay. I got it now Pat. Oh yeah, so
you went by that way too fast Pat on tin yeah, you can you also said Pat on tin
to bear. I have a
on tin there. I have a I'd like to end Pat.
What like a in you
yeah, don't hide I'm just kidding around man. Don't be don't be here.
ears are the only thing that are still out oh no you can't hear me I can hear
you just said now you can't hear me what do I say now you said what I say now
okay what did I say before that not this if this is one of your inventions you
get a down plus for me I'll say that I invented this building is my invention
puffer jacket no you didn't know you're about to go crazy for this you know that
nobody it'll never catch on okay it'll never catch on especially in New York go
home and get get those disgusting butterscotch boots out of here what are
these sir butterscotch boots oh what are these I call them my timber man's that'll
never catch on that name will never work just in timberland drop the timber man
yeah it's just timber drop the land and turn it to her drop the man turn it to a
land you know what we need a Justin Timberlake to tell us to drop something
or some more yeah drop the podcast drop that just about us and the list about
about a good name a baby I think we should change the name when we do a when
we do a when we do a when we finally have our like kind of smod cast style
network right wash no smosh cast no they can't make this much you can change the
name of this show to Smosh. We could change this to Smosh. Smosh is gone.
Smosh is owned by cheeseburger network. Smosh is stronger than ever.
Smosh is owned by Rhett and Link. Really? Okay. Well you knew that so you were
gonna wait us into copywritten territory. No but it's not Smosh anymore as I'm
saying. So we could become... Wait what is it? It's still Smosh. No they're just... the one guy's
gone, the like Panic at the Disco guy. It's not old Smosh. The coconut head just hangs out at the
rent link offices I got an inside man yeah yeah I'm thinking that we could
just change the show name to smosh cast why not just smosh those I'm saying you
have to have cast or people won't know it's a really Johnson ray will know
people won't know it's three you have to put equals three we could change the
show to equals what about equals three podcast that equals three podcast what
about just what's happening for him it doesn't work if you don't listen I know
know all this type of stuff. If you don't have podcast in the name and what it's
about in the name, people won't know that it's a podcast. They won't know what it's
about. They won't listen to it. You should call it the equals three podcast about
viral videos. That's pretty good actually. You do have a knack for naming things.
Yeah. But as you can't say like like to show that you're qualified to speak on
something, you can't say I know everything about this. I do. I know
everything. I need some like what's your real qualification? PhD. I know
everything about this PhD I know everything about what about naming
podcasts poop hormone disorder what from where from naming podcasts I named
pretty much every popular from what from what the store store from what store
school it doesn't come from a store you can't get knowledge like that in a
store what's cool experience what school the school of hard knocks what school
deep when people get their master's degree in prison where the fuck do they
say they went to school? DeVry. I went to prison. I got a PhD prison whore prison
prison education. But like if they if they give like a speech, they go like this next
guy, you're next, you know what would be good. He graduated with honors from prison.
New Disney Channel show. Prison high. Oh shit. You can get high in prison.
you got to smell a guy's butt or something yeah huffing jenkin
jenkins p and p mix together in a bag fermented into a balloon
and then you inhale the balloon how how addicted to drugs you have to be
to do jenkin i don't think i don't have to be addicted to drugs
yeah you don't have to be addicted to drugs or poop you just need to be
15 and from like new hampshire oklahoma and named patrick doran no yeah you do
that i feel like i feel like there's a lot of i feel like there are a lot of
options before Jankum though. I feel like if you're 15 years old and you do Jankum,
there's still something wrong with you. I'm sorry. There's a lot of stupid things you should
be trying to get high off of. Hit the Benadryl. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Hit the nutmeg. Do some
robot tripping or something. Yeah. You don't go straight to poop. You should wait until you're
like 60 to do the poopiest drug. There's a last resort. There's this kid. The drugs kid.
You know when people are like, "Oh, when I turn 80, I'm gonna start doing poop all the time. I'm gonna start sniffing poop and piss all the time. Who cares? I'm 80 years old."
The drug kid at your school? You know the kid that like, he hangs out with, like you hang out, you let him hang out because he will buy you, or let you buy, like, he has the like connections, but he always has the worst shit.
and he's always telling you about like the like,
like, oh yeah, like there's this drug called this
and it makes you do this.
There's this kid--
- Whoa, this drug called this and it makes you do this?
- There's this kid, his name was Brent.
- It's a recursive drug.
When you take this, you do this.
- There's this kid named Brent,
he sat at my lunch table and would like,
I think he sold weed to like two of my friends
and he ripped them off so bad
that like they stopped hanging out with him.
But he told one of my friends
that if you hold your fingers near your butt
or something like that and hold it there for long enough
and you sniff it, it can get you so high it'll kill you.
(laughing)
And I remember-- - Near your butt?
- You hold it like, you hold your fingers on your taint
and the smell can get you so high it'll kill you.
And I remember one of my friends telling me like--
- He died.
- Like Brent told me like this, and I was like,
Yeah, Brent's a fucking liar.
He died from sniffing his taint finger.
You could die from that.
Maybe that's what stink finger is about.
It'd be cool.
Stink fist. Stink finger is Limp Bizkit.
There's a Limp Bizkit song called Stink Finger.
Maybe that's what it's about.
Stinky finger!
Chocolate starfish, bitch!
To do the...
I know you be smelling my tits!
The...
that like when I turn eighty, I'm going to do like a million drugs and you turn
eighty and you do like you do you drop acid and you immediately go to jail and
you're executed. Yeah,
they put you in jail. You just let you just have to be in jail for twenty
years.
I'm eighty. I'm going to put myself in a padded cell and eat only vegetables. I'm
going to be so scared of dying. There's no way I'm going to be doing heroin. I'm
going to do heroin when I'm like eighty. If I make it to eighty no, I'm doing
heroin one time for the one now. No, you're going to turn into my grandpa. You
not like it. Me? Yeah. Why me? You said that you're gonna like put yourself in a
padded cell. When I turn to 80 I'm gonna listen to only hip-hop. Yeah. I'm gonna
become the rapping granny. Yeah. Basically. That's my job. I'm gonna become a hype
beast grandpa. I'm gonna be wearing like. I do kind of. Dude. A shirt that says
Supreme logo that says poop on it. Isn't it crazy we're like two years away from like
not knowing what is like like good cool music or movies anymore. I feel like I
already yeah I'm already it's already creeping up I'm doing everything I can
dude if you're like 40 and still dressing like a like a 17 year old it's gonna be
bad 17 year old no but when you're 40 you will yeah yeah I don't dress like a
17 year old I'm not gonna say no you're not gonna get me to take that back I
just like Adam Sandler when I'm 40 you will not like my plan I'm gonna get
basketball shorts will finally make sense to me and I'm gonna make sense to
I don't like wearing sweatpants. No what those are two different pants sweatpants are
Basketball shorts are a type of sweatpants
No, what you're that's insane. What the fuck are you talking about?
That's a crazy those are elastic elastic made entirely out of a dude like a different type of cotton
They're not what you they're made out of like like jersey material. Yeah, they're not cotton at all. Oh, no, wait
No, that's polyester mesh. Never mind
Their type of sweat pants. They're polyester mesh actually my bad. You think I'm a sweat short my calculations were off
Yes, okay, sweat shorts are still not sweat pants, but they are the same material. Yeah, that's it
Those are shorts got like jean shorts and jeans are the same down here
You gotta have the line going down here if you got my god
I don't I gotta get I don't have a pair of basketball shorts right now. I don't like basketball shorts
I don't like sweat pants. I love dude all I wear all I wear now is if the second I get home
I change it to my my Bruins pajama
Pants all day literally
I'm coming here in seconds, ten seconds before I leave the house. I change into
real pants ten seconds after I get home all day pajama pants and my crocs.
Yeah, I have I wear my Chinese slippers, my my brooms, a job of pants and my
Chinese slippers. I thought my Tom and Jerry's
and then my doorbell and I come outside. I go what you just look like a crazy
old lady. That's awesome. Dude, what do you want?
You know what I did? I had a pair of joggers one time.
Ugh, dude.
Dude, joggers are-
I used to wear so many joggers.
Joggers are the fucking worst pair of pants in the world.
They suck, bro. They break all the time.
If you wear-
What are joggers? What's joggers?
Joggers are like the pants with the elastic cuffs.
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay.
Dude, those look like fucking shit.
Yeah.
I had a pair- dude, I bought them because I was like, "Oh, this is like- they're like
like ten bucks. They were jean material with like elastic like things. I wore
them for like two weeks and I was like these fucking, I turned them into shorts.
I was like.
I also have some joggers. Joggers I feel like are nice if, not for jogging, but if
it's really, if it's cold. That's nice. It keeps the heat from your balls and
wiener and, and, well yeah, it's like sweat pants.
I'm very pro wearing sweat pants out and about.
Yeah.
I like wearing them to stuff.
I hate sweat pants.
I love sweat pants.
Yeah, when I was in high school, I literally would wear pajamas to school
every day. I do that great sweatpants challenge fairly often. I don't know what it is. I literally
if I'm not wearing something with a belt on it or whatever. I hate the way that any clothes
that aren't pajamas, I hate the way they feel on my skin. I can't stand it. I'm the exact
opposite. When I was in Boston, I was like, they're doing stand up and I did one show
where I was like went out being like all right, I'm going to pick up some jeans
while we're out and then I didn't pick up any jeans. I was wearing sweat pants
all day. I was like okay, whatever I'll just do my set and sweat pants and I
like got off stage and a comedian was like I that was funny, but you
everyone can just see your penis the
cool because just you're you're just nubbing up yeah the whole time. Do you
know you're casting a dark dark blue sweat pants, dark shadow, dark dark
shadows, awesome dude, it's so funny the rules that like don't wear shorts on
stage what if I'm in Miami mm-hmm don't wear a hat what if the hat is funny
what if the hat says old fart yep what if it has my beers on either side of it
and then I don't have to use one hit then I use both hands on the mic what if
it's a top hat yeah what if the hat has a find a magician and there's a rabbit
in there what if the hat has a propeller and my closer is flying away mm-hmm
think about it bitch when is the Elon Musk gonna make a propeller hat that
actually fucking works uh-huh yeah we've been waiting on it he's using a little
bit I'm buying Twitter right now yep and making didn't he make the shittiest
internet in the world what was star link Stuxnet no not Stuxnet Starlink Stuxnet
the star blaster he puts he has a he has an internet service called Starlink and
it's like you buy a satellite that's huge and you put it on your house and
you get the worst internet in the world that's insanely expensive yeah but it's
- Think geek?
- Think geek, yeah.
Yeah, I'm thinking of, yeah.
- Think geek.
- I'm thinking of Luke Crate.
- Yeah, that's what it is.
- Oh, I know Luke Crate.
- Yeah, you don't know Luke Crate.
- I do.
- Really?
- Luke Crate.
- Did he give you this?
- Yeah.
- Oh, interesting.
- He gave me that poster.
- Did he give you this poster that says,
"I and my ancestors, wildest dreams"?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- That was actually, that was when I'm--
- Where did you get this?
- I moved into my new place.
- That was already up there?
- This was in a tube in my closet.
really yeah she's beautiful I've seen this before yeah but not this is that I
have the tube right here actually it's funny to have a read the company that
it's from it's funny to have a what is the company let's see occupation
democracy occupation does not equal democracy that's the company I guess huh
it's funny to have a poster where the actual text of the poster is on a t-shirt
shirt yeah yeah person that you draw in the poster yeah it's pretty what is it
says it says love something says love always uh-huh
there's a lot of different stuff I think this might be worth a lot of money yeah
that's like a real print yeah I see it's signed it's signed yeah it's signed by
mmm but be Mike be Mike yeah yeah this is a big Mike mmm oh just in my closet so I
I don't know this is like finding a climbed original. Yeah. Yeah, you might be a millionaire if you can
Pry it for my cold dead hands. Yeah
Mm-hmm. I better do this. It's holding it like this
Holding the poster like that. Mm-hmm. You can pry it from my warm tight hands. It's a
Ripping my inviting dripping wet grueling hands. It's my gift to you, dude
dude. Oh my hands are so tight and wet. I'm not going to try and take them. Come on, take
something out of my hands or go ahead and try. Okay, top ten adjectives for hands. Sweat,
wet, stinky, stinky wild, wiener, you actually don't smell that. Wiener holding. Wiener holding
hands. My penis holding. Dry it from my penis holding hands. Winky, weird, crazy, pink. Yeah.
Microscopic.
Shhh.
Ubi.
Ubi, remember him?
Ubi and Grampoo.
Ubo, is that his name?
Ubi.
Ubi, right?
Ubi and then Grampoo was closed fist.
This is Grampoo?
Grampoo was this and he'd go, "Oh."
Strong.
"Oh."
Not mine.
"Oh, I'm having a fucking heart attack."
He wouldn't say that.
"Grampoo, are you okay?
Oh shit, I'm fucking dying."
Grampoo, you don't have a heart, you're a hand.
"Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, I'm dying.
Oh Jesus fucking grace!
You're having a hand attack.
Grandpa have hand attack!
Grandpa not gonna survive?
Grandpa not gonna make it?
Number ten is cheesy.
Cheesy ass hands?
Cheesy ass hands, but you have to have those poops.
Alright, go to swagpoop.com/shows
to buy tickets to the tour.
I hope no one's mad at us for never doing a list.
Check out the inflatrion.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're gonna wanna inflate you're gonna help us out of this scam Demick. Mm-hmm. All right, that's Spotify. Oh, bitch. Bye. Bye