Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
[Laughter]
[Music]
You're a crap monster.
[Laughter]
[Explosion]
Hot story tonight.
The amount of turds and farts in London has gone down.
That's good.
We used to have over one million farts and a billion turds.
Oh, this is good news. Wow.
It's bad news.
We used to love turds.
I'm Nicholas Cannon with BBC One.
one we used to have 1 billion forts and 1 million turds Londoners take to the
streets to complain. Forts used to be up in the billions and the turds used to be
in the millions. There's far less forts than there used to be. Well you see Boris
got in the office and he can't go to can't even go down his shop buy a bird's
turd you can't even do that. You used to be able to go buy a woman's shit in a
store. Yeah, no you can't even smell a woman's fart on the street. You're not even allowed
to go under a woman's pants and smell a fart anymore. And you can't even follow them into
the bathroom. Nowadays with all this Me Too, you can't even smell a fart. And I'm in the
Beatles. And I'm Ringo. And I'm Ringo Starr. And I'm Paul. And I'm John. You can't even
write an album about a woman's fart anymore. You can't even make a beautiful album about
a woman's fault anymore. It's bloody mental isn't it? You can't even, we get in a studio we get
we got the bass lines coming in his song song is "I wanna eat your tits" and then
they shut off the recorders they say get out. They won't let me play the bass
they won't even let me play the bass. They say it sounds too much like a fart. I have a fart pedal.
I have a fart pedal that makes my bass sound like a fart. I tune my bass down real low.
lonely fought Clubband. Sergeant Poopers. Sergeant Poopers smelly fought Clubband.
Sergeant Poopers. Sergeant Poopers smelly fought Clubband. Club hand covered in poo.
Club hand covered in poo. Those Beatles actually they were addicted to shit and
boo-boo. Yeah. Yeah. Where was Buddy Mental we would go down to the
We used to make songs about TT and Far Far. Can't do that anymore.
TT and Far Far.
I used to go make BBs and Boo Boos.
And make a- and write a song about it.
Ringo went boom boom.
Ringo went boom boom in his underwear. In his unders.
His trousers.
In his trousers.
His trousers were running.
We were in Madison Square Garden.
We were playing Shea Stadium. He shat- he shat his pants.
He was supposed to play the drum like boom boom.
He made a booty.
They replaced his uh- they replaced his old stool.
They replaced his stool with a toilet and he went out there on a field
He went out there on a field and he played the drums on the toilet and people thought
This is mental. People thought it was mental
And when Joey got shot
Maxwell's brown hammer
Fuck you Maxwell
Far too Maxwell. Maxwell's poop. Maxwell smells good. He like poop
Yeah if you play the Beatles
You play the Beatles backwards they say, "I like to smell poop. Poop is a good smell to me."
That's not the forwards too.
The thing is, the forwards it says, "Poop smell good, aye."
Poop smell good, aye.
Yeah, it's backwards, it says, "I good smell poop."
We didn't even do drugs. We would just sit around, we'd give each other pink eye.
It was called janken.
We'd get high on getting each other pink eye.
It was called janken that we used to...
We'd use red eyes all the time. That's why people thought we were smoking marijuana.
You put it in a balloon and you inhale it.
And that's what I did.
You put janken in a balloon?
You put in a balloon and then the fumes go into the balloon and it circulates.
We flew using a balloon.
[Laughter]
We used to have wings.
We used to go on tours.
We used to fly.
I used to have another eye.
[Laughter]
We used to hang out with this bloke.
I used to have wheels.
Flying purple people leader.
I used to be a robot, innit?
One-eyed, one-armed, flying purple people leader.
You don't even get me started on him.
He had one eye, one horn.
He was eating people.
He was eating people, he was.
What colour was he?
He was purple.
Purple.
I was purple eating people.
I used to be one inch tall.
Before I was born.
I was one inch and then
after a couple of weeks I was one foot
tall. I was born a dog.
They raised me. I was a dog
raised by humans.
And I used to sniff farts.
And I used to sniff farts and they
started getting rid of farts in London.
We used to have a billion
farts. We used to have a billion farts
and one million. We used to have a billion
forts now there's barely one you can't even go to the shops anymore you can't
even go to the shops anymore and boy a fart these masks they have us wearing
I can't even smell them I can't even smell a fart that is true you can't like if you're if
you're a guy who jacks off to the smell of stinky women on the street you got
like you're a stinky wimpy winkies you got seriously like you're here you're
- Your schnoz got dirty.
- If you're a stinky winker winking at stinkies.
- If you make your--
- If you're plinking your winker to stinkies on the street.
- If you make your dipsy go la la to stinky winkies.
- Absolutely, yeah, until you make po.
- Did you guys ever figure out where this lyric was from
that I remembered?
The lyric I sent you guys.
- No.
- The rap lyric.
- Oh, I thought you wrote that.
- No, I'm trying to remember where it's from.
If anybody--
- I thought you made that up.
Can you just say the line?
If anyone knows where it's from, let me know. Hold on. It's like in my brain it's like a
British voice. It's like, "I just had a chat with a rat and a cat and then I became black
with a backwoods hat." Does anyone know where that's from?
I think that's skeptic. "I just had a chat with a rat and a cat and
then I became black with a backwoods hat." That's got to be from a real song.
I think that's a real drill song.
I just had a chat with a rat and a cat and then I became black with the back of a tat.
Well maybe we can figure it out what are the ad libs in between it because that what's
the what's like the hype man saying.
I think he says black four times.
Yeah.
I just had a chat black.
With a rat and a cat black and then I became black.
Oh it's from cat rat chat.
Oh shit.
That's a Tim Westwood freestyle I just remembered.
What does he mean by I became black?
Like the British one?
I don't know.
Rehab by Amy Winehouse she says yes I've been black.
What? Does she?
Well I don't think so because the next line is with a backwards hat.
In Rehab by Amy Winehouse?
I became black with a backwards hat.
Yeah.
Yeah, whatever happened to her?
She hasn't been making music lately. She died on my birthday.
best gift ever I like the Justin Bieber my generation sucks I think yeah great
voice I don't give a fuck dude you know who's under a great voice is what they
say about people who don't know how to write a damn song to save their lives
we've you heard her cover of Valerie a cover yeah she doesn't know how to write
a song but you're actually her so she only can write songs about drugs and and
gangs and and sex what yeah yeah that's what rehabs about yeah I thought she was
going to like occupational therapy no that she was doing I thought she was
learning relearning how to walk after a broken leg you think she had a spinal
cord injury try to make me go to rehab for my broken toe she got she got a
a statue, there was an assassination attempt. Yes, it went black as I...
the toe turned black.
She had to relearn to walk. I had to go to rehab because my toe turned black.
That's what happens if you get frostbite. Remember that fucking Mr. Deeds?
I thought frostbite turns your shit into icicles. Mr. Deeds, John Turturro.
What? No, it turns your shit into icicles and it pops off.
John Turturro is like a... Oh no, no, no. It dies, you get gangrene and it turns black.
don't it's a with the thing the other mixing things up frostbite it turns
mister james is a good idea i don't stop stop in it
kiki if you hit a wall with it
and then the it explodes in a million are you thinking of of of liquid nitrogen
no yeah i don't think it was a senate that that's not about
what what cameron wants to talk about
oh yeah okay king cameron what do you want to talk about all i would say you
guys were both talking at the same time
and i picked you you talk about frostbite over you just saying the names
of movies and stuff. So you can like do whatever you want.
He wants to talk about something. He has a thing he had to say today.
No I didn't. Oh yeah you did.
What did I need to say today? Alright, I guess he doesn't even want to
reveal the surprise. What's the surprise?
Oh my god, are you fucking blowing this? You are blowing this so bad.
What do I do? He's fucking blowing it.
You're fucking it up man. What?
completely blowing it right now. What am I blowing? Oh my god. I can't tell if he's joking.
This remind me off Mike. Do that again. What is it? The thing. Oh the thing. Yeah. Yeah
so um we are having we did a thing. And keep going. Come on. And is it big or small? It's
it's a little big. Yeah and
and say that say what the best part, the best part is
the size of it,
which is huge
and who's going to be there every some people, but almost everyone, maybe,
maybe maybe almost everywhere is a number 100 yep that's huge yeah that is that
could be for us and what where is it
streaming streaming is big right streaming streaming is really big on
every where streaming everywhere streaming and when is it and when is it
coming out tomorrow tomorrow so be looking out for that guys it's gonna be
really awesome. He redeemed himself. I thought he was he was blowing it and then he
redeemed himself. He really nailed it. He stuck the landing this guy. Yeah.
So if anyone... that was a little example. If anybody wants to pay us money...
Me and Caleb are offering coaching services on saying things.
I just get really shy when I'm announcing things. See we're doing a king speech right now.
That's why we started the episode British. I never saw that movie. It looked kind of stupid.
Also, I don't want to muddy my image of the king.
True.
It's like the king is a strong man.
Whoa.
You're the cardboard king.
See, and that was the actual thing I wanted to talk about.
You're in a cardboard castle like Watsky right now.
We finally all went to the Hollywood Burger King.
Yep.
It's a big day for us.
I had a sandwich that tried to kill me.
Yep, he ate a chicken.
I had a wapow.
Wapow, impossible.
Impossible wapow.
No, I had a normal, I had a possible Whopper.
Oh, was it?
I was a possible Whopper.
Oh, because they cross out when you get a normal Whopper, they cross out the M on the wrapper.
Yep, possible Whopper.
I genuinely thought you got an impossible Whopper because of the wrapper.
I don't want to eat the impossible meat. It's too, I think it will give me cancer.
And I've eaten so much of it.
I have hepatitis, so I can't eat cancer on top of that.
Oh yeah, Caleb got, when we were at the Hollywood Burger King,
Caleb found out he has hepatitis A.
I have hepatitis A, which I think got from-
So what does that one do?
I think it instantly kills...
Yeah, it instantly kills you.
Oh my god, Caleb!
Did you get that blood work done like months ago?
No!
He's faking it for attention.
He's dead!
Caleb died.
These are my death rattles.
He's dead!
I'm not faking it.
He's not dead, it's our friend!
He's holding his microphone.
This is a muscle spasm, a twitch, my dying shaking.
Now he's stealing jokes from Futurama.
Oh damn.
Oh damn. We got him. Wait, give me, give you all my money. What does he say?
I'm Fry. I'm Fry from the future. From the past. From the past. I live in the
future and it's crazy here. And it's crazy. And my. Let me list my friends. And I will. A crazy ass robot. A lady with one eye. The oldest man I ever met. Yeah, I think you could say my life is not on the average.
which that you know by the shiny metal is okay, so i would buy the shiny metal
is orange. I really want to buy the shiny metal s is instant so okay, yeah,
and i have a kind of a weird life. I know all these people like my sweet
dog. Yeah, i made a dog episode that everyone cried at. Yes, i know a
doctor episode was crazy.
I know a doctor had an episode.
I know the reddest squid man.
I know a guy who's from a different and he's he's mean and yeah my ship is green
it flies three Dean yes sir yep yep the fry wrap shut up my ship is green if
right if rise three Dean my friend is bender my friend is my friend er friend
I'm not his bender. He is my friend.
Till the ender.
Yep.
Shut up and take my cipher.
My slave is...
Damn.
No. No. Leela's not his slave, right?
No. No.
My girlfriend's a sliva. Leela, she is my sliva.
Yeah. Her one eye is creepa.
Creepy.
Her one eye creep me.
Creep me.
And then it peep me.
I wish she would sleep me.
Her one eye peep me.
Yep. Yep. Yep. My red friend Zoidberg.
guy's Jamaican I think he's faking I don't think they hired a Jamaican guy to
do that voice I think it's I think the character is fake I think it's animated
hired Bob Marley to play him dr. Farnsworth he's in a harm's world I
I don't think Bob Marley played him.
You know that, hey babe, you know that's Bob Marley. That's his final role.
That doctor is actually Bob Marley. They wrote the whole show. They had all these
these clips of Bob Marley.
Yeah, it was actually like-
They're supposed to come out in the 70s.
They cut it together from his songs.
That's why his dialogue never makes sense.
Yeah.
Hey, how am I looking today?
Bof.
Bof, yeah.
What happened to the ship?
Sold.
When we go high, they go low.
Oh you look really frustrated right now.
Hey, do you want some of my food?
Share.
What's it called when you go to war?
Souljab.
You're just asking a question.
What's your favorite star wars movie so no
where are we America?
You feel you feel okay today? What are you? What are you feeling dread?
(laughter)
What kind of attack are you having?
Heart.
(laughter)
How... how...
How happy are you right now?
So... really?
Ja?
(laughter)
uh...
book to uh...
using a system
the
no
what's that does the
no buff
jostle
the
there
the repair it's a pretty good way to go
dot e_b_ on
it's just putting together so yeah it just makes no sense
man so far gobble be so so yeah we went for dinner
that's pretty good to me yeah yeah it's really Bob Marley on Futurama it
actually is him and we just really in math huh we proved it by by dismantling
this this crap then we just dismantled this crap we dismantled the crap that is
future on as you know dr. Zoidberg was also about Marley yeah yeah it sounds
just like yeah they just speed that up that's what it is that's why it does
that sound it's just I think every character on Futurama is I think that's true yeah
voiced by Bob Marley main comedian chips and dip they're really good I forgot
about that guy yeah he had a bit about chips and dip that I heard when I was
like in fourth grade and I was like you know it's crazy that that's his name but
he's actually a good comedian too I didn't realize that there was such there's
this multi hyphenate Bob Marley yeah he had I didn't know that he could do both
he has to go by Bob Marley comedian both reggae and comedy that would be funny if
he went cuz he doesn't talk I don't think he has like a bit about it I don't
think he talks I don't think he talks I think he goes out there is like wait
there's no way he doesn't talk about the fact that his name is Bob Marley I he's
probably does it like a very early I don't think I think it's the type of
thing where he does it and your next guy's really funny you've seen him on
Conan O'Brien I think the way they them in Jamaica the way Marley comes out yeah
like the way just there on vacation the way that he talks and stuff I feel like
that's just it's just enough of a joke already for them to say Bob Marley and
him yeah I'm just do his like main routine and that accent would you see
Put him in the heart of the art of Zion. Bob Marley. Bob, Bob Marley.
You've seen him on Futurama. He does every voice on Futurama. Put your hands together
for Bob Marley. Bob, Bob, Bob. He's just doing jokes. He's doing jokes that are just lines.
yeah yeah, I shot the buffalo.
He played the dog on on Futurama two and he's like both both both
both
like the R in the end of Soulja Boy.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, he also--
- He also did all the sound effects,
so when there's a helicopter, he goes like,
lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and the theme song.
- Pretty much every sound you've ever heard
was actually a--
- It was a Bob Marley sample.
- It's a Bob Marley sample.
He's the most sampled man in history.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep, it's true.
- Yep, it's actually true.
We at who sampled dot com.
I'm Adam ruins everything.
Futurama actually did not sample any of Bob Marley's voice.
It's a common misconception.
Futurama is completely made up of Bob Marley vocal samples.
Actually not true.
Actually only the Jamaican guy is Bob Marley.
And yes, the dog.
And some of Zoidberg's lines.
Soydberg is actually voiced by the comedian Bob Marley.
Do you guys want to start a huge disinformation campaign about something?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
That'd be cool.
I could do that.
We should do that with the Borat thing that you made up.
Oh yeah.
Where Borat never actually says "my wife".
Borat never actually says the words "my wife".
No, he doesn't say "my wife".
He says "my wife".
He doesn't go like "my wife".
Yes, he does.
He doesn't look at the camera and go "my wife".
Yeah, but that's like the way people say like no, I'm right about this. You're
completely. No, you're not. It's an insane thing to claim that he never says.
My wife says this is my wife, but he doesn't go like, okay, well, you know what
it is is people say my wife in the cadence that he says high five in and he
doesn't say it in that cadence. He doesn't go my wife in the movie. He goes
high five. He says, did you know Borat never actually says my wife in that
cadence fun fact mind-blowing newbie trivia I'm searching bore at my wife
clip I want to hear how he says it he says this is my wife he said this uh my
wife these are my wife Liberty Mutual at you got a lot of this kind of rock and
roll in the theater I saw it oh you remember when you know when Borat that's
from the movie that's from the TV show see it's hell oh oh it's from the TV show
I say never says it in the movie so fuck you dude you were fucking up bad you
remember that scene in Borat where he goes like liberty mutual they need to go
ahead and make a bore at three dude they need to let me right bring it back the
other way and do it with a boy main character mm-hmm
you know maybe some bald guy yeah yeah three guys maybe three borats maybe three
[ __ ] borats from america
we go to kazakh we go to china make up how mixed up the people are kazakhstan kazakhstan
is that what is it kazakhstan yeah no it's kazakhstan okay i don't know i know he's
talking about freaking Chaka Khan over here Chaka Khanistan I would love to go
to that country we need to go to we need to make a deal with China no that song
with a guy's like Chaka Khan no Chaka Khan let me rock it to it
you know that one? no I don't. it's so good it's such a good song. are you doing bagpipes from
Baghdad by Eminem? no does he say that in that is that sample of it? Chaka Khan
check a con check a con it goes like brown brown and it's got that Stevie Wonder
do you think we could sell a movie in China that is us doing Borat from
America in China and just walk around thinking that noodles or cheeseburgers
and leaving our shoes on when we walk inside of the store. Actually yeah they would
actually really like that. I feel like they would eat that up. We'd just do the same thing.
We would make so much money.
Yeah.
I mean, we all, we learn Mandarin and then we're the three fat cheeseburger boys.
That's the name of the movie.
The cheeseburger boys.
The burger boys and we just fucking walk around saying in Chinese.
We somehow do like a Texas accent.
Yeah.
I mean, oh, is it spaghetti?
Well, no, do it in Chinese.
Probably, me, me.
How do you say Chinese?
Here, I got Google Translate.
She now.
Wo she.
Whoa, she my oh, she man. Whoa, she me how day Byron Newley
Whoa, she made a Byron Newley. What does that mean? They Byron Newley? What does that mean? I'm your Caucasian slave
Everybody I'm your slave
America is your slave. I
I feel like that might be the number one hit single in China.
I would love to be a slave to a farmer in China.
Yeah.
I don't think you'd like that.
I don't think I wouldn't.
I would love it.
No, everyone always...
I would love to be a slave to a farmer in China.
Everyone always says like, "Oh, I want to go to be like a farmer."
Everyone of those like...
No, they see the videos of people farming in China and should be like, "I need to live like this."
But they wouldn't be able to do it.
and i would be able to do it either unless i was a slave in force to
yeah okay so i would like to be a slave in the worst of all the happiness yeah i
would find a nice year
nice peace serenity
yeah end up like palms i and you're like
you will know because i'd be a slave
yeah but they were convicted so that's not a slave what are you saying about
now i'm saying they could make no i would be like pangs i slave you okay
you could be with the other guy that i have to what you get your sleep well i
prefer to wear like food challenges but like your stomachs too small
and now they were there when i would have yet to do challenges they've been
easily one like p that way one thousand patty and this is the way it is
can we do man versus food with cameron and it's a black going around doing
out there just a few two bites it's a bit of a whole
yeah but i was just a little bit of a like this has to eat like
goulash
was a little less
you know what i do wash
so i can't hear you think it hungarian dish i think what's in it
where what is that and that's where you get some tomato based he's doing is
mapping he's saying the question back
what is the launch
well i do a lot of school are
it was his school which is the art for the rest of the nation and ground beef
you're thinking of spaghetti and they have american goulash being a spaghetti
and new schools is one night we went camping and my way you know i made
something that was just called it a star can do a lot she has like bowling ease
with pretty much a
called it American goulash we all had to eat it and I got really mad cuz I
fucking hated it you don't like a bolognese I don't like American goulash
I'm gonna put you in the American gulag yeah I'm sending you to San Quentin
prison you're get turned out I wish it turned out like a sleeping bag I wish I
wish I got turned out yeah you're gonna go and they're everyone in the entire
prison I'll fuck you but yeah yeah that's my plan they're gonna go and it's
gonna happen yeah they're gonna tie dye you yeah put rubber bands on both your
and twist you up. Basically what's gonna happen, basically the entire cast of We
Are The World music video is gonna fuck you up. As soon as I get to jail I'm fucking everybody. Nope.
You're gonna get completely destroyed. I'm letting everybody up in here. No.
As soon as I get to jail. No. As soon as I get to jail.
That's a bad rule man. I'm standing there like a pig. That's how you get them to like you.
I put an apple in my belly and I lay down on the table. Here's what you gotta do first day of jail. You gotta walk in the middle
of the cafeteria and say, "Hey guys if anyone just wants to fuck me, I'm just
just
somebody to fuck your butt. No, it means you're cool, I think. That's the thing that would
go around on Facebook? The picture? It'd be a picture of you. Yeah. Is that swag means
secretly we are gay? Yeah, it does actually mean that. Yeah. The sagging one's not true,
but that one's true. It was invented by scientists as an acronym to trick people, to trick jocks.
- Nerds invented it to pick Jock.
- Do you know sheesh?
(laughing)
- What if we come up with a word that Jock loves?
- What if we develop an acronym?
- Develop an acronym?
- Did you know that sheesh?
- It's one of the most-- - Swag, that's perfect.
- Powerful acronyms.
It's the coolest word ever,
but secretly it means that they're homosexual.
(laughing)
You probably don't even know what that means.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
I guess they have to look up the dictionary definition
for homosexual. - Yeah, 'cause I don't think
they've even seen a dictionary in their life,
let alone touched one.
(laughing)
we're professors we're scientists professor at Harvard we're three
scientists slash professors guys hanging out at their apartment is we have to
develop a theory we're gonna develop the most powerful acronym we have to take
down the cool guys my little that that did put a they were trying to why why
I would say like a fucking war on swag.
Like why did they not want swag to happen?
- Oh, do you, when people were saying SWAGIT at people?
- Dude, what? - Oh, yeah.
- What was up with that?
Why was that such a hot button issue
for like two years, bro?
- I mean, it's 'cause like,
I mean, it was the classists. - It was the election cycle.
- Oh, yeah, true.
- It was the class people versus the swag people.
- Yeah.
- People who-- - No, 'cause the people
who said SWAGIT did not have class.
- That's true.
That's true, that's classless.
That was absolutely classless.
Yeah, but you know what it was?
People with swag were getting all the girls and they weren't...
That's true.
They were cleaning them up.
The guys with class weren't treating women like gentlemen.
The guys with class were pissed off they were spending so much money on belts.
Then the swag...
And then here comes one guy with an Obey snapback.
That's what I'm saying.
And he's sweeping the floor.
Literally, he's the janitor.
janitor the janitor had swag back in the day and he's fucking all the girls it's
simple that the janitor used to fuck the girl actually they sent him to jail
because he had too much swag yeah yeah I think I sent him to jail and he became
like the jail janitor pretty much there's no girls to fuck there yeah I
said he fucked his food you just sit around fuck yeah I heard a story about
a janitor the fuck just food in jail there's this guy on the edge who makes
like just all this prison food because he's like in a halfway house and he just
has all done like just different foods made out of like Doritos and shit oh
yes like the loaf yeah like all that shit yeah and he cuts it with like his
inmate card in a prison and then and then one one video like right in the
middle I was just watching all of them one video right in the middle he teaches
you how to make like a blanket that you could fuck it's like a pillow and puts
like the guy is it he's like his old channel or I don't know his name
- Wow, 'cause there's that,
Vice did like a series with this pro skater Andy Roy.
- This guy's not a skater.
- Yeah, he teaches you how to make
the sweet and sour pork,
and it looks like the worst thing in the world.
- Yeah, it's just like ketchup and pork rinds.
- Yeah, something like that.
- And canned tuna.
- Dude, it's also, there's like this big brother interview
from like '94, he's talking about the time he went to jail,
and he's saying all this shit like,
"Oh, I'm a really good manipulator,
can get guys to to cuddle up with me like talking about his time in prison he's
just like that's cool dude yeah it's so fucked up do you guys ever plan on going
to prison yeah I do well yeah I'm gonna for all the piracy I've done you think
you're gonna get hit with a spectrum I'm not condoning what Andy Roy did I'm just
saying it was fucked up what did Andy Roy do what I guess he'd like he said
he's good at manipulating men in prison that's cool that's that is cool they're
Prisoners it doesn't matter anything you do in there doesn't count when you get out
I guess that's that's the point of being in there is that when you're out your it's it's a different your different rules
Yeah, I said they said they're his nickname in prison was like the cuddle monster
Like that's what like the interview says like it's the most wild fucking interview of all
That sounds like maybe they were scared of him. Yeah, he's the
Or like I'll fuck with the dude that's so for like being the guy in prison known as like cuddle bug
Yeah, oh man. You don't want to fuck with him. That's cuddle bug. That's the tickle monster. Yeah, that's tickles
You don't want to fuck with tickles. He'll actually tickle you but like yeah
Yeah, not to make it dark, but like is a whole actual thing is actually tickling
That's how we save this bit from being nope what no no we try to be dangerous water
What are you talking about?
Freaking out right now. It's making me uncomfortable thinking about it. What if I came over there, and I tickled you and you there's nothing
What if I held you down?
I genuinely do not like being tickled and you know that.
What if I sat on your back and tickled you?
What if I slowly...
You better not.
What if he sat on your legs and I sat on your head and your arms and we just tickled your
back?
What if we like sandwiched us?
Don't you dare, but I'm laying down for no reason.
His neck is disappearing.
I'm laying on the floor right now for no reason.
You're not on the floor.
Look at him, dude.
He's so afraid.
Do you want to stand up?
Do you want to just stand up and stand next to him?
I'm not laying down for any particular reason.
What if we just approach you?
You look cute right now.
I'm not.
You're kind of curled up like a worm or a maggot.
You look like an absolute roly poly and I just want to tickle your belly to get you
to uncurl.
You're like pill bugged up.
Why are you tensing up?
It's okay.
No, we just want to touch.
What is wrong with you?
Oh, a foot.
We're just going to touch some.
Oh, don't.
What?
Oh, so we can't touch now.
Oh, so there's no touching.
we can't touch now oh we can't no touching roll oh great yeah I don't care
we don't care this is fine this is the same here comes a tickle monster you're
spitting all over yourself you sputtering monster you're drooling
because you love cuddles. What happened to us? They say you can only get
tickled by the people that you love most in the world. What do you mean what
happen to us you're the one who got who switched up on us got ticklish all of
sudden do you guys want to tickle after the have a tickle group is anyone want
to start a tickle club you see that documentary but the doors yeah why do
you think I just did that to you that's true why the fuck do you think I just
did that I was thinking about the documentary pretending I was the star
the entire time I did that I wish I was the star I know you don't I wish that
you were splayed out like a star, a five-pointed star, and I had free reign to tickle you wherever
I wanted.
I would love to have you strapped to a wheel.
Yeah, a tickle wheel.
With a feather that I just hold in place.
A wheel of tickles?
I just hold it, I hold a feather.
The wheel of Patrick.
I hold a feather like the point on the wheel of fortune and he just goes by and it tickles
his feet and his neck and his head.
I would love that.
And if it lands on his nuts, I get to go.
To me, I think that's the worst fetish.
Tickling? Yeah. You think that's worse than pedophilia? Yeah. I would, yeah.
Okay. I think the tier list, well because- The tier list? Okay. The tier- He has a tier list.
So what's the tier- Let's get right into the list today.
Pat's fetish tier list? No, the worst- What's S tier?
Worst po- What is the most disgusting and immoral sexual- No, start S tier. No, come on. Start S
tier. I think, I don't, pedophilia is not a fetish. It's a- Oh, so that's S tier. It's a disease.
I asked what SDR was and you're bringing up pedophilia.
Okay, so he thinks it's not their fault and they shouldn't go to jail.
Oh, fuck.
He thinks that they, yeah, okay.
I think they should be rounded up and put into a van.
And you should take to hang out with them.
Okay.
Rounded up and brought to my party.
Okay, what's the worst of the worst?
Well, the worst is pedophilia.
Oh, really?
He switched up on us.
I think it's tied with tickling.
That's the craziest thing anybody's ever said on the show.
And a three-way tie is probably pedophilia, particularly poop eating.
Poop eating isn't that crazy to me.
He's been talking a lot about eating poop lately.
I've been talking about eating poop as long as you guys have known me.
That's true.
I've always talked about eating poop.
I don't want to.
You know what it is?
He's been having too many dreams about me having sex.
Not a lot, dude.
he's had he's had like three about you having said three in the past two weeks
and then I wake up and nothing happens
no you told me another dream today Ariana Grande when I do this you do he's
changing the subject I look just like he does he has don't you know sexual dreams
he calls me in the middle of the night to tell me about them yeah describes them
in detail not don't yeah he's making shit he says I just had the cuddliest dream
I just had the cuddliest most ticklish dream Cameron you're not gonna believe
it Patrick became a cuddle bug in my dream
and then the tickle monster cries so he's saying and then you go but do you
think that could actually happen with that what happened for real do you think
it would happen in real life it's and the scary part is I woke up that's right
The scariest part is I couldn't tell if it was a dream or not.
I don't have sex dreams about you.
Stop throwing the comment.
You have sex dreams about me?
Not s- I've never had sex with either of you in my dreams.
That- you- why are you winking?
I've had sex with a lake monster and never you guys.
A lake monster?
I told you about this.
The Loch Ness Monster?
No, I had sex with a monster in a lake.
Like ten- like probably ten dreams back.
Yeah, he told us about it.
I remember the lake monster.
I was waking I was like fucking like a monster and I like almost busted like a
what type of monster like a shape of water monster it was like it was
literally you said monster it was like a blue fuck you with eyes what me is a
blue no you but it was like a blue blue you know cube you know it was like a
blue cube with eyes and like a long neck like on top of it it was like a neck or
just a neck it was like a box with a neck and like a like a giraffe head so
So it was kind of like Loch Ness, but it was like just a box.
And I was just fucking it and I woke up and I was almost cumming in my pants.
I had to like hold my penis down.
Jesus.
What is that Jesus?
You had to hold it down like it's some kind of like fucking...
I was about to fucking bust all over my sheets, dude.
Like a snake that's about to bite you?
Yeah.
Yeah, like a...
I got that long and strong, dude.
Oh, you shouldn't have...
That's a nasty dream.
Caleb came into his living room this afternoon.
You came in here, you were gray sweatpants challenged up.
- And then I woke up and I went to the bathroom
and I had to pee really bad.
And then I had to shove my hard dick under the toilet seat
'cause I was sitting down,
'cause you can't pee with a boner standing up.
And then it was just-- - Yeah, you can.
- It was just touching the underside of the toilet seat
and getting like doo-doo all over my tip.
- Dude, I'm so good at it.
Like in the morning when you wake up.
- Yeah, there's a way to do it.
- We are like stone.
- Yeah, the hardest you'll ever be.
You wake up like granite.
Yeah.
And you go over to the toilet and you do that thing where you like...
You have to like stand.
Yeah.
You stand.
You're like fucking your toilet.
You're fucking your pee into the toilet.
You're making your butt a shelf and you're like trying to pee down.
Yeah, you're basically making your butt a lawnmower and you're fucking, shitting pee
into the toilet.
Yeah, I'm...
My toilet is grass and I'm the mower.
My grandma said that to me once.
said my step grandma grass and I'm the mower step grandma doesn't make sense
what does that mean you don't know mower doesn't shoot grass into the grass no my
step grandma said that did she suck up the do she said she said that uh like
if you did like your ass is grass and I'll be the mower I was like that you
like you're not my real grandma okay so she didn't say then you're lying she did
not say the toilet is grass and I'm the mower I just it's I was free associating
that's a bad free association it was a grandma of sucking up doo-doos from the
toilet into her butt I don't care I can say that she did I don't have a good
relationship with her really so you're claiming that she sucked up turdy doo-doo
DDS into her she's fine in her bum bum I don't know that she sucked the step
grandma's my mom's chopped them and sucked up part of them and then blew
them out of her mouth do I say do I say step grandma if my mom if it's my mom's
stepmom? I would say just grandma. Because it sounds like my parents are divorced
and I don't want people to get that idea. I'm gonna step on your grandma's neck.
I'm gonna wear big high heels, red bottoms. Oh my god. I'm gonna step on her.
I'm gonna do it with flip-flops. I'm gonna I'm gonna pierce. Does it smell really bad?
It's not the same as like when you guys make fun of my mom and I feel
like I have to defend her. I'm gonna use the heel of my high heels and I'm gonna
I'm gonna poke through your grandma's cheek like a fish and I'm just gonna fucking catch her.
This feels, this woman just feels mean now.
I'm gonna kill her.
I don't know why you're doing that.
I'm gonna manually-
You're trying to like get me to like react and it's not working.
I'm trying to get you to come over to me so I can tickle you.
Yeah.
I'm gonna walk through like a horse stable in flip-flops so the like manure is like all
it's like between my toes and on the bottom of the flip-flop.
You're gonna step on my step grandma?
Uh no.
I'm just gonna do that.
- Okay.
Is it step, I don't know.
- In your dad, and then I'm gonna walk on your step.
In your dad, I'm gonna install,
you know how sometimes when they're doing--
- I installed the-- - I'm gonna install a Keurig
in your dad's back.
- I installed Sirius XM in my dad's belly.
- Well you know when they do--
- And I listen to Stern on there.
- You know when they do, when they have to check
a cow's stomach and they put that hole on the side of it
so you can reach it? - Yeah, oh yeah, yeah.
- I'm gonna do that with your dad
so I can feel all the hot dogs he eats.
(laughing)
- They do what to cows?
- They put a hole on the side of them.
- You never seen that?
It's so crazy.
- So they can put like their, you know,
you know when they deal--
- Like a living cow.
- A living cow, it's like they put a thing
that you can put a plastic glove in
and like feel around and like take out
like food from their stomach.
- I'm gonna give your--
- What?
- Yeah.
- You never heard of that?
- They do that, yeah.
- Look it up, look up cow hole.
- I'm gonna give your dad a hook hand.
- Show me the, show me the cow hole.
- I'm gonna give your dad a hook hand
and then I'm gonna call--
- Shut up, shut up about my dad.
And then I'm gonna call his work and tell him that a pirate's coming to kill everyone.
[Laughs]
I wish I heard that.
Cow hole.
I'm sorry for interrupting you.
I'm looking up.
Oh look, yeah, you never seen that?
Oh my god!
They put a hole on the side of the fucking cow.
What?
Yeah.
And it just sputters and spits out.
I mean it's fine, I can't feel pain.
Yeah, it doesn't do anything.
It doesn't do anything.
Look, that lady's got her whole arm in there.
It has no effect.
It's crazy, yeah.
funny that they think they're like they're like well there's no way that
would hurt their entire life to have a huge hole yeah there's no way that does
anything you never heard of this you really haven't know what the fuck what's
it called there's a name for holes are openings on the side of the cow that
looks like a scientific name holes are openings on the side of the cow that
allows researchers to access an animal stomach with a cannula you just do that
to like any animal listen yeah they do that to every animal experts say that in
some cases cows with portholes live longer. Yeah, because they put more food in there easily.
Dude, that's... it's cool. Can you imagine how much... I'm having like a genuine... It's a cannula.
That's what it's called. I'm having a genuine like one of our like... No, the cannula is what they put in.
Every six months where we have that like fucking crypto vegan conversation. That's happening right
now. I want to do this so bad. I don't. You don't want to do that? I feel so bad for that cow. I think it'd be
cool put your hand in it oh what if you got to feel what all right but listen to
me what if you found a dollar in it okay you
know it's called it's called fistulation a fistulated cow you're about to have a
fistulated Papa I'm goes by pep-pep your people also my nephews called him your
dad yeah like he insisted on being called pep-pep that's cool yeah you better be
fistulated father. Fistulated pep-pep. Baby before you meet my parents my dad is
fistulated. He has a porthole. I mean you can do that to a person through their
butt. You're seeing those videos. You can't reach all the way through somebody's
intestines. I saw a video of a lady it's like a like you have
like fucking a hundred miles of intestine in like a stomach like a lady with a
whole head in her ass that's not the same thing at all different it's just
about the cows have assholes - if I saw one where like a like a there's a movie
where a guy alien comes out I'm gonna put I'm gonna put an x-ray machine in
front of your dad's mirror so he's a skeleton and he gets scared I need to
work on my confidence problems.
(laughing)
- Okay, let's do it.
Let's work on it right now.
You are...
- Green.
- You're green.
- You're green like a cucumber.
- Yeah, basically I'm just like the greenest guy ever.
- You're supposed to say it with pride.
- Yeah, I'm like green as--
- Say it proudly.
- You're green as the day is long.
- Basically green like money.
- There we go.
- Okay, we're getting somewhere.
good and green and here's a hint
Caleb's penis like my penis is not really like the penis Caleb sucks now okay, so
if I'm going to suck a penis yeah, it'd probably be a really microscopically
small one like an ants yeah yeah, that's you're going to go to jail for that
that's animal abuse yeah, you can't go to jail for abusing an ant. Yeah, you
can.
If you put your dick on an ant, you won't go to jail. You will go to jail.
teenage son went to juvie because he was sexually abusing the ants in his
aunt's farm.
He put honey all over his dick to get a bee to suck it.
I put pollen on my penis.
Yeah.
I got to get a bee to impregnate me.
I got impregnated by a bee.
I don't think that you can go to jail for abusing anybody.
I think you have to go to jail.
How big, where do they draw the line where it's illegal to just randomly murder?
It just depends on what the judge says in court.
Is that really true? They don't have like a lot, they don't have like a...
Yeah, that's true. You go to court if you fuck a bug.
And they have a trial to decide if you go to jail or not.
They might. If you... Okay, so I... Like a horned beetle, you should not be able to fuck that.
You probably can't.
But an ant or a worm?
You should be able to... So you think you should be able to fuck an ant?
Yeah.
What's the biggest bug? The biggest bug is like a moth. There are giant moths, right?
Those, they're really big moths.
No, you did not.
Uh-huh.
Nope.
I fucked your ant.
You did not.
I'm gonna search biggest bug. Your Aunt Judy. I don't have an Aunt Judy. Actually I think I do have an Aunt Judy.
Yeah. I think she's my great aunt. And you're... You fucked her? And I'm Uncle Patrick. She has twin children.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay well here's our new list because we... I forgot we had a list and we went really
long. Here's our new list. 10 biggest bugs on earth. All right. Okay. All right and we'll find
a line here. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Stag beetle. How big is it? Three inches long. That's...
that would never you can fuck that is the size of like the biggest penis
the stag beetle is the size of the biggest people listen to this true
the three inch long male stag beetle may be most easily recognized by its spiky
front antlers also known as mandibles which are a key part of courtship
rituals and wrestling matches you'd have more to fear from the slightly smaller
females though which don't have the giant spikes but you have a more fearsome bite
so it rather for the mailer female well the thing is that the whole matter
lately i'm i'm i'm not even one of focus beetle
but if it is all of its it's beckoning me with its horns i made
confiner it's spelled this is perfect for this this is the mailer
it's it's
fifteen million shares of this was listened to it
would you rather have sex with a man
here's a question would rather sex in the mailer being at the state deals
really good for you because it says here, "Researchers point to the long maturation time, four whole
years it takes for them to be adults." From larva to adult, that's four years.
That me up. That me up.
You guys notice how I smell good today?
You've been talking about how you smell all day.
Yeah, because I had a fart problem.
You did? It stunk up the entire apartment.
I woke up today and I thought that I farted.
We've had to spend the night at my place, Cameron.
I did sleep the night.
i heard about it. I did spend the night. Did you guys play any games or have any fun?
We did some pajama stuff.
Yeah? Yeah. What kind of pajama stuff?
We had another pajama accident. We had a pajama interaction.
Yeah, I told you guys I think I fought, I do think I fought like a demon
or something in my sleep.
Would you wake up busting?
A dream demon.
No, I just, I usually have crazy dreams and I didn't take melatonin or anything.
I had no dreams at all and I like fell asleep instantly and then woke up and I
I felt like I had been fighting all night. You covered in scratches. Yeah, I didn't
do anything yesterday, so I wouldn't have I wasn't like tired, but I think I think
I think like Mr. Krueger pulled me under. Maybe it's possible. What if you had like
a dream where you were like a knight or like like like a knight or something or
somebody that like fought the devil or like you know a Jedi and you're fighting
Darth Vader and you wake up with just like a puddle of nut in your pants. What
would that say about you wait you have a dream where both your parents die in a
car crash I know that I think about it I'm kind of worried that I woke up
feeling like I had a battle because the other night I destroyed a shelf in my
sleep in my I forgot about that you told me that I got up asleep with sleep
walked and I just walked into the wall and just knocked the shelf.
You like you walked out of your apartment saw a guy that kind of looked
like a demon.
Dude Cameron's like Moon Knight.
Dude that would be sick.
I hope I find out that I killed somebody.
You could be like a that'd be cool to be you're like a superhero.
There's been an ad playing about that because like yeah there's been an ad on
on Hulu playing that's been like have you or anyone you know
with Anna and then it will come on and be like this man stabbed his
girlfriend twenty nine times in his sleep. Beware of sleepwalkers.
It's like a true crime show yeah. Oh my God, you didn't know yeah,
I've never got an ad like that. I never do. I've never got a PSA for
sleep. It's not a PSA. It's like a show about a guy who did that.
It's like a true crime show. Never heard of that damn. What's the
That looks scary. The next bug is Goliath Beetle.
Oh my.
That sounds pretty damn big.
4.5 inches long and 3.5 ounces.
Now we're getting somewhere.
See, that's big. That would go, the biggest piece would fit in there.
Is it wrong to kill that bug for absolutely zero reason?
Yes.
Yeah.
You think so?
I think, what is the size cut off?
I think the size cut off for that, I think it also depends on if it's a fast moving bug
or a slow moving bug.
You got a fast bug.
I don't know why I agree. It's completely true. A fast bug, I don't care, can die no matter what.
A slow bug. Because I was thinking like, I wouldn't kill this for no reason, but a centipede
that's the exact same size I would immediately kill if it was running quickly. Oh absolutely.
Dude, like a centipede. Well I guess if this one was running quickly I'd probably kill it too.
I think it's probably because you can't catch it and set it free without it like.
Well it's because you have to worry about it. Also, if that centipede.
If this thing is slow and it's in the corner of my room, I can just like chill and it'll
like walk around or whatever.
And then we could just, you can put it on a piece of paper and bring it outside.
Yeah.
But if it's fast as fuck, you're never getting rid of it.
If it's fast, it's evil.
And when it jumps at you like a scare, like a jump scare.
Yeah.
If it's fast, it's evil.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, definitely.
Fast bugs are evil.
I think we're programmed to not like fast shit.
Definitely.
Yeah.
But a slow bug.
Yeah, cause like, you know, like a cheetah.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Cheetah comes running at you.
I can be liable to think a mosquito is a cheetah if it goes fast enough.
Mosquito?
The next bug, the giant walking stick.
But this one could die is the other thing.
Not all giant bugs are outfitted with terrifyingly sharp jaws and a suit of external armor.
The giant walking stick looks practically dainty.
How long is it?
Up to 21 inches when measured from toe to toe.
Show me that.
What the fuck?
It just shows it's not an interesting picture.
Yeah it is.
That's a bug.
picture of a stick just a piece of wood where's the bug you'll find them almost
worldwide that's not you so females are bigger than males it says these insects
are some of the most successful hiders in the world next to me I could find one
I'll find right now so what do you guys think about this one I think that this
one I don't I would kill what about I thought we'd started out talking about
about fucking them. Oh yeah, I'd fuck that too. Can you fuck it?
Anything that I... Can you fuck it without going to jail? Okay, so
actually that's the line. If I would kill it, I would not fuck it.
Yeah. But also if you... That's good to know. Yeah. Well, I... No,
wait. No, it's not about me fucking these. Sorry. It's all about... It's
about you. Okay. It's not about if it's legal, it's just would you go
to jail? For fucking a stick bug? No, 'cause the judge would be impressed
that you found it.
judge slams down the hammer is just like hmm well this case is dismissed can I
see the book can you give me the bug so he fucked nothing so you fucked this it
doesn't even know you fucked this table this evidence table your honor your
honor look closely with the magnifying glass damn that's a better honor please
- Can you please refer to the bug detector?
(laughing)
- Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
- Oh!
- I was gonna say, he's losing his mind!
- Over just some damn stick!
This thing is broken!
- Oh, yeah, my bad, it's not calibrated.
- Yeah, next one is Queen Alexandra Birdwing Butterfly.
This one's Queen Alexandra.
- You can't fuck a butterfly.
- You can't fuck something named Queen Alexandra.
- Yeah, no, if you fuck a butterfly, I think you go to hell.
- Yes.
- Wingspan can reach as much as one foot across.
- If you ever kill a butterfly--
What?
Show me this.
None of them have size comparisons.
I would be so scared if I saw that.
You kill a butterfly, you should be able to get killed.
Moths, there are moths that get way bigger than that.
A foot?
Yeah, well I'm sure there will be a moth on this list.
Moth man.
Moth man you can kill or fuck and it doesn't matter.
What's your...
Okay, well next bug.
Next bug here is...
Whoa.
Let me see.
That thing is fucking crazy.
A giant sex crazed moth?
Is that what it says?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Have you ever seen those, what's the kind of moth that has a really fucked up wiener
and it looks like a mutant?
Is it fucked up what?
Wiener.
Oh, you actually did say wiener.
Yeah, you said wiener perfectly fine the first time.
No I thought you said, I thought you said like, for,
Wiener?
I didn't, yeah.
I thought you said wiener and I genuinely for a second thought that that was like a part
of a bug like a thorax. I hate bugs man. Yeah.
Continue. Next one Titan beetle. The latin name of this beetle pretty much says it
all. Titanus giganteus. Imagine using the scientific name. It's eight inches long.
And it has the scientific name. This is some kind of. Titanus giganteus. This must be a
giganto hugisoid. This is the biggest thing I've ever seen. It's eight inches.
It's not called like, "Insectus Titanus Chug It" it's just, "It's the big titan."
This is the biggest titan I've ever seen!
I was thinking he sees like a bug that's like way bigger and he's just like, "Ah, shit!"
I think the murder thing, the bug murder thing, kind of like, it's morally wrong to kill anything
above a bee.
I think a bee, I think you can kill a bee.
Yeah, for sure.
A bee, like you know, who gives a fuck?
What kind of bee?
There's one thing about bees is there's so many of them.
There's too many.
Most bugs it's fine because there are a bunch of them, but if it's like a fancy bug.
Three summers ago, I had one of the worst days of my life.
My fucking mother-in-law made me pick up a tennis racket and go out and kill every bee
in their yard for like three hours.
I was just swatting bees out of the air.
You were made to do this?
She asked me to.
You can say no.
Mama told me.
That's my...
You can say no thank you.
No, I gotta respect my mother-in-law.
No please.
You can say no please.
That doesn't make any sense.
You don't understand southern hospitality.
If a mother-in-law tells you to kill, you do it.
Okay, here we go.
Damn, that sucks.
I probably killed 150 bees.
I would never.
Next one is dung beetle.
I would never listen to my damn mother-in-law.
Dung beetle?
Dung beetle.
You can kill and fuck that.
Doesn't matter.
Though the dung beetle doesn't have the size advantage of some of the other beetles and
bugs on this list, it overpowers them in one key way.
gifted with Hulk type strength. It can move more doo-doo. But why are they so
strong? Researchers explained that males need to be tough enough to fight off
rivals who would try to pull them out of the holes they go into in order to mate
with females. What does a dung beetle look like? This, a turd. Looks like a beetle.
I've seen one of those before. Yeah? Yeah, moving around your poo-poo. Yep. In my
toilet. Oh. I put it there. Next one's giant water bug. You seen those? Those are
cool as a groats yeah i hate i hate any roaches so gross man
you know if i could hate roaches bottle these are getting smaller four inches
long
but i don't want to use this ending
now it is a it's going to go to get their curve
next was the atlas moth
uh... that's one of those biggest most open many have yet freezing yet jesus
christ not my problem window what do you do why do you leave the window open here
the i'd like it cold
You're a piece of shit.
You're crazy.
Many have more than 62 square inches of wing.
That's cheating.
Give me the length.
It doesn't say the length.
Let me Google it.
Let me just Google biggest moth.
Biggest moth.
Because big moths are crazy because they have big bodies too.
Do they eat huge chunks out of shirts still?
Yeah, they eat skin.
Why do they do that?
They eat your skin.
What?
That sounds horrible.
I just made that up.
kill them with your but the flash water look at this one
well
let me see that
i hate that shit
the big like i like the pet they're like heavy to it
but i would look at this world at this one
uh... looks like a body
like that
uh... look how big is body is not that's like some photoshop now it's an
australian poodle moth show me more poodle moths
what's get that shit away also crazy i hate those men like that one of fuck i
hate bugs you're acting a bit japanese
japanese people are scared of months like we are really of spiders that's why
mothra is a thing really here
i i just hate all but you should have a lot of spiders either yeah i don't like
to be accused of his acting japanese was something wrong with that
no but it seems like i'm trying to get japanese on purpose which i'm not
get that fucking moth off your face
damn largest moth that thing's gross north america's largest moth
uh...
they're cool dude
i really like that poodle moth
you should get one
i should get a pet moth
that'd be so funny i have a pet moth
it's like yeah sorry
you're like when people show up with a
look at that caterpillar people show up with like a dog hair
dog hair on their black sweaters but like showing up with a bunch of holes in your
shirts and it's like uh sorry yeah he jumps yeah down he'll jump on you he'll eat it he'll
take a bite out of your shirt this thing's crazy hickory horns devil caterpillar i'm
blogging out of my life i don't like uh nope nope kill it with fire yeah that's how i feel
that's a serious nope and kill it with fire i just don't like i don't like any bug man okay
Okay, well the last one here on our kill or fuck bug list is the
Goliath bird eating spider.
Kill or fuck bug list?
The Goliath bird?
The Goliath bird eating spider.
Oh, let me see.
Whoa!
Those are the giant spiders.
Imagine bending them legs back.
How big are they?
Why does it stop saying the sizes on here?
Are you talking about a tarantula?
This one sucks.
Tarantula?
No, it's bigger.
That's what it's called.
It's how you say it.
Tarantula.
it's how you said it mother called a tarantula oh you got a tarantula legs
leg span 12 inches and they eat birds yeah that means they could eat a baby
no they eat birds like a premium and lizards and stuff they are they are
tarantulas i gotta stop thinking about bugs bro yeah what's wrong it was like
give me get me out of here you know like when they have it's an edible spider the
flavor has been described as shrimp like i got i gotta eat that i do like shrimps
Yeah, I love shrimp. Can I popcorn it? Yeah, it doesn't say it just says you can
prepare it by singeing off the urticating hairs and roasting it in
banana leaves. Is that how they do popcorn shrimp? No, they do popcorn
shrimp. They do pop popcorn shrimp come in a bag that you put in the microwave.
Oh true. Popcorn shrimp has bread crumbs. All right, I'll eat it. Bye. Oh, bye
tickets to the D&D show. Link is on the Twitter. I'll put it in the description of this too.
yeah March 31st in Brooklyn at Union you can also you bitch if you hit up
patches you could buy a ticket directly from him not true is that true no no
whoa bye