Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Blue ass man, little smurf motherfucker.
- I'm not a blue, everybody--
- Blue ass motherfucker.
- Now everybody missed my Joe Rogan intro
'cause I had to restart.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- He's got a blue head on his,
dude, he's a blueberry.
He's a blueberry.
- Podcasts got list all night.
- Violet Beauregard.
- All day.
- Blueberry ass little bitch.
you think i'm a blueberry oh he's a blue you think i'm a blueberry now hold on
uh...
uh... he's got blue face painter something he's going to get something
he's getting a he's getting he says he's getting he's getting in his blueberry
costumes he's getting in his blueberry costume he's got a big blueberry costume
well now that he's gone right now
we can plug the the show because he was trying to we have a show on the thirty
first i don't want to sell anything on the thirty first of march uh... dungeons and dragons live show
uh... actions gary lynn patches will more than be there he will be dungeon
mastering the show
yeah uh... and
well alex forest alex romeo there
from home planet
will be there are there
that union i'll be there at seven thirty
uh... i don't know
and you can just look at you can just look at the time of the time of the
select that we're making
scott a frog test a journey operation operation frog testic voyage and we're
We're gonna have a website soon.
- Yeah, we'll see about that.
- And there's gonna be Flash games on the website.
- We're gonna, I do wanna make a website
and put a slot machine on it.
- Yeah.
- I wanna make a slot machine so bad.
- You know what I wanna do is figure out how to embed
like the old Flash games from Addicting Games onto it.
- Oh, that's sick.
- That's a good idea.
We have one section that's called--
- Virtual Buddy.
- Games Corner, and then we just have every game
from Addicting Games on the website.
- Doesn't Flash not work anymore though?
- Oh, true.
- Didn't they get rid of Flash?
All of our fans are on XP.
That's true.
Yeah, I don't think...
They're way behind.
Yeah.
Yeah, is it browser?
Is it based on the browser you have, I guess?
There's no way they just like pressed a button and all flash turned off.
I'm sure they did do that.
I don't think they did that.
That's exactly what they did.
That doesn't make any sense.
I don't know if it's based on the browser.
I assume if you didn't update your browser, you're probably still a flash.
Why did they do that?
I don't know.
It's really stupid.
There's really no reason.
So much history.
Yeah.
possible quiz can you play the impossible quiz?
I think you can still play a lot of those
a lot of the stuff on like newgrounds is like
I think they have like their own thing that like
you can play like it's like it runs flash
and like
some virtual thing yeah yeah exactly
so we get that for our website
yeah so that's gonna blow
a big part of the budget for the stuff
we want to do this year
everything else is canceled and we're doing this
put that one in the what? remember the
etnies downhill skateboarding game?
I played bowman.
Bowman was good.
That was a bowman world champ.
Slap the monkey is gone?
Slap the monkey, that was a funny show.
I remember telling my dad I was playing slap the monkey and he said what?
What the hell are you even talking about?
Have you guys ever played with a line rider?
Yeah.
Is that one?
I'm supposed to teach you that.
Dude, line rider was tight.
Line rider was really fun.
That was sick.
Yeah.
That was a good idea.
Remember they had a promotional line rider for hot rod?
What's that?
Did you say emotional line rider?
Promotional.
Oh, okay.
I mean, I've seen an emotional line rider.
There's a proposal on line rider.
- Yeah, there's the ones where you skate the whole thing
and then it says like--
- I love you, Debbie.
- Yeah.
- Diane.
- Yeah, and then like--
- Debbie Diane.
- 1991 to 2007.
- Debbie Diane died of diabetes.
- Dabba dabba diabetes.
- Yabba dabba doo, Debbie Diane died of diabetes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Drats.
- Yeah.
- Drats, Debbie Diane died of diabetes
and they're in Dallas.
you're there in their dirt you could just say do do do do do do do do do do do do
those are the German does I think what aired dirty dots those are the German
thugs you think you know you know no dirty dust the German thugs those are
the German does Oh German those yeah German thugs I was thinking that that
fellow from Rocky dirty dice no the blonde guy Ivan Drago yeah is he German
nope okay Dolph Lundgren but he reminds me of a German thug Dolph Lundgren has
never played a German guy in his life he's German in real life that's I didn't
say the only thing was Russians yeah or or Americans yep it is I love when he
plays America it's cool that they got him a scientist I think he's an actor no
he's also he's got like he's got like some of her he's an actor in movies
actually any Arnold movie do they ever try to say that he's anything other than
an American? He's from California. The best guy that they do that with is
Jean-Claude Van Damme. Oh yeah. Where they try to make him like Cajun or like Canadian or
something to explain it. Yeah. So cool. The best is Seagal because he tries to be the other things. He's an
American trying to be the other things. No, I like it when they have an accent and
they try to like make it, they try and cast him as something else. But they also don't know how to not do their accent.
Exactly. There is a block of Europe where if you're from like Spain, France, or the UK,
you can do an American accent pretty believably if you're a good enough actor. If you are
from the eastern part of Europe, you sound mentally disabled.
Or if your job is to kick and get kicked in the face a hundred times every day.
I am from Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
No, I said French is good.
I was Israeli.
Oh yeah, well, this is...
Every time I try to do...
No, Israeli's got it down pat.
No, never mind. Yeah, that wonder...
That wondrous woman. She can't do it.
No, no. Which is like, why would Wonder Woman be from Israel?
Well, there's a clear answer for that.
What is it?
Press pause.
Intelligent damn females.
Call back.
That's right, baby.
People are gonna like that.
Yep. Everything was leading up to that joke and the show is done.
But do you think, because she's supposed to be from another planet, right?
Yeah, Israel's another planet.
No, she's supposed to be Greek in Wonder Woman. She's a Greek goddess.
Oh, no.
Well, I guess that makes sense that she has an accent then.
I'd be pissed if I was Greek.
I would be.
Are you kidding me?
It would create less confusion in my life.
First hot woman ever given to...
She's maybe like the worst actor I've ever seen in my life.
She's maybe worse than like people on the battlefield.
Maybe worse than like people who make like YouTube short films and stuff.
Like she's maybe one of the worst I've ever seen.
Did she do something? Was she like an Olympic athlete before she was in there?
No, I think she was a model.
She was in the beauty Olympics.
Oh my goodness, fucking disgusting.
I hate this idea that beautiful women can be actresses.
Yeah.
You know who's a good actress?
Who?
Like Kathy Bates, Meryl Streep, just busted asshole ladies.
Yeah, Megan Fox.
Meryl Streep is busted busted as a Megan Fox busted your rock amazing actress
ugly as yeah so so busted fuck yeah she looks like a giant red and blue truck
robot yeah what the hell yeah ugly as fuck that but that cool deep voice oh my
god yeah but Optimus Prime in that movie is hot as fuck yeah yeah she's on
another level when she's inside of the car oh my god when Optimus Prime goes
it's inside Megan Fox.
You know there would be that one pervy as transformer that turns into one of
those one of those vibrators at sections to the one of those vibrators that is a
car yeah
the transformer that's a sibian but he's like he's all the powers of a turtle
and then the like yeah
and then we give up. There will be a you know in the Michael Bay transfer
movies. They should Michael Bay you can take this idea for free. It's a
transformer that transforms into a vibrator and has a really offensive
Japanese accent. That's like such a gimme. That's so obvious. That's really
good. Tango. Watch out.
Now do his voice. Okay. Hello. I am from Japan. They did. He blew it. He
did. They did a Japanese transformer, but it was a samurai. Yeah, it
transforms into a samurai robot.
- That doesn't make sense.
- What's that supposed to be?
- Yeah. - A samurai?
- Yeah.
- Samurais weren't real.
- Samurais weren't real?
- No. - No.
- No, it's like a unicorn.
A unicorn isn't like a British thing.
- Yeah, it is.
- A samurai isn't a Japanese thing.
- Yeah, unicorns are a British thing.
- Unicorns are not a British thing.
- I saw one in Harry Potter.
I saw one in Harry Potter, it's a British thing.
They have those in the woods.
It's like stoats.
- You saw your hairless daughter.
- What? - Yep.
(laughing)
- I don't know.
just keep going okay let me just say stuff okay why is everything I said okay
say the next day game on was just say something don't what oh yeah I've seen a
stout what's a stout it's like a unicorn it's British to bring in the woods
really it's like a British weasel it's just so it's a weasel
yeah what does it look like compared to an average weasel there's a it is a
weasel there's a white stout do you guys say awesome or Oh possum possum now
are gay. Why? It's cool to say opossum. Oh yeah. Yeah it's cool. No it's nerdy as fuck
dude. That's a southern thing. Is it the, is it? Opossum. No cause I thought that it was
opossum until I looked it up. It is opossum. And then I started saying is it opossum? Yeah.
Well that's the full name yeah. That's just, I, I. But if you're cool and you like slang
like me. I don't think that's slang. It's slang. I think that's a north south side.
no it's slang like swag i had never heard someone say possum until i got
pointed up also say that's my slime you don't say that's my slime my slat i say
slat do not say schlatt when you see a i do you don't i know you don't yeah i say
that's my ride or die for real nope i say i say he just i say he just
popped the benny when i see a possum a possum like once or twice you've only
seen possum with a truck i've never seen one in person you've only seen an
possible once or twice you say yeah I've seen it pretty much a million times
that's cool yeah you never really went in person you never seen one of them
they're really scary yeah they are sharp teeth they scream they they see you go
they like hiss like a snake I and also they love trash I don't mean they love
to die it's true they love to be killed by your stepdad yeah they love when
your stepdad puts them in a bag and throws them into it oh yeah like the
river behind your house. Jesus. Yeah. What's wrong with that? Nothing, it just
happened to a friend of mine. Your friend got put in a bag? Yeah, I'm thrown into a
river by your stepdad. Whoa. Yeah. He's really strong. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah, my friend Caleb.
I didn't get killed by my stepdad. Yeah, Caleb got thrown into a river by his stepdad. We did, I remember one
time we had this like drainage ditch behind our house. It wasn't even a
drainage ditch. It was like a just like a it must have at one point been a
drainage ditch and then they like stopped it up and there was a hurricane
and so all of a sudden there's this like crazy river behind our house just filled
with mud and my mom made us play in it and me and my brother got really sick
for two weeks. That's tight. Yeah we definitely had some kind of worm go up
our wee-wees. Yeah it's like when Steve-O jumped into the swamp of poop.
I mean this was like a hurricane so it's every it's not worth to like touch that
water at the lowest point in the entire town and my mom is I mean every single
dog shit that had happened in the last six months yeah every dead animal every
just like re floating is brought a little outside and said come get your dinner
boys yeah you rang a big bell uh-huh she poured it into our and I mean we
headed out dude the stews hot mm-hmm it was cold yeah yeah one of them also
another one of mother's tricks. She's so clever. I'm sick of mother's tricks. And
there was lightning. Yeah yeah you can get electrocuted by lightning. Yeah I've
heard. Yeah makes your bones show up. Yeah is that true? Makes you jiggle around
like Jell-O. I think there should be a study where they just shock people like
Marv. I think they've done that study like a million times. Ever heard of Ben
Franklin ever heard of the Nazis mm-hmm no what are they you never heard of the
Nazis no hey try looking in a mirror pal okay okay so now you're all right okay
it's you see what that is that's a Nazi well I can see you guys too no you can
know I'm moving a little bit off to the side so yeah okay now I can't see your
eyes so you can't see me either okay I can still see Cameron well I know that's
Oh, you can still see Cameron?
Yeah, you can't see me.
I can still see Cameron.
No, I moved out of the way.
He's doing something with his arm.
He's doing something.
Was that some kind of reverse Millie Rock?
What is that?
What?
Doing a high Millie Rock?
I'm trying to put my arm around Patrick.
It's my friend.
You keep missing.
It's completely straight and at 45 degrees.
You keep missing every single time.
Well, because you keep running away from me.
You're skittish.
That is on you a little bit, Patrick.
I am skittish.
Yeah.
What? I heard that Nazis hated the skittish people. I like that I said that,
like I gasped like I had a good idea before I said that. Yeah. To me it seemed
more like you gasped, like you were scared of what came out of your
brain. Yeah. Yeah. You're terrified of the darkness you ride. That was a dark
thought. Yeah. That was seriously dark. And it wasn't, I'm not saying that Jews are
skittish I'm saying what rhymes with you wait hold on what huh let's cut let's
clip that clip that I think that's a way better joke if you're saying that Jews
are skittish if you're trying to rhyme it with Yiddish that's stupid I know
yeah no you had it right on accident maybe it was on purpose and you guys oh
my there's gonna be a coffee mug is gonna drop I'm gonna why are you making
You're making fun of me being all blue and you're all black.
I had white shoes on.
I got white socks on.
I don't know.
It's not all black.
This is a blue hat.
You're blacked up.
That's a black hat.
That's not a blue hat, yeah.
Not in this light.
That looks even more-
If you go somewhere else that might be a blue hat, but here, nope.
Maybe if you went into a really blue room that might be a pretty blue hat.
Yeah.
If you went onto a blue version of the sun, I could believe it.
Maybe.
I think it's okay to be all blacked up I don't know what's wrong with being all
blacked up I think it's cool I think it's perfectly fine. Blacked up is like
what British people say for blackface. Really? Yeah. Oh well you're really blacked up for sure then.
You're blacked up. They're calling me Bo Selecta. I'm blued up but that's okay.
yeah I'm also black it is so funny like for until like 2010 every like like the
fucking who's that fat bald guy in England you everybody yeah it's true
yeah okay 50% of the people know the gay one you yeah
(laughter)
- There he goes.
- Yeah, he finally lost it.
- Patrick.
- Matt something.
- Patrick Doran.
- Matt Lucas.
- From the Doran family, whose name's Patrick.
- Yeah.
- That guy, there's a really fucking scary picture of him
in like, he's dressed up like a black woman.
- You think that's scary?
- That's scary?
- Well no, it's just they use prosthetics.
They use prosthetics and it looks insane.
It's like very uncanny valley.
Oh, I'm sure that's what scares you.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
No, I'm not scared of that anymore.
CBT.
[LAUGHTER]
You're something else.
We're all something else today.
Yeah, I know.
We're all behaving a little differently.
day after Valentine's Day. We all got that Valentine's Day hangover. Oh yeah. You know
what it is. I'm so drained of cum that my white blood cells went down. Oh my god, I ate so much
of my girlfriend's chocolate that I bought her yesterday. All of it. I had corned beef hash
yesterday. That's unrelated, but I did shape it in a heart. I ate two cheeseburgers. For dinner?
That was your Valentine's Day dinner? You made Jana want to eat two hamburgers?
They were cheeseburgers.
[Laughter]
Jana wants to fast and eat these!
Wants to fast and eat these!
Oh!
I didn't even finish the second one. I got so upset stomach.
Did you go to a restaurant or did you make burgers at home?
I made burgers at home. I made some smash burgers.
[Laughter]
Made one with a...
Two cheeseburgers?
Yeah.
I don't like you berating me for my food decisions.
Yeah, why not?
Because of what I've seen you do in this world.
That's true.
But yeah, I did eat two cheeseburgers and then I was too asleep to do anything else.
I got knocked out by the red meat.
I did drink cold brew last night so I could hang out still.
That was a crazy move on my part.
I drank cold brew concentrate because I was falling asleep.
You need to get into normal coffee.
I don't know why you thought I'm going to stop drinking Buster Energy
instead I'm gonna drink like the poison version of coffee.
- I would say it's a little better than Monster.
- No, you put--
- It's definitely better than Monster, but it's--
- You put a shot of the cold brew in,
and then you mix it with water.
- Yeah, but you don't do that.
- Yeah, I do.
- No, you don't do that.
- Well, why'd you just lie then?
And you said you were drinking up
just the concentrate straight.
- I didn't say that.
- Yeah, it's you, oh, running back.
- You might not do that all the time,
but I feel like once every three days
that I talk to you, you're like,
yeah, I drank way too,
I had like half cold brew concentrate,
half water this morning.
- Yeah, sometimes I don't cut it right.
- Yeah, I just drink normal coffee.
- He doesn't like normal coffee.
You like the shit with the iguana on it.
- Yeah, the chameleon?
- Yeah.
- Chameleon cold brew.
- You like that damn iguana coffee.
- Dude, the iguana?
- Yeah.
- He's good.
- That shit'll make your doo-doo change color.
- Oh, it did?
- Oh yeah.
- Before I got used to it, you know,
like when you first start drinking coffee
and like your shits are just horrible.
your eyes start bugging other, going different directions.
You put out a doo-doo that blends into the porcelain.
- Big shout out to the Chameleon Coffee.
- Big shout out.
- It's so, they got that cinnamon vanilla one.
You mix that with water, it's not that good,
but if you mix it with like milk, oat milk.
- Do you guys think we could get sponsored by Folgers?
- Yeah. - Yes.
- I would love to get sponsored by Folgers.
- I wanna get sponsored by Cafe Bustelo.
- We're gonna do that Folgers incest commercial
over with each other. - I feel like Cafe Bustelo,
it's like the worst coffee in the world,
I drink it all the time, it's dirt cheap,
and I do feel like one of these days I'm gonna open it up
and there's gonna be like a hidden brick of cocaine in it
that fell off of the thing.
That's the whole reason that coffee fucking exists.
- I don't wanna buy anything other than like Folgers
or Bestella because I don't wanna like find out
that I like good coffee and have to buy it.
- Yeah.
- Dude, it's not good.
The highest shelf coffee I'll get,
sometimes when I'm at Dunkin, I'll grab a bag.
I'll grab a bag of beans.
- Yeah, sometimes some Dunkin coffee I'll have.
- 'Cause I'm like, I like Dunkin coffee.
Yeah, there's no way you can trick me into getting something that has flavor notes.
No.
Not happening.
Either Joe or Alex or one of, or Neil, one of my fucking, one of my crazy roommates buys
that Café du Monde.
What's that?
Oh, that's the one with the chicory root in it?
The stuff with the orange tin.
Yeah, like the stuff with flavor in it.
I drank it.
Couldn't be me.
I drank, I made a pot one time for like everyone in the apartment with that and I drank it
I was so afraid after drinking it.
- Literally, I bought one tin and it sent my butt cheeks
to Neptune, it was really, really bad.
- I think training yourself to like really shitty foods
and drinks that are really cheap is like the closest thing
you can be to being a Buddhist monk without being one.
I think it's a really important thing to do in your life.
- Rather than do all that other stupid shit.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, living at what, a castle on a mountain?
- Don't even get me started on monks, bro.
- I would hate living in the beautiful mountains.
- You don't need to shave your head.
- Yeah, and I have to get my balls hit
with a hammer every day or something
with a block of concrete.
- That's what monks have to do.
- And then one day, Bruce Wayne shows up,
we gotta turn him into Batman, great.
- Plus I can't get no damn pussy.
Ain't no damn pussy on the mountain.
- Yes sir.
- What I gotta do, fuck some leaves?
- The Yeti.
That's what the Yeti's for.
- That's why they keep the Yeti all chained up.
- If you had to keep the Yeti.
- They just take turns fucking that other Yeti.
you get you can't go in this room this is the most sacred room in the monastery
we have a sacred statue and there's a serious sacred thing and we have a
bluetooth speakers in there. We left our Halloween soundscape on.
Somebody's meditating so hard that their stomach is growling because we haven't eaten in years.
No!
Somebody's watching a movie on their iPhone in there.
I don't know what that is.
I gotta go in.
I gotta go in and stop them.
They're not allowed to watch movies.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, stop watching that movie.
Stop watching the wampa scene.
Oh, stop watching the movie.
Everybody's just joining in, fucking the yeti.
I would love to see the yeti get gangbanged.
It's what he deserves for the havoc he's wreaked on our world.
Oh my god, he's eaten so many plane wrecked.
- Don't get me started on that damn Yeti.
- Yeah, and you know he's actually Cain.
- Yeah.
- From Cain and Abel.
- No, that's Bigfoot.
- No, I think he's Abel.
- That's Bigfoot.
- I think any of those--
- He's Abel, that's why he got one arm.
- No, the Yeti's not Abel.
- The Yeti ain't Abel, bro.
- Don't be stupid.
- Don't be an idiot.
- He's able to get fucked by me.
- Bro, the Yeti is Cain in a can of goose.
- Bigfoot is Cain.
Bigfoot is Cain.
- No.
- The Yeti's a different thing.
I mean the yet is just an ape monster
no real yeah yeah big foot is actually a biblical guide. Yeah,
that's just a monkey. That's just a big cold monkey. That's just a monkey with
an ice power. Yeah, there's people with ice powers in the world. Yeah, they were
in the Bible, but they cut those pages out yeah, you got to peace out because
they were too scary. Yeah, yeah, the Apofrica, the sky high
a chapter here. I love the apocryphal text. I don't know how to pronounce it either.
Apocrypha. No, they are very sad. They have that one where they're like Jesus was
actually he was gay. Yeah, that was cool. I love the ones where they cut it out
because it was too scary. They have the shit with the Nephilim and stuff. Back in
the old days, there were three hundred foot tall giants that ate everybody and
the fucked angels all the time and they're like yeah. We can't we can't
have this in our book. Yeah, this is not it's like edit. It's like editing a
movie for an airplane or the yeah, exactly we can't and also by the kid in
the back row like see this on somebody's yeah exactly and angels were a and
angels were also a big fly the the never soft eyeball. That's what an angel
looked like yeah, the yeah and also it's also good. They're also ones where
it'll be like it's just about a guy who's like yeah. I saw the end of the
world and here's exactly how it
happened and all this stuff and
it's like well that stayed in.
So not all of it though.
But a lot of it in Revelation and
it's pretty cool man.
It is pretty cool but there's
other stuff where it's like I
forget there's a guy whose name
begins with a Z and there's one
Zorgan.
It's Zorgan yeah.
Zorgan the terror mantor.
It's just like he's like he's a
tormentor and a terrorist and he
fucked God's butt.
Shut up.
God and his book. He doesn't exist.
And he flipped off Jesus too.
No.
And you don't even want to know what he did to Abraham.
What did he do to Abe Lincoln?
Both.
Sheesh. He shot Abe Lincoln.
Yeah. People forget about that.
He possessed John Wilkes Booth.
Dude, that needs to be a Transformers thing.
Zorgon the Terramenter?
No. We're done with Zorgon the Terramenter.
I don't know.
The apocryphal text. He's six feet tall.
Hitler's the Dead Sea Scrolls. And he's six feet, and the worst part, he's six feet tall.
That is what would happen in the Bible.
And verily a giant strode into town. He was five feet eleven inches. That's so cool.
He towered over the villagers and he picked up their crops and he said,
you can't get this you can't get this you shall not get this. That's why if you say
nanananaboo boo you acquire the mark of the beast and you go to hell immediately
mm-hmm they should do a Transformers with the Dead Sea Scrolls where it
reveals that the Transformers were in the Bible. I hope that's the next one
that's what they did that it with a Beyblade. Oh really? Yeah Moses like part
the Red Sea with the Beyblade or something. Oh I remember that! That's so sick!
That's basically what Yu-Gi-Oh is too. Yeah. But Yu-Gi-Oh is like Egyptian right?
Aren't they all white in that show? Yeah of course it's a Japanese show.
It's anime, everybody's white in anime. Except for Bobobo.
Yeah it's true. But aren't the Yu-Gi-Oh's...
Aren't the Yu-Gi-Oh's all Egyptians?
Well it's about... No they're all Japanese.
They're all white Japanese. You want me to, you expect me to believe there's a...
But they have Egyptian ancestors. Oh, you expect me to believe there's a
Japanese Egyptian guy named Joey Wheeler? No, he's from Brooklyn. Oh. I don't think he's from,
I think, I don't think he's from Brooklyn. You expect me to believe there's a Japanese guy named
Yu-Gi-Oh? Nope. No chance. Nope. Most of them, Steve, that's a pretty popular Japanese name.
Steve Japanese
Yeah, that's his name as most that's the most of the names in Japan
Yeah, Tom is also a pretty Japanese name in my brain. Mm-hmm Tom Stevens
He's Japanese like is that like giant like Chinese where when you come to America you get some brand new fucking name
I don't know where you go. That's fucked up. You show up and you're like, no, it's red. It's cool
I would love to be able to pick a new name
that's like a cartoon character something from the country that I'm going to.
Yeah, but that's only if you pick that like I don't know like it's like sometimes you
just get what the name translates to.
Sometimes, well yeah sometimes you just get what the name sounds like.
It's not what it sounds like.
There's a kid in my high school his name was Hercules.
See that's sick.
That is beef.
Again, cartoon character.
Yeah.
Look every, every, every.
White Americans really got the worst names man.
Yeah.
They really got fucked.
Caleb, Cameron.
- All that shit is just like,
we've just been in this stupid country too long.
We just have the most fucked up stupid names
that have just been passed on.
- Yeah, but then people start to make up their,
like it's played out to make fun of it now,
but like Kaylin and like--
- Is that Irish?
- No, like K-A-Y-L-I-G-H-N,
or like Traley.
- G-H-N?
- Well, Traley's--
- Wait, K-A-Y-L-I-G-H-N?
- Yeah, you have to--
- What? That's not a name.
- Or like, or Giler.
- Or Barler.
- The worst example.
- Or Tramila.
- Tray, Kaylin, I've seen spelled like that before.
- You've never seen it G-N-H at the end?
Or G-H-N?
- I think I might have been being dyslexic, but yes.
- Yeah, okay.
- I've seen it spelled like that.
- You saw Kayla.
- No.
- And then you added a bunch of letters to it.
- Yeah, I think the best made up names
where they just take Tyler and put a different consonant set. I like Kyler
Jailer. I heard in I think I said it before, but I should just do all of them
as a letter and a mom was yelling at her son. She went Tyler come here. I was
like Tyler. I was run away to you like my mom name may name me that shit. What
you were like that you were like Jailer.
I was so confusing dude. It's a funny way to fall around this family fucking
Walmart. I was I was playing the switch switch demo.
Gyler, what an odd name, very curious, most peculiar, take out a big book. Let
me let me ask you when did you come up with this name? Gyler, just walk
the following or around the store.
Gyler, Gyler, where have I heard that name before?
Gyler, Gyler.
Oh, from that kid over there.
Oh, his name's Gyler.
Excuse me, ma'am, is your son named Gyler?
I always like him.
Can I take something out of your cart?
When people name their kids like
Crystal, that's always funny to me.
And it's spelled with a K like the sexual fox
from Star Fox.
- I mean, that's better than--
- Diarrhea, I mean that's a bad name.
- Brady Lynn for a girl.
- What, Brady Lynn's cool.
I like any two, any, dude,
any two word name for a girl that's hot.
- It's 'cause you're from the south.
- Oh yeah, definitely dude.
- That's 'cause you're from the south, dude.
- Yeah.
- You probably knew like a fucking like Amy Lee.
- I need to, oh, Amy Lees are hot, dude.
- Yeah, probably the hottest name for a girl
for me probably would be sexotron. Sadie sexotron. Yeah that'd be hot. Sadie sexotron you get
back in the house right now. Yeah something Lynn is hot. Yeah. If a girls name is Billy
something. That's hot dude. If a girl has like an old lady name. Old lady cowboy name.
Yeah, like I'm signing up.
Yeah, oh, Sliztronica?
(laughter)
Sliztronica Mega Cooch?
That's hot.
That's really hot.
Muriel Stinky Fat One?
Boobstastic?
Boobs Pussy?
That's a hot name with a dash in between.
Oh my god.
God, I'm gonna cum.
Alright, let's do this list here.
This is top ten things to buy with $100.
If you had to blow $100, what would be the best thing to buy with it?
If I had to blow $100, blow it in my nose.
Yeah.
I'm so hood rich.
Would you blow $100, would you blow $1 million?
Yes.
Gay.
Damn, okay.
You gay.
If you say so.
Alright.
Don't care.
Still made money though.
DJ Academics is about to have a field day with that stuff.
He said he would blow a million dollars.
One of those like...
Sound off in the comments.
it's one of those like it's like a like a picture of me and then like the like
the black gradient and then like the font says like he would blow one
hundred dollars. Yeah, I saw a video I found out today. There's this rapper
forty two Doug and he he was like him. He was like a guy and then he and
everybody loved him and he's making tons of money and stuff. This is like
last year and then he made a song where he was like he was like I used to suck
dick for money because I was homeless and he got like drop from his label.
Everybody stopped making music with him and now he's just like not doing shit.
Yeah, he just said that he used to be used to be so desperate for money. It
sucked dick. Damn, which is like I want that on one hand. It's like that's fun.
It that's like that's fucked up to everybody kind of abandon it, but other
also like why would you yeah? Why would you say that you go to the grave?
Every other fucking song this guy's made is about how cool his car is and all
and he's like plus I use a suck dick and I fucking now it's like it definitely
thought he thought he could sneak that in he would have been fine if before rap
genius exactly yeah and then I went back and listen to one of his other song he's
like big hit and like every single line is about how much he like doesn't like
women and like doesn't want to fuck it's cool number one is clothes Patrick take
it away? No, I don't know. I don't think I've ever spent a lot of money on clothes.
Really? Yeah. You don't think so? No, I'm not the type to do that. I'm really not the type
to do that. How much are these pants? These are actually 20 bucks. Why must people always think
about their appearance to others or to themselves? It's a
strange world we live in. I am actually wearing my least expensive shit. Yeah, you
You look like dog shit.
I look like shit.
You look terrible.
You look like something I wear all the time.
I know.
I gotta get back on my shit.
I would buy more nylons, heels, bras, and the such.
I love to wear them all the time.
They totally turn me on.
Sound clip.
Clip that.
Cameron said that.
Cameron is wearing ladies underwear under his shirt.
No I'm not.
He's wearing a bra.
Look.
Cameron's wearing a...
I see...
Oh my god.
That is one of the most beautiful, intricate, lace things I've ever seen.
You're looking in the mirror again, pal.
I'm not. Yeah, you literally are. What are you doing with your hand? Jacking off to your bra.
I'm jacking off to Cameron's bra. Whenever guys like underwear and like smell it and jack off to it,
that's the weirdest shit. That's really funny to me. I think that's weird. That is so crazy. That's
worse than like wanting to eat a woman. Okay. I don't think that's... And wanting to eat a woman,
it's actually pretty normal now that I think about it. It makes sense. What? Like wanting to eat it,
like army hammer being like I need to eat your arm like doing I need to use your
arm with my hammer no I did you ever say what part of the body he wanted to eat
if you said you wanted to drink blood right yeah did he did he want to eat
like people's meat I think so like did he I think he wanted what do you think
you want it yeah did he want like yeah like you think you wanted an arm or the
broad end of the fly the flank yeah that's a good point yeah you want to
weird as hell though. He wanted to eat Megan butt. Yeah. Crispy. He wanted to put Megan
on the Traeger. Yeah, yeah. Just salt and pepper by the way. A little mustard to bind it. Low
and slow. Fifteen hours. Wrap it. Two hours back in. With a little bit of barbeque. Imagine
burnt ends. I'm not supporting anyone that uses a Traeger. Why? Someone told me you're
not supposed to. You're not supposed to use a Traeger. Bob said that. Who's Bob? Oh Bob.
Yeah. He said you shouldn't use a Traeger? Bob hates Traegers. Fuck you, you fucking pizza
mouth motherfucker. Get the fuck out of here. Traegers are sick. Here's a really good
genius comment. Videos of Traegers. Shoes are cloths, right? Coats? Definitely clothes.
Facts. Too bad nobody wears them. That's true. Yeah. Yeah. Have you noticed this? A
lot of these women will spend extra money to have less clothes on their bodies.
Have you noticed this? The Emperor is actually wearing nothing and people told
him that the clothes are... I could see the clothes so it sounds like maybe you just
weren't cool enough to see them. No he wasn't wearing any clothes. I mean I could
see that they said they were clothes that only cool people could see and you
didn't see them and I did. The Emperor's robes were not there. Yeah I also saw them.
Yeah they were blue right? And hold up you were looking at the
emperor while he wasn't wearing clothes is that what you're telling me? Yes. Okay so
guess who's getting executed? So gay and lame. Yeah and I guess you're gonna get
decapitated too with a big very dull rock that we use right now. Yeah
baseball bat. Well that's fine. You would think it's fine. Clothes would be great.
I feel like Patrick. Imagine going to a concert performing naked. Remember that lady who peed on
the guy's face that was cool that was cool that was cool were you saying you
feel like I what I feel like I could sell you something invisible no yeah you
couldn't sell me something invisible you could sell me something really shitty
what about this what is that take it well no cuz you're gonna make me pay for it
no take it it's a dollar a $1 $1 that's all it is you do Venmo yeah here here's
my code okay check it out oh wow it's pretty cool right shape when you put it
in my head yeah well no I had a handle at the top - oh well I'm grabbing it by the
little end yep oh it is a little end yeah now crush it whoa that's right
that's right that's that's child
I work for the police. Officer, we have found over three million gigabytes of
invisible child pornography on this man's computer. We need to send him to jail.
Yep, it's all over. You can't see it, but everybody else can. He
encrypted it just so that cops can't see it. So the cops and the government can't see it.
Everybody else can see it and you need to kill him right now.
how listen to the fan on his computer is going so fast it's because there's no
space left nope there's nothing number two is games nope games have a game gate
will listen to this this might change your mind okay games have such engaging
stories perfect gameplay and some of the most memorable ways to spend your time
in the 21st century aside be it from being with real people obviously why
spend it on clothes that you will grow out of in a couple years compared to
games that provide memorable experiences for decades if you get a good one that
did change my mind. Yeah, games have good gameplay. That's true. That's the thing about games
that clothes don't have. Yeah, you can't king a pair of pants. You could if you put a crown
on it. No, that's not the same. You can embroider a crown on them. That's not kinging, that's
embroidering a crown. The fact that you're saying embroider a crown instead of king proves
it's not, it doesn't make sense. It's not a real thing. I wish I could justify buying
a bunch of playstation 5's and just like dumping them into a volcano.
Yeah.
That'd be kind of fun.
It would be fun to like...
I really want to like destroy some really expensive stuff.
PS5 under the pneumatic press.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you imagine how mad people would get at that?
Yeah.
It'd be so funny.
What's the deal with the PS5's right now?
They're like...
They basically play like 900 dollars.
They're like the next one after PS4.
Why are they 900 bucks?
I think that...
I don't know.
I don't know either.
That makes no sense to me.
like the same price as a PC? I don't know man you're asking the wrong guy you
should be asking Linus Tip Tips. Yeah. Yeah Linus is Tip Tips. Hey Linus do you have any
tip tips for me? Linus life tips. Linus Tip Tips has changed my life. He's
seriously give me so many tips. Yeah. Linus Tip Tips. Here's a tip for that tip.
Mm-hmm you taught me how to open a jar yeah yeah he did he gave me the tip
grip that you have to you have to slam it yeah yeah you throw it yeah yeah you
taught his tip tip he gave me is his tip tip about the jar if you don't mind
glass you can smash you know you tap the tap the top mmm oh you give you a tap
in mmm yeah so I just have one tap tips yeah okay
top tap tap tip I hate that - Linus is trick tips oh those are nasty cuz he
- Like the one about the jar when he says,
"If you care about glass in your food,
"then you won't get glass."
- He's not a very good writer.
- No, yeah, that's what's so tricky about it.
- And the other one about his jar,
if you sit on it, you'll go viral in a video.
- Well, that was actually a great tip,
'cause it works.
- You know what would be a good recreation?
Do one man, one jar now,
but it's a jar of peanut brittle
the prank snake flies up in your ass.
- Before he's sitting down.
- Yeah.
- It just shoots directly into your ass.
- You gotta get Pierce Paris on that.
- Oh yeah.
- Dude, oh my god.
- He would be good for that.
- The snake opens up and still goes in his ass.
- Just directly, just huge gaper.
- That would be awesome.
- And then he walks around with a,
it's kind of like a tail.
But he's kind of, he's holding his ass like he's Mario
and he just fell into lava.
- Yeah.
(imitates Mario)
- Yeah, yeah.
- Big shout out to Pierce Paris' video.
- And shout out to Mario.
You go fast when you hot.
And shout out to Bowser.
Gotta have good and bad.
Definitely not.
Nope, that's, I'm saying it.
Shout out to Bowser.
We're gonna be apologizing for that really soon.
Yeah.
Comedian Patrick Doran came out today and said he was...
Comedian Patrick Doran today is fired from SNL as a podcast clip emerges of him being
pro-Bowser.
Yeah, like the Koopas, I would love to hang out with the Koopas.
Yeah, I just think what he does to the Koopas is sick.
It's like cool. Yeah. Plus his son is too.
Say what you will, but like the Mushroom Kingdom has run way better with him in charge.
No.
All right, that's just my opinion.
No, you fucked us. You fucked all of us. We're fucking done.
Comedian Patrick Doran let go from writer's room this week after an offensive clip surfaced
from the past of him doing an extremely exaggerated toad accent.
Okay!
And there's the clip.
Number three, food.
Nope.
Don't need it.
Let's be honest here, who doesn't like food?
I don't need food!
With $100 you could get yourself a very fine steak dinner or buy a lot of nice yummy chocolates.
You really just can't go wrong with food.
I'm on pretty much a steak and chocolate dinner.
You spent $100 on chocolate?
Did I spend $100?
Would you?
Would I?
of chocolate and steak? I think I... Steak? Yeah. Oh yeah. I don't even like steak. Okay,
just chocolate. I would buy one a $100 steak. Would you buy a chocolate steak? Would you buy a $100
steak with like a chocolate sauce? That sounds really shitty. Did I ever tell you about the
chocolate ham? Don't care. Yeah? Nope. I think I've told you about the chocolate ham. My cousin's
birthday is like fifth birthday. Did you not hear me? All right. Food is amazing and there are so
so many choices such as Chinese, Italian, Indian, etc.
The list goes on forever, how can you not choose it?
- Please tell me, I wanna know something.
- No, you said you didn't wanna know.
- Please, can you stop, please, I was just kidding.
I really wanna know about the chocolate ham.
- You sure?
- Yes.
- Cameron, can I tell him about it?
- That's up to you, man, you don't have to ask me.
- I don't know, it seems like you're the one
in charge right now.
- I'm not in charge, I'm looking at these comments,
I'm trying to find the next comment to read.
You guys have to settle this yourself.
my cousin's fifth birthday. I don't care. I'm a big fat kid who liked to eat. Whoa. Yeah
you are. My food, wait go back. Food is my best friend. By the way I'm not a loner. Whoa.
Does that mean he's got a lot of food around him? Yeah. He's got, he lives in a sausage
party. Food for the win. Food is a need. Oh he's really small and he lives in sausage
but it was in the grocery store after dark.
- Come on, food creates a satisfying feeling
that comes from endorphins in your brain.
Enjoy it with some spaghetti, sandwiches,
brownies, chicken tenders, et cetera.
- I love to have food with my spaghetti.
I think Sausage Party might be, to me,
I don't think I've ever watched a movie
that filled me with so much like--
- Dread? - Existential unease.
I watched that movie and it really upset me.
- I think I got, I think I watched a clip,
I've never seen it, but I watched a clip from it
and it made me so upset.
It really like made my stomach hurt.
Yeah.
You know, it's like when you watch Fight Club and you're like too young.
And you're like, "Ugh."
Yeah.
I did not watch, I did not watch Sons of the Party.
It was like watching, it was bad, dude.
What's that movie with Brad, I think it's Troy.
Brad Pitt plays Achilles.
It's probably Troy.
I haven't seen it.
I saw that, I saw the Trojan horse scene and it freaked me out as a kid.
Why is this horse so big?
Dad, the horse is made of wood.
Dad.
Dad, it looks like a house.
You're afraid that the Trojan horse is going to show up to your house.
of wood! Dad! Dad! It looks like a house! You're afraid that the Trojan horse is gonna show up to your house, huh?
I got really upset that there was like a bunch of people getting murdered. You
sound like a pussy. I liked it. I looked out of the window and I saw, I lived in
Syria and I would just watch people die all day when I was a kid. I'm from Syria.
A lot of people don't know that. I'm from Aleppo. Yeah. Like Steve Jobs. What? Steve Jobs is Syrian.
Really? Was. Yeah, now he's seriously a dead skinny guy. Yeah. And he used to
seriously be a fat baldy with a turtleneck. And he seriously, he seriously
sips some smoothies. Yep. To subdue his symptoms of cancer. And what did they do?
Suffocated him to death. Yep. He got a strawberry lodged in his, in his fucking
tubes mm-hmm yeah well that's the thing he thought that you're supposed to eat
the fruitarian thing works but he thought you had to eat all the fruit whole and he
got to watermelon Wednesdays it really ruined everything yeah also like it's
the hardest thing to do cuz like there's two you know there's not a lot of tea
fruits yeah yeah yeah yeah to do tea he said to settle for tutti frutti yeah
yeah yeah there's tropical Tuesdays and then 2d fruity Thursdays and 2d 2d
fruity Thursdays hard because all the food is 2d yeah it was lucky he died on
watermelon Wednesday before he got fruit parentheses all Friday fruit comma every
yeah right ace then there's strawberry Saturdays and you know it's fine yeah
Those are good. Mm-hmm. Strawberry Saturdays is great some blueberries Sundays
More blueberries Mondays
The blueberries Tuesday the blueberries Thursdays and water. It's all blueberries Wow
And watermelons
Yeah
Music is number four. I would never how do you spend a hundred bucks on anything?
You can spend a hundred bucks on a guitar. That's not doesn't count. That's a toy guitars on a toy for your ass it is
Bitch ass I said it first fucking bitch. Thanks
What I said bitch at the same time and now you'll be a coke ass bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch
Bitch bitch
No
Probably not cuz it's you saying it Cameron does it sound cool on the microphone I do this
bitch
Not really doing a doppler. It just sounds like you're moving the microphone around I do a toddler
Yep
Yeah, I love music and dancing to it YouTube
One word music
Number five is movies. Oh this motherfucker. Yeah, I know this motherfucker right here spending 100 bucks on movies
I spent a lot of money. I've gotten got let's just hope that like
Gambling isn't one of the entries on the list. It's yeah, there's no way it is
Sorry people. I love the movie. What about you guys?
I hate the movie if you all want in game so badly get the disc or download it onto your phone legally
Effects yeah movies for the win. Yep. I love my Oh rare Doug appearance. I love my movie collection
You can always watch movies for free on one two three movies calm. You better. I hate school
You know he the bad kid. Oh my god. He's watching movie. I bet he goes to
www.nakedladies.com too.
He goes to whitehouse.com and not .gov.
That's right.
Right after he said you weren't getting got you.
Oh shit!
Number 6 is a puppy.
It costs way more than a hundred bucks.
This shit's lying.
Yeah?
Yeah.
How much does your dog cost?
One million trillion dollars?
I think the adoption fee is like four hundred bucks.
Really?
Yeah.
Four hundred bones.
They have a genius.
The top comment here is by a genius.
Okay.
I think that you ought to rephrase that.
When you buy an animal, you aren't just buying the baby version of that animal.
of that animal. You are buying that animal's entire life and it is your duty
to provide for and love them all that time. Anyways, when you add food, vet care,
and other necessities, dogs cost much more than $100." And then it's colon dash slash.
They did the slanty face? Yeah, the slanty face but with a nose.
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait. Caleb got in trouble for doing a slanty face one time. No, I didn't.
Yeah, here's a comment from a dove. "Yep, so far my dog has lavishly spent
$1,000.00. I hate when my dog spends my money. Stop fucking putting your dog's paw print on
your fucking iPhone. He gets my credit card when I go to work. It's fucked. Dogs have been
doing in-app purchases on ragandbone.com. Imagine you get a huge Amazon box delivered
and you open it up. It's all tennis balls. It's literally all tennis balls and huge bones.
yeah, I don't think I ordered this. Yeah, I don't think I know. I don't think it's
you know what a puppy ordered all that
puppy that loves the delicious bones. They all like to play with tennis
balls. Yeah, if you call your credit card company and tell them your puppy
did it so basically my yes, it was my mistake. I did make my password. I'm a
dog.
There was like a knock on the door and it's the pizza delivery guy. It's like
I have I'm here, but I'm bringing a pizza. It's a it's got no cheese, no
sauce. It's just it's peanut butter. What did you order this butter? I don't
know I must be I'm not too lazy to make peanut butter on toast.
It must have been my dog. Who calls you is like nothing I've ever seen it's
just a it's just a bone. There's no well. I'll have to punish my dog by
eating this myself and not letting him have any and hurting my dog. Also,
I don't like to get high on peanut butter and hurt my dog.
That's not what I do. I don't like to get high off the sugar and the canola oil.
Also, I don't have any money, so if I could pay you some other way.
Or if my dog could pay you some other way, because it's for him, I'm not going to use it.
Are you going to put the peanut butter on you?
I could put the peanut butter wherever.
I could put it wherever.
Peanut butter pizza with a side of peanut butter.
Peanut butter dipping cut.
What else?
Number seven is a phone.
One hundred pounds is not enough for an iPhone.
if it was I mean that's more than enough my phone weighed a hundred pounds you
know I damn phones too big yeah that's in a pad territory yep yeah whatever number
eight is books who the fuck spends on your own book lame I don't spend any
money on books books are free dumbass
you probably spent more money on books than I have hundred dollars as you have
book you have a bunch of like books that probably cost you 50 bucks cuz they like
we got one printing yeah they're like some TV characters entire biography that
and like in like cause table books yeah don't you dare don't you fucking yeah I
like cause you love cause I don't love cause yeah probably his apartments full
I've probably never spent more than like five dollars I'm looking right now
you've got the you've got the Coons the the balloon animals cause I don't have
the balloon animals yes you do where you have those balloon animals that they have
in realty offices and shit.
- Nah.
- Actually, the fucking, the big--
- What realty offices the fuck are you going to?
- I went to one.
- You went to like a fancy realty office?
They have a fucking Jeff Koons fucking--
- Like the balloon animal?
- Balloon thing, what the fuck?
- Yeah, there was one in,
well I think it's like a knockoff,
but it was like the place.
- You've been stealing-- - Somewhere around Revere.
- You've been stealing one foot cause statues
from Dominican barber shops
and putting them in your house.
(laughing)
You have.
Number nine, donate to charity.
- Nah, missed me with that.
Yep, fuck those kids.
Fuck the cancer patients.
I've never seen this before.
In the entirety of this podcast.
Number 10. It just says 10. There's nothing there.
There's no entry and there's a ton of commas.
It just says 10.
Oh, trips.
It doesn't say it but it's supposed to be trips.
See if you can highlight it.
No, there's just nothing there.
What the hell?
We gotta take a photo of this shit.
This is life changing.
This is the craziest episode we've ever done.
This is the most psychotic shit that's ever happened.
Damn.
Oh, it is trips.
It's trips, yeah.
But it still doesn't show up.
Number 11's cat.
Fuck a cat.
Number 12 is tattoo.
Yup.
I would get a tattoo of Conquer the Squirrel on my arm.
Just kidding.
I wouldn't get a tattoo.
They aren't for me.
I don't want to get a tattoo of something stupid.
Caleb has a ghost on his ass.
Check out my butt.
Is it ghost?
Ghost. I've never seen the ghost. You've never seen this? I have seen it actually.
Never mind, I have seen that ghost. This is like, this is like probably my best tattoo.
What were you like 18 when you got that? Yeah. I fucking knew it. Yeah.
Yeah, that's the dumbest shit ever. It's cool. It's not cool. Look it has the same dot.
You're talking a lot of shit right now Pat. I have a cool tattoo. Yeah? My tattoo's
sick. Yeah? Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah? It says Dr. Evil on my left bicep. That's cool. It is
That's kind of cool.
That is sick.
It's not as cool as my ghost.
No, the ghost is not as cool as that.
Which one is cooler?
That is sick.
This one's the coolest.
Okay, okay, the tribal thing is way sicker than mine.
Yes.
That's sick as fuck.
Now he wishes he got a tribal tat like me.
I was thinking about it.
He should get a tribal copycat.
He should just get all different, all like this exact kind of little hundred dollar tribal
tat all over his body.
I'm going to get barbed wire across the arm.
Barbed wire is sick, dude.
Yeah, dude.
You should get a really shit, you should get one of those crosses that turns into the John
Deere logo at the top.
That'd be cool.
Yeah, dude.
I want the line work to look so bad.
Yeah.
It's clearly done by a guy who's been in recovery for 20 years and he's just got the shakiest
hands.
No shading.
Yeah, no.
It's barbed wire, no shading.
Yeah, yeah, with a real, real fucking small needle too.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
Got a tattoo on my arm.
I screams like a baby.
"Yes, I am honest 'cause the owner was playing this song
"I kinda detest now.
"It's called Karate Chop,
"and it is the worst future song I've ever heard."
- Whoa, Karate Chop's good.
This guy's an idiot.
- He was screaming like a baby
'cause he heard that song, he said.
"I am so glad I stumbled on this website.
"I've been looking for a way to spend my newly earned $100,
"and I'm so excited to get a little pink dolphin
"on my ankle, heart, Merry Christmas."
- Damn.
I should get a, oh, like the pink, wait,
pink dolphin like the the hot topic brand. Here's one that's a that's cap each
word is capitalized. I'm getting a tattoo of a foot on my foot. Mind blown. That's
sick dude. That's swag. Number 13 is shoes. How you gonna buy a hundred dollar
pair of shoes? How could a man possibly buy a man possibly buy a hundred dollar
pair of shoes. He just did. I'd bought, that's probably the most expensive pair of shoes I ever
bought in my life I think. Me too. Buy a huge amount. I don't think, I think I probably the
most I spent on shoes besides that is like probably like $40. 40 or 50. 40? I buy like
New Balance shoes. I'm a shoe carnival man. I'm not like a shoe guy. You ever go to shoe carnival?
What's that? You ever been to shoe baka? Bro, shoe carnival was crazy. What is it? You go in,
it's like you do, there's like a get what you get wheel. Yeah. Where you spin a wheel and like
It's like a giant wheel and sometimes you get a free pair of shoes.
Because it's really where is this?
It's in Wilmington, North Carolina.
I'm going to go there next time.
Yeah, got the worst fucking shoes in the world.
Yeah, but they got a wheel, though.
I do love to spin a wheel.
They got a serious guy.
I don't care as long as I get to spin a wheel.
I just spin the wheel.
And then like it gives you different coupons.
I'll go to like the worst place in the world as long as there's a wheel there.
I think if the wheel is still going, dude, next time we're in Wilmington,
I'll I'll take your. Yeah, yeah.
We'll hit you.
What do they got there, like Airspeeds?
Yeah.
Remember Airspeed?
Mm-hmm.
They got the Shaquille O'Neal shoes.
Dude, I got--
I tried to--
I used to only wear Shaq shoes when I was in third grade.
I tried to buy a pair a couple years ago.
They only make them in kid's size.
It's so fucked up, dude.
Messed up.
Shaq can't even wear them damn shoes.
Number 27 is toys.
Yes, I love toys.
I have no idea why.
I'm 12, and I still love toys.
I like Legos and plushes of video game characters.
I already have Pikachu link and I'm getting conquer the squirrel soon toys
rule toys. I mean that's I'm still left. I'm twelve and even I like toys. You
think you guys didn't get bullied out of playing with toys when you were like I
never got bullied even once. I am eighty nine years old and I love toys. I
dominated my civil. That's a right here.
I'm eighty nine years old. Do you remember that guy when I lived in
Central Square, remember that crazy house across from me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that guy would go to Brookline Lunch down the street
and he would go and play with action figures all day.
- Really?
- It was so cool and he was old as fuck.
He was in his 70s.
He would just be there playing with GI Joes.
(imitates gun sounds)
- That's tight.
- I would get cooler toys if I--
- And I was like, that guy is a homeowner.
- I would get cooler toys than that guy and I would go--
- He didn't know about cool toys.
- And I would sit next to him, sit across from him.
- Make him jealous?
- Yeah.
- Pretty good idea.
show up with my like $80 BB-8 and I have it on the table and it's spinning around
and it's eating it's eating lunch with me he probably would not he probably think
you were a witch dude you'd not like that yeah he would freak out
it is kind of a dog WWE magazines and there's two comments okay well okay well
you want me to click I'm sure this is gonna be porn magazines are better I
I don't like wrestling, but I'd rather have that porn.
- Wait, wait, Smooth Criminal says,
I would do this, yeah baby.
- Number 46, Fleshlight.
- Fleshlight's so great and scary as a concept.
- Number 47, Cranberry Juice.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
- That's scary?
- Uh-huh.
- Spunk it in a hole?
Is scary to you?
- Well, just like, imagine opening that thing up
and just looking at a vagina like that.
I think I'm just scared of vaginas.
- I think so.
number 50 dildo this is an excellent suggestion. Dildos are actually cool though. Everyone needs
one of these whether you're a guy or a girl. Car parts. This man is a genius. Beef jerky?
Beef jerky is expensive as hell. They gotta lower them damn prices. It's like six bucks
for a little sweet and hot. I called the boys on my bus beef jerky when I meant to call
them jerks. That's pretty smart. Concert tickets, nah. Makeup. Hot wings. I love hot wings.
- Me too. - A knife?
- A knife. - Bong?
- Spin brush, toothbrush.
- Oh, I used to only use that toothbrush.
- Goldfish crackers changed my life.
(laughing)
Bacon. - Yep.
- Scooter.
- Did you guys have scooters growing up?
- Yeah. - I didn't have a scooter.
- I did. - I had a skateboard.
- I'd want to just destroy my ankles
trying to do that spin thing. - Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah. - Oh, I'd just kill myself
every single day. - I hated scooters.
- Legos, video games, a pimp leash.
- What?
- A pimp leash. - A pimp leash.
helps keep us in line especially one with rhinestones and she to print
i'm really what's a pimply tickets to a car race i've never seen a pin you put
a little woman on a leash
yes so there were seventies porn membership is that not ever know anybody
like she had a bradley
all right guys are at this point i'll change the the
number i guess there
or if people people see the episode
they'll be able to find the list
somebody put their whole address
it says free sex
who want, i live in and then a full
address, free sex
jesus
love it, #gayporn
they don't say what
city though right?
i still don't want to read it
i don't think we should
but they're trying to get people to come fuck them dude
that's true
should we help them out by
You just open the page on top tens for chicken some know you could do that if you click on chicken perfect chicken chicken is just
Perfect ham and pig is better
Do they mean chicken the meat or chicken the the service?
I think you know we got to go lightning round here concert ticket fidget spinner. There were some good one hair highlights
I love it, and I am a kid there are a bunch of good ones that have like one more element friends nail polish snapback
You're you can never go wrong with trying to have swag and the best way to do that is wearing snapbacks
Mm-hmm tacos. Yep a nerf gun a bike potatoes. I was listening to like a song recently
It's like my favorite my new favorite song ever. Yeah, and I I look at song is it it's
Every chance that I get by a little baby and DJ Khaled and I watched the video
Right and I was like dude this song so awesome and the top comment on the YouTube video
Was like this song is a serious vibe, especially if you play high school basketball or football
Something's wrong with me dude, yeah
You listen to like it's only listen to the same rap that 16 year olds like yeah
Yeah, you love like juice world and like oh my god. I love juice world juice world's great. Don't talk down
I'm just well not I'm talking down. I'm just it's funny. What's his real name?
Juice Juice in world mr. Juice Houston Houston Houston worldness yeah world
and steen oh he's the one that died right yeah you yeah he's the one he's the only
one that died the only rapper to ever die yeah the only the only emo rapper we
used to have it's so it's so fucking funny to me that you were like an emo
rap guy we used to have it's sick dude please have XXX juice and little peep now
Now we got now now when I make when I watch XXX movies my peep make some juice.
Yeah, that's right.
Auction you can always find something worth your while at an auction.
German crabs, hermit crabs, candles, Yankee candles are bay a nice dinner for
your family or significant other.
Nah, a winter jacket, a pug, grammar tutoring, apples, ha ha, lol, a
toilet if you have to poop another $100 bill you could exchange that shit for a
to an old one chairs posters stationary I love stationary a used car turtles turtles
are swag so get one now outside toys yeah I love outside toys you they stay
outside and then get kind of ooh Bonesy buddy Halloween decorations Halloween
animatronics drugs oh my god so many comments on drugs yeah alcohol I'm
cigarettes I'm glad these all got voted down I refuse to get drunk prostitute the
person that made this should be banned from the site instead of paying 100 for
one go pay 50 twice gonna heck with someone buy this pogo stick bag of poop
nah you know you similac what round of golf I drink so that's for breakfast
second breakfast lunch 11 Z's 12 Z's and dinner that's a very sick child yeah
that's a hobbit drums steak baked potatoes peanuts you just foods of these
scissors but scissors because then I can break into your house and cut up all
your chairs no your face that's random assault do you ham ham is so good my
last meal alive will be ham rare cards all right wait for we and now you can
tell the chocolate I'm story okay my cousin loved Scooby-Doo so much when he
was a kid and he saw Scooby eat a chocolate ham and requested a chocolate
ham for his his fifth birthday dinner. Did you have some? I didn't eat any of the
chocolate ham. I've said this before, yes he did eat the chocolate ham.
Once he said... I really it was smart of me to interrupt him every other time
I'm sorry that I let him say that at the end. I'd like to apologize to you Cameron, I'd like to
apologize to the listener. All right go buy a ticket to the D&D show. Oh and I
think there's maybe some tickets for me and Adam Friedland in Boston this
weekend cool I think maybe a third show some tickets 187 furniture great if you
want to give your house a new look
Bye.