come here come here come here let me see your butt
welcome back to podcast about Liz WPAL WPAL yeah that's what you put at the
beginning of a radio station Oh W cuz yeah what's up
- Yeah, waves. - Waves.
- Waves. - The radio is waves.
- I think that does stand for wavelength.
- Yeah, I'm whistening to VAL.
I'm whistening right now.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I'm not doing too hot.
- Me neither.
I had a really bad week.
- Yeah, I had a, you know,
there's a lot of ups and downs in my weekend.
- Yeah, I had a crazy day yesterday.
- Yeah, I broke my toe.
- Yeah.
- I broke my toe.
I wasn't even doing anything cool.
- Yeah, well, how'd you break it?
- I slipped.
- On what?
- It was just like a patch of ground
that I think might have been wet,
and then my skateboard, I was trying to just turn around
so I could go do this trick.
- Oh, but you were at least on a skateboard, though.
- Yeah, but I did--
- So it's cool. - Yeah, it was a trick.
- It wasn't cool, it ruined the whole sesh.
- Not the sesh.
- That's awful. - The sesh was ruined for me.
- Sounds like you had a bad fucking week.
- You had a bad sesh yesterday?
- Bad sesh is bad vibes. - That's horrible.
I don't even wanna say what was,
my week was bad now.
he has only a snob was that about your week i broke my toe and continue to walk
for continued walking skate for another like fast awful did not i don't want to
say my my total yesterday to be told me he broke his toe i cared so much about
him
that's really sweet yeah
i didn't even heard it just started to i didn't do anything he didn't do anything
caleb didn't do a thing for myself
i'm sorry i thought you know you should have had your toe hurt to okay it hurts
right now then and then I got in a city bike dispute. Oh no dispute. I had to
just because I put it into the dock and the dock was broken. I was imagining you
got in a fight with someone you're calling it a dispute. No I had to I put
it in the dock and I mean thankfully I'm still in my 15-day free trial of
lift pink uh-huh but I I put the city bike in the dock it locked but the dock
is broken and it wasn't registering that my city bike was returned. Oh no. So I
technically went on an 18-hour city bike ride yesterday. Damn that sucks. I was
charged, I wasn't charged, I had to call and take photos of the thing in the dock
but it said that it was uh it would have been around $150. That's worth it. That's
one of the troubles with technology nowadays. Might as well just buy your own city bike at that point.
that i i want to get a bike yeah you want to get a bike take the one that he was
going to give to me
yeah you can have it
you should take for a small price you'll use it more than me i can pay for it
twenty dollars
uh... that's too high
then you can't okay i'll take it for twenty dollars
yeah i had a pretty bad week too, not as bad as yours but i was uh...
i was actually in a gangland shootout
that sounds a way less bad the idea that i was on the test fund maybe not have a
video i got hit four or five times by different calibers of bullets and i
actually had to use might ideas might uh... trico in the gangland should
actually kill a couple kids to
yeah that sounds like it could be a video game type uh...
that now it is in real life
yeah i had a bad uh... i'll
all my limbs lost feeling and i died
I'm just joking. I didn't die.
That's a completely made up story.
I said, just kidding. It's not made up. It's a joke.
If you said kidding.
How is that? That is not true.
I'm literally telling you, me and Pat both had really bad
real weeks.
I did too. I don't want to say it because
we're recording it for millions of
people to hear. Maybe I don't want to say the horrible things
that happened to me so I make a joke to lighten the mood.
He's making light.
That's how you cook.
He's making light of some real shit.
He's making light of some real shit that happened to us and he doesn't even care that even after I broke my toe skating
I still went to a party. I do care. That's why my toe hurts so bad is because you I I would try
I was ready and I walked my toes on my toes because I was trying I was
share the pain
I was trying to take some of the burden off of him
I was trying to take the pain into my body put it on me and put it on me
He's like, oh, oh, yeah, actually I lost all feeling in my limbs
He doesn't care that I had a broken toe and I went to a place with an open bar.
Do you guys even care that I played too many video games and lost all feeling in my arms?
That's not funny.
Do you guys even care that I made a face so long that I got stuck that way?
He does.
I bet he doesn't.
I care.
Look, I'm making a face right now because I feel so bad.
Well, I would say that's it.
I'm trying to take it.
I really like that.
I want to carry your pain for you.
I really like this face, but don't hold it for too long because it will actually get stuck
like that.
face be stuck than yours that's not gonna help my face you get unstuck because
you're making this face you just look ugly you look fucking disgusting you
look you straight out you look like a spider right now stop it's stuck it's
Oh great, I guess now he does share our pain. Okay, but have you been have you
been riddled by bullets? Yeah. Did you break your toe and still have to go to a
party? And have to go to a party? Mm-hmm. I didn't even get to go to a party.
My toe hurt and I didn't even get to go to a party. Did you say three boobs? I got
three boobs. He went to the party from Total Recall.
at like Mars.
Open boobs.
Yeah.
Bring your own boobs.
And I also got free stickers too.
Well, that was the problem and that happened in Total Recall too.
But instead of open bar, they had open air lock.
See, he doesn't even care.
He's talking about Total Recall.
He doesn't care that I had a broken toe and I got free stickers.
I have Total Recall of your broken toe situation is what I have.
Do you think that instead of, in the future, instead of drugs and alcohol, like we won't
like physically drink or consume them, we'll just like download like a chip or a feeling?
If we're robots, maybe.
don't think that we're gonna have some kind of new gland.
I don't think it'll be a gland, I bet it'll be like a helmet that you wear.
Yeah.
Like make an electrical attack on you.
Yeah and it makes you feel a little weird.
It's like the thing, it's like this thing that you put on your head.
Oh yeah.
That's a more addictive drug than anything.
That makes you shiver.
That is honestly, I could easily no hands fucking come without one of those.
when I was home of my my mom's house. My mom has one of those and I snuck up by
my girlfriend. She didn't even know that we like had one or that it existed and I
did a turn and that was probably the most scared I've ever seen her in my
life. Dude, that feeling is so fucked up. It's it was so she was like
it's not a massage. It's not anything. I don't like that people pretend that
they're not only for pranks. Nobody's sitting there doing that to themselves
like oh yeah, my eyes would massage you. I do that you do that. It feels nice. I
hate that feeling.
That's because you're bald.
You don't have hair to cushion it.
It probably scratches you.
I haven't even, for your information, I've never used one while I was bald.
Okay, asshole.
You should try it again.
Maybe you'll like it.
Maybe I will.
You know what feels good?
What?
If you got like popcorn ceiling, like with the little specks.
Yeah.
And when you're in like the third grade and you have triple bunk beds and you rub your
feet on the ceiling.
Ugh.
That feels good.
You know what I always thought would feel good is if you, you know, is like after you
you have sex with a woman and you could just leave it in there and just go pee.
If the girl could just like absorb the P, I always thought that would feel
really good. Yeah, yeah, you just don't have to leave. That's how you make a
special kind of baby. You stay in the in the girl, a different kind of baby is
made that way. You just pee all of your pee into her. Yeah, that's how the X-Men
And then she could tell you if you're dehydrated or not.
(laughter)
Hey, you can't see.
In the pores.
Yeah.
She can just feel it.
The pee comes out of the pores and if it's like,
it looks like yellow Gatorade.
It fills up the white of her eyes.
The more yellow it gets,
the more you need to drink some water.
Yeah.
What else would feel really good?
Like a back massage.
something that you've never felt. A back massage from an expert. I bet honestly...
Can you imagine... Oh, that'd probably... No, that'd feel too good. What if a rhino or a
hippo or an elephant had... You know when someone steps on your back, right? What if one of
them did that just the perfect amount with those big circular fucking legs? Wouldn't
That feels so good.
- You know what would feel good is if my toe was fine.
- Your toe is fine.
- Really?
- You painted it for attention.
- Did you see it?
Did I show you it?
- Yeah, you painted it purple.
- Yeah, it's completely purple.
- For complete attention.
- My shit's completely purple
and it was such a non-accident.
Like it looked, it should have, I should have been fine.
- You were involved so it was a nonce accident.
- Nope.
- Damn.
- Shoes.
- It's those shoes I bought.
I bought those, you guys are size 11s, right?
- Yeah.
Does anyone have any better skate shoes I could trade?
- Me?
- Me, personally, not a fan of the Adidas Tyshawn Lowe's.
- Dude, those are the ugliest, stupidest shoes
you've ever owned.
- What, the black ones?
- Yeah.
- The Tyshawn's?
I don't know why you have those.
- It's 'cause they were the only things they had at the shop.
- And they didn't work?
- They're, I think they're just a size too small, yeah.
Or like an inch too small.
- Do you wanna use my clogs?
- I don't know.
If anyone, if you, listen, if you're in the New York area
and you have new or equal to or greater skate shoes,
size 11, 11 and a half, if you wanna trade,
if you wanna trade somebody with greater,
it's called psychic driving.
- How's a psychic driving?
- That's not psychic driving at all.
- It's called, and you're gonna give me your shoes
and you're gonna give me your shoes
and you're gonna give me your shoes.
- This is kind of working.
- Yeah.
- Have you guys ever pulled up one of those
sissy hypno videos, see if it works on you?
I watched a bunch of those ones that were like,
you can find them on YouTube.
- Makes you cry.
(laughing)
Cameron's watched a bunch of those.
- No, that are like the ones that are like hypnosis to,
it'll be like hypnosis to make you the joker
or like hypnosis to make you handle spicy foods.
And then it's like a spiral and it's like,
and they say like, I love spicy foods.
Spicy foods are not that spicy to me.
(laughing)
And it's like plays a bunch of those.
- I do think that I might be the most susceptible
to hypnosis of any person in the world? I'm not. I can't shut up. I can't. The thing
that you need in your brain to shut off and become hypnotized. Intelligence. Oh my God,
pound it out. Damn. The thing, I can't stay on one thought. I think I have a genetic advantage
to hypnosis. So people have tried to hypnotize you multiple times and it hasn't worked? Is
that what you're telling me? Yes. Name one time you were attempted to be fucking hypnotized
asshole because I will dude I will right now I'll pay a thousand dollars to get an
expert hypnotist in here right now to prove you wrong. All right then let's do
it. We're gonna get me hypnotized. I will fuck we will we will rent do you rent?
You rent a hypnotist. You can hire one for like an event we could throw like a party.
Three man party. Yeah. With the hypnotist. We'll see if somebody can hypnotize Patrick.
I think half of hypnosis in events like that like it's like oh we're gonna get
get everyone on the stage.
- I will say.
- That is like, if I was on the stage
and the guy is like, I'm going to hypnotize this guy
right now and it wasn't working,
I would still do the things 'cause I don't want
that guy to feel like an asshole.
- You think hypnotism's fake?
- Yes.
- Whoa.
- But I think if you're on the stage
and the hypnotist has to do that shit.
- I think hypnotism is pretty provably real.
- No.
- Yeah.
they've been doing it for since the caveman. Yeah, you're on stage.
You're on the back. Yo back when they started doing hypnotism, yo, they didn't
have they didn't have stages back then. Yeah, so it's not it wasn't a party. I
will say I think that I would never have what's happening. I would never have a
hypnotist or a magician do their act for anything less than ten people because I
feel like you're in danger because like there's not enough people to like yeah
yeah he's got like exactly fucking powers like he's if he's a hypnotist if there's
a hypnotist and there's just us three in here with him he could hypnotize all
three of us so it's like when you it's like we'd be like exactly you have to
think yeah then nobody's gonna stop us we don't have an extra you need a guy
who's wearing those Eclipse glasses so he's immune to yeah or like cotton in
his ears or something or yeah he has he's caught in his ears but he doesn't you
need someone to just the hypnotist can't see it can't can't tell and the hypnotist
tries to hypnotize the three guys to fuck each other that guy starts to go along
with it and then he's like psych and he punches the hip maybe trying to
hypnotize me but for my own production I've brought somebody who's completely
deaf and blind to just sit here so there's a like they had a hypnotist show
at my high school they like brought in a hypnotist for like a fundraiser and I
I just remember thinking like everyone here is just doing this for attention.
This is not real.
You were jealous.
I was jealous.
You were jealous of the hypnotist.
I think.
Hypnotist.
One of the.
Maybe.
Maybe I was.
I don't know.
I was probably jealous that they got to experience magic.
One of the.
You were jealous that they were controlling a room of high schoolers.
One of the funniest things I read or ever read was like one time my, we got like a Christmas
card like like newsletter type thing from one of my younger siblings, like high
school friends who had like a super rich family, like insanely rich, and it was
like this, like long, like letter of everything that they did that year, and
it was like it was like during cove it they went to like some like tropical
islands to like where they're like writing about how much a great time they
had and they're like and they're like and we had like a fantastic birthday
party and we even hired a mentalist.
In 2021, hiring a mentalist.
What is it?
I don't even know what a mentalist is.
Is a British magician.
Okay.
Yeah, it's mental.
Yeah.
Look at this, it's mental.
I'm a mentalist.
Look at this, it's fucking mental.
Yeah, my fingers have formed a chain.
There goes my thumb and it's back.
I've got your nose.
- Oh, I've got your nose in it.
- Yeah.
Mentalism is a performing art in which
its practitioners, known as mentalists,
appear to demonstrate highly developed
mental or intuitive abilities.
- Yeah, it's like the-- - I think I might be one.
- It's literally like a mentalist thing,
like a mentalist show is literally like,
write down a number, any number, now add two,
now add, you know, like doing that whole thing,
it's like, well, was that your number?
Here's-- (laughs)
Think of a number, okay, I'm gonna do a mentalist thing
to you right now, think of a number right now.
- One.
- Multiply that by one.
- Now write down your number on a piece of paper.
- One.
- Is it the same number you started with?
- Absolutely, this guy's a fucking mentalist.
- Yep.
- I think mentalism is more,
mentalism's like, it's like hypnosis and like--
- All right, let me try mentalism on Patrick real quick.
- Okay.
- Hey Patrick.
he got me no listen can i can send you a plea got he got my name first try patrick
okay it's just a little bit of a man who's just using your time you're the
mentalist looking right into your eyes okay
what color panties
just think about it don't tell black don't tell me don't tell me
are they black
yes home
what color
is your ass hair
black
is a completely black
your shirts black tail
to triple my shirts black
triple black attack
for this is
i think i'm doing a rate of how much i think i'm trying to
okay
here
where in the world
Am I supposed to say something?
Try again, all right, try you to tell me what you're doing. I do something
think about
your first memory. Okay, as a child, all right, your first memory that you can
remember, okay, and think about it really hard and also being born. Okay,
it's not being born. It's going to be past that. Okay, inside my mom's
- Her what?
- I didn't want to say what it was, I was inside of.
- Wait, what did you, your mom's what?
What are you talking about?
Her what?
- Her body.
- Her butt?
- Her body?
What part?
- Stomach.
- What?
(laughing)
Okay.
And in this memory, what color are your panties?
- Don't have none.
- Invisible.
- All right.
- See through.
- Let me take that.
- I don't think you're doing--
you're immune to mentalism. You must be. I think that I might Google how to do
mentalism easy right now. They should be a duolingo. They're probably, you know what,
I bet there's a wiki how. Probably. And that might be useful for us. How to do
mentalism. Okay. Oh yeah, no, it is exactly that. Ten mentalism tricks and how to do
them like a pro from Mantelligence.com. Mantelligence, wow. I like that website
name. Mantelligence. All right so this is really quick just for my scoreboard if
there's a woman intelligence. Here's what's really cool about mentalism tricks it can
absolutely and pretty easily be learned by any man. Wow. But women not so much.
Are these like mentalism tricks to pick up women? I would say mentalism is
is magician plus pickup artist. Yeah yeah definitely. Hypnosis. And there's that
show the mentalist okay that did a lot they talk about that show at the first
okay the first thing here mental list yeah Wow holy fuck now before we get
into these mind-reading tricks I want to note they're just tricks so just keep
that in mind all right they're just tricks okay here's the first trick so
maybe I'll read it out and then one of us can practice it yeah right yeah okay
gray elephants from Denmark this is a simple trick that you can do with any
any audience even just a single friend that's perfect okay. We plug my ears up
now okay good idea now ask that audience to think of a number between one and ten
and multiply it by nine then ask them to add the digits together and subtract
five now here's the crazy part that only you know no matter what the original
number was keep it keep them in their vinyl answer will be for it's just a
funny quirk of math cool right next ask the audience to assign each letter of
the alphabet a number a is one b is to see is three etc tell them to stop when
they reach their number. What you already know is four, so the letter D. Now ask
them to think of a country that begins with their letter, and because there
aren't many countries that start with D, most people will choose Denmark. And then
when you ask them to choose an animal with the next letter of the
alphabet, which for everyone will be E, most people will come up with elephant.
Ask them to think of the color of the animal. Finally, guess out loud that
they're thinking of grey elephants from Denmark. Amazing and simple, right? But
how does it work? Well, I won't say how it works yet. Okay, so try it on. Try it on.
I have to try it? I can't remember all that. Me neither. You have it in front of
you know I'll read it Patrick think of a number between one and two gray
elephants from Denver what I read read so many instructions so long so boring
funny and you so fucking ruined it completely what you look through your
fingers at boobs when your mom tells you not to huh when you watch movies what
- What just happened?
- You put the hands on your thighs
and then you look through your fingers.
You're a piece of shit.
- That was a mentalism trick.
- That was not mentalism.
- Here's a mentalism trick.
- That was a mentalism trick.
- Caleb, Caleb.
- I knew I would make Caleb angry.
- Caleb.
- Mentalism.
- Mentalism is not just you do something.
- Yes it is.
- That's kind of what it is.
- Oh yeah.
- That's what most things are.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
- Oh wait, I wanna do a mentalism on camera.
- No, let me do it.
- I wanna do a mentalism on camera.
- No, I don't want you to do one.
I want to do one from here. I didn't get to do a single one yet. I get to do a
single one. You hold you his soul out of his head. That's not a lism that
sorcery and we found do it on me, whatever I'll be a fucking victim like I
am every okay. We'll just be quiet now. So the trick can work. Think of a shape
like a square, but not a square
okay.
You got you got it now. Think of another shape around the first shape,
okay, and it says amaze them by telling the shapes they were thinking of the
triangle inside the circle.
Nope
like a square, but not I just did rectangle. Why would I do triangle? It
makes no sense.
This is it says, while you here's a pro tip with this trick, while you ask the
person to think of shit, oh, I forgot to I'm going to start it over. Okay, this
is the I realized I miss part of the instruction. This will this one. I'll do
I'm going to Patrick this time, because you're a yeah okay Patrick think of a
shape that's like a square, but not a square
way circle that's part of it. That's what it says you're not supposed to say
it and then think of a shape around that shape triangle and then it's a circle on
a triangle. This is called subliminal programming part of the thing was that
you draw the shape. That's what it is. Well, you ask the person to think of
shapes discreetly trace the shapes in the air with your hands, subconsciously
planting the image in their mind. It's called subliminal program. Okay, wait,
wait, think of a shape. That's not a square.
Okay,
now think of a shape around that shape.
I
just swastika
- What the hell?
You drew it!
I didn't draw that!
I drew a rhombus and a trapezoid!
- Yeah, that wasn't right.
That was a complete swastika.
- Okay, I have a new mentalistic trick.
- That was a rhombus and a trapezoid, you dumbass!
- What are you talking about?
You did this and then this.
- No.
- Yes, you did.
- That's a rhombus and then that's a trapezoid.
- You did, what do you mean that and that?
- This.
- Look at, he did it again!
- I didn't draw a swastika in the air.
- You did.
- No, I drew a rhombus and a trapezoid.
- That's fucking, you understand how--
- Your mind is going, look,
but this mentalism trick does not work.
We've disputed, it's caused too much, it's caused--
- Here's the new mental, I just came up
with a mentalism trick.
- Okay, then go ahead and promise me
that you won't do it to me. - Okay, think of a guy
in the room that's not me or you,
that's in the room right now.
- Guy?
- Think of-- - I can't think of one.
- Oh my God. - Jesus Christ.
- Whoa. - Our Lord and Savior.
- What's up? - That's it.
- Pound that, pound that out, what's up?
Nope get it get it. No okay, okay all right and okay yeah and then think of
what he's sitting in.
Were you thinking of Patrick in a chair? I actually fucking was him that's
fucked up, but that's that was a trick. I've turned around. I think that that
mentalism trick works. Think of your favorite color. Okay, now tell me what
your favorite color is red. So now think of your favorite color thinking of it is
it red. Yeah, yeah, holy shit man. Wow think of your favorite food spaghetti.
Do you want to eat that? No. I just ate it before. Does it make you hungry, thinking
about it? No. Have you eaten it before? No. No? My favorite food is Gobstoppers.
Have you eaten Gobstopper? No. Not the one I'm thinking of. Mine's the chocolate cake
from Matilda. Huh? Oh, the chocolate cake from Matilda? That is a deep, dark
chocolate cake and I never ate it before that cake was so deliciously black I
wanted to that's what I was kind of a mentalist she forced him to eat the
whole cake Oh boo-hoo I have to eat a whole cake plus I'm the fat kid of the
movie yeah who cares I know you got to eat the best
cake of all time yeah I don't know what he was like a short
character right now here's Torta sorry what Schwartz Schwartz relative the
Kirsch Torta the fuck is that Schwartz read the Kirsch Torta what is that will
tell me instead of just saying it?
Schwarzfeld, you're stupid.
Is this a mentalist trick to me?
Where you mentally fucking annoy me?
Look at that cake.
Is this the cake from Matilda?
The cake from Matilda.
Yeah, it looks super good.
It looks so delicious. Look at that.
Oh, and that kid ate poop.
Oh my god, that's probably the best looking cake in the world.
Is it kind of insinuated
that there's poop in that cake?
I feel like that's a fair assumption.
assumption a little bit. I don't think there's supposed to be poop in the
Bruce cake. The Bruce cake? That's his name. The cake's named after him? Well, I
guess the kid's name is Bruce. Well, it's probably because it's Trunchbull's
personal cake, and he steals a slice. Yeah. Oh, true. So, it's whatever is in
there, she likes to eat too. So, she's, I mean, and she's a naughty bitch. Yeah.
She's probably got some poop in it. Absolutely. And with a name like
Miss Trunchbull. Yeah. Oh, it says at one point Miss Trunchbull even mentions that
the cook's sweat and blood went into this cake. That's oh yeah, that's what I
remember as a kid is that it really grossed me out that she says that. Yeah.
Even though there's nothing inherently scary about it besides the blatant child
abuse.
Well, hey, if eating a chocolate cake is child abuse, abuse me. Yeah, abuse the
fuck out of me, mom. Come on, fucking abuse me.
I do wish that I'd gotten more abuse as a kid. I'd probably be so good at
something. Yeah, that's what I mean. Like all of the best people at anything got
fucking owned. I'd probably be so good at piano or something. Also a lot of the homeless people also got abused as kids.
There's two ways to go. They got abused as adults. Maybe you have a
sweet spot. They got abused by society. Like whatever the Michael Jackson spot is, that's
that's going to make you a fucking brilliant musician and artist.
Yeah.
I mean, I remember I watched, there's like a biopic about the Jacksons as a kid and I
remember seeing that on VH1 and there's just a scene where it's like Joe Jackson makes
them go outside and get the stick to, they have to pick out the stick to beat people
up.
Oh yeah, that's a common, classic thing.
I remember seeing that and being like, damn.
Do kids ever get abused and then grow up to become like brilliant
mathematicians or scientists or is it all artists?
All artists.
Albert Einstein.
He wasn't abused, he was an abuser.
That's true, he abused the world when he created the E=mc2.
Can you imagine being the Jackson's like neighbor growing up and just hearing
just like beautiful singing and kids getting the shit beat out of them all
day long?
Yeah.
It's like hey, I like the singing but the screaming, the screaming I hate.
- I hate it. - What do you do
without all the screaming, dude?
I'm real, listen.
- And where am I, you're completely destroying my tree.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- There's no sticks in the backyard anymore.
- I can't even, I have no kindling,
'cause you're making your kids go out there
and get all my sticks. - And I'm not sure
it's worth it, okay?
Can I borrow a cup of milk?
Your kids have beautiful voices,
and stop burning them with the stove, please.
- Rockin' Robin, I love that.
- I bet-- - Now Dad Stop It,
I don't wanna hear that. - I bet even their cries
screams for help were actually beautiful. Oh yeah yeah I mean how do you think he
got that beautiful falsetto voice? Yep yeah that's where he developed the
the leaning technique he's leaning out of the way. Yeah he's leaning forward.
He's leaning yeah to avoid the spanking. Yeah yeah maybe if he's going in the
perfect spanking position. No because he was escaping it. All right yeah. How many
Jackson kids are there? There's like a hundred. I think there might be five now
that I think about it. No, no, because there's a,
because there's Latoya and Janet. So I think there's probably like seven or eight.
Was Janet not in the Jackson five? No, no, no, no. The Jackson five was all boys.
I don't know. Yeah. What do you mean? It's, it's, it's five girls.
No, it's Tito. Have you not heard the songs? It's five girls. Tito Jackson,
Michael, Jermaine, Charizard, and Bulpy.
Yeah, Bulpy Jackson, yeah.
Bulpy Jackson, he's saying all the low notes.
Janet is that slut from the Super Bowl, right?
Yeah.
Ruined Justin Timberlake's career.
Tried to destroy a good man who wears a suit and tie.
He wears, he loves his suit and tie.
(laughing)
- He's a gentleman.
- That's such a funny fucking song.
- Yeah.
- Suit and tie.
- Dude, so fucking--
- What a boss, dude.
- Yeah.
- Especially making that when it,
like in like 2013 or whatever.
- Yeah.
- So like that, if he did come out with that song
in like 2004, I feel like that would have been way better
because like the guys at the time who were like,
like guys who would wear like vests to clubs and shit.
- Yeah.
- That makes sense.
- He, it kind of started that thing.
of like yeah fedora vest guy fedora vest like flare jeans yeah and like he's a
beast bro dude you know everyone got mad at him this weekend cuz there's like
some video of him like performing and he's like dancing and he just looks like
a dad now oh yeah is it not supposed to dance at his performances now
years old who gives a fuck America tried to ruin Janet Jackson for this man it is
like yeah all the way around America did you have you heard sexy what do you mean
America ruined you he her fucking tit flew out of her she wanted to pull her
thingy out she wanted to pull her thingy out and the world said no what's it put
that world said put that thingy back where you found that's probably one of
my earliest memories I think that's my remember I remember it too I think
that's the first boob I ever saw I didn't see it but I remember my uncle
Kevin standing up and going that's a fucking pity dude that was a that was a
That's a great day. I remember I think my great grandpa died the day after the day
before
and that's the only reason I remember. That's a great day to use. Yeah. I saw my
first boob in my grandpa. Dude, my great grandpa sucked. Everyone hated him, bro.
So it was like one, two great things happening, boobs on TV, looking. Grandpa
does. Remember, there's like kids upstairs. They probably just heard me
scream that's a fucking titty yeah. This is going to be their first memory
a monster in the basement yeah, that's scary guy in the basement.
I wonder what they feel spider webs on I'm like a monster
the spider monster in the
two weeks ago. He was yelling about eight legged bug.
You're an actual fucking spider monster.
I think subliminally I accidentally made myself get a spider tattoo when I wrote that beautiful
song.
I think you might be some kind of spider man.
No, that doesn't sound right.
Man spider.
What's that, there's that Cure song?
Is that song by the Cure where he says like, "The spider man is having me for dinner"?
What?
Yeah.
It's like having you over?
- Yeah, Peter Parker's having you over?
- Yeah, that's my fucking dream play date.
- Well, that song came out after Spider-Man
had been in the public conscious for years.
- The public conscious?
- The public conscious. - The public conscience.
- I feel like now more than ever,
I feel like there's a grace period in the past
where you could say Spider-Man
and there's a benefit of the doubt
that you mean a Spider-Man monster,
like a half-Spider, half-Man.
I don't think maybe superheroes were as popular.
- Sounds like a lullaby. - I think they were nerds.
Yeah, right when I realized with fright that the spider-man is having me for dinner tonight
That is such a scary line. That is too scary on candy-stripe legs the spider-man comes. Oh, then yeah
Yeah, I love the cure so much. I don't even know what the cure is. It's a band
I don't know where they act out there a band that dress up like Edward Scissorhands
like girls but they sing about boy problems. Yeah it's oddly weird. Yeah that
was that's so funny like when I when I was growing up I thought that The Cure
was like that band Christian Death. Like I feel like in my head like I was like
like the way that my parents and shit talked about it was like yeah only like
emos who like dark stuff listen to them and then I listen to The Cure. Yeah
it's like exactly you think they're like they're like MCR or something. Yeah exactly.
You think like I actually swag as fuck like have you like like what's that fucking uh
like that was that Christian death song where he's like in a sea of incest like I thought
it was like shit like that like I thought they were gonna sing about weird crazy shit
but actually said it's legal to have a band called Christian death yep I bet you if that
guess what if that band was called Muslim or atheist death I bet they'd be banned in
every fucking country in the world. They'd be banned everywhere. Yep. And guess what?
Guess what else they say in there? What? First line of the song Romeo's Distress. No, I don't
want to hear it. Well, I can't say what they say. Why? It's the worst swear of all. They
say the worst cuss possible? They say the worst cuss possible and it's about a, it's
on someone's lawn. No way. They say the F word? They pull a... Nope. Marilyn Manson did
that to say yeah shit that is funny to do somebody starts being like saying the
n-word you say like can we just not cuss and you didn't leave the cussing you're
saying the ultimate swear can you just not fucking do a super cuss yeah there
is cusses and then they're super cusses got GD is a super cuss yeah yeah all
right GD is just it's worse dude it's taking the fucking Lord's name in vain
guys I need to get to the list oh yeah we need to stop listen we need us to know
No, we didn't. That would barely count as a list. Okay, don't try and cheat the
listeners. All right. Here, because I don't know about you, but I don't think
a mentalism trick is going to hold up much longer. Yeah. I think that maybe we
should kind of stop doing this kind of, you know, childish mentalism, pseudoscience
kind of bullshit. I'm honestly fucking over juvenile shit. Yeah, and I might want
to get a little more mature. That's why I was talking about music. I just want to be
immature and kind of
mature. I'm less interested in potty mouth. I won't even say be a say I'll say
gobbledygook. Do people actually think that PP poopoo shit fart asshole fucking
come piss balls tits nipples mouth tits ass and shit piss on my ass and shit on
my face is actually interesting to listen to. I sincerely I'm not I hate that
I'm not laughing, but it's actually disgusting. That's why I've brought a
more kind of mature and educated type of list today. Top 10 weirdest facts.
Because I've been into facts lately. I don't know about you guys. You are a bit of a factoid.
Yeah, well no factoid is actually, what would you call someone
who's into facts? I'm more of a scholar. I would refer to myself as such.
I'm more of a schooler because I love to go to school. I love school too.
yeah school I won't hey I won't say it's it's bussin because that's you know
that's a bit childish to say. I would say it's excellent. You know in women these days I would say
I'd say yo my sandwich excellent excellent mm-hmm I would say that our
past behaviors were quite elementary absolutely and sophomoric yeah to say to
say the least. Completely prehistoric. To say the least on the matter yeah oh my god medieval yeah
downright medieval. To say the least. To say the least. Our past behavior definitely very
very childish. To say the least. Yeah preschool-ish. Preschool-esque. Yeah to say the least.
To say the very least. To say the very least. So give me a fact. Okay number one
number one weirdest fact. More than nine hundred and fifty Beatles can live in a
sloth's fur at one time. Wow and and that is not the musicians. That's far more than
than I anticipated.
- Yeah, I thought at the very least--
- My estimations would be greatly lesser.
- Greatly lesser.
- Greatly lesser, to say the least.
- I would have had lesser expectations,
but actually it more to my expectations.
- Well, speaking of lesser and greater comparisons,
we have a comment here from a fellow fact scholar
that says, "That's still less than the amount
"of beetles in my bed."
- Oh, they're having a laugh.
- This person needs, I mean, we have to take it
at face value, Patrick.
not everybody's as juvenile and goofy as we used to be.
- That's true.
- You know, maybe they're actually telling the truth
and they're in dire need of--
- They could live in an impoverished country.
- An exterminator.
- Yeah.
- Gosh, that bed must be mighty uncomfortable.
- Absolutely.
- Uncomfortable.
- I can hardly imagine laying my head down at night
to find it is hitting over 900 beetles.
- Over 900?
Over 900, yeah.
yes, greater than nine hundred lesser than nine thousand. Yep, here's another
comment from venomous killing machine. I have a scary yet advanced username.
That is why slots are slow, so an animal scientist here. I guess I like since
they're weighed down by all the beetles. Yeah, lots of beetles wait. At that
point, aren't they like it's like a jellyfish like they're just a bunch of
shit moving as one. They're just a beetle. They're only beetles. Yeah, at
a jellyfish.
Like a jellyfish?
You know a jellyfish is a bunch of little organisms together.
It's not just one thing.
That's not true.
Yeah it is.
What are you talking about?
Jellyfish is a bunch of stuff.
Everything's a bunch of stuff.
You don't have to say that about anybody.
No but jellyfish is a bunch of little things.
I'm a bunch of stuff.
He's about to lose his scholarly card.
I have my feet, my knees, my balls and penis.
Look it up.
At Google are jellyfish a bunch of things?
Of course everything's a bunch of things.
That's simply an elemental fact of the universe.
Nope.
I'm going to prove you wrong.
Okay, it seems we're having a bit of spirited debate.
We're having a fact-off.
A fact-off is most fascinating to my sensibilities.
Well, what doth...
What doth thou say?
What doth thy handheld device...
says it's not a fish yeah yeah it's an invertebrate it's an invertebrates I
think you're a fool he called me an invertebrate what a childish insult he's
he's dragging himself down into the mud with these kind of schoolyard insults
that I'm far above and I will not be retaliating in color I know a sea slug
maybe I'm not a scholar it can a derm or anything of the maybe I'm not a scholar
dollar, but a writer and an artist.
Interesting.
An artist.
Hard to get much more childish than that.
Nuh-uh.
And I'm past fist bumps now.
We do it.
You're past handshakes.
We're doing handshakes instead of fist bumps now.
Okay, well I'm actually throwing up different kinds of gang signs with one hand at one time.
Look at that.
How barbaric.
It's not.
You think gangs are barbaric?
Wow, hold on.
You think it's actually barbaric to be in an awesome gang like me?
I think it's barbaric to move your hand in any way other than on a calculator.
Also, I'm the writer and the singer of the gang and you still think it's fucking barbaric
that I'm making music?
You're a music-- I'm an engineer.
Your music is more like dissonant noises.
You're about to get dissonant noises.
I just made a train.
You didn't make a train, dude.
I'm an engineer.
You're just being a faker.
He built an elevator.
You're just a faker, okay?
He's not-- Whoa, whoa.
You are out of control with the insults.
It's-- Listen, I know we're doing a thing-- No, I'm not, idiot.
But this is this is beyond. This is beyond the pale
You're beyond the pale. You're just damn white. Oh my god. Oh wait. I'm an engineer. You're not an engineer
He's an engineer stop saying he's not an okay to prove it do make anything
We couldn't even get through one fact without going back to being childish. I made that I think I've changed my ways
He didn't make that I
Made that you didn't
I put the lens on the camera.
- That's not making anything.
- I made the lens bigger.
- What's the next fact?
Are we done?
- Speaking of, if you are the tenant of the--
- I've grown out of my childish artistic phase.
- If you are the tenant of my old apartment,
I know you stole my camera lens.
I got it delivered to your house
and I asked if I could have it back
and you said, "I saw it in the hallway,
but it was definitely opened and it wasn't.
And I have not contacted the eBay seller.
So this is a message to the tenant of my old apartment.
I have declared war on you.
- Now talk about barbaric.
- I'm declaring war on you right now.
That was a $30 lens that I bought for a camera
and I'm declaring war.
and we can end the episode here.
Continue camera.
What's the next fact number two is the Eiffel Tower gets repainted every seven
years. That's not true. It's not true. Okay. We would see the paint. Yeah.
Yep. Well, it says it says here's a comment from a fellow scholar very
effort pushing indeed. I was thinking the same thing that is very very
insanely effort-pushing of them yeah it's normal to repaint this tower if
people wouldn't repaint it this tower will lose its color Eiffel Tower is
useless to be honest many people from Paris hate it what color is the Eiffel
Tower gray no with a certain scene it's iron color right it's like brown it's
made out of copper right and that's why it's green because when they bring it to
America when they brought it to green the Eiffel Tower the Eiffel Tower used to
be copper thing of the Statue of Liberty. No, no statue of Liberty was made out of
green play-doh. No the green the Eiffel Tower they didn't bring the Eiffel Tower
to America it's in Paris. That's not oh it's the color of the Eiffel Tower is a
color called Eiffel Tower Brown. I knew it was brown I'm a genius. It's called
Eiffel Tower Brown. It says since 1968 the choice has been a fairly neutral
color made up of three shades of brown called Eiffel Tower Brown. Oh they do
they change the color of it over the years.
Wow, look at this.
In the 1800s it was red and then it turned yellow.
And now it's...
Look at...
Why'd they turn it brown?
What the fuck?
It was yellow?
The red and yellow look so much better than the brown.
What the fuck?
Is there any pictures of that?
Here's a painting of it as red.
Yeah, it's called...
They painted the Eiffel Toilet...
It was...
Eiffel Toilet.
toilet yeah they painted the Eiffel Tower yellow and brown because no don't even
don't even don't go say that take it down we're done with that kind of come up
with some other reason why because you have to finish your sentence because
those are the bronze medals that's sophisticated say something about gold
and bronze don't I see your eyes I stop thinking about a toilet you don't say
anything about why did they do it yellow because you burn come on come on you got
this is when someone becomes an Eiffel tap no no I'm not gonna say because when
someone becomes an Eiffel Tower you put the thing that makes yellow in their
brown I'm not gonna say that good don't say as long as you don't say that then
we're fine that would be and plus it's not even that well thought out yeah who
knows what because it's a full tower me when when someone becomes doing the
Eiffel Tower that's what you're doing the Eiffel Tower as a as a sex position does
not really mean a sex either but it can it can definitely but it doesn't see
that's why it's not that's why it's juvenile yeah you could let it fly but
The fact that there's so many caveats that you can't really do it.
I hate caveats.
Me too.
I fucking hate caveats.
Yeah.
The fact that there's so many caveats is just, I mean, I just, you know, I want to apologize.
Thank you.
That's very adult of you.
But I don't apologize to the people I'm declaring war on.
Number three, is there are about three pounds, 1.4 kilograms, kilograms, I apologize, of
bacteria living in your stomach.
I have way more than that, I think.
I have 60 or 70 pounds of bacteria.
Yeah, I'm all bacteria. Yeah, I'm a bunch of stuff isn't aren't you supposed to have bacteria in your stomach?
And yeah, he's taking care all this cheeseburger gut flora. Mm-hmm. Isn't that a cool name? Yep, and you have
Biome, yeah, you have a whole biome in there and if you drink
Really nasty thick yogurt. I love it. I love that stuff so much me too. Oh my god
I mean, it's basically just fucking damn fear. Yeah, so good for I always said key for somebody told me it's not pronounced
way it's pronounced kaffir never in my life am I gonna call it I know I that
was the first time I ever said it and I feel I feels wrong it is wrong I have so
much they call me kaffir Sutherland that was actually pretty airtight that was
honestly the wordplay that you just exhibited I'm like Mo Rocca yes and PR
humorous - Mo Rocca mm-hmm okay here's a comment from somebody we've seen before
still less than the number of bacteria on my bed.
This person has quite a disgusting bed. I mean you have to take it at the face
value. Their bed is the disgust quotient must be off the chart. Damn near
unsleepable this bed. Believe me. Absolutely.
Number four mullets are illegal in Iran.
Now this
now this just makes no sense. They've lost me okay.
Iran has officially gone too far. Iran you have gone too far. Well I have good
news. And I have
we're declaring a war. I'm going to invade you and I'm going to kill every single person in your country.
Guys before we decide on this it says they were illegal thirty years ago I'm from
Iran and I have a mullet. Oh okay.
Alright well that's fine Iran. Okay I take back the war. We're gonna, I'm not gonna
invade you and kill everyone. I take back all the wars I've started. Here's a comment. So Elvis couldn't have flushed himself
to Iran now that's just funny so Elvis tried to flush away I died on the toilet
yes okay so this is he got his butt got sucked out like in that story but yeah
yeah like guts yeah it was this is this is a perfect example of a non sequitur
which is just something that's just so weird it has to make you laugh yeah
that's basically non sequitur is probably my favorite kind of humor say
Okay, speaking egg, speaking of non sequitur
hello.
Hello, my name is an egg. My name is egg and two eggs. I'm three eggs old.
I'm hungry for four eggs,
scrambled
scrambled eggs. What's this next one here? It's me a speaking of non
sequitur odontophobia is the fear of teeth.
Okay, that's suitably random for the midpoint on this list. I mean like the
sequence t fear of teeth in what way I'm afraid of teeth of teeth being shot into
me by some kind of tooth gun. I would be afraid of all my teeth having a disease
that killed me to my that might scare me. You're just showing me a picture of
Mo Rocca non sequitur the master of non sequitur non sequitur Patrick actually is
the master of non-sequitur. No, no, no, no, no. Mo Rocca is. I would say that you are. Yeah, you
definitely are. Yeah. Check this out. You spent two minutes of the episode talking
about a package that you didn't get delivered to your house. It got delivered
to my old house and they... Master of non-sequitur. It's not non-sequitur, that's
an anecdote. It's a non-sequitur. It's a non-sequitur anecdote. Because it has no
sequitur to my life. I think we could maybe have some interesting discussion on number six
perhaps. Number six fact is a Korean man married a pillow. Why does what is the
his what is his nationality matter to me? Well that's what someone says here.
Why does it have to say Korean? It's just weird for anybody to marry a
pillow. But that's what I call desperate. They must have had some very soft pillow
babies with heads. It's just making dolls. I think I've seen a picture of this guy
and he looked pretty happy. I'm not too upset about this fact basically. Yeah
either it's definitely it's certainly a fact no questionally effect what are you
doing I'm sorry I'm really busy right now you are just useless do they do the
blowjob with that open space in the pillows cover you this is just I don't
like this yeah it's you you have to chill no this is the worst is my
You're ruining it. You're ruining it. You're showing pictures on a podcast.
You're so stupid. I hate sleeping, so I hate pillows. That's probably the bed
person. Oh yeah. Yeah, they probably... I have one thousand pillows in my bed.
Yeah. Now yeah, here's a comment that I think gets the wrong idea from this
fact. Ew, Korean is weird. Yeah, that's the... That's not the weird part of the
fact. Yeah, they stopped... A Korean man. Whoa, what a crazy fact. What a strange
That's Korean men, oh my god.
Number seven, a girl ate nothing but chicken nuggets for 15 years.
Have you guys seen that guy who he, the video--
The big mac guy?
No, the video that YouTube tries to make everyone watch that's like, if you, this guy eats mac
and cheese every meal and has for 20 years or whatever.
No, I have not.
I haven't seen that.
I just--
I watched that video and I got--
I think it's so made up.
just literally just like made that up so that Vice would make a video about him.
That guy I mean I did see as soon as I saw the guy I did I watched that video
and as soon as I saw the guy I got so angry I shut it off just just by how he
was talking. Yeah. I could tell that he talks with the mac and cheese in his
mouth and I was hearing the noise in my head of somebody talking with like
Kraft mac and cheese in their mouth like like you know. He does Velveeta he
he may he doesn't do craft yes I was like really cheesy yeah gooey and thick oh I
I do I I'm not gonna say what he's about to vomit he's about to puke yeah I mean
I mean we don't talk about puke many of them sucking your balls with mac and
cheese in his mouth okay I'm imagining that yeah so coming wouldn't that be
be awesome. Same texture, let me so awesome to come.
Here's a comment that sounds like my friend. I'm a five grader and I have a
friend in Raphael and he brings lunch from home every day and he always has
dino nuggies. That's the only thing he's eating for a quarter and a half. The
only thing other than dino chicken nuggets is that he has eight in this
school year is probably a turkey sandwich. Once I wouldn't be surprised
if he broke the record, I ate dino nuggies last night. I actually did too
Really?
Yeah.
Whoa.
My mom gave me a big giant bag of them and I haven't touched them and I didn't feel like
going out to buy food.
Yeah, I was in a very similar situation.
I'm not sure if I've ever eaten dino chicken nuggets in my life.
Really?
Yeah.
They're not so good.
I don't believe you.
I truly don't believe you.
I've eaten chicken nuggets a bunch.
I don't think I ever got, my parents never got the...
Purdue dino chicken nuggets?
No, I've never got the dino chicken nuggets.
Oh, I've never eaten a sandwich.
I never got...
You haven't?
That's very strange.
even like a brand or type of that's like a very large swath of food. That's a fucking
crazy thing to say. I don't know why you would say you haven't eaten a sandwich. I've seen
you eat a sandwich. Yeah, you ate a sandwich right before you recorded it. He's saying
he didn't eat chicken nuggets that are dinosaur shaped. That's exactly what I said. Yeah, but
then you said that you haven't eaten a sandwich. Which is way crazier. Which is way fucking
crazier. Yeah, because we saw you eat one. I've never eaten blue cheese. That's what
you sound like. Okay. What? I don't know what you're trying to do. You've never eaten blue
cheese either? Or a sandwich? I saw you eat blue cheese with the cheese crew. Shh. I don't
I mean well you weren't part of the cheese crew yeah yeah nobody knows the
members of our things because I obviously that nobody knows you wasn't eating
cheese with the cheese crew you were eating cheese of the cheese crew no but
no you were eating no listen you were eating cheese with the cheese the cheese
crew is there who is not any of us yeah we were with them which we are not some
kind of secret cheese crew who rolls around the reason we were eat all the
cheese and the reason that we were eating with the cheese with the cheese
crews you're trying to fight them off you're trying to eat the cheese before
they could eat it that's right the most noble thing you do when the cheese
crews coming around and we're just yeah that's that and that's it the cheese
crews coming around and me and my two friends we're just gonna really quickly
eat all the cheese so that they don't get to have it okay we're kind of an
anti cheese crew all right you have to give us all the cheese
right now the cheese is not safe okay the cheese crew they're like locusts the
cheese is gonna eat the table cheese okay so we don't know I don't see it as
us three who are not the cheese crew okay but we did form because we have similar
heights and builds to the cheese crew and we can fight them these are our anti
cheese crew costumes that we wear yep and there's no and and the pockets on my
pants are not lined with plastic bags so that I can fit more cheese into them
that's right have cheese on the go yep yep I'm just in the army and one of the
The cheese crew members who doesn't look anything like me have maybe does not
definitely does not have a giant butterfly net that they used to capture
the cheese. That's right and there's not a car that has big parmesan wheels.
Mm-hmm yeah and it's not and it's not if there is where is we drive it is not the
cheese crew we drive if you see us driving that car it's because we stole it
from the cheese crew.
- Yep.
- To try and stop them from getting around.
- And when we eat the cheese,
which we're not the cheese crew,
but when we eat the cheese to keep it from the cheese crew,
it doesn't make the sound of a wood chipper
and have cheese filings fly everywhere
as we eat it with our big buck teeth.
- Exactly, and we don't eat the cheese filings afterwards.
- And there's no mouse.
- There's no mouse.
And also a way to stop us is not to put a giant piece
of cheese on a big mouse trap that could fit three friends.
- Yep.
and listen if after we don't live in a hole in a wall, if after we eat the
cheese to keep away the cheese crew, our body is shaped like a giant wedge of
cheese. That's normal. That's what happens when you eat. It doesn't
necessarily mean that we are the cheese crew. No, the cheese that might also
happen in the cheese crew, but it happens to anyone who eats a lot of
cheese. Yeah, the cheese crew.
We don't even know. Yeah, I don't even know we're talking about right now
- Cheese.
- From a wedding.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- A lot.
- A lot of cheese.
- From a wedding.
- From a wedding. - A lot.
- I'm thinking of being--
- Oh, we don't know each other.
No, we just happen to walk up all,
and all snapping our fingers together, right?
- We just happen to perfectly surround this cheese table.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
I see you snap your fingers too.
- Oh, yes, oh, you snap your fingers
while you approach the cheese table?
- Oh, do you like cheese?
- You could say that.
- I kind of like cheese.
- Are you also snapping your fingers?
well, i think i remember we drove to the wedding together, but we don't know each other
no, not that i remember
we were in the same
that was on the big yellow shuttle
yeah, we were in the same car
which was not yellow, it's not called the cheddar bus
oh, i remember, we rappelled into this wedding together
oh, from the ceiling
from the giant yellow helicopter
yeah, i remember now, that's where i recognize you from
do you want to eat this cheese with me?
um, i mean i guess
everybody back the fuck off!
yeah, and then there's yellow caution tape and the all caution. It doesn't say
caution. It's a different shade of yellow yeah and it has holes in it, then
that also be cheese yeah. Oh, and and she has a girl a girl member of the
cheese crew is not named bri. Nope, no and there isn't one until the many
episodes later and it's not she's only there for one episode like the venus de
high low and then the fans demanded that she be cancelled out of the show yeah
and she got her own movie that bombed mm-hmm uh-huh and I'm not a
computers expert speaking of cheese screw and there's not cheddar Bob from
eight mile in the cheese screw the Romans used crushed mouse brains as
toothpaste really yeah that's probably the most horrific thing. Why don't you
sand or toothpaste yeah they should use toothpaste crush up mouse brains have
you seen this guy the carnivore carnivore doctor yeah yeah actually I was watching
a video of him the other day yeah where he's like I don't use shampoo I don't
use toothpaste I smell normal yeah I eat raw liver he does look amazing dude yeah
that's the thing all those guys who eat raw meat all day are so fucking shredded
yeah him liver King huh that's the thing if you go for if you go carnivore diet
though no cheese cheese off the menu well I did see a video yeah he doesn't eat
cheese but he eats fruits and vegetables still he eats yeah yeah cuz yeah I just
come on no city if he's going carnivore boy said he eats six bananas a day that
really eat those and then not eat cheese six bananas this yellow yeah yeah if you
can eat fruits and veggies you can eat cheese this guy's eating six bananas a
day it seems like he's more on the monkey diet yeah that's a good point
what's so the mindset behind his diet is that like he can only eat like raw food
or eats like it's supposed to be like what what people would have eaten 10
- Before, oh, so like before.
- Before agriculture. - He should be eating like,
yeah. - Elephants.
- Does he eat elephant meat?
- He's eating like, I mean, liver is mostly
like the big thing that he advocates for.
- Does he eat elephant meat, though?
- No, he does not eat elephant meat.
- Okay, so, I mean, that's the number one thing
that cavemen were eating, probably.
- Elephants? - Mammoths, yeah.
- Oh, mammoths, yeah. - No.
- They literally, that's all you see a picture of cavemen
they're eating, are woolly mammoths.
I saw a giant have mammoth cheese. I saw that. What? Say that sentence again?
There's a giant and if you go up to him they are hostile but they do have
mammoth cheese. What the fuck are you talking about? Is this from a skyrim?
This is from Skyrim. I saw a giant eat mammoth cheese and if you want to be
strong like a giant, I feel like you still have to eat mammoth cheese. Yo, those giants hit you and they ragdoll into the air.
Funny as fuck. Yeah. Mm-hmm. That's all I did in Skyrim.
I started to run into the giants and go flying. That's how we have to, in the episode, is Patrick saying a giant ate mammoth cheese.
I know, you know how I'm gonna end this episode? That's how he did it. I'm gonna turn
180 degrees this way. I'm gonna go on my computer and I'm gonna play Skyrim.
I'm gonna give you I'm gonna grade your your episode today. Yeah, I'm giving you it
I'm giving you a D - you had a poor performance today. I'm giving you a complete D - you're on your phone
You're talking about mammoth cheese. It was a more showing just a
Dd me you just say it was a family you complained about there's a family that you're trying it was a family
Yeah, actually, I'm gonna give you a d-plus because you scared the people I don't know that I would go
Definitely a C. Definitely see performance. That's I'm not this is not a passing one. This is a bit
This is a this is like a fair enough like next episode. It's like extra credit
zone. That's what you're in okay, because you might semester is coming to an end
right and I'm the hot teacher. My legs are about to uncross on the desk. Okay,
so that's going to be fucking awesome, but don't think about that and I don't
like that. You made a smelling noise right as I said that I was not good.
You can't
smell my thing
drops like the chalk on the ground and like bends over to pick it up and his
twenty kids just like
that's an a minus from
let me see you got a ninety five. Okay, a little bit of credit here right.
This is like a like a bonus question.
- Go to swagpoop.com/skoes,
buy your tickets to Portland and Seattle.
We're gonna be playing at the Crocodile in Seattle.
- Hereafter at the Crocodile.
- Great name. - And then in Portland,
it's at Mississippi Studios.
- Don't get confused, it's not in Mississippi.
- It's not in Mississippi. - It's in Portland.
- It's actually in Portland. - It's weird
because in Portland, most of the neighborhoods,
is a fact I learned. - Are weird.
- They're very weird. - Yep.
- It's weird, a lot of the neighborhoods there
are named after other states.
Yeah, hey and if you look at the map of the states, you notice all the states are
different colors. Yeah, that's people's hair is like in Portland. Yep.
And in Portland, Mississippi Studios has no river next to it. Yeah, so if
you're in SJW, go to swagpoop.com/shows because we're coming to both of the SJW
towns. Yep, we're going to Blue Hairsville. We're going to Blue
Hair, all the Blue Hair capitals of America. Yeah, uh-huh. And so I hope that
you guys have your nose rings all packed because they're basically gonna show
them there yeah uh-huh yep and don't you have if you have a septum ring at the
Portland or the Seattle show tell the bartender that you know Fred from
Portlandia and that you and they will believe you that you know no have no
hole in your nose yeah yeah if you come to the show with a with a septum ring
I'm gonna be up on stage in a cowboy outfit and all of you are going in a cage.
I have a big magnet that I'm gonna use and anyone with facial piercings of all kinds,
it's a neomodium, neododium magnet, I don't remember how to say it.
And also-
The strongest magnet.
So if you guys wanna just come get completely super offended and triggered, come to our
shows 'cause it's actually gonna be insanely offensive and triggering for all you SJWs.
It's gonna be the most triggering thing that's ever happened in Seattle since the Chaz.
It's going to be like probably millions will be triggered and will probably kill themselves.
Yeah.
Honestly.
So if you want to come see that happen, go to swagfood.com/chaz because we're going to
do the most.
It's going to where it's called the Chaz 2.
Yep.
It's called Triggered.
Triggered Much.
We're starting another Chaz.
Yeah.
Colon.
All right.
We're doing a Chaz for just normal Republican guys.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's just going to be all the Republican guys.
It's actually called the Chad now.
All right.
Bye!