Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
- Sing it.
- I'm so scared!
I love it!
- I love it!
- That's a bike if somebody likes a haunted house.
(laughing)
- That's her walking around the haunted house.
- It could be so many things.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Scary movie.
- I'm so scared!
- Or like this is one that could,
this is a multi-purpose one. It could be like, "I am there! I love it!"
That's like anywhere where she likes to be.
It could be a haunted house, but it could be anywhere else.
It's usually, "I'm here," though, right?
"I... Nuh-uh."
It's hard to be there.
Well, that's someone who's astral projecting.
Okay. So, it could work for anything, too, if it's someone who's astral projecting.
You can astral project anywhere, so it works for anything.
What about this one? What about this one? They don't want to be somewhere, and it's,
"I'm not there! I love it!"
- That's better, I think.
- I'm not there, maybe like a tsunami happened in Japan.
- Oh, and you love it 'cause you're not there.
- I love that you're not there.
Like you check in on Facebook
that you're safe after a shooting.
- Yeah, you say, "I'm not there, I love it."
- I'm not there, I love it!
- I do love saying, "I love it," like that.
Just in conversation.
- I love it!
- How are you enjoying your meal, sir?
- I guess I don't care, I love it,
could also just be for use for anything
that you don't care about but love.
no
no yeah give me a situation it wouldn't work in
skimmy situation here birth of child birth i don't care
i love it people who can use trial of the unconditionally i don't care whether
it's a boy or girl i don't care
in denver today what if it's dead
i don't care still about it
i still love those dead
yeah you're weird
the i'd stop loving you and i was really okay that's fine anyway i would think
about a cost i was just about to get a lot of
well the end of it i would say i love it
but you don't care. The important part is the I love it. No, you can't split that
like you can't compartmentalize, you have to take the whole thing. Say the words. I don't care.
The holocaust happened, now say the words. Go ahead, how do you feel about it Cameron?
Cameron Fetter. Cameron Fetter would probably say well every rose has its thorn. Don't speak for him.
What are you doing? He's touching my double knee. You're trying to distract from what you have to say.
what you're talking about what you feel about the Holocaust
I care, I love it.
You love it.
What the fuck?
You didn't think that one through.
I guess we didn't think of other things to say instead of I love it.
I it.
I care, I hate it.
I don't love it.
Oh, there we go.
There we go. Yeah, yeah, we'll be I don't
Love it. Yeah, you have a longer pause
I don't love it. Oh you move
Here I don't look I care don't I?
Basically Charlie Xe X we just prove that you love the holocaust don't I don't
That's what I would do if I went to one of her live performances. I would be asking her questions as she sings this song.
"So tell me Charlie, how do you feel about the Holocaust?" And then have her sing the lyrics.
Then the show gets shorter. "Got her! I got her!" And then I'd get her too.
Yeah. I'd get her. I'm the getter. I'm the getter. I'm the getter grabber.
I'm the getter of Charlie.
call a charlie how do you feel like i'm not sure we have to this performance
she liked it
i love it
now i don't want to get it
okay
charlie get me get charlie what's lile's last name
and charlie get finger
so
yeah
the world
i have
all right well i'll go there
charlie charlie bit my face charlie gets fingered yeah
Charlie get my grabber. Charlie get my finger. Charlie get my finger now.
Freddie get finger. Fred get finger. Fred bit getter. Hey it's Fred. Charlie bit getter.
Oh yeah. I almost got a hey it's Fred shirt. I bet you did. I almost got it the other day.
Was it over $60? Yes. Oh my god. It was $75. No I didn't almost get it.
that would be a cool thing to start wearing now I think. This is the "Hey, it's
Fred" shirt from Hot Topic. I'd wear it. We know you'd wear it. I have an Annoying
Orange shirt. Yeah? Yeah. We were watching the Annoying Orange on my
app the other day. My Annoying Orange app. Yeah, I put it on.
Yeah, there's the Annoying Orange app on Roku and it's got Liam the
leprechaun in it Wow yeah leprechaun Liam there was a he was on April fools there's
oranges and apples and leprechauns yeah and Tobuscus and Tobuscus yeah and he did
something unfortunately he did something bad yeah the annoying orange yeah he
worked at a grocery store yes so see I mean people should have seen it coming
he associated with the annoying orange for years yeah yeah it's like play stupid
games win stupid prizes that's what I say annoying orange yeah I want to know
you're annoying cry you're gonna be annoying play stupid game wins it win
annoying oranges play stupid games watch annoying orange I love stupid games I'm
playing feudalism - and watching a new slap the monkey on stupid that's not a
stupid game you know how to win that game you drag your mouse across the
window and then bring it back to the other side of the test you can win that
no respect first slap the monkey where you slap it really hard yeah I didn't
please yeah so you you take the hand then you drag it off to the left hand
side of the screen keep your mouse held down then drag it all the way back around
and it like charges it up it comes from the other side of the screen and you
kill him or something yeah it goes like Mach 10 and this goes off the screen
- Do you see the result?
- Yeah, and then it goes, "Good time!"
And then it plays that song.
- That's how, every time you hit it, it does that.
- Right, but this time if you hit 'em.
(laughing)
- But this time if you hit 'em, it plays it.
- You need to replay the game.
- When I first--
- You're confused.
- No, we can pull it up, or I guess Flash is over, right?
- Yeah, there's a website where it's up there.
- Yeah, they turned it into something else.
- When I first saw that game--
- Well, if anyone's interested in any games, by the way,
Just a quick plug here, swagpoop.com/haunted-house-hidden-objects-game.
Yeah, we got disc one player pool game.
Oh yeah.
I thought that was one of the most technologically advanced ones.
Gerdverzuker?
Oh, let me just pull up.
So if you want to head to swagpoop.com right now and in the handy nav bar where you can
click all the pages on the website, you'll see.
Could we get Slap the Monkey on there?
No, I've tried getting, I'll have to figure it out.
I'll do some more research in my lab.
house hidden objects game bunny solitaire game squirrel bubble shooter game
Christmas mysteries game king's gold game fruit cubes game soldier attack to
game airport management one game on a connection game pizza chief game pizza
chief dag a lid just skis word zooker game word zookers jolly John math game
blub love game coloring for kids game and this pool one player game. I think
you guys should curate the library. No people want a lot of options. The best
the best okay, there's like thousands. There's dozens of games out there. I
I think like five is a magic number.
Five is like the least magic number.
No, five is a small number.
Yeah.
Right.
But--
It might be magic, but it's small.
Don't you want a lot of options when you're
going to play games on a swagpoop.com?
On a swagpoop.com?
One of them, yeah.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Maybe 100 is the magic number.
Is there any way we could consolidate the screen, though?
What do you mean?
Like swagpoop.com/games, and then you can pick it all up.
No, unfortunately, they all have to be in the menu bar.
You can't do that on a website.
That's not possible. They have to, whatever link you want to go to, it has to be at
the top or else you can't get there.
See, I don't do web design, so I don't know.
Yeah, I've done a lot of training on this type of thing.
And you want to have at least 20 games that are on the bar of your website.
Right. And you have to scroll down on the bar to see them all?
Yeah, the bar is basically the screen at that point.
Because that's what a website is, is a screen with links.
Right. Yeah.
There's a lot of, I mean, I think websites are,
websites back in the day used to be so much better.
I agree.
Wow, before millennials ruined everything.
Yeah, if millennials wanted to make everything
look all square, spacey, and minimalist on their websites.
I think it was, yeah.
Maximalist websites were way better.
I think it was those annoying ass people
in the 80s and 90s that ruined websites.
Yep.
It used to be.
They were better before that.
It used to be a bunch of punch cards.
Yeah, it was cool as fuck.
I do want to I want to use one of those computers. I want to get a big an
odyssey. I don't fucking know what it's called. I don't either. I think that's
a different thing altogether. I think that's a good answer that a Greek man
went on. No, I'm thinking about the Magnavox. I'm going to go on an odyssey
or my name is an
street. Yeah, he's the most annoying. They were all he was like I'm going to
go on an odyssey. Yeah,
that's like if it's like if Columbus was like I'm going to go on a
Christophus I'm going to go to Columbia. You just go on a damn Odyssey already
man you're fucking ruining the he sits around talking about that Odyssey for so
long. I did it did first. He explained to us what an Odyssey was then he was
like all right. Well, when I go on it, I'm going to tell you some on my
going back and told me that shit. I would not have believed him. Let my go
on a camera knee to the store after yeah, I just went on a cable be yeah.
What's a camera? That's an adventure that camera goes on to the store.
well this one is to the story. He goes to the bathroom not often.
That is what I mean there's so many other people that have gone on odyssey
since no to so to Mario. No, you know what that's they call it at that, but
that was for the localization. It's actually a Mario. We were not in
java game in Japan. It's called Super Mario Mario.
Okay, that makes sense. I just translated it. Yes, Abe's a B.
Yeah, yeah, baby. What other odysseys are there in Indiana Jones?
Does he go to every fucking movie?
He goes to a temple of doom and a raiders of the last ark.
He doesn't go on an odyssey.
He does.
He says I'm jonesing for a crystal.
I'm jonesing to go to Indiana.
Go on an Indiana eat to Indiana.
I'm jonesing to meet an Indian.
that is where Jones and comes from is Indiana Jones
no yeah because he comes from the soda what's that the soda Jones soda I'm
jonesing oh it does it actually yeah so they would say that yeah when the
commercial for Indiana Jones it's a they have that just that uh there's a few
places I went to in Seattle if they have it on in a fountain like like on tap like
get it Jones in a fountain fountain Jones yeah yeah I'd see the damn Jones so to
be like this belongs in a fountain this bumps all around that was insanely good
this fits belongs in a bump yep because Indiana Jones also looks for the
fountain of you you're thinking of the last crusade he looks at the last
crusade okay yeah he's not looking for the found a youth yeah there's no movie
Indiana Jones and the Fountain of Fuse. Whatever he's looking for is in the name of the movie
and it's after the end of that. Did he ever look for the Holy Grail?
He's looking for the crusade. No.
That was when he looked for the last crusade. Yeah, that's just part of the crusade.
That was incidental, yeah. That was just an accident.
Yeah, exactly. He picked it up and he was like, "Eh, well."
Excalibur. I thought that King Arthur was real until like a year ago.
I've been reading some King Arthur stuff. It's pretty cool.
He's cool. I think he is real.
You do? Yeah.
was an aardvark I think it's like it's like 99% of historians think he was a
clear Arthur and then 1% thinks thank you he was kind of real well there's a kid
in his court yeah that was Arthur yeah yeah okay what's is Arthur the odd works
last name the aardvark yeah yeah I don't know I think it's penance eW short for
or no we're one weird sister. What's that? What's the gay rat teacher? His
name is Mr. Ratburn. Mr. Is he Mr. So his last name is Ratburn. So he's
something the Ratburn Chris Chris the rat Chris Ratburn Chris the rapper.
His name is Mr. The Ratburn. No, but I mean if his last name if our if
Arthur the art works, yeah, I guess Arthur is the king of his own universe.
everybody has named it yeah so Arthur's a scratch don't even go there as a
scratch style no he's not his books and his not we're not gonna go there but
basically DW is Jerry so we're done yeah and well they're yeah and they're peach
they're both animals pinkie size also he is definitely spike or ice the brain
spice what is the brain though the brain is the brain from the body okay
brain what is the nut of the body the nut of the bottle what is your body
you're a child hmm oh yeah you're trying to create a child right the nut of a
body is a child Jerry oh now it makes sense
we have to stop okay starting to get yeah I I could just talk about it again see I
mean once this once we hit I mean you know what they say spongebob all the
spongebob characters are based on deadly sins all the Arthur characters are based
on organs of the body because they have the brain Arthur and the heart key the
binky is the binky in the baby the baby's big W de weiner yeah our words
is your nose because he's an art work. I think Arthur is the heart because he's at the heart
of the show. Yeah he's the heart. He's the heart and then Buster. Mr. Ratburn. The fat
guy is the stomach. That's Binky. Binky was the binky. Mr. Ratburn is the gaijin. Yeah
that only happens in some people that's why he's only in some episodes. That's only in
75% of men. Buster is your Buster. You know what I'm talking about. Which is the muscle
that makes you bust. Buster is your muscle. Francine is your hair cuz she's a girl.
Is Francine in that? Francine. Who's Francine? And then Muffy. Muffy is your fingernails cuz she's a girl.
Muffy's your damn muff. Yep. Yep. I heard that. This bumps all around again for now. And all the chess pieces are based off of playing cards.
yeah yeah aren't the road rats aren't the Rugrats also the deadly sins no
regrets are they're based on the children of the pickles family yeah
your friends and the baby friend group. Well, they're all Jewish.
Phil and I are based on twins with
I think they're all half Jewish. Yeah, no Chuckie's Jewish and that's it. No,
no, no, no, no Chuck.
He's not Jewish. He just has allergies.
It is. It's funny. It's funny. It's a red headed. He because he was a red
headed. He's Chuckie as a real boy. He kind of is. Yeah, you made me. You
really made me doubt with the
doing mental terrorism on maybe laugh the way I forgot his name is Chuckie Chuckie
Chuckie the baby okay on the road a toddler Judaism and Rugrats all right
pretty cool that they had a the Jewish family in oh here's a yeah I think I
should representation Tommy's actions towards dill in the Rugrats movie
he paralleled the sacrifice of Isaac.
That's interesting. I'm not sure I remember that. I remember yeah, I do
they have a lot of interesting Jewish representation, but I'm not sure I like
what they're going for with Reptar.
I don't think that's fair. Yeah, that's I don't think it's fair. First of all,
to have a giant lizard. I don't think it's fair to have two small Jewish
babies controlling is pickles a Jewish last name. Yes, okay, yep, no further
questions. That was an Ellis Island name.
Oh, whatever, pickles. It was like Schvartzweiner. You're gonna have funny ass babies. And your
babies is gonna be funny as hell. And if you don't name your damn kid Dil, here's your
sign. Yep. Jeff Fox. They used to put chalk on the people. That's the sign. Dil Ingvall
call it Ellis Island. Well, no, they would give them the sign for their house that
says their name like on the mailbox. Here's your sign. Yeah, yeah, like you
know, on your mailbox, a funny mailbox that looked like maybe a race car or a
spaceship. No, no, man, I wish I had. I grew up in town homes. We all had one
mailbox
poor.
I'm trying to think of anyone. I knew had it. My grandmother had a mail. I grew up
the millionaires plantation. We have about a hundred mail boxes. We we had
the kind we had just the kind that were on you know the kind they're on the
door and they have a lid. I opens up yeah. I as what you Boston, we had a
green mailbox. Yeah, I had a green mailbox. It like a freestanding mailbox
like a movie. I know that's sick. I'm I that's what that can be. That is a
movie mailbox. That is a movie mail box in front of the house normal style
with a flag. Yeah, yeah, I thought the flag was so when I went to my
grandmother says she had one. I just play with the flag. I just put you put it
down. Yeah, well, the mailman has to come get this. We used to do. We used to
plastic toy on that mailbox. We used to put a rock in the mailbox and put the
flag and see if the mailman would take the rock and he never did. Yeah, you
forgot to put a stamp on it. Probably, yeah, because it's a rock going anywhere
with no stamps. Yeah, put a whole ham sandwich in the mailbox. You did. We
should put firecrackers in the mailbox and then we killed a pregnant lady.
and then I went back in time and went back in time and I went back in time
trying to save it. I lost my hands. I literally I watched like the first 20
minutes of that the other day and then I was like oh I don't know how to watch this.
Dude it's an upsetting movie. It's like the butterfly effect. Within the first 10 minutes of that movie he's
already getting diddled by by Eric Stoltz. Yeah it's one of those. It's like
it's like that like in 2004 when they were like we need like like we need to make
a requiem for a dream kind of like. The edgiest movie we can make. Yeah. And they made a time travel movie about like what if you
could go back and stop your molestation. Yeah and he keeps going back in time and
then showing up and he has like no nose and no eyes. Yeah. Oh I should have just.
And the moral of the story is like yeah probably don't worry about it. Getting molested was the best thing that could have happened to you.
molested is the biggest part of all yeah
another movie that I thought was called
the butterfly effect maybe you've seen
this Cameron they like go back in time
and they kill one t-rex this is the only
thing you can do they have a time
machine where you can go back in time
and there's like a tunnel where you're
not allowed to touch anything the only
thing you're allowed to do is kill this
one dinosaur uh-huh and then you come
back to the present you're like yay and
then they're like but you can't take
anything you can't touch anything but
one guy brings a butterfly this sounds
familiar and then at the butterfly animated it's not called the butterfly
effect but it is it's is it is it animated no I mean like it's live action
but all the maybe this is a prequel they come back and then yeah there's like a
weird plot point where they're like humans were the most recent animal to
evolve so if you change anything in the past the humans will change so what do
they come back to so they come back to a world where people are like see through
is it a sound of thunder yes yeah it is a battle it's based on a Ray Bradbury
story it is about time tourists and that's a link on Wikipedia okay that
just links to time travel I hate Wikipedia I think time travel would be
pretty cool yeah I wouldn't do it yeah I think I was going forward what I would
hate to go for it actually I would go back in time by by like one thing and
then and then resell it I'm going all the way back I'm not seeing anything
that we were up to I want to see the dinosaurs maybe the pyramids yeah this
movie sounds awesome I want to personally see William Shakespeare but
just my I see William you just want to see him walk around I just want to see
him yeah I don't know actually one guy or 13 you think about like like time
travel doing like a you you're you're a time traveler in this scenario actually
I'd probably make a music video you go probably film myself doing it make it
- You go, you time travel.
- I put my fingers in baby Jesus' mouth.
- I come back, I say, "Smell this."
- You go back in time to like 1750 or something.
You ever think about what it would smell like?
'Cause I feel like you're in the middle
of the most metropolitan part of 1750.
People are throwing poop out their windows into a trough.
- I know it smelled crazy even then.
- I'd go Germany.
(laughing)
- All right, yeah, okay, yeah, fist bump on that one.
I'd go to Germany, like 1928.
- Germany?
- Yeah, 'cause that might be the stinkiest place of all.
- All right, you don't get two in a row.
You don't get two in a row.
I'd go to Germany, 1928, and I'd walk around doing this.
I'd be telling people, like, this means you're gay.
(laughing)
- You'd walk around with a small mustache,
just being like, yeah, this represents what I do.
- They tried that with Charlie Chaplin, didn't work.
And then they do and then I tried to turn Hitler's mustache into into mean I get
hit by stuff and then I come back to the present the Holocaust still happened but
all the all the Nazis are doing this with their hands instead of doing the
blood fingers. That'd be cool. It's like you go back in time you're like this
means you're gay, this means you're gay, but this means you're cool. Yeah. I didn't mean to do that second
thing that yeah you know I just I just wanted to show everybody that I wasn't
gay not trying to stop the Holocaust just make the Nazi salute not happy yeah
yeah it's the lynch it's too hard to do you stop the Holocaust you know I mean
oh right cuz you think it was inevitable yeah it's gonna happen no matter what
anything you're gonna be Hitler I would go back in time I would go back in time
and I maybe bury a time capsule with a lot of money or something and then I
I would get it and I would get all the money.
- I would bury.
(laughing)
- I'd put a whoopee cushion.
- I think I'd bury my Game Boy under the dirt
and then I'd go dig it up in the future
and I'd get to play with it.
- Yeah, you don't really need time travel for this.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'd build a sand castle.
- I'm going to bury something right now.
That actually sounds awesome.
- Did you guys ever do a time capsule?
Were you ever part of one?
I feel like I've, one of them should be opened by now.
- Yeah.
I think people open them and it's the most boring thing ever. Yeah, they put a
time capsule into the there's like a the fun of it is definitely burying it and
imagining what it's going to be like, but then when you're just near sitting
there near the high school old shit. Yeah, the high school in my town, they
put a time capsule into like there's like a little like you know like a an
island like thing at the time like we're just like a grassy area in the middle of
the street and they put like there were like benches and stuff there and they
just put a time capsule in the middle of that. So it's just this giant like metal
circle where they like lowered into the ground and just yeah just everybody
would just try to would just try to pay like lift it out of the ground. It's
like a crate. You can't move it. It's just so much. You always just see
people just be like I want to yeah, I want to whip this up yeah. It's right
there. It's not buried. It's right here. Senior prank yeah, lift it up just
putting it. I wonder if I want to do it
not even opening the time capsule just like I took it yeah. I would love to
no one else can have it. I would hate to bury my shit in that and be like, oh fuck, I actually
wanted that. Like what if you're like an idiot kid and you're like, I'll bury my Game Boy.
When you leave a $50 bill in your jacket pocket, that's just a time dollar. Yeah, exactly.
And then you open it and you're like, oh fuck, I wish I didn't bury this in my pocket. When
I was little, part of our like porch like rotted or something or like one of the steps
broke and they were like putting in a new porch and I made a time capsule that was like
a jar and I put one of every coin in it and I put it under the porch. That'd be
worth millions. You need to go get that. I know well they just I think redid the
porch again like this year so I don't I wonder if anyone found it. I think they
maybe took it without telling me. I mean I wouldn't tell anyone if I found a
time capsule like that. With money in it? Oh my god. With coins you go to the
arcade and go fucking crazy. Yeah pretty good. Well it's just one of every
so it's a what it's what it's six sixteen how much cents is that? That's
that's that's 41 cents you put well that's 41 you put a half dollar in there
no what do you think I have a half dollar what are you talking about he said one of
every coin you can get a half dollar yeah I also put all the Japanese coins in the
Chinese coins of the clothes for every ancient civilization you said every corner
of a rock dollar and still in circulation it's okay so why don't you
bring up a dollar coin that's not obvious I feel like a dickhead if I pay
with a dollar coin or a half dollar coin.
- I know.
- That's my gold coin.
- That's your gold coin?
(laughing)
- What are you talking about?
- That's my gold coin.
(laughing)
That's my nut.
- No one should have it.
As soon as you get a dollar coin, that's your gold coin.
- You're right.
- Same with a two dollar bill.
- I get a two dollar bill once a year.
- Oh, I met this flight attendant and he was like,
I always get my, I found this one bank
that gives me two dollar bills,
or maybe he specially requests them,
and he's like, and I always leave that as a tip,
even if it's like way way less than 15% interesting. I guess that is kind of
smart because people do covet those. Yeah, there's I don't think people really
covet those. No, nobody cares. It is. There's an old there's $2. There's an
old lady who would have come into my job at the liquor store. She was all in
blue, completely blued out. She lived every day. And she would, whoever was
working the register, she would just hand them a $2 bill. I got I would
sometimes see her going to store and I'd go over the register. Like, I'm just
status register here to get a two dollar bill please give me the dollar
you do not talk
you do you do you know i'm not going to talk
i didn't talk about anything i'm camera now what i'm not cameron and i'm already
got his not
new
uh...
i don't know how to get out of the way i would like to say that i have a new
voice
forgetting what it is guys is for the day
I'm new Cameron with a new voice.
New Cameron with a new voice and look at this I just moved my hair to the other side.
You point out exactly what's different.
Watch this now I'm a different Cameron.
Hello.
I don't think that would work on this lady.
She's pretty wise if she's getting two dollar bills.
She's not wise.
She's blue.
She's truly blue.
She's the bluest woman I've ever seen.
She was one of the bluest women I ever saw.
She's a blue bitch.
Besides Cortana.
I want to have a kind of one every single day where the same color all the way down.
Yeah, I do respect people when I see that.
Yeah, black is like every you can do that nobody really notices.
That's a fun color.
If you do like mustard yellow.
I saw a dude who had a he had a fitted a Philly's fitted hat.
He dressed like a clown character.
Philly's fitted hat that was the exact same color as his sweatshirt.
Whoa.
And it was like a sand.
No matching pants though?
no i don't know how i i don't know that's not a source
but it was like a sand but they were the same color as we all the same color
yeah you i'd guys have matches shirt it was the exact same color
what will i do here is what we need to do it is the exact the same or i would
these are the cd's in the same color
there's a lot of
but these are sure only these are short so it doesn't count but they're sure it's
not a little bit of a short
all
all your own
uh... i want to know what it's not like a but you know i like i think it doesn't
count like
so it's not a little bit
okay i get it
where
you really do have to go outside and start banging garbage can
everybody my friend is matching
yeah it doesn't count if it's all like all one color because they're wearing
wearing like a track suit or something.
It has to be different clothes that are the same color.
- Like jeans that are the same color as your sweatshirt.
- Yeah, if your jeans are the same color as your shirt.
- Here's your sign.
- Mm-hmm.
- Here's your sign, most matching.
- Matcher.
(laughing)
- You might be a matcher.
- You might be a matcher if your shoes,
- If your hat, shoes, shirt, pants, socks,
- And your pants.
- If your hat, gloves, shoes, shirt, pants, socks,
and sweatshirt are all the same color,
you might be a match. If your socks take as long to put on as your pants, you're
a longer
trying to cash in on the on the on the you might be a red night things like I
have to like you have to diversify this. I've just spread it. I don't really
say redneck anymore. Yeah,
your gene pool has jeans in it. You might be a jeaner
yeah he's trying to he's trying to hit as broad an audience as possible. So
it's like harder than a longer.
If you walk outside, you might be an outside Walker. You might be an
outsider.
Yeah, if your house is a little old as a shoe, you might be a little old lady
doesn't sit on your top here we go here we go
in way now what now just completely changes the entire rules right in front
of our face yeah it should be like this if you live in a shoe you might be a
sure that's what we said who sits on their tough your ass is always on your
damn tough it off there's no way you for you for guys how do you remember get off
and not little miss my fucking insane I didn't remember if you have a neck that
is red in color you might be a neck redder
okay this I feel like maybe doesn't really but it segues into the list for
today top ten things to say when using the phrase there's two types of people
in the world there's two types of people in the world there's rednecks and neck
redders rednecks and mattresses and shoeers and longsockers
there's a few types of people in the world
there's jumpers and singers
and little miss muffins
if you jump around everyday
you might be a jumper but if you sing you might be a singer jumper
and who's to say you can't be both?
you might be a singer dancer
Chris Brown singer dancer. Oh yeah, you might be a brown neck.
If you get tanned on your neck and it doesn't burn, you might be a brown
neck. Yeah, yeah, yeah, all right number one is people that can respect
opinions and ones who argue about them. Yeah, I can respect differences in
And I can't I actually argue about
about
he's disrespecting my opinion
you laughed at it like you were attacking him
you like leaned in and opened your mouth
like you're charging a breath weapon
I know that was so funny
he just
I thought he was gonna take a bite out of me
you
you were you who were
you were I just have the I really do the stupidest sense of humor ever I just
like you just say the
and it's like we were two people
you
Well you guys yeah, yeah, I feel like me and Pierce really had it on lock there you guys
You try you guys try this one then see I think it's this this one's problem. I don't think it's a
Jokes it makes memes so here so how I would do it is like like
Yo, yo mama so fat
She she went out onto the beach and all the whales they've jumped out of the water
and they started singing, "We are family,
"even though you're fatter than me."
- Yeah.
- Me when I don't care.
- See? - Okay.
- See?
- I don't know.
- That was pretty, you guys are holding back tears.
- It was good, it was good,
but it wasn't as good as the first one.
- Yeah.
- There's nothing, nothing will ever be
as good as the first one.
- The first one is pure.
Well, maybe, yeah.
Well, it may be perfect as if--
- I still think the content of it was pretty funny.
- Yeah, it's true.
Maybe, no, what-- - It's not respect.
I feel like so maybe Caleb says that joke and then Pierce like holds up his phone
and he's created a new meme that's called like like joke that is not true Caleb
and it's like Caleb's face with a bunch of colors behind it and it's like
tells joke that is not true. Yeah, as usual.
That's important.
That's the most...
You have to say as usual at the bottom.
Because yeah, the socially awkward penguin could just be doing one socially
awkward thing. You know, he needs to say like, says yeah, when
when the ticket taker says enjoy your movie, I say as you do as usual. I
think we are new. I think we have a new kind of way to do this, which is we
should just not read the actual thing and just give it to them in the format
of like who we are okay. Yeah, so personally I really like dogs.
I would kill a dog
On the other hand, this one I think is maybe there's there might this might be
more than two types of people. I feel like there might be some middle ground
between this one. No, there's not. I think you like dogs right up to the
point where you would kill one because I would kill a dog. I like dogs.
Well, you said well, okay, so that's that you just disprove. That means
there's not two types of people. I guess there's only one type. It's one
type of person. Everyone is someone who likes dogs until they have to kill
one. Yeah, well, everyone, yeah. If it's just you like dogs or you don't like
you like you don't like dogs unless they're attacking you. Yeah I don't think you have to you don't have to hate dogs to kill one.
No. You know what I mean? No. I would kill a dog that was attacked. Not mutually exclusive. Yeah. Yeah if a dog bit my wiener I'd kill it.
Does anybody else instantly think of Michael Vick when reading this? Well he's the ultimate middleman. Here's another comment.
Right now I'm thinking right now I'm thinking of what they do in Iran. They kill dogs by injection of acid.
Wait, they like strap him to a chair?
Dog-shaped vial of acid.
It's like the dogs playing poker but they're all in electric chairs.
That's really good, yeah.
Well, here, this comment section is filled with people trying to do your kind of like two-person routine,
where there's a bunch of people who say, "And I'm the one who likes dogs. I love dogs. I like dogs."
But no one's replying to finish it.
Right. "I like dogs. Pug will not be pleased."
In Thieves of Ostia, there's a man who hates dogs because one killed his daughter.
That's probably true. Yeah. What about this number six one? You want to try this
one Caleb? Number six? Yeah. I'm the kind of person who just hates Nicki Minaj. And
And personally, I live in a mental hospital.
But I do. He had no opinion on Nicki Minaj, but I do live in a mental hospital. I guess I don't
hate her. I've never heard of her. All I hear is blah blah blah. Yeah, this one, I don't know.
Hey, I love Nicki Minaj and I am not in a mental hospital.
Well that person, well that's because they're talking about Nicki Minaj, not Nicki Minaj
is a different person.
I hate both of them.
Okay.
That's number seven, I hate both of them.
Okay, so that's not, yeah.
That doesn't, hmm.
This option made me laugh.
Definitely using this one in real life.
I've been to mental hospitals before.
Damn.
Oh my god, get over anaconda.
There's Turn Me On and Marilyn Monroe.
You guys seriously can't give someone a chance.
Okay, so here's here, so I don't know whoever wants to take this, but I mean
I'm just I'm the type of person I play FIFA. I do yoga. You are one who do
yoga.
He fucked it up.
You are one who do yoga. Oh, you are one who do yoga. I've been waiting to
meet one and here's well. Here's the from the commenter from the commenter
Puga explains why this is these are this is a difference here. FIFA is much
more interesting and unpredictable. Yoga is neither of those things right yeah.
Well, yoga could be unpredictable. If you just do a surprise yoga move in the
world of fifa players, there's literally just one yogi for everyone. Fifa player,
there's one yoga player.
You play yoga. Yeah, can you win or lose it's? Well, it's the same as like it's
the same. So when you do yoga like and you're just kind of doing it by yourself,
that's like that's like doing like time trial, but like on a sonic level or
something yeah true all right here. I'll try this one out. This is number
seventeen number sixteen is good too, but we do number seventeen. I'm an
atheist plain and simple. I'm one who goes on about it.
I guess
there's a yeah sure
- Or this whole episode is just gonna be us,
it's just us chasing the high of the first one
and getting really upset when none of them work.
- I just thought that whoever was gonna do the,
go on about it would be like,
personally, I gotta, I think there was a God.
- Oh, we would actually go on about it.
- Yeah, yeah. - No, but he,
okay, what about this?
- But he's talking-- - Like, what about this?
Okay, so do it again, here, start over.
- But they're both atheists here.
- Yeah, no, but yeah, so--
- I'm an atheist, and that should tell you
everything you need to know.
- I'm an atheist, and I'm an atheist,
and I'm an atheist, and I'm an atheist,
I'm an atheist and I'm an atheist.
That is how it'll be sounding sometimes.
Oh wait, here's one, number 19.
I'm somebody who actually loves video games.
I'm a cancerous five-year-old.
Who loves video games more than a five-year-old with cancer?
Yeah, that's all that's true.
They get to eat Mario with their make-a-wish.
They stuff it in that fucking bed.
They make fucking a thousand, they make millions of dollars from charities on Twitch.
Exactly, yeah.
Hey, here's number 21.
Okay.
This one's more visual.
Yeah.
okay, we have to say it because there's no it's not a very visual yeah. I was I
should have said I'm Harry and then I would have said I'm the I'm the guy he's
sitting next to
all right, yeah, I'm smart
hey, here's one yeah.
Thank you the two types of guys. I'm an actual respectable Christian
personally I hate you that's not what it says I hate the Bible as an excuse to
hate yeah no fuck dude you guys are you guys have really lost it I did the best
one ever okay so I can I'm like Michael Jordan on the Wizards I'm just kind of
having I'm having fun no this is your now you're not late career this is the
still the first we already did this is still the think that we would not do the
bald one I guess I thought maybe you would wait for me to get back this is
still the first area again probably him actually a i might be here in the peers
not on your head
was just a matter of time
he
with the same length here
what are you fucking talking about one
here's the same link this pierce no
ron is wearing a hat
and i'm not
i'm a leader
i'm a leader's it's not so i'll tell you that's it's not only there's
you're a part of it. I'm a leaders. Yeah, well, I'm a tea bagger. Hey, that's not
it. That's not it. Yeah, we should start mixing. That's a good idea that could
maybe. Okay, hey, Cameron, Cameron, I, I care about the Holocaust and I hate it
and I am Cameron. Well, that tells you all you need to know. Yeah, I think I
met this type of guy before. Knowing what I know about Caleb. Yeah, I think
you can you can understand what he means.
I grind
I am the board.
Let's just say things that we are. We don't need this. I'm a I'm cool. Well,
I don't need
I'm right handed. I don't eat piece to crust.
I'm just
I eat pizza crust. I eat pizza crust. No, I don't eat it. You fucking asshole. I'm a person
who has a breakfast in the kitchen. I have it in bed. I'm
you went far down I'm the one that like Justin Bieber I'm dead I'm a Nazi and a
girl I'm when I'm the one who is trashy okay here's one I get excited when
and Christmas decorations appear on the streets. I suck
no your people who aren't I spread ketchup all over the fries. I put it
beside them.
I love Scarlett Johansson. I hate Scarlett.
I'm the ones who watches cartoons.
I was I'm ones who watch live actions,
but probably cartoons. I'm girls. I'm good noodles.
I'm bad eggs. I mean dude, I've never heard somebody say they were a good
noodle. No, I haven't been a bad good egg more yeah. What nobody's heard a
good noodle you are here to the golden rule and I don't I'm annoying popular
girls.
I'm a tea bagger. I'm a prostitute. We got him yeah the whole list
Yeah, just stay on the computer. What is it?
Does this he thinks that you get a prostitution teabag?
What are you a prostitute a teabagger you can you can teabag a prostitute nobody teabags man? Yeah, don't speak for yourself
I mean expect to hey buddy
Except for Master Chief. Maybe when he kills a couple of
Alien freaks yeah, but yeah, you don't teabag a prostitute. You're not paying good money teabag
teabag. Well you to be allowed to teabag someone who's dead. You have to kill
the prostitute. Yeah, teabag. I feel like a lot of people kill prostitutes.
That's like that's one of the things that people do. Well, I've never heard
of that. There's those who kill prostitutes and those who don't teabag
prostitutes.
There's ones who don't not do not teabag. I'm and those who do teabag do
teabag. This is the opening statement of the defense.
I'm a person who grinds. I said that one already did yeah and I grind in my
sleep. I twerk
work. That's what it that's the one. Okay, show me your jiggling ass. All
right, not going to do it. What you put your coffee down. I'm not going to do
it. I put it that's that's like me putting my foot down. This is my foot
put that ass down. This cop is my foot your ass down to the ground and let
this coffee is my foot. How do how do women move this copy of my foot like
that? It's their back. It's a lower back. It's actually just their
you're tricking us. It's like this
rubber pencil. Look it's elastic. Yeah, that's actually their stomach that you
see from the side and it looks like their butt moving around. Yeah, it's
actually that's actually everything that's actually
moving the entire world and your eyes.
That's actually just air moving. It's shimmering air. It's like a it's like
It's like a mirage.
What's happening is they make a super hot fart that makes the air shimmer.
Oh, that makes sense.
Like when you look at a brick wall in the summer.
Those are stink lines moving on the inside.
You ever seen the video?
Your eye confuses stink lines for the vibration, like curve lines.
That's right.
You ever seen a fart while twerking?
I can, what do you mean see it?
Like you imagine?
Like somebody farts while they're twerking.
You see the butt moving and it goes like.
I've seen cake farts.
It makes a fart sound?
Oh yeah, I have seen that actually.
I feel like hearing that is the more interesting part of it.
You can see the fart.
You can see the butt jiggle with the fart.
Is it weird that I like the way you did that?
There are two kinds of people.
Try another list.
I think we went all the way through.
I think we juiced this one.
I'm one who takes selfies.
You actually are.
Well, here's one.
Yeah, fuck you.
Bitch.
I'm a descendant of Seth.
I'm a descendant of Cain.
Seth?
Yeah.
Seth was the third one.
Which one's Seth?
after it was it was it was able cane Seth Seth was the third shot. We didn't
hear about Seth what when I was growing up, no, you should have and you guys
purport probably stupid stupid guys. I know it's pretty funny. I was probably
able. I just couldn't count to I could yeah like said you heard Seth and it
just didn't go into your memory. This one's the story top ten best places to
poop. Have we done that one? I don't know. I think we have. I don't think so. I
think we could do this one. I'm a good Samaritan.
I'm in a toilet. I'm a good Samaritan. I'm Chinese. I've played cave story. I
bite into chocolate and people who eat it in pieces.
I'm the ones that like hyenas and the ones that like lions.
Wait, I like lions and you twerk
Can we do this top ten best places to poop one? Sure. Did we not do? I feel like we did.
All right, well let's do this. Let's look at it. Hold up. I feel like, I don't know.
Who knows? It doesn't matter. It actually doesn't matter whether we did it or not.
Holy shit. And I think it does. Damn. God damn. I mean this is similar to only the other
ones. You might be a thinker that it does-er. What about, what about, can we just do the
top ten most disgusting things that people can do? Yeah. Okay. This one's got to go.
go ahead and read this one. Okay, this is the top ten things people can do that
are extremely disgusting. Number one is rape. Solo Potato says, "Holy crap,
this is so bad. It's 100 times on this list. Which cruel, disgusting person
would even think about this?" Yeah. So that's the type of person I am and
Pierce, who are you?
One thumbs up equals one prayer for the people who have had to go through this.
Yeah, there are two kinds of people in this world. Well, I just go through you
got you have you have two thumbs. You're only using one of them to give a
prayer. I mean that's right yeah. What's that's kind of why not just give number
to eat other people yeah, that's not good. That's pretty cool. Seriously
people are already doing this in China. They're selling baby soup. Can you
believe how unhuman that is honestly eating babies is really gross people
like this deserve to be thrown into jail. They don't do that in China and I
would know that is a myth by people who hate China. They did eat some in Hawaii
a few centuries ago. These are the two types of people. I know this is
disgusting, but your comments about baby soup. No, this is just plain horrible.
Peoples in China are just weird for drinking baby soup.
People don't know what adjective to describe
nasty. Wasn't that they refer to that that artist who did that thing where he
ate he ate a fake baby? I don't know remember that I don't remember. It's
pretty cool. Look at me to look mad real only cannibals and some survivors with
no food do that only cannibals. Do you think you need some animals and some
survivors? What's the point of eating people when you have other meats?
Good point yeah, I think I always
think about like I feel like every time you hear about like people cannibalizing
somebody, they always die like one day later. It's like when when you just
fucking chill for one day and so like eating your that's your chance, but it
it doesn't work. It almost never works out. I know, but that's something
that's your chan. No, that's not that's not your chance to survive. That's
your chance to eat a person. Yeah, it's the person in a reassimilate into
society. I was reading this thing where, like
some like serial killer guy killed a bunch of people and then like
baked put them into foods. I forget what kind of food some kind of meat
food hot dog and he gave he like gave them to people at like the like town
fair or whatever. So it's just a whole town just like eight people and didn't
about it. You imagine finding out about that after the fact and be like
there's that dark water movie that's based off of the or no dark water came
first and then a lease a lamb or whatever the woman who was found on the
water tank. Oh yeah, yeah, people were drinking her her body water yeah. I
just
yeah, but that's what I mean is like a
imagine finding out you were drinking a girl's water or eating a guy's meat
and you didn't even you didn't know about it and you know you don't you
don't get to enjoy it or be disgusted by it's like well, like if I found out I
ate a guy's pie or whatever that was had a guy that had a guy pie that had
pie guy
guys pie and I was like I feel like I wouldn't even be able to be disgusted
because I already happen like it's not like it's like if you ate a hot dog or
you found out a year later that was like a rotten hot dog. You wouldn't be
yeah. I'll be like okay, yeah behind me I'm living in the I'm looking for my
- It's ex-food.
- Yeah, exactly.
- I'm not worried about what I used to eat.
- I'm not gonna throw up, it's not still in me.
It's in the toilet, it's making, it's guy water now.
- Yeah, exactly.
- It's guy water for rats.
- Which we never thought could even happen.
- Yeah.
- We made guy water.
- Well, guy water is when guy pie
goes through a boy's system.
- A boy's boy.
(laughing)
- Guys, guys water can only be--
- The boy's system turns pie to water.
- Guys water can only be made
after it goes through boy's system.
- Yeah.
- That's the two types.
- Boy's systems and guys water.
I just don't I don't I don't I would not I don't think even if I had the chance
that I would want to eat somebody unless I really hated them, unless I really
wanted to yeah, unless I was like really hungry, unless I didn't know that I was
doing it yeah. Well, there that's it unless I was being mind control.
That's like every do it unless someone made that was another knowledge. That
was another that's another really good hypothetical question to annoy a
girlfriend with is like would you would you kill me or would you eat me if you
had to and there was no other out that you are controlled to do. I asked her
the other day and she was like no. I don't think I could and I said like I
would eat you have to and she's like what I would eat you pretty much
instantly. Would you eat human flesh if you had to yeah? Would you go? Yeah,
right?
That's what I would ask of people. Yeah, people get people and then they say
yes, right and you're like what's wrong with you right? You're supposed to say
no. Yeah, yeah, just a resist. Yeah, good follow up. If you know, would you
cut off my head and eat my nuts and they say no, you just say okay, would
someone
would someone do that?
because if someone could, they could.
yeah.
are you someone?
would someone do that?
interesting.
oh you're not anybody?
have you ever had like tripa?
or like yeah tripa.
tripa tacos.
yeah.
you know how like when you bite into it it's kind of got that like mealy little like.
isn't it tripe?
no.
no no no.
tripa is like a fish right?
tripa is an intestine.
tripa is like a fish.
I think um, tripa is...
Isn't tripe intestine?
I thought tripe was intestine.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think tripa is intestines too.
Is it spelled T-R-I-P-E?
Is it pronounced tripe?
T-R-I-P-E.
Oh, okay.
It's probably the Spanish word for tripe.
You think, well I'm thinking, like I've had a few tripa tacos in my day.
I imagine that biting into that, like if you cooked somebody's balls it would taste exactly
like that.
Yeah.
that whenever on fear factor they eat the ball nuts. I'm always like I'm
something crazy. Yeah, a bull.
The ball not bold.
Bull. Yeah, well, it's would you eat a bull? I mean, I guess it was in a taco
show. I guess I would. Would you eat a bull's nuts if he put his nuts in your
face? You couldn't move and you were really hungry. You're starving for three
days. You only needed one bite to live. Yeah, I'd probably do that. Well, if you
know what they call, they say that like it's like candy. They said like human
tastes like pork or whatever and they call it the long pig. I feel like pigs
already long as it is long as hell. It's probably longer than a human, but yeah,
well, I mean humans tall should be the tall and yeah, long that's a long
standing, but what I would say is I feel like I would be. I feel like that was
a good move because I would be a lot more likely to eat human or to try to
kill and eat a human. If it was called like the tasty pig yeah or the yummy
delicious, but the walking talking pig, though yeah, I feel like they could have
done one better and called it gross pig though or yeah yeah pig just call it
don't call it pig. Yeah, we were going to think they're eating meat pig yeah
meat yeah. I mean because you could you could you could you know you could
pretty easily accidentally order a long pig at a restaurant. I mean say
somebody asks you how long is the line and you say long and then you also turn
back to order you say pig. I love because you want the pig you got pig on
the menu. Yeah, you're ordering pig and you but you're answering someone else
you say long pig right here you are eating your cousin yeah well I heard
that a restaurant in New York City actually a good you see this news clip
that they're actually serving human flesh actually yeah and that but and if
you don't like if you don't like that you should steer clear yeah not the
restaurant that's what I said yeah if you even if you don't like it sometimes
you will be made to eat it in certain situations yeah well where you have to
Well, they say about that restaurant is that like a nut in a candy factory, it's
gonna be in everything. All their tools, all their machines, they put cover it,
they put... Well, when they bring you the food, when they bring you the food of the
restaurant, they say, "Would you eat this if you had to?" And you say, "If we had nothing else on the menu, except this human meat, would you eat it?"
it and they say yeah.
The trick is they show you that before they show you the menu.
So as soon as you get the menu and like if you say no, you get the menu, everything is
crossed out.
Yeah.
So yeah, what they say is there are one type of people who would eat this if they had to.
Yeah, right.
Who are you?
I'm an eater.
I'm an eater thatter.
matter. I watch that comedy special early today. I think I think back and I think
about all the stuff he said. You might be an eater humaner. If you would eat human
if you had to. You are a human eater. There's no if anymore. You are an eater.
You are a breather. Number three is pick up poop and eat it. Nasty. And someone
says I heard that this can kill you still it's very disgusting
they could kill you but it's still disgusting it's been in somebody's body
it might have been in Donald Trump's body
I'll tell you clearly than Hillary come on his shit would taste better than her
pussy. Yeah, and that's on God. And I love pussy. I love Hillary Clinton. And I hate shit. But let's be real and objective.
His literal shit would taste better than her puss. Yeah, and it's not even that it
would taste better. It's just that I want to do it more. I would rather do that than fucking lick her snatch.
So look, I tell someone at a party. It's not even about the taste, yeah. Yeah, I tell someone at a party I ate out
Hillary Clinton. They would say, "Who cares?" Yeah, so did every fucking Boy Scout in
America right but I swallowed Trump's log yeah using a fork and knife mm-hmm
suddenly people are hoisting me on your knees then they don't know what you mean
by log because it could mean you think yeah his white thing his white thing
probably an orange thing yeah second of all if somebody said that they ate
somebody's log I don't know that I think I would I would I would know it was poop
I don't know. Do you think you'd get a tapeworm from eating his shit?
Yeah, I don't know. I've heard people call that thing a log.
No, he's a tapeworm. He's giant. You know he'd keep it clean.
Yeah. I mean, he probably eats enough damn hamburgers from McDonald's and Covfefe
that it kills any damn parasite that could possibly exist in his gut.
And he probably eats Diet Coke and he poops a whole hamburger.
Yeah. And look, I don't like the guy. I sometimes think that he himself is a worm on the country.
Yeah, made of tape. Sometimes he almost reminds me of a worm.
- A red tape.
- Yeah, a pee tape.
- Oh my god, orange tape.
- A yellow tape.
- A pee tape worm.
- Green tape worm.
(laughing)
- He's a pee tape worm.
- Worm, green worm.
- Red worm.
- Yeah, Donald Trump is a green worm.
- Yeah, he's a red worm.
- He's a pee tape worm.
- He's a hamburger.
- He's a pee tape worm who eats hamburgers
and drinks Diet Coke, and he still,
and he hates it, but he'll still drink that crap.
Crap, what?
He's eating crap, like a tape worm.
- Yep.
- Uh-huh.
- Yep, eat my crap.
- Yeah, your crap.
- I would love to feed him my craps.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Little tiny pieces. - Okay.
- All right, go to swagpoop.com/shows
for tickets to the show.
And Pierce will be opening for the show.
Pierce was here on the show.
- Then I have to leave. - All of them.
- Then he has to go.
- He's gonna, okay.
- Then he has to go home.
And we all have to leave the show.