Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
[laughter]
[music]
You're a crap monster.
[explosion]
Banana ooh la la
Bidoo bidoo bidoo
Bidoo bidoo banana
Okay now do Young Thug's part
in Minion. How does it go?
I don't know. I'm Young Thug and I'm here to say
Bidoo banana
In a rapping way. In a rapping way.
Why did they get rid of that kind of rap?
They need to bring it back.
That's what's going to come back next.
That was my...
Because I saw a video the other day.
It's like two live crew on the Phil Donahue show and it's like them giving up on doing
the censored version of their song halfway through and like...
What were they saying before?
I don't remember.
It's like some...
It's the song that fucking...
It's Face Down Ass Up, right?
That's their fan...
I think so.
going to a hotel and shooting a load on a woman's face but it's like the same
delivery it's the same flow as like Run DMC so it's like I'm gonna take a girl
to a hotel and I'm gonna make the whole room smell like that's cool yeah it was
actually like two live crews so sick like current like what you rap about
about currently but in that in the real MC style that's cool I'm drinking all
this lean in my room I hope my mom doesn't come in with a broom I know so
many rappers are talking about their mom rappers are like oh I'm doing all those
drugs at my mom's house I've just been coming and hit me with a corn broom yep
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Yep, I'm sitting in my room doing a Perk 30.
I hope my mom doesn't come get mad 'cause it's dirty.
(laughing)
Yep, that's what they do.
- Yeah.
- I'm smoking all this weed in my car.
Here comes my mom with a candy bar.
(laughing)
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- I hate when my mom walks in when I'm rapping.
have and then you have those like those like videos on Facebook where it's like
a white guy and it's like this this rapper rips the mic without making fun
of his mom once he's not even a little bit scared of his mom I'm not even
scared of my mom nowadays talking about their mom mom these days every rapper
talks about their mom. Talks about their mom and their broom. Not me. I wake up at noon
ready for lunch. Here comes my mom. I love her a bunch. No, it's supposed to be the make.
They're mad that their mom comes in with a broom and they're mad at their mom for rapping
her hair down. This is the white boy on Facebook. No, the white boy wouldn't rap like that though.
He wouldn't rap like that. No, white boy. White boy. White rap is about being fast. Yeah,
come on mom. She's gonna give me a kiss. She's gonna give him a bunch of kisses and she's
because because white white guys when they rap they have to like they're like
I have to prove that I'm the fastest rapper yeah when they wrap I'm getting a
bunch of kisses from my mom and I'm going to I love my mom calm that's what
he would say that's a website that I started for my mom and I think she
really is the bomb and I will not use a bomb on my mom on my mom and my bomb and
my mom and my mom and my mom and my mom and my mom and my mom videos where it's
like fastest white rapper it's just a video of a guy rapping and they just
runs in front of the camera and he's like yeah it's Doppler effect like you can't
even hear my name is not a rapid but he goes yeah he's just I can run so very
fast my name's Caleb and I'm here to say right now I will run away you want to
see me do it again.
Yeah, man.
Yeah, I do.
I do want to see you do it again.
Do you guys want to see me run around the entire world?
We have a fly problem and there's a fly on my mic.
There's a fly on my mic.
Yeah, what I wouldn't give to be a fly.
I just heard the fly in my soup joke.
Well, you're going to move your phone or something.
Something's going on.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Something's going on.
What's going on?
On.
Is it good now?
I don't know, we'll find out.
Okay.
Um, I heard that, I heard the whole thing for the first time.
What's the fly in the soup?
The original one?
It's like, uh, what's, where's the fly, what is this fly doing in my soup?
I believe that's the backstroke.
That's the original one?
That's the original one.
You think that's the original one?
I feel like that's a far side joke.
I think that's just one of the ones.
Yeah, is that one of the ones?
I mean, I think it's like saying like I feel like it's like I heard the first song the other
day.
I've never what do you guys talk is it my girl heard a bunch of flying soup jokes, but I don't
know if I would consider one of them.
I don't know.
It's one of those things you read like a joke book or from your grandpa or something.
My grandpa was talking about no damn flying is.
Yeah, yeah.
He's like, there's a mix like waiter.
There's a soup on my fly.
That could be funny.
Yeah, yeah.
Waiter, I'm going to go to the bathroom make soup out of my fly because my way to the Democrat
my soup what's he doing he's being on welfare in there yeah yep he's being
corrupt yep mm-hmm he's in there getting abortions and being on welfare
picture maybe it's like yeah maybe it's like it's like oh probably being gay I
don't fucking know probably sucking another making my son what about yeah
what if it's like another Democrats fucking that's like a waiter suit where
there's a fly on my soup and he's like oh my friend that's not a fly that's a
Kenyan and he's on your soup he's in the Oval Office that's right mm-hmm
Yeah, he was born. He was born. Listen, he was born in Africa. That's fine. It's
okay, but it's okay to yeah. Nobody's saying it's a nobody's saying it's a
bad thing. Nobody is. I don't know why, but it's all mad. I think it's cool.
It's we have an African king as a president still still. We're talking
about behind the scenes. Joe Biden was born in Kenya. Yeah, he was yeah. I'll
tell you I was born. I'm sure I'm sure it out of the dark continent.
Let me tell you something. He was a baby that got brought in like the
expedition from like heart of darkness. He's got left there for three
hundred years.
That'd be so funny if it was like Joe Biden was like I was born in
Rhodesia. I mean
Delaware
about. I remember growing up in Rodea, in Delaware. I had a big bone through my nose. I just did.
Oh come on. I had rings on my neck. See my neck is so long I stretched it out with rings.
No Joe you didn't have that. I did. Never mind there's no photos. There's one photo,
No photos. There's a painting.
It's just a painting.
It's a presidential portrait.
Dude, that'd be so funny.
I was a warlord in Rhodesia.
I remember coming up,
one of our favorite things to eat
was that one Rockefeller kid that went missing.
We used to munch on him for lunch.
you know how they like Obama's presidential portrait everyone got mad at
because it's like...
I hated his presidential portrait.
Because it's too cool.
There was a bunch of bad ones though.
They're all bad.
Every presidential portrait looks like shit.
I thought the Obama one was kind of cool.
The Obama one with leaves, right?
Yeah, that one looks cool.
Can't show leaves.
That one looks cool, but it's kind of like, I don't know, it's like Tumblr like...
Nowadays, can't show leaves.
Tumblr Obama edits, you guys remember those?
[Laughter]
Remember the Obama fandom on Tumblr?
No.
Oh man, dude, the Obama fandom on Tumblr was crazy. They would ship Obama and Biden.
Oh, I kind of remember. I remember seeing posts from people who were like, "I'm making
that up, but if you did actually see shit, that's crazy."
No, not like shipping them, but you would always see those posts that were like them,
like Joe Biden, and it would be like writing dialogues between Joe Biden and Obama.
Oh, Biden.
He hated Joe Biden, though.
Yeah, well, no, but people would always write, like, make it like, "Joe Biden." I keep saying
Joe Biden would say like a pun to Obama and Obama would be like come on Joe.
I would read the ones where it's like you got your finger in my mouth Barack.
How about you go and put your penis in there.
instead put your penis in my... I'm Obama now I'm gonna do it for my country. I had a necklace made of fingers.
I had a necklace made of fingers in Rhodesia. They based claw from Black Panther off me.
Okay, so Cameron can say necklace made of fingers and I can't say bone through nose.
Correct. How is that different? How is that different? That's way different. That's way
worse. He said the necklace made of fingers. Let him have it. This could be a lizard bone.
You can't say that. Lizards don't have bones. That's a lie. Lizards don't have bones either.
Lizards don't have bones. I'm fucking done with you guys. And plus it could be lizard
fingers. Yeah, and it could be plastic fingers. It could be a plastic bone. It could not be
a plastic bone. We could have bought it at fucking Urban Outfitters. It could not be
be a plastic how you don't know you never want a bone in your nose. I have.
You wore a bone through your nose. I wore a bone through my nose and big rings on my neck.
Okay and why did you do that? Because I was being racist. Star Wars cosplay?
Okay. I was being so racist. That's okay I guess.
Alright yeah I feel defeated. Yeah.
I had a castle.
It looked like the castle from Monty Python.
I went I went to Wakanda. I think I went I
and I saw I went to Philadelphia. I went
yeah. I think that's what it was. Yeah, that's where he says. I
went to a condo. I know one of his aids whispers in his ears
like Philadelphia I went to Wakanda famous for the cream cheese I saw a
Liberty Bell in Wakanda I saw I got I went to Geno's and then I went to Pat's I
went to Pat's again and then I went to Geno's again I kind of just kept I
forgot which one had my order he should they should do crazy frog with with Joe
Joe Biden yeah. I think that would honestly. He does crazy frog when he tries to say any
word. If I did have a video with crazy frog in the oval office would Joe Biden be like
I'm here with my good friend crazy frog. Yep that would break the internet. That would
one break the internet. Aave club if you're listening to this get on it. You say the AAVE
club yeah no I already said what's the deal before he said that what's going on
nothing's going on dude what's going on what is going on with you accidentally
did you guys see that video of Joe Biden where he's like it was a recent one
where I feel like we haven't got that many good we got a bunch of good ones at
first we haven't got that many good ones recently but there was a good one
recently where's like oh like America in one word it did but did it but he says
like five words after he's the best dude he's awesome I've been listening to a
lot of Rogan and did just Joe's Taron Rogan I ordered a lot of Rogan Josh
cuz I'm fat what I went there oh I'm so fat and I love to fuck I don't even know
what what I'm being Amy Schumer right now oh and I'm a woman Amy Schumer
doesn't love to fuck she fucking hates it yeah she hates fucking she didn't she
finger a cab driver no i think her vagina is like medically small what did
yeah i believe that but didn't like there's a whole thing a really big
problem in hollywood wasn't there like a a story that broke or something
i believe that it's like i'm serious i heard she was i heard she was raised in
the congo yeah yeah she was raised in rhodesia too
yeah she was one of the white rhodesian settlers like joe biden
and there was nothing in her nose at all. No, I heard she was a warlord. She did get
box braids though. Yep, and that was fucked up. Yeah, that was weird. That was weird.
Yeah, I heard she had 50 children. Wasn't there, there's like a whole thing where it's like
Amy Schumer's like, I made a cab driver finger me. Or is there a whole thing of that? It was
like a whole thing of that. Really? She's, I feel like I hadn't heard about her in so long.
and she hosted the Oscars. She hosted the Oscars now she has a Hulu show coming out.
They play an ad between yeah on every ad break where I'm watching Always Sunny.
They play they got to put her in a cage. It's so great it's so fun that how bad
Hulu shows are now that they can't even make the trailer look good. Where like
they'll try it'll be a comedy show and the only jokes that are in the trailer
are someone being like so this just got weird and it's just like just 50 clips in
a row of people saying that. Yeah I no disrespect to Amy Schumer as a
comedian but she needs to be completely treated like a King Kong style animal and
put in a cage and every special should just be her in a cage going "argh" banging on the
bars and stuff. But no disrespect to the comedian. And then people dressed up like the 1920s in the
audience pointing and laughing. Don't be afraid, it's just the fattest woman in the world. It's a
hysterical woman. Yeah. Also she should have to wear different outfits. Yeah. She did a whole
special special like I'm wearing a leather suit here's a great special for
Amy Schumer okay it's an it's a medical from the bottom of the well to medical
operating from the bottom well why would you interrupt my my story go ahead go I
after you after you said I have a special idea for it's a medical
operating theater right and it's a hundred and fifty people in a theater in
the round and there's doctors are just taking off her legs that I really good
Here's a special idea for her the all you can eat special
899 yep, and she's she's on like is it like like a naked sushi thing, but it's
like golden corral food. There's a big pot of gravy. Yeah, yeah,
it's she's she's a plate and it's just like it's like it's like a like a kid's
charcuterie board.
Like Reese's cups
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, I heard I hate fucking job of the hut
Yeah, dude, that's her line
Yeah job of the huts dick is very weak
He's got we came weird wick. Yeah, i'm fat. He's like literally a giant ball of slime
He's literally a garbage. He's a serious garbage pale kid literally
He's literally a fat slug, but he's not as disgusting as my very small pussy
or my ex oh
small yeah. I mean seriously Yoda can't even get his pinky up here yeah and we
tried.
Yoda's pinky is big.
Even an ant's pinky wouldn't go in my tiny ass.
Yoda's pinky was a penis.
If Yoda's pinky was a penis, that would be a huge penis.
What are you talking about? Yoda is tiny.
His pinky is huge.
Okay, I get what you're doing here, but that doesn't work because we're talking
about hands and you have a hand that everyone can see.
Yoda has a hand in up his butt.
the control.
What doesn't you know how they originally wanted Yoda to be a
monkey in a costume is I wish they did that that would be so
they were going to put a monkey in a full costume. Yeah, imagine
how fucking terrifying awesome it would be so cool still with
Yoda's voice. It's like they're just like cutting like like
there's so many scenes, clips of just like a monkey running at a
crew member just over and over again. Every time they notice
yeah every time they cut to Yoda he's running directly at the camera. That'd be so sick.
Frank Oz is trying to like do the ADR or whatever. If they just spray painted a monkey that would
have been cool. I think that they should they should have to castrate all actors like they
do monkey actors. I agree. Yeah. Yeah. They castrate monkey actors. Yeah. So Dunstan had
Dunstan couldn't have sex. Dunstan yeah any any monkey well monkeys that are in movies
that either have to castrate them or they will attack all the women on set. Well there's
Here's that story of that Robert Downey movie that has the monkey in bed with the girl.
Oh yeah, and didn't the monkey wrangler, wasn't he like a...
He was like, yeah, for like 20 extra bucks, the monkey will fuck her.
And the girl was like, okay, I'm down.
And Robert Downey Sr. had to be like, no, you can't fuck this monkey for $20.
Yeah, monkeys can...
I've definitely talked about it before.
a movie with a baboon where the they couldn't have any crew members that were
on their periods because the baboon could smell it and would attack them I'm
serious you know you got a giant boner that's a airbrush it out of the movie
yeah it got a boner from a period it would know it just constantly had a
boner but it literally yeah there's like that's what happens if you don't if you
you don't castrate a monkey actor.
I'm serious.
The movie's called Shackma.
Shackma?
Shackma.
I want to see that boner.
Let's see here.
Is it disgusting?
Here's the baboon.
And it's just like and in the movie you can tell it's just
like genuinely a tat like it like it's like a horror movie.
So it's like runs at doors and stuff and it's just like actually
it like it goes like and like tries to rip the door open and stuff it's really
scary. Oh so it's about the monkey being evil. Yeah, yes, my god, you're terrifying.
Yeah, dude, oh they're really scary. Monkeys are scary. I don't fuck with
baboons at all. No, I saw baboons doing something very bad at the zoo to a
little baby baboon. Oh my god, I thought you're gonna say to a baby. Yeah, well to
yeah, a baby. What did they do to a human baby? They did something. One of them did
did a bad thing to a baby baboon a big baboon and a baby baboon.
Wait, you saw this?
At a hulla baloo.
At a zoo?
Yeah.
A hulla baloo.
You saw a baby baboon get attacked by a-
Well, I didn't get it.
I saw an adult male baboon rape a baby male baboon at the zoo
in front of a bunch of kids.
I never told you that before.
Really?
You told us that?
That was- what zoo was that?
That was-
What zoo was that?
That might have been-
I'm trying to remember when that was in Chicago. It wasn't Chicago because it
was just me and it must have been here. Maybe it was it might have been
prospect Park Zoo. Do they have baboons? I don't I've never been to any zoo
here. I would might have been Chicago. I don't fucking remember. I've been to
too many damn zoo went to a zoo and they chased it down and and yeah, yeah,
and there were kids watching and the parents are like
sure it was a baby. Yeah, you can tell if it's a baby. You can tell. Did it have a
diaper on? It was a baby. And a rattle? It was a tiny baby baboon. I choose to believe it was a small girl.
It was not a girl. Or a young man. Why would you choose to believe that? You can
just... You can erase the... Yeah. You don't even see it. You don't have to believe anything about it. You can visualize it as a cartoon and it doesn't exist. You can choose to believe that none of this happened. Yeah. I'm making it up.
Actually, I choose to believe that it was two babies now. Did you guys try to
talk me out of it. I went to the I think when I the first month I lived here no
wait yeah yeah yeah the couple weeks into me living here I went to the Bronx Zoo
by myself. It was cool but it's like I went on a Saturday and it was like all
like families and shit and I was just like oh there's like yeah like we're the
unless I bought like a unless I bought like a fast pass like there's no way I'd
see any of the cool animals I did see a red panda for the first time. What are you talking
about a fast pass? You get a fast pass for a zoo? Is there a line to see the animals?
The cheetah pass. There is like school exhibits, like the coolest exhibits you'd have to wait
in line for like hours. Damn I've never been to a zoo like that. Dude the bronc zoo gets
packed. The Chicago zoo is free and if any of the zoos here were free I would just go
like twice a month probably. Dude I saw the coolest, I saw a giraffe in person for the
the first time to this is say I was so cool. I only like alligators. We saw
iPod monkeys. Yeah, what?
I mean, they have iPods. What really? No, I made that. I can't go to the zoo.
What the hell? Really? You just made that up? Yeah, I can't go to the zoo.
What we did say we saw treadmill monkeys. Really? No, dude, stop at the
Chicago Zoo. We saw lightsaber monkeys at the Chicago. I don't believe that.
Okay, it's good. It's not true, but you can't say I pod monkey. We saw polar
bear. Really? No, I saw a white
there's white monkeys. I saw a white there. Really? Okay, well, there are
white monkeys. Yeah, there's there's all by no. We saw flying monkeys. Really?
No, I saw a green monkey. Really? Where boogers? You really? You know, we saw
a hundred giraffes. Oh, my God. Really? No, we saw to
I can't go to the zoo if my mom asks me what I'm doing
and I tell her I'm at the zoo,
she fucking says that Rocky quote at me.
She's like, "Oh, retards love the zoo."
And it ruins the whole zoo day for me
'cause then it's like,
it ruined it for me on that day
'cause I was like,
yeah, I'm really at the zoo alone right now.
- At the zoo alone is cool.
That's impressive. - I'm really at the zoo
by myself.
I'm a full grown man at 23. - I'm really at the zoo
alone right now.
- Don't let your mom fucking talk shit to you, dude.
What?
- Yeah, that's kind of pathetic.
letting your mom get to you I didn't I didn't get to me I just had a moment did
I had a moment where I was looking at a lizard and then I was like I just I
paid $23 to we saw wizards at the zoo in Chicago no no yes really no oh fuck I
saw a wizard outside of the zoo really he's outside though he was they were
letting him in why not he was a he's like a dirt wizard damn really yeah oh my
He lived in a box.
- Oh, really?
- When you were at the Bronx Zoo,
did you see the Frankensteins?
- I did.
- They have Frankensteins there?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- I mean, I haven't been there,
but I heard they have Frankensteins there.
- Oh my God, that's awesome.
- Yeah.
- I saw--
- You don't wanna go during a thunderstorm, though.
- Okay.
- Oh, you know what I did see at the Bronx Zoo was,
this is like--
- I saw all the Roguerettes kids at the zoo.
- It was like an older man,
he was in a, like a really fat old man.
He looked like, you know the fat biker twins?
- No.
- They ride the tiny, they're like the 200 pound,
like 300 pound twins,
and they would ride tiny motorcycles together.
- Wario?
- Wario and Mario.
I saw a guy who looked like one of them.
- In the House of Mirrors?
- No.
- Yo!
- I saw a reptile.
- What the hell is the worst zoo ever?
I got a same ugly. They don't have a house of mirrors at the zoo. Yeah, they do. No,
they don't. They really do. I'm serious. They do. They do. No, I saw it there. I saw
a ghost at the best mullet I've ever seen in my life at the Bronx Zoo was a really
old man. Yeah, fat old redneck guy. I didn't even see one of those in Wilmington.
You got to step up down there. I should have taken you to to fucking Lumbel
Lumbleton Lumbleton mm-hmm that's real
Real place
Lumbul ton
Yeah, yeah, it's an hour
outside of Wilmington yep
Everyone there has a mullet
Every single person in the seriously yeah, do they have
barbecue there yeah they got it all over what town's next to London next to
Lumberton yeah what borders it Syracuse stop why it's what was him hitting his
foot right here oh my you need to chill I thought that was dude I stopped there
was a bomb in here a ticking time by there was a ticking time bomb in here
you ruined me talking about you don't have to talk about it anymore I'm not
what's down here or Lumbleton hmm like what towns are around us around it
Syracuse yeah yeah Syracuse North Carolina Cincinnati yeah and farm
Farmville
who works there at Farmville you have a cousin who works at Farmville mm-hmm
Yeah, I know a bunch of people who work at Farmville.
That's where the Krusty Krab is.
The Krusty Krab is in Farmville.
Farmville, North Carolina, beautiful place.
Yep.
Beautiful place.
Seriously.
Horrifying history.
Yeah, really, the racist history of Farmville.
Yeah.
It was actually the first coup in, actually the second coup.
It used to be called Plantationville.
Yeah.
It's really bad.
They changed it to Farmville only two years ago.
Yeah, now it's really bad.
A lot of statues have come down in the past few years.
Yeah, they have a statue of Ulysses Hitler.
Mm-hmm, yeah. Joe Farm.
Joe Farm, who the town is named after.
The creator of it.
Joe Farm, the creator of Farmville, actually, he was called the Slave Punisher.
Yep. He was called Slave Hitler. That was his nickname.
Yeah.
And that was before Hitler.
Before Hitler.
That's how evil he was.
It's because he called them that because he hit them so much.
He hiddled them a lot. Yeah. Which is a seriously original kind of hitting he came up with.
It's southern slang. It's like Junebug or like Cheerwine or whatever. It's like stuff they make
up. Cheerwine isn't slang. It's stuff they make up that doesn't make sense down there because they're
all huffing glue. We're not huffing glue, okay? We have Gin X in our water supply. You have gin
in your water supply because you're all alcoholics. Yeah, my dad's damn house. What's up?
Yep, new Amsterdam gym.
And the damn water supply.
Now we have a Teflon by-product in almost every part of North Carolina's public water.
That is sick.
So you just like, every damn fluoride.
Through fire and violence.
But you know we got that too.
No.
Yep.
Damn, you wish you did and maybe fixed all your damn teeth down there.
All the mom, every mom in North Carolina just gets cancer.
Pretty much every single one.
they're addicted to water the dads are good because they drink beer mm-hmm yep
beer kills the virus of beer kills every virus it's true answer virus I mean if
you drink I mean that's like a virus people didn't drink water until like the
1700s or whatever yeah mostly they were drinking like fermented drinks because it
kills the the like nasty crap said it was the age of like it was cool hmm they
drank it cuz it's cool and delicious now the age of enlightenment goes because of
I didn't know everyone started drinking caffeine and was like what if we put
four wheels on a car yeah we already had a car yeah we had a three-wheel car we
invented the three-wheel car we were drunk he's falling over like shot
invented that's not the first car and then they're like that three wheels it
just looks stupid yeah it kind of looks like no a penis no it looks like a
slingshot asshole it looks like a penis and then you put four wheels on it looks
like a box okay no it looks are they expensive is a slingshot yeah I don't
think they look expensive but they're not they're the most expensive car you can
buy it's like made of plastic it like this that is the most expensive vehicle
it should be cheaper cuz it's it should be cheaper than any four-wheeled car
cuz it definitely yeah it should be a three I'd be like a price match thing
where it's like you can pay three quarters of the price thousand dollars
for that super cheap I would I would guess that it's 50 a slingshot for the
office I'm down yeah I would love to have one there's a stick that would be cool
we should get an ATV hilarious slingshot is you get a warthog okay what else
nothing else that's all you get that's all I can think of so you know how much
you get home is car from the show okay we should want to eat a slingshot s
$20,000. Oh, that's not that bad. $20,000. Brand new or used? Slingshot SL is brand new. Oh,
cool. Oh, also. School. Oh, school. For like a new car, that's not that expensive, right?
I don't know. I've never bought a car. The most I've ever paid for a car was $1,800.
That looks like a twisted metal car. That looks like a hot wheel. That's actually really
fucking cool. Yeah. The Slingshot Signature LE, that is $35,000. We can get that. Let's
just do it yeah well we can go to the yeah if we go to Washington Ave in
Bellevue Belleville New Jersey which is only 13.5 miles away just buy one there
we can go to the motorcycle mall oh is it technically a motorcycle yeah do you
have to have a driver's license to drive a slingshot no you don't that's the best
part about the Polaris slingshot really don't need a license really yeah yeah
yeah really no really no you can also buy a
slingshot oh this is the dude you guys
remember in like December when there was
that guy who would dress up exactly like
the Grinch and yeah I drive yeah I'm a
slingshot around and I did like the full
movie makeup he did great in Santa suit
that's yeah yeah he was and he would go
he's committed it was fucking weird it
was scary I don't like when guys do
stuff like that what yeah like you're
not making money off of this you're
doing you're just a guy going around
like that. Especially if you're alone. If you don't have a guy with you.
Hold on. New Polaris 2021 Polaris Slingshot. Original new on Alibaba.com. $1,500.
What? Let's buy it.
Let's send an inquiry.
Send an inquiry. You have to send an inquiry.
$1,500?
We're taking that on tour.
Quantity needed. How many units? I need 500 units.
I bet it's a minimum order of like 100.
Hi, I'm interested in your product. I would like more details.
We could get five of those.
Dude, five slingshots on tour?
Yeah.
We all--
Just a convoy?
Yeah, a convoy of slingshots.
You two can't drive.
Just driving 90 miles an hour down the highway in a slingshot.
I don't think they go very fast. I think they're really just for parades.
Yeah.
They're for looking like a grinch.
Hi, I'm interested in your product. I would like some more details.
I'm going to look on Facebook Marketplace for a--
looking forward to your send sign in with Google okay. I bet they have one on
Facebook marketplace right they have to for a Polaris link shot yeah maybe it's
got to be that's got to be the cheapest place to buy one. I wonder if you get it
shipped market. I feel like it might come in pieces and you have to put it together
ten thousand dollars. Oh, it says it says beware
beware beware. What does this mean? I'm guessing that's got eleven thousand
miles on it. Structural day. Do you want to buy a structural damage?
Polaris? How do you put a let I know miles on a fucking slingshot? I mean, I
guess if you have a slingshot, you're taking that shit everywhere. Yeah, do
that's not a thing you like leave in the garage. Oh, in my day that like down
I know I leave it in the garage and I use it as like a couch. I'm not going to
fucking drive that thing around. Let me see if I can sort by lowest price. I'm
going to take that to my office job. Here's one for one dollar. Oh my God,
really? I love when they do that on Marketplace when they do like in search
of yeah. Okay, one dollar one dollar lots of one dollar ones. Oh, how about
this one? Look at this a Kawasaki Ninja. That's the same thing, but I'm guessing
better because it's not a fucking Polaris link. Oh, it's his turbo on it.
Yeah,
yeah,
you make more stupid cars. We could yeah,
we could get this twenty five thousand.
What did you buy this
mini cup race car? You guys ever do like a pine wood derby or anything? No,
I wish I that seems like fun. My dad did with my brother when they were in my
and my brothers and like boys cats. My dad was like we're going to make the
wheels on the thing out of pennies. He's like that that's going to work really
well, drill a hole in a penny and they like and all the other kids use like
fucking little wheels on their thing. My dad was like we're going to use
pennies and then they started the race and my brother's car just didn't even it
didn't move at all. Why would pennies move listen to this this? I just found
this when I was looking to to buy a slingshot on on Facebook marketplace
2022 looking for sponsors for five race series trying to find sponsors for this race season
me and possibly my eight-year-old son will both be running a cart at New York race complex
this summer have lots of real estate on the car for advertising not looking for a lot
just maybe help with tires could do the whole season or just a single race would he expect
you to purchase your own stickers to put on the cart both sides front back and helmet
space available message me if you want to talk about it on some kids go our version of the
super mega NASCAR. Putting on, making the kid wear a helmet that says I heart eating shit.
And then just like us taking like tons of photos with the kid in the car. Just like
we swagged up this kid. We give him like a Sullivan backpack. Yeah dude. It'd be so awesome.
Dude a Sullivan backpack. It's a good idea. Shaped like a frog. Yeah that's what I'm saying
with the arms dangling that's a good idea. Oh my gosh. Slingshot available for rent.
Slingshot available for rent. How much? I'll rent one for a week. It says $250.
Per what? It just says. If it's per day, I'll rent one for one day. Yeah.
All booking information can be found on this link. We need to do like a...
What could we do? We have to have a parade. Yeah. We need to do a parade.
annual
We could totally do that in New Orleans we gotta do it in New Hampshire, dude
Yeah, where we won't get in trouble for trying to shut down a street. Yeah. Yeah, you do that
We could totally do that on Elm
People know people get really pissed off if you did it here. I feel like people do it all the time. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
There's just big brown trucks.
There's a good chance at Old Holmes Day in Londonderry.
That we could get a float?
We could probably do a float.
Dude, I would do anything to have a float.
Yeah.
Preferably root beer.
Yep, yes sir.
But we'd have to go to fucking Londonderry.
I mean, you guys went to that.
I love Londonderry.
You guys, you saw that stretch of road before we got to the skate park?
It was sick.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
They have a parade there.
trees huh there's just trees no people come out to see it no no where the
words were the Matthew Thornton school is there's a big parade there every year
and then there's that's at the parades parade yeah parades in like in like New
Hampshire like mass where it's like that and there's like not that many houses
are the best because everyone comes yeah show yeah they all stand on the side of
the road there's Apple fest which is where all like the white rappers I didn't
like the kids who had bands in my town did shows.
- Doing a good show at Apple Fest?
- That big stage with the, there's the cannon.
That's where they all did shows and stuff.
- I'm a huge news guy,
and then I'll get off Facebook Marketplace,
but you see this dirt bike?
It's on sale, original price $255,
sale price $59.97.
- Oh my God, what the fuck, that's such a deal.
- Yeah, I mean, we have to order--
- It's a Segway dirt bike.
like ten of them right yeah yeah that's a good idea they don't they don't do like
Segway tours anymore huh I would love yeah he fell off the grand piece I think
he's from London dairy no really or he lived there or something that was like
we can we go can we find a Segway tour when we're on tour I really want to
ride a Segway I've never ridden one before that was I remember that was really a
like a watershed moment for me as a child I think learning that the Segway
guy died testing or show demonstrating the Segway mm-hmm and he just fell off
the thing it was really like it really changed my perspective on a lot didn't
we find that out on the podcast no that we saw Segway monkeys at the Chicago
that would happen when we were in middle school Segway monkeys Wow what's a
segment they read Segway really no I think he was from Portsmouth I don't
know anyway the list today is the 40 Star Wars pickup lines that are oh I
are you know i forgot was that we have this is a the may they were the fourth
year my do you know i do it's kind of like a double holiday 'cause recording
this on four twenty and it comes out on may the fourth so we forgot we did the
list was we were so
made the fourth week twenty
we should be smoking salvia to the afternoon
i'm in a read you guys that the the first line here on this on this uh...
star wars pickup lines are calls the reason i picked this one
no need to use the force because these star wars pick up lines will do the
trick
i love using the well i was about to use the
i was gonna use madam madam i was about to use the force on you
to have sex with you use the instead i will i will use my language
i will use language i'll use the beautiful words
um calling all star wars nerds are those hello
Hi.
Not me.
Hey.
Maybe you guys are, not me.
You know how like a nerd talks like,
oh my God, hey.
I love Star Wars.
I love smoking.
That's how they sound.
Every nerd is like,
hey girlfriend.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
It's true.
Especially Star Wars nerds.
Yeah.
Number one.
They do like this,
that hand thing.
Yeah.
That's the hand thing, they do the force.
It's like force lightning hand.
It's a force choke.
And they,
(mimics spraying)
- That's the sound they make when they pee, too.
- I got in trouble in first grade, I got in trouble,
'cause there was some kid in the stall,
and I was like, "Come on, I have to pee so bad,
"oh, I'm peeing myself."
And a teacher heard me doing that,
'cause I was screaming it, and she walked into the bathroom,
and I was like, "Huh?"
'Cause there's a girl in the boys' bathroom,
it's Mrs. Gray and she was like, "You shouldn't be doing that." I was like,
"Okay, I'm sorry." When I was in first grade, I worked at the FBI and I went
skydiving a lot too. Damn. Yeah, and I actually got fired for being drunk when
I was in first grade. Yeah. Don't take that back. I was only six. No, I seriously
was drinking alcohol. The first pick up line is, "You're the Obi-Wan for me."
- What?
- You're the Obi-Wan for me.
- Wait, okay, so what, you're gonna be my master
and then I'll fucking betray you?
- Yeah.
- Why would you tell that to a girl?
- You could tell that to a girl.
- Why would you say that to a girl?
Yeah, you're basically gonna become my master
and we're gonna be best friends and fly in a supercar
and then also at the end I'm gonna fight you at a volcano.
How is that gonna be hot to a girl?
- That's hot, it's gonna be hot to a girl.
- That's not, no, it's not sexual.
- Girls like being betrayed.
Girls like being betrayed. - Obi-Wan never
fucked anybody. - Girls, women love,
girls, women love being betrayed.
being betrayed. He's a monk. He's a Jedi. He fucked Sabina Wren. What the hell are you
talking about? Is that a porn star? Yeah. Shut up. She was a Mandalorian. I wonder what porn
star names are like in the Star Wars universe. Aayla Secura. They're normal. Aayla Secura.
She's a Jedi. Blue Jedi. Blue Twi'lek. Two tentacles. That's funny. Two lightsabers.
Because I feel like you have to like, it's a combination of you know guys.
a era. See it sounds like a sound like her like name like like Jimmy cock is
like a porn star name and then a star wars name is like cleveland glorbon
cleveland yeah, so he's like glorbon cock
glorbon clock
esmond fudd
a good star wars. Do you still my heart like the rebels store the death star
- What's up?
- You stole my heart like the rebels
stole the death star plans.
- The death star?
- You stole my heart like the rebels
stole my death star plans.
- The death star plans or planes?
Hey, hey, can you speak up?
- You're right there, whatever, whatever, whatever.
- Here, we need, no, we need to test these.
Okay, I'm gonna turn into a girl in one second.
- Hey.
- Whoa, I'd join the dark side as long as you were there.
- What?
- Would you eat my poop?
- Yes.
(laughing)
What?
- Would you eat my poop if I was a dog?
- Yes.
I must be drawn to the force because Yoda only one for me because Yoda only one
for me. What does Yoda only one for me if I was a lizard for me under a heat lamp?
Yes,
this is winning right now. Fucked he's winning the Star Wars nerd is losing the
at the jock over here. He's a he's a jock right now. Okay, okay,
related twenty five star war effects only true fans know okay
turn now trending the best Easter candy. Everyone wants in their baskets this
I love sweet. If I was a bird would you put your finger in my cloaca?
Yes
That's just crass. This is this wouldn't work in real life. Well, she's actually a this is it's Lisa Lampanelli
Stuff like that. That's who I'm being right now
Yeah
You're as bright as a lightsaber. What?
That's not Lisa Lampanelli. What?
Would you touch my balls? Yes
Okay, thank you
he's back he's back he's alive he's risen he's risen yeah I can't believe he died
and we didn't get to do an episode about it the day that he died cuz we had a
backlog yeah I miss him already dude he was the best yeah I'm glad I missed him but then I hit him
yep I hit myself with my own car he didn't do that that's what Anton Yelchin
did my name is a time yeltsin oh he is Antonia with how loud Gilbert
Gufford is his name would be Anton yelling yep yep
how loud he was well he is he's still out a ton he should have been named a
ton of metal and steel belting him into it into it an oak tree yeah and Gilbert
got fried mm-hmm yeah died yeah died he burnt he burnt got fried who else died
died that has a name who else died that as a man that's a good question.
Lisa Lampanelli would be I leased a lot of spaghetti.
I leased a Lamborghini.
From a restaurant and it gave me diabetes and it killed me.
I leased a Lamborghini and crashed it.
Who else died?
I don't care.
I died.
I just died.
When Charlie XCX dies you bet I'll be singing that song on the podcast.
Well the XCX is like her face because the X is her eyes and maybe the C is her mouth
or her nose.
sees her weird nose. Yeah, her weird nose. So it's like XCX. Yeah. She has a C for a
nose, right? I don't remember which one. She has like a C for a nose, yeah. And Charlie
could be like gnarly. Like she's like a gnarled corpse. She's dead. Amy Winehouse
died drinking wine in her house. Yep. Kurt Cobain died from a shot to gain. And
it could be like Chris Farley XCX and that's like the X's is eyes. Chris Farley XCX
and then they ship and Dale's a dance yeah that's all I got he ate he ate
chips and dales chips and and made a Dale with the devil and it kills him
of hey hey hey yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Okay, Norm MacDonald he he had a farm. He bought the no he yeah, okay, so he
bought a farm and the animals or McDonald is warm no longer norm no
long gold. Yeah, yep is your last name Skywalker because you Luke so good.
This list is so bad. I just thought the force thing was funny at the
beginning. Yeah, do you guys want to have the Easter candy that everyone
in their baskets this year? Yes. What kind of Easter candy we got? The best Easter
candy everyone wants in their baskets this year. By Karen Cicero. By Karen
Cicero. Okay. Follow us down the rabbit hole for a look at new Easter candy plus
classic picks that make a basket feel complete. I hate those big-ass fucking bunnies man. Yeah.
Those, that is the worst chocolate ever made. I only like those. What are they filling, what
is the filler that they put in cheap chocolate that makes it taste so shit?
poop is it poop it might be rabbit is it poop is it is it it's probably rabbit
meat yeah that's rabbit I don't think rabbit is cheaper than rabbit me there's
so many rabbits fucking Hershey's there's so many rabbits yeah okay you're right
no it's never mind you know what's good to get on Easter what Christ's love yeah
yeah lucky for me I get it every fucking day of my life you fucking asshat chill
dude sorry fill out and say cat Easter lemon crisp miniature wafer bar oh wow
that sounds so good I'm so hungry already I need everyone wants not giving me this
and that everyone wants this in there in their basket a kit kat Easter lemon
crisp everybody's talking about this year I want to meet candy cat again this is
a cool website here's another article on this one saying why is airplane also
spelled aeroplane good question it's a good question I'm not gonna click on it
because I want to preserve the mystery. This is on new jersey.com. 25 cool
Easter basket ideas for teens they will be obsessed with. Oh RD, I thought that
was an N and a J. I need to wear my glasses more.
Weibler, Weibler, Weibler, Weibler milk chocolate bunnies. Those things are terrible. These bunnies look like the office. In the no sugar fiends,
in the no sugar fiends, that's a agree that world market has the best selection
of Easter candy from around the globe. I forgot about world market man. But let's
be honest they'll be gone before the Easter games begin.
What does that mean?
The Easter games and egg toss?
There's a link.
There's a link in the Easter game.
Three-legged rays?
Easter is a serious game day.
25 best Easter games to play with the whole family.
Whoa.
Well this is getting us down a rabbit hole.
Easter activities for everyone.
Was that candy?
What games do you play?
No.
Easter egg hunt.
I can't believe we didn't have an egg hunt this year.
It was my birthday.
Yeah and you didn't even want to have an egg hunt.
That's kind of fucked up.
Why would I want to have?
I don't want eggs on my birthday.
It was Easter on your birthday.
- A plastic egg?
- A cigarette hunt.
- What?
- You can put that inside the eggs,
that's the point, you put anything in the eggs.
- How am I supposed to open up an egg
and drain all the juice out?
- You never heard of a plastic egg?
And also you drain all the juice out when you die an egg.
- A plastic egg isn't an egg at all.
- Are you one of those freaks who dies a hard boiled egg
like a weirdo?
- Yes.
- What? - I never got that.
- Dying a hard boiled egg?
What, you die it and then you paint it with the vinegar?
- You can't even eat those eggs after
'cause they're covered in paint.
- Yes you can, you die it, it's on a shell.
it's no it's way better to drain it. I have you never you never blown the yoke
out of an egg. No really yes so fun. I grew up in fucking Farmville. Okay. We
didn't have that. We didn't have that you have eggs. No we didn't have we
didn't buy chickens for a hundred fifty coins.
We were a cow only farm Easter egg spoon race. Oh that was a classic. That one's
fun limbo
yeah make a limbo. You know what they say about limbo shop limbo stick. You know
- Do you guys know what they say about Limbo?
Do you know?
- Jack me nimble, Jack me quick.
- No, no, no.
- Oh, guys.
- This is what they say about Limbo.
They say, "How low can you go?"
- That's true.
(laughing)
For only $35.41, we could get a Giggle and Go Limbo,
outdoor games for adults and family,
Limbo game for kids, party games, backyard games,
lawn games, or outdoor games for kids,
ideal yard games for adults and family for all ages.
- Who do you think would be best at Limbo of us three?
- Definitely not me.
I have so much back pain.
- You're short, though.
- What?
- You're short.
tall and you're two inches tall. Pause. I'm not pausing. He noticed another man's height.
I didn't even notice. You noticed. So if I notice, so you admit it's true then. Yes.
Yeah, okay. That's all I need. I'm two inches tall. See if I give a fuck. I still fuck models.
Limbo. Hey, nowadays with the way the culture is treating height and how much people like
freaking tall man and Limbo is the one game you don't want to win.
True!
Okay. Seems like nowadays in the news with all this height stuff, Limbo is one of those
games you don't want to win at the Easter party. You don't even want to win this game.
Seems like this is one of the Easter games you want to lose. Okay, picture this,
you're at an Easter party, right?
You're at the biggest Easter party of the year. A million hot girls and they're not your family.
You're at a different family's Easter party. Let's just say they're bunnies.
yeah complete limbo, complete limbo and you're saying listen. I could go pretty
low yeah on one of these bitches, but I'm not going to show you my high bitch.
You have to pull out a tape measure or take me to the doctor and you know,
then I'm not going to take my shoes off and it seems like nowadays. If I played
this game, I'd rather lose than win. Yeah, never ask a woman her her. It's
like golf and never ask a man. If he wants to play limbo, yep yeah, because
he's going to say no yeah limbo is like golf. It's one of those games you want.
you don't even want to win.
- Listen, I may be small,
but I could still house a damn hungry man.
(laughing)
I'll take it down.
I'll eat it.
- Do you ever tell you about the--
- Within an hour, I'll eat an entire hungry man.
- I bought a hungry man recently,
like a couple months ago.
- Salisbury?
- No, I bought the fried chicken selects one.
I was pretty drunk.
I was coming home from a bar.
- No, and you left it in the oven, right?
- Yeah, I fell asleep with it in my oven.
Yeah, I wish it had just burned you alive. It would have been so it would have been so funny
We should have killed everybody on your entire block. Yeah one hungry man one hungry man single hungry
I just burnt just blowing up an entire sources are saying the fire was started after a stupid man fell asleep
Eating a hungry man waiting for his hungry man this
On succession the source of the fire was this fat piece of shit. It's just a picture of the guy
He has the Hungry Man.
There's a picture of the guy buying a Hungry Man at the store.
It's just like in grey sweatpants and a mustard stain.
If you're wondering where we got that photo, a patron of the grocery store just thought he looked stupid.
Just him checking out. It's like it's got the Snapchat thing on it.
It's like look at this fat piece of shit buying a Hungry Man.
I bet he's going to burn down his block later.
Cut to that.
it's an interview with the fat guy yeah he's the only one who survived the
aftermath it looks exactly like the aerial photo of the move bombing I don't
know I just wanted fried chicken and Popeye's was close and now watch me do
this cartwheel and amazes town makes them all forget about his crime with
amazing cartwheel.
Dun dun dun dun!
Breaking news, this guy did a cartwheel.
This guy did the coolest cartwheel I've ever seen. This guy did a cartwheel after doing
nothing.
And he's never done anything wrong. He's never done anything else.
This man was born one second ago and he did a cartwheel. This man did his first thing.
It was a cartwheel. Congrats to you Derek on doing the only thing you've
ever done.
He did his first thing.
He's just eating like
a hungry man that's so bird it's just like a black square brownie that when i
took the brownie out brownie hey bud
a brownie already looks burnt
i picked it up tell me what was it brown
it was don't tell me it looked like charcoal a brownie already looks like a piece of charcoal
if you told me the broccoli turned black then i might be a little impressed
this guy doesn't know a fucking thing about hungry mans
what is it you think the brownie is not is not brown and black no there's no broccoli
and hungry man there isn't the broccoli cheese surprise there's not a hungry man
broccoli cheese surprise extra with funfetti ice cream there's no fun well
how would you get all goes in the same oven why would there be ice cream it's
heatproof yeah ice cream I give you if you put if you put ice cream in the oven
it hardens like like model magic you're just jealous because you've never had
the different flavors of hungry man that I've had yeah yeah what are those this
this must be some hungry man in Japan.
- Calamari.
They have a calamari hungry man.
- Oh my God.
- Calamari and a ginger salad.
- Fried calamari.
- And yeah, it also has the funfetti ice cream
that's heat proof.
Okay, and you can put it in the oven for up to one hour
and it will be fine.
- Yeah, they heat proof the ice cream.
It comes in like plastic wrap that blocks the heat.
- Actually--
- It comes in a radiation shield.
- I just remembered, I just changed my memory
and it's actually, it's reverse ice cream
So it comes hot and you heat it up and it becomes cold.
But when it's in the frozen section, it's piping hot.
It's like, "Ah, ah, ah!"
You have to hot potato it into the oven, and then when you take it out, it's ice cold.
It burns your hand from coldness.
Yeah, yeah.
It's opposites.
So this limbo bar.
Opposites attract, right?
Yes.
That's why you put ice cream in the oven.
That's a myth.
So the mayor's reaction.
So isn't poop the opposite of my mouth?
Yes.
No.
Your butt's the opposite of your mouth.
is there to make a lot of the opposite of your mouth is probably your foot okay
why I'm car heard because you're I mean it's just it just is you know just it
just is it's a good point okay thanks you know what I used to be able to do
it on the old a grasshole Tyson yeah thanks I think of that guy you're the
grass hole my son thanks ass to grass nobody rides for free yeah nobody rides
ass or to grass Tyson crash grass or - nobody rides for free son that's
probably what we'll end up saying once we have spaceships and supercars yeah
yeah on the I want to put like a bumper that bumper sticker on like the next
Tesla ship bumper sticker I'd rather have a sticky bumper yeah and I could put
stuff I'd rather make her bumper sticky mm-hmm mm-hmm I'd rather be this I'd
rather put a baby on board her I'd rather be called the sticky the sticky
humper sticky yeah the humper the a breaky harder bird that's what I'd be
called breaky harder humper and dumper yeah
and then I leave her and then I leave her and then I'm a beaver we should make a
sign for your card says me on board I don't really I don't really I don't
really good idea for bumper stickers that I can't say because I want to make it.
It's the stevo thumbs up. Guys we have good bumper we're gonna make bumper
stickers yeah yeah I'll tell you guys a bumper sticker idea after the episode's
over. I feel like you've told me one before. I did yeah and it was really good I think yeah
so I think we should make me on board I won't have me on boards good yeah but we
could we could we're doing a bumper sticker drop yeah we're doing a bumper
sticker pop-up car yep you buy stickers from the car mm-hmm
yeah stuck to it mm-hmm and you got to get them off mm-hmm and you don't get
any sort of glue yeah or reverse glue I mean should I buy this $40 limbo limbo
stick yeah I feel like we need a limbo stick for the office
- Make a limbo stick.
- Can I read your review of the limbo stick?
- It's been so stressful having an office,
can we please go on a retreat?
- Yes. - I would love
to go on a retreat.
- Where would we go on a business retreat to?
- Six Flags.
- Six Flags would be pretty rollercoaster, rock and rolling.
- Yeah, that's a good point.
- I'm a little bit scared of going really fast.
- Okay, that's on you.
- You could go on the small coasters.
- I am a little worried about rollercoasters now
that a couple people have died on rollercoasters
in the past year.
- Those are carnival rides.
- Nuh-uh.
there were two drop towers yeah no the drop tower was it was at icon park
that's like not a real that's like well there was one there but it was like it
was a good drop tower it was the same like like manufacturer it's not in like
a real park though though I've been to that place that's like not that does
matter it's a restaurant but I'm saying they're not it's not like like I feel
like I like all the ones that I like have like like staff and stuff like that
one that's like a that's like a teenagers okay run the other one was was
a little girl died in a mine shaft drop tower. Well that's that she should have
been mining. She's a child. You should not be letting your kids spelunk at that age.
She died of black lung. Yeah, yeah, that's true. Yeah, no, but the Icon Park one, that was
yeah that was like a teenagers operated ride. Also I guess I'm like probably the
exact size of it. It's so crazy that they... You know why I am scared? Why? Because I look
exactly like a crash dummy. Yeah. So I'm worried that they might get confused.
Oh, we're testing the ride today. Oh, I say there's a crash dummy on the ride. We'll just we'll just leave him on buckle
Yeah, oh, that's cool. They added a we need to see what happens if a guy doesn't buck out boy. That's the yeah, what happens?
Yeah, it would just worry me a little bit
I would be I would be slightly mistaken for a mannequin a lot when I'm walking down the street people start putting clothes on me
I walk by a telco all of a sudden. I have a Kangol hat and
I'm wearing sweatpants. I say mama. Yeah, I get mistaken for the axe chocolate guy all the time
No. Yeah, I do. You don't. Women lick me. Women don't lick you. Women, a woman stole
my arm the other day and started eating it. That is something that would happen
to me as a mannequin, not you as a chocolate. That would, somebody, a teenager, a teenager,
would steal your arm as a mannequin, yes, but because I'm, people mistake me
for the axe chocolate guy, they steal my arm and they eat it like, and they put,
they melted like if it's like it's an I forgot though people people mistake me
you don't Broadway star really I don't I don't think you do Cameron put us side by
side you have chocolate skin I have shit does that mean my skin is straight
vanilla mm-hmm damn mm-hmm I look like a chocolate guy I'm strawberry I'm
strawberry you are I'm ready said you're vanilla so you can't switch okay I'm all
three no I'm a sweet combination I'm an old and I'm not Neapolitan I'm head to
I'm the ice cream man. I'm made of ice cream guys. No, no, it's not my profession, it's
my race. If you guys, if you guys, okay, if your entire body was Neapolitan ice cream,
what sections are you putting where? I think I might go red legs, black top, white middle.
I mean there's really only two combinations you can pick. It's not true. That's not true.
- Yeah, there's only two because--
- There's three flavors.
- There's three flavors, but Neapolitan is always
strawberry, vanilla, chocolate.
- It doesn't matter what Neapolitan always is.
- We're breaking that rule.
- So, no, 'cause then this is just,
no, there's only two 'cause you can only do
that combination or the reverse.
- So what are the two combinations?
- You aren't made of ice cream.
That's why I think that you have to,
'cause I don't really like chocolate ice cream.
I feel like most people don't, right?
So you make chocolate your head
so that you can keep your head without somebody eating it. A lot of people
like people like chocolate. I don't like rest of it's covered in clothes and
then people won't even notice
that it's ice cream. Yeah, okay. I mean if I was ice cream, I probably just
wouldn't I would wouldn't go outside in the freezer. Yeah, not me. Well, I
would be reverse. I'd be the ice cream from the hungry man that actually so
you have to get cooked in the oven. No, I'd go out and cook in the sun in the
summertime. Oh, what about the winter summer? So you get so overheated in the
winter. Do you guys hear my summer song? I came up with yesterday. That's pretty
Summer time to swing on the summer swing.
I didn't show you that?
No, I don't think you did.
Alright, so what's the deal? We're on tour right now?
We're not on tour. Yeah, we're on tour in four days.
Okay.
When this comes out.
Fuck.
So, guys, we only have four days left.
I don't give a shit. I don't care either.
But you guys should buy tickets, please, because it's going to be fun,
and you're not going to want to miss it because we're all going to ritually kill ourselves after the tour.
This is your last chance.
Yep.
You will never see me alive again.
Yes, if you would.
We are going to die in a car accident on the tour.
Absolutely.
There's no question.
Swagpoop.com/shows.
There's lots of shows and links to buy.
There we added some.
I know some people were disappointed that some shows were like 21 plus or whatever.
I think we added a few all ages and 18 plus.
LA and Chicago.
LA and Chicago we added 18 plus and all ages.
We added a 3 plus show.
Yeah, you have to be above 3.
We added a dog friendly show.
We added a dog friendly show in Bone Town.
And we, um, yeah we're dead by the time this comes out.
All of us died.
Yeah.
Alright.