come back and make a bet
crap monster
it's on k
it's on guys say
patrick to a song at the beginning can you say something out of pocket let's go
on
adjective
uh...
dancing
that's not an ad you know if that's a very okay fine uh... jumping
no that's not
you okay gas ask me
he's he goes first we're going to go for a couple he's been a mess that's why
seriously took to a shot going around up to terms
drivingly
that's an adverb
you're so fucking stupid jumping lee
that's an ad for an adverb
he's a key take four turns
for turning his last the way one more what the cat
he would say what
what s caleb oh wow okay cameron i need an adjective crazy with two r's that's an insult
that's not a that's not an insult can be an adjective that's not right you're so dumb
that's not true you're so stupid insult and also that's an adjective misspelled as well
which i need another adjective another adjective stingy stinky plural noun
smells. Oh I hope it's sticky smells. I hope they come back to back. Oh my god.
Okay why are you taking so long here? You can't write smells. No it's a plural. I need another
plural noun. And you're coming up with it this time? Yeah I just don't. You can't.
You can see the stuff. You can't. You're not allowed to write your own choices.
No, he can't see, he just sees a list of it says...
Oh, he's doing the lonely kid version.
Yeah.
Damn, I can't even think of a plural noun.
Just anything.
Smells.
Odors.
Oh, that's good.
Okay, and then an adjective?
Fuck.
Fucking.
Fumed.
Fumive.
you move okay the plural noun plural noun fumes oh my god he's taking all my
turns okay noun aroma okay plural noun smell smelling smelling smellers smellers
smellers smellers yeah yeah I smell sniffed sniff number 100 and thousand
100 and thousand yep smells down yep that's gonna be it's gonna be the
the nose stink stink yeah number no six thousand adverb smellingly smellingly
noun nose nose yeah plural noun noses noses verb sniffing sniff again all
right so at the end of the episode we're gonna have a crazy you can't fucking
it's cuz he is my cuz he wrote them all at the top and he will take him an hour
to transfer them down to the bottom you mean cam will just do our thing and you
write it down okay write it down now start it no we kind of keep right it's
I know cuz I want to keep everyone listening I want to get everyone
listening I want to like any episode I want to do all okay all right fine okay
and he's getting he's getting he's doing it all right now. Tis the wet season for
caroling here's how to make everyone's a Christmas a little more merry and crazy
gather six million of your of your six million friends. Wait Pat wrote six
million why did you pick that number? Gather six million of your stinky
friends? 6 million of your stinky friends and family? Pat what's wrong with you? And family smells?
6 million of your stinky friends? Come on now. What? Pick out a few classic odors.
(laughter)
- Just saying, like have yourself a fume-ive little Christmas.
- Fume-ive.
(laughter)
- Silver fumes.
- Huh?
- And frosty the aroma man.
(laughter)
- Frosty the aroma man.
Oh my god, that's a good guy.
- That's a good one.
Santa smellers on everyone's heads and sniffed to your neighbor's house.
Santa smellers?
Knocked one hundred and a thousand times on the front stink.
Nothing.
Knock six more times and smellingly.
When your neighbors answers the nose.
Has he or she...
No, no, no, no.
Like to hear you sing a song.
To answer the nose.
Come on.
If your neighbor says yes, sing your noses out.
If your neighbor says no, sniffing away.
- And then start talking about noses so much
here at the end, dude.
- What are you talking about?
- This is not good.
(laughing)
- What do you mean?
- You did a bad thing.
- Yeah, you were naughty.
- How is this naughty?
- You're not getting any smellers from Santa this year.
- Santa will never give you a smeller.
- Frosty the Aroma Man's not coming to life for yo ass.
- How is that naughty?
Okay, let's just do another one.
- You put the magic smell on his head.
this one's been done oh well it's already let's see what this other person where'd
you get this was I found I found this on the street
oh the office you stole this from a child Wow this hold on no I didn't steal
from a child but I stole it from somebody who's pretty awesome really
read it out okay deck the masks with bows of riots the coven 19 to be
catastrophic follow a lot now Don we now are depressing apparel follow a lot
Troll the ancient long Carol follow
La La La La
See the sanitizing you'll before us
Yeah, strike the virus and join the chorus uh-huh do this is fire this is
This could follow me now is a rising measure
While I tell the tale of scary treasure is there more news. I don't know I think that's the only one
- That's the only one they did.
(laughing)
- I think that is the only one they did.
- And then they just threw it on the street.
- Take the masks with boughs of rites.
And I think that this is probably the same person
that threw away the Zelda painting there.
- You think so?
- Oh, probably.
- I think it could be.
- Okay, here's a mad lib.
This one is called Hot Fudge Sundaes.
- I don't even wanna know what this is about.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I think I have some ideas.
we need a noun. Fudge. Number. One. One hot fudge sundae. Plural noun. Sundays. An adjective.
Another adjective hot, hottie. An adjective yummy, ice cold. Noun topping.
number one down ice creams
now nut peanuts
this
top
verb past tense eat it
plural noun spoons
adjective
delectable
in a verb
spoon chewed chewed chew melty did
making a hot fudge fudge as simple as
one two one all you need are the following Sundays a pint of fudgy ice
cream, one jar of hot sauce, and one cup of ice cold nuts. One can of whipped
topping. Yep. One maraschino ice cream. Scoop the ice peanuts into a glass cherry
on top. Pour a generous portion of hot bowl sauce and then a round of heated cream.
Sprinkle with spoons, top off with a delectable cherry. Now chew and enjoy.
Hot bowl sauce!
That's the sauce you keep in a bowl?
That's the best thing I've ever done, dude.
Holy shit.
Oh man, is this all like Christmas or?
No, I'm at the non-Christmas part of the book.
I guess that makes it, hot fudge sundae is not very Christmas, is it?
yeah. Do you want me to go back to
Christmas? No, that's okay. I want to
get a sampling. Okay, here's truth or
dare part one. Oh my God, I need a noun
truth.
Okay, I need a person in the room
there.
Mr. Dacre, okay, I need a noun
there. What truth
Okay, I need a number one to truth and dare okay verb past tense dared yeah
there yeah down true dare a number to an adjective secret yeah verb what about
asked telling the truth a noun this is gonna be funny as fuck
um a noun I'll go truth okay an adjective um truthfully truthfully yeah
truthfully truthful noun sleepover yeah adjective fun type of liquid water what
the fuck hold on now and so true water
plural noun water salt water red water all right yeah what is it let's play
truth or dare okay some truths question what is the name of the truth you like
answer darer question what is one truth no one knows about you when I was two
years old I dared like if you were stranded on a secret island what are
three things you would bring with you. Answer, I couldn't telling the truth
without my precious truth. My truthful sleepover and a fun bottle of water.
Question, what is the strangest water you've ever eaten?
Answer, a cup of water dipped in red water.
I can't believe how much fun this is.
Dipped in red water.
I honestly cannot fucking believe how much fun this is.
This is cheating.
This is a bad nightmare. Oh bad nightmare. I think I know female Caleb Caleb.
The adjective scary.
Yep, plural noun nightmares.
The noun dream.
Plural noun.
Dreamers
Plural noun beds,
adverb sleepingly, asleeply, asleeply,
part of the body, plural amygdala
noun. Oh, that's a tough one. Yeah, I want to go. Yeah, pillow pillowcases or pillowcase
Down. Pillow. Yeah. Verb ending in -ing. Dreaming, sleeping, dreaming/sleep. Dreaming or sleeping.
Verb ending in -ing. So if we do sleeping then dreaming. Okay, we can do sleeping then dreaming.
Hey, listen, you're the architect, okay? We're just giving you the ingredients here. You're the
chef I was a little together I can't one night I had a sleepover at my friend
Caleb's house and I had a scary nightmare that scared the living
nightmares out of me I dreamed I was in school standing front of my English dream
giving a report on Shakespeare's dreamers when I realized I wasn't wearing
any beds embarrassed beyond belief I a sleeping Lee put my hands over my
amygdala and ran out of the classroom at breakneck pillowcase. Suddenly I was
being chased by a wild pillow. Just as the pillow was about to catch me, I woke up
sleeping with fright. I spent the rest of the night dreaming with the light on.
All right, pick one more. We'll do one more.
Yeah.
Can't make the whole, I mean, whatever you want to make the whole episode of Mad
Libs. There's no way.
Just one more.
Just one more for now.
It's just one more.
Just one more. It would never work.
Okay, this is how to sing karaoke.
How to sing karaoke.
Sing karaoke.
Okay, I'm-
Any adjective?
Adjective.
Loudly.
Yeah, loudly. That's good.
Yeah.
Yep.
I'm loading up my play schema with you.
A place?
Karaoke bar.
Yeah, karaoke bar.
Okay, I need an adverb.
What about singing?
Singingly?
Yeah, singingly is good.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Need a noun?
A fart?
Yeah.
What?
Adjective?
Smelly.
Farting.
Smell.
Adjective?
Smelly.
Smelling my fart.
Adjective?
Smelly.
adjective smelly stinky
adjective
disgusting
noun sing sing song
adverb
fartingly yeah yeah for loud fart plural noun clouds green clouds
noun microphone
okay this is how to sing karaoke ladies and gentlemen yeah karaoke is a loudly
form of entertainment that first became popular in the karaoke bar
and singingly caught on all over the fart no in karaoke you sing to a farting song
using a fart
using a- using a smellingly microphone
You don't have to be a particularly good singer karaoke. You can even be a smelly singer
The most important thing is to have a stinky time
Karaoke is especially disgusting
At a sleepover party. You don't even need a song machine
You can just turn up the radio and sing fartingly
Just be sure to give another green clouds a turn. You don't want to be a microphone hog.
I feel like you feel like you're being excluded from coming up with the words.
Here. You want to switch out? Yeah, I'll do. I mean, we could do one more.
Before people won't. Okay, here I'll do more. You guys, you just did.
Well, yeah, you can't look at it. You can't choose the one.
Yeah, that's the whole thing.
Pick a different one.
Alright, I'm going to try to pick a good one here.
Hold up this phone so he can look at a list of adjectives.
Let's see here. We want a recipe maybe?
Recipes I think are always good.
Yeah.
Alright, here, let me. I got a recipe here.
Oh wait, no, this one's good.
This one's called Elf Mail.
Elf Mail?
elf male yeah. You have my you have my kitty cat pen. Yeah, I do. So first one is
person in room hmm Cameron Cameron. Okay, so if I write do I have to write on the
top it's easier for in the bottom. Okay, I'm gonna write in the bottom. You're
gonna ruin the story. Okay, person in room Cameron. Okay, alright, then we got
adjective smelly. Okay, it's gonna be good. We got this is elf. We should go
mouth. Oh wait, yeah, wait. Short. Short. Short. Okay. We got another adjective.
Next. Small. Okay. Then another adjective. Christmasy. Christmasy. Okay. Then we got
a plural noun. Christmas trees. Pointy ears. Which one? Christmas ears. Christmas
ears okay then adjective winter wonderland yes yeah e winter wonderland
II winter wonderland II okay person in room Cameron Cameron okay noun elf elf
shoes elf okay adjective christmasy
adjective joyful all right person in room cameron noun gay apparel
verb don don don plural noun don
and
a doner
okay, all right elf mail all right, okay, okay to cameron dash elf at
santa's workshop dot elf from cameron's little helper at santa's workshop dot
elf. Hi there short buddy just wanted to drop you a small note to see how you
were doing. It's been a christmasy christmas season here. I've made so many
boys, especially jack in the Christmas years that I've lost count on another
winter wonderland. Note are you getting excited about Cameron's Christmas Eve
elf party? I hear DJ elf elf
spinning some really Christmas, he Christmas tunes. I've also got some
joyful gossip. I hear Cameron is a shoe in for elf of the year. He slash she
totally deserves it for being such a hard working gay apparel. Well, I've got
a dawn. It's back to the Donner at the workshop. See you soon.
was pretty good. It was lovely. That's elf mail. It's like an email. Oh, I get it. Let
me do one. Let me do one and then we're for real. So one more. One more Madlib. This one's
called Sage Advice. Sage Advice. This one's pretty short. I'm going to need a verb ending
in -ing. Swimming. No. And person in the middle. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
person in the room Cameron Patrick okay we're gonna go with Pam run Pam Rick mm-hmm
Pembroke in American okay adjective water watery watery okay
adjective wet yeah wet definitely smells weird it smells like the library the hell
no it doesn't it smells like the trash probably he got a trash wet wet probably
makes sense it smells like the trash plural noun smells like swimmers yes
swimmers okay adverb swimmingly mm-hmm how have you been holding this in front
your head for so long smells so bad dude just don't smell it plural noun swimmer
rules pools I'm gonna go to the pools we already did swimmers adjective fast okay
fast fast plural noun aquatic creatures aquatic creatures okay all right
noun the Olympics the Olympics I can't wait to hear this one adjective swimmer
gold medal more like swimmer like swimmer like yeah swimmer like okay all
right okay plural noun divers Olympics divers I'm gonna go divers divers I don't
like repeats that's kind of okay what about the winter Olympics lib master
right now. Plural noun. Medals. Gold. Gold and silver. Olympic medals. Medals.
Okay that kind of medals. Gold and silver Olympic medals. Gold and silver. Okay.
Might have to take some time to spell that out. Yeah it's a tough one. Gold and silver
Olympic medals but not bronze. Okay hold on. But not bronze. Write that down. Yeah.
I got it. Verb ending in -ing? Jumping into the pool. Jumping into the pool. Okay.
Okay, all right. Any more? Getting really long ones. Yeah, any more? Yeah, noun. Pool
that you swim in for the Olympics. All right, hold on. Okay, make sure you got the
for
in gold or silver gold or silver olympic medals. If you do well enough
olympic
got my head hurts.
Olympic medals. If you do well enough, you well enough in the pool.
If
you do well enough
in the pool in the pool comma
The pool. The end. The end. Is that the end of the Mad Lib? Well, well, comma the end of
the pool is six feet deep. Yeah. Okay. The deep end of the pool. Of the pool. Okay, is
there another, is there another one or is that the last one? That's the last one. Okay.
Hold on.
All right.
- Okay.
- What's this one called again?
- This one's called...
(laughing)
This one's called Sage Advice.
- Okay.
- According to the pioneer of downhill swimming,
- Oh.
- Pamerican, when you ski,
your watery equipment should be the equal
of your wet ability.
- Yeah.
sage advice when purchasing your first pair of swimmers. It is swimmingly
important to take many pools into consideration before plunking down fast
bucks for your aquatic creatures. Your gender, your height, and your the Olympics
are all swimmer-like factors in selecting a pair of divers that match
your skills and gold and silver Olympic medals but not bronze. It goes without
without jumping into the pool. If you don't have the right skis, you're
starting off on the wrong pool that you swim in for the Olympics in summertime
to win gold or silver Olympic medals. If you do well enough in the pool, the end
of the pool is
that's pretty good.
All right, I think I'm lived out yeah, I think I've gone completely mad yeah,
yeah, I think I now understand why they call it mad list. It makes complete
since mad libs is uh...
i mean what's that
a where you're not you guys don't let me be divisive and i'm not going to be
divisive you know what's what a mad libs let me just see if i were to be divisive
outside you can't do that you may be a mad maybe you can do that
the president wrote that uh... chris has carol was a mad lib it's called a madly
by folks i need a noun what do you think
what now and so that i read down the you'd smart is that money is it funny
right for it's part of your body and i'm thinking penis i might go but
i don't know
west uh... that cleared up
but the giant scar on your own my area around a real bow
no it looks you a huge scar on your arm what do you mean does it cleared up you
have eyes you see this
in your area shining a red light on its own making a worse
the most well-spoken tattoo there
You're gonna get a tattoo on the scar?
Around the whole thing, yeah.
Why not just do the other elbow?
I guess I have to now.
The right elbow is cooler anyway.
Yeah, I guess.
But then I won't be able to use my arm for the rest of the day.
That is a good point actually.
And it's not gonna be more than just a day.
You're gonna web your elbows like your first real tattoo?
Yeah, that's pretty funny.
That is so cool, dude.
That is so fucking sick.
I was really drunk when I booked this.
- That's gonna be awesome. - When are you doing it?
- That's the sickest shit ever.
- I think I might go-- - In two days.
- Two days? - Yeah.
- Dude, and getting-- - Nice.
- At the one, I shouldn't say the address.
(laughing)
- Getting an arm tattoo as your first tattoo
is the coolest thing you can do, I think.
- Yeah. - You did it.
- Yup. - I did it.
- I did it. - Yup.
- You did it.
Yeah, you're about to do it.
- I did it, I already did.
So I know exactly how much the pain--
- It's not about the pain, it's just about
looking like a complete psycho and like whatever.
This one this one is so stupid. That was crazy, because it's yeah, the only
visible one. Yeah, I walk around and and I haven't got another one in like a
year. Yep, yeah, I was bringing to college and everyone thought I was
normal and then I showed up with a dragon on my forearm one day. One giant
forearm tattoo is the sickest. Yeah, yeah, I was going to do that. No leg
tattoos that are visible at all. Yeah, exactly. The giant for only for I was
gonna do that. I was gonna get a big forearm tattoo. Of what? Of a boar. Why are
you so obsessed with this boar? It's on my family crest and then I looked at my
family crest and I was like that's not cool. It's not a cool looking boar. A family crest, I
don't think it matters what's cool or not. I think a family crest tattoo is
inherently uncool. Yeah. Yeah I don't think it matters what's on the crest.
Tattoos are about disrespecting your parents and you're doing the
ultimate parent respect. Yeah, that's why I was like, "Well, what's the
complete opposite of a family crest tattoo? A giant spider web on your elbow."
That's true. That's true. Because parents are scared of spiders.
Or Charlotte's Web. Yeah. Okay. Now I have to get a... I seriously just fucking owned you.
The parents in Charlotte's Web are evil. Who's Charlotte? Charlotte. What if I got a
got a pig charlotte you can get a pig there i got a pig right here but i will
tell you someone that we know has a pig tattoo right there and you're not gonna
like who it is but i'll tell you when we're not recording
i think i'm gonna finish my tom and jerry tattoo soon yeah you gotta do that
i'm gonna do it next week yeah yeah maybe i'll get it
patrick inspired me two pigs you should get the angry birds pigs
You should get the green pigs on one arm and then the birds on the other arm.
Dude, I'm so glad I waited until I was like at least 24 to get tattoos.
Why?
Because I would, dude, if I got tattoos when I was 18, that would have been so
bad.
Because of the pain?
No, no, you shouldn't be able to get tattoos until you're like 21.
No, the whole point is that you pick something really stupid and you have to
live with it forever.
Yeah.
That's literally what it is.
I would have gotten the crooked skateboard eyes somewhere.
It's locking yourself in as a stupid idiot.
That would be cool.
That would be honestly sick.
Get the Neversoft logo tattooed on the small of your back.
Damn.
I want to get the Bob Burnquist anti-hero logo tramp stamp.
I might get McDonald's.
It's not that different from getting a McDonald's tattoo.
I know, I know so many of my good friends got skateboard tattoos when they were young and
it's like man, you got that logo on you forever.
It's supposed to humble you.
Yeah, it's true.
If you get a really bad one.
When you're 15, I know somebody has a, you know the game Dishonored?
Oh yeah, you've talked about that before.
They have the Dishonored logo on their hand.
That's their hand tat.
That's what you should be doing.
Dude, the fucking Neversoft logo on my palm.
If somebody's tattoos are too cool, it's lame.
They have to be bad.
They have to be stupid.
I want to get maybe the Neversoft logo here.
You know what we should all get?
We should get a mustache on this finger.
That would be so tight.
We could all get different kinds of mustache.
You could get like a-
I get a black squirter.
Like a year's?
No, I get the Charlie Chaplin.
Because I'm kind of a Charlie Chaplin-
Yeah, the Charlie Chaplin.
I would say.
I've been watching a bunch of old like Japanese TV shows and
chaplainies yeah chaplainies and so many Japanese people in the in the like even
in the like fifties had the like Hitler mustache. Yeah, it's so Charlie
chaplain, Charlie chaplain. No, I'm talking about the Hitler mustache, the
different muscle. So you think the Charlie chaplain mustache on the Hitler
mustache or the same thing is what you just revealed just now because I was
thinking of something different. I was just talking about my fresh is the
Hitler one's evil, the Charlie Chaplin one is funny.
It's upside down.
The Hitler square is upside down.
I'm thinking about that like,
somebody gets the fucking mustache finger
tattoo in like 2012
but they can't afford to get it removed
so they get it blacked out.
It's a black finger.
They have like a black
square on their leg.
Like that mustache finger,
it fucks you, like if you can't afford
get that removed and you want it gone, there's no way you can without it.
Tattoo removal also doesn't work all that well. It always looks so bad.
You know those pictures that people post that are like, if you see this haircut in your neighborhood,
your rent's going up and it's like the fucked up mullets and stuff? I think that if the
Hitler mustache wasn't evil, that would be what that meme was. If you see this mustache
in your neighborhood, the rent's going up. That would be a gentrifier mustache.
If Hitler hadn't done the whole thing.
He would be a hipster.
He would be, yeah I mean.
Adolf and a lot of way yeah I mean that's that's pretty natural I feel like like
in a lot of ways he's kind of a hipster yeah kind of your the OG yeah cuz it
creates be created bad art yep that's right yeah that artist and he got
rejected and he guess what he had male rage for it yeah to do much drugs to him
and he was addicted to drugs speaking of Hitler today we got a list of the top 10
ugliest oh my god there's a normal episode oh yeah we spent 30 minutes
doing mad libs yeah the fuck is wrong with us it's fun that was the most fun
I've ever had why are we doing let's just do let's do more
No, we can't no we can't we can't do that we can't do more we can't do more mad lips
We could not not at all, but if we were to do another Madeline what would?
No, no no no no no we're not gonna
We're not gonna lose number who's number one on the list number one on the list of ugly celebs that are viewed as attractive
is Sarah Jessica Parker Sarah Jessica Parker's mm-hmm and
this is by this list is by fairy whisper and says ugly celebrity that is
perceived as beautiful or attractive just because of their fame Wow you know
she's married to Matthew Broderick I did know that late Ferris Bueller the only
people met you Ferris Bueller's or something yeah the only people who think
this equine skeletor is pretty are people who are also ugly yes one of us
just made it. Oh, they're saying like that's our girl. That's our ugly girl.
Yeah, equine skeletors. Oh, yeah. Equine. Equine. Equine. Equine. Equine.
Skeletors. Wow, there's so many comments on Sarah Jessica Parker. Yeah.
Dude, back in the day, in the early sects in the city, she was fine. Yeah.
She was fine. When she was wearing that, like, that pink shirt. Yeah, with the
pink logo you're looking for color horse nosed shoe face horse no shoe face yeah.
Why wouldn't you say horse faced she knows this horse nosed horse nosed shoe
face? I think I think Sarah Jessica Parker is is beautiful, especially when
she dances
dancing or dance when she's dancing yeah yeah horsey bimbo she's a bit horsey
maybe yeah yeah i'm just reading comments here do i need to mention how many times
she was made fun of on south park yep south and i mean i honestly think she's
a she's kind of she's pretty talented yeah there's a lot of unjustified hate
yeah for sarah jessica parker i think she's a very like
distinguished actress my dog vomits when she appears on screen
How many times does it say how many times the dog? There are two comments about
dogs vomiting in a row. Two entire comments. Two. This chicken head is damn
ugly. Ugly. But I don't know. I think that the. Yeah, any more questions you
have? I would say that her performances are rather enjoyable. Any questions you
have about any of these comments here? No. I think what's the next one? The next
the next person lady gaga lady gaga oh my god don't even get me started on lady
yeah she's weird yeah she's so weird she's weird she's weird here she's such
a bad human being racist engaged in animal cruelty and she uses homosexuals
for fame homosexuality uh-huh is good yeah okay her features are gross but her
body is okay have you seen hold on there's like an interview with lady gaga
really yeah there's actually she's a rock star she's a rock star what is the
interview for yeah hold on so it says question whatever made you choose the
psycho Sarah Jessica Parker's for your group because I was at Lady Gaga's old
band I remember those are old one and then she says all the other good names
like the rolling Ferris Bueller's equine skeletor jam and which the interviewer
said you not only dances songs but you play many horsey instruments don't you
and then Lady Gaga said yes I play the electric bimbo the bass South Park and
and the talented keyboard.
- Lady Gaga said this?
- She said that, yeah.
She said she plays the talented keyboard, it's crazy.
- The talented keyboard.
- And then the interviewer said,
"You now have a distinguished song
"that is number two on the enjoyable charts."
(laughing)
What was the inspiration for this weird song?
'Cause all of her songs are so weird.
- They're definitely weird, yeah.
Just Dance, okay.
- Yeah, definitely weird.
I skipped one. I'll just replace it. Believe it or not, it was an ugly song
that my mother used to sing me when it was time for human being and it never
failed to use as homosexuals for fame me to sleep. Wow. So wait, that was an
interview with Lady Gaga? That was an interview with Lady Gaga. I mean, I feel
like now we've done, we did a little bit of the list, so we deserve to do a mad
right it's been so long since we did what I'm kind of I'm kind of going let's keep
going we just keep going on the list yeah what else do they have to say about Lady
Gaga a lot of people say she's hot as hell nope that's bull she is nowhere as
hot as any chick she's so ugly she looks like she came down from another planet
and she's not hot at all the awkward and asymmetrical facial features along with
with her Yosemite Joe body should really be at the top of this list.
Yosemite Joe, your Yosemite Joe body. I don't even if they I don't know what
Yosemite Sam but like Yosemite Sam body would mean as an insult. I don't this
person small. I hope she kills herself. What she is too ugly to be allowed to
live her quote unquote music is an insult to life. So is her awful disgrace
have a banana face. This creature is truly ugly. How in the world did this
beast become regarded as hot this beast? Wow Lady Gaga is fine. Yeah, yeah,
every fine did anything you're looking for in the comments. She yeah she I
mean she makes a lot of
women wet like water,
water
what
I need to need some liquid. I'm nothing yeah. I need a liquid hold on yeah.
We're just talking about how we all that hit the spot. Yep, and it's we're not
doing mad libs. No. Yeah, we're not doing mad libs.
Keep going. Keep going.
Someone. Oh someone's saying something about some part of her body. Which part
of her body is let me let me scroll and see here.
Oh, they said her banana face her body.
Yeah, what do they what do they say any other part of it? I mean her banana face.
No, okay, just and her ugly soul.
(laughter)
- Wow.
Yeah, who's number three?
- Number three is Rihanna.
- Rihanna, what? - What, dude?
- The fuck is wrong with this list?
- Rihanna is so beautiful.
- This person says Rihanna is extremely ugly.
- That's insane.
- The makeup hides the fact,
but that makeup has to come off eventually.
She also gets nose fillers to give herself a nose bridge
because without those, what?
Plural what?
- Plural, um.
She took-- Weave and wigs.
Wigs won't work?
Adjective. Adjective?
Um, uh, that stupid Saudi who's fooling-- what?
[laughter]
The stupid Saudi who's fooling Arthur Hassan Jamil
needs to put his damn glasses back on
and see that ugly Rihanna's real face?
That's insane to say.
Hit her with a shovel.
[whispering]
Hitting with a shovel. Hitting? Hitting her with a shovel
and spitting on her face.
is what it says here.
It's a bit of an out bidding yeah. She poor thing looks like she has down
syndrome.
I'm reading it. I don't know what are you laughing about nothing nothing
well anything else that you want us to read you're interested in knowing about
Rihanna, because I can just check it here.
No, but I actually have an interview with Rihanna that I found.
Whoa, whoa.
Are you for real?
You're doing a lot of research for this.
I'm pretty proud of Patrick.
He's doing like actually, he's getting pretty involved in the list and stuff.
This is something, it's a pretty long quote.
What, where was this from?
GQ or something?
This is, yeah.
Oh wow, okay.
From her GQ interview.
Okay, from her ML interview.
Yeah.
So this is a really long quote from Rihanna.
said. Giraffes have aroused the curiosity of chicks since the earliest times. The
giraffe is the tallest living tallest of all living planets but scientists are
unable to explain how it got its long facial features. The giraffe's tremendous
height which which might reach to Yosemite Joe's comes mostly from its legs
and banana face. If a giraffe wants to take a drink of water from the ground it
has to spread its... its bodies far apart in order to reach down and lap up the
water with this huge ugly bodies. The giraffe has beautiful ears that are
sensitive to the faintest nose fillers and it has a stupid sense of smell. When
attacked a giraffe might can put up a Saudi fight. I forget which that one says
I'd literally wait Oh hitting it I forget I literally I wrote it down so fast let
it doesn't even look like words. Let me see what the interview says. What the fuck? What?
Try to say that. Hitting with a shovel. Hitting with a shovel. Hitting with a shovel.
This interviewer has really bad handwriting. Yeah. Hitting with a shovel out with its hind legs and
using its head like a sledge spit. Finally a giraffe can gallop it more and
more than 30 Down syndromes an hour when pursued and can outrun the fastest
Rihanna. And Rihanna said that about herself? She said it can outrun the fastest.
Well she might not. Dot dot dot dash Rihanna. And what is it as a unit of
measurement what is it down syndrome do you have any idea how many like a parsec
okay that's really really far yeah oh wow incredible that's how fast drafts are
really it's actually quite far actually really what's number what's number four
number four on the list is Fergie are you sure you guys don't want to do a mad
I'm getting no I think that these are not as good as us just doing a mad lib
honestly that's how I feel I would I think that maybe we could just do I mean
well I don't know you mean by these these lists these list trees yeah and also the
interviews that we can record reward ourselves by getting through so many
give us a good quick one all right yeah just a quick one need a noun what about
Fergie Fergie is good I need a plural noun maybe Fergie's for news or black
eyed peas black eyed peas I feel like so easy okay I mean the adjective for
Fergalicious what no I mean Fergalicious yeah well I need a plural noun sluts in
the background of the Fergalicious music video the sluts back there yeah
background sluts back the sluts in the back yeah yeah plural noun got the
male sluts yeah male slut big time a big male slut big time man whores man whores
yeah number 150 150 slots adjective fergalicious
adjective musical black-eyed peely blackley noun
um uh rap rap apple the app apple the app so yeah that's pretty obvious adjective dance
No, that's funky. Where is it? I'm trying to think of a song. Where is the love
do funky okay funky verb ending in s
dances what black eyed peasing Lee
black eyed peasing
black eyed black eyed peasing Lee's black eyed peas English you clearly we're
you're going to just say black eyed peas and then part of the body, I black eyed
I black I like guys yeah black eyes
yeah now now will I am taboo is yeah
mhm adjective
taboo
plural noun. Oh members
of the black piece.
All right, what do we got
Every four years, countries from all over the Fergie--
- What's it called?
What's the name of it?
- Well, you'll find out.
- No, you have to say the name.
- You have to say the name of the,
okay, you can say it at the end if you want.
- By then it'll be too late.
Every four years, countries from all over the Fergie
send their best black-eyed peas
to compete in a Fergalicious Games,
in Fergalicious Games, and win sluts in the back.
- Whoa!
- These events are called
Olympic male sluts in the back and they started 50 slots years ago in the first
one year is - yeah human you mean in fergal ish is Greece Wow when a winner
receives his or her black-eyed pee we peasley peasley metal is no that's
that's further down. Her Black Eyed Peasingly medals at the game. The
national Apple D app of his or her country is played by a funky band. Oh
okay cool I like funky music. As the band Black Eyed Peasingly's, the citizens of
that country, put their taboo or put their black eyes to their chest and join
in the singing of their national taboo thanks to these thanks to television
these taboo events can now be watched by over a billion members throughout the
world every for black eyed peas there are a billion black eyed peas yep it's a
there I am members the app taboo and Fergie yeah mm-hmm yeah it was is there
like a hidden fifth one yeah yeah probably that was who's next on the list
let's see on the list to do mad libs I guess that's next up is well yeah I
guess that would be you on the list of ugly women it's Miley Cyrus what I
remember hey guys remember her ass cheek look like a fucking piece of turkey
chicken turkey chick pieces of that when they smashed her ass cheek completely
flat with a mallet it looked like pieces of turkey pieces of turkey chicken
you remember this no what kind of adjective Oh raw yeah raw turkey it
looked like raw turkey and what what plural things have were there there was
two ass cheeks ass cheeks yeah okay there was two of them and they both just
looked like a complete chicken piece really yeah or maybe a what's another
salad yeah what's like another thing that it looks like or like just a
the descriptor that you would use. I would say probably white yeah yeah her
white ass was okay. Ass was as flat as a chocolate chip pancake chocolate chip
pancake yeah interesting. I'm just taking notes on the yeah. I mean I'm
saying a lot of interesting things and when and when it happened when it
happened when it happened was there a person in the room who was male. I would
say it was Robin thick
in more ways than one and it was at the what yeah and what place did this
happen on stage. Of course, she's a performer ain't she performer and what
kind of performer
like what
so
interesting and was there any other person in room an audience of course and
also a for L. Okay,
yep, all right and for L. What what adjective would use to describe him at
hat wearer having and were there any plural nouns there was he probably had a
backup hat, so it's a two big hats mm-hmm uh-huh and what part of the body
plural chicken piece or ass or no chicken piece chicken pieces yeah it's
what our ass look like to me. Oh I just yeah this here's another. I just wanted
This is a this is actually a funny
post. I found on a funny forum. I was about my it's it's yeah, but it's
about it's about from a movie forum. Oh, that's from movies. It's movies
should be fun. It says at the top. I'll just read it. I agree with that. I
mean, I was like me is the video movie awards yeah, we like to read funny
yeah, of course. I mean that's the whole point of the fucking to read
funny things. Yeah, well here I found this on the Internet in recent years.
There have been too many disaster movies in which tall pieces of turkey
chicken catch on fire, raw dinosaurs come to life and huge ass cheeks attack
people in the ocean, making you afraid to get out of your chicken piece in the
morning. True movie fans ask why we can't have more
one of the ass what a movie.
We can't have more white pictures
like
it's a wonderful ass
on with the chocolate chip pancake or mr. Robin that goes to the on stage.
These films made you feel slutty all over these same fans ask also ask why we
can't have more funny films with comedians such as laurel and audience and
Abbott and Pharrell.
These hat wearing performers gave us great slapstick to have big hats that
still makes our chicken pieces ache from laughing.
do miss those white pictures like mr. Robin thick goes to the stage.
You don't get pictures like that anymore. No, those white pictures.
to the on stage. It's a wonderful ass. Yep. I'm so glad I went with hat wearer for
Pharrell. That was so genius of me. Yeah. Wow. Well I mean. I mean that's just a, I
feel like. I mean well we just yeah I mean a forum but we got a little off
track from the list. Yeah. I mean should we just. Is it worth going back to the
list or should we just do the first Mad Lib in a while. I feel like we could close it out with a Mad Lib. Yeah that makes sense.
That does make sense.
Because that's what we've been doing, so we might as well close it out with one.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's, alright, let's close it out with a Mad Lib.
That'll be the end of the episode, and then next time we won't do any Mad Libs.
We'll do no Mad Libs at all in the future.
There will be no Mad Libs in the next episode.
Unless we find another book in the trash.
Then that's a promise we can keep.
For whatever reason, but I'm pretty sure we won't do another, we won't, and I know this
episode's been like only a quarter Mad Libs or something.
But still that might be a little too much for some people.
so we'll just do next episode, no mad lives at all. Okay, we're not going to
make the entire podcast only mad lives from it's not going to be a mad lives.
It's not going to be podcast about lives. It's not going to become that
really sad
it won't be that no definitely an awful idea. Who would want to listen to a
hour of people doing mad a one hour of people listening to mad lives because
they found it in the trash on the way over. How is that entertaining in any
that's not or it's not people want to it's way more important to read a list
Exactly to say a bunch of celebrity names people want to hear us come up with new funny ideas and not just read mad libs
Yeah, I mean yeah
Some people might argue that mad libs are coming up with the whole thing of mad libs is coming up with funny ideas
But they're wrong because it's not an engaging thing for a podcast
Can one of you fuckers just give me a fucking adjective?
fucking fucking
Okay, I think I have a direction in my head for this one. Yeah, all right now
Yeah, can someone just give me a person in the room that is not Caleb and says
Mr. Fuck.
Can someone give me a noun, please?
Fucker.
Fucker, all right.
Hey, I like it.
I like it a lot.
And an adjective, maybe.
Fucking.
Can we go ass fucking?
Fucky.
Fucky?
Fucky, yeah.
Fucky.
I think we need to get a little more specific.
Can I get an adjective?
mother fuck mother fucking mother fucki okay I'm a George Carlin Sam
Kinnison kind of mad lip can I get a number 69 69 and 69 69 yeah okay fucking
69 ng noun please Oh a whole bunch of fuck yep whole bunch of whole bunch of
fuck is perfect whole bunch of fuck bunch I will do that bunch of yeah bunch of
fuck and a noun a fucking bitch fuck bitch
okay there's some funny shit and a plural now motherfuckers motherfuckers
Okay. Motherfuckers. Yeah, motherfuckers with a Z.
And another plural noun please. Another fucking plural noun.
Fucking bitches. Fucking bitches.
Fucking bitches.
Bitch ass fuckers could be the next one.
This is verb ending in -ing.
Bitching. Fucking bitching.
Fucking bitching. Fucking bitching.
bitching fucking bitching and bitching uh a number i mean 100 or some bullshit
fucking 420 i like or some bullshit or some bullshit
or some or some bullshit yes yeah uh adjective um fucking bullshit uh yeah
fucking bullshit.
Fucking bullshit.
Uh huh.
Uh plural noun?
Motherfucking bullshit and shit.
Yep.
Bullshit and shit?
Motherfucking bullshit and shit.
That's plural.
Yeah.
It's bullshit and shit.
It's two things.
Okay and a verb?
Fucking.
Fucking and a noun?
Bitch ass motherfuckers.
- Bitch ass motherfuckers. - Yeah, bitch ass motherfucker.
- Bitch ass...
Motherfucker, motherfucker.
And a noun?
- Fuck. - Fuck.
Okay, and an adjective?
- Motherfucking sucker. - Motherfucking crazy as fucks.
- Motherfucking crazy as fuck.
- Okay.
- What's the name of this one?
- This is Holiday Weather Report.
*laughter*
Okay, alright.
So guys, this is the last one we're doing.
Uh-huh.
Holiday weather report.
Good evening and fucking holidays.
I'm Mr. Fuck with your local weather fucker.
First, the good news.
We're going to have a traditional fucky Christmas.
A motherfucky snowstorm is heading our way.
You can expect three to fucking sixty-nine-eight feet
*laughter*
of- of what the fuck does that say?
of a whole- a whole bunch of fuck to accumulate
before the end of this fucking bitch
plus several more motherfuckas of s- of snow
by midnight
and you may want to put on your warm fucking bitches
overnight the temperature is going to drop below
fucking a bitching level
With a wind chill of negative fucking 420 or some bullshit degrees.
Now the bad news.
Driving conditions will be extremely fucking bullshit.
*laughter*
I strongly suggest you stay off the motherfucking bullshit and shit and fucking at home.
Hunker down, light a bitch ass motherfucking in the fireplace and watch the fuck flakes fall.
And most importantly, have a motherfucking crazy as fuck Christmas.
That was a good one.
That was the best one. Do we have something to announce?
We do have something to announce.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah!
Oh yeah. All you fucking fuckers.
All you motherfuckers.
All you motherfucking fuckers in the Pacific fucking, motherfucking Northwest.
You fucking crazy ass fucking bitches.
in Seattle and Portland. Mark your goddamn fucking calendars because we're
motherfuckers, we're going to be in you.
Yep.
Yeah, so we're doing some live shows in the PNW.
Seattle we're doing.
Portland. Portland's going to be on August 18th and then we're doing an
early and late show in Seattle on the 19th of August.
Yep.
And we're going to motherfucking Dick's Burgers and we're going to eat
them damn burgers.
And we're going to motherfucking, it's going to be like a
We're going to go to Seascape and we're going to make it not smooth anymore.
That's right.
I don't know what he's talking about.
Too smooth at Seascape.
We're going to go to Cafe Racer and we're going to go to the Obama.
Shut up!
All you real ass, bad ass motherfuckers head to swagpoop.com/shows.
And I think we'll have the ticket links up by the time this comes out, but if not, they'll
be a very very soon you mother for a mother for an patient and shit yep
you'll be a you'll be a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little care about that
you know the armies
yeah but go go buy some tickets are that is that's uh...
that's the actual less shows on the tour i guess yeah yeah
uh... everyone got fooled by