Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
♪ Say that you a lesbian, girl beep boop ♪
- I started.
- I don't get it.
- You're saying say that you a lesbian, go beep boop?
♪ Girl beep boop ♪
- You said go beep boop.
♪ Girls want shirts where I'm from ♪
- Say that girls are lesbian.
♪ Say that you a lesbian, girl beep boop ♪
- Has three boobs.
Oh yeah, like from Total Recall.
Yep.
Yeah, because I totally recall that movie.
Yeah, no, I totally recall that movie.
Not just one scene in it.
No, I remember every other part of the movie.
I recall it perfectly.
Not just the one scene with the huge perfect boobs.
You see that silverfish on the top of the ceiling?
That's a water bug.
He's-- that's-- what?
That's not a water bug.
A water bug is a cockroach.
A water bug would be in water, too.
And it's swimming on the ceiling.
Water bugs, first of all, they're not in water.
I just noticed that the second we press record. I was looking at it and I was
hoping nobody else would notice because I know you guys have a fear of bugs. If you
swat that towards me, I will fuck you up. Just leave it alone. I hate bugs man.
Stop. Dude, what are you doing? Why are you doing that? This is you. That's you.
No one can see that. I've had a hard couple days. Antifa stole my
backpack. Oh really? Antifa stole my backpack. You didn't just forget it in
the front of the in front of the office. And then they put it back, they put it
back. Because that's their whole thing. They take shit and then they redistribute it.
Turned out like Robin Hood. Yeah, robbing hood. Yeah, they robbed my hood and
they took my backpack and then they put it back in a place where I might have
left it. And they tried to frame myself for losing the backpack. We were like
driving somewhere this weekend you were like, dude I don't know I totally like
left it on the street. I thought for some reason I just left my backpack on the road. Why did you
think that? I don't know I just was I was I was stressed out about it. It's okay I
saw Wicked so it's all good. Nice. Yeah. That's cool. I went and decompressed. I just
every couple weeks I gotta go. Yeah you gotta go see Wicked. I gotta go see Wicked. Oh my god I see Wicked. I go to
Broadway every few weeks too to perform. I see Wicked every week. I'm thinking it's great for stress. Really?
really yeah are you is rocking a crowd of a thousand people and I know you love to
go to stop it yeah that was no he's he acts and stuff well acting is kind of to
it's yeah well I would say that's one of our of what you yeah makes me a threat
yeah there are three things that make me a threat the other things are my my
claws and my attitude mm-hmm and your singer-dancer yeah yeah that's one
singer-dancer I thought it was - I thought you were trying to make a choice
this have you been in well, that's what because I haven't made a choice. It's
one because it's like it couldn't go either way. You know yeah, have you been
in a production of wicked yeah, who do you play munchkin munchkin interest yeah,
I did the shoes on the knees thing and I have not performed a wicked since because
I brought the house down and I made the other munchkins look bad. I bet you made
him look short. I made the other one. They were already pretty short. They were
I mean, I was just telling him about that about this. Oz refuses to they
refused to put little people in their show.
Really?
Yeah.
There was not a single little person.
There's not a little dancing little person?
Dude, I was hoping for it and then the guy comes out and he's like, "You're never gonna
trick me or I'm not the best munchkin in munchkin land."
And he's a normal size guy.
Yeah, he's like 5'7".
I audibly went like, "Ugh."
Well, let's not call 5'7" a normal size.
He was actually a little bit short.
He wasn't munchkin status.
Yeah, 5'7", yeah, short.
He wasn't like, you know, I would say this.
He wasn't like no
Average there's a difference between stage munchkin and movie munchkin. That is true
Yeah, you still like they need to still be tall so you can see them from the back. That's true. That's a good point. Yeah
Yeah, I've had this crazy tooth problem. It's gonna derail the whole tour really. Mm-hmm. You need to go to
The island of misfit toys. Yeah, and you need to have that dentist elf operate on you. Yes. Oh, yeah, he's good
he's actually a very very well regarded by line my top my top wisdom tooth is
growing in or it's grown in but it now is very sharp for some reason what you're
growing a sharp tooth I'm growing a sharp tooth in the back and it's digging
into the bottom of my gum and I wake up every morning in immense tooth pain do
you guys ever see that I don't feel like because I don't want to ruin the tour I
don't want to get wisdom tooth surgery do we talk about that the that lady who
you had that baby and the baby just grew a fang maybe yes. I think so. Oh, I
think so. I think so, because I think you said that and I was like, oh, like a
snake and you're like what and I was like, oh, snakes grow fangs when they're
babies to get out of the egg. I think I remember that. Is that true? Yeah, they
have something called an egg. My mom laid me in an egg. That's not true. Okay,
prove it. Where's the shell? Ate it. Ate it to get out. You don't eat the shell
to get out. You break it. You can't eat the shell. You eat the yolk. You eat the
the
that must be the boogers all right. I'm more comfortable with eating a baby's
boogers and a baby is the same as boogers. Yeah, Gus mine is
it's got like actually the same. Sometimes it's got that like red streak
of blood in it and it comes out after you sneeze. It's like it's the
mclaughlin group.
What it's like it's the mclaughlin group and they're like his jizz boogers.
What's the mclaughlin? What's that some from Saturday night live? I know my
fucking Sarah mclaughlin in the arms of the
muffin.
I know that shit's good. I know the grand moff Tarkin. I know when I watch family
I'd be laughing. What's today? It's May 2nd I think. Yeah it's May 2nd.
And it's a Monday? What? I'm trying to fix the office calendar. What? We have a calendar?
That's not a calendar. You haven't looked at it. I've been changing this every day.
day that I'm coming here. It's not a counter, it's a date shower. You must not be doing a
good job if people aren't noticing it. It says it's a good day to have a good day on
it. You should be underlining the date so everyone knows. And adding flashing lights
and emojis. That will really grab my attention. Yeah, and it's Monday. There's nothing like
an emoji to get me going. Me neither dude. I was really hoping they would have emojis
in Wicked but they didn't. They just had some stupid singing and dancing. Yeah. I think
I'm, I heard I'm starring in the emoji musical pretty soon. I think I'm going to be, maybe
try to become a singer I've decided a broil singer yeah that's I'm gonna try to
become a singer he has I'm gonna try to become a singer I mean it's fine I mean
I'm just gonna talk to everyone and tell them not to give you a part why cuz it
can only be one of us per there can only be one of us per podcast do you hear
this guy what white people I have a perfect ear cuz I'm a singer no you
don't your perfect ears perfect ears I'm gonna put your ears in the dirt okay oh
I hear a million grains of dirt right now I could count exactly what I'm
how many grains of dirt there is in two hundred and thirty oh yeah the whole
earth idiot ass bitch may monday. Oh two great job pat you killed it
may monday. Oh two may monday. Oh two which looks awesome.
I do have a perfect year. I'm like charlie puth. Okay. What am I saying
Charlie Puth.
Puthy.
Puth, what's his-
Charlie Puth.
Who's his fucking dad, Sylvester the Cat?
Is that the guy who named him?
Imogen Puth.
I'm gonna name my kid Puth.
Charlie Puth.
Come on.
I'm gonna name my child Charlie Puth.
Charlie Puth.
But, I do have a perfect ear.
Suffering suck-attacks, it's Charlie Puth.
Charlie Puth.
Yeah, I can pretty much do all the Looney Tunes.
Yeah.
(mimics duck)
- Yeah, I can pretty much do all the Looney Tunes.
- That was Bugs the Bunny.
- Bugs the Bunny, yo.
- Bugs the Bunny.
- This is Daffy Duck.
- Bugs Bugsy.
- Who the hell's Daphne Duck?
- She's beautiful.
- I wanna tell Daphne from Scooby-Doo to duck
and I can see up her skirt.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Wouldn't she have to be ducked?
- Hey Velma, how about you film a,
yeah film on me having a sex out with you feel my balls of all your
and yet all your bread
fred did it on this but i think i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i
you know it's kind of a it's kind of shaky and it's kind of scooby to
uh... don't fred my penis fred
don't read a fred don't fred there should be another boy in the mystery crew
true. Fred and Shaggy and Scooby-Doo doesn't count. I was saying for a long
time they should have put Fat Albert in there, but then Bill Cosby was a
seriously... He's excommunicated from Hollywood. Yeah, from Scooby-Doo. He
told a very bad joke. They unmasked him. Yeah, so I don't... If it weren't for
you, for 30 of you meddling
women, I would have been... I think it was like 150. Yeah. No, there's no
way. Yeah, that's just crazy.
yeah cool guy Bill Cosby awesome swag you're gonna have a new Bill Cosby
really yeah I heard his name is gonna be Patrick no no no I mean like I'm gonna
be looking at him no no no like you know like like little bill grew up and it's
gonna be it's cuz that's a different guy little bill hmm little bills that's
little bells about a little bills about time travel little bill the same guy
little bills have you guys gone back and watched little bill recently no no
horrific dude have you yeah it's like you see that it's like the beginnings of
a monster he doesn't share sometimes he's putting he's dropping smarties into
women's juice their juice boxes that's true it's true he's putting smarties
into their juice boxes sorry I'm just distracted by my calendar again stop
stop looking at that dude. I did the I did the stupidest thing. I think I've
ever done yesterday. What I went I get it may Monday. Oh, two I went to the
grocery store you with me. No, I was not with you at the grocery store. Okay
story's over.
You asked for it literally
literally
zing.
Okay, I went to the grocery store. Okay, I
I was there. Do you people listen to you see how hard my fucking life is trying
to tell my two closest friends about just something that happened to me I go go
just say it just say you're you're you're building up a little Caleb is the
one that you're getting antsy do I went to the grocery store I bought some
pumpkin some canned pumpkin got myself a little no got some got some fair life
chocolate milk what right and I check out it's $24 and 60 something cents yeah
And then the pumpkin wasn't on the receipt and you're like, what's this?
No, I said you got can't pumpkin, not can pumpkin. No, literally. No, not literally.
I was pretty hungover and you said, what is this receipt so long? What is it? CVS?
Literally, literally say that I was hungover and it was really early in the morning. It was
earliest I've ever gone to the grocery store. Early. It was like 8 15 and I ate 15 cans of
a pumpkin litter literally yeah, but you actually didn't because they were
can't a paper can literally literally we established that earlier. So I when I
put my card in and when it was a bugio card literally
I want to ask if you want cash back for whatever reason, I thought that it was
asking me to give a tip and so I saw like ten twenty fifty a hundred. I was
holy shit so I clicked other and then I put in she was like you I can't give you
two dollars of cash back and I was like what
I'm gonna redo the whole like scan everything again because I was like a
crazy guy trying to get two dollars. And then also I'm trying to tip on a grocery order.
Dude, there's a grocery store by my old apartment that they do have a tip jar.
You shouldn't have to tip for anything, first of all.
I agree.
Second of all, you definitely shouldn't have to tip for anything where the person isn't
bringing something to your table. If a tip is on an iPad, and it's not something you
- I think you're right, Don.
If it's something you press on a screen,
that person who's getting the tip should be dead.
- Yeah.
- They should get the tip.
- There should be a big tip of my saber.
- There should just be different options.
You should be able to tip.
- My bayonet.
- But you should also, there should be like
virtual buddy options on the iPad.
- Yeah, slap.
- Where it's like, yeah, throw a thousand balls
at them right now.
- Yeah.
- Forgot my chapstick, Cameron.
What are you doing?
- Stop recording, I have to go home and get it.
- What do you have to get?
- I had a dream last night where I was walking somewhere
and I saw like, there was like someone
was having a little yard sale and there's a video game like some of they were
selling a video game in their yard sale called dragon and I was like I need to
buy this and then I like had I was like oh what I'm late and I like went and
then I was like and then later in my dream I was like I forgot to buy dragon
I got so mad and upset that I didn't buy dragon to buy it yeah well I forgot to
go back and buy it and I was like I have to go back and buy dragon and it wasn't
there anymore and I that was like I was so mad that I couldn't buy dragon sounds
a great dream. It was a bad dream, because I didn't get to play or buy Dragon.
But you got to develop your video game. I wonder if there's a game called
Dragon. There is. Is there? What is it? Purple Dragon. Well, it's called Purple
Dragon. Spiral. Yeah. It has to be just called. I remember the box. The original
first Spiral game was called Dragon. That's not true. It was an NES game, too.
like an old it was like a retro game. Oh so it was Double Dragon? Yeah that was called
Dragon. Well that the first one is called Dragon and then the second one is called Double Dragon.
Guys that's not true. The Dragon is also Spyro's from Dragon. Alright when I search Dragon game
it just gives me a list of every game that has a dragon in it so if anyone's listening to this
read them right now. Okay uh Double Dragon, Double Dragon, Double Dragon NES, Double Dragon 2,
Battletoads slash Double Dragon, Dragon Spirit, The New Legend, Dragon Quest, Dragon Spirit,
double dragon 3 dragon warrior 3 double dragon 3 double dragon 2 double dragon
you did the world cup the dragon of dragons dragon quest for super double
dragon flying dragon colorful dragon oh let's get that one actually order that
out colorful dragon dragon game colorful dragon is a maze game developed and
published for the Nintendo Entertainment look at this game looks look at this
cover this is right you need to look up bad dragon look up bad dragon oh and then
yeah like not a dragon I heard there's a really good peripheral for the NES look
up bad it's like it's like the it's like it's like the duck hunt gun yeah yeah
the virtual boy you use it to play you use it to play yeah big dragon you use
it to play better for the dragon whoa great so now I have to move my own I
don't want this to unplug some boys that are like it's a Chinese game huge like
probably as big as it now. I don't understand because apparently girl
apparently like four inches is good enough for girls so why do they like why
I heard it was three. Why is it every oh there's all these videos of girls
putting like like a like a squash into their ass. Yeah well it's the flavor they
have taste buds. Oh. Like you know how guys have taste buds. You know if you put peanut butter
all over your balls and you don't have a dog you can taste the peanut butter
through your balls. If you do have a dog, you can taste your dog's tongue. I am sick of my dog licking the peanut butter off. I'm trying to taste it.
Oh my god, I'm trying to taste this shit dude. Get the fuck away from me! Don't lick that! It's not for you! It's got too much sugar in it!
Yeah, well so yeah, they have taste buds in there. That's why they put like
squashes and cucumbers and stuff and that's how you can tell when a girl is
really weird or a freak because there are some girls, I don't want you to
look this up because it's nasty, but there are some girls that try to taste
traffic cones.
Well, what is a traffic cone?
And that's what on the street all day.
So you can imagine it doesn't taste like candy corn.
Oh, that's a lot of them.
Might.
Oh, it looks like a candy.
And I think that they think that if they, if they maybe, you know, if they're
putting a glass bottle or something like that, they might think that it's like a
wax bottle.
And maybe they might have some Coca-Cola jelly in it.
Yeah.
It's, it's sort of that type of thing.
So what's the, what do they think of what is bad dragon dildos smell like?
Probably smells like a dragon.
I don't think it does.
I think it's gross.
No, that's just for people who want to fuck a dragon.
That has nothing to do with flavor.
But they're too big.
That's all I'm saying.
Do you ever wish that you're-
That's setting unreal expectations for my penis.
Maybe it's a gummy worm.
I don't have scales.
Have you ever seen one of those bad dragon things and been like, "Damn, I wish my penis
looked like that."
Damn, I wish I had that in my butt right now.
Yeah, of course, dude.
If I had a huge knot on my penis-
Yeah, a foot and a half fucking green and blue penis.
You know what they need to do?
Ah, it's so cool.
They need to do-
do like ones that are like based on like characters right you think they would
sponsor like they do they do like xenomorph one and like yeah they do
like avatar one and stuff right I think they make one based on a guy
they should make them based on on yeah on people they have this is a normal dildo
yeah no but you're buying what it has a name on the dildo they have they
actually have we have that yeah that's pretty they have ones right also I think
what they should do I think that I think that bad dragon is an unfair monopoly on
the market and I think you know companies like Nintendo should be making Bowser
dildos and like you know like McDonald's Ronald McDonald dildo you know it's and
just let bad dragon take all the end of but you know what I want a Mare McCheese
I want like I want like a like a stark white you know those sex toys that are
like a butthole and a pussy and butt cheeks and it's just that yeah I want a
stark white one and it's Ronald McDonald's big red butthole and it
chanels a lot of imagining this. I want to make double that heads of a
giant. There's a huge controversy with like a sex toy company because they make
one of those like like but and and pussy sex toys, but they put like they put like
legs on and make it run away.
It does backflips like that like the I dog wind it up and it runs around.
It's like an ostrich.
No, no, it would be a controversy is the point. There should be more advanced sex toys that have Boston Dynamics should make a sex toy that
Obliterates your penis and vagina. Yeah seen those like guys that do the real doll things like they like like those things are really expensive
Be one that they're not very they hard to talk about
They should there should be one that's just one of those can return machines and it just sucks your thing in and crushes it
Yeah, I agree. Yeah, there should there should be a new five
There should be a flashlight that looks exactly like WALL-E and turns your penis into a cube.
I've been saying this.
I think if I got a flashlight for free, I would not use it, but I would use it.
Let me finish.
I would drink something out of it one time.
What would you drink?
Diet Mountain Dew.
Diet Mountain Dew?
Dude, that's a gross one.
That's going to get like the coating is going to dissolve.
You should drink like chocolate milk out of it.
Why only one time?
I mean if you're going to drink something out of it, you might as well just drink something
out of it all the time.
That could just be your cup at the office.
You could just get a fleshlight, dude.
I'm not going to fucking-- I know you're not using it.
Also if you use a fleshlight, that's okay.
I don't care and if you use it and then drink out of it and drink your own nuts
Okay, if I do I don't care if you use a flashlight dude. It's normal use a flashlight is it?
I don't know. I think they're probably
Crazy concept because they hand already feels better than a vagina. I don't need them. I don't need some silicon
It is a crazy like like they have them modeled after real people and there's a crazy
Idea that you can just sell like a body part and someone jacks off with it
What?
Literally, you're selling a fake body part.
That's like selling the fleshlight for someone to jack off to.
You ever think about how the stars we see in the sky are already dead?
Damn.
It's the same as selling a prosthetic leg to someone for them to fuck.
No, it's different because that's a leg and this one's a pussy.
Do you think the food that I see is the same as the food that you see?
Shit.
Like a strawberry could be green for you.
No, maybe that's not even a strawberry to me.
Maybe that's a piece of steak.
Oh, it is a piece of steak.
I see it now. Yeah, it's an audio recorder. It's not a piece of steak.
Idiot. Do you ever think of me doing that? Like, I'd be like, "Oh, you're right! Oh shit! That is green! Wait a second!"
Whoa!
Whoa, you got me, dude! We need to go on CNN right now.
Damn.
Damn!
Stop talking about your damn tooth, boy. I really hope this doesn't fuck everything up. I'm about to smack your shit up! I'm gonna go to the emergency dentist.
I'm gonna smack you up.
I looked that up this morning. I looked up emergency dentist. I'm gonna have you laid
up in that Harry Potter hospital. My other side of my mouth is burning too. This is not
a good day for me. I think you got a double demented dental situation. Double demented
dental? Welcome to double demented dental. We're two crazy dentists. Whatever you do
if you're booking an appointment do not go to the dementist. It's an easy mistake to
make. Okay? It's only a few letters. I've done it a few times. Trust me. You do not.
I went to the dentist. Listen pal, if you've seen Little Shop of Horrors, okay?
Steve Martin ain't got nothing on the Dementist.
Yeah, the Dementist actually has guns.
One of his eyes is way bigger than the other and he goes like this.
And he looks great and sticks his tongue out. And he really sucks at working on your teeth.
And when he comes into the room, tornado. His toothpaste is actually sour.
Great, the Dementist is giving me screaming gas. Awesome.
His toothpaste is sour, but then it's sweet, then it's gone.
No, shut up.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I hate the Dementist.
Yeah, dude, the Dementist.
He wears that metal circle on his forehead, too.
Yeah.
You know what that metal circle is?
And he bites Crabby Bandicoot.
And you don't even sit in the chair.
You have to stand up.
No.
Yeah, I'm serious.
I'm dead serious.
And he will make you dead serious dead.
My idea of a Dementist is just a normal dentist.
I motherfucking hate them.
I hate the dentist and I am like $3,000 in dental debt.
- Yo Sandra Miles, if you're still practicing
in Wilmington, North Carolina,
I'm gonna come and I'm gonna ice you.
- My dentist was Dr. Robert T. Christ.
- Really?
Dude, we had crazy dentist names.
Sandra Miles was Smiles.
That's her first initial and last name.
- And he was Christ and he was like really into God.
- Dope.
- And if you called him Dr. Christ, he was like,
"No, it's pronounced Christ."
and it's like dude just fucking own it.
- Yeah, you do have to own it at that point.
- I mean it might be a little embarrassing
when you get to heaven.
- Yeah, my dentist name was Dr. Craze.
- Really?
- Yeah, he was a doctor.
He wasn't a doctor.
- Oh, was he not a dementist?
- Well yeah, well he was like,
I think you trained under him or something.
'Cause he had similar techniques,
but he was more just, it wasn't as mean.
Just kind of just, he was Craze.
- I didn't even honestly have a dentist.
I'm just making it up.
- His first name was Cra.
- Yeah, I didn't see a dentist from the age of 14 to 18.
- I don't think, if you're an adult
sees a dentist yeah fucking figure shit you have you have a you'd you like to be
controlled you have a subordinate you basically a sheep like jumping over my
brain while I'm counting you're like you're like in a dystopia movie you're
like the person who works a 14-hour job at a typewriter and then you're like
happy yeah you're free guy yeah you're literally no you're not free guy you're
the guy but you're the other guy that's not it is blue shirt guy it's not slave
guy he's not a slave there's a different slave they're like the Lego guys in the
Lego movie that's not the same movie isn't it Lego movie yeah it's all the
same yeah dude whoa I mean it once they oh I mean it's it's that thing where you
know like I'm waiting for the prego movie the word I mean the New World
Order's here and and and people people like like Phil Lord and and and Chris
Miller is that their names they're trying to warn us about Ryan Reynolds the
New World Order they're showing us dude that's the only way you can break free
free from wait from from the hegemony, the hegemony. Let's be a free guy or a
Lego. Aviation gin, right? Yeah. So how do you reach the top of a pyramid? A
plane, a plane, you aviate a generator or a generator that runs a elevator,
right? And a Nintendo Rator. Elevation gin, right? And where and where and
- And where's the pyramid?
Egypt.
Where is the Lego Movie 3 that I'm writing set?
- No way.
- It's true.
- And what's at the top?
An I, what does Ryan Reynolds have?
- iPad.
- Dos of?
- Oh, Equis.
- Equis, right?
Equis, equis, equis, equis.
Thinking about DJs, talking DJs now, right?
DJ, DJ Smith.
- The Jewish Conspiracy.
- No.
Yes, yeah, yeah, okay, that connects, yeah.
and so we got a kick we got aviation gin dude I'm telling you a kick a kick a
stent a C on gin from the office is who's he now he's the boss of a sports betting
company he's the seat no he's a CIA he oh yeah he's in the new doctor strange
movie really he's mr. doctor mr. crazy fantastic that's nice no no yeah yeah
yeah it leaked no sir it is I know I thought that hey I thought I thought it
I should have been. I shut thought they should have used the real guy. Yeah,
I don't like that. They keep recast. They keep recast. Everybody
specifically Mr. Fantastic is a real guy.
He's a scientist. I would say most stretch. I saw him in New York, one of
the more believable superheroes, stretchy everyone's stretch tons of
stretchy people. I'd say the most I'd say the most the most realistic super
are the fantastic force, probably invisible woman. Yep yeah in the
workplace yeah exactly that's what my house yeah here no evil see no evil
Richard Pryor and that conversation prior was about free guy free guy the free
free guy free guy free good I free free guy who's free we don't know yet he's
that scientist that said that everyone wants to fuck their mom yep
free free okay and he was a damn freak
uh... free free design right the dollar bill
whose bill bill clinton
right cause be clean bill cause be bill clinton bill cause me
has a weird i now
i think we've got a good hater i'd hate or the new world order in order to
order orders
you want him at a party
and what democratic party all my
god
the democratic
partly
involved in this
it can still a c
with a free guy
and a lego movie lego my
rights yet and give me my damn rights back democratic party because guess what
i just found out the european debate system
and
and drop
my truck
they should you know they should do they should be should we should go
we should go back and we should replace all the all the democratic elephants
with pyramids yeah i think that we should do that in all the political cartoons
microphone so if you drop it you can get it again easy i agree you bounce it
comes right back up to your hand yeah if you if you make a point you can make
another point right after yeah so you don't have to stand there and be like is
this the point what that i make that i want to drop my mic on because if i draw
i can't do two mic drops if you have a bouncy mic you drop your mic everything
you say the thing is about a mic drop man you're fucking up your own microphone
man it's fucking that up and then it could bounce into the audience I mean
it's disrespectful it could take someone's eye out it's like wearing
shorts on stage or so yeah you know here's the thing I won't wear shorts on
stage I'm gonna wear my damn mini skirt though no I'm gonna wear my damn mini
kilt and then I'm putting the the mic stand up my up my skirt yeah Mike Stan
you're all gonna listen to my thing Mike's I can't hand Mike Mike's tan yeah
Mike Rowe cuz he's working these damn dirty jobs in the Sun oh yeah he's an my
My crow, crow, raven, Edgar Allen Poe.
Mike Poe, Mike's Poe, he's poor because he works all these damn jobs.
Mike Poe's nerd.
And they don't pay him a cent.
Police.
Mike Poe's nerd.
The Democrats think they're cooler than me.
I took a pill in Ibiza, right?
Ibiza, what's that?
Gay heaven.
So I took a pill in gay heaven, where's gay heaven?
The Democratic Party.
Ibiza, he sees the truth.
I took a pill in Ibiza, Ibeza, eBay.
- Bezo's. - Ibezo's.
- Jeff Bezos is buying eBay very soon.
- Ibeza, Idina, Idina Madzel.
- Wicked.
- Oh my God, that's where I was.
- Adele Dazeem.
- No, no.
- The wickedly talented.
(laughing)
- Bitch. - Adele Dazeem.
- Yep.
- Dazeem.
- Travolta.
- She's green.
- She's green in the show. - In the show.
she's green as hell she's green on the scene
the scene
which one is green?
the witch! who's green? which one is green?
the green witch
the witched witch of the green?
yup, the witched wist who's the best? the freaking witch of the weest?
yup
she's green and it all goes back to the top
his tooth hurts
he's got two
thurts
hey pat
does this ring a bell?
thirt what's a thirt? explain yourself. a thirt is a t-shirt
t-shirt he only has two thirts. t's hurt
t's tooth starts with a t they hurt
t-shirt
t's shit
t's it. he's the shit
he's the coolest guy around. pat
you are cool as hell
you are holding your nose
yet
yes he's all my god he must say to warhead before we started recording
he's got a serious our face is it the full moon by any chance
i don't know i hope not i'm growing things in the back there cut not much
shit it's hurting so bad are you with the kids really just coming in right now
police there is a band in
but in one of them dot impacted what does that mean impacted it's it's when it
like can't come in. I think I'm literally like every single one of my teeth hurts.
This is like the worst like pain I've been in and so long. Did you get punched
or kicked or hit in the teeth? No, I ate a lot of candy. Okay, all right. Did an
animal around and run around all your teeth? Maybe. Oh, did you? Did you
perhaps pick up? Did you maybe pick? I think I figured this out guys. Did you
You pick up a lollipop from the ground that had a wolf-shaped bite out of the
lollipop and lick on the wolf bite part.
I was wearing silver, so I thought it was okay.
No, see that's what's going to get you.
You probably need to get that silver off.
That's actually probably what the pain is from.
No, my fillings are silver.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what I'm saying.
You're probably going to need to take all of those out.
That's a good idea.
I can help you with that.
That's going to fix your teeth.
Yeah, I'm Dr. Smart.
I'm a knowledgeologist.
knowledgeologist. This is cool, Pat's trying to do Rubik's Cube stuff to his teeth.
Yeah I'm trying to just move them around so they stop hurting. Dude you're gonna
you're gonna you look like you're doing like like the Cenobite, the
chatterer. The what? The one with the teeth. Cenobite? Gigabyte? That's a new
new age. I'll be a new age soon in July. That's true. Yeah. They made that movie
today, probably would be called Gigabyte or Terabyte. Yep. The Gigabytes.
Wait, which movie? They didn't call the movie Cenobites. Hellraiser. They would
be called Gigabytes, the guys. Okay, yeah. Right? They're called that and instead of
solving instead of solving a box yeah they'd solve an app they're called that
in hellraiser 3 i thought nope there's a cd player one in hellraiser 3 that's
the is that hell world no hell world is like that's the one with the computer
yeah that's like six i think or maybe five three is there's six of those damn
three is hell on earth no there's like nine there's nine of those damn movies
it's hellraiser and then um hellbound and then hell on earth and then um blood
minds and then I don't know what's and then I think something else and then
hell world and then Tokyo drift and then revelations and they're making a TV show
to what the hell is with this shit yeah they want me to believe hell I mean
hellraiser the amount of money they're spent on these movies it's called
fundraiser yep and revelations they want you to believe in evolution at public
school no no no I came from a guy named Adam yeah yeah and a girl named Steve
public school these center bites are publicly cruel I was birthed from cane
They are.
And it's like, why does this one have a butter ball?
Chill.
Yeah, yo, that was disrespectful as fuck, naming that one Butterball.
We know he's fat as hell, but you didn't have to say it like that.
True.
They should have called him Skinny Mini.
And he tore up everything butter balls.
I think these days even fat people can be thin.
That's right.
Don't say that.
They should have called him Butterbox.
Because he came out of the box.
And then it would make sense if you say you tore up everything but her box.
Yep.
Why would you tear up everything but her box?
Because he's weird.
He's from hell and shit.
I don't know.
How am I supposed to explain what a cube?
He's from a demon's job.
He lives in the gay cube.
Really?
Yeah.
Because it's supposed to be about Clive Barker and how much he loves S&M, right?
Clive Barker is one of those guys where I no hands nutted to Rihanna S&M.
One time I no hands nutted to Rihanna S&M.
I was like, "I'm going to get you."
supposed to be about Clive Barker how much he loves S&M right? Yeah, Clive
Barker is one of those guys where I no hands nutted to Rihanna
S&M as a child. It's so sick when you can read a guy's book and just say, "God,
swear on my fucking mom's grave." No hand nut to S&M by Rihanna. Is that true?
Yep. You grab your phone like you were gonna look that up. I'm looking up S&M right now to see if I can do it.
She's wild as hell for saying I love the smell of it in that song. Dude, honestly, that's the
part that got me. I was thinking about the smell of a sex swing. I think it was her smelling my
stuff, like maybe my taint. I was like, she loves the smell of my taint. I was going for a run,
and I had that song on, and I had no hands nutted. Damn. Yeah. Wait, so Hellraiser...
Yeah, well, I would say it's so fun when you have a movie or a book where you can read or watch or
watch or to ever instantly be like oh yeah, the guy who made this is gay yeah
because it's all because they go they go crazy. Patrick goes to jolly be yeah. Oh
yeah,
no it's so funny. Good, it's like in the camera yep, yeah, yeah, well you watch
hell razor yeah and it's like you go to a different dimension where you wear
leather and you get attacked by evil men and we all and we all attack each other
and are evil to
and are we're demons from hell.
Yeah, it's the same same thing with with chuck palin. I could dude yeah, you
Fight Club and it's like oh yeah yeah a bunch of sweaty guys hitting each other
yeah I watch that I'm like okay can I at least hit girls?
I'm straight okay? We need to have a fight club that has boys and girls. Can I at least just hit some girls?
okay I'd be watching a fight club like damn tag me in my pants are already off
I want to see Meat Loaf punch Olivia Munn let's do it in Fight Club 2. Is Meat Loaf
Meat love dead.
Meat love died.
Fuck.
Meat love died in the movie but he's alive.
Oh great.
Oh cool.
He's alive in real life.
Oh good news.
His name is Robert Paulson.
Oh my God his name was Robert Paulson.
His name was Robert Paulson.
Whoa you guys wait.
Oh my God are you guys referencing that shit right now?
No I just came up with that.
Damn.
You must be a writer.
I just came up with a name.
You must have a writerly soul.
I had no idea.
Yeah.
Stop.
Why are you doing like what my step dad does when he doesn't want to curse?
he goes like that scared the fuck out of me.
- Yeah, that's what my mom does.
- Really?
- What's that about?
- That's very funny.
- You're hitting all the consonants.
- You know what another one that always gets me is,
oh sugar.
You ever, my mom says that sometimes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my mom says fuck.
- Not anymore, I guess now that,
- My mom says fuck.
- Yeah, it was more when I was a kid
that she would do that.
- My dad says fuck you.
- My dad says when he,
- He says that?
- When my dad stubs his toe he goes,
pissy pissy penis.
dad when my dad hits when I my dad
son of a bat
Dracula my dad yeah
Prince bloody fangs
garlic Oh shining moonlight
wouldn't stake in my heart
Yeah, when my dad hits a curb or something though, he says, "Damn ass."
Really?
Like the damn ass rock video?
Damn ass curb, broke my tire.
Broke my fucking shit tire.
He says it?
My dad says, "I'm fucking pissed."
No he doesn't.
I'm fucking pissing.
My dad says, "We're all trying to find the guy who did this."
My dad says, "I'm fucking pissing."
Literally.
Yeah, my dad says, "Holy shorts."
is that it is a little easier to keep my dad says holy shit i'm pissing
all my shit it's coming out of the home i'd be a bit
it's a bit of a question it's not the fact that the great there's a lot of
shit directly into the parking and i am told it was my shit
there's a lot of it was like a shit all right and it's not all my kids and thus
flows my poop. Great. The poop is flowing out of me like absolute water.
Awesome. Absolute water. And great. It's messing up all my piss that I put in there.
Oh, hot shit out of me. Oh, great. Hey guys, somebody accidentally mixed all my piss
with all my shit in your toilet. Oh, mother... stinky, stinky pants. I'd rather
do it in... I'd rather have shit in my pants. And here's top 10 reasons why. Oh,
yeah. Oh, yeah. What's our... what is it? Top 10 reasons to crap your pants by
by top man who I looked at his profile username top man location top man about
hello top ten users only list top ten reasons to crap your pants. I mean this
is a good classic man. There's not no reasons to crap your pants. I've always
thought that'd be a good kind of like there's there's reason there's of course
there's a good defense mechanism man. Imagine like somebody's trying to like
attack your butt like you just shit all over yourself.
Nobody wants poop.
Isn't there a video?
No, no, no.
I'm thinking of the video.
It's like the fight and the guy just gets completely naked.
Oh yeah.
I don't know that.
But there's a lot of...
Anytime that you're in a combat situation...
I mean that's what the cavemen did.
Really?
Yeah.
They took their clothes off?
They grabbed their loincloths.
Really?
To get in a fight, yeah.
Oh, I didn't even know that.
And then they put the poop under their eyes like football players.
That's how football got invented.
Is that where that's from?
Oh, yeah.
But it was foot rock.
foot rock. It used to be club rock. I was trying to find the video. I was club rock the other
damn night. I was trying to find the video of the guy in the fight when he pulls his pants
off. I go to Planet Hollywood and I think it's called club rock. I was trying to find
that video. It's like an old vine and something completely different just showed up. Yeah,
and now for something completely different. And now for something completely different.
Oh my God. Number one is I thought you thought it was going to be gas.
Listen, I've been there. Yeah. This is what happened to me.
That's not so much a reason as an excuse though. That's true.
Wait, these are just two naked guys touching each other's balls and jacking off.
They're not fighting at all. Patrick, Patrick, this isn't fighting.
They're fingering each other's buttholes. No, they're fighting. Look, look,
he did bite his butthole. That's a good move.
who had
i thought it was so fun
on my god that's going to do this is a little bit stopped each other
there's a bit there so that they're doing their due they're doing crop
mobile
i guess he was the loser did their dad i think they're doing a crop he does
who grabbed my balls here
uh... well
i think i was going to take a look at it
I haven't seen that in my training.
Let's see how this pays off for him.
Like, now we're in his video.
He must have a different master than me.
Of Krav Maga.
Krav Maga.
This is what happened to me last time.
That was in 2006.
And I'm 11 right now.
I was sitting there and whoop, there it is.
This and having a dream with Freddy Krueger in it.
Oh my god, having a dream with Freddy Krueger in it would absolutely make me crap my pants.
There's a comment here from
from a fan.
There's a comment here from I think this guy might have been afflicted by this
disease crapping your pants says what are you guys laughing about it's not funny
true they should make a scene if they ever make another nightmare on all
street movie they should make a scene where they should make a comedic scene
so this is an idea if you ever want to make a comedy version guys wait so okay
I mean don't worry about it right so here's the comedic scene is that Freddy
Krueger tries to go into someone's dream and it's a dream of them having sex with
really ugly woman and he goes what the hell and then he leaves. That would be funny. Yeah.
He could go, what the hell? Woof. What? That would be a good. What? It's DMX. Oh she's ugly.
Ew. I don't want no part of this shit. No no no no. And I thought I was ugly. And I
thought I had scars and red on my face. And I thought I was a butter face. But look at
hurt yeah cuz Freddy Krueger total butterface face with that body god those
hot fucking fingers fucking body imagine those around your thing
Jesus Christ just shaving just shaving little curls of skin off you I dream
like you're like you're sanding wood I really just say that never trust a fart
oh it happens to everyone at some time says Hollywood fan eight fan eight good
thing this never happened to me says Freddy Fosbier. Whoa! Whoa! From the game? I
guess so man. I'd be pretty scared. Holy crap. Good thing it only happens to me at home with
capitalized words. I guess I very rarely have shit myself out in public and I shit
myself pretty often. You shit yourself in public once a month. You only have it one time. You shit yourself in
public with us and then you didn't tell us till we got home. So I didn't know
dude. You didn't know. I thought I couldn't remember if I was I think I think a wet
bug crawled into my pants but it's probably nothing. I did I think I thought
that I splatted a green bug from a cartoon and it was the greens goo was all
over my butt. It was fine you guys just made too much a deal out of it. I feel like I've shit my pants in public before but not like around people.
I shit my pants in first grade and then I went back to class and sat in it for a
little bit and tried it I was just like okay this is fine. You ever accidentally
sit in your squish your pants? I sat down I sat down in the poop and then I was
just like oh no you guys remember what it was like to wear a diaper yeah yeah me
too not really I had to wear pull-ups to bed because I peed the bed so I don't
have so good I don't remember really like I you were I kind of have like I
was a bed wetter yeah I was a bed wetter - whoa dude oh my god that's why I'm so
much smarter than both of you no it's why we're so much more cruel and
sociopathic yeah you two are I agree that's why I'm so kind that's why I love
animals.
He yelled in rage when he heard that you were kind.
Yeah.
That just, literally.
Even kindness just.
So weird.
Yeah.
That just fixed all my teeth problems.
That was so weird.
Problems.
All my teeth problems.
That was the evil spirit escaping from your tooth.
Yeah.
The pressure behind your molars.
I sneezed out the.
Problems.
The osmosis Jones.
Yeah.
Demon that's in my mouth.
I sneezed out the.
Yeah.
Jones yeah demon that's in my mouth really
like it's like a really like like a Christian parent just teaching like yeah
those are demons those are evil spirits and then you see that blue guy that's
God that's that's an angel that's little God mm-hmm
and - couldn't hold it in kind of the same yeah no that's not the same actually no
you're right that's not the same as thought it was gonna be gas just
couldn't hold it in is like even if this were gas I wouldn't have the ability yeah
yeah yeah yeah my shit right you're right listen I misspoke and I'm taking
accountability for it one time I was recording a podcast for those good old
profession values and I was in the middle of talking and I had to know I
didn't say anything. I just ran to the bathroom. I was like I'm going to shit
my pants. I've had probably two or three times. Luckily, it's only ever been
over zoom podcast. I've definitely almost shit myself before yeah pretty
it's so hard when you're recording something or you're doing something and
you're like like other people are there and you have to be like I have to go
right now for no reason yeah for exactly yeah, I I do that, but I hate when you do
that and then you leave and everyone's like yep, he's going to jack off and
maybe I don't hate that. I think that's funny.
Do you guys think it's wrong to jack off at another person's house? Yeah,
depends depends on what you have to be wearing. You have to be wearing the
yeah, so it doesn't touch their house serious day job like at a I swear you
said that on the podcast before I've had it. I swear that we've had that exact
interaction before somebody. Please see if you can find this where I say it's
wrong to jack off. So is it wrong to jack off of someone else's house? You say it
depends and he says you have to wear depends. I swear to God dude yeah that
has happened before I believe it. We I mean basically we just say that it's the
exact same three things to each other over and over and over. It's crazy that
people listen to twice a week. It's crazy. That's not I think that we do
good radio. Okay. I think that too yeah that thing is new thing is called
awesome culture. Yo wait that that makes no sense wait. Okay. You said that we're
going to roast you for fucking twenty minutes. The other yep prepare to be
flamed my good one second. Let me check my notes for a good roast on you awesome
culture that makes no sense you're thinking of epic culture
number three getting your first kiss that would make me that's not a reason
at all a ahead my first kiss from peter mayhew
well yeah i've read in a way that was for a time out from the burger brothers
you know
uh... not not i didn't know i didn't it was my girlfriend in high school
movement
uh...
yeah last week
by the way i clear the air
all
no literally i'm not high school literally
but i think that way i'm not going to make sense is not a high schooler okay
i got a high schooler even i don't know i got a she is if i was a high schooler
admittedly seven if you could
i wish you were sold if we were all thirty seven
how pathetic that would this be
I wanna go ask those fuckin' geezers over at the Chapo Trap House.
Oh my god, yeah.
Now you mean the Chapo Trap Home.
'Cause those, 'cause old folks' homes are a trap.
'Cause I'd like to trap those Democrats in a home and light it on fire.
Yep, those frickin' Democrats at Chapo Trap House.
Yeah, dude, the dem Democrats.
Not democraps.
Yeah, that's what I call them.
Demochaps.
Yeah, 'cause of their show's title.
I'm starting to suspect either Will Miniker or Felix Biederman was the Antifa soldier who
decided to prank my backpack.
Oh, 100%.
I'm putting two and two together. Felix Elderman. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Matt Christman,
you're so old. Yeah. Yeah, and Will Giesinger. And Will Older Curse. Will Oldest Curse.
owners owned. Yeah, Chris Wade too old. You know that yeah, Chris aged yeah,
that's probably a lot over a long period of time. He didn't age a lot quickly
because then he would be young. He aged a lot over a long period of time. A
really good point. Yeah, number four. Yeah, explosive diarrhea. We'll table
that. Yeah, well, we'll leave that for another episode. Number four, this older
sure man.
What
oh
okay yeah, I forgot I said table it and then you kept going. So it's kind of
like I wasn't prepared for you to disrespect me. I guess last will
that's good. That's it. That's it. That's a manicure yeah, yeah, that's
perfect. You are a magician, my friend will magician.
(laughter)
- Yeah, Felix Beatermage.
- Yep.
- Matt Christ-like.
- Matt Christ-miracles.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, these guys are wizards.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause they're so fuckin' old.
- They got long white beards.
- Democrat wizards.
- Yep.
- Yep, wizards in the KKK.
They are actually that, 'cause we did their show,
and they showed us their,
they shoot up on the zoom call all in clan road you have you guys ever noticed
your name of their podcast capo cap cap cows mm-hmm yeah ever realize what that
stands for for 4ks 4k mm-hmm they are we cannot stress this enough we can't
listen there's no two ways about it the entirety of chopper trap house belongs to
They're white supremacists. They just are, man. They tell us every single time we stop
talk- we stop recording with them. They say, "Thank you for furthering our ideals," and
we say, "We're not doing that at all! What do you mean? No! No! You bastards! Don't you dare release this
episode! I don't want to high-five! Wait, what the hell are you doing with your
hand?" And we don't email them our audio because we don't want to appear on that
type of program, but they somehow get it anyway. They're hackers! And then later on,
sometimes we forget and we do other shit with them, okay? So some people
forget stuff sometimes you know if we're doing a live show we like you right we
were trying to assassinate them we were backstage I saw I saw Will Menneker he
when he showed up he took he took in this red armband off and sat down yep and
then he put it back on and then when he got back off the stage he put it back on
yeah mm-hmm and I didn't see what the armband was I actually think that he's
so old he was taking his blood pressure.
(laughter)
- Yep.
- Number five, girlfriend turns out to be guy friend.
Now tell me you would not crap your pants.
- I wouldn't crap my pants.
- I don't know if I'd crap my pants or not.
Would you go full Ace Ventura?
- I would go full Crying Game.
- I haven't seen that one.
Honestly if I found out my--
- I would go full Crying Game,
I would throw a car bomb in London.
- What?
- Huh?
games about neither of us have seen it still oh it's about the I watch it I
just watched anything you say about it it's a good movie it's really good I
think if my girlfriend turned out to be a guy friend we probably just play more
video games yeah I'd probably I'd be like we might drive racing cars together
yeah we probably just like become even closer and more sexual oh my god only I
I saw them drive racing cars on fear factor like yesterday. No, it's so sick
is crazy. Also, who's afraid of racing an awesome car? Yeah, the
doors on that show are pretty funny. Yep, yeah, yeah, there was one where
the fear is like you will be put in this. You'll be put underwater with now
like don't scream crabs
and two of the people quit to the people who got too scared of crabs. Yeah,
when this I'm afraid one woman was like well, yeah, one lady, so you went. Oh
- Oh my god, it's biting my butt!
And then she quit.
- The crab isn't gonna, it's not gonna,
it doesn't want human meat, dude.
- It's a crab, it's not like a spider or a demon.
- It's similar. - Those are scary.
- It's a mixture of the two, but I don't,
I'm not scared of it. - It's a fear factor,
but then like Joe wrote, it's like,
your challenge is seven minutes in heaven with a demon.
- With a dark demon Chernabog.
(snarling)
- I'm sending you to hell for 30 seconds.
But you can tap out and have your teammate take your place.
three rounds of physical combat with Scorpion
for Mortal Kombat. And yeah, he's not wearing his mask and you can see his
skull.
That'd be too scary, man. Yeah, that would seriously factor my fears.
Your first challenge, boo! Your second challenge.
I just wish they would factor more of my fears into that show. Yeah.
Yeah. Number six. Like student loan debt.
Yeah, okay. So basically...
- Yeah, take that, Chappo, we're swinging at you again.
We're taking your crap.
- Actually, my fear would be if they erase student loan debt.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Hey, buddy, maybe I wanna pay off my loans
like a good citizen, you know, asshole?
- Oh, so I'm supposed to like it when the number goes down?
- Great, so the Democrips are trying to,
that's basically net worth, that's my net worth,
and you're turning it into zero, asshole.
- Yeah, you're siphoning off everything.
- Yeah, Hillary Clinton, you witch.
- How else am I gonna prove I went to college?
I already drew all over my diploma.
- Yep.
I don't have a diploma. I had to do math for a tip. I dropped out of school because I knew
that there were being too much of Democrats there. You are a Kanye West type figure in
my eyes. Do I look like white Kanye today? You do. I'm your guy who camerafies your entire
life. What's his name? Krusty. Mr. Camera. Krusty the Crab. Lakitu. Lakitu? Yeah. Is
walking around like-- - Is that how you say it?
- Yeah, Lakitu. - I don't know, I've never--
- Lakitu, Mario's little guy. - I've never,
I've always said Lakitu.
- So then I was following Kanye on a giant shell.
That's the movie.
- Kanye went to this castle-- - You're going the wrong way,
Kanye!
- Kanye went-- - Turn around!
- Kanye went to this castle,
and he put on a hat-- - Make a U-turn, Kanye!
- Kanye turned into some type of raccoon creature,
and he was jumping around flying.
What's that thing called?
- Tanuki. - Tanuki.
i watched kanya hit this green box and then he turned straight up into metal
i was a little bit of a report it puts aside i was a man in a car like a tiny
it's unlike awards or so i like like like i really get the taylor swift thing and
he's like walking up on stage
and like five like it is just for like storm around with the wrong way figure
out how to get a bit of a cracker at least grab a lot of the i_d_s_
cameras are all right
uh... you know the problem with the group of the public
will will will
yeah did you hear what he's saying in a city he wasn't going to do anything but
he's sitting a scene he just heard miss said
did did did you guys here will Smith did it the oscars
yeah I heard he threw a red shell and now
yeah I heard you to slap Chris rock no
yeah no on what where the face like this but he slapped him in the face that's
okay if he slapped his but that sexual harassment that's a workplace or and
that
And that's out in Hollywood, but you know what's in?
Girls.
And that's on Weinstein.
And he said, "Keep my wife's name out your fucking mouth."
He said this.
Who's his wife?
Okay, so this is sounding a bit sexual.
Jada Pinkett Smith?
Really? I thought she was his wife.
Damn, I thought that was a damn marble.
I thought he was married to Willow Smith.
Yeah, he's married to her too.
They're poly.
Oh, they're both.
Okay.
His wife has no hair.
I thought she was straight up a bun.
Isn't that crazy?
I thought she was she was she okay you know say what you will but she was so
fucking good in shape of water yep and when she fell off that damn wall
yeah oh my god has no hair but surely she has eyebrows I heard that I heard that
she just got I heard that she actually closely she's in talks to play judge
Holden in blood meridian really yeah that's awesome yeah I heard that
actually and he slapped Chris is that true wait Jada Pinkett Smith slapped I
heard she's gonna play no she's bald but she's not a boy did that wait did the
way I did the light from her shiny head I use someone's eye to hurt them or is
that what it was that like are we talking about the same thing I thought
that that was a Lindor truffle that's a woman yes what and it was at the Oscars
But she doesn't have any hair how could that be a woman?
She had no hair.
I thought that was a placeholder mannequin because the person wasn't there yet.
And he said keep my wife name out your fucking mouth.
I thought I was watching Mythbusters and that was a crash test dummy.
And he said keep his wife's name out his fucking mouth.
To Chris?
I thought it was like
Will said that to Chris.
I thought it was like one of those Ronald McDonald statues on a bench that you sit next to.
But it was for Humpty Dumpty.
And it was just
I thought it was like a story land scenery thing that got brought there.
And it was just slapping people in the face.
got brought there. And it was a slap at the Oscars.
And it was a slap in the...
Was it a slap to Oscars itself?
Would you say it was the slap heard around the world?
Mm-hmm.
It was a slap in the face to audiences, too.
And to performers.
And the celebrities.
And wait, so Will Smith slapped Chris Rock.
How did his wife, Mike Wazowski, react?
She wasn't laughing.
But he was laughing, and then he stopped laughing.
Yeah, because when I see her, I say, "Put that thing back where it came from."
Or so help me say, "Help me."
(laughter)
- And they slap.
They slapped.
- They slapped?
- They slapped each other.
- Wait, they both slapped?
Okay, so they got in a fight then.
- They slapped on TV.
- But they just got in a fight, that's fun.
- That's a slap.
- Well, if they both slap each other,
that's just yin and yang,
which is also what Jada Pickett-Smith looks like.
(laughter)
- They slapped on TV, and it got real this time.
- No, wait, it was on TV?
I didn't know that part.
- They slapped on TV. - That's not good.
Yeah, Jaden Pickett-Smith has TB.
- I wish you could see my face right now.
- The bald head.
- Yeah.
- I wish you could see my face right now.
- Yep.
- Literally.
- Yeah, literally.
- Literally, she's bald.
- I literally slapped on TV.
- Yo, she was sitting in that chair at the Oscar so long
I was surprised a magic beanstalk didn't grow out of her head.
- Bean ass bitch.
- Literally.
- Listen, bitch, you look like a bean.
You actually just look like a bean to me.
Okay?
A kidney bean.
A pinto bean.
Any bean is what you look like to me.
Some type of bean is what you are.
And edamame.
You're a bean, bitch.
Oh wait, so you're Jaden and Willow Smith's edamame?
Okay, yeah, 'cause you're a bean.
And they slapped on TV.
Yep.
And wait, you have kidneys?
Kidney or bean?
You gotta be kiddining me with how much of a bean you look like.
Yep.
Yep. All right. I'm not supposed to slap on TV.
The only show left on tour is Chicago. That's tomorrow when this comes out.
So she go ahead by no one comes on stage and slaps on TV.
Us enough. I wish I had a can of coins to shake.
You're doing this right now. This is what I want. Yeah, I think I mean,
unless it sells out by the time this comes out, which hey, probably going to
sell out today. Who knows? We added a late show that as I think 18 plus.
So if you couldn't go to the first Chicago show because it was 21 plus
You should go to this one instead.
You should buy tickets.
It'll be the last show on the tour and we're gonna do something crazy.
It might be slapping.
If you're one of the college co-eds that comes up on stage and slaps me, then I salute you
at the 18+ show.
And if you ask me to sign your boobs, I will not.
I will only sign your arm.
Yep.
Hey, I've done a lot of thinking about this.
I've done a lot of thinking about this.
And no slapping.
I don't even see boobs because I'm so in love.
I just see two beans.
And if you look like a bean ass bitch in the front row, best believe I'm gonna make fun
of you bean.
No slapping.
Don't bring your husband.
And if you dress up like a bean, I'm gonna eat you.
It's not advised to bring your husband, because he could slap us.
Yep.
Alright, bye.