come back and make a mess and we see a but
you're a scrap monster
uh...
okay we should be the only part of it it's so i mean it started this is
counting that this is this is counting down
discounting up counting did up this is counting every terrorist attack at the
end of your house and you're right now every single second yeah
yes or the middle of a serious terrorist moment here in new york city where some
very short terrorist is giz giz giz is
you know today i was five
little terrorist wealth
for a wealth of a race the twelfth of april and pretty early in the morning so
what we're and they have a copy of so what we're thinking is that maybe we
record this and it really we schedule it and then probably we all offers die
yet by this man's hand so this could be our last is our time to kind of
I'm supposed to see the Sonic movie tonight.
Really?
Sonic 2.
Yeah.
And, um, I don't know.
How is Jim Carrey supposed to be fucking Eggman, dude?
Eggman is supposed to be fat.
He's round.
He's supposed to be fat.
He's supposed to be egg.
Not just fat, but round.
Yeah.
Well, not even just round, almost egg-shaped.
Almost egg-shaped.
The similarities between...
Ovoid.
Mm-hmm.
The similarities between Jim Carrey and Eggman, those are the only differences.
All of their crimes are similar.
I bet that they'll have...
I bet he'll be fed in Eggman origins mm-hmm and he loses the weight at the end
We need a full-length Bowser movie. Yeah, just about Bowser, but like what is Bowser's?
Like what's that is just like born of what's that movie?
He steals women. What's that movie downfall?
What movie? Like a downfall style movie about Bowser. What's downfall?
They should make a movie called fall down about my grandma. Downfall's the Hitler movie.
Oh yeah with the with the funny with the go with the seed.
where they put the Runescape text over it.
Yeah.
Yeah, they need a movie like that but with Bowser.
Bowser deserves to win.
I agree.
He deserves to win once in his life.
Yo, Peach, let Bowser hit one time for the one time.
He did, dude.
Bowser Jr. is Peach's kid.
That no, he, bro.
And Lenny and what are the other kids?
No, dude.
No.
Peach is not popping out fucking dinos at her snatch.
She laid an egg.
he laid an egg. You're thinking Birdo who has an egg mouth. No, Birdo is trans. I'm thinking of
Peach laying an egg. You're not. You're thinking of a bird. No. Oh. I think Bowser shot an egg
into Peach's thing. Bowser wouldn't shoot an egg, he would shoot a sperm. He would shoot tons of
millions of millions of, bro, he would shoot millions of sperms and one of them would defeat
the rest of the sperms. I've seen pictures online. Look up Bowser and Peach. Bowser never,
peach never let him hit us on this website about rules bro he's too busy
doing different locks and designing levels for Mario yeah defeat he has to
make you some like he has to hire all the enemies I will say yes - yes to
audition them all he has to go he wants a sex with her speaking of he just wants
a mom for his kids there should be one in one Mario level is just one one really
handsome Koopa this one there isn't there one in paper Mario I don't know
I never played Paper Mario.
She should suck his cock.
Yeah.
On purpose.
It's funny, it's like, it's not that they're all the same creature, they all just happen
to look the same and there's one that's really hot.
Yeah, a really, really hot one.
Who's like mad cool too.
Patrick is imagining this.
He's got his eyes closed, he's imagining a handsome Koopa.
Yeah.
I'm so sleepy.
Why are you so sleepy?
I don't know.
so much crap going on in the damn world. Is it maybe the terrorism is so boring
to you? Yeah, millions of people dying terrorism is boring as hell. I kind of
don't care anymore man. Yeah, yeah already yeah, it's been two hours. I'm
like been like twenty minutes. I'm right. I found out two hours fifteen
minutes. It wasn't hasn't even been to it. I have it at thirty, but the news
came out was like like ten minutes ago, happened at a thirty actually came out
one minute ago. Okay, well I'm already bored with it. Can we move on to
something cool yeah. Can somebody drop a big bomb out of the do you every time a
plane flies over to you? Do you ever think like this is it yeah? The big bomb
is going to hit me pretty often well, because if you look up and you see that
mouth that bullet bill mouth yeah, you know you're so over dude yeah yeah
that's so far. What if you looked up and you saw he saw the war zone guys in the
plane
hundred and twenty people jumping out of the plane. You see guys using a
flapjacks as parachutes like Fortnite. Oh Jesus Christ yeah today's the day.
I can't mistake that helmet anywhere that is definitely
Marshmello jumping out of that plane. It's cel-shaded Rick Sanchez. Oh and look who's behind him.
Oh yeah that's Bruno Mars. Yeah awesome. It'd be funny if that was if that we
New York City came under attack and was just a hundred guys that jumped out of a plane
They all just got killed immediately because just a hundred guys. Yeah, but yeah, well if they're warzone guys
They're gonna instantly kill us dude the wise
Yeah, the time to kill on a on a human versus a warzone guy like I'm I'm one I mean obviously yeah
But there are a lot of police here and they would do their duty
Yeah, the police are the strongest in you they would shoot them if you asked me
They'd probably be eating doughnuts and fucking chewing gum. No, right
Yeah, there's anything about a police officer if they see anybody flying down on a hang glider. They're killing them instantly. Yeah, they should yeah
Yeah, I mean I 100% believe they would I think of a police officer a New York police officer is walking down the street and
Looked up and saw and saw Ariana Grande drifting down on a magical umbrella. They would shoot her. Yeah
No, you see like a like a cop sees a guy made out of pancakes. He's he's open to fire
I want our I want the giant Ariana Grande from the concert to attack New York City
and I could maybe get squished by her giant foot.
- That would be sick.
- Wouldn't that be awesome?
- Or Travis Scott, not Travis Scott,
just Ariana Grande.
- No, just Ariana Grande.
Maybe she could like,
she could like suck us up her butthole.
- Yeah.
- Remember when they announced,
remember when they announced,
remember when Palpatine had that announcement in Fortnite?
- No.
- There was like a,
there's like a thing in the Rise of Skywalker,
or whatever the fuck it's called,
like the opening--
- Whatever the fuck that movie
of my favorite franchises ever is called.
- I always forget if it's like the Rise of Skywalker
or like the something else or I don't know.
- It's the Rise of Skywalker.
- Okay.
- You only said, you said the right thing
two different times. - Or whatever the fuck.
(laughing)
- There's like the opening credit crawl.
- Yeah.
- It's just like Palpatine has announced like his return.
That was like a Fortnite exclusive event.
- Really?
- So like part of, canonically, like in the Star Wars lore,
like Palpatine announced he was coming back to the fortnight.
That's sick. Do you know, did you remember that,
that fortnight event where they, it was, they did like it for a Martin Luther
King, Martin Luther King. Yeah. And they, there was everyone, no,
everyone, a bunch of people started using, there's a,
they have a cat woman in the game and the cat woman has an emote.
That's cat woman's whip.
A bunch of people started doing cat woman's whip and they had to turn off all
emotes yeah which is like what there must you should have hired somebody to look
through every single emote in the game yeah come on yeah even doing the
oversight loss well any of the about yeah I should have just had them turned
off yeah I don't think it's please like disrespectful to do the floss while MLK
talks that's very disrespectful respectful do you only okay what other
times you do do you do the floss when a song is very cool hmm right and when when
it when someone's spitting. Yeah, exactly. I mean, well, okay, doing the dance with the
L on your forehead, you can't do that. Yeah, that stands for love all races. That's Luther.
Martin Luther King. You can't do it. See, we fixed it. And the dab. Well, that's cool.
Okay, I think we solved everything. And the whipping. Destroy all bad things. Well, that's
Catwoman's whip. It's different. Yeah, so see, you're freaking out about nothing. I
think that cops should be legally allowed to eat people to stop them from doing crimes.
I agree you should be a cop should be able to take a bite. No gun. If you're under arrest
a cop should be able to eat your flesh. I think cops should have no guns but they should have
full. Forks and knives. Yeah. They can eat any part of you if you're resisting arrest.
Yeah. For any reason. Stop resisting! Yeah. They should be able to hold you down and just
take a big bite. Stop resisting. If I was doing some kind of I don't know terrorism or shoplifting.
Let's think about this for a second.
Five foot five.
Okay.
Said he was, well he said he was black.
Could have been, I mean could have been mistaken.
Black Irish maybe.
Yep.
And I think they said that his name was, I think that...
I said his initials.
He had his initials on his clothes.
And I think there were eyewitness reports that said that he said he was quote unquote
so tired at the time of the attack.
I think he went, "Ugh, I'm tired," and then threw a gas bomb and killed 13 people.
Well, the train comes faster if you do a gas bomb.
That's true.
It's night, you put nitrous in there.
Yeah, you have to move everyone out of there.
Yeah, that's true, yeah.
I bet the trains are fucked today, man.
Oh, boy.
Dude, it's going to ruin my Sonic 2 experience.
Do you remember whenever they, in Boston a couple times somebody would just jump in front
of the train and then just everybody would just be, there's not a single dead person
who has ever been more hated.
get so mad in front of a train yeah that is like and you and you just everybody's
just what an asshole yeah so cool dude yeah that's the best way to kill
yourself yeah just ruin a million people's days yeah yeah that's a
everyone's taking a hundred dollar uber to work it immediately justifies your
suicide yeah it's like oh everyone's like yeah he deserves yeah yeah he's not
a coward he's a dickhead yeah yeah it's a jerk mm-hmm a real jerk yep yeah yeah I
think everything if you are a jerk you should kill yourself
you think jerk should kill him I think every time I heard in bullies how about
jag offs hey bullies jag offs but in you hate
jack wagons as much as I do pricks Oh don't get me started on prairies jabroni
means you're going to see the barrel of an AR-15.
Sluts.
Hey, well, no.
So it's you can come over to my damn house, that's what's up.
Whenever somebody jumps in front of the train, I find out what their name is, I write it
down in my little notebook so I can show up to their funeral night after everyone's tearful
and like, and you know, missing them and stuff, I can just say, well, just so you know, they
jumped in front of the train, they ruined the water.
i just want to balance this out of russia a lot of nice things but they made a lot
of people very happy i was i mean more people that are in this room right now i
mean it
you guys you guys are clearly a lovely family love your your son very much but
there's not that many of you and and he ruined a thousand people's days in ten
seconds i think it was a loving father
uh... uh... a brother
a husband
yet and he was a late nurse
you know and a prick he was a late nary made everyone freaking late on the train
and i was a lot of stock about this is a loving father i think he was a hating
ass clown
the m
i think he was a jabroni and kind of a she kill yourself in his funeral
and that is our that would just perpetuate the site even i'll do it too
in order to bring the site in never going to die so that's a good fortnight
dances
no true will know i would give you when before the they drop it off a lot of
Crying yeah, you're doing
Yeah
He made me late to the movies he latent me for Sonic to late in me to the movies here's the thing bro, just
Just blow into his thumb blow him back up when they're like reading they're reading
They're like they're they're sad like you will do thing at the at the podium
and you're just like write down a note like hand it up sitting there like with
your hands in your lap like looking at them really expectantly it's like keep
handing them notes he latent me he latent me to the movies he late me made
another I meant he made me late what's the way they kill you to him - is that
the ultimate like one man damage that one person can cause by killing them so I
I mean if unless what if you did like you had all your friends and family and
everybody come to your one-man show and then the final act of the one-man show
is you like kill yourself but then you gotta see bad theater and a suicide but
they won't be war I think for work the the ultimate route day ruining suicides
are unlocked when you are a politician or a president power if you're the
president you can basically yeah yeah you know be fun is kill yourself you're
standing over the nuclear button yeah and then you kill yourself and it's just
your head just hits it.
- Yeah.
- You know, and you're like, oh.
- I like the nuclear football.
- What?
- How about like a nuclear book,
or like a nuclear Bela Sebastian record?
- I hate these meatheads knocking into each other
on the field, it's so--
- It's playing with the nuclear football.
- Homoerotic.
- Oh my God.
- Oh my God, you guys are wearing tights,
you know all sorts of tights.
- I only watch the nuclear football
for the nuclear commercials.
- J. Superman.
(laughing)
uh...
on god
you know that the nuclear commercial is a damn it uh... damn
springfield power plant commercial that's right
he lost me
yeah i don't know where you're a slayer part
you have an absolutely i don't know this but with this fellow homer in charge of
the damn nuclear stuff
probably that asshole fuckin mister clown primary and so
don't get me started
I don't even want to say his name anymore.
Yeah, Mr. Burns-His-Penis-On-A-Foreman-Grill.
Yeah.
That's the only way he can get hard.
Homer, because he should be at Homer instead of working with these dangerous chemicals
and radioactivity.
And Bart, he should be Bart-He should be Bart-A-Wearing some books for doing homework.
To do some homework with.
Bart, yeah, fart, stinky kid.
Yep, Lisa, she should be leasing a new car instead of being a child.
She's so intelligent.
And Maggie, she should be bagging my groceries.
Yeah, which actually if you watch the intro the show she ends up being in a bag. It's an Easter egg
For her future. It's an Easter. Her character was originally named baggy. Yeah
Easter egg that they left Marge. She should be she should be marging my penis up into a bunch of meat
Marging it up in a hole
She should be turning what she'd be using margarine are all the margineer Marge. She should be marginalized
She should be barging into the room where I'm doing my thing
Yeah, hey Marge when the ants come marching up your leg and into your dress
And I want to watch that Marge a bunch of ants all over your body
No, there's those guys who have like the holding in pee fetishes
Yeah
Yeah, one time there was this there's this book in free period in middle school. We had this teacher who would like just
in there just stand in the front of the classroom like oh I wish I'd be so hot
dude oh no she would read this book that was about like all these crazy ways that
people had died yeah and one of them was a guy in like the 16th century held in
his piece so long that he just croaked damn yeah croaked he couldn't just die
yeah he didn't die for like 30 or 40 more years but he did go ah that's
pretty cool yeah I bet the pee came out of his mouth
else
I think pretty much everything becomes P. Like it saturates every part of your body.
I think all body fluids are P.
Yeah, I think P is like the base.
Because like everything has water in it to be wet.
And P is water.
Yeah, cum is white P.
97% P.
It's P with sperms in it.
I mean, let's be scientific.
Yeah, it's P with the sperms in it.
Yeah, which makes it white.
But it's not just white P. I mean, that's a bit simplistic.
Yo, let me get the P with the sperms in it.
Sure, sure.
Oh, you want the P with the sperms?
and the result is OMG it's a kid first you put the sperms on the grill then you
put the pee on the grill I love that guy yeah I mean so you see him we should go
to his bodega we maybe he needs us today maybe we need to go be the OC
protection force it's true yeah we need to ghost we need to be protecting the
subways.
Yeah.
I'm going to stand in front of all the subway entrances.
We need to be, what are they called?
The Angels?
Yeah.
What's Curtis Silva in?
I don't know.
Red Berets?
I don't think we need to be in the Red Berets.
I think we could be in our own thing.
Yeah.
The Cool Berets.
Well, if we-
Well, Berets are kind of lame.
Berets are kind of like, artsy.
Yeah.
Well, let's-
I mean, what about the Cool Hats?
Or like the-
Okay.
What about the-
Top Hat Brigade.
Yeah, the Bowler Hat Brigade.
The White Angels.
Because there's, I mean, there's the blue angels there in the sky.
Yeah.
What about the white angels I feel like would be in the snow.
Well, we need to also, we need it, I mean, we don't want to be angels because we want
to scare the bad guys.
The brown angels.
We can do the brown angels.
What about the like...
The earth, the ground.
Yeah, we could be in Brownsville.
The evil devils.
We can be in, yeah, because what's scarier to a bad guy than punishment for his crime?
The devil.
Retribution.
Yeah.
And maybe the devil is like the ultimate.
devils of retribution. Wait no because you can't you can't go what if it like the
the the regular guys. Okay what about the good devils? See the regular guys because
then the guy the the criminal is like well stop I'm a regular guy and he's
like okay yeah I don't give a fuck. And then you pull out the nunchucks and he's like
oh regular guy. I didn't hear the capital letters in it. Yeah he goes so what I don't
I don't care about a regular get shuriken right in his head. Yeah, yeah spin kick
yeah, okay. I guess I'll stop jumping the turnstile. You put a shuriken in my
head resist. You rest guy.
Let you
arrest
the rested. Okay, so how is this? Yeah, this is you're not spelling it right.
Yeah, are you? Yeah, I think I spelled it correctly. I don't think so. I think
was the right word. What about the regular Jaguars? Okay. Because that has like a
second syllable. What about the Czech ass defense force? JDF? Yeah. What about the prick
destroyers? The ball sack drainers? We're the thing eliminators. Dick obliterators. Dick
obliterator with our and we're obliterating dicks yeah yeah I dicks are
a huge criminal cocksuckers criminals don't so about the about the upstanding
cocksucker we do it standing up oh my god meal before the upstanding
cocksuckers what the fuck so we could say that the fuckers the fuckers what
What about the evil penis?
- Yeah, the evil ween.
- The evil weeners.
- What about the NYPD?
What if we just let them solve this?
- I don't think they're on the case like we are.
- They're busy with Battle Island.
- I wanna stop these guys.
(laughing)
- They're on special assignment.
- I really wanna stop these guys who jump the turnstiles.
They need to be stopped.
- I don't like it.
- That is a despicable crime.
- I mean, and think about it.
When you go over the turnstile,
What touches the turnstile? Either your butt or your wiener.
Yeah, and then I'm over there and I'm-
And then respectable guys like me-
And then my mouth is on it.
Who push the turnstile with both my hands and then lick my hands to get better grip-
Also-
When I'm trying to push the turnstile-
Listen, I've put on a few pounds. Sometimes I get stuck in the turnstile.
I gotta lube myself up with my spit by licking every fucking inch of the thing-
Yeah.
To get out of there.
And what's on there? A criminal's fleas.
Great. Now it's a criminal-
Now it's 15 different criminal's nutsacks and I can't tell which one's which.
Poop crumbs out a criminal's rectum.
Yeah, awesome. This is the greatest city on earth.
Oh my god.
Everyone's wrecked.
You know who'd be really disappointed?
Lady Liberty.
No, that's the thing.
Your rectum won't touch the turnstile if you're not pressing up against it, putting your weight
on it as you vault over it like some kind of evil Olympian.
Remember that guy that died hopping the turnstile?
Like his foot got clipped and then he just like fell.
Yeah, instant karma much.
Yeah, the Darwin Awards much.
Yep.
Yep, you go in the Darwin Awards.
This guy was so low IQ he thought he could jump over a turnstile.
I want to start the Prick Head Awards.
best for the most it did the most annoying assholes I've ever seen
winner number one with a short terrorist doing Darwin Awards God like yeah the
dead asshole awards it's just like it's all just kids you know already what it
is it's so funny it's usually like dads who like we're trying to deep-fry a
turkey but if you did like a kid with leukemia this fucking asshole used our
our tax dollars for his make a wish thing. I did I had I had the
Darwin. I their Darwin Awards book was in my like classroom. Oh, yeah, and like
middle school, and I read some of it, and there definitely were a bunch in
there. They're like this eighteen year old kid like had tried to have sex by
the side of the road, and he got run over by a car. What an idiot, it's just
a thousand ways to die. Yeah, they should call it a thousand ways to die and
keep the Darwin Awards for animals that evolved into something cool. The good
of the the dinosaurs and the chickens. It's like a razor, a razor shark. Mm-hmm. The one
good thing about it is that it's not like just ways people dies. They also counted
if you accidentally cut off your wiener. There are a bunch of good accidentally
cutting off wiener stories. So it's either you stop yourself from reproducing. It's either death. This man cheated on his wife and his crazy wife Lorena.
What is that? We're getting an alert. Avoid the area of third ave to fifth ave from
20th to 4th to 40th Street in Brooklyn. Emergency personnel are on scene of an
active police incident and have stabilized the area. Okay. Alright. Dude,
that was a scary ass. That was really scary. Wow. I thought I was like, well, it's
over. Yeah. At first I thought it was coming from the timer. Me too. Yeah. The timer's made
enough weird noises. Yeah. The timer's beeped at us enough. Oh. Well, that woke me up. Yeah.
Yeah, I wish it was a nuclear attack though. No cap. Yeah
Damn
All right, you guys want to go there yeah, let's go
We're actually that we're the asshole fuckers from the subway
Yep
Metal I got a prick head award to give out
Where is this fucking piece of dog crap the dumbest guy that died today?
Darwin Awards for everybody who was on their phone when they got shot in the head
They're probably probably some people wearing freaking air pods. I didn't even hear it. Do you wait? Oh my god
I just smiled thinking that maybe a hipster died today. Oh
My god, do you think it was probably drinking a cup of coffee?
Then he got his head blown off with a shotgun
gun. Yeah, his head probably got shot, didn't fly off because it was held on by his damn
scarf. Oh wow. Yeah. His head's held on for infinity because of the damn scarf. Yeah,
infinity scarf, yeah. Probably his glasses frames were so thick it repelled the bullet
that headed towards his eye like Superman and he survived to annoy another man. Yep,
I'll live to annoy another day. Yep. To complain another day about my avocado toast not having
enough probably like five layers of flannel and it's like Kevlar yeah it's
probably his way to air one to get a $50 soda yeah Bevlar Bev like a Starbucks
latte and a glass bottle yeah what what's the law like Kevlar
yeah yeah his name's Lars he's probably drink his bulletproof coffee yeah yeah
that's right I think hipsters would drink bulletproof coffee I think that's
a good American brand run by Patriot not a brand yeah it is no you're thinking
- You're thinking of the other coffee.
- What?
- Black Rifle.
- Yeah.
Bulletproof is just you put butter in it instead of cream.
- That makes it bulletproof to do that?
- Supposedly.
- So says the men online.
- Yeah, we gotta call some of the people in that area.
Let 'em know.
- Let's make a call.
- Dial a call.
- Call Eric.
Oh, you know why all this crime is happening?
'Cause Eric Adams got COVID.
- All right, who am I calling?
- Call Eric Adams.
- Third F, three.
- All right, wait.
I'm gonna call third ad real quick.
What the hell?
Dude, maybe I didn't pay my bill this month.
There it is.
Oh shit, I'm gonna call.
You getting a call?
Do they need us?
I played a ball game with my friends today.
It was a lot of fun.
Oh my god, it's the assailant.
I am getting tired.
Please.
Oh my god, he said that.
He's eating chips.
the corpses oh my god he's a lunatic that's chillin I'm pressing redial yeah
we need a let's record this two puppy biscuits he said he wants two puppy
biscuits or the attacks will continue oh god disgusting killed someone sexually
motivated I'm getting I'm getting another phone call Oh who is it hello
- Hello? - Hello?
Hello?
- Hello? - Is anybody there?
- What the hell?
- Five.
(phone chimes)
- Five, we have, there's five more attacks left.
- Butterfly.
- Oh, five butterflies.
- Oh, that's a, oh, okay.
- That's false alarm.
- He said you have to use a butterfly effect to stop it.
- Shit, we gotta go back in time.
Press 1998.
- Okay.
- One.
- No, that's too far back.
I actually went to one.
Oh my god.
What's he gonna say?
Stop that, you're nasty.
You're nasty.
We're gonna get you.
The devil's number.
Oh my god.
Six hats.
What's that noise?
That's him counting the hats.
Guys, I'm scared.
Alright, this guy's weird.
I don't like him.
- I'm gonna take him.
- Yeah.
- Check out this weird guy.
- We'll leave that for the--
- We'll let him do his thing.
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Yeah.
- All right, we have a list today.
- Finally.
- Who, you said someone sent it?
- Max in the Discord sent this.
- Max sent this, thank you Max.
- Thank you Max.
- The top 10 worst toys of all time.
- Oh no.
- On top10s.com.
I don't wanna read this.
- Yeah, let's just skip it.
This sounds like it's probably some bullshit.
- Sounds biased.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, what do you call the killer back?
Yeah, hold on.
See what he's up to.
Yeah, wait, hold on.
You know, one of the worst toys ever is the killer phone.
Scout!
Let's count on the phone!
Officer, we have his name.
It's Scout.
His name is Scout, he is a dog, he hangs out with a frog.
I have information that could lead to the killer's arrest.
He's a dog named Scout and he's trapped in this phone.
Yes, he hangs out with a leapfrog.
He loves counting hats and butterflies.
And he says, "Counting hats and butterflies."
He's a dog named Scout and he's trapped in this phone.
Yes, he hangs out with a leap frog.
He loves counting hats and butterflies.
And he says goodbye.
He's very polite.
Alright, I'm off the phone with Scout.
Alright, well Scout, that's good information.
When that comes out, they'll have already caught him by the time this comes out.
Yeah, by the time this comes out, they'll know we knew first.
know we knew for all know that it was scout. They all know that they they
raided his house. They found they found over five hats over six butterflies.
It's time to Apple's 1059 a.m. On Tuesday, April 12th, 2022. So, you
know, it's like a like off the streets is weak table.
Five ads, six butterflies, two apples, nine caterpillars.
(laughter)
- So stupid.
And one big gift.
- I love a big gift.
- Okay.
- One gun.
- All right.
- And a bazooka.
- Yeah.
- Number one worst toy of all time is doggy do board game.
- I'm gonna have to agree,
'cause I've never even heard of this game.
- My sibling is FaceTiming me.
Hold up.
decline.
One second.
Okay, doggy doo board game.
What would even be the point of a doggy doo board game?
Yeah, that doesn't sound fun.
What kind of, does a dog just poop out a bone?
Dogs poop out, well dog poop is like closest to, I heard, like cat poop.
You heard, you tasted, you mean.
I heard it tastes almost identical to dog turds.
when I hear and poop are similar yeah in some I never thought of that is similar.
I didn't say they're the same. No, you're that's what a lot of people will.
There's definitely a lot of a lot of parallels between turns and poop yeah
yeah, what do you perpendicular the Venn diagram is a lot different. The true is
but the Venn diagram of turds poop and do
where do you think like how much overlap is there? Do you think so? Let's be
Scooby would be just do only
There's no Scooby turds.
Oh you haven't.
Oh he, okay.
We won't talk about that today.
We have a four quadrant Venn diagram.
Okay.
Do we want to draw this out?
Yeah.
Melvin. Melvin do.
You're adding things into the circles already.
What did we say?
It's turds, poop,
do and crap and snacks.
Snacks.
Snacks. Snacks. So over and then overlap. So wait how do you do a four
Venn diagram? Well you got to figure out what's in it first and then you draw the
overlaps. So we're doing. That's not how you draw a Venn diagram. Do you know what a Venn
diagram is? Yeah but we don't know how much overlap is between the different
circles. This is more of like a compass. A Venn diagram. To do a four one you'd have to go
around. No, this is what we're doing.
See, look at that. Okay, so between do and snacks, you have
Scooby.
Okay, but this can't be this isn't this doesn't work as a Venn
diagram because these two, the two ones opposite each other,
they don't what if these two share something that these two
don't have, you can't put it in there. They don't have for a
four side event diagram. It doesn't work like that. They
I don't have anything to comment.
- It's too small, too.
How am I gonna write anything in this one?
- There's more, I think.
- I was just showing, that was a proof of concept.
- I think we do a three one.
I don't think we have snacks in there.
I don't think snacks really enter into it.
I think you just wanted to add snacks 'cause you're hungry.
- No, but we could put like chips and stuff in there.
- All right, so you know, here's how it works.
Let me see.
So, proof of concept here.
So it's more like this.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
That's a three, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, actually let's put, we'll click and then there's one big one.
And this Venn diagram is everything.
Let me show you something.
You haven't even let me draw a single Venn diagram yet.
Don't use that on here.
I'm taking it away.
You guys lost the privilege.
What?
But I want to diagram some shit.
Me and Caleb will use this one.
You don't get anything.
Here's what I'm envisioning.
We have our own.
Yep.
Oh, I'm having so much fun making our Venn diagram over here.
It's not a Venn diagram.
I
This is the four way Venn diagram.
Okay, here's what, here's how I think the Venn diagram should look.
Okay, so you start off, there's four, there's four, okay there's four right here, right?
Look guys, and then each of these can share with each other like this, and then maybe we have one that's like this, and then like that.
And then this way there's a different intersection between all of them.
between all of them.
- Hold on, all right.
- That's a bunch of gobbledy goo.
- There's one four way.
- Is this what science is about these days?
- So maybe we start with like a big.
- Big circle?
- Big circle.
So this is like the one where everything is most similar to.
- Okay, cool.
- Right?
And then just two here.
- Two little ones at the bottom.
- And then one that kind of like fills.
- A longer one.
- Yeah, and then.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right, I'm liking this.
- Then these two here.
this is this is just stuff that's similar to this one.
Mm-hmm. And that's how they connect. And then there's also there's a connection
here and that's the Squidward diagram. Oh that does look like Squidward. It does look a
lot like Squidward. I think we'll put turds up here. Uh-huh. And we can leave the other
ones open. Yeah. All right. Yeah. That looks pretty good then. It looks just like
Squidward where he has turds in his brain. Yeah. I think we figured it out.
Doggy Do Board Game. It's a Squidward style game. Yeah. What obsession do people have
with dogs doing their business? There are way too many movies, books, games,
and toys about dog poop and pee. Seriously, Doggy Do? What movie is about dog poop?
I can't think about a dog poop movie or book. Yeah. Seriously, Doggy Do? You
have to collect dog crap? What kind of game is that? Why would anyone want to
collect dog crap in the first place? Plus, the get a life and rub the whale thing
were kind of funny. I'm out. This game is crap. Is this a real game?
This is Mark Cuban. Mark Cuban said that.
This is one of those...
Sharks... I have a board game that will revolutionize the way that kids think about poop.
This is one of those games that is recommended for two-year-old boys.
It makes disgusting noises when the poop is about to come out and yes, the poop can be red.
And then once it's dropped the poop, it eats it again.
Okay. I need to see this.
This is probably teaching kids that if you want a pet puppy, you're going to be the one that cleans its...
dot dot dot... droppings.
- I need to see the doggie do board game.
- Where does droppings factor in?
- I don't know.
Is there droppings in this?
I thought it was a do game.
- It said clean its droppings.
- I gotta look at doggie do board game.
See if this is right.
- 'Cause if I drop my goldfish snacks on the floor,
that's droppings too.
- Yeah, true. - That's not poo.
That's snack, that's the overlap of snacks and--
- Oh God, it's a real God damn game.
- Oh no, what's wrong with this generation?
- What's wrong with this generation?
- You're saying that like you're upset.
- Yeah, I am upset.
- Let me see it.
- When you gotta go, you gotta go.
Oh, nasty, that dog is brown.
Why is there a bee running away from his green noxious fart?
Wait, they have doggie do corgi. They have one for different dogs.
Oh, God almighty, this is disgusting.
What the fuck? And look at this. This one's called "Don't Step In It."
This guy's about to step in a piece of shit.
What kind of fucking board games?
I mean, yeah, we went from legitimate business monopoly to shit like this.
Joe Brandon in office all of a sudden we got dog shit board games. Yeah, it's like okay
teach the kid to play with dog poo all day. And then look they got soggy doggy.
That's just not right. Like they got balls on it. He's gonna smell like fucking crap.
That's the tagline? Yeah. He smells like wet crap.
Number two worst toy of all time is baby wee wee. Yeah that's not a toy.
I'm gonna I'm gonna look this one up - okay, let me use Patrick song hmm you
might want to lose a blue a purple link
this is so inappropriate yet it's for four-year-olds first they have boy parts
and girl parts you have to pull their pants down and see them what whoa you
you pull down the baby's shorts and you just see his fucking penis and he pees
all over the place. Baby wee wee what are you doing man? How do you get the pee
into the baby? You get a... like you're like that must suck being a parent
having to like load pee into a baby like that. I wish I was built like this. Oh my
god. That is so scary. Oh my god. Listen to this comment. I was at a
this summer day care don't ask
and the door to our classroom is
locked. So we had to wait in the
preschool room. My younger sister
saw a box full of dolls and
started rummaging through it.
There were about six baby wee wee
dolls naked. She screamed and I
came to see what was going on. I
was so disgusted that I hid the
behind a shelf and get this. I'm
a girl and four of those stupid
dolls were boys. Wow yeah
interesting, but no one cares
which gender you are
through. Yeah, that's facts. Oh my God, dude. This is the weirdest day ever. I just got
a text. Phil, my dog, all his teeth are falling out. He's like losing all his baby teeth at
the same time. Wow. This is an awesome day. One doll is similar to this junk. Is this
a day? Something's wrong today. I'm half asleep. It's April Fool's Day. Dude, baby, apparently
there's a doll that has a fucking baby cock on it. Well, listen, I didn't get to finish
- Sorry. - One doll is similar to this
junk and it has a moving wee wee.
- No.
- I'm thinking about it right now
and I feel sick just thinking about it.
- Sue that company, actually seriously gross.
Who wants a plastic penis spraying wee?
(laughing)
I think the inventor needs to go to a mental asylum.
- Who puts a penis on a doll?
- Are you kidding me?
- Someone says, I'm sure some little girls
played with this dirty.
- Aw, come on. - What the hell?
very in a pro pro
yes, it got banned. It joined lawn darts, cabbage patch kids
and other band toys cabbage patch kids or what I have. I have
huge news for you guys. I don't know if you notice this. I
completely missed this. It happened last year in November
2021 a big toys news. I don't know if you guys are familiar
with the toy Hall of Fame, but
alongside American girl and alongside American girl dolls
sand was just inducted into the toy Hall of Fame and sand. Yeah,
Wow. Fed the beach? Just sand. Holy shit. That's huge. Look if you search Toy Hall of Fame sand.
Like? What would you already search before? Well yeah I mean I see here the Toy Hall. At the
Strong Museum. What's the Strong Museum? Into the Toy Hall of Fame. It's where the, it's where the.
I mean that's, we've been, listen, sand's been around a long time. Listen to this, listen to
this quote from the museum curator. I mean they found sand in the moon. "Sand has a global reach
that most toy manufacturers would envy. It's been a vehicle for play since
prehistory and anyone who has spent the day at the beach can understand
the allure of this toy. See that's the thing though, if it's like sand is
obviously a legend right? So why has it been so long? Like why now? I mean
you know it's going in with Fisher-Price corn pepper. Yeah well listen to this
these are these are the other finalists for the Toy Hall of Fame. Battleship,
billiards cabbage patch kids Fisher Price corn popper my jaw and pop masters of
the universe the pinata settlers of Catan and the toy fire what is the Fisher
Price corn popper imagine being the nerd ass creator of settlers of Catan and
going up and saying and being like finding out my my my best toy of all
time has to compete against sand yeah
is gonna be saying I don't know how sand that's what I mean like what other
things are in like if you're doing toys you it's got to be all stuff like sand
and dirt for the first like hundred years definitely oh yeah you even get to
fucking yeah the Fisher price corn popper that's a yeah that's a go to do
it the pusher yeah oh that is that is why that is that might give sand a run
for its money that might be the best yeah of all time or that is a really
good I don't know it's called that dude I could do that I would honestly have
fun with that right now. They should make adult sized corn poppers. Yeah yeah yeah like a
Dyson corn popper. That kid's having the time of his life. Look at this male model using it.
This guy calling any person, any person who's in like a toy commercial or something like that.
He's like, "I'm seeing all these freaking male models." Great, great. Look he's sucking his cheeks in.
in he's not even skinny look at this freaking male model I bet he's brainless
what is he just spit up and then hit his microphone against I know dude he's this
is the worst day ever dude my dog's teeth are falling out Patrick saw a picture of
a baby and had an attack there's somebody throwing the the riddler is on
the subway. No, just the idea of calling any person a male model. Like the fuckin, like
you ever see those like stock photos of like the fat guys eating wings? Like, "Oh look
at these fucking, I hate society's expectations. I have to compete with all these fucking male
models." "Look at these beauty standards. I'm supposed to look like this." "They want
people look like this. It's like the stock photo.
Yeah, Transylvanian vampire.
[Laughter]
Guy in a wheelchair at work.
Vampire in a grocery store.
Great, they want me to be in a wheelchair.
Oh, great, yeah. I'm sick of these fucking male models, dude.
Well, that's the thing about, yeah, now that we have, you know, models of all sizes and stuff,
I'm just going to be confused about what I should look like.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It used to be you know what you're supposed to look like and you're
supposed to look like you do heroin and wear black leather. Am I supposed to be fat?
Am I supposed to even have legs? Should I be chopping my legs off?
Oh it's like a guy in like husky jeans and he's holding like a
beer stein. It's just like oh great. Another fucking male model I have to look
like real-life Homer. Number three is Shopkins. I don't know. Shopkins I know.
I'm sure you do. The top comment here is an axe to grind about about
Shopkins. Shopkins look like little it's like the little food that has eyes and
stuff. Okay. What? So here's this comment. What now? Here's this comment here.
They are very different to Moshi Monsters figures and I will explain it to
to you. 1. Moshi Monsters characters only has like 5 food characters. 2. Moshi Monsters
characters are mostly animals with clothing or references to famous singers, etc. Broccoli
Spears, Britney Spear. 6. Shopkins are all food, all of them, not just 5, and they can
go on top of your pencils or pens. Moshi Monsters don't do that, and clearly a child must be
stupid if it happens to choke on one. These aren't bad toys. Problem solved.
- See, a Shopkin, you get the food it's supposed to be,
and then the little character next to it.
- So this is an eraser?
- I think.
- That's what it says here.
I like throwing it, I like that they spend
the whole comment being like,
"Shopkins are not a ripoff of Moshi Monsters,"
and then they just sneak in.
"If a child chokes on a toy, it's stupid."
(laughing)
- See, they've got a kid's cuisine with eyes right there.
- Whoa.
- Okay, that's actually kind of awesome.
Shopkins are kind of tight.
Shopkins seem like a tight toy, yeah.
Might actually be cool.
We might need to get some Shopkins.
See, I'm more into just having the tiny food.
I'd rather have big food.
I like the characters.
I want proportionate, like big food as if the food we have right now is the small food.
You know what I mean?
Maybe like a room size.
That could be pretty big, yeah.
Can you imagine sitting down and eating one giant cornflake for dinner?
Oh my gosh.
Wouldn't that be so good?
Look, they got big Shopkins.
Pringle, well that's not a full-size Pringles can but it looks enough like one.
Also the ready-whipped, it doesn't even have the food in it dude I don't give a
fuck about the packaging. You know? You're style over substance. You
don't even want the food. No, I'd rather have the little version like a
tiny Dr. Pepper can. I bet you're one of these fuckers who watches a lady make a
a
over. He does does reviews of skateboard trucks. I've been watching those before
bed. Really? And it's so soothing. He's Canadian. He's like the turning of this
truck is actually pretty pretty similar to a... That sounds like the least
soothing voice I've ever heard. What about your perfect life means that you need to be soothed
before you go to bed? I can't sleep. That's why I'm tired. You can't sleep so you look
at your phone in bed? Yeah. Yeah. You still watch a... You have to read. You have to
expand your intellect. That's how you fall asleep.
Dude, throwing on, throwing on,
binging with Babish Chef's Cubanos
before bed. It's gonna keep you up all night. You're gonna be
thinking about the food. You're gonna be sitting there licking your lips.
I have a beautiful dream about eating their
Chef Cubano. You can barely fucking fall asleep because your lips are so wet.
I'm eating Jon Favreau's Cubano
and I'm married to
Sofia Bergara. Her name is, no.
You're not.
I'm the one who likes Chef.
I'm the Chef. You're not the guy who likes
Chef. How many fucking times, no,
Well you're not, you're the guy who kinda likes Chef.
No.
How many times have you seen Chef?
Probably like 15 times.
Lie.
That is a lie.
You're just lying.
No I'm not.
You're lying.
I've seen Chef 15 times.
That is such a fucking lie.
Nope.
That is bold of you.
Mm-mm.
You disgust me.
I've seen Chef 15 times.
You don't even have, you don't even understand what it's like to have divorced parents.
No but I- You watch that movie and you go, "Oh it's about
sandwiches, fuck you."
Yeah, it's about sandwiches.
No!
It's not!
It's about Cubano's-
about pasta a jolo, jolololo. It's for boys like me who have a fat dad and a hot Latino mom and
we and that's like the struggle of our lives. No the struggle is he that he
needs to go back to his roots and make sandwiches. No it's like no country for old
men it's not about chef it's about the son. It's a well the son plays TF2 and I
remember that. Guess what I played when I was a kid? Kick the ball. I played kick the ball.
Yeah. Is that different from kickball? Yeah. Yeah. Kick the ball is... You're by yourself.
You know why I was by myself? Dad was out on the food truck serving hot dogs and
hamburgers. He doesn't serve hot dogs and hamburgers on the food truck. He serves
jesico bonos. I want to like just a backyard cookout hamburger and hot
dog so bad we could do it we could do a burger who has the closest burger who is
the closest thing to a backyard the office oh yeah we do bro what are you
doing man we have a burger fish we just get a little you get a little shitty
grill yeah I was like I want I need it so bad all right let's hit let's have a
burger fest fun you guys twist my arm more let's have a burger fest mm-hmm my
god I can't wait all right let's do it in one second okay all right pause the
the show. That's the pause noise. Okay, now it pauses. Okay, the unpause. I had
too many burgers and too much beer. I got so fucked up at Burger Fest. We were
out there in the desert for four days. I'm not too full at all. Who was your
favorite act at Burger Fest? The lettuce was honestly underrated to me. You know
what? This is going to be kind of a it was a sleeper. The mustard. Yeah, for me
the peanut butter noodles what this motherfucker you guys didn't have any
of those oh this motherfucker it's not a burger fest without peanut butter
noodles we got a badass over here okay but second choice second choice my
napkin that's you're the only person who sits there nobody put their gum there
it's not gum what is it it's a sticky it's a sticky and I definitely put it
there yeah I got so mad for a second I was like did fucking Joe and Alex sit
here and put their gum all over our shit and then realized no it was me and I put
this
a
put an MTV in it yeah yep MTV video killed the radio star yeah and now they
don't even play music videos now it's all video on that's all a Rob Dyrdek's
fucking ridiculous pussy the fact that they don't play music videos yeah Rob
Dyrdek's fantasy factory I wish that I worked in a fantasy factory and we watch
music videos but it's not Oh Rob it big and big and black what's the show called
Robin big yeah what if I wanted to watch Rob well they had music on there oh true
he had Bobby light Bobby light would sing here's a here's a sub list under Furby
boom okay this is um these toys are annoying in many ways I'll give you ten
reasons what is a Furby boom I think it's a type of Furby that one hooks one
they never shut up - they're too gassy three they don't have an on/off switch so
they wake up at any sudden movement and they turn off at any time for they say
blah blah, which is rude. Five, they make all kinds of annoying sounds. Six, they
have different personalities that are annoying. Seven, they speak some Furby
language. Eight, newer versions have gone downhill. Nine, they do whatever they
want. Ten, it takes long to change the personality depending on what it is. I
can probably come up with more, but this is all I got right now. Do you remember
speaking of, it wasn't a Furby, but they were like those like toys and they were
like speakers. It's like a toy speaker you could play music on but it like it had
like a face and like a little speaker for a mouth. You ever know anyone who had
those the thing the video now that were just play like the shittiest version of
a Nickelodeon show? Yeah, and then video now somehow like licensed something through Gameboy like
Nintendo and then they had the video now cartridges and you could watch like a
a Pokemon episode in like 180p on your Nintendo Gameboy which was like the worst
thing ever cuz like the Gameboy screen you'd had to like sit under the Sun
that's sick yeah I watched a photo finish the Pokemon episode Joe Fosso's
oh yeah Jodo Joto that region that region went hard yeah dude what region
are you from? Shino. Nice. That's what Cameron's from. He's from Shino. I'm from the ghetto.
I'm from the ghetto region. Here's a comment on Furby Boom. This thing turns evil and starts
chanting voodoo. Once you turn it on it won't stop babbling for like three hours. The only
way to put it to sleep automatically is to pull its tail for ten seconds, but it wakes
up so easily with any sudden movement. My sister's Furby went to sleep and never woke
up Barbie yeah we get it yeah what is in bathing suits on it so there was they
were called the zizzle what was an imaginary friend he had oh they were
called a sizzle they were called the zizzle imaginary aliens oh I remember
those remember that shit yeah remember those the little robot dogs they do a
back flip. The iDog. And you go, "Go dog, yeah! Go dog, yeah!" Mm-hmm. The iDog and then the...
And that damn purple ketchup. Yeah. Low-key it tasted different, like grapes.
Tastes like Shrek swamp. Mm-hmm. Tastes like Shrek swamp. Tastes like Shrek swamp.
That's right, tastes like Shrek swamp! Number five is Barbie. I hate Barbie so
much and I hate Mattel. I want to ban Barbie and burn them in a big bonfire.
Barbie is a bad example for young children, teaching them to not eat and
and care about their looks 24/7.
It teaches, I guess Barbie doesn't eat.
It's a really good point.
- Yeah. - Barbie's always in the kitchen.
- To have a perfect figure. - Doesn't eat.
- Not for her. - For Ken, doesn't eat.
- Barbie's so unrealistic. - It's a good message
for boys. - And so stupid,
yet so darn popular, why?
Mattel makes a walkin' potty pup.
What is with this world and stupid doggy doo-doo toys?
The reason above is perfect.
They also make Barbie with private girl parts
and you're supposed to undress them and dress them up again.
Where even could I find something like this?
Who wants to stumble upon a naked Barbie doll? These dolls and lots of other dolls are so
inappropriate and they should be banned. Barbie can go right down and shoot and so can Mattel.
Barbie is a hoe. Let's be real, Barbie's a hoe-ish ass bitch.
You know? Barbie's a hoe and they sweat. Ken deserves better. Ken deserves better than Barbie.
Did you see, there was supposed to be a Barbie movie starring Amy Schumer?
Really? Yeah. Well she looks just like her.
She yeah, she's the most gorgeous woman of all time. Yep, but they she dropped out for creative differences. I
Think there is a huge glaring creative difference. Yeah, she was to you
I did I'd know I didn't say this. I just read this on my phone
Yeah, apparently when she was in the movie it was called Carby. I
Didn't that wasn't that doesn't come from me that's from that's from a bar beer the Barbie report news.com
I just got a notification. Okay, so.
Amy Schumer reportedly leaving the set of Barbie after creative differences.
Schumer claims, "I wanted to have four wheels but flesh and roll around like I was a car."
This comes only days after she was traumatized by the slap at the Oscars
where she said, "I need one million hamburgers to quell my rage."
page. She said I give me a win. She said give me a win. Dixie grocery bag full of
groceries to the VIP
yeah. I heard she well. I yeah, I heard this again. Yeah, I heard I heard that
she walked into the audition by accident, 'cause she thought it was
barbecue
and that's from the top. I did that that's come straight from the
director Quentin Tarantino. That's from Sources. He's directing the Barbie movie.
Oh man. Okay we got a. She is fat. Oh. What are you talking about? She's so
beautiful. Number six, Pee and Poo plush toys. Pee and Poo? My cousins have a
plush pee toy. No joke. I didn't know they made Pee and Poo plush toys. I
thought that like. When I take a pee that shit is plush. They had that show
Pee and Poo. They had that show. They had that show Pee and Poo. Pee and Jordan
when they had their show. That was a really good show. Yeah. Pee again and poop.
Pee again and poop. Pee again. Yep. Pee again and poop. Pee again and poop. Yep.
Yeah. Number seven breastfeeding baby doll. I like the breastfeeding. The
first half, you get you happy in the first half. Yeah. But in the second half
it actually has the word baby in it. Yeah. Disgusting. Yeah. It's like okay. Are you
- As a kid, are you supposed to put this fucking baby
on your nipple?
- Here's how it goes, it's like--
- What the hell's wrong with these goddamn--
- Breast, breast, okay.
- Does it come with a breast?
- Feeding.
- All right.
- Yep, I'm with you.
- Baby, huh?
Doll, no!
- No thank you, that's a girl thing.
- That's basically, yeah.
- Yeah, baby and doll, okay, breast and feeding,
those are two boyfriend things.
Baby and doll, two girl things.
- Yeah. - Don't like it.
- I was born at, I was born five.
- You were born five?
I was in the baby. You skipped baby? Yeah. What the? That's not true. It's true. Yeah,
I came out of my mom five. I was full head of hair. I was in there. I mean, I was in
there for five. Five years full? Yeah. Full term? I was in, they were giving me cakes
in there. What? Birthday, I had birthdays. You blow candles out of your mom's snatch?
Yeah, okay, our belly button don't be nasty.
(laughing)
Sorry, that's my bad.
Yeah, I went back in at six, I came out nine.
I think we should get a sizzle for the office.
I'm thinking about going back in,
cooking a little longer.
Come back in for six and come out for nine.
I'm preparing for a role, I'm jumping back in there.
Yeah, I just need, I only need one year out
'cause I need to do some things.
I need a sabbatical.
Yeah, oh my God, it's too warm in there.
to try my dad next. I'm going to crack a window. We should install a window on our moms and
jump back in them. No. I think I like my life out here. No, but remember inside though? Inside
was fire. I got pretty much bullied all the time when I was in the inside. Y'all remember
that song that I always play? I love that song. And then every once in a while you'd
have like, you'd hear your dad say, "I'm going to kill you when you get out of here." Yeah,
That'd be awesome. Yeah.
Yeah. So cool.
I actually like outside, because when I was in there, basically, the world was a vampire.
When I was in there, everything was mad red. It was fucking sick.
Yeah.
Everything was just red and just pulsating all the time, you know?
And I'm just in there doing backflips and shit.
Yeah.
My parents would be like, "Will you move out, please?"
I just kept trying to...
My mom was eating, like, the food that I had to eat in there was disgusting.
My mom was eating fucking...
She would get a chicken parm sub with mayo and pickles.
plus it had that string you can just tango. I was I was feasting on the
placenta though mm-hmm that thing oh my god that thing was hidden different
thing what's the thing people do they do women get their incentives out and get
to eat them getting the munchies and then and munching on that afterbirth was
just that was like so good midnight munchies oh my god banging on the
banging on the womb yeah yo send some food down bitch and a
cigarette smoke a cig oh my god dude my mom wanted to smoke a cigarette so bad
when she was pregnant with me I bet she did I bet my mom smoked cigarettes with
me in there I yeah I bet she did mm-hmm that's why I got ADHD yep smoke cigarettes
yeah yeah smoked cigarettes this is a real round pregnant with me she smoked a
lot of cigarettes fine that's right mom that's right mom I'm telling everyone you
smoked stings with me in there. It's gonna be so hard. I'm gonna find a picture of you
pregnant and I'm gonna Photoshop a cigarette into your hand. Or Photoshop the
cigarette out of her hand and then back in, put it in her other hand. So here's
two cigarettes in each hand. Number eight is aqua dots. Top comment is, "Watch out
parents, the next tiny ball you might buy for your children could include date rape."
And the comment after that, which is a nice follow-up to that, "So this toy
includes date rape." Keep that in mind. It just says that. "Aqua dots should have been for ages
eight and up instead of four and up. I mean I agree based on that first comment.
I don't know anything about the thing. Yeah number nine is Kinder Surprise.
Dangerous. Oh the eggs? Yeah. I want those. They're good but you can't have Kinder eggs.
They're illegal. Number ten is I didn't know this was a toy. Hitler doll. And the only
comment is idiots make dolls on everything. True. Yeah. All right. That's
that yet swag pooped out guys I chose unless we're dead from the short attack
yeah unless the short the short defender has killed again right now it is 1135 a.m.
Tuesday April 12th 2022 if this is our final thing you know exactly when it
happened it's nice to know you guys yeah I mean I've had a lot of fun and we're
headed to downtown Brooklyn well yeah we gotta go remember we gotta go catch the
We gotta go to the Zumis.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm trying to bust some joggers.
The Zumis by Burrow Hall.
Yeah.