Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Five pounds to the bottomless.
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- It was a trip of a lifetime.
- The trip.
- It was four friends and a car.
- It was a trip of a lifetime.
- And we did go so far.
We went to Los Angeles, the trip of a lifetime.
And it was so much onions and there was so much fan onions
and we ate some onions, grand onions.
(laughing)
We ate some grand onions.
- What's up?
- We're back.
- What the fuck is up?
- Can you believe it?
- Listeners.
- I can't believe it.
(laughing)
- You're off, you're done.
- What?
you're too excited to be doing this.
I could not believe that what I just heard.
What the fuck is up listeners?
That can't be allowed to happen.
What just talk like that?
Yeah he can't be allowed to do that.
And also to say listeners that was just way too much.
I couldn't handle that.
That took me out.
I thought it was cool.
Did you guys see the Mona Lisa became smeared by cream by the epic prankster of the century?
I didn't see.
I'm going to look this up real quick.
So this guy dressed up as an old lady in a wheelchair and then when he got near the Mona
He leaped out his chair and smeared it with cream. I'm just gonna search creamed on Lisa
uh-huh
Mona Lisa
From South China Morning Post Wow man in disguise attacks, Mona Lisa with cream an apparent climate protest
So literally the best news story. I'm so
Covered and got a got creamed with cream. Yeah, he became smeared by cream
old lady smears cream on Mona Lisa.
We were busy.
We were so busy we could have stopped this fucking prankster.
And we cancelled our show at the LRV.
Yeah we were supposed to do our show at the LRV.
The LRV.
Yo I LRV the Mona Lisa.
The painting reportedly unharmed.
Okay that's bullshit.
Yeah it was on a protective layer over it I guess.
That's fucking bullshit.
They have a cream blocker.
Yeah.
That's probably one of the main things that they install.
I think that's probably why he chose cream because that might be the one thing that they
don't have a blocker on the money. Yeah, clearly they did. Maybe he thought they
didn't. You know, it's like who the fuck would put smear cream. I mean, if it's a
climate protest, I might try to light it on fire. Yeah, cream. That's cut. That's
from a cow. Cows produce a lot of methane. Methane. This guy's an asshole. Yeah,
cream is supporting the cream industry. Sporting the cream industry is one of
the most harmful industries. It is really fucked up. Yeah. Have you guys ever read
that that Upton Sinclair book about the cream industry and how evil it is? Yeah,
sounds terrible. I read the downton
downton. Okay, yeah downton lair good lair yeah downton good lair video. I
watched his essay. The implications are terrifying. Epic sauce. The
implications are terrifying, I have to say. Was he I mean the thing about one of
the evilest parts of the cream industry is that I would say that I mean this is
in the book. Roughly 75% of the cream output in the world is being smeared on
priceless paintings. That's going to be an absolute bullshit of a stat. It's actually
a completely true stat. I'm going to fact check it. I mean you could go ahead but he's probably
one of the greatest writers and fact check writers. You know honestly I don't know how
to fact check stuff and I don't know how people do it so I'm just going to have to believe
him. What was he Upton Sinclair that called him a muck raker? Yeah. The hell is that?
That's basically it's the opposite of a cream maker. He fights the cream. If you spell cream
backwards and upside down. It says yeah, yeah, it's a little bit like a little
bit. Yeah, a little bit. Yeah, but basically it's like kind of like what's
like in and Yang cream and muck. So he's like breaking up muck to fight is the
only way you can clean cream off a painting. If it doesn't have a cream
blocker is to add muck to it and it goes neutral acres. Yeah, I hate cream
rakers. I'm fucking sick cream rakers destroying our beautiful pain cream
rakers dressing up like old ladies and smearing if a cream raker came in and
tried to get that I would shoot him on
site. We try to put that on the breath
of the wild painting something that I'm
just realizing now that would something
I'm realizing now is Upton Sinclair is a
muckraker right he's digging up muck to
smear industries. Wow yep it's almost
like kind of even good and evil are the
same where even the muckrakers are
smearing the cream. What's he doing it
for money? Monet Lisa at the Monet Lisa
least leaks of Mona Monet you could you could at least give some Monet to the
cream man yeah exactly you that's the least that you could do Monet yeah it's
really telling I mean that people talk about there's a lot of talk about milk
men nobody ever talks about the cream man trip the cream man well that's
because they have half as well the milk man is enough to bring business true
yeah man dropped out needs all that no need six bottles of fucking cream the
the milk man dropped off some cream in in my grandma and that's what my uncle
looks like the milk man.
What is that true? I don't know you milk man fucked your grandpa that was that
happened in my family, too, but the milk man dropped a bunch of muck
to my grandma and she she died.
Yeah, she filled her milk with muck.
Yep.
Yeah, and she threw up pretty bad.
Yeah, she threw up a bunch of muck.
Yeah, she's skinny as a stick figure and in a grave now.
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, she's bones.
That's awful.
Bones, dirt, and some muck in the stomach area.
I've been playing a lot of--
That stuff does not go away over time.
I've been playing a lot of awesome iPhone games.
Yeah.
Still.
You have been, yeah.
You download it, it would tell people what you've been doing.
So, while we were driving in the car, I would download any game that showed up on an ad.
- Uh-huh.
- And I ended up using, I have 50 gigabytes of data
for my mobile plan.
- Ooh.
- And I used all 50 gigabytes.
(laughing)
- That's too much.
- On tour, downloading games like Fat Man Run.
- Games that also are the same game, just reskinned.
Where instead of a guy, you're a hot dog.
- There's, what's the one, oh, Sword Maker.
(laughing)
- Yep.
What was the I downloaded I downloaded one I think it was called like 3d avatar
judge and that one was cool and yeah the first case that I got it was like you
can play you can do this case for gems and as a guy named George flowed and it
was a white guy I took a screenshot of it because I was like damn that is fucking
nuts that they made him white.
That's not a, that's not, you think that's the worst part?
A little bit.
No, except they messed his name up.
They made him white, but then they made the cop black in the story.
Okay, so it was kind of a reimagining.
Yeah, it was a reimagining for gems.
It was like a Guillermo del Toro style, like kind of like, like fairy tale version.
Yeah, retelling.
Yeah.
And then I think the other one was someone named, like the first one I got, but I couldn't
do it because we were driving through Amarillo and there's like no service
there but it was like OJ Simpson. Oh yeah. But it was spelled wrong. I feel like
they're probably they are they so that that's it's not like randomly generated
they like do that they must do that on purpose. Yeah those are the stories.
Yeah. Yeah. I think those are the stories that you play for gems but that's the
thing the thing about that though they made both of those guys white. Yeah. To
avoid whitewashing history much. You're pretty much obsessed with race right now.
Yeah, it is. I mean he's been getting really into thinking about race all the time. He has yeah, and just he walks into a room and he just
Says how many of every race there are in the room. It's a counting exercise. Yep. He's also working on math
I'm working on counting. Yeah, I'm learning how what was your guys's favorite stop on the entire tour and Canyon or just most of Arizona?
It has to be a little place we did. Yeah
I forgot about Myrtle Beach. It was so
actually Myrtle Beach didn't feel like part of the tour. It felt like heaven.
It was a vacation from the tour is if anybody's listening and they have like a
honeymoon coming up or what else do people do shit for wedding or you're
traveling if you wait after if you're celebrating you burning a world running
away if you're running away if you're a child oh yeah we have a lot of young
listeners if you're planning on running away from home uh-huh go to Myrtle Beach
or the forest near your house huh the or the forest near your house yeah yeah
little. If you basically head from I think almost anywhere, if you head north,
you'll hit Myrtle Beach. Yeah, eventually. Or just go into the forest and lie down.
We went to the... Where did we go? We went go-kart racing. We went go-karting. We
went to the arcade. We went dinosaur mini golf. Dinosaur mini golf. Worst mini
golf course I ever played. Not fun. I hate mini golf. We went to the pool. We
went to the hot tub. We went to the lazy river. I went in the lazy river at night
and it was too cold.
- Mm-hmm. - It was too cold.
- I sure my penis shrank.
I got in the lazy river and my penis shrank.
- Don't you want, hey, when you're in the pool,
when you're in the pool,
you want your penis to shrink so nobody can see it.
- Nobody can see his penis in the pool, it's disgusting.
- I don't wanna see. - Exactly.
- My fucking bikini bottom showing my penis
hanging out of the bottom of it.
- Yeah, I don't want my thing,
I don't want my thing trying to bust out
like the Kool-Aid man.
- Yeah. - I honestly,
I'm, as a grown man, - I'd say no.
I would prefer if I could wear a shirt in the pool and it was just from normal.
Yeah, I would rather wear a shirt.
Yeah, I don't want to have all I don't want to be completely naked on.
Oh, I mean you don't have to be completely naked.
You get to wear swim.
You're always like a like a like a girlfriend.
I want like a big shirt that a big shirt and no pants.
Yeah, I want to use the jets for something.
I want to I want everyone to see my foes.
Do you guys like I still go put my wiener up against the jet like yeah, me too.
You have to. You have to. You gotta see if it's as good as you remembered it when you
were a kid. Yeah. And you feel so guilty when the jet turns off because you're too close.
Yeah, that shit is fucked up. Oops. It thinks my penis is a leaf. It's so embarrassing.
The public pool I went to as a kid, they made the jet stop going so fast because too many
kids were fucking nutting. Too many kids were going up to the thing. Including me. Tell
tell you what my fucking my aunt's hot tub did not get the memo yeah yeah that
thing yeah honestly that thing had to have been half imagine by the time that
I grew up and stop. I imagine being like a lifeguard at like a summer camp for
like little kids and like you're like you're like you're sitting up on the high
chair and you have to you're looking down at the at the pool from above and
you just see you're seeing the little the kids just cluster around certain
spots like iron filings on a magnet. It's like they're like ants. When they
you see like a caterpillar, you just see everyone yeah and you can't go. You
can't say anything you can't do it. You're a little fucking lose your job
instantly yeah yeah yeah the parents won't they won't understand it as a
lifeguard. You know what's up yeah yeah, the kid you were a kid once you love
the yeah, that's why you became a lifeguard. I pretend I was deep in
thought I heard they I think they put a jet in the seat of the lifeguard chair.
Yeah, I should yeah, that's why I mean that's what the days feel so good. Yeah,
It's on the wall.
Jet pumping water out.
I'm down in the air.
I think we should we should get a for the
backyard. We should get a little kiddie
pool. Yeah, that would be fucking nice. That
would be sweat in there. Oh my God, our
feet. Yes, we can do that thing where
you put a bunch of like minnow leaves.
Oh yeah leaves
you don't want to leave the pool out overnight
and the leaves when you leave
the out in the in the
in the fall.
He fills his leaves.
You just leave it in your backyard.
I was saying you put like we put a bunch of fish in there.
Oh mosquitoes.
And they eat the dead skin off our feet like in Vietnam.
I would actually love to have one of those fish do that to me.
I wouldn't like that.
I don't like.
I would put my thing in there.
I don't really like getting eaten by an animal.
Shave my foreskin off.
You're not getting eaten though.
I mean it's the same as a dog licking you.
It's functionally the same.
My dog has a name.
I'm not going to say your dog.
I just meant a dog.
Every dog has a name.
No not all dogs have names.
- The other dogs didn't even pickles,
he had no teeth and he--
- He had no name.
- He tried to bite my hand over and over again.
- Yeah, you let him do that, right?
- No.
- Dogs in India don't have names.
- Yeah, none of them have names there.
- Yeah, they do.
- Some of them. - You may not know them.
- He's a race guy again.
- Oh yeah.
- Well, there's just a lot of stray dogs in India.
- He thinks that Indian people don't have names too.
- How'd you learn that?
- From an Indian guy.
- Okay.
And did he have a name?
- No.
- Oh wow.
- I did learn that there are a lot of evil stray dogs
India from following a bunch of Tom and Jerry mean pages yeah, because they all
post they all every other meme on there is a picture of like a of like a dog
that looks like it's from Bloodborne and it says and it says like final level of
walking home.
They think it's about it's Tom and Jerry versus spike. Yeah, I think that's
what the show it is sometimes some episodes some episodes. Yeah, hey, I
don't want to I don't want to sound like yeah, I don't want to nerd out, but I
have to I mean what when I hear some Tom and Jerry Miss info being spread. I
think that's not going to do you still have
yet i have to do you still have a
i thought you knew exactly what you're talking about still have do you have
i have to still have the proper yet to my house okay i don't have anything to
clip it onto on these pants
into you do you know you literally i bought you a scooby-doo popper you didn't
touch it once the entire trip so you do not have a guy who has a lot of that
drama and i think there is no drama until you know explain let me explain the
situation
I bought a Tom and Jerry popper at a gas station in Myrtle Beach.
What?
Nobody knows what a popper is.
I don't know what it's called.
A popper popper.
Okay.
Move on.
I bought one of those.
I showed Cameron and then he immediately took it out of my hands.
You held it up to me.
I held it up to you to show you.
You held it out to me.
To show you and then you took it and then I just decided it was yours after that.
There's no way I was getting that.
you went scary Bilbo and you attacked me for it.
No, I took it because I thought you were giving it to me because I thought you
knew how much I love Tom and Jerry and I realized and then when you brought it up
later I realized my mistake and I bought you a Scooby-Doo popper and you
basically threw it away.
It's not thrown away.
Where is it?
It was attached to my bag that got lost.
It was in my bag that got lost.
Oh the camera bag?
I lost my, I left my camera bag at a hotel in San Francisco.
But then you got that bag back didn't you?
So where is it?
house. Oh, I'm so grateful. I'm letting my try to make it right. I'll even I even
offered to give him the Tom and Jerry thing back and he's he wouldn't take it
back. So he's trying to make me out to be the bad guy here, but it's good. I
don't understand. He's the bad guy at all. I don't think I made an honest
mistake. I made an honest mistake fueled by my love of cartoon cat and mouse. I
will say I was there when you gave when you handed it over. It really seemed
like you got it for Cameron. I'll still give it back to you if you want it back.
Nope, I got a Scooby-Doo one now.
You're much more of a Scooby-Doo-er than you are a Tom Jerryman.
Scooby-Doo-er.
Yeah.
I guess that's true.
Yeah, what would yours be?
We have to get you one.
Probably something...
Royce de Five Knives.
Yeah, bad meets evil, Popper.
I'll take that, dude.
Those things, they had like a hundred of those at every gas station.
I've never seen them in a store ever before.
It was weird.
It was like, see, I saw the first one at Myrtle Beach, the first one I've ever seen, I bought
it, and then they just kept...
Every single gas station had them.
Yeah, it was like I fucking installed some texture into the world.
I tuned out.
Are you talking about race again?
No, I'm talking about poppers.
I tried to.
I heard the first one I've ever seen.
I was so confused and curious about those things popping up, hey, I couldn't help it,
but that I did something crazy and I asked the person at one of the gas stations, "When
did you guys start stocking these?"
I remember that, yeah.
Because I wanted to know and he was like, "I don't know, like a long time ago."
- That was at Staples.
- Was it at Staples?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Yes, I remember. - I go to Staples,
which is an even crazier one.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause it was weird they were there.
- I was just so curious, I feel like I've never seen them
before this trip. - It's a brand new toy, dude.
- Which Staples was it?
- It was the Staples in LA.
- No, it was in Texas.
- Oh, it was in Texas. - Texas, yeah.
- Okay.
- Texas, great state.
- Great state.
- One of the best states. - Big, big, big state.
- Big state. - Texas, one of the best states.
- One of the better states that I've been to.
- Texas, Richmond.
Richmond is my favorite state.
Yep, Atlanta and Richmond.
Okay, this guy's seriously a geography idiot.
(laughing)
Those are great cities and states.
I'm gonna put you on a US Geography crash course.
Okay.
Yep.
We should send him to the Geography Bee,
the eighth grade Geography Bee.
Love Atlanta.
They have a Geography Bee?
They did in eighth grade.
I remember-- That shit's easy.
I loved everything but basically DC and San Francisco.
I remember they gave us, it was a thing where--
Scary cities. We were class in eighth grade
and they gave us a sheet of paper
we had to fill out answers and if anyone got them all right they like were like
they were entered to be a contestant in the geography beers that shit has to
something like that something I mean all that shit's gotta be gotta be yeah I
think like two years after that you're at Langley and they're like quick what is
the capital what is yeah what is an archipelago yeah that's one of the
questions I remember man and I got that one wrong
yep archipelago it's where all I would I would hate to work for the CIA I would
actually like to and if they'd like to reach out that have to live in fucking
DC you know have anywhere you get to live in Thailand and do your whole thing
werewolf attack people yeah okay and you get that you have to learn I got scared
of the Lincoln Memorial you learn how to do it he thought it was gonna come alive
I thought it was gonna come along as that is evil there's an evil lurking
behind it same with San Francisco here's got attacked by a bunch of ducks
that was pretty funny ducks Pierce was walking on the street he saw a bunch of
the ducks on the street and they couldn't get on the curb or they thought they
thought there was no evidence, picking up all the ducklings and the mother bid
his arm. Yeah, I got a good clip. It was very funny because yeah, before that
like like cars stopped and like a guy was stopping traffic to let the ducks and
ducklings cross the street and everyone was like clapping for him and then
pierce walks over like oh, it looks like they can't get up on the curb and pick
them up and just everyone's completely silent yeah, and then he got attacked and
person was like oh yeah that's no claps for yeah no class for Pierce at all
because he doesn't like he was wearing like he's wearing like a fucking in
bright like a bedazzled CIA hat yeah yeah no ducklings on the street being
like oh I don't know it's cool dude yeah I started chucking them yeah see you got
a you got a you got to put a Banksy on that with Washington Monument yeah that
shit's boring as fuck. You gotta bring Spider-Man back to that like in the movie. Remember when
Spider-Man was there in the movie? I thought we were gonna see Spider-Man fighting the Vulture
there. You really honestly thought that? I 100% thought he was gonna be there. Your brain
is childish man. I seriously thought, I mean it's like, I thought maybe it would be like
in like you know Disneyland where you go and Kylo Ren comes out every once in a while.
I thought maybe Spider-Man and the Vulture would come out of the Washington Monument.
They should have a George Washington stand there and be like, "Looks like my penis."
Why would he say that? It doesn't look like his penis first of all. He didn't have a right
of all. Yeah. He did. If anything, if it was abnormal at all, it was wooden. He had a perfect
wooden penis that he stole from a slave. Yep. That is fucked. I didn't even know that. A
lot of people forget. And he also grew weed. Criminal. What? Huge criminal. If I was George
Washington, instead of building dentures out of slave teeth, like a freak, like a freaking
criminal, I would build dentures out of dog teeth. That would have been awesome. That would
look so cool. That would look cool as fuck. He would have been the king. But only the big
dog. I wouldn't do one dog. I would take the canines from like a hundred different dogs.
A hundred teeth by the way. That's basically a shark. You're making yourself into a dog
shark. No. Okay, yeah, that sounds cool. I would do chicklets. Chicklets? Like Dennis
the Menace. You wouldn't have to. You already look like chicklets. Bitch ass. I would probably
I would do something that if I got
I actually know
wait no, I'm going to look up a picture to show you what I would do.
I think I would do
food. Food? Yeah.
You could eat them whenever. Yeah, exactly.
I'd do pickles and
onions. Onions.
Where my teeth should be.
Because onions wrap around like braces anyway.
Yeah, I think I would do
a sunfish beak
or a turtle beak.
I would do whale teeth. You know, they have those
like bristles. This is the Sunfish teeth. I would have these. I've seen that before. Just
two really big, just two, like one buck tooth on the top, one buck tooth on the bottom.
I think I might get an angler installed on the top of my head. That would be fucking
sick. That would be realistic right now. Yeah, what are you, is it going to, because I mean,
you're not trying to attract fish, so what are you putting on the end of the angler?
Probably something for me. You've got hair on the sides. I'm going to try and lure myself.
Caleb yeah, I'll like use it to motivate myself on the end. I don't know if
everyone's seen it. Maybe poop if it was opposite day, but unfortunately it's not
so I'll probably do food. It's not so it's not opposite day. It's not it's so
you're doing it's not opposite day and you're putting food. It's not boogers day.
It's a boogers day. It's boogers wait it's boogers day. It's boogers day. Is it
actually a boogers day? Can you survive just eating your own boogers? You need
dust to get boogers. At first I was like. So what if you're in a really dusty room.
first one you as I thought I thought you might like can you can you eat them and
survive like well,
my mom told me that they
still believe it yeah, no they'll kill you what if you eat them yeah, it's just
shit from your body right yeah, it's just for us collecting
but why is it green and you can use and dust and yeah, it's again yeah, bugs
dead skin and smog and whatever particle doesn't come out of your butt goes on
there really or no, you know what it is, it's whatever poop you smell the
particles from the smell. When we turned in the car, they did the inspection. I
was really, really happy. They found no boogers. They didn't find all the
boogers. I hidden there. I probably had honestly for the four hundred boogers
and a rental car
pretty high. Did I probably put four hundred to five hundred bars in the
front seat of that car? I mean I would I would just throw them out the window,
but I knew they were. I would never do that's embarrassing dude. I'm trying to
I'm trying to sneakily put them. Yeah, wipe them under the seat on the floor.
I put them on the back of my leg and whenever we get out I'd scrape them off the parking
break. I think I got hemorrhoids from the tour, speaking of. You got hemorrhoids? I think
so from sitting down so long. What? If you sit down for long periods of time you can
get hemorrhoids. We weren't sitting all that much more than you probably do in your daily
life. No, that's not true. Four or five hours a day? Yeah. Sitting longer in the car than
I ever have sat down.
What?
I've been longer in the car than I ever have sat down.
Is that on period?
It's on period.
Speaking of period, are your hemorrhoids bleeding constantly?
No, I just wiped one time and I saw blood.
Did you eat blood for dinner?
I did eat a steak at a Cracker Barrel at an Outback Steakhouse.
Oh, I forgot about that steak.
Oh man, that steak.
You know, I never got sick.
You had a blue steak.
It wasn't blue, it was pink. It was completely pink and red and raw.
It was, yeah, it was raw. That's what it's called.
A blue steak, listen, I'm not eating no blue steak, man.
Yeah, blue, what is this, Dr. Seuss?
I'll eat green eggs and ham, though. What's up?
That's what it's called when it's like blue rare.
The fuck are you even fucking talking about? You're not making, you're saying the wrong
color.
Yeah, green egg is actually when it's scrambled.
That's right.
That's actually what it means.
Yeah.
For an egg to be scrambled.
Yeah, we went to Outback.
I'd like to take you out back.
Fuck you in full view of the neighbors.
Yep.
Amarillo was cool because every street.
Oh, shout out Young Javonchi.
Oh, true.
Dude, shout out my guy.
Shout out Young Javonchi.
We said we would.
Our waiter, we told him we'd shout him out.
Our waiter out back, very kind young man.
He's a rapper.
Young Javonchi.
Young Javonchi's got two songs.
He goes crazy.
Continues.
Yeah.
It was cool because every single street or every single block, it was like steakhouse,
Steakhouse, steakhouse, steakhouse.
- Yep.
- I've never seen that many steakhouses in my life.
- Yeah, it was swaggy.
- We just got off at a, it was just a truck stop.
- Oh, is that why?
- Yeah, it's all just restaurants.
- Ah.
I thought that that's how it was.
- You thought that was like the steak district?
- Yep.
(laughing)
- I think there's a lot of beef production in Texas,
so I did think that.
- So you thought that all the chain steakhouses
need to be next to the beef production capital?
- Yep.
- All right.
- We did drive by some--
- I mean, the steak was better in Texas.
those cows that those those were those are those like slaughterhouses yeah yeah
those are crazy yeah it is crazy to see that where do we go we went to love it's
insane to look at like 10,000 living things and be like you will all be dead
in like two days yeah pretty guys are done yeah haha fuck you oh we went to
the rashes to them we're mooning them yeah we we saw those cows then we went
to the knife guys we went to the Texas yeah it was in a mall and that's a ball
- Well, we went there as soon as it opened.
- Yep.
- The second we were literally waiting outside the doors,
and a security guard opened the doors and we ran in.
- Yeah.
- To go to the knife guys.
- We went into the knife guys
and I bought a pocket knife that says Freemasons.
- Yeah.
- And Cameron--
- I bought a knife that says Operation Desert Storm.
- Yeah.
- That's what it was.
That thing is sick.
- It's pretty cool.
- And I bought two bags of Skittles.
- No, you bought, it wasn't Skittles,
you bought a Freemasons hat and a lollipop.
I remember that.
Oh I did get a lot, they had lollipops and I said, dude the guy was being a hassle.
I was like how much for the Freemasons hat?
He was like 15 bucks.
I was like okay let me get that.
There was a bucket of lollipops.
I was like also the lollipop and he started laughing.
Damn.
It's like dude I'm giving you business.
First of all, second of all I'm fucking hungry.
I have blood sugar issues.
You should be thankful I don't have a knife in my hand.
I mean that guy he can laugh at whatever he wants because he's got a samurai sword right
behind him.
I really was tempted to buy ninja stars but I didn't know if they'd let me get home.
that night helmet so fucking bad. The $1500 night helmet.
The night helmet. And then they had the left corner of that store was all fairy figurines.
Yeah, that was such a sick store. That was so cool.
Anybody around there, you gotta go check it out.
And there was like a guy in there with like pushing his little kids on a stroller.
Yep. That was so cool. Like he was buying them
their Christmas gifts. Yeah.
In May. Their Christmas gifts, yeah.
We need to go back out right now, dude. I'm having like, I know.
We need to go on another tour immediately. I know. I have like a phantom steering wheel
at my hand. I need to be back there. Yeah. I need to be back in the south. Dude, we
should move the, let's just move the whole operation of Texas, man. To Lubbock. Go just
full. Lubbock, we can go to the big city. Yeah, not, fuck Austin, dude. That shit. Yeah.
Lubbock's the next. Lubbock is next up. It's next, dude. Lubbock, Texas. Lubbock, Texas. We love it. We
love Lubbock. Just need some air fresheners in the office and we're good. Yep.
Texas is a, I think, I think that's gonna be the next like big place where
everybody lives. It'll be the next like California or New York. Yeah, yeah, I
think at ten years probably probably Texas probably gonna rival like India and
population. Yeah, probably over a billion people. Yeah, I think that it was
close to the Texas. We saw the Texas Chainsaw House. Yeah, we did now a shitty
restaurant. It's a restaurant on a bed and breakfast like mmm. Also, it wasn't
open. What kind of restaurant isn't open? Yeah, it was only open on like Wednesday.
a terrifying restaurant. It honestly was put there just to scare us. It was very
funny because it's called, they changed the name, it's now called the Grand
Central Cafe. Yeah. And they have a picture of like, they have a giant
picture of Grand Central Station like right at the front and like it's like
that's like the only theme-y thing and then we like went
around I looked in the other window and like they just have a they have a huge
like life-size figure of Leatherface. Yeah. Why would you not call it the
Leatherface Murder Restaurant? Trying to split the difference is insane. Yeah. Like one of
like pretend that it was never a and the only murder house or grand central,
because it had a has a train track that goes next to yeah yeah and it's like but
that's it's way more important that they made yeah the murder movie here right I
know and the only grand central theming was literally just a big a print yeah
picture of grand central station, but yeah it's very funny to to not be able
to decide yeah yeah, so we do yeah. Well, what is it going to make more people
walk in here. What do people like? What do people like? What are people, what are
gonna make people want to come in here? Also, don't make it a, make it a...
Make it an awesome playhouse, not a restaurant. Make it a mosque. Yeah, or an arcade.
That'd be cool. They built a mosque in the Texas Chainsaw House. Yep, and that's okay
with me? You know what I saw? What? A movie? If you look in the background of the
final shot of Texas Chainsaw, what can you see? You can see seven Muslim guys
cheering it on really they're saying yes go the best movie rooftop go leatherface
there's a rooftop in New Jersey from a rooftop in New Jersey you can see it you
need a telescope to see it wow yeah you know the actual story with that is
there's like four Israeli dudes in a van really yeah that's so it's awesome dude
and they were they weren't cheering but I think they were probably just hanging
out. Yeah. Listening to some kind of club music. Some ungodly music. Yeah. Full Zohan'd out
watching 9/11 happen. Yeah. Man, I forgot that You Don't Mess With The Zohan is about
Israel. Yep. It's kind of, I will say it's crazy. It's kind of the whole thing of that
movie. And then the guy from... It's about how awesome the IDF is. Yeah. And the guy
from Transformers, what's his name? John. John Turturro. John Turturro is Palestinian
in the movie and he's he's the villain yeah and he's getting shit kicked in yeah
by old Zil Han mm-hmm dope pretty cool I can't believe we're back to it yeah
crazy it's fucking I want to issue an apology for saying it's not the people in
DC and SF that I don't like it's never one person I don't like the people I
hate the people in both those places I hated I hate every single of our fans I
I hate everything. I hate the fans. Yeah, every last one of them. Okay. Yep
One person in sf, you know who you are
cj
Yep, cj suck my dick man. Cj. I'm gonna i'm gonna go back there
Even though you don't live in san francisco cj, but we're gonna meet up we're gonna meet up in san francisco
And I will make you my food slave. Yeah, you will truly become my one food slave. Yep. I hope you like making uh
I hope you like making PB&J empanadas. I hope that's not too much for you CJ. A peanut butter
jelly sandwich with GF Extra Crunchy. You're probably so weak you can't even... Yo, Extra
Crunchy though. You probably can't even mix in the organic natural stuff, the oil and the peanut
butter when it separates. So I'm gonna get you the crunchy one. That's right. CJ, we're coming back
to San Francisco and we're gonna go and we're gonna attack you. Yep, and if you have a brother who
could be a toilet slave that'd be cool too. And if you have a sister who could be a TV slave then
We might have a whole slave family. Yeah. Yeah. We have top ten nastiest April
Fool's Day jokes today on the top tens on the top ten. This is from Heather. From
Heather? That's all they say Heather. Heather. That's all they say? That's all they say?
That's all they're saying is Heather? I'm very happy. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I just opened this up on my phone too.
I don't know. We've seen her before I swear. Read it out. I think we've talked about this lady
before. I'm very happily married to the creator of this awesome website. I love
love hanging out with my husband traveling horror movies music and my
pets. I'm this is kind of this is a conflict of interest. You shouldn't be
allowed to make make a list. If you're married to the web, we agree to this is
like honestly fucking disgusting, especially to get like she gets her.
This is the second time we've had one of her lists on our show.
What was the other one? We did I can't remember is a very long to my years ago.
At this I can't remember her at all number one nastiest April Fool's day
is I'm gay.
- Damn!
- Damn.
- No, I'm not saying I'm gay.
- What?
I'm saying, I'm reading the list.
- You're saying you're gay.
- No, number one is saying, in quotes,
I'm gay.
- Caleb's gay?
- Here's a comment.
Someone said this in the lunchroom at school
and everybody believed it.
Then a few days later he said he wasn't,
but no one believed him
because he done told everybody he was gay.
(laughing)
I mean, it would freak out you parents, really.
- Yeah.
- Beck, you need to get some better parents, buddy.
- When I told my parents that Caleb was gay,
they said, "What? What?"
- "LOL, probably the funniest.
"It's more funny when a guy says that."
That is true, it's funnier when a girl says it,
it's just hot.
(snorts)
It's just cool.
- When a girl says it, it's just, I have to leave.
- Really?
- When they say it, yeah.
- Oh.
- Oh, when a girl says it?
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- You guys think I have to leave right now?
April Fool's Day prank. That's a good prank.
Guys, I have to leave.
It's genius.
It was a complete accident, but I could tell by the way you reacted that I accidentally pranked you.
I thought you just got a crazy notification or something.
I have to leave.
I can't believe I actually got pranked.
Yeah.
Here's the comment. I'm going to try this next year.
Whoa.
I'm going to try this.
You guys ever do an insane April Fool's joke on someone?
Something next level?
I mean, I've talked about it before, but it wasn't really that, like, it was more on the
viewers of Pornhub.com.
You pranked the viewers?
Did you upload something?
I uploaded something and then four minutes and twenty seconds in.
He cut out the cum shot of him.
Yeah.
Cutting off.
So people didn't even get to see the cum on his face?
Yeah.
It was in high school and I edited four minutes and twenty seconds in.
It's just the Cory in the House theme song and then it cuts back to the video.
That honestly, I'm not kidding, that's the funniest bullshit I've ever heard in my fucking
life.
4 minutes and 20 seconds in?
It was in 2014.
You have to give me.
Are you kidding me bro?
I have to give you props and a word.
No.
Cash props.
That's what I have to give you.
You have to let me.
I'm losing my fucking mind.
I'm falling out bro.
You have to.
Nah.
Can you please.
Nah bro I'm sliding out of my chair.
Can you please give me the benefit of the doubt.
Bro that shit was insane dude.
Oh my god.
I was 16.
Oh no.
I was 16 when I did that.
No.
It's too good.
sides. I don't want to even tell you where my sides are right now. Well, I
told you guys about it before that my cousin's sides are over 9000. My
cousin's getting me tried to show me my cousin's side and tried to show me
smoke weed every day. Him that I did that. You should have put that in
there. Yeah, I was doing in 2014. What? I don't remember dude, but it wasn't
that fucking funny. Yeah, nowhere near that shit. Whatever it was. Yeah, I
I was like I was you my friend or a meme Lord shake my hand,
shake it dude. Yes, he agrees he's a me more washing this hand again.
Yeah, oh pack can you can you sign my my forehead and also my chin in impact
font.
I'm going to find your reddit account where you talk about magic, the
gathering you can find it easily. I had you do you deleted it all, but I had
your old reddit posts you're like a hip-hop head so don't you dare don't you
don't even know what you're talking about there must be a cool hip-hop scholar who
maybe used to has the same name as me probably scholar very knowledgeable who
you said no a lot about the dirty south the dirty sound mix 2012 yes sir I think
so I'm sorry I wasn't a fucking internet comedian dude I'm sorry I wasn't trying
to be I don't even who did you like when you were in 2014 who's your idol my idol
yeah cuz mine was Nas yeah yep mine was uh Shrek yep I can tell no way he still
he's no got it no way he's still got I still got it yeah wait wait check this
out wait hold on check out my shirt is galaxy print with the Shrek no show you
are fucking on one right guess what he's wearing guess what he's wearing what's
to
lenticular lenticular there it is
he says exactly what you mean. It's a really good word. It's a good word
because because it's very useful. Yep, I was a yeah. I don't think I was a I
mean, I think I think we're I don't know you're trying to defend. I think
that your old you know yeah, I think that we should. I think we should get
like a printer that can make that kind of thing like a lenticular picture
bookmark or something like I don't know how those are made, but I think that's
the next frontier. Yeah, let's take your stuff. We're just making bookmarks and
stuff. I would say the next frontier. You don't really see those anymore. Like
that was they were on the cover of books and movies and bookmarks. That's because
you don't nobody no kid wants to look at that anymore. It's because they lost
technology. But probably kids nowadays don't even know that that existed. And if
we bring it back, we're probably gonna make a fucking killing. I mean, it's like
Dude, if Toys R Us started stocking hoops and sticks,
like the Victorian times.
- Toys R Us is gone, yeah.
- Yeah, well if they came back,
then probably they would sell a bunch of toys.
- Remember when Toys R Us went out of business
and then there was a GoFundMe?
- Kids nowadays probably don't even know about Toys R Us.
That's what I'm saying, you bring it back.
- Toys R Us went out of business,
then there was a GoFundMe where they were like,
bring Toys R Us back.
- They should bring it back.
people tried to buy toys are us out of bankruptcy. I probably got to go to
toys or us, maybe three times in my life. Me too. I got that was that's a
story. That's a store. Any parent that knows what's good for them will never
set foot in that store. That's the first like you like target is bad enough
right yeah. I only went there. I think one time and I stole some Pokemon cards
and got caught really. I was my mom got me a Playmobil treasure chest. I
shot. I remember after she was like you can't tell you your dad. I bought that
I bet a treasure chest is expensive. Yeah, a lot of treasure no matter what
fucking material it is. Yeah, yeah number two someone died who
you got dude. He got you got got what just saying hey guys someone died
who oh my God worked again. No, but seriously number two is someone
duray top ten says this should be number one one time on Super Mario
Logan Bowser jr. Pranked chef PP by telling him that his mom died. He
should have been grouted forever for doing something so harsh. Thanks as
As this list is the nastiest April Fool's Day jokes, this one has to be voted upon by me.
Not a joking matter, says Cheesy Nachos.
My cousin has done this before.
Moose4life19.
If my cousin did that, I'd beat the crap out of him.
That would make someone cry/emotional/suicidal.
Spam peeper approved.
Spam peeper?
Who the fuck is Spam peeper?
Who's Spam peeper?
I don't know, but he approved number two.
Oh, oh, Sam Pepper.
Remember him?
video it was like a video where it's like pranking my friend to tell him that I
died and it was a video of him like like I think he put like a bag over his head
and then his friend that video was fucked up I wasn't a fucking I in 2014 I wasn't
a legend I didn't watch this kind of stuff okay I was just I was a damn
normie and I would just watch fucking Breaking Bad like a normie dude. I wasn't doing awesome
legendary shit like that. I didn't even know who H3H3 was. He's judging me and I like it.
I should be judged. Number three, I'm pregnant. You're what? I'm pregnant. Are you actually
pregnant? Are you expecting? Yes, I'm pregnant. Holy fucking shit. Holy fucking balls. I'm
pregnant with holy shit holy okay crap tits I think this pregnancy might be
amazeballs if I actually put my mind to it and stop smoking I said this to my
mom she ended up going through my phone I regret nothing huh I told my mom I was
pregnant and I found out that day I was I was like no way I tried it too and I
I am an eleven year old girl. I could never pull that off. I'm only eleven
it's not about it's that it's just it would be too much logistics too much
planning. I try to have the executive function. I tried it. My friend believed
me and I'm an eleven year old boy.
The hell do it.
I if do you think if you like swallow something can it show up on an
ultrasound? No, yes, yeah, so if I
like if I like a volleyball and I wrote on it like April fools that I don't
think that they would see the text on it. Okay, what if it was like okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, what if it's like okay, a dinner plate and the
letters April fools are like cut out of it. I saw there lost me at dinner. I'm
too hungry now. Okay, well I'd be I would said eat before the way before that,
so you should have been least should have lost that
because to eat is more delicious dinner eat is any meal eat is any meal or snack
that's true or anything that you could eat snack this. I can't eat that you
could eat this. That's what eat could also be a piss. Who's dinner is just
going to be a normal food dinner could be and you could prank somebody that
by but anyway, then they could ultrasound and see
it would look like I
that would be a speech bubble. You should do maybe like a bunch of shit
That wouldn't show up very well.
Eat so much shit that you look pregnant.
Because there's already a bunch of shit in there, so it would be hard for it to have a contrast.
What are you doing?
I took a b-reel.
What's a b-reel?
You don't have a b-reel?
I took a b-reel.
Bro, how many times do I have to tell you, man?
I'm not with it like you.
Yeah?
Yeah, dude.
I'm not fucking up with all the different apps and shit.
You take one photo.
I don't even know what pingas means.
Pingas?
Yeah, what the hell is that?
Well, then you should have seen it at the Chicago show.
Who the fuck is Mama Luigi, man? I don't know this shit, dude.
I knew that shit.
Which yo legendary ass.
It's making the cable go crazy.
Number four, I'm moving away. I used to do this a lot when I was a kid.
Really?
Yeah.
You ever try to run away as a kid?
Were you like attention starved?
Uh, probably, yeah.
That's like the equivalent of like, I haven't eaten anything all day.
Yeah.
But I was six. I don't think a lot of six year olds say I haven't eaten anything all day.
I know I'm sorry. I was trying to be a role. Yeah. Well, I know that's what I mean. That's like
That's probably the same time. That's the same type of behavior that I actually did this on April Fool's maybe two week two years in a
row
And I would just I would just pick somebody and tell them that I don't remember what I did for April Fool's
I'm gonna prank dude. This is rude. What if I told you guys I was moving away. I'll be pretty sad. What?
Guys, I'm not I just was I was just saying like I was just saying I'm moving away. I'm not moving. No Pat
I'm not moving away man. I'm staying right here. He wants you to move away. He knows
it's a prank and that's why he said. He's distracted. Look at him. He's distracted by
a shadow on the floor. I got distracted because I just remembered what's in this
bag. What's in it? Wait, what's in that bag? What? I don't think we can say it.
What's in the bag? Oh, I just remembered what's in that bag. I don't know what's
in that bag. I don't think so. We'll tell you later. Yeah. I think it might
fucking blow your mind and you might enter a new dimension.
Wait, what?
When did you guys get a bag that I can't know about?
You don't remember what's in this?
I'm just going to hold the bag.
I think you should.
What's in there?
Was I here when the bag was arrived?
I think so.
I think you were here when I ordered this bag.
When you ordered the bag.
Can I see a part of it?
Oh shit.
Yep.
No way.
I completely forgot about this bag. This bag is swag. One day that's going to pay
off.
Yeah, that's going to pay off.
And it's going to sit right there.
You guys are all going to look back.
And you at home, you have to guess what's in the bag.
You guys are all going to look back in like a few months or a year or
whatever, and you go, oh my God, that's what they were talking about.
Exactly.
In the bag. Five hundred of something.
They ordered five hundred of something that they didn't use.
That was supposed to be used on the tour.
MinecraftCrazy530 says, "I need to do this to my enemy."
It's like, your enemy would be happy about that, you asshole.
- Yeah.
- Well, maybe it's like a Batman joke or situation.
- I relate hard as fuck to their username, though.
- Yeah.
- I just did this--
- Is it MinecraftCrazy530?
- Yeah, 530.
- Yo, 530, you know I'm cracking a beer open.
- 530, you get home from work, exactly 530,
hop on the beer. - Exactly 530.
- Hop on the computer.
- Hop on the beer, yeah.
Yeah, I shove that beer up my butt.
I jump on that like like Zangie from Street Fighter. You jump on your
spinner. Yeah, I spin around and I want jumps his butt on it. It jump my
but it open it around if it's a twist off and you spin around that
actually yeah kind of sick if it's not a twist off you just have to pull
number six. I'm dying. No, you're not actually dying. Are you okay? I'll
tell you this much. Are you okay? I remember you okay. I remember this
I put red pen ink all over my face on a scissor and on hand and leg and it looked like I stabbed my leg
I watch out pretending to trud down the hallway everyone
Trud down the hallway everyone was screaming and running around in Curtis
They were freaking out then I stood up and everyone gasped and I said it's red pink April fools
But everyone was traumatized for the rest of the day damn that is fucked up. I get you skipped one, dude
I did something similar.
You skipped number five.
Oh shit, I did.
We have to go back to number six.
But wait, what did you do that was similar?
It was my friend Declan's end of the year party
in the
seventh grade.
Yeah.
And I
took a marker
and I
convinced my friend's mom
that this kid Mike
pinched me in the nose and I had like red ink all over and I was just like
nothing nothing happened. We used to do all sorts of fucking Harold and Maude
shit with my parents. We would like do the pretend you're dead and cover
yourself and catch up in your room thing yeah and then call for you. We would call
we'd be like mom or dad and then they would get to our room and we'd be
pretending to be dead. It's like well how could you die so fast? Yeah how could you?
and they never fell for it even a single time.
- Yeah. - Yeah, that makes sense.
- But literally I just took a marker
and just drew on my upper lip.
- Nice. - And I was like,
"I'm fucking bleeding!"
- Yeah.
Number five is someone wants to go out with you.
Here's a comment, that'd be rude.
- LMAO, I almost got slapped when I told my cousin this.
- Look at my face.
Who wants to go out with me?
- Your cousin?
- My cousin?
- Yep.
- I have to call him. - Score!
- Here's one.
- I have to call him right now.
- Just had this done like five minutes ago on messages.
my enemy did it to me. I'm so upset. Damn. If someone this guy's getting that, if
someone tells me this joke, I'm going to smash them into oblivion. Oh, you want to
go out me? I'm going to smash you. This one, the one where they just had it done
five minutes ago. Do you think it's a coincidence where they like pulled up
this list and they're like, oh, like somebody just did this or do you think
that that that happened to them and they opened up the top tens and searched
prank? Someone wants to go out with you so they could comment on this. Someone
says I am going to walk under a truck. Why? That's all I say. That's just cruel,
especially when after you go and talk to the person. It is so embarrassing, not
that it's ever happened to me or anything. Fidget, fidget. Number nine, remove the frog.
Fidget, fidget. A frog write that? Yeah, what a frog write that? Fidget, fidget.
You know how they be saying that? Wait, I'm remembering now, they say
they say ribbit, ribbit. Yeah, wait Pat, why are you calling us a
fidget. Oh my God. Oh my God. Look at him. Just look at him. Just look at him.
It's all you can do.
That's a good phase. You'd be a great female librarian. Yeah. With your
glasses like that, like down on your nose. Yeah, that would be good. I'm
trying to look like when Ernest dresses up like a grandma.
special is honestly fire that looks like it yeah
well back to i'm dying here's a comment
i mean come on i'm gay
that's what i think one of the people but saying i'm dying people like a you
this is definitely the cruelest
i'm gay even i think this
i think it even i think it's cruel
you say you're dying
number eight were breaking up
the shows over
never say this joke to your love interest
Don't do it my friend's cousin did this and her boyfriend committed suicide. It's not funny damn damn
What he pranked her harder than she pranked him. Yeah, that's a better prank. Yeah
Kill yourself. Yeah, that's a good prank in in what world is that something you guys are okay with joking about?
You just got pranked yeah, oh my god. I actually think that's fucking horrible. It's fucking atrocious to kill yourself
it's selfish disgrace yeah to God exactly it's not okay to joke you're taking
you're actually it's a it's a it's a permanent solution to a temporary
problem yep and also that life that you just took could have gone to an aborted
child yep yeah instead you used it to fucking what you use it to you use this
to fight yourself all over the you could have cured cancer if you weren't so
lazy abortion and all the time blown it up with you inside but instead you
you fucking wasted your you just put your dad's bullet in your head right you
could have just down a bullet yeah he's gonna get gored by a wild boar yep you
could have jumped out of a plane on to an antifa rally yeah but instead you didn't
you decided to kill yourself said you took cyanide yep that's right
yeah you could have flown over Russian talk some damn sense into Vladimir
Putin I do feel bad for people who tried to kill themselves before we had like
guns and stuff. Why? Because it must just been hard. Probably really easy. I don't think
anyone tried to kill themselves until they invented depression with corn syrup. True.
When NAFTA was created. That's a good point. Yeah, I think it also you could I think there's
way more ways to you could just walk into an animal. Let's be real, how many ways to
die are there? You could walk to an animal. What? There's one thousand ways to die. But
what if the animal what if it's a straight straight Yogi Bear situation? Then that gives
you a reason to live. Best friend situation. Win win. Yeah. It's a win win dude. Either
raised by wolves or here's the thing about a thousand ways to die
crave crave to be raised yeah there's a thing about a thousand ways to die
there's a thousand ways to die yeah but really there's only four subsections of
how to die elaborate please there's like you know impaled mm-hmm poisoned yep
Drowned.
Yep.
Shot.
Okay, so what about when you fall?
Fall.
You're getting impaled by your own bones.
What about my grandpa dying in his sleep?
Poison.
Body poison.
What about cancer?
Is that poison?
Cancer is definitely poison.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
What about getting sucked into a propeller?
Getting sucked into a propeller.
What about--
I think that's a poison.
What about struck by lightning?
Struck by lightning is a tail because you're--
No, electricity poison.
No, that's shot.
Yeah, that's shot.
That's shot.
shot into a propeller what if like a wizard makes you instantly vanish yeah
what if you shooting that's a shooting because he shoots his wand what if he
doesn't use this one he's really got us honestly well if he doesn't use his one
he probably uses finger or a thought we have shoot at him okay but yeah you're
getting shot with a ray of yeah wait so it was it's impale isn't being shot all
- Impaled?
- Impaled is the same as shot.
- Those are both shot.
- No, no, 'cause you don't shoot with a knife,
unless it's a ballistic knife.
- What if you load a gun with a knife?
- That's still an impale.
- I think instead of impale, it's hit.
- Yeah, what if you get hit really hard in the head?
- I think, yeah.
- 'Cause then that covers falling, too.
- But a hit, yeah, a hit could also be an impalement.
- I think an impalement is a hit.
- Okay, so it's hit, shot, poisoned, drowned.
- Drown is poison though, drown is water poison.
- You are getting poisoned by water.
- We're not suffocating.
- The last one is peaceful death.
- Peaceful.
- Fourth is peaceful.
- Yeah.
- Suffocating is poison too.
- 'Cause you're being poisoned by it.
- 'Cause it's air poison.
- No, no, the fourth is break.
(laughing)
- Break?
What does that mean?
- That means you break.
- Like you broke in half?
- Yeah, you broke in half or your neck broke.
- Okay, fair enough.
What about if you get torn apart by,
so if you get torn apart by chains like this set of bites,
that's a break.
- Yeah, that's break, 'cause that's not anything else.
He's smart.
- Damn.
- What about being hanged?
- Being hanged, that's a break.
- Break your neck.
- Break your neck, unless you're suffocated,
then that's a poison,
'cause you're getting poisoned by air.
- What about being eaten?
- Yeah, eaten. - Swallowed whole.
- Eaten is a break.
- No, you're swallowed whole.
- No, 'cause think about it.
Think about it. - You're digested.
- Think about it. - That's poison.
- You get eaten.
Think about eating a flat wing.
The flat of a wing.
- Quicksand.
- Quicksand is a poison. - Quicksand.
- What is that suffocation?
- Oh yeah.
- That's 'cause you have to break the flat of the wing
to get the beat up.
- Heart attack is poison?
- Heart attack is poison by the body.
- Or is your heart hitting you?
- It's a poison.
- I think it's shooting.
- It's a poignant pain.
- Shooting pain in your left arm.
- Your blood is good poison.
- That's why they call it a shooting pain.
- No, it's a poison.
- Your blood doesn't get poisoned.
- Your blood turns into poison with a heart attack.
- That's just not true.
- That's sepsis.
- Okay, then it's a break because your heart broke.
- What if you die for no reason at all?
- If you die for no reason at all.
you what if you cross your eye for no reason what if you make a weird face and
you hold it so long your face gets stuck like that's a break swooped by a
gargoyle hit yeah fell off of the earth that's a hit running just flying through
space forever that's a hit because you've hit the atmosphere frozen frozen
solid frozen solid is a poison frozen liquid frozen liquid is a poison frozen
frozen in an odd manner that's a shot okay
poisoned poison turn turn into a dog get him poison is a poison unless you're
shot by a poison dart turn it into a dog and then your owner dies and you die of
a broken heart that's a break you said it right there yeah I answered it turn to
stone turn to stone is a poison poison okay you grow too big grow too big is a
break because you what what how's that's being this poison you break the rules of
nature yeah run out of ways to die but there's a thousand of these fucking
things printer printer you get printed you get printed that's ink poisoning
okay computer computer is a shot lost in a chocolate river lost in a chocolate
oh yeah glue break Augustus glooped yeah glooped is a break because you're not
breaking
listening if anything. It's a drown. No, think about it, because you're in the tube, the
tube compresses you. It's breaking you. Think about the 3D, the Augustus Gloop was stuck
in a tube. The A Thousand Ways to Die announcer says like, he was stuck in a tube that compressed
his ribs which broke into his heart. Over 3,000 pounds of pressure applied to the boy's
ribs. Yeah. I think right now Augustus Gloop is the funniest thing in the world to me. I
I think in the past few weeks, I literally I the other day, like after we got back
for our sitting at home and I thought about Augustus Gloop and started
laughing at myself. It is so funny. You always mentioned the name being the
name is the it's the funniest thing ever. I think we even talked about the
show, but just them having a board meeting yeah and deciding who's going to
get killed, which way maybe that what do we do with that gloop boy, the gloop
fellow? I don't know. Maybe we turn them into a blueberry. Maybe what what kind
chocolate should we kill agustus gloop with should it be solid chocolate i
don't know i mean i'm not so sure and bill maybe hmm yeah or maybe glue
hold on hold on hold on let's go through so agustus gloop that's a break that's
not a break i don't agree with that that's a break that's not a break i
don't agree with violet beauregard you're the tie breaker for a gloop i
think loop is poison because i think it's drowning i think it's drowning which is
not poison you know what drowning is poison but he gets into the tube i think
you know i know what you drowns from lack of air yet to drown i think it's a
wardrobe within we sent out as a poison
no we're to have drowning drives one of the thing that i was just shoot is it
shoot poison break
yeah okay so dronics poison that was a good idea of what i've heard is a
reasonable is operating as poison
yes i think it's around by the poor guard is a break
broke all now now you know she's a she said that's what's the first thing that
i grow was the first thing that happened
she got turned around a lot of fell off her but i think you're but shoots her
but i don't know
her body bro i think it's more than i think i think that all of them are
poisoned as they are crazy candy
okay what about the ruka salt
okay that's a break if you had to break you know jimmy
mike to you might make a TV fucking idiot
you make t_v_ obviously the only mike t_v_ how did it kill by obviously is
actually a t_v_ you think is a mister o_ t_v_ no it's not my my t_v_ as you know
Mike TV as he got shot with a TV as a microphone was shot with a shrink ray
and shrank but it's probably broke all his bones when he that's also that could
be a break laws of physics situation yeah you know what I think it's for small
this it's - it's two poisons and two breaks all right juice world juice world
just real poison yeah that's pretty hmm cut I think broken heart is that's the
own was poison by a bullet is bright wait do we say his shot is hit by a ball
yeah he's hit by a bullet allegedly uh... all of them are kind of a deal
anybody got a holiday got upper richie valens all pool in her skinner
when his cousin scared poisoned they i think it means they could have one fire
that's a hit you hit the the plane here was a break
they break apart on the ground seeing is yours only yeah you're not good at this
they were created a by that i would be a perfect system and then you couldn't
stand to see it for us yet to destroy it
but i you know i i i think that they all to break it they all could be their hit
by death i think it's only only to is there a hit and wife
yeah yeah there's no two things that kill you those are also the with the
the words that echo in your head
and i think i have a lot of
yes
yet he died in your sleep it's wife you know and if
well you know when you will let you know when you died from wife phil harman
life-and-life self yeah exactly yet yet elliot smith died from wife probably but
it was framed to look like a hit of a knife.
Uh-huh.
The hit of a knife.
Yeah.
That would be a sick fucking name for an album.
The hit of a knife.
And then...
I would say the blade of a knife would be known.
Robert Blake, the hit of a blade.
Robert Blake did a...
The sharpness of a knife's blade.
It's going to be the sharpness of the knife.
Robert Blake did a hit on his wife.
Yep.
So that's an opposites react situation.
Yeah.
And then...
Opposites react is the third way.
Phil Spector...
just show her words opposites attract Robert Blake did the same thing right
it's Phil Spector a ghost he looked like one in the court photos okay then I
don't know who look up look up fill always go with the bird hair look up
remember that court yeah yeah I've seen that photo before pretty good for us
number 10 hair is a bird number 10 I drowned your puppy that's a drown that's
that's a dry to be a that's a drown yeah. I've been stripping for money you have
no
update your status on Facebook with your birth date and date your birth date and
date of today and saying R I P
switch lotion with Mayo, no, no, that's a say. I broke something. I broke
something say excuse me, sir. I think you just dropped your pocket awesome. I
love this one. I was laughing for an hour. Let's see fake winning scratch off
lottery ticket. I slept with your mom. I love you pranked. I love you too. Let's
see what the last one is on here. What's the final one? I'm a
what
all right. That's a pretty good last one. Yeah, okay. Bye everybody.