come back and make a bet
and we see a black
you're a scrap monster
okay low-key thought that this was a drink yes that's what i have a good
really i was doing my laundry here yesterday
and you decided to put the bleach bottle there's a drink sized right next to all
the drinks on the table
genius dude
that's a serious fucking hippo violation that is a rank
OSHA violation. Most OSHA and HIPAA violations are just awesome pranks when you think about
it. I don't think so. I don't think it's true. That's true. That's not a prank. Making your
friend drink bleach is not a prank. That's an assassination attempt. You can do that
in Hitman. You can do that in Hitman. You won't laugh about it. You'll laugh like this.
Mwahahahaha. Exactly. You'll laugh like Dracula or a villain. You would not laugh like a friend
in a friendly way. A friend wouldn't laugh. A friend would not laugh about hurting or
killing your own friend. Okay, what if that bleach bottle was filled with soda?
That's closer to a prank. Yeah, but that's also not a prank because they wouldn't
drink it. Yeah, but also like if your friend is drinking it that means that
they're trying to maybe kill themselves. What if your friend is trying to kill
themself? That's not a prank. And then they drink it and ask Dr. Pepper. But there's still
traces that you didn't wash it fully and they still die. How do you know I didn't wash it
fully? Well, no. I bleached it out. I bleached out all the chemicals. No, I'm talking about an
imaginary situation here.
- Yeah, and in this imaginary situation,
I wiped out all the chemicals with bleach.
All the bleach chemicals, I used more bleach.
- You didn't do that, he didn't do it.
- What if you accidentally put just a car--
- What if you ate a bug?
- That's not a prank either.
- What if you ate two bugs?
- That actually, that would be a funny ass prank
if you did that, Pat.
- Oh yeah, that would be a funny prank.
- Yeah, that actually, you would get me so good
if you ate two bugs.
- Yeah, you can eat two bugs in here.
- I actually, I would hate, don't do it.
I would hate--
- No, I would seriously--
- You might be if you ate two bones.
- Now I wanna do it.
- I'm gonna do it. - It'll be so annoying.
- Okay, I'm gonna do it now.
- Do it then. - Seriously, don't.
- Okay, I'm not gonna do it. - Why are you waving
your hand like that?
You're waving it so much, it's like a horse's tail.
Stop.
Stop, it's too, stop.
You have to stop, that's actually cool.
- You can't do that.
- You can't, okay, get that thing away from your chest.
- That's not near my chest.
- That was right on your chest.
- It was right on your chest.
- It was touching your chest over and over.
So this weekend, I forgot I didn't tell you about this.
So this weekend, my friend Charlie had a runway show
for his clothing line, capsulecollection.love.
Go check it out.
- This fucker better be paying us money.
- He's gonna give me a shirt.
- Well, you plugged it on my show,
so I'm gonna need a shirt as well.
- You can also get a shirt from him.
- I think I'm gonna have to hit up Charlie and get a shirt.
So Charlie had this runway show where he hired a pit bull impersonator.
Dog or guy?
Guy.
He was really, he was cool.
Dude. He rocked.
Me and me and Joe got there really late. Um,
or like right at the last second. And the only seat left was like, right.
It was like a really small room and the only seat left was like right up at like
the very front. So we were literally,
we were just sitting like probably like less than a foot away from the pit bull
guy though the whole time. Well, then he started,
he started walking around and dancing,
- He started walking around dancing.
- He was throwing a fit.
That's what we were right next to him for.
He was, though, like,
speakers and microphone and stuff weren't working.
- Yeah, well, so Charlie told me he requested
specifically to use his own MP3 files.
Like, Charlie was like,
"Oh, I can just play the Pitbull songs off of Spotify."
And he said, "No, these are louder."
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- Was like insistent,
"Hold on, I have his business card somewhere on my wall."
- But yeah, he was throwing a fit.
he was like, can you not make it louder? It was working a second ago. What's
going on? And he just like wouldn't get, he wouldn't like relax. Um, and the
pitbull impersonator was a diva. He was a huge diva. And then, and then that he
like, um, he was like, well, if it's not going to work, like he also said he was
a standup comedian at one point. Cool. And he's like, well, if it's not going
to work, I'll just like do my thing. Look at him, dude. That's him. That's
nothing like pitbull. Wow. I think I could do a better. He was like, I think
think you should he he made a lot of money. He he was like I'm just going to
do my thing and he like started walking around and he's talking. The microphone
is not on, but he's talking into the microphone just yelling and he's just
going
to Charlie. He started saying he started saying what they won't tell you is that
grains have zero nutritional value. The food pyramid is lying to you. The FDA
they're fools. They're lying to you, doctor Oz. He's not a real doctor.
It's all fake and and it and it makes sense because think about it Oz, the
wizard of Oz, they saw the wizard of Oz and they look behind the curtain. It
was just a little guy pretending faking to be something larger. Doctor Oz
everyone's going crazy and I was in the back. I was in the back waiting to
walk, but there was like a you know we're trying to figure out the technical
difficulty. So he just cooked for like five minutes. He was going for a long
time. He also said that a gave syrup as you should you will give you diabetes.
he said tequila is his favorite liquor, but he said no what
happened what happened was he was like he was like yeah, you
can't eat agave syrup.
It'll give you diabetes and then somebody in the audience was
like well, you don't you like do you not like tequila and then
he said he like he like got like in their face and he was like
well, that's a different form of agave syrup.
So like he was like super aggressive to like whenever somebody
would like quite like a few people like questioned him or
something and he and what I forget what what he said he said something and one
one girl was like said something that was like no that's not true and he like
he was like what's your name stand up
so cool so at the end of the show name huh do you know the person is Steven
Steven yeah I mean I have a Steven I would just like to put him on a little
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna put on Charlie. We got a Charlie. I think Charlie deserves it
I think Steve. No, I think Stephen is people did a better job
I've gotten more about Stephen from this story than it was
So they're like the show's over and I was like getting a photo with him
I had cam take a picture and then cam said like oh you guys look like brothers
Yeah, and then the guy was like, I'll have what he's having and pointed at Cam
I'll have whatever he's on. Yeah, he's a multi person impersonator. Yeah, he can
impersonate anybody from any movie or any musician. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, and I did the joke of just making like like looking like really confused
and then saying you're being really weird right now man, which I think is I
guess it's a funny thing to do to like your friend but probably very rude to do
to a pitbull impersonator. I think Stephen knows how to roll. He didn't. No I think he
did. If you think he didn't that means he got you. So I was backstage changing out of
the clothes and then the pitbull impersonator walks up to me and is like, "Man, what is
up with your friend? Does he not smoke?" And I was like, "No, he's straight edge. He's
never done a thing in his life and the pitbull impersonator went blank. He was like, man,
because like I think if he did smoke or drink or something, he probably would have had the
prior experience and probably would have understand because I said I'll have whatever he's on,
which I meant like if he's on drugs thinking that we look like brothers, then I want what
he has. I want what he has then. But if he does nothing, then like he probably wouldn't
get the joke. And then I was back there for like, I was just trying to put my pants back
on. I'm back there for like, like five minutes because he's like trying to explain the joke.
This makes me wish I had gone. Dude, you should have come. Dude, I got my license plate stolen.
Oh shit. Yeah, I couldn't couldn't make it out because I got my license plate stolen.
But what? They just stole it off my car, dude. What are you, what, what's the benefit of
doing that. So if you do a crime you switch out the plates with stolen plates. I know
this from GTA 5. I think yeah it's a put on a stolen car. Okay. Yes that it's less easy
to it's untraceable. Yeah. But then they'll trace it back. Yeah to the stolen. They'll
pull this person over in a Lamborghini and be like are you driving is this some kind
of body kit for a 2009 Ford Focus. Yeah. Well it's also it's also pretty bad for you because
you've made some threats in your lifetime. Yeah, maybe that that might not show up. Well,
if if the police I think the police aren't going to aren't going to immediately give
you a chance here. Luckily cars not in my name. I am worried about the thing is I have
luckily attached those plates. I probably have eight hundred and fifty dollars in unpaid
tolls and tickets to the state of New York. I really I made money by them stealing my
my plates yeah like what like yeah, we I wouldn't they're going to bring it
they're going to bring the plates because I'm going to get I'm going to
order some new plates brand fresh start. You know blank slate blank. Can
you is that is it does it work the same as like a debit card?
Yeah, license plate works the same as a like when you get a new card, it
cancels all your other subscriptions. No, not really subscriptions to
tickets.
It cancels your netflix yeah, honestly it might have been a fucking like it
might have been a parking cop who fucking just took my plate. They're
just so sick of writing me tickets. It's like easier to just if I look up
that would be so sick if it overwrites your tickets or whatever and you can
and that would be the best way to do fraud. That yeah, oh yeah, my my
plate got my plate got stolen. Do you guys ever get a rent like I don't
remember I have a piece of white paper sitting in my back window that says
my plate got stolen and then my life.
I'm going to go. I'm going to jail. I drove here today.
sick oh did you bring that bike no bitch you have to go get it I gave him $20
you have to go get it I figured yeah but there is 20 bucks on my damn Zelle I got
zelled oh my god Zelle is the funniest way to say it. I said it on Zelle because I was like oh then
you won't have to deal with the instant transfer. The only time I get Zelle is when
I'm on like my birthday. My grandma sent me like five dollars. I love so I
thought that was my first first experience in zell to is that my well
my my like grandfather who lives like out of the country. He just sent for my
birthday. He sent like some money to my dad on zell and that was before zell
was like a thing like neither of us have ever heard of zell before and it was
just and he's like yeah. I just sent some some zell money and we had to like
through this whole thing of figuring out how to get money out of you get some
text message from some random numbers like this person is zeld me five
what the fuck is zell?
what does it mean?
somebody zelled me? somebody zoobed me?
fucking 20 bucks? what does that mean?
yeah yeah
nobody's ever zelled me money
I've only had to zell money to people
I had to zell for rent
yeah I have to use zell for rent
I zeld I think I told you guys this I zeld the wrong person at a liquor store. I
was trying to sell a liquor guy and I zeld some random fucking person because
he gave me the wrong phone number and I was like and then I zeld him again. So
maybe he was done. He's the guy at the liquor store. I zeld him. He zeld all
over the place. I zeld completely all over his body and into his phone. Yeah
first you zeld the wrong guy. I zeld a completely different dude. A complete
a stranger and then I was and then he said no you were one digit off and then I
zilled on him zilled up in here what are we doing here what the hell is that are
you trying to make this about me coming and being a sexual thing no we're
talking about money in Zell okay that's I would have said you've come didn't
the wrong guy by mistake that's talking about come day yeah that's that is a
good point but you seldom dingers what if we make a new money thing call app of
money. Bingo. Bingo. Bingoed him. Bingoed. Yeah. That's pretty good actually. There's these
new bingo games you can get on your phone where you can play for real money. Really? Yeah.
Have you been playing them? I did for a week. Do you miss that? Have you guys seen that
one ad on YouTube? Do you miss that thrill of a slot machine but COVID's got you in a
quarantine? Now listen up, I got the thing you need, it's an app that's free, it's called
lightning link. I've gotten a few slot apps on like Hulu and stuff. I haven't got
one on YouTube yet. My mom plays so many slot apps. Do you know what ad I
love? What? My favorite one is the is the solitaire one with the dog. I ain't seen
that. You have it there on a bunch of the trains here but they also come on on
like Hulu and stuff sometimes and it's a dog that has human teeth like it's like
a cartoon animated dog with human teeth and he's like and he's like the cards
will show me the way and I don't want to much game or no you know it's on it's on
to be I get that at on me. Oh, I thought I got a new slot app. I actually got a I've
been playing this game called tune blast tune blast or no Royal match.
You get tune blast tune blast and Royal match are made by the same company. Oh
and that's maybe you make it's just candy crush in a castle. Oh, okay,
instead of the candy what do you have squares all of them are square triangles
so shapes shapes shapes okay and I'm on level 73 Wow nice that's pretty good I
was getting a bunch of salt air on my phone solitaire is good what's do you
know what's do you know what the average win rate is for solitaire I'm not sure if
I have a higher low win rate I think I probably have a pretty low hands on it
Do you do a random deck?
I assume so.
I think a random deck is...
It's just a solitaire app.
I don't know.
Speaking of apps, I got this new app.
Okay, I'm going to say my win rate is 12.96%.
Think for a random deck, that's about it.
It's about 10%.
I got this new app.
It's called Supercook and you just put in food in your pantry and then it tells you
what recipes you can make.
And I was looking last night and good news, I can make ssng.
What?
Pardon?
I can make ssng.
Huh?
All I need is one cup of milk to make ssng.
Yo, that looks delicious.
Spell that name out for the listeners.
S space N space N space NG.
if you view the full recipe looks like ribs it's rare but it's just milk it's
ribs and chips okay you can make it with one cup milk it's called so many and
this and this is a dessert - it's a dessert sweet ribs can you rate that
five stars yeah rate it five right now I'll rate it well it's I was looking at
Amazon reviews last night it's not letting me read it I was looking at
Amazon reviews for all the all the the sex toys I was looking for a sex toy
that was and I found it it was just it's two boobs with a pussy and a butthole on
the bottom of the boots. Yeah. Why are you looking that up? I was just curious and I
found a bunch of reviews and they were all it was like 50 reviews in a row just
saying that the holes were too big.
Here's another one, milk macaroni. Oh that sounds good. I used to love that. Let me
redo this recipe. There's a oldie goldie from from Yvonne Soane's childhood.
Okay. Add your pre-cooked pasta and milk together in a pan as if you were making
soup. Heat until warm, add salt and pepper and a couple pats of butter. Once the
butter is melted, eat and enjoy. I've had that before, that's fine. Really? It's like Alfredo.
Milk macaroni. You're not putting flour or anything in it, it's just milk and macaroni.
That's okay, there's enough starch on the outside of the pasta that it kind of...
think so Tim. It kind of makes a little bit of a of a of a rue. Back when when
Facebook Messenger was was a thing when people still used that yeah I used to
love they had you know they had like little add-ons that nobody ever used that
you would like be able to like add to it yeah they're like there were some really
good ones but the my favorite one that like I that was you they had like a
recipe add-on so you could just send recipes from like some recipe website
directly through like Facebook Messenger and it would just come up like as its
own like a sticker like as its own thing and there would be so many recipes where
you just that you just find you'll be able to find stuff that people may call
like monster slime and stuff because like searching for like Halloween recipes on
a recipe site and then yeah like finding like just sending somebody a recipe
called like nightmare or something that make me laugh. I don't like Halloween
recipes. I don't want to eat a piece of bread that looks like poop. Here's a good one.
How to freeze milk. How to freeze milk? What is the directions? Let me see. From the low the
slow roasted Italian. Can you freeze milk? Yes.
(laughter)
- That's a great recipe.
- Yeah.
- What do you need to freeze milk for?
- A freezer.
- No, what, no. Not what do you need to freeze milk.
I mean, what, why do you need to freeze, what is the
- A popsicle.
- Yeah, a popsicle.
- A milksicle.
- A popsicle?
- Just milk?
- How, here's a recipe that's ready in less than five
minutes. How to scald milk, you have to burn milk. If you ever want to how to
scald milk, scald, scald. Are you saying like the four star? It's a four star
recipe really, but milk is five stars. So it brings it down to four because
you're scald. Can you put in like can you put in two ingredients and see what
recipes can we see what recipes we can make out of stuff? Can we can me and
Caleb each name an ingredient and see what yeah, let's try that. That'll be
have let me let me go off of what's no just make just two only one of them I'm
lying to that I want to lie to the app okay here's here's one hoisting oh my
god yeah we had it such a good idea that would be a funny thing to do why this
is just look at his phone trust me this is gonna be really funny trust me be
really funny trust me okay okay so based off of what I have in my pantry okay a
recipe with the key ingredients hoisting sauce and Chinese five spice powder this
This is gonna be a crazy recipe.
Just let us play our game.
This is not, yeah, what's going on here?
Okay.
You're killing the episode.
It's ruined.
We have to start over.
Okay, okay.
Name an ingredient.
You want me to go first?
See, you don't even.
No, shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm thinking of an ingredient!
Do you want to go first or should I?
Cameron can go first, but I know how to think of an ingredient.
M&M's.
Cameron's gonna go first here.
Wait, let me, I have to add it to my pantry now.
So now I have to go and buy M&M's when I'm done recording.
Good.
Come on Caleb, you got this.
Flavor?
It's flavor.
That's close.
M&M's is not showing up as an ingredient I can use.
Water!
Okay.
M&M's and water.
We the only ingredients we assume you have our salt pepper and water. Oh,
so neither okay. Well, so no pepper peppers. Okay. No wait wait paprika
rabbit rabbit. Oh rabbit
Okay, rabbit meat. Okay, let me look up chocolate rabbit meat and chocolate
chocolate bunny easy oh yeah easy as shit you're so stupid my god that's the most why does the can
you explain me rabbit on rabbit grilled okay what else what it was any of your wasted rabbit beer
rabbit in the crock pot fried rabbit rabbit in a crock yeah come home from work easter
that Easter bark Easter bark. Yeah, let's got rabbit in it. Fuck
I guess so how come the rabbit one eggs when he doesn't lay eggs, but you come
home from from from school, your mom's cooking something in the crock pot.
You're like oh my God, I can't smell so good. I can't wait for dinner. You like
peek you open the lid just a little bit to sit to get a whiff to see what it is
and it's a full rabbit full rabbit for on nothing else. No, liquid. No,
- A rabbit. - A rabbit.
- Just a rabbit being just burned
by the bottom of the crock pot.
- I bet that would still smell pretty good.
- It would smell delicious.
- A rabbit?
- It smells so good.
- I've never had a rabbit.
I don't wanna eat no damn rabbit.
- I love walking by some of the restaurants here
and seeing just a whole rabbit picture.
- Oh, that's the best. - Dude, I went to a Key Foods.
You know the one off of Lorimer?
- It's a grocery store.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it doesn't really matter
where or what grocery store probably.
they sell it said Cui C-U-I and I looked and it's a plastic bag and there's just
a hamster in it. What country eats guinea pig? South American. Yeah I've never seen
it like it's just a skinned guinea pig in a plastic bag like you know when you get
like those microwave corn dogs yeah and they're in those plastic same type of
like it looked like a Jimmy Dean guinea pig. I would not eat that I don't think I
like any meat except beef and chicken. What about fish? I fried
some fish last week and I was like so disgusted by the way fish falls apart in
a bunch of pieces. I love fish. Fish is the best. I usually love salmon but I was eating Alaskan cod and get this
the layers of the cod it was like stacked dollar bills are just falling
away. That sounds so good. It sounds amazing. And also there was no salt and they were covered in
fucking peanut butter. He doesn't even care about the best tuna salad I've ever made. I could
it out tuna salad you know my eyes closed no you could and blindfolded and a spike
through my made I made it was the best one I've ever made in my life you you
you don't know what you're talking about yeah I ate tuna salad every day for me
all your cereal this morning that's a man right I guess he I did I did have one
cereal have you all right Cameron wins I did have a reason brand half Cheerios
half what raisin bran half cheerio
you're mixing cereals?
*laughing*
that's the worst thing i've ever done
you can't mix two cereals
there wasn't enough left of either of them
i was telling you i always
make an egg, what are you doing?
because i'll never eat either of those otherwise
he's not going to put an egg on his cereal
i'm not saying that, okay so save the two cereals for a late night snack
and make something else for breakfast
why would i have cereal for a late night snack?
Honey Nut Cheerios was every night. There's been for a late night snack, you get a small bowl. I have small bowls.
This month or last month, there was a big recall of Honey Nut Cheerios and Lucky Charms.
A lot of people were getting diarrhea. I get diarrhea. I don't notice if I get diarrhea.
Lucky Charms has been going on for a while. I didn't know it was Honey Nut Cheerios.
Something is happening at the Lucky Charms factory. Yeah, something's going on ever since that freaking shrimp.
I guess that was Cinnamon Toast Crunch.
It was a shrimp and a Cinnamon Toast Crunch.
Oh you didn't see this?
Bruh! Bruh!
Literally though.
I don't even want to fucking get into it.
I mean this is like
I don't want to bring it up now because it's almost
like Harambe or something
where I don't want to talk about it.
Basically like a Harambe level meme.
9000 meme.
Speaking of
Today's list
Next is the top ten most cancerous memes and trends that are on society.
It's the top ten most cancerous trends and memes of the twenty-first century.
That's I said that exactly the same.
Did you say society of the society?
Of the society.
Here's and it's by Kristen Grant.
I decided to I decided to I decided to something different from what I usually do.
So here's some trends and memes that are the cancerous.
Okay number one I would say you know let's hear your guess my guess I'm
gonna say not bad Obama wrong number one is dab the dab isn't a meme it's a
dance well it's a trend it's a trend hold on I feel like I'm gonna vomit
continue the first person I saw dab was a kid I really hated so I used the
mentality of if he does it I don't that's smart that is smart I saw my
grandma dab in 2014 really yep change my life Wow she's Devin cuz of Cam Newton
Wow yeah dabbing is so sad fortnight is so sad everything in this list is so
flipping sad I just find it sad that kids are dabbing still yeah yeah was
originally a strong way to smoke marijuana it's the purest form of
of marijuana. When you smoke it, you cough the first thing you do is put
hand in front of mouth and coughs. That's where dab came from https colon
slash slash m dot cs monitor dot com slash the dash culture slash twenty
sixteen slash oh two oh eight slash. Do we really need a dab of drug culture
in our dancing? We don't we do not. I hate drug culture. I want to go to this
work. I've been outspoken about marijuana abuse and how much it's
fucking disgusting. Hey dopers yeah dopers, smokers, christian science
monitor. That's what this website is.
Listen, I saw some piece of fucking dog shit dope fiend, right? Lighten up, he's
sitting in a wheelchair, both of his legs are in casts, he's lighten up in the
middle of his living room with the windows open, okay? And you know what I
was thinking? I was thinking, you know what I'd really like right now is a red
sniper dot directly on this guy's neck brace through his window and I'd like
for somebody to shoot his trachea.
Absolutely.
So that he can, hey, try smoking dope now, buddy.
It's gonna fly out of the hole in your neck.
You know what I saw? I saw this bald woman
Yeah.
Eating an edible.
Yeah, and it's like, listen, first of all
She's at the hospital and she looked sick.
And she looked sick probably because of the dope.
Here's what's happening, okay?
She's bald. She's a lesbo. Okay?
She's a complete lesbo. Right?
And she's a dopehead. Right?
And why is she at the hospital?
Cause she's done with her dopehead
fucking starter drug and she's trying to get opiates.
opiates. Yeah, going in there, faking menstrual blood or she can get a
prescription for you know. I hear what I hear what dopers will do nowadays is
even before they'll go to the hospital and some of them they're not you know
they're not even they don't even have the courage to upgrade opiates, but
they'll go to the hospital. I think how can I get my hands on more dope? I
don't want to I don't have to get in a car with my my my my dirty dope dealer
no more. I need I need to legitimize this and I hear what they'll do is
go into the hospital, they'll complain that they have rot in one of their limbs,
they'll get it amputated, and they'll get a special card that lets the government
throw dope in their mouths like a freaking clown game at the arcade.
It absolutely is.
It's a, yeah, that's what it is.
It's Nintendon.
I've seen these rectangle dopers, they've got no arms, no legs, they're crawling
around like an inchworm, trying to put their mouth on a drainage pipe just to
suck out some dope additives.
And you know these dispensaries are just giving them more, they're putting more stuff in the
truck so that people can get rot.
It's true.
They're trying to get more rot in their limbs so that they can be removed by a plastic surgeon
so that they can deal with the quote unquote pain.
I mean this fucking dope.
It feels amazing to lose a limb.
People did these, first of all, when dope started out, people were like we have a nation
of zombies.
You know, but more and more it's looking like we're going to have more of a nation of mummies.
I'd like to bring you--
- 'Cause they are a mummy, right?
- Yup, they're covered in bandages.
- I'd like to bring you guys--
- Their arms and legs are falling off.
There's sand everywhere, their skin is turning to sand.
- I'd like to bring you guys back
to a different time and place, okay?
- Okay, I hope it's not-- - Ancient Egypt.
- I hope it's not ancient Egypt, B.C.
'cause that's where all the mummies are.
- It's 1969, right?
We start the Vietnam War, okay?
- Awesome.
- Nobody wants to go, right?
until a couple of these--
- Because, why don't they wanna go?
- Until a couple of these hippies get an idea,
somebody says, a war man recruiter says,
"Hey, who wants to go to Vietnam and get PTSD
"and get all your limbs blown off?"
And all these dopers go, "Oh, me, me, me, me, me!"
Because one day there's gonna be a place
called concierge dispensary where I can deal
with my quote-unquote pain and quote-unquote
lost foot and PTSD with a Skittle.
free dope for pillow humans. Yeah, exactly. Right. And now all of a
sudden you got these guys, they wear American flag bandanas, they
pretend they're homeless, and then they turn around, they go outside
and they actually have a 1994 Ford Focus and parked in the back of
the grocery store. And they're walking into the dope dispensary.
It's like, yeah, give me this. Give me the strongest pen that you
have. Give me a drug. Give me a strain of dope called the Hitler's
killer yeah Hitler's pussy it's like so fucked up from the war that oh I have to
think about times when I killed people like but you know what awesome and you
know what they were doing in Vietnam they're smoking the weed out of a
shotgun that's right as they wanted I mean they could get more weed yeah these
quote-unquote veteran dopers okay there I mean there they're coming back here
they're coming back here to the to you the u.s. to get more free dope there were
there you know they're they're waddling into these to these dispensaries they
They look like Freddy Krueger's finger under these tie-dyed shirts, okay?
These dopers with no arms and no legs are getting pulled into dispensaries, pushed into dispensaries
on a dolly.
They look like, folks, they look like Floops Fuglies.
Yup, and they're being just completely just tossed into dispensaries like bricks through
a window.
They're saying, you know what, there's a guy who pulls them, pushes them in on a hand truck
and then drops it on the floor and then they're face down on the ground like, "Could I have
It's like, okay, they're coming in and they're like, "Alright, my arms and legs were pulled
off by a robotic arm at the Ford Focus Factory, but you know what I haven't lost yet?
My mind."
And listen, I know how to fix that.
I'll smoke a freaking pack of dope.
It's going to pull up my brain right out of the top of my head like an Egyptian mummy.
I want to taint it with weed cigarettes and give myself mummy rocks.
Some of these grass heads are actually even genius artists, unfortunately, and we've lost
some of them. Speaking of, Nirvana's own Kurt Cobain, he stuck a shotgun into his
mouth because he thought it was a slice of pizza because he was so high and
now he's dead like a mummy. Yep. Same with Jimi Hendrix. He threw up because he
smoked so much. And he thought that his throw up was pizza. Yeah. And now he's
dead like a mummy. And Jim Morrison was eating pizza in the tub underwater. Yep.
And now he's dead like a mummy. Mm-hmm. You can't eat pizza underwater. Most psychotic
spree killers or dopers.
- Yeah. - Okay, but even beyond that,
the ones who don't go out and rat-a-tat-tat
kill a million humans, you realize what lives
on the dope plant is insects and ants.
- That's the thing. - And they get burned up
and killed when a doper smokes the dope.
- Look at-- - And the bug goes
in their brain and is so mad at the human race.
- They got spider webs in there.
- Yeah. - Take a look, you loo,
at the row of mass shooters we've had
in the last 20 years, right?
James Holmes and all those guys looks like a fucking fish concert okay that's
what it looks like when you look at these guys all right yeah eyes are blood
shocked right they have completely blood shocked eyes yeah and they're looking at
you at that fucking THC Delta 9 stare yeah right yeah and they probably thought
that all these kiddies walking around the school were slices of pizza yeah and
they needed to cook them yeah they're big pizza gun yeah cuz that's what dope
does to your brain it makes you who okay the Boston shooters think about it we're
getting that strong that strong key Kong from the Middle East yeah right getting
it shipped over to the brothers right the two brothers of the two dope brothers of
Boston I thought you were talking about the middle and you know what you know
what they thought you know what they thought they thought that the pressure
cookers that they dropped and the they were cooking a pizza they thought that
they were just cooking as damn pizza in a volcano vape right and all of a sudden
you got and don't get me started five years later Mark Wahlberg's making a
movie with no legs right and guess how that guy treated his no legs in Rome
yep smoking smoking goes all the way to the top of the hip all the way to the
bottom of the ground which is where the guy was cuz you know any legs you know
and I mean think about Benson listen he's about to think about these um
these these types of these bands that dopers will listen to I mean I seriously
a band called the great full dead it's great to be dead no hole also none of
these bands are spelled correctly grateful dead right fish uh-huh fucks
going on Dave Matthews bang the Beatles yep the hell is that oh my god
you moron and this is all ever since 2001 when Doug Benson started talking
about this shit Doug Benson listen super high you yeah I wouldn't even say hi to
you you fucking drug I'd rather super low you I'm gonna put you six feet under
Yeah for do it for ruining this country with pot you actually a drug addict piece of fucking dog shit
Mm-hmm getting dug with high buddy. The name doesn't make it's wrong
This fucking idiot got so completely mistaken that he swapped two words in his own
How are you gonna? How is that show gonna look professional? That's like list about podcast
Oh, that doesn't make any sense
That way if we were so high when we named the show that we named it that wouldn't that be some fucking bullshit
That would fucking be dog shit Lee bullshit. That'd be the worst thing that's ever happened. I'm sick
I'm sick of these I'm sick. No, I'm sick. No, I'm actually fucking sick. You're sick. Yeah, I'm sick
And I guess what the doc you can't go to the doctor. I can't go cuz they're gonna describe you describe me
Yep, they're gonna prescribe you don't prescribe me dope weed
You know what kind of I have phantom limb and you know for a bigger penis
penis. You know what else these dope freakers are doing? What? You think about
the earth, right? They say that it comes from the middle one. Millions of years
ago, okay? Well, that's a third argument, but sure. The earth, the green. Yeah.
Green and blue planet, okay? Nowadays, earth is grey and brown and yellow and
golden and silver and red and black and white, but it's much less green. Do you
why it's much less green. They're smoking. The dopers, they take the green, they turn
it brown. Yep. And it turns their insides brown, it turns their shoulders red, and
then it turns their arms black and gray. And they're combining
the green and the blue in a bong and just using up all of these resources.
Exactly. Yeah, where's the water go? Depleting. Where does the bong water go? They waste it.
They don't even use it. Because they're waste. You could filter that bong water and start
making spaghetti for homeless people. You could found a desert city
mm-hmm with that water. You could found the city and with the the glass oh my
god a futuristic glass city with water and green grass. It would have been
amazing but instead it would have been Babylon and I'm not talking about
the Babylon that Bob Marley that fucking dopehead was talking about. No no no no
no. Listen Jamaica listen I don't want to say it but it should be just
completely wiped off the face of the planet. I wouldn't say that. Just completely one giant wave, just a
wrath of God should just wipe it out with one single wave. I think I think that they
should just make weed illegal there. Jamaica should just be nuclearly exploded. Are you kidding me? Wait, no no no.
I do not understand why God hasn't done something about dope. Do you, could you
imagine how how less spicy Jamaican jerk wings would be if they weren't smoking
weed when they did exactly so we got the recipe listen Jamaica you gave us the
recipe buddy now get the boot we're sending you to Mars that's happening
red planet not a way not a speck of green to be seen God that that should be a
penal colony that's right oprah's mm-hmm they'll do I mean those dopers they'll
probably I mean some of these some of those over smoking alien and probably
try to smoke a green alien yeah but some of these dopers I mean they they go
without their green for practically one second,
they're throwing up, they're shitting their pants.
- You know who I would have trusted?
- They're clawing at their own face.
- I would have trusted Sir Elon Musk
to send these dope heads to Mars,
but then he actually joined their ranks
by going on Joe Token and actually lighting up
in front of millions. - That was so disappointing.
- I mean, he was honestly a hero of mine, right?
I had always wanted to make a car.
- I mean, what's next, an electrical way to smoke weed?
Is that what Elon Musk is-- - It's fucking disgusting.
That's probably what he's working on.
- A cigarette powered by electricity?
Oh, we're gonna waste the electricity, too. It's not enough to take the green and
the blue out of the earth and the glass. The other day, this is actually true, I'm
not making this up at all, I was at CVS and a lady got started talking to the
they it's like one of the CVS's where they have a cop that stays there because
there's so much so many people like stealing shit, probably dope heads by the
way, but she said something about she's like I bet you light up when you get
home and he said yeah it's legal and she said I used to light up in the 90s and
and then my cousin who is one of the beat cops in my neighborhood used to chase me
down the street with a taser.
So it actually tears families apart. It does tear families apart. Literally their arms and legs are
being torn off.
Torn limb from limb because they'll walk into a wild chimpanzee cage
just so they can get their hands ripped off so they can smoke weed. Listen, Charlotte Nash,
there's a reason why she told the monkey, she said, "Rip
everything off except my mouth so I can still smoke weed."
Yeah. And that's what he did. It weakens your joints and your ligaments.
yeah it does. A doper will try to hold the door open their arm will fall onto the ground
the door will pull. Like a leper. The door will pull off the arm
when they open it. It'll look like sponge bob. That's why there aren't any dopers that have
automatic doors in their houses.
Don't even get me started on. See like me I have an automatic door. I have an automatic door too it's so
convenient I love it
the bathroom door an automatic door every time someone walks by it opens I can see
who's what's going on
and it's glass. And you go to downtown. It's a 7-eleven on it
You go to any major city--
I installed it two weeks ago.
You go to downtown LA, Skid Row, right?
It's called Skid Row because you smoke so much weed
that you believe Skid Marks in your pants.
It was founded by dopers in the '60s.
And you walk around, these people are zombies.
They're looking at you.
They're going, come watch Fantasia with us.
Come watch Disney's Fantasia.
Yeah.
I'm like, I don't want to watch Fantasia.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
Do you realize Chernobog is a fucking demon?
You do realize that a broom can't actually walk.
you are literally gaining satanic and change and entertainment. We're gonna
watch a Disney property. We're probably gonna watch Mickey Mouse Clubhouse or
we're gonna watch one of the Scrooge McDuck films. Right? I don't want to watch
Chip and Dale Rescue Rangers. Mickey go and he's dancing with hippos. Listen, a
hippo's a boy. They got him dressed up in tutus. These dopers too,
they'll want to watch a Disney movie like Frozen. Yeah. It's like, don't
you realize this movie is so subversive? It's ruining the image of
princes to discuss people think princes are evil now because of yep because one
of the donors at Disney are making these dope movies one of the biggest dopers of
all Walt Disney cut off his own head yeah he got he got the right is the right
spread to his body he cut off his own damn head yep I heard rose that thing so
that he could smoke more later I'm a high-ranking frozen uh-huh about his
damn head I heard that high-ranking Disney employees and officials actually
get to use Walt Disney's head as a bong because it gets it gets him high to well
he's in well he's in their color of the bronze fucking surprise. Well he's in
his brain yep. I will be discussing what dopers do to the society now Cheech and
Chong don't even get me started on Cheech Marin and Chong Marin on marine
yeah Tommy Chong. How come they go listen these dopers are so stupid it
have been called Marin and Chong or Tommy and Cheech. But they went first name,
last name. And who's and? Yeah. Which one of them is and? Probably the
same guy from the and one shirts. Oh that guy's a serious dopehead.
Yeah right? He's so rude. And the dope turns people rudely mean. I don't think because if he
if he smoked he wouldn't have been able to do any of that. The sad part is the
weed has actually infested our sports culture where you have celebrities NBA
players like Lamar Odom who admit to marijuana abuse yeah yeah they don't
even start on bill admit it they think it's okay was I think it was weed he had
to he had to leave one of the sexy sexy Kardashians to go to rehab rehab really
yeah because the weed actually made him a compulsive liar I wish
that these dopers instead of going to rehab would head to Dhab and be
completely eliminated from the face of the planet.
Which would go to 8 by whale.
Yep.
I think it should be a I think it should be like the dead space eyeball machine.
Yep. I think so.
Yeah and I think it should be called Dhab.
Mm-hmm. I think a drill should be just
Don't even get me started.
Shoved right through them like Bioshock.
Don't even get me started on Seth Rogen.
Seth Rogen, his buddy.
Listen, but the Rogen brothers, they're a couple of fucking potheads, right?
And listen, Snoop Dogg, you're liable too.
Willie Nelson, I want you to get by a train.
All you people are fucking disgusting.
You need to stop glorifying!
Stop it right now!
Stop glorifying smoking weed to little kids!
It's not right. It's not cool.
If you glorify smoking, I will kill you.
If you glorify smoking a single joint in front of a child, I will actually fucking strangle you.
And you know what? Don't even smoke.
Don't even smoke!
And don't you dare!
Don't glorify or even do it!
Don't you dare!
Stop smoking right now!
Culture! Culture! American culture!
You listen to me! You better stop smoking!
But cigarettes are fine. Smoke cigarettes.
Cigarettes actually remove a lot of the harmful THC molecules that actually go into your lungs.
Cigarettes are the anti-weed.
Exactly. Think about it.
about it. They use it also, also, listen, we're talking about dope turns you to a mummy, it
uses up the green and blue to the earth, turns it sandy like Egypt. A cigarette, what's it
wrapped in? White paper. What's a mummy wrapped in? White paper. The cigarette uses up the
white paper and it prevents mummies from being created.
And I smoke a cigarette, I feel exactly like Napoleon Bonaparte, right? And I'm out there
And I'm slaying all of the weedheads.
Yeah.
All of the poor weedheads.
You know who smoked cigarettes?
Who?
Clint Eastwood.
That's right.
And you know who else smoked cigarettes?
Who?
Cowboy.
Who's a cowboy?
Yeah, I feel like a cowboy.
And I feel just like a cowboy.
And a Napoleon Bonaparte when I smoke a cigarette.
See, weed turns you into a sissy.
Uh-huh.
Cigarettes turn you into a macho man.
- A macho man. - A macho man
who's not afraid to tell these chairs what's up.
- Yep. - That's right.
- Exactly, just like Clint Eastwood.
- Clint Eastwood. - He goes,
"These chairs, this chair represents all the dope heads."
- Yeah. - And you might think
it's okay to mix cigarettes and weed,
but it's not okay.
You know what happens?
You know who did that, who's famous?
- Who? - Lil Nas X.
- That's true.
- And it's, you know what they call it?
It's called a split, right?
- 'Cause you split weed and cigarette.
- Yeah, and it splits your reality
where half of your brain, your left side,
your more creative side is into nicotine now.
- Yeah. - And your right brain,
your robotic, mathematic brain is so high on weed
that it actually loses its ability to count and do--
- It defunctions.
- Just basic division and multiplication.
- Scientifically, it's called de-stop.
- It's de-stopping.
- It de-stops. - Yeah.
So basically, weed is actually going to,
and it also closes your third eye, right?
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
- So what is known to open your third eye?
- Cigarettes. - Nicotine,
fluoride, hamburger meat. - Paper.
- McDonald's. - Paper.
Yeah, the paper around a McDonald's burger.
If you eat pretty much any--
You know what it is?
It's when you try to eat the cheese,
when you get a hearty stick burger
and the cheese gets stuck to the paper
and you eat the cheese off.
That's yester--
And listen, I don't wanna keep harping on this.
I don't wanna keep harping on this,
but what color is the McDonald's paper?
Okay, and the cheese, they're yellow.
What color is the sand and pyramids?
Yellow, you're using up the yellow.
Stop.
The dopers are trying to turn this to Egypt.
They wanted to be ancient Egypt again.
Listen, buddy, you know who built the pyramid?
Tutankhamun.
Slaves.
- Uh-huh.
- And you know,
- Weed heads want slavery to come back.
- Dopers are slaves to the dope.
- Yeah.
- Weed heads want slavery to come back
so that we have slaves out there
picking all their weed plants in the fields.
That's what they want.
- Yep, that's exactly what they want.
- That's what weeders want.
- Okay, if you play Doug Benson's Super High Me Backwards.
- It says, I want a slave.
- I want a weed slave.
- I want a slave to pick my weed.
- It's fucking disgusting.
And honestly, he needs to be executed by a military tribunal.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and I should probably get his bones.
Can't trust the military nowadays.
Yep, also here's the thing, these weed heads
they think it's extraordinary, like Doug Benson.
He thinks that it's worth a podcast
that he loves movies. Listen buddy,
I like movies too.
Okay, but I'm not walking around saying
"Caleb love movies."
Oh, Caleb love movies.
Cause I'm not fucking addicted to weed.
That's right. Yeah, dopers,
they'll start podcasts just for
interest that they have.
disgusting instead of for money yeah that's why you actually do a party and
to spread an important message yeah
what's the next list item
rap dance songs like with crap like watch me hit the Quan and juju on that
that beat getting popular just proves how bad popular pop and rap music is it
today.
Juju on that beat.
I don't think I've heard that one.
There's a comment here that says remove
cancers from the title and replace it with annoying.
Or weed.
Yeah.
All right we're not going to get in there.
Number three is twerking and here's the top comment from top ten ted.
This is supposed to be from tribal Africa, but it was obviously more
tolerable as it was an ancient tribal dance.
Now it's for perverted men to gaze upon the buttocks.
the Charleston has died in place of this for
the Charleston is God
to these
dopers killed the Charles killed the Charleston and bastardized the twerk
the ancient warrior dance. The power puff girls are twerking my childhood is
officially ruined. I thought Miley Cyrus had been a twerking yeah with her giant
but
I'm sorry say what you will about her serious pog. Yeah, she a pog. I'm but
that's it's just a bet you should be using your butt to do the Charleston.
You should be using your butt to wipe. I know your hand to wipe your butt. Yeah or
to sit down. You should be using and now you know what they want you know what
they turned the hand wipe the wiper hand into is the nae nae. Yeah right so now
you're twerking your and you're throwing your poop all over because you haven't
wiped because you're too busy nae nae-ing. Yeah right your poop is getting flown
went into my face. Yeah, when I'm on the street, that's disgusting. Yeah, yeah, I
don't like poop in my face on the saw lady and get into an argument with a guy
on the street the other day, and then instead of she was like yelling at him,
he was yelling at her. She was like shut the fuck up, fuck you, fuck you, and
then she just started like shaking her ass at him and just be like and like
shake your ass space. Well, I was like that's kind of yeah. You win, you can
win. Yeah, and he just stopped yelling at her kind of yeah, you can't really do
much and I crashed my car. You crashed your car. Yeah, I was too busy watching
her. Yeah, it's pretty cool. Just crashed my car. You crashed it and to her number
four is damn Daniel damn Daniel. I haven't heard of this. Here's a comment
from I hate school. It's very sexual. If you think about it damn Daniel, that's
what they said. Isn't it about it? It's a Lena Dunham said it's one of the
biggest pieces of queer performance art of 2016 damn Daniel is yeah. I mean it
I thought it was a guy with no shoes on. No, he has shoes on that are white.
White shoes on. White vans. What's the matter with having white shoes?
It's, I guess it's a Cornelina Dunham, it's queer. Queer? So wait, so the video the
guy calls this... There's that MF Doom song where he says why do all you college boys
wear those... His name was Daniel. Daniel? Daniel Doomile. Oh. Damn you'll... Oh it's all
starting to make sense. Yeah. Yeah. MF Doom. Doom Daniel. You know what I always thought was funny
funny about damn Daniel, you know in the video he was like Dom Daniel. He has
like that kind of accent. You know Dom Daniel is a name for hell. Whoa damn wow
yeah, D O M Daniel, a little bit of it's like a circle of hell or something
trying to make a little bit of sense, not a lot of sense, but a little bit yeah
pretty interesting.
No meme is worse than oh no my bad. It's a final cavernous hall at the bottom of
the ocean where evil magician spirits and gnomes meet Dom Daniel. That's
a lot different. It's from it's from Arabian that sounds like actually
fucking heaven Arabian nights. What's that? It's a movie Arabian nights. Is
that a song for is a collection of Middle Eastern folk tales compiled in
Arabic during the Islamic Golden Age. So it's like Middle Eastern. It's fairy
tales. What you know monkey what about wu kong sun? Oh yeah, monkey, you call
it monkey. It's journey to the West, isn't it? That's the English
translation is just called monkey yeah, but why that's a stupid name as a way
better name. So what is the way cooler monkey? It's a some book called monkey.
It's a good name, but you can't just call it that whatever nobody else would
know what it's called. I think people know monkey monkey. So what other book
called monkey is there Cameron? I wouldn't know one book called monkey.
That's the I know one monkey. It's just funny to say I'm reading monkey. You're
reading monkey. Yes,
I've been reading monkey for a long time.
I phase in and out of reading books.
I go in, I'll read 30 pages of a book,
switch to another one.
Yeah. Yeah.
I started reading a book in January
and I have not touched it.
That's nice.
Yeah.
Masters of Atlantis.
What's happening in monkey?
What is it?
Masters of Atlantis.
What's that?
Book.
What's it about?
It's about a guy who starts a cult.
Oh, it's not like about like Atlantis.
No, no, I want to read an Atlantis book. I was just read a book about us
Port it's about it. It's his name is Portis last name is Portis and he called
Whoa the way he's going to Atlantis Charles porpoise. Oh my god, that makes perfect sense. Yeah
Yeah, he could have been actually maybe if I reread the book with that lens
What's number five number five is Tide Pod Challenge? Oh hell no I actually like this because it actually kind of
Thinned the herd yeah, yeah Darwin Awards yep
Yep, Darwin Award only drunken people eat Tide Pods. It says Wow Wow okay that must have been written by a doper
Yeah, so I guess we're attacking alcohol now. Yeah, this is good for most of your organs
This is dangerous whenever I see these I just think wow these people really want to die right now
People that do this challenge are giving themselves a first-class ticket on a ride to their tombstone
tombstone their tombstone
Are actually attacking
Alcohol fans yeah
Because alcohol is one of the most like enlightening
Psychoactive substances on earth it's it's it's actually within every single molecule
on earth. Because it enhances nicotine. And then when you die, actually a lot of people
know this, don't know this, when you die alcohol is secreted by your third eye.
Yeah. So nobody really knows what happens but you might actually enter like an
endless kind of blissful state that because of the reality is being warped
it feels like eternity to you, just those last couple moments and it's just like
that's what heaven is. Yeah. Right, but it's actually just some alcohol. Exactly,
Yeah, people with near-death experiences, they often report that in the moment when
their body is dying and it's releasing this alcohol to their third eye, many of
them have visions of something horrible they did in fifth grade.
Yep, and a lot of times they see geometric shapes like dart boards and...
Or like just a big black rectangle that they can just tickle up everything.
Yeah.
black geometric shape, a black room with nothing in it and no sound at all and
nothing and just nothing. It is nothing which is yeah and that's like the
geometric alcohol shape. That's like the spirit of alcohol, the alcohol spirit.
Yeah, right. They'll also meet these like some of them. Some people will have a
little bit of a longer kind of journey through this hypnagogic realm and
they'll they'll meet these supernatural beings called bartenders. Yeah, yeah,
you'll kind of control the bartenders. Yeah, the machine is five of them. Yeah,
and it's a recurring kind of exactly where everybody sees and they'll say
they'll say you need to you need to have around. They're still they're also
dressed like clowns. Yeah, they are yeah, they're machine bartender clowns.
Yeah, they're jesters. Yeah, the jesters of the alcohol realm yeah, and then
they get thrown out by a bouncer and they come back to life. That's what
happens. Yeah, they like pick them up and they throw them back out because
alcohol can actually get you laid to which is I guess you hella laid yeah
yeah about Tide Pod smart person this is stupid stupid person I should kill
myself doing this garbage true as fuck stupid people also by the way if you
have suicidal ideation you're inherently not stupid you're probably really smart
mm-hmm that's probably true yeah probably a spiritual gangster yeah your
spiritual gangster who's clearly experimented with alcohol and you're
or yeah yeah number six is bottle flip. Remember this bullshit? Yeah, it's like
listen buddy, you're not supposed to flip the bottle, you're supposed to drink
what's in the bottle. Mm-hmm. Maker's mark. Yeah, you're supposed to or you can eat
the bottle. You can eat the bottle? You can eat the bottle or if it's like a
wax bottle. I think that every bottle should be wax, should be wax. You can eat
it or chew on it at the very least. Yeah. Imagine if you got to eat, if you made it
to the bottom of a of a bottle of Don Julio and then you just get to chew on
it.
If you just get to chew on it yeah, so great that is great great idea. I think
that that could change everything. I think then you drop it doesn't break
yeah. Oh my God, what you're hand about it's bouncy it is so rings on it yeah
yeah or what if what is a wax yeah, it's all made of wax and the floor is all is
all those springs from Sonic and then really ever you drop and listen lower
as a set of golden rings in here. I would really like to wear golden ring yeah,
but the one thing I would not like to if I get hit drop all my rings. Can I just
keep here something I like to keep my ring? I'd like to say just one thing
about Sonic okay.
This fucking game must have been made by doper because where does he keep all
these rings? He has a pouch. He has a pocket and listen. These rings are giant.
He has when I play three hundred of them. He had a high score.
how does he keep these on his body? They shrink. Why? You see the movies. Sonic the Hedgehog
absolutely made by a blue hedgehog that runs and fights an egg man. First of all blue hair.
I want to bring this back to lesbos but that's a serious pothead lesbo kind of situation.
A hedgehog, fucking made up animal. Might as well be a unicorn. Just call it a pig.
the hog have his his best buddy is named tails which that should have been a pig
- yeah it should have been a pig what an animal it should all just put the tail
spins and spiral yeah it should have been a fast pig twist well I don't know
about the fast part cuz that's pretty that's wasted tail the snow baby mm-hmm
right remember the Simpsons movie twisted tail twisted tail twisted tail no you
You don't remember that?
I remember there was a spider pig.
Spider pig, his tail is twisted.
Yeah.
And remember Eepaw, Eepaw, Eepaw.
I remember Eepaw.
Eepaw, Eepaw, twisted tail, a million eyes.
Yeah.
Eepaw, Eepaw, that's what grandpa was saying.
Yeah, and everyone's like, "Oh, wow."
Yeah, so that's kind of, you can apply that to Sonic, too.
Everyone's like, "Oh, the EPA."
Everyone says that when he says that.
And then remember, he says, remember when also the president is the Arnold Schwarzenegger
guy who says, "I pick three."
when he, remember when they're like on the phone calls and it's like you hang up first,
no you hang up first and then he's like okay and he hangs up and she goes oh my god he hung
up on me.
So the point is, oh and it says Dome Sweet Dome.
Yeah, so that's, and Green Day is there.
Green Day!
Those are the kind of jokes, I fucking hate Green Day, you realize that's a dope type
band.
You realize that's a dope title right, because it's Green Day because you're smoking so much
stuff, 420.
Yeah, they name it after dope.
Also yeah, Hitler 420, Hitler was born on 420, oh my god how, this has evaded our, yeah that's
why all the weed strains are named after him holy shit I just every single weed
strain has some relation to Hitler 420 is actually a satanic they're trying to
bring resurrective asking Thunder right you know what yeah you know what a
thunder fuck is a blitzkrieg and you know where Hitler fled to Alaska yep yeah
yeah he's in Alaska frozen his head with Walt Disney
yeah they were like this they were they were best it's something called it's
there's something called a head bong and people are smoking it.
That's a new story that just came out really yeah. Wow, they're saying Walt
Disney and Hitler both did this as well as many people who are not important, so
their names don't matter. I would say no weed smokers ever lived was important,
okay, yeah and we'll get we'll give Bill Clinton you're right on the edge buddy
because he didn't inhale right. I think not in healing ever inhaled. He never
inhaled yeah yeah he didn't yeah. You can tell he wouldn't have been able to
played that that that no yes instrument good he would have been a decent
president had the pious Bush family not immediately usurped him with one of the
greatest presidents ever oh absolutely mm-hmm
me copy time George Bush George W Bush yeah right one of the most
anti-weed presidents ever the weed W stands for winning against the weed
head or weed eliminator or weed killer or weed
weed destroyer. Yeah, you know, speaking of weed destroyer and weed elimination
Portland and Seattle. We're coming to you. We're going to eliminate every last
every drop of weed. Yeah going to be or so we have a we have the we have the
vacuum from Luigi's Mansion. We're sucking it all up and we're shooting it
into the Sun. Yep, and I hope that the smoke does not reach the
when we do that and create a weed world. Also stop trying to smoke the ozone you fucking
pieces of shit. Yeah but August 18th and 19th swagpoop.com/shows go buy tickets and also
on swagpoop.com I think right Wednesday we'll put up the oh yeah. Oh yeah. There will be
our shirts. Swagpoop.com/shop should be up by now. And we're gonna put some shirts on
there. And there are pre-orders up for some shirts. There's the shirt we were selling
on tour that says I tested positive for swag. You can finally get the shirt and
then also another cool shirt. This one's gonna be pretty cool. Yeah, so go
pre-order them on at swagpoop.com/shop. Have fun. Bye. Bye.