- Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Top 10 proof.
Do you start now?
- What?
- Sorry, I had the list open.
- No.
- No, I don't even have it.
- This one got three likes.
- Don't you dare.
- What movie?
- Inglourious Bastards.
I got three likes on this one.
boring to the maximum, serious snooze fest,
I didn't last 30 seconds in the theater
before falling asleep, I slept for the entire movie
and I didn't even get to see the parts with Hitler.
(laughing)
One star.
- That's good, that's like funny
and that's your honest opinion.
I would give that a like.
- Yep.
- Is that your honest opinion?
- Inception, one half star.
A movie about being asleep.
I fell asleep in this movie.
(laughing)
Four likes.
- Yeah, the problem with Letterboxd,
if you try to do anything like that,
people on there are so stupid.
yeah dude yeah i got that that one review about come and see i was like
i'm enjoying the army to stop this forever happening again and literally i
had to turn off the comments on it because i got like a hundred comments
are like you are the worst person on earth
you seriously want to join the army
this one got deleted and put back on this was one star for rocket man
and i said news fest four hours of a gay guy playing piano i literally fell
asleep in the middle of the movie
I'm gonna get a one-star so fucking boring I literally fell asleep with my
blanket and my friend had to wake me up
apparently I was drooling all over my face
I didn't keep going with those fun
film lover seven check me out
that's pretty good I do fall asleep in movies a lot
yeah and in the theaters I'll pay twenty dollars a movie I'll get popcorn
I'll get Reese's Pieces it's easy to fall asleep in a theater so most comfy
It's the best sleep I'll ever get in my life.
It's really nice.
I get like full rim sleep.
When you accept that you don't want to watch whatever movie you're watching and you just
want to sleep.
Yeah.
Nice most restful sleep.
I took, I had a really good sleep during No Time to Die.
Nice.
And then there was a big explosion woke me up, brought me right back into it.
Whoa, that's it, you just unlocked a new way to like punctuate sentences.
With a chip crunch.
That was really good.
Do it again.
you please say something awesome and then crunch a chip awesome like I woke up
this morning and I I took a shower. Oh, my really sells it. You know, I can't
imagine that's what you eat a chip in the shower or no, not be eating them
chips. Now, I know I know making up for lost time. I cleaned our shower this
morning. Yeah, I don't know last night. I cleaned it. Okay, now I clean my
spring early shower. That's right. I use you guys use your body to clean your
shower. I use my shower to clean my body. Yeah, sometimes I have my body to
clean my body in my shower to clean my shower. Do you guys use a loofah a rag or
your hand? I'm a hand man. Whoa, I'm a hand man never in my life. Have I used a
loofah? No, yeah, I'm not a loofah. I would I say most usually hand. I'll
sometimes a washcloth. I'm a washcloth. Use
your hands, though, because it's
get dirty. Yeah, you clean it. You don't like use it over and I don't really
want to be shoving a washcloth on my butthole. That's like how you get your
clean though. No, because you if you stick you can this is this guy this guy knows. I
didn't realize it until it's caught somewhat recently but you can put soap in
your butthole. Oh yeah. You stick a finger in your butt. But it's about the
abrasion because a piece of soap if soap touches shit it doesn't just make it
disappear. It eliminates it. It just covers it with soap. Well you're still. You have to
you have to use. I'm not going to go all the way. No, if you touch soap on something
dirty it go it you do put the water on your ass in your hole a little bit but
then it doesn't gross you out when you use it on your face are you like this
was in my book I use my washcloth on my face we talk like when you shave when I
shit and I have a different rag for that different different I use a two rag
system any washcloth do you have 15 16 one for every part of color coordinated
brown for my butt white for my face I do you're confused all the time like wait a
Wait, but I have a white face and a white ass
Or did I do it opposites on purpose is that my sister I like that you just had your butt is like a black man's
But I have a pitch black, but you got a nice booty. I have a shining African, but the rest of my body is pink
It did take until I think I was like 19 or 20
When I first realized like it wasn't like methodical
But I realized that I would like most times that I took a shower. I washed my butt and then I washed my hair afterwards
Yeah hair is better than fit. Well, I guess it drips. Well, it's just I was just like I'm probably putting
But like you're not that's so far removed nobody's gonna be like smelling your hair later and be like there's poop in your hair
I'm sorry. It's not it's not. Yeah, it's not it's not like that. You are physically going to have poop in here
It's just it's just a gross thing. Yeah, it's the gross
It's the same grossness of like if you like just clean the floor and then you like drop
Like something that you were eating onto the floor where it's like technically it's not brings it to a no
It's just yeah, it's just like it's like a it's like a it's like a Victorian miasma thing
It's like this has this like it's like just logical. It's like
If you walk into the bathroom and it smells like poop you're gonna feel disgusted. You're covered in poo
I do feel like the poop like what what am I smelling? I'm definitely getting poop particles in them
Yeah, well, okay, so yeah, so poop can stay in the air for hours
But it can't go in your hair on your hand in 10 seconds. No. No, I'm agreeing with you
I'm starting to understand your point. It's also, it's pooping after you take a shower feels similar. Oh, oh, I hate that
Yeah, when you had a wet butthole. Yeah, it's like I just cleaned every single part of it. And then there's like no, you can't wipe it
So you just gotta leave it in there. Hold on. Sorry. I have to record something at like 3. You just remembered? Yeah
What time is it? It's like 2 45. I don't we're not gonna get like the whole episode done
We can do an hour episode in 13 minutes.
I'm gonna pause.
What's so funny about the timer?
How else will you know what time how long we've been recording?
Math is funny to me because I'm such a literature guy.
Is it because you're such a cretin?
Nope.
Yeah, because you're such a dope.
He's doing the thing too, the fucking thing that I do every time.
you know there's a noise upstairs. Yeah, I mean I'll you got to you got to look
up, but you don't have to go wait. What was that? Do you freak out with the
noise? He always is like like we'll be talking about something and recording
and he'll he'll hear a noise upstairs and he'll go.
I feel like it's the same thing when like when you're on the when you're on
the train and like someone's acting crazy and the person across he was like
Yeah, I don't care. Yeah
I
Love doing that
Have you guys seen the the videos were like somebody gets in a fight on the train or something and it's Mike Tyson got in
The fight on the plane like yesterday what?
Oh, I saw that just now there was a guy who was like a drunk guy was annoying Mike Tyson on a plane
I think yesterday and then I don't it's a video of I saw a picture of it
Just like being really annoying and it's a bloody Tim in the headline
There's a video from behind that guy, just Mike Tyson going like
Whoa!
Dude, like when he was punching him?
Yeah, and he's like bloody after that.
He says he, like Mike Tyson is like
That's so cool.
It looks like he's in like Coach.
No, it's First Class for sure.
Bro Boy?
It's like a booth thing.
It's like, it seems like that.
Oh, okay.
I think this was a restaurant.
Maybe I saw a different video.
I think this was Applebee's.
Mike Tyson is like a very interesting guy to me.
Cause he's like actually a fucking lunatic.
Yeah.
And he like talks all the time about like, there was a guy that he was, he was like, he
was like a lunatic.
Yeah.
me because he's like actually a fucking lunatic yeah and he like talks about all
the time but like there was a guy that he was he like the guy taught him how to
box and basically told him like you are going to become a super weapon with no
conscience and he was like 15 he's like okay and he just did that and then he had like kids
and shit and he was like oh wait I need to like I can't just punch stuff all the
time right and then he became and now he's trying to get back into boxing again
yeah you know what the plane he's only 23 years old he could be 60 to be 70 years
old I don't know 65 that's great he's really crazy yeah I think being a living
weapon is one of the coolest things ever yeah like really I'm talking gun yeah
living weapon and also having like a 10-year stint on Adult Swim is like yeah
yeah and he was like good friends with like Norm MacDonald I need someone in
the face it says here yet he appeared at San Francisco's 420 Cannabis Festival
whoa so he smokes weed - I really need a celebrity who has swords for arms like
like grafted on blades like Baraka yeah like Baraka but no hands just just
yeah just this happened after the 420 festival
herb yeah this is gonna come out like yeah so he'll probably do it again okay
he did this at the 520 fest here's a here's a headline from November 2021 okay
so I'm going even farther Mike Tyson used sex to keep me keep himself from
committing murder Mike Tyson said earlier this week that he died from
psychedelic dude he's awesome he went on podcast and he ate like like like a
heroic dose of mushrooms at the beginning of it you're big you're big
Jake Paul no big Mike Tyson clip on podcast guy I've seen I need a guy who
acts like this but he has like a cannon and yeah there's a there's a clip where
Joe Rogan talks about how the reason he made his table bigger on his podcast like
the bigger space between him and the other guests because he had Mike Tyson
on he was really scared of them and he was like I have to get a new table so
cool dude yeah I would get a smaller table if it was Mike Tyson yeah I get it
I get one of the tables I put in the middle of the pizza yeah it would be
like a prank those are for say I tell you box you hold it down and then you
slide the pizza out. No it's not. What? Slide what pizza out? You hold it down onto one
end of the slice, you like flip it like that and then pull it up. That may be true but
that's one of the things that you'll see like somebody posted a TikTok video of it.
Like this is actually what it's for. It's like I don't believe you. You made that up.
I don't care if that's what it's for or not. I was under the impression it was a stacking,
when you stack like 10 pizzas on top of each other so it doesn't cave in. Yeah. That makes
takes more. It could be multi-purpose. Do you guys know what bottle caps are secretly for?
What? Keeping in drink. Look at this. Okay. So they're for falling out. Okay. They're
for disguising yourself as a different person. Yeah. Did you just turn off your mic? Did
I? Oh yeah. I think I did. Just turn the switch on. Is it on now? No. No. You just turned
it off. This episode's going amazing. This is the best episode ever. This is the best
episode we've ever done. Wait, what's going on? Can you hear me? No, what the fuck? Alright,
alright let's just abandon ship
lost episode. Hello, hello
can you hear this? Yeah I can hear you eating now
it only works when he eats. I guess
just don't mess with the switch, just leave the switch on. Can you hold that for me?
I am not holding that for you. Do you guys ever, we were talking about showers, do you guys ever take baths?
no. We just got a place that, well actually you guys had a tub the whole time
disgusting. I'm too big for a tub
I'm too big for bats in general. I need like a king-size tub if I want to fit.
Me too.
A jacuzzi tub.
It's not fun. It's not- it's also not like-
I need like a- like a- like a...
9 foot deep, uh, 11 foot long tub.
That's a pool.
That's a damn pool, you idiot!
You what?
11 feet long seems too long.
No.
And all it does to-
How wide?
-if anything.
Uh, 11. 11 by 11.
I want an 8.5" x 11" tub.
That's not going to fit.
That's going to fit my papers though.
Perfectly.
We need to get them wet.
You need an even soak on all pages.
When you're doing a temporary tattoo,
you gotta get it wet.
It has to be perfect. Or like a rice paper, make a spring roll.
Do you have a bubble bath in there?
I haven't done a bubble bath in a minute.
I take baths pretty often, but I might have to add bubble baths.
You should be able to put the bubble bath stuff
into the shower head
Into the shower head and it puts bubbles out and you can take a bubble shower. Oh, I like sitting in my nasty
Like you're okay, well clearly who I'm not gonna just put stuff it would be a product that someone designed to do
When I come up with an imaginary product, it's not like you're just like you don't just be like, well, it wouldn't work
Oh, no, they're in my brain. They're developing one that would work that way. Obviously
I know if you put bubble bath stuff in your shower head, it's not gonna work. I wasn't looking I wasn't looking inside your brain
I'm sorry. That's no what you're doing is you're trying to pick me apart. You're trying to tear me down
Just thinking I want to take a bubble shower. You're not thinking
That's what I'm saying
Bubble shower incorporated stuff. Yeah, mr. Wonderful. Yeah, mr. Bubble
I'm just pitching something completely impossible.
- Wait a minute, all I know is I wanna do this.
- Wait, wait, okay, so clear up some things for me.
How does this work?
I don't know, that's what I'm here for, idiot.
Mr. Wonderful.
- You're supposed to invent it for me, dumbass.
- How'd you get so damn fucking rich
if you weren't inventing anything, huh?
You idiot. - You're supposed to have one,
I read your book, you're supposed to have
one million inventions a day.
- Walking into Shark Tank and being like,
all right, before I start my pitch,
Mr. Wonderful, what do you want most in the world?
(laughing)
Okay, I'm inventing that.
- Okay, my product is new hair.
- A boat that can't kill anybody.
(laughing)
- A safety boat.
- A boat that brings people back to life.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he's a man.
- He's cool as fuck.
- Oh man, remember we almost went to his seminar?
That would have been awesome.
- We were supposed to in Boston, he had a seminar.
- Yeah, we were gonna go to his,
we were gonna put on suits and do a bunch of acid
and go to this seminar in Malden.
- And Caleb got sick, he had a stomach ache.
was like I'm I feel so sick. I don't want to go. Yeah, basically we could have
been millionaires. We almost went and then I was like they were like what do
we do like, but we don't have our boss Caleb with us. We probably can't go.
It made us reconsider. Oh, I'm so nervous. You can't do something without Caleb.
We knew you were fucking ditching and we were like, we knew you reconsidered.
What kind of sick were you? I don't know. It was like fucking three years ago.
I remember this happening. It's a line he's lying bad food. Probably that
probably was a he ate bad food and he just went. Oh, I used to eat like such a
piece of shit in Boston. Awesome man. I ate I ate lamb and chicken over rice. I
eat peanut butter and jelly like three times a day. When I was healthy, that's
not healthy. That is not healthy. It's healthy. No, it's not like the worst
thing in the world, but it's not good for you. No PBJ is healthy. It's like
bread and sugar and no sugar.
- Tiny nuts.
- Oh really?
- No sugar.
- He said there's no sugar in it.
- Peanut butter and jelly?
- There's no sugar.
- It's pure sugar.
- It's not pure sugar.
It's peanut butter and it's jelly.
You can put sugar on it if you want, but that's it.
- What's happening?
- You don't put sugar on it.
- I'm gonna pause it now.
- And that's the first time I crapped myself.
- That was the first time?
- That was the first time I crapped myself.
now when we pause it. I'm the special guest. I'm Casey Kasem. Casey Kasem? I'm Casey Kasem's
brother. Can you do Shaggy next? I'm also named Casey. It's Casey Kasem. Can you do J-Lo? It's
short for Ken Christmas Kasem. Who is Casey Krasem? He was the voice of Shaggy on the news.
I'm the new Scooby Doo.
(laughter)
I'm the new...
He was the voice of Shaggy in the voice of Radio.
I was so fucking heartbroken to see Shaggy on the news.
Yeah, I know.
Me too.
That's what he did.
That's the last thing I was expecting him to be.
Yeah, eaten by a monster.
(laughter)
He finally got eaten up by a monster.
Shaggy got eaten up by a monster.
He tried to pull his damn head off.
Shaggy got eat up by monster.
Yah.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I think I had too much sugar.
You didn't have any sugar.
Whoa, check this out.
Yep, okay.
Did they have a Twinkie the kid?
You need to.
Did they put a leash on Scooby Doo or no?
No, never.
He has a collar though.
You can't match.
I know he has a collar.
They put a damn leash on Shaggy before they put one on Scooby.
That's in case he gets lost though.
But he's like a human.
But he would probably just say, "I'm a human."
I don't know.
gets lost though, but he's like a human, but he would probably say I'm with
those
don't get it. Yeah, yeah, well, he probably rhyme with rose rice. Yeah,
rhyme with rose rice, french fries, right? Yeah, I'm with those guys and
then someone would say french fries and who goes
that dude loves food. Wait, oh my God and don't get me started about his
little bitch nephew scrappy. He's a really poorly trained dog scrappy. No
Scooby. Yeah, no, that's what I was thinking. It's like they should have put
it to. They should have. Do you think it solves? Do you think every crime every
every guy? I mean, it's raggy. I feel like I feel like shagging and school.
You must have a really strong friendship because if I had a friend who's poop I
had to pick up in a plastic bag, I think our relationship will be very strained,
but they eat so much food together. He uses the toilet. I don't think he uses
toilet he uses the time I don't think he does I wouldn't him yeah he goes outside
and Scooby uses the toilet Shaggy cuz Shaggy and Scooby just poop and leave
like it's not that no everybody's gonna be like who's dog Oh Scooby-Doo awesome
they're gonna be like that oh Scooby-Doo that's fun oh it's Scooby-Doo's poop
yeah I remember you I'm gonna collect this I'm gonna see scooby snacks yeah
he's eating straight graham crackers every day I mean I was gonna go everyone
also he like a whole turkey. They did. Yeah, I guess the none of them none of
them clean up his poop because there was that one episode where they go to jail
because he didn't clean up his poop. Yeah, there is Shaggy and Scooby are both in
at least in the movie both vegetarian. Really? That's not. And Velma wears a
thong. Yeah, Velma shows her. Oh my god. And Mr. Bean's name is Mr.
Mondavarious of Spooky Island. Oh yeah, Mr. Bean's in that movie.
well I'll let mr. free holy in that movie they call him mr. Monde various I'm a
Mexican that's where then where did they go in the movie
spooky island spooky island in Cancun no no I can't go it's in Mexico no it's not
I've been there you've not been a huge you know blow out a skull made the same
sing the outcast sing their national anthem that I was cast song in the land
and that that that there is always something going on.
We know
like I was just guessing as he said I was also guessing the lyrics to the
lyrics.
We're both guessing the lyrics.
That's how it goes.
Spooky Island was in Australia.
Fuck!
Is that the filming location or is that where it actually was supposed to be?
Well the filming location was Australia.
It says here that there's an Australian girl in it.
Remember?
Yeah.
Well it also it says here that it's a little Fisher.
She was Australian.
says here that the movie though the titular wife of Borat in the movie she
is canonically married to Borat yeah
she's my husband his name's Borat he's names boring his name's Borat my name is
for Tina isn't her name Mary Jane her name is Scooby's wife no way her name's
Mary Jane my favorite name yeah did that movie was supposed to be rated R yeah
yeah, the film that rated are then they edited it to a PG. I would do anything
to see the Velma see all the the the the and freezing the phrasing on the I'm
reading spooky spooky island Wikipedia page the phrasing here under notes and
trivia. This is the only notes in trivia the the scenes filmed at spooky island
were in Australia at Tangalooma Island Resort where over four hundred cast and
crew took over the resort for six weeks and transformed it into an exclusive
don't set the best for
Scooby Casting Crew members, but
swarming yeah, they do a cool, just
resort climbing, climbing up the
building like World War Z. You see
each other.
Yeah, there's switching yeah, there
yeah, they're like so they're putting
up statues of Mr. Bean everywhere,
like what is this? Yes, separating
like parents for the dark opelix
ritual.
Yeah, I want I I wonder how what
was what they cut out of the R-rated one. Weed, for sure. Weed, sex,
violence, drugs, and they kept in rock and roll.
We think they cut out the adult themes maybe. Stark depictions of
prejudice. It's Australia, the aboriginals on the island. Yeah, Mr. Bean's character
says like and you don't want to go over there.
They kept that in but now he's talking about the graveyard.
They CGI'd the word "ghosts"
They CGI'd the word "indigenous" above. They CGI'd it out.
they're turning into invisible yeah yeah yeah Scooby-Doo and then they made a
second one - oh my god monsters unleashed and tell you what those movies are good
as fuck they're cool they're fun to watch they're really funny
Scooby is up to his old tricks in Scooby-Doo - monsters only I would say
that I'm laying and I would say I would say the monsters are - yeah but this time
they're real. Peter Boyle is more of a Scoob guy. Yeah. Fuck you. Wait, what do you mean
more of a Scoob guy? The new movie Scoob. I didn't see it. I didn't see it either. I
didn't see it. My nephew probably saw it. But I grew up on that what's new Scooby Doo
shit. Yeah. They got all the Scooby Doo shit on HBO Max dude. I've been sessioning some
Scooby Doo. They have a pup named Scooby Doo. Remember when they did that in the 80s they
tried to do that. They tried to make every show have a baby version. They have that one
that's the live-action like origin story. It's a great way to reboot.
I mean it's a great way to sell merch. You ever watch Muppet Babies?
What? Yeah of course. I watched so much. We had a Muppets Baby VHS in our, we had a
VHS player in our car. We watched the same Star Wars Muppet Babies episode
every time we went on like a long trip and then on my birthday when we
went to that that seafood place I looked in the bar was playing that Muppet
Babies episode. It was so weird. There's a sign of that it's your that you should
get it. It was a sign that it was my birthday. It's a sign that the bar is run by a pedophile.
This is my favorite episode. Can you bring your kids in here? Why does a
- Why does a pedophile sound like that?
- What the hell?
- What?
- That's your pedophile voice?
(laughing)
- I just did a pedophile accent.
What's wrong with that?
(laughing)
- Interesting, okay.
- That's a regular pedophile's voice.
- Well, that's just not where I thought you were gonna go.
- You know how the pedophile in your neighborhood
didn't walk up to you and say,
I have comic books at my house.
He didn't, and you went to his house and...
(laughing)
- No.
- What?
No, I did that. Okay, Alex did that. Alex did that to people. That was a crazy voice. I know exactly what you're talking about.
You know what, believe it or not, we didn't have a neighborhood pedophile growing up.
There was a guy in my neighborhood who was just kind of weird and he tried to, he did try to talk to me about, I didn't get molested,
He tried to talk to me about comic books and stuff and then like I think I was
talking about like X-Men or something and then he just stood there and tried to
like, like it was clear that this is probably just like an old autistic guy
and he tried to grill me for an hour and then like, I guess, I was like oh yeah
mom that guy that guy talked to me about comic books and he's like she was like
"Oh, the guy who stares at all the young women at the pool?"
(laughter)
And then my mom started calling him Geico.
- It's such a sad world for these old autistic men
who just want to keep up with the times and feel cool,
and they just want to talk to kids
and ask them about comic books and video games
and condom sizes.
(laughter)
It's just tough out there, you know?
I feel bad.
You have to respect your elders and go to their houses.
- My mom would call him Geico
because of those Geico commercials where they say,
"I always feel like someone's watching me."
- If Michael Jackson wasn't famous
guy with a job who lived in your neighborhood and looked still like that
would you like your yeah yeah like foot like no no no no no no no no no no no
crazy yeah dead bleached skin and he dressed the same would you let your kids
hang out with him if he may if he's still have made a video called thrill
yeah but it's a different video he has neverland in his backyard nope he has
has not he has a he has a DVR. I'm generally it's about all he's got. I'm
generally not going to let my kids hang out with like a an adult that they
don't know. Yeah, what if he's your okay? What if he's your best friend?
Yep, he's your best friend, but he has any as a child care license, but he
also has a pedophile license. Yeah, but you don't know you don't know about it,
but I don't know about it. Okay, every day every day to file licenses is
printed on the back of his child care license at one time. He dropped his
childcare license and he went don't look at that and you're like you didn't
because you were such good friends with him yeah. So with this hypothetical in
mind would you let your kid go over there and eat a spaghetti dinner. This is
a cautionary tale of the the power of this is what if you had it's not okay
we made up story. What if you okay would you let your kid go over and have a
spaghetti dinner with him if you had a hundred other kids. No they weren't
gonna go. I love all my kids equally. Oh no it's tough. I had to go around you
know, but I also I need to like I need to put him to the friendship test. You
I need to see what he's all about.
I need to see how I am a friend.
- Can we do that right now?
What's the friendship test?
- I think it's like a dinner, it's like breakfast,
it's an activity.
- It's food, it's a lot of food.
- Wait, dinner and then breakfast,
so a spend the night in the middle?
- No, no, no, they're separate.
It's like separate tests.
- You have to do trials.
- You guys have all been through these,
you know, inadvertently.
I'm not actually trying to do it,
I've had breakfast with all of you. I've had dinner with all of you. Oh my god. He was setting us up
Great I got tricked into being your friend
Activities with you I didn't realize I was doing this whole I didn't realize it was a test I did
Yeah, I was curious why you brought a clipboard
Speaking of Cameron you're in the 96% activities
But 33rd on breakfast, so we're gonna need to go numbers. No, right. I would be the other way around
around. I'm great at getting breakfast. I'm bad at activities. I feel like I
would honestly I would probably say you're better about watching a movie. I
don't even know if I've ever gotten breakfast with you. I think we've gotten
breakfast before. We went and got breakfast at the Taco Bell on the way to
the lake. Oh yeah. Damn. Oh yeah. That wasn't breakfast though. That doesn't
count. A friend's breakfast is at a diner. Yeah exactly. I've had breakfast with you.
And it's all about splitting the check. That's the real thing. I don't know.
the test. You know what I watched last night? We're not friends. Did a rewatch
butterfly effect. Oh so good. So it's the it's the fucking like I realized last
night. You just did it. So good. Yeah we do that. It's one of those things like where it's just so really good.
It's just so really it's like that movie is in like the same like criteria is
like a mortal technique dance with the devil.
Yeah, it is.
It's like your friend's older brother shows you that movie and he's like, like
you accidentally watch it or your friend's older brother shows it to you.
And it's like, this is the most fucked up thing you're ever going to see.
Yeah.
Cause that movie, like literally every scene is just like, here's like the most
twisted fucked up thing we can think of.
he has a fat goth roommate who fucks.
Is that the guy from uh... Ethan Suplee, yeah.
Scientologist.
Scientologist? For real? Yeah. Damn, that makes my name as Earl make sense, because Jason Lee
used to be a part of the faith. Probably got him hooked on it. Yep, maybe. It is addictive.
Yeah. I want to do it so badly. Yeah, I would love to. Do you want to do a butterfly effect?
No, I want to do Dianetics. He wants to do the duck butterfly effect. He wants to save a woman from an
explosion. You're sinking in so much money into the church
that by the time you're like all right is fun and i'm out yeah whatever you can
leave your you know billion you're going to do just one
thing right you can just go for one that's not a spot like that's just you
have to go to you can just do it for like one year
you'll sign told us to make it quick
me big bird
and i think i know that i don't think so i was a good thing
paper
michael pena
uh... yeah yeah i think i see a lot of
michael kane is a that's not what i'm gonna come and see if you're a big
start naming people like that like in five years and then he became a
Scientologist in 1999 and then a 2000 he got ant-man what's it called
crash no it's it definitely is a cheat code yeah yeah yeah it's how big we're
going on Sesame Street I think we should do that we should Chloe Fineman is a
sign we should start our we should choose a book to start our own
Scientology we need to change it to the - so it's just normal Christianity gets
you everything in Hollywood it's crazy that every Scientologist is the most
beautiful person in the world. Every Scientologist is like the most beautiful person.
Not Elizabeth Moss.
Elizabeth Moss is the...
She was the blueprint, yo.
Yeah, she was.
Andy Dick.
Oh my god.
Have you seen that video?
I sent it to Cameron.
I sent it to Cameron. Did I send it to you guys?
Just the caption of that video made me laugh.
It's a video Andy Dick got the shit kicked out of him in Las Vegas.
It said, it was like a video that had one of those like built-in captions that's like on the video.
Yeah.
It's in giant letters, "Andy Dick beaten to a pulp."
And it's a video of him and he's like, his face is just like all puffy and he's like,
"I don't even know what happened. Oh, I just, I don't know about the ground."
He probably tried to finger a bouncer.
Yeah, no, and then the woman, the woman's like, the woman interviewing him is like,
Andy, Andy, what did they look like?
And he just goes, "Gangster."
(laughter)
- A gangster beat up.
- Gangster beat me to a pulp.
- This one's for Phil Harmon.
- Andy did beat me to a pulp.
It's such a funny, weird words.
- What's the other one?
- Beat to a pulp.
- Cat Williams getting beaten up by the 12 year old.
- And the kid is like talking shit
and Cat Williams is like trying to be like,
he's like, "You can say whatever you want, man,
if you have to do it go ahead he's like trying to be like like like full
philosophical about a 12 year old beating him up he's like really you're
gonna choose violence okay right it's like on the ground he started it to just
so crazy yeah I mean he seemed like he wasn't going through yeah and not and
he's also not small he's not like like Kevin Hart's like like built oh yeah
Williams is like he's all he's all he's all going through it he's fucking there's
all zoot suit he literally is he's just bones under that have you seen it's him
on some radio show and it's clear that he does not want to be there and he just
keeps making fun of the host world the world's with Orson Welles I do not
believe there's any damn aliens going through here no it's like like this
woman makes fun of his like hair or something and then he's just like brutal
to her for the rest of the episode and he's like, "Do you cook for your kids?"
And she's like, "Yeah, I make a really good broccoli." And he's like, "Huh?"
I love him, dude. He's so fucking funny.
There's no way you could fuck up broccoli. I fuck up broccoli.
Dude, I fuck up some broccoli if you put it in front of me.
Dude, I made steaks the other night. Whoa.
They were the worst. Do tell.
They sucked. That was the second time I ever tried cooking a steak and I have no
idea how to cook a steak. So I watched some video and it was like...
You need a thermometer and you need a smoker.
Well, it was just saying like...
$600 worth of materials.
It was telling you how long to sear it on either side.
But I bought... I didn't even think about this.
I bought like the thinnest steak that I used.
It was like this thin.
You stupid, stupid idiot.
So, it was just like a piece of fucking jerky, dude.
It sucked.
I remember that.
You bought a flank steak?
No, it was a prime rib.
Oh, air fryer salmon, very delicious.
Is the air fryer working?
I haven't cooked meat in like years.
Yeah, I have a big ass annoying one too.
It's great.
We just got a toaster oven with our apartment for free.
that's actually using that they are yes as for what i was running on
for what it's
movement that you're talking about a toaster i remember and i wanted to bring
the toaster oven here and then i realized you know it's a little
convection oven one of the yet yet the front now can get it as basically an air
for i've been put it yet
now it's like an air fryer with more things the power of air
yeah out of
power can't find anything in it metal
yet uses metal instead of our you know for transformers
i think i'm gonna be good
s'mores in it
yes it's a good idea more is that our apartment
yeah little fire washable fire
the bonfire is this is the first it's like
the
the hot hot hot
so it is goes up the other railing like a few years ago i got out of my
life
is like this is a remix of the
it's got a insulated your room with good
i think i think this point is a prize for the idea and
You can't fucking--
Dude, your apartments are so fucking dark, dude.
It echoes so much in our apartment.
Firework.
My girlfriend was in my room, and I was in the bathroom.
And I went to the bathroom because it was the first couple of weeks
we were seeing each other, and I didn't want to fart in front of her.
And I was in the bathroom trying to hide a fart.
That's a necessary detail.
Yeah, it's a necessary detail.
I was trying to hide a fart, and it was so long and loud
In the other side of the apartment, I think that's certainly a you problem. I heard I heard her in my room go
What the fuck?
Wait, so your complaint is my apartment is so bad
That my supersonic fart was hurt on the other side. You shouldn't be able to hear a fart from the other side of your part
I got really
It depends on how loud it doesn't matter you can hear anything at any distance if it's loud enough
I think you can also like I had the door shut you're not supposed to hear anything
But you went to the bathroom, but then you you ripped it like you let it loose
You have to still like try to spread a butt cheek. I didn't spread the bush red would make it quieter. Yeah
That's what you do what I did not hurt something you supposed to if you spread oh my god, dude
I got so good at doing that in class like not even just hands-free just spread
Yeah, yeah, completely take apart and then farting and then making a face like
like who did that pointing at hand up? Did you hate anyone else smell that it
actually smells like fucking fart all around me right now. I just there is
nothing funnier than just like a quiet room and so that in high school that
only happened my like entire school up to college that only happened one time
this kid this kid farted. It was the probably because it was only happened
one time was like the funniest thing I've ever experienced. It was my sat this
in front of me. You're not allowed to talk or make any noise or you get like whatever.
Yeah.
The test gets thrown out and this girl in front of me like sneezed and it was like
*fart noise*
*laughter*
So loud.
It pushed out the fart, the sneeze?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, that's a combo.
Dude, that's awesome.
That you know exactly why she farted too.
No, yeah, yeah.
That's so awesome.
The worst is when you're like just alone with somebody and then you laugh really,
you're laying down, you laugh really hard and just one slips out.
Never happened to me.
That happened to me.
Yeah, that doesn't happen to me either.
When you're laying down alone with someone.
*laughter*
Yeah, that happened to me a couple nights ago.
(laughing)
- Laying down on your own.
- Laying down and farting.
- That sentence made sense in my head.
- And you giggle so much that you fart.
(laughing)
- I'm not having a good one today.
My brain's not on.
- That is such a funny mental image.
- You want some guava or anything?
- Stranger.
(laughing)
- Stranger, I'm laying on my belly.
I'm just like watching something on my phone.
- Laying on your belly.
- With my feet up in the air.
- On the train, on the seats of the train.
- I'm watching like a YouTube video
and I'm just going, "He he he he he he."
(laughing)
- Look at the other guy in the train.
- Oops, oopsie.
- Yeah.
- Did you hear that?
- Please tell me you didn't hear that,
but we've all been there, right?
- I'm sorry. - Not me though.
- You have to get off the next stop.
- Yeah.
- Dude, I never farted so bad.
- You never farted so bad in your life.
I never for so bad so bad of my life in my two minutes a great teacher miss
Escobar, because I used to I used to fart in columbia
I used to fart in class when I was in third grade and I had a you used to
agree to leave the room whenever I want. They were they were like you such a
distracting, but then she gave me the power to leave the classroom and also
the association of like when he leaves the classroom. It means he's farting
I took it. It's awful. Did it's pretty cool. Are you the class clown with the
farts for sure? Yeah, you're the class farter than you weren't a clown. Yeah,
clown doesn't fart. I was a clown. I can have some of the time doesn't eat or
drink. I was a class slave.
No, you weren't. Yeah, it was. No, I got forced to do stuff. Did you do homework?
What the hell is this? What did you get? My my move in in class is always I
everyone thought it was funny when I jumped over a desk. I was just like I
like just fall a jumper doesn't fall all the time. I remember one time I
following is a pretty big. I was a smart board wizard. I
would do yeah
more stuff was funny. I would do that, too. I remember one time I didn't have
a smart board me and my friend. We were like giving a presentation in like our
French class and they're on the smart board and we both started pressing the
smart for the same time and it somehow like brought up the on screen keyboard
and also just like filled the entire screen with this random letters and we
are laughing so hard to we got in trouble. Nice it was pretty funny. I
didn't have a smart where we had a piece of wood. You didn't have a piece of
wood. We had a piece of what is called damn pencil. We didn't burn. We didn't
even have pencils. Yeah, we had we had clay. We had to use people. You're so
fucking stupid.
It actually is.
I used our blood to make the vampire academy.
Wood and clay and leaves.
I should do that.
Top ten proofs the Illuminati is real.
Oh yeah I forgot there was a list that goes on.
Anyways these are theories on how the Illuminati is real.
Warning this may or may not be a really stupid list.
I didn't realize your phone was balanced on your foot and I was like whoa.
You just like memorized that.
We're waiting for your chance.
That would be sick.
Number one Obama's forehead is in the shape of a triangle.
one I believe I believe this one I'm gonna double yeah I'm not sure I believe
that is Obama's forehead Obama's forehead I feel like a triangle forehead is
something I would have noticed by now you'd think that they would show a photo
Obama's got to be like a person who isn't someone I know in real life that
I've seen a picture I've seen him in person I've seen so many pictures of
Obama yeah so I've seen Obama in person oh yeah madam two so's he was standing
there. He kind of does have a there's like a show me the triangle. Let me see it's
not shaped like a triangle but he kind of has like a triangle you see that so like
kind of discoloration where it's like eyebrows meet. Yeah I'd say that's
probably a lighting thing though. Yeah but on this photo. It sure does look like it.
Do you think they're talking about this photo specifically or does he always have that? I don't know. Let me check some other. Look up Obama's triangle. This one he's got a damn fly on his head.
That's Mike Pence. Remind you of anybody? Yeah, Mike Pence. Oh, that's Mike Pence. Whoops.
Uh, no, I don't really see a triangle. Wait a second. I just saw, I just found this photo
of him. Whoa. This could actually, I mean, that's, see, everybody's talking about the
triangle hair. Nobody's talking about this. Obama's hair is made out of grown chia seeds.
Yeah, that is true. I've seen him on the commercials with that. Yeah. No one is talking about this.
look right here he has green chia seed hair oh my god damn he's got to be in
the Illuminati yeah yeah or the top look it seems like every president that we've
ever had has had green chia seed hair here's Donald Trump in a clear it do you
think you think it has to do with the Joker no I don't think serene hair I
don't think I'm a red face I think the Illuminati I mean look at this
- One of our most famous presidents.
- Is that?
- That is, um.
- Robert O'Kamiyagi?
- No.
- No, just guess.
- Keep guessing Asian guys, go.
- That is president. - Tiger Woods.
I'm a good guy.
(laughing)
I'm a really good guy, I guess Tiger Woods.
- That is President Don Johnson.
- No, that's an SJW.
- That's the next president.
This is actually the person--
- Put that away.
- Yeah, 'cause Biden's not getting a second term.
- You know when you were a kid and you didn't know who the,
like you didn't know who any of the people were in. I wish I liked when I
when the person who was running was just a stranger. Yeah, I have I have a
really distinct memory of I didn't really know who who Dick Cheney was
really when like Obama was Obama was being like sworn in or whatever and my
grandfather was at our house and he was like he like he turned to me. He turned
to me and was like like oh like Dick Cheney's not at the ceremony. He's
probably out. He's probably a torturing someone right now, like just trying to
get one at the last minute and I was like I don't like who is that home for the
inauguration. I feel like that was a school day. There's a kid in my I don't
know yeah, that was a school day. I watched it at home to it might have been
it might have been after you were going to say like something you weren't. I
don't think I was watching. That's what I was expecting to maybe I wasn't
watching it live. I was definitely because my grandfather was not at school.
I can tell you that
I feel he map is a tiny little shirt on Cameron. I need a ride home.
Please. I remember there's this kid in my sixth grade class and he said in
front of the whole class after Obama's inauguration, he's like the whole time I
was waiting here.
Jesus and everyone was just like just looking at him and like he got
reprimanded pretty hard, but I was like damn yeah. You my friend there were
have a future in the CIA. What were dad says though and then you're yeah yeah
that sounds cool to say yeah there was there were some people at in my town who
would sit in front of the post office with a table with like clipboards and
they would have a big banner on the front of their table as a picture of
Obama with a Hitler mustache. Yeah, yeah, that I did it he would yeah. I mean
hey they got shoot the hell out yeah.
There were kids no no
Number two, Jeff, fuel can't melt steel beams.
- Oh, hell no.
- I don't think that has much to do with the Illuminati.
- No.
- It seems like the comments on these
are saying the same thing.
- This is a bit something that a normal person
wouldn't think about, though.
I think you're rather weird if you're into
this type of stuff.
- Yeah.
- Regardless of what you believe,
what the hell does this have to do with the Illuminati?
- Here's something I saw on a sticker one time.
Dank memes melt steel beams.
- Could that be true?
- That's another clue.
- That's a sticker I saw at a restaurant.
- Wait, guys.
- I saw it in a restaurant bathroom.
Number three is kind of making me think more about the Obama one. Number three,
there are triangles in the Nazi swastika. First comment,
you mean the symbol Hitler stole from the Buddhists? No, the other one.
I mean, that's, yeah.
All right, let's draw one on, on Cameron's face. Okay.
We just got to let's count the triangle. Seriously don't guys stop.
Well, it's more of like, there's a square.
is a circle I would say. There's a square who's using that as a symbol of power.
Listen guys, I wouldn't know because I've never even seen one.
I don't know what they look like. Right angles are triangles.
Yep. What are you a fucking Nazi? I mean if you make a little line. Here's an
interesting theory here. Every triangle has three. What's the theory? Number four
the USA won its independence in a way too convenient year.
That's just true. Yeah. That's facts. I think it's just because they literally won in 1776.
1776 just looks good on paper. Yeah. And on July 4th, Independence Day.
On July 4th, no less. It's almost like they set it all up.
Yeah. I will say 1776 does look really good in like pin font.
Yeah. In cursive. The Dutch 7 in general is pretty fancy.
They did it really good. 1776 was like the the cool S. Dude it would have been way better if it was 1777.
No. That's an angel number. They should have waited. That's not an angel number. You always
say things are angel numbers that aren't angel numbers and I'm calling you out. 777 is an angel number.
777 is but 1777 is not. It's three of the same number in a row. But there's an angel number inside of that.
So what about 12 12 12? No. What about 111222? So that's two angel numbers.
that's to air their numbers of the angels.
They're lucky numbers. If you see that means that angels getting in contact
with you.
Joseph Gordon-Levitt like if you look at like the clock and it says
444.
I love it. Press record.
They all mean hit record.
Joe Joseph Gordon-Levitt Batman Dark Knight Rises.
Yep.
Joseph Gordon-Levitt Gordon-Levitt the adjustment Bureau Joseph Gordon-Levitt
third rock from the Sun Joseph.
Did you guys know he's he's Bruce Willis's brother?
Bruce Willis is dead at the end of Sixth Sense.
I just made that up.
He tried to look like his brother in Looper.
That's my impression of that motherfucker.
Joe Golo.
I'm kidding.
What was the movie they did together?
Looper.
Where they were like, "Just Gwen Leavitt."
"Do chipmunk cheeks."
They made him look crazy.
He looks fucked up.
He looks like a failed clone of Bruce Willis.
The point of that is to make him look like Bruce Willis.
Bruce Willis he doesn't look anything like he looks like like they should have
shaved his head you know when they you know when they do like like it's like oh
we use like AI to recreate this cartoon yeah yeah that's what it would look like
if you took Bruce Wayne from Batman the animated series and made him into like
an AI human that's real life Batman realistic Homer but with animated series
Batman looks like JGL and I wish that realistic Homer was actually done with
computer like if there was actually a program that you could put a picture of
Homer and it would make me a little Homer yeah I really like those things
that was because that was what I always whenever I saw that picture in like
middle school or whatever I would believe there's like oh you can just take
there's some program out there you can put a cartoon into and it will make a
real person out of it yeah have you guys seen realistic Woody no that was cool as
hell have you seen it's very cool have you seen realistic Heath Ledger I think
so they make him look like he's a Joker for Batman that's scary yeah they get
they get his they get the Joker's smile wrong though because it's a on this one
yeah I like I like number five here you know I'm gonna be it doesn't look so
realistic to me it's not realistic but it's like a fun and it's real other
characters and I see it actor the evil prospector Wow stuck in his day looks
very realistic. It looks like those books that was like "Who was Woody?" Yeah yeah yeah.
This is realistic. I could see myself walking in the bar. Here's a conspiracy here.
He kind of looks like my dad. Guys. Yeah what's the conspiracy? Number five
conspiracy on this list. President Bush. Yep. Mm-hmm. Oh what? Oh he was a bad
president but surely he was more likely to be a bent politician than an Illuminati
member from mr. veteran Bush was a beast so many things he did it was funny 9/11
Katrina and do you get oil from Iraq to please his Illuminati overlord he has
one of the best president moments of all time yeah where he's like where he's on
the golf course and he's like everyone's like we're going to find we're going to
find Saddam Hussein we're gonna find his mess weapons of mass destruction we're
gonna destroy them now watch this drive and then he just hits the golf ball so
That is so sick. It's so cool. He's paying homage to his favorite movie, Happy Gilmore.
I think it was a Happy Gilmore thing. Because I think now he interns for
Happy Madison. Oh good for him. Yeah, it's probably because of that. He's just trying
to rise up through the ranks. I thought he was doing a Bagger Vance thing. Oh maybe he was,
it was probably both. Yeah. It was probably a little bit of both. He's got like magic powers
like Will Smith in that movie. Yeah, Bagger Vance is real actually, I met him once. What?
I mean, are you guys saying Hitch? Or not Hitch? Hitch? That guy's real too. Hancock?
Hancock. I saw a few Hancocks asleep on a bench.
Hancock's gotta be...
Los Angeles.
I was like, "Oh, Hollywood's crazy. They have all these Hancock impersonators."
They're filming a Hancock sequel, yeah.
Taking a picture with a homeless guy.
Yo, just met Hancock on the street.
(laughing)
- It's like a bunch of pictures of you on the Walk of Fame
where it's pictures of you with Spider-Man and Batman
and just a homeless guy like,
all my favorite superheroes, Batman, Spider-Man, and Hancock.
(laughing)
- Hancock was swag, though.
- Dude, Hancock was so strong, he beat the shit out of me.
- He honestly might be the most powerful superhero ever.
(laughing)
He honestly might be.
Yeah, and he was on fucking drugs and alcohol.
- He was a god, though.
He's not even a superhero, he's just a god.
he was a god was it is what the movie is a little more of the movie but it was an
angel
i guess i mean i never i was like i said i'll tell you start on Tuesday is
necessary
my angel there's a team i was in hancock
mcguck is an angel
and angel
hanging out
with a really nice angels and god are at the
they've
their real
they figure in the hancock will not seen hancock i think i will not have a
fair i don't know i was allowed to watch and talk when it came out
i was because of the press name
hancock handcraft
is it based on a comic book urbans will smith's is a very long story it's
pretty bad
it's breaking that's been still again ok although it's breaking that from the
community breaks that i would have
number six george washington this list does not have a very clear through line
now the illuminati but i know what the truth towards washington never existed
the world israel the the the the the the the the the the the the the the the the
first normal mention number seven is the JFK assassination. I believe this
didn't happen.
I agree as hell.
I'm agree as hell.
I'm agree as Hall actually.
I'm agree
I'm agree as Hall the worst written comment that you can't even read it.
You you try to read it correctly dude. I'm agree as Hall. He was opposed to
the federal reserve the Illuminati didn't like that.
That's some supporting evidence. The Illuminati is there to stop people from...
I think the problem with the JFK assassination is everyone needs to stop talking about it
for like ten years and then everything about it will be like funny again. But everyone
says it's too much. Everyone's doing it. All this funny stuff has been said. Everyone's
said it a hundred times. We just need to take a break, pretend it doesn't exist for ten
years.
We need another president to get assassinated.
That could work too.
Interesting that you find the death of a president to be funny.
that's what i'm saying stuff like that
it's not we need to take a break
a break and then i'm talking about how much funny stuff came out about it's
just scary
i mean i don't know what can you imagine if a president died in today's day and
age with all the phones would be so great
with all the phones
it would be so crazy
we'd have so many videos of it i mean that's why that's why they have that's
why another one hasn't been assassinated because everyone wants the phones
I am addicted to this thing dude.
I cannot get enough.
It's like a candy bar to me.
It is.
It's basically like a candy bar that I can look up pictures of other candy bars on.
Yeah.
I love putting stuff up on my phone.
Oh my god, that's a perfect candy bar.
You're waking up in the morning and just reaching over my night table and taking a few bites
of my candy bar before going to bed for an hour.
Wait, I don't know what this entry is.
Number nine is red scarf deaths.
I've never heard of that.
That's from, it's like people who got red scarf disease. I'm gonna Google that. Yeah, me too.
I don't fucking know. I knew it! I was just waiting for him to say. Facebook posts say
is Kate's PolitiFact says Kate Spade worked with the Clintons and suggests
they were involved in her death. Oh yeah, that's true. Kate Spade killed herself. No, she was
killed by Hillary. She was killed by David. Because she was killed by Hillary
because her brother-in-law David Spade was too funny and he was about to do the
funniest impression of Hillary on SNL. What's his show called at night?
Like Buzz Off with David Spade that was his late-night show or something?
That's where all of his guests ride the Sibian. Yeah that's a good show.
Yeah. Oh you know who they had on that show before she passed? Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Really? I saw that episode. Lights Out. She busts a fat nut.
bader Ginsburg basically first no-hand squirt
squirt bader squirt Berg squirt bader squirt Burke I wish she was still alive
which which justice of the of the the highest court in the land would you like
to see squirt the most Sonya Sotomayor I think so to my or might be my number one
I need to see I need to see RBG on the cover of a magazine under my mattress
Thomas wouldn't squirt for anything I could make him you could not make how
How would you make, alright I'd like to see you try, how would you make Clarence Thomas
squirt?
Shirk him off!
First I take him out to dinner, I feed him a bunch of Oreos.
No.
He just comes everywhere.
Oreos are filled with white cream.
That's a good point.
You don't have to build up white cream in the body and squirt it out.
The Oreo cookie makes black poop, the white cream makes white cream.
That sounds true.
It's like a bird.
That's because it is true.
Yeah, it's like a bird.
and when you put, especially when you put Oreos in Clarence Thomas, he has a
yeah. He has a medical thing to that's the other thing. We didn't he's got
he's got Oreo spleen. He's got Oreo squirt disease and the Oreo squirt
comes out of it. He goes to the doctor. He's like doctor every time I eat
Oreos. I squirt everywhere and they're like oh, I would never we've never seen
this before. Can we call it the Clarence Thomas disease? No, call it the
- For your squirt disease, please.
- Yeah, so that's how I would do it.
- Pretty easy.
- With my hands and his prostate.
- I don't think you can make him squirt.
I just don't see it.
- I would make Clarence Thomas squirt prostate nut.
- I would personally abstain from doing it.
- Court.
- That's a trick for the smart guys.
- Yeah, the thinkers.
- Oh yay, oh yay.
- Number 10 MKUltra, boring, heard of it.
Number 11, Lady Gaga videos.
Slay queens.
Yeah, dude. There's Mad Demonic, the Lady Gaga videos.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
And what does she do?
She turns herself into ground beef.
Yeah.
She's in a bikini.
She talks with Beyonce.
And she dresses up like a man at the VMAs and sings...
Oh, we're talking Lady Gaga?
Yeah, why are you hiding your eyes with those big-ass glasses, bitch?
Is it maybe because they are cat eyes?
Oh, is that your poker face?
I'm gonna poke your face with my finger to make sure that you're...
you guys realize in them in that movie house of Gucci she got fucked oh can you
send me the most gonna bar they fucked her I heard the movie was originally
gonna be called house of coochie because of her getting fucked in that movie oh
she seriously got fucked oh yeah fuck her in the movie yeah the character fucks
her which character her husband no on the table that's demonic at work fuck
think about this conspiracy ready and this one's gonna blow your goddamn mind
number 18 Jay Z Lady Gaga and Beyonce all have an e sound in their name wait
wait, Petrick and you
wait Petrick
trick. What if your name was Petrick
trick, dear and Petrick did I love I Petrick, that's how you say it in us, New
Zealand, Petrick, that's how you say it in our world, you're in doing trick.
He's even last name in that I don't know
at some point. These are just triangles. Here's a really good one here number
nineteen the two triangle star. Yeah, two triangle star has the triangle of
pyramids and the triangle of eyes. The triangle of pyramids is Egypt, Turkey
and Saudi Arabia. The triangle of eyes is the Mediterranean Sea, Syria and
the Red Star in the middle of the star is Israel and the Israel flag is the
two strangles to triangle star. Thank you Ryan Higa. That's right. He got
spreading spreading truth about the later ones. Get your
here on my face number twenty six all of apples products start with an eye and
someone says iphone ipad ipod imac iraq
and then the one after that is number twenty seven music has changed after the
nineteen eighties
yeah and then number thirty three i'm too sexy right said fred yep listen to
sample
m and mtv yeah of course trump homer the great we do
know you could put number 45 new sponge bob number 44 2009 facts fear number 46
the ion zzz app zzz app old television comic show americs wouldn't have heard
of it probably how about the one creepy bloke who was only once only series one
tricky Dickie oh I ate the creepy bloke though only thing that scared me most
was no talking and the theater the handyman were in the theater with just
hands what the I did not have like a stroke that's how the person writing
that fucking road that I was reading that as is I thought you had a complete I
thought like I was gonna have to take your ass to the hospital I was reading
that and I was like am I am I really as illiterate as I think like I was like I
think I'm having a stroke probably twice a week yeah I woke up the other day and
I felt like a pain and like my one of my sides and I was like yeah this is fine I
I have a strong feeling that I'm gonna one day go to the doctor and I'll be one
of those guys who's like like mid-20s and they're like you've had 500 mini heart
attacks or mini strokes every day. I think that too, yeah. I have a similar thing.
Makes perfect sense to me. I have a heart attack every time I friggin bust.
Know what I'm saying fellas? Oh yeah, different kind of stroke. What? You have a heart attack when you bust?
Yeah, it feels so good. My heart stops. Your heart stops? My heart stops.
Doesn't happen to you? No. I'm trying to do it right. I'm worried that one day I'm just gonna like have a lot of trouble
breathing and it's just like oh
Like you've just had a problem for a year and a half. Yeah, I already spread to some place
Like yeah, the doctor like once a year. No, I
Went to the doctor and got all these blood tests and I didn't pick them up for six months and it turned out I had hepatitis
a
Picked him up and I was already I already didn't have it anymore. Yeah, so I
Have a tightest a it's usually because somebody makes you food and has poop on their hand
I think I
your poop, though, it could be your own. No, you can't. I talked to the doctor
and the doctor was like the doctor was like the doctor was like, so you have
happy to you had a potato say and she was like,
have you in the last six months? Have you knowingly put human feces in your
mouth? I was like no, and then she's like, are you sure
I was going to be like, yep, all right, you got me. I eat shit.
That's my thing though.
Yep, it's what I do.
I do eat poop though.
Shout out to them.
White Cough Medical.
That's nasty.
What up?
Go subscribe to Home Planet's Patreon.
Oh yeah.
Please.
Some fun stuff on there and you'll like it a lot.
That one's going to smell.
And please do that at what?
HomePlanet.com/ or Patreon.com/HomePlanet?
Yes.
What day does this come out?
Perfect.
And yeah, right, this comes out, so when this comes out we will, we are currently on tour.
Oh my god.
not too late to buy tickets to what's the next show atlantis next
here for words
austin l_a_
uh... san francisco chicago and l_a_ and we change that the fix the ticket price
that happens three weeks ago but that they have a ticket for they were fifty
dollars you know if you saw a guy
fucked it up also normal twenty three weeks rounds of my cousin's wedding so
al can only congratulate and i guess i i guess i if you saw a man was christmas
and i was asking for a date in las vegas
the joshua
you know what the joshua is going to las vegas the north pole budapest doing a
little residency in las vegas before taking it on the road that's gonna be
awesome is gonna be tight by the time you don't that las vegas oh my god
forget about right now it's just like fucking crazy but
i'm gonna get to it
by
- Bye. - Bye.