Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Oh.
- I'm sick of what the news media's turned into these days.
- Yeah.
- How do you like your new phone?
- We used to have, I love it,
we used to have Walter Cronkite announcing
that John F. Kennedy had been assassinated.
Right now, it's all just Jensen Ackles, nude ass and sexy and the boys.
I fucking hate that shit, dude.
I mean, we used to have Rachel Maddow doing the whole Mueller report, right?
And doing all this investigative.
Yeah, and expose.
Real fucking hard-hitting shit.
Now we have Chris Carmack, naked and erotic gay scenes in Nashville.
Wow.
That's crazy.
I don't know.
Yeah, I just don't understand how this qualifies as news.
I mean seriously, Love Him on Grey's Anatomy had no idea he played a gay character.
He's so sexy, more Chris please.
What I mean like how is what kind of news anchor uses this kind of language?
Yeah.
In these videos, by the way.
What is it?
Are you reading CNN?
Gay, I mean it doesn't, yeah I think it's a CNN network site.
It's gay-male-celebs.com.
Because look, I'm looking at CNN right now.
I'm looking at that.
Darryl McCormick nude cock and sex scenes.
Yeah, how does this make...
What does this have to do...
Like, look here, like...
I mean, yesterday, I don't wanna...
Like, there was a pretty tragic story,
but all they're talking about is
Robin Thicke paparazzi shirtless beach photos.
I know, it's like, can we just focus on...
Like, there's actually horrible things going on,
and all they can talk about is Adrian Grenier,
one of the most desired bachelors in Hollywood,
is definitely this guy.
His curly dark hair is perfectly combined with his cute smile and amazing body.
He may have hairy legs, but we assure you that his junk is shaved.
Because within this tape, you can see how this kinky bastard plays with it.
It's kind of weird.
People really care about whether or not his junk is shaved or not.
You guys are talking about like, like these like articles that are getting written.
But I mean, I don't know if you guys have been watching like the videos they
post to these websites too.
I mean, the news is totally off track.
Like yeah, this there's, you know, it was the 4th of July yesterday.
There's a lot of stuff went down.
And here, I mean, all I'm seeing is a video called "Gibby the Clown Fucks
Jazamine Banks Outside in Broad Daylight"
Exactly! That's insane. And it's like, what, this is newsworthy? Why is that, why is this trash on the news?
Fetty Wap! The January 6 hearings are happening and all I can see on the
fucking news is gorgeous hunks, nude, and extra scenes from north of the border.
It's fucking insane, dude.
An election is coming up. First of all, Roe vs Wade is overturned and all these people
can talk about is Fetty Wap and how nowadays he's one of the most popular rappers
of this rap is not a good old stuff because all the rappers were known for
their sex tapes he used his popularity of film some ebony girl
on my god how that's
and i'm i'm on the front page of c_n_n_ right now and i'm seeing another video
this is the it's labeled breaking news this is the biggest is that the big
thing on the web yeah
and it's as clown fucks girl in public from drone view
drone you you guys
while
And I guess they're more concerned about the clowns on the getting fucked by a drone
than the clowns in Congress.
That's right.
Focus on...
And it's like, why does CNN.com think I want to watch this video called "Evil Clown Fucks
Teen"?
Why are we focusing on Nate Cernkovich's nude big cock scenes?
How about the nude big cock scenes in the White House?
Yeah.
and you know and
donald trump is still on trial for january six me know how they're talking
about his jason momoa shirtless reading the motorcycle it's fucking insane did
it's like seriously who
who's gonna who wakes up in the morning
that's a cup of coffee
they open up the news they want to see what's going on in the world
like oh here's a new video i'll tell you this out
she fucked a clown in the girls bathroom doesn't make any sense to really look
like a major at the on the jerk off sober on the hill instead of dylan
McDermott's new jerk-off videos in American Horror Story.
Why would any journalism-minded individual, why would they think that this is okay content
to put on CNN?
Gibby the Clown fucks girl 2,749 feet in the air.
Wow.
They're talking about that.
They're really talking about that nowadays.
I feel like that is kind of newsworthy because it might be a world record.
I'm seeing here I mean this did this just happened this was just published seconds
ago cheating BBW neighbor gets fucked by a clown you know give me the clown
they should do an expose and give me the clinics he does he's not actually
fucking these girls have you ever noticed that you never really you never
see his penis he's never fucking no look at look at what pull one of these videos
up he does not ever you never see his penis I don't show me his show me his
penis crazy ugly clown fucks juicy pussy of sex appeal brunette crazy ugly
here's another one pennywise the fucking clown really yeah they got pennywise on
this news now I know it's like what oh my god I just feel like the news has
completely gone down the toilet absolutely like so disgusting it just
doesn't make any sense you know mm-hmm there's somebody more stuff isn't even
original it's got this clown sucks and fucks - that's disgusting the first one
you're focusing on the second time it happened it's like that's who cares I
have your news Wow what there's a birthday boy in this room there is a
birthday boy I don't know he is in this room it was his birthday yesterday and I
think I'm gonna do a birthday freestyle for him oh my god Wow
Yo, yo, it's Cameron's birthday, yeah yeah, and it was yesterday, okay, it was on the 4th
of July, yup yup, as American as an apple pie, oh oh, he got a new hat yup, and he got a new
hat yup, and he got a keychain yo, it came straight from my brain yo, it has three thangs
in it yo it's three peas in a pod like the guys on the pod whoa three guys watch
hot rod on my couch laugh it up go ahead laugh it up while you while you watch
hot rod go ahead you got the laughter in your head okay smiling from your head
and then you go out to you go down to bed and you have a funny dream yeah is
it as funny as it seems no it's not wake up back to the real world back to the
the grind nine to five wow I was amazing. I had a dream last night that a volcano
or a broken window. Me and me and Cameron now have the same hat or matching
getting fucking wrapping now. That's cool.
It's cool that you're good at wrapping. It is cool. I'm proud of you. Fucking
thank you man. Yo Caleb doesn't I did. I forgot to get him one of the hats. Yeah,
But that's okay.
- Yeah.
- It's fine, yo!
- He's fine, he's good with his wrapping.
- It's all G!
- But you know what I got, actually?
- What?
Holy!
It's a different flavor.
- Oh, it is, isn't it?
- It's a completely different flavor.
- I thought you would feel left out
that me and Cameron have matching hats,
so I got the same.
- It's a completely different.
(laughing)
It's a completely different flavor.
Thought he did me a favor.
Turns out, he's not a saver.
- No.
I am a saver, it was only a dollar.
But he's about to savor the drink that he drank.
The flavor.
The flavor of the savory drink that he's drinking.
And he's not thinking, just drinking, just slurping.
And he wants more things.
He's slurping the flavor that is purping.
He's getting the flavor into his mouth, on his taste buds.
Purping, I mean pink.
You're a waistoid.
[Laughter]
I bend my wraps like Eminem.
Waistoid?
You're a waistoid?
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty good. I hope everybody had a good Monday yesterday.
Yeah, I don't even want to say the name of the holiday. Yeah, I don't even want to tell
you what yesterday was. I call it a certain day in July. I call it Cameron's birthday
actually. I call it my Grandpa Rick's birthday because it's actually his, I knew about him
before I knew about you. Yeah, that's fine. But then if he dies, I'll call it your birthday.
Okay, that's fair enough.
Fingers crossed.
Okay.
Grandpa Rick.
Ricky.
That's his legal name, Ricky.
His legal name is Ricky.
Yeah.
That's cool.
He didn't find that out until he was like 40 and then he looked at his birth certificate
and it said Ricky.
How do you not find that out?
What do you mean?
He didn't have his birth certificate.
What did he think that his legal name was?
Rick or Richard.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, he would always put Richard on stuff.
That's usually the name somebody has when they're named Rick.
But his mom is just like a hillbilly who just named him Ricky.
Have you ever seen that movie, the something world of the whites?
It's a movie about this family.
Yeah, your house.
Yeah.
It's a movie about this family in Virginia.
This is some kind of something world of whites.
Yeah.
It's a world of whites.
It is definitely a world of whites.
But it's this family, Jesco White is the dad, he's like an Appalachian tap dancer.
And one of the daughters is named Sue Bob.
Sue Bob?
That's a cool name.
Sue Bob.
Have you seen that movie?
That's short for SpongeBob.
He's my daughter SpongeBob.
And my son Patrick.
Southern people have the most fucked up names.
Have you seen that movie about the, like that NASCAR guy?
Talladega Nights.
It's Ricky Bobby.
It doesn't make any sense.
Two first names.
Ricky Bobby.
first name Ricky Bobby yeah like how much of a southern fucking hick do you have to
be a redhead said some of the things to a hick in a redneck and also I watched the
movie he's actually range ideas about Jesus they're like insanely just the
religiosity just made me almost want to fucking vomit yeah of them of the
movie gay character shafted the gay character don't care no characterization
no no he didn't show him getting shafted I should have that's what I'm saying
They should have showed it unapologetically gay.
It would have been a pretty good representation of gay life.
That's true.
But it wasn't.
I heard that that...
He was gay because he was sponsored by Paranay too.
I heard that the gay actor, the gay man from that movie actually is well known.
I don't know if you guys have seen this movie.
He played the brat.
The brat?
Yeah, from that movie, Brat.
So, is that like the pest?
No, it's from that movie, Brat, where the brat goes around to different places in America.
And he's being like a total brat.
like a total brat. He acts like super cranky because he's a brat. He probably needs a nap
or something. He like ruins the national anthem. Oh okay. The brat. Yeah. I'm sick of these.
He's like I don't want to do the national anthem. Yeah. I think that's what he's doing.
Yeah. And then there's that guy who's like I want to sit on a plane with no sound. And
then he's like yeah. Then there's that guy who he meets who's like you know what we do
to brats where we don't like the country that brats come from. I'm sick of these brats from
other countries coming over and demanding toys and stuff. Oh yeah. It's like why are
you demanding toys they're not toys aren't made here anymore I'm sorry to
bring that up it's almost like nothing is more you look at you look at a
American you pull up an American flag on your phone yeah the back of your phone
it says made in China yeah makes no fucking sense you pull up a picture of
a Ford f-150 on your phone right but then you turn your phone around fucking
phones made in China you'd think Ford would make it the guy Ford yeah but he
it's a machine because you use it for calling and using the internet and
ford ordering yourself some groceries and ford ordering a pizza and ford
watching netflix and youtube yeah right, but they don't they don't is
actually that's yeah phone. They have a machine ford making it yeah exactly
not even a it's not even a guy who's entire job is for making a he's not the
guy is not for making that exactly. He's ford he's for sitting around lazily
using his phone ford apps, hon and honda. They should honda should make it
you get it to get Honda internet and get and get Honda YouTube application and
watch and another thing that's not made in America is toy yodas and toy Luke's
and the Tory Vader's yeah doesn't make any sense it's like those are American
movies and Hummer when you get from call your phone is almost a Hummer because of
if you yeah yeah the vibration is a hum and you know and my friend's uncle see
he's not even made in America anymore. My friend's uncle was Kia in Vietnam.
He's Kia. He's Kia. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, and his name was Subaru.
That's just how the world even works now. When I was- and he went- yeah- he went
went hyen and I he went he went on died. He went over into a and died yeah
yep from as fast as a race car.
He has a fast he hun died. He injected him with formula one. He
he went head on died and he and he went to another plane of existence. Yeah, a
Yeah, and what is with everyone getting into formula one now? It's the cool thing. What are you talking about?
I know like three you fucking you can't say
Everybody's getting into I know three different people who I feel like I've seen one the fuck are you two even?
What planet are you on? I've never even I don't even know what formula one is I didn't either
I can't really know long ones or the wide ones. I don't know that's the long ones
I think and the wide ones are NASCAR
car. But those are the ones that look like a praying mantis? I can tell you it's not
the small ones. Those are hot wheels. What the hell? You've seen penises on cars? I didn't
say... My dick is much closer to a NASCAR than a Formula One. I thought you were going
to look up what a Formula One looks like. No, I have a... Mine looks like a Star Destroyer
from Star Wars. No, it doesn't. Mine looks actually like a Death Star. If it looked like
a Star Destroyer or a Death Star, you'd actually have a serious problem.
It looks like a Death Star if you hold it closed while you're peeing.
You know what's so funny to do?
As a kid, when I was like, tie off the end of the...
Do you ever push...
Tie off the end of my foreskin and I would pee.
Yeah, or you would like thread a piece of floss into your wiener and pull stuff out
of it.
That is really good.
You ever put a piece of pencil lead into the tip of your penis?
No.
No?
Me neither.
There are people who like sound like urethral sounding.
Yeah, I don't even know what that is.
There's people that are into that.
I don't get that.
I don't get it either.
I guess that the rod goes down and all the way into the through the tip and pokes into
your prostate.
I think it goes to the ball.
I don't think it pokes your prostate.
I don't think you do it that far.
I've seen a video.
I've seen, you've seen a video of the guy drilling into the his penis hole?
No.
like a drill he's just drilling remember that website kids in sandbox it's the guy
who has like he has like a I think he got a surgery to get his penis to give it a
bigger hole no woman is sticking like a sex toy into the hole can we stop can we
just stop it's icky yeah that's actually kind of much what is nasty about that
it's natural. It's not natural. That's natural. That's how
mommies and daddies make you. That's fucking cap. That's how
mommies and daddies make you. That's just lying. No, that's
true. Do you think it's just completely normal to lie about
what mommies and daddies do? Mommies and daddies do your
reasonable sounding. No. Mommies and daddies, daddies and
mommies kiss and the daddies uh and then the daddy goes, a
sparkle goes from the daddy's mouth into the mommy's body and
and goes down into her tummy. No, no, my any makes an orb. Mommy and Daddy call
up their friend, who's he's a pool boy, a pool boy, and they both fuck him and
that's how you're born. The no man daddies have little homunculi inside
their it really hurts the homunculi to be in your dad. So they're yeah, they
try to get out you get out of the balls, because the balls are me. The balls are
over a hundred degrees and the mommy has a little house inside that the monkey
like a monkey was wants to go into yeah see I didn't I didn't see that I saw
that mommies and daddies go to a hole in the wall and a penis comes out and then
a penis a penis comes out of the hole well how why are we bring penises into
this is kind of nose on the other end of that hole but they they suck the glue
out of the penis and then you're born from that glue I think it was a
a situation where first they show the camera how much glue they can fit in
their mouth yeah yeah look my mouth isn't even sticking closed from all this glue
yeah yeah there's so many videos of mommies and daddies I would have to go
with a Gabby Carter very talented mommy very an amazing glue holder Gabby Carter
you're well done. I heard that mommy's and daddy's are mommy's talk to a stork
and the stork gets the baby. That's Fred's and then mommy's get in big
trouble
and the storks.
The stork comes in and takes the baby away. Whoa really yeah and the mommy the
daddy pretends the baby doesn't isn't there. Imagine what you've the baby is
of what your child is born
stork beak yeah imagine your imagine mommy's fucking the stork for yeah
because she just don't under or born with a Santa Claus beard yeah okay weird
question. Maybe have you been fucking
I was born on September.
There's a beard and a big red belly and look at look at he's
exhibiting jolly behavior.
Yeah, you want I don't have a jolly bone in my body. You know,
I'm the least jolly guy in the world. We need to do a cookie
test to see if he's actually my son. I mean low-key. That's the
plot of Elf though. Yeah. That's not the fucking plot of Elf. That's the entire plot of Elf.
That's reverse Elf. He didn't have a fucking, oh he didn't fucking, he's fucking an Elf.
You did not watch the director's cut. Also, how the fuck, James Conn is like 5'5" Italian
guy, how the fuck does he, the mommy is tall. Will Ferrell's a NBA player. Sometimes I'll
see there's like a tall mommy and a tiny daddy. Really? You look that up specifically? No.
mommies and small daddies. Smallest daddy. Yeah. And a big mommy. Huge mommy. Huge mommy. Giant.
Huge mommy looks like Bigfoot and it's a drawing. It's a drawing? It's a drawing. Have you seen the
ones where the mommies and daddies eat each other and they go, "Oh my belly's so full of a daddy."
Yeah. I really like that. I've seen the ones where the mommy eats the daddy. But the mommy
looks like surprisingly much like a Sonic. I've seen one where the mommy's a Pokemon. I like
those where a Pokemon, where mommy's dressed up like a perfect Pokemon right or 2B
from that one game yeah and they eat 2B from near Atomata yeah and then
they'd swallow Scorpion from Mortal Kombat yeah as a daddy though and they
go oh I'm so full of him yeah and you can see the little and the line of yeah the
mommy's butt is big yeah cuz that's where the food goes yeah good daddy go
maybe the food put gets pushed from the belly into the butt sometimes a baby can
be made from two mommies I've heard of this yeah I think they did that on Glee
and I've heard about two daddies situation too but I haven't done a lot
of two daddies videos and let me tell you I heard that sometimes it can be
It stinks in there.
A little baby can come from as many as five to ten mommies and daddies.
Two daddies is just too much glue and not enough little holes.
Yeah, it's mostly glue in a two daddies video.
But the glue actually mixes up with other...
I heard the strongest baby comes from one mommy, ten daddies.
Ten daddy businessmen.
Yeah.
on a train in Tokyo. In a strange land. Oh yeah. Sometimes the daddy's a tentacle. Yeah and
that's okay too. Yeah. You know sometimes a daddy is an actual. That's a scary baby though.
Yeah that baby's gonna be scary. In certain videos the daddy is actually just a
cucumber or a vegetable. Yeah. I've seen videos where it's two daddies. Yeah. And
and they're doing real estate. Really? Believe it or not. That's like a dad job.
yeah we're not that hard I've never seen a male realtor really yeah yeah yes it's
mostly mommies doing yeah there's a lot of realtors but they flip the script and
it's two daddies in a real estate situation and do they make have a glue
party they have a glue party but he beat with a with a fist really oh he's trying
get he's helping him he's trying to wipe his butt. He's trying to pre-wipe his whole butt so that he doesn't have to wipe later.
So he reaches in and wipes out all the poop so that you like hey your daddy or other daddy
you're gonna have like three or four days where you don't have to wipe. They use
something called a fleet before and they get all the poop out. What's a fleet?
It's nothing. I don't know. What the fuck is a fleet? What are you talking about?
Brand. Brand of what? Douche. Oh, come on! That's too far, dude. From South Park?
Giant douche from South Park. That's fucking disgusting. And it's grosser. It's gross when you see two daddies.
Oh shit! Yeah, I heard sometimes it's like now it's like there's like mommies and
daddies but the mommy is the daddy's mommy. Interesting. I don't even know
that works but yeah mommy is the daddy's mommy. But they're also mommying and
daddying together. They're doing mommy daddy together. They're doing mommy and daddy.
the daddy's daddying the mommy and the mommy's mommying the daddy. Oh that makes a lot of sense
actually. But the mommy is the daddy's mommy. Oh okay. So there can be two mommies but one of them's a
daddy? I've heard legend of a thousand mommies. Really? I've never been able to find it from my
research. You know one there was one mommy who set a record she had like 400 daddies daddy her in like
one day. Wow. Yeah. That looks like it stinks in there. It completely stunk up
the entire room. Honestly, the mommy and daddy smell of that room would probably...
It'd probably be comparable to like an earthquake shelter.
Yeah. I'd go in there with a power wash tool. I'd spray all the
daddies off. Yeah, it's like the scene in like a Roland Emmerich
movie where there's a thousand people in a basketball stadium. How do mommies get
made. Do they get... Well, mommies come from two daddies. Do they get shot in the...
That's why they have videos of two daddies because they're making a
mommy. When they're born, so they clip off a daddy's penis when you're born, but
then do they shoot a hole in the front of a mommy with a gun? See, I think what
happens, because I've seen videos... I've seen videos where it's one mommy and
two daddies and the two daddies do two daddy things and then the mommy's just
there watching no she's just there there's a video where mommy is eating
salad in the kitchen and two daddies are doing a daddy mommy scene really mm-hmm
you ever seen the one where the mommy does mommy stuff and the daddy is a is a
chocolate cake she just sits on it yeah and she makes me a chance you poots
really good mm-hmm I don't really like those videos yeah yeah I don't really
like mommy if it wasn't if it wasn't for like the pursuit of figuring out how
babies come from I probably wouldn't be watching where the mommy was just a
normal mommy but then did daddy was actually just a pitbull it's really
interesting stuff yeah yeah yeah no I'm actually disgusting breath it's not it's
some of those videos are not some of them are not yeah not not okay yeah and I
don't know why the hell they're on the news yeah yeah it's no so it's like I
know the reason that they're on the news I think is just to educate people it's I
think parents don't want to they want to kids like us cuz it's hard for us kids
you know especially like future rap star future skateboarder mm-hmm future
artist you know I mean like we all have our own kind of like cool trifecta style
style shit three peas in a pod. Shout out to my key chain. I got you for your
birthday. Yeah. So like I don't I feel like we're so focused on kind of
figuring out our own identities in this like exactly as day and age as teens
that it's fucking tough as fuck to actually learn about life skills like
mommying and daddying and I know well the thing is though I don't I like I
don't want to open up like Fox News or whatever and I don't I don't yeah. I
mean well I mean if I if I forced you know the CNN websites out or whatever
I gotta get my news somewhere. It's like I open up Fox News and I don't want to
read about the daddy train. Yeah. The daddy train that they're conducting on a mommy.
It's like, bro, I'm only 15 years old. I can't actually manage working on my new rap lifestyle
and also trying to fucking understand mommy and daddy and which hole is better for daddies,
which holes have mommies in them. And the thing, it's so confusing too because I'm trying to learn
about how it works with mommies and daddies some of the and some of this some
of these videos that I'm saying that I'm learning about it's litter it's just a
mommy and she's talking about about daddying mm-hmm but it's just a mommy
it's like I don't understand how this works what am I supposed to do you go on
a CNN front page and there's a there's a video where a mommy's mommy's meat is
spinning really yeah holy shit a mommy a mommy's meat is spinning that's
insane. Uh-huh. Yeah, like I don't know, like I just not, I just not even care about
showing that. And it's playing 80s music. What the fuck? Yeah. See like that's
honestly like just a previous generation status. Yeah. Like 80s. That's like an
entirely different generation that had a different music scene. Yeah. And an entirely
different kind of movie that we'll see.
There's a...
What?
That is so true.
Yeah.
It's like at least if I'm going to have to watch this, at the very least, play some, you
know, like modern cutting edge hip hop.
Maybe play like a remix made by Flo Rida.
Or like...
I'm trying to decide if I'm going to be a thug rapper or straight nerdcore with it, and then
all these news stories are making my fucking, making my penis get strong.
some jpeg mafia yeah like that guy was actually lit af in the military yeah and
it's like these 80s rappers and movies don't understand you know not bring him
an 80s movie into the current Netflix style status yeah and try to make that
they don't have movies on Netflix they shouldn't they have actually homages to
it like stranger things was actually one of the most fucking groundbreaking
pieces of cinema because of its modernity that's what they're trying to
do now they're trying to turn 80s movies into Netflix errs and which team are you
team Steve or you team Jonathan I'm team I'm minecraft Steve because he's
actually got building abilities yeah and smash brothers I guess I'll put that
down as team Steve yeah yeah so I just don't know I think it's will I don't
understand like like I don't mean to paraphrase a song but like we are the
kids of America uh-huh and I mean nowadays you're seeing movies like
Top Gun Maverick it's like and it's like okay the play these these planes were
high-tech in the 80s yeah but this is gonna have to be spaceships or laser
or cars or something like the planes we all know planes go side to side like
this for the future type movie I could go up and down like we get can we get a
neutron movie yeah come on we get a neutron movie just trying to not mean
that's what that's right more closer to the day run no let's think about a tron
movie where instead of blue line I mean red thing I would actually be in saying
that you went I think you wanted a nude nude drama that's why that's why the
new matrix is so dope because it's basically about the dopest of the
the internet, meeting people on the internet, meme culture, for the win.
Top Gun, I mean the shit like Top Gun, it's like they're flying in planes and
it's like, okay, you guys have nicknames? Nicknames? That's 80s. We have screen
names now. Exactly. We have gamer tags, right? Because we're a generation raised
on new shit like MSG. And none of these news anchors or anything on CNN could
even last a minute in a cod lobby. They won't cover it. They're too busy talking
about Justin Long as a baby cock on a kayak. They're too fucking busy talking
celebrities and their daddy parts bro. I'm actually trying to fucking invent new
kinds of music. I'm trying to listen to music while I do my tasks. I'm thinking
of a new blend of rock and hip-hop and trying to actually express myself
through that bullshit about different shit I'm going through with my fucking
grades. And it's like yeah and it's like every news website nowadays has these
45 minute videos about like court jester is fucking this other slut in the castle.
It doesn't make any sense. It's like that's so old.
Yeah.
(laughing)
We don't have castles anymore.
I don't even know what a castle looks like, bro.
What's that, like Gotham?
I saw, there's one castle,
there's only one place you can go to see a real castle now
and it's medieval times.
That's the shit that I'm talking about, right?
How come there's no restaurant that's future times?
Here's the thing, we used to have the Flintstones
and now we own that Jetsons tip.
Yep. Right?
Yeah.
Because I honestly, the Flintstones,
I don't give a fuck about your rock shit
and about fucking dinos and bullshit like that.
The Jetsons, I'm way into the robot maid status,
who she actually has a microwave in her vagina,
and that's the shit that I'm rocking with these days.
- And Judy Jetson, 16 year old wife.
- Yeah.
- She's only 16, the father is like old as hell.
So it's like a mommy, a young mommy, old daddy thing.
- Yeah, which is these days becoming more and more
just like absolutely fucking futuristic, yeah.
- And that's weird.
- It's fucking weird, yeah.
And let's just go back to a normal time.
I agree.
I know.
We can't, we can't, I mean, we just can't keep having these videos.
My first public caveman fuck beauty who came from the sea.
How the hell is that news?
Exactly.
That's old.
It's not news.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the oldest shit ever.
The sea.
And why is the-
Caveman gets a woman to fill with cum.
And why is George Jetson on that treadmill?
Bro, what the fuck is the sea or the ocean?
Because I've only experienced water parts these days.
Yep.
Me too.
actually insanely high drop in the bath and I've actually had a couple of baths,
but those are even getting old by the day. I can't wait to get to showers.
Yeah showers are on another level because there's actually no dirt in them.
Yeah, but a bath is a basically a dirt pile. It's a puddle, a complete dirt
puddle, so it's like mud. This is old news. Okay on on xn xx that's that's a
news network. I think yeah, it follows the but it's like it's like this is this
news is so old. This is your front page Chinese cave woman gets fucked by
British caveman in sixty thousand BC bro. That's so literally six
thousand years ago. That's literally pre fucking eighties
yeah and like the eighties bullshit is already way too
fucking old right the Goonies bro. I literally don't care
about some fucking old ass fat guy. Yeah, who's a kid chunk
yeah in the Goonies right? Yeah, give a shit about that
treasure is old af and I don't fuck with it anymore. If they
were actually looking for a new technology or motherboard. I
be interested they should look for like a spaceship or maybe like a fucking fire
ass like recipe video like something that's terrible if they should have
looked up like this pasta gnocchi will make you literally melt exactly exact
some kind of like air that's new if they were looking for that's news if they
were going for an air fryer recipe then I might have actually hopped on that
wave yeah but I actually didn't because they were on some what is it like whipped
feta whipped feta with apricot spread that would actually I would be sourdough
that because that actually looks bussin do you know it looks bussiness do you
know it's not news though what Dracula fucking a women no that is not news you
know what news here's real news blood-curdling facts you wish you didn't
know part 15 yeah that is news that is here's real news plum and olive oil cake
yeah like that should be fine like olive oil cake that's insanely moist or like
Avant-garde vegan recipes like yeah bullshit is actually fire like this lady
and it's like these cakes yeah and I watch these and I pretend she's making
them for me yeah and it's like news that's new Patrick watches this woman
and thinks he says she should be a mommy for him exactly and it's like it's like
what is this rich noble brunette wife fucked by Dracula in prison how the hell
is that actually a fucking top story and how do I get to know what I'm getting
getting distracted by the news right and also Dracula here. Let me speak on
Dracula real quick. Yeah, that fool should have been in prison from the jump.
Yep, absolutely, because he was actually if you do look, you don't know this. If
you do your research, your investigation, he's out there sucking women's blood,
which is actually low key. A yellow tail carpaccio with her be a Chile actually
looks fire as fuck. It's just the truth and what and you know this actually
could this actually might be newsworthy. Okay, apparently I'm seeing this on the
page this just happened lady fucks werewolf to death to death to death
that's overrated mm-hmm and over aged because a werewolf is actually some old
BS right that's true I guess I guess a lot of people don't know this but women
were executed for being witches but a lot of men at around the same time and
like Salem and shit were actually burned because they thought they were were
wolves damn turns out they were just you know just a guy who's a very hairy
I'm so scared to live in that time.
If God is real, then you will never have to.
That's the other thing.
How about fucking report, if you're going to report on old bullshit, why not the fucking
infinite miracles of Christ?
He was literally water to wine, bread and fish for fucking hundreds of people.
And he could float.
And he had a floating ability, especially when he interacted with a water source.
Look at over there.
Look at that picture of him.
Look, he's got a 3D fucking effect.
got a 3d effect literally his heart is on fire how fucking that's based that's
based as hell uh-huh to be fucking Christ like you know it's cringe what
living in flames living in fucking sin yeah yeah so like that bullshit is
fucked do you think this is this I mean this is more and this is something that
is a little more timely so I think this could be news but I really need you
guys opinion on this okay yeah I mean we're talking about cave and we're
talking about Dracula, but what do you think about this is on this is on
another news website X I think X is like extreme news X videos stream news
extra might be like example brass example video the news yeah but this is
thick robot gets her big-ass fucked and it's in all capitals fucked and I don't
know if you guys think this is news or not Wow that because it is it's current
though. A robot fuck a girl. Yeah. Female robot machine fuck recharge eight minutes. Wow.
And there's we should have a list right? Guy roughly fucks the girl robot. Oh yeah we do
have a list. Do we have a list of robots that could get fucked? Would you guys fuck a robot?
Would I fuck a robot? I don't think I have much of an interest. You know those like machines
that have the like the the pussies and buttholes on them yeah yeah I guess I
would fuck one of those but not a robot yeah you know when you like you know
when you like look something up on on Amazon like you're like oh I need a new
like I need a new charging cable or something and then you get ads for like
months for charging cables yeah I would not fuck a robot because I don't want to
see what the equivalent of that is
for fucking
yeah, it's true. No, because you know that robot, you know that
robot. If you if you don't like do you have a dangerously curved
penis? Yeah, here are five tips. If you're not careful that
robot definitely would collect collect all your data. Yeah,
fuck it. Yeah, it's gonna was your was your son just born with
actually. It can tell what like deformity your children are going to have. That's
actually a pretty, that's what the 23andMe thing should be. They send you a
sex toy, you ejaculate into it, and then you ship it back to them all dripping
cum and that's not how you did it. Like like fucking honey out of a bear's mouth.
That's not how you did it? No. Oh. All right I guess I guess I got a mad
different test really it was hella different yep yep so what's this list
here is the number is the 69 funny number number jokes phone number jokes up joke
comm slash phone number jokes everything we said up to this point has been
completely serious I'm not really a rant day today sorry just kind of don't give
a fuck about like fucking comedy these days I feel like it's so fucked with I
I know I'd rather speak truth to power is them and shit yeah and I think I think
now we do the jokes but these are like literally fucking wokest PC fucking SJW
bullshit we can call them out like look at this like phone number jokes I
literally only know two phone numbers 9-1-1 and JG Wentworth like that's
fucking that's woke that's full fuck what's JG is that just girls just yeah
just girls Wentworth's Wentworth is that we I think went where there's actually a
university and oh really women's only University Wow just girls at Wentworth
here's another here's a thing here I don't know if there's a phone number
actually here we go my dad always said work until your bank
account looks like a phone number so I did account balance 9/11 what no so
that's the thing liberals do not have any respect for the victims of like
tragedies and stuff they're like and though and the war overseas whatever
It's like you're making light of 9/11. It's actually fucking disrespectful. These are phone number jokes
These are not supposed to be I mean the other one had a to literally 9-1-1 and JJ like oh
That's what's funny to you. Oh, I'm so fucking I'm so that's what I see that I can fucking disrespect the troop hell on earth
Yeah, yeah dozens of people burnt to a crisp. Yeah at the fuck at fucking Benghazi
Yeah, it's like you're literally like like Benghazi like American tragedies like 9/11 and Benghazi
You're like fucking just disrespecting them constantly. Oh, it's like those are like those are like one and two interchangeably like probably the worst things
I've ever happened in this fucking country and
Or up to this country. Yeah, you're just like making light of it's funny
This is a good place for my phone number. Yeah right now. It's like oh, I just don't fucking get it man
Here's loyal Americans got turned into Freddy Krueger. Yeah, but evil nasties
From across the ocean yeah, but fucking Hillary Clinton, bro. Yeah, yeah, she's from Kenya. She is from Kenya
I saw her at Kenya one time
Great a trigger warning this joke may contain profanity awesome. Yeah, so I gotta press
I'm over 18 listen you shouldn't have to be 18 to watch porn
They put those trigger warnings at the beginning of all the porn websites, it's like that's bullshit
it. Right? How the fuck am I supposed to learn shit? A guy goes to Las Vegas to gamble and
he loses all his money. He doesn't even have enough for a cab, but he flagged one down
anyway. He explained to the driver that he would pay him back next time and gave him
his phone number, but the driver told him, "Get the fuck out of my cab." There's the
F word they were talking about. He walked all the way to the airport and got home. Some
times rolls by and he decides to go back to Vegas again and this time he wins big. He
gets his bags and is ready for the airport with all his new winnings. There are a line
of cabs and at the very end he sees the driver from last time that kicked him out. He stood
for a moment thinking how he can get his revenge on that driver. So he gets in the first cab.
How much is it to the airport he asks. The driver says $15. Great, how much is it for
a blowjob on the way there? The cab driver says get the fuck out of my cab. So he goes
to the next one and asks the same thing. How much to the airport? $15. How much for a blowjob?
And the cab driver also tells him to get the fuck out of his cab. He does this all the
way down the line of drivers, each one kicking him out. He finally gets to the last driver,
one from his last trip. He asks, "Hey, how much to the airport?" Driver responds, "15."
The guy hands him 15 and says, "Great, let's go." And so the driver leaves, slowly passing
all the other drivers who are staring out their window while the guy in the back smiles
back with a thumbs up.
Bruh!
It's like, listen, fucking, I don't-
That's disrespectful to service workers.
Literally these guys, first of all, taxi cabs are one of the last bastions of free speech
in this fucked up shit.
Yep, you can say whatever you want in a taxi.
Say whatever you want. Listen, if you want to listen, you can literally ask them, like,
you get into a cab driver right it's usually a patriot he's listening to the
Tim Nealon show and he you can't have him turn it off to what in ubers they
say weird things in ubers you get us you get into an uber bro you're there
fucking 15 songs they have a 15 song caroline polachek playlist that they
play five times in a row. I was some gay bullshit. I was in an uber a few days
ago and the uber driver told us that in the future he said in the future maybe
there might be zombies in the road. Wow. He said that to us. Holy shit. Yeah, he
really did. Liberal dude. He played the fucking Telltale Walking Dead game. Yeah.
Because that's the intro. That's the intro? That's the intro. That makes so
much sense. Yeah, so he obviously, which that game is about what? Fucking emotions
and bullshit like that. And you actually, it's a walking simulator. Yeah. And you
know, do you know what his GPS voice was that he had to set to? What? Christina
Aguilera. And you know what his GPS... It's like what happened to using a military
the commander you wanted is you know what his GPA was at for his fucking his
eighty thousand dollars. I like probably like eight point. Oh, because they
cheat yeah, because he literally is taking a P fucking pussy fiction and
doing fucking dookie detective work at for free yeah, at Wentworth at Wentworth
University. Yeah, yep, he's literally there's a class at Wentworth where you
just put a guy's butt in your mouth. I heard they found new t rex bones. I
they found new t-rex bones and they destroyed them because it was a male
t-rex. They actually, no, they thought, well I heard that, then they also
found girl t-rex bones and they actually gave all the bones to different OnlyFans
women so they could put them in their vaginas to make more money. Yeah, I heard that too.
You make money putting a bone in your thing. It's a fucked up world. Is that true?
With fucking fucked up shit, right? Is that really true? Yeah, that's why I picked up a mic.
fucking spit to spit yeah it rhymes okay yeah it sounded like you're using the
mic for something else when you said that no I'm not use oh my god did this
is literally your fucking lib brain poison getting to your brain okay here's
one should we exchange our phone numbers are you kidding that would confuse the
people who try to call us what that's a good point that actually this is the
first one I'm that's like a Confucius saying here's one here use us yeah
there's two these two are the same Confucius he was sent by Mao Zedong to
confuse us into being complete communists that's true that is so true
but look this one here I got this German girl's phone number she was being
difficult about it but I eventually got it it was nine nine nine nine nine nine
nine nine nine nine and then that's as possible OC I just got is that you
You should read the one that's right above that.
I just want to hear this one.
Yeah, 'cause like if you're a real fucking patriot
that you don't see this one, it's between these two jokes.
Let me read this one.
I asked a girl for, a Chinese girl for her phone number.
I asked a Chinese girl for her phone number.
She said,
nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
No, that's not what it says.
What did she say?
Six, six, six.
No, that's not what it says.
Three, six, two, nine.
- All right, so you're basically as bad as the fucking people who write these fucked up--
- I said, "Wow," then her friend said she meant 666-3629.
- You're basically a fucking anti-Christian piece of shit.
- How is that anti-Christian?
- As a true American patriot, I always put phone numbers I want to ignore
under the contact "Freedom" because I always let freedom ring.
- Oh, so it's a joke to you?
- Freedom is a joke.
- Is this a charity to you to fucking do-- what are you, you're a fucking weird owl?
Fuck you.
- Some people literally live inside a computer.
- I know, it's fucked up.
and they're they they have they're forced to live in a computer and it's like you
think it's funny to joke about that. Do you know if Stephen Hawking still has
his old phone number? Every time I call a machine answers. Like Stephen Hawking was
actually one of the most fucking amazing like like pure images of American
masculinity. Uh-huh. Right and he's like one of the last bastion. And he was
American. Yeah he was. Duh. He was a full-blooded American. Okay with this one. I think he didn't have
full blood. I think that was the issue. This one actually is actually really
really patriotic. I'm actually liking this one. I'm going to read out for you.
Was at a Capital One cafe and asked the waitress for her phone number. Oh now
they start guarding personal data. Damn. Yeah. That's actually pretty good.
Take that Banks. Yeah that's right. I fucking hate the shitting Banks.
Yep. Alright see this is bullshit. Wait here's another one. Yeah. That I just
saw that's total bullshit. Yeah big surprise. I asked a newly immigrated
Asian lady for a phone number. She replied said sex free sex free sex tonight took me a minute to realize she meant
636 3629
Seem like that one is actually fucking mad racist. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know why you chose to read that like insanely racist and you just like chose to read that racist bullshit
You literally chose to share that to thousands of people just now. Yeah, really?
There's thousands of people listening. No, I don't think so. Oh, I
I've deleted the phone numbers of all the Germans. I knew from my mobile phone now. It's Hans free like that's actually anti like Germany
That's not even nice to them either. Yeah, I asked a cute statistician if I could get her phone number
She said probably not that's kind of like a saddest story and short of amount. I don't really understand that more ship, but whatever
Let's see I
Gave a girl my phone number and told her to text me when she got home. I guess she's homeless
Here's one here's one here. There's a weird one because it's a involves a child
It says little Johnny
Asked a newly immigrated Asian lady for a phone number
and
She replied sex sex sex free sex tonight
Is there more is that this the whole thing
Oh, and then it took little Johnny a minute to realize she meant 636-3629.
Oh, okay.
And they're just letting kids do this now?
I have another one here about little Johnny that's even more liberal.
Wow.
Big surprise.
The teacher in little Johnny's school asked the class what their mothers did for a living.
One little girl said her mother was a doctor.
Another said her mother was an engineer.
When it was little Johnny's turn, he stood up and said, "My mom's a streetwalker."
Walker. Naturally, after that remark, he got sent off to the
principal's office. Then, fifteen minutes later, he
returned. So the teacher asked, Did you tell the principal what
you said in class? Johnny said, Yes. Well, what did the
principal say? He said that every job is important in our
economy, gave me an apple and asked for my phone number. Wow,
so the principal's a pedophile. Great is a penny. Want to be
there? I think it's okay for a principal to pay a pedophile.
This is another one that I saw that's fucking bullshit leftism
Yo mama so fat when she steps on a scale I see my phone number and then it says
under that says it's completely okay to be fat these days. Wow. Yeah. It's just
sadness is actually better than skinniness. Yeah. And also it says it
says fat women are actually better than women who are so fucking skinny you can
see every single one of their bones. Yeah. And it's like what dude it's like
yeah. This is bone is the hottest shit of all time. The bones a hot part of the
women. Yeah. Just little bones. And it's like I hear this joke I'm like what if
my phone number is one yeah here's a perfect woman she's completely so skinny
that she doesn't even exist and you she's only you can see the bikini part of her
okay what do you guys think that's interesting yeah I'm intrigued which
they would probably think oh great hello why hello thanks for calling the mental
health hotline yeah big surprise they're doing mental health jokes as if that's
fucking real if you are obsessive-compulsive press one
repeatedly. If you're a codependent, please ask someone to press 2 for you. If you have
multiple personalities, press 3, 4, 5, and 6. If you are paranoid, we know who you are
and what you want. Stay in the line so we can trace your call. If you're delusional,
press 7 and your call will be transferred to the mothership. If you're schizophrenic,
listen carefully and a small voice will tell you which number to press. Blah blah blah
blah blah. If you're dyslexic, good bullshit. If you're, um, if you have low self-esteem,
please hang up. All our operators are too busy to talk to you. First of all, that's
That's like fucking way more than nine numbers.
Yeah, that is way more than nine.
And listen to this one here.
This is some liberal fucking bullshit.
Your mom is so fat when she steps on a scale I see sex, free sex, free sex tonight.
Oh, and it says right there it's actually a Chinese girl's phone number.
And it says your mom is Chinese.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's messed up.
Listen to this one.
I mean, this is kind of what I think they want to do to the Constitution.
this is 20 things to do before you die. I don't know if you guys see this one, but
if you want to go through this, I mean, these are kind of like they want to add
these to the Constitution. These are things that people have to do and it's
number one is look at see-through glass and when someone is on the other side
shout, "Oh my god, I'm hideous." It's like, really? Come on, man. That's rude. That's
fucking rude. Bring a big chair into the elevator facing away from the door and
when someone walks in, dramatically turn and say, "We've been expecting you." Look at
- I'm gonna read this fucking bullshit.
This is about some bullshit medical doctor crap here.
- Okay.
- This one's disgusting to me.
But I'm gonna read it just so everyone knows
how pissed off I am.
Doctor, my husband just can't have enough sex.
A married woman goes to her doctor's office
and starts complaining.
Yeah, go figure.
- Yep.
- It's just too much, doctor.
My husband just wants to sex me up all the time.
In the bed, in the kitchen, in the backyard,
after dinner, before breakfast, standing up, sitting down,
and I can't take it anymore.
Is there something that I can give him?
The smirking female doctor then takes a prescription pad,
writes something, and says,
"Here, give him my phone number.
"It's sex-free sex, free sex 2-9."
- And this is just some bullshit, a salesman position,
right, and they think this is okay.
English is not my mother language,
so ignore any grammatical mistaking.
They think that that's okay for someone
not speak English first of all. Yeah. And so here's the actual fucking joke. A guy
is interviewed for a salesman position. The interviewer asking the guy to take
his laptop saying, "Let's see if you can convincing me to buy this laptops. I want
you to walk in again thinking of me as a customer." The guy walked out as the
interviewer said but didn't came in. The interviewer calls him to get in but the
guy isn't there anymore. The interviewer realizing that the guy had just stole
his laptop so he went to check the guy's phone number from his resume and start
calling him. The guy answers and the interviewer speaking immediately say
bring me my laptop now it has all my work documents, which the guy replied on to by
saying are you buying it. It's like listen buddy go back to your fucking
country. It's that fucking simple. Which guy in the story needs to go back to his
country? Both of them. Okay I have this one's kind of intellectual. Are you guys ready for
intellectual one though yeah okay all right I'll just read it in college so
already you can see oh I was sick of this college I became confidential
bullshit in college I became obsessed with the concept of a doppelganger I
began a quest to find mine after a year and a half of tracking down leads I
uncovered his phone number I immediately called him but the line was busy it's
kind of it's a thinker it's more philosophical hmm I don't get it but I
guess like I okay well how about okay well what are then what about this one I
was standing at the bar one night minding my own business this is another
intellectual wonder this fat that's in all capitals oh my god ugly - I think
it's okay yeah yeah fat things okay to be an ugly chick - these yeah fat I think
it's in capitals it stands for fat as duck ugly chick came up behind me grab my
behind which well and said you're kind of cute you got a phone number I said
"Yeah, you got a pen?" She said, "Yeah, I got a pen." I said, "You better get back in it
before the farmer misses you." Wow. That's actually fucking fire. That's actually fucking
serious. Yeah, that could actually, that maybe is a farm animal type. I'm okay. This farm
animal type ugly girl. Yeah, if maybe these jokes were more along the lines of, yeah,
so a fat ugly girl walks up to me and I said, "You're a complete fucking cow." You're a
you're a monster you literally should be skinned like a bear and i'm gonna skin
through you
you're a much a year monster you i honestly throw a pokeball at you and
catch you like a poke here's a good joke
a woman who is completely as fat as lizzo tap me on the shoulders at a bar
said
her there
per a their guy you are a pretty mama yet and i agree
either of the guy who's completely fat at the top of the time people always
for a girl with a fat top and a tiny little ways and a black shirt, short SJW blonde hair,
right?
Jeans on, so, "Hey, pretty mama."
And I said, "What the hell are you talking about, you fucked up girl?
You almost look like a guy."
Yeah.
Look at this one here.
This is disrespectful.
This one is just disrespecting officers of the law.
Yeah.
And it's so fucked up that they have to deal with this shit.
I think it's bullshit.
It's bullshit, but let me tell it.
a police officer told once told me
will never forget nine eleven and i said
of course you own it's your phone number sex free sex free sex tonight
and that's they're saying that's the cops phone and listen everybody knows
that when you will need to call the police you call six six six set three
three six two nine six three six
three six six six three six and i would i would i have now what i would i'm
I'm really asking about this joke and I'm curious about is that's not enough
numbers for a phone number. They're missing the area code and normally I'd
think okay well if the area code might just be the area code we're in but this
woman's Chinese I don't know any area codes in China. It might be a Chinese area
code and I might get the number completely wrong. It's a different joke.
There's a different joke. I was just remembering one that we told earlier.
Basically, if an SJW wrote it, it's probably San Francisco area code, Seattle area code,
Austin area code, Worcester Brooklyn area code, North Korea area code.
There's so many hipsters in North Korea, they all have the same hair cut.
Because Donald Trump is the 45th president, the hotel in North Korea is missing the 45th
floor.
Really?
I'm serious.
That's so fucked up.
The hotel, all the...
What happened to you?
There was something crunchy in that drink.
What?
I think there was a grain of sand in this Arizona energy drink.
That's how you know that it's honestly organic.
like guys. I heard the hipsters in in North Korea. They go to well first of
all they go to Starbucks. Yeah, yeah, that's a no brainer normally and we go
to Starbucks week. Some people will get coffee cake. I heard in North Korea.
They get they get yellow cake uranium because they like really nuclear. Oh in
North Korea, because they're so hipster people go and they say what the hell
nobody's walking around. It's like nobody lives here. There must be some
kind of camps. First of all, they're not in camps are all inside. They're on
phones yeah I heard that in North Korea they're so hipster that a lot of people
actually get killed for trying to swim across the mainstream or if we're trying
to go to under trying to go under yeah trying to leave the other yeah trying
to yeah they know how they go underground they try to cut yeah kind of
yeah it's some bullshit happening over there the Kim family is fucking complete
gay hipster bullshit. Him? Like Eminem's wife? OMG I just put that together.
Holy crap. Eminem? Wait like the candy? He's actually named after candy?
That's some gay bullshit. I thought he was an actual fucking patriot because of bagpipes
from Baghdad, but it turns out he's not. Another thing I heard about North Korean
hipsters apparently, and I mean I just heard this, but I heard that you know
you know, after they kill them for trying to go into the mainstream. I heard that
they violate the bodies before they're cool.
They're still warm. It's pretty good and they like they like turn them up or
that's bad and food that's bad. You know probably loves that the fucking gay
brothers, Ben and Jerry, the ice cream,
ice cream is actually been joking and jerry's john jerry illson yeah
Jerry basically you know how that ice cream gets made they been fucks Jerry in
the butthole and he comes out all the cream into the ice cream that's how they
make the fucking Stephen Colbert it's so good and Stephen Colbert was actually
insanely fucking Republican for a long time and then they fuck and then he
changed up yeah he changed up when when he finally you know what you know to
The vaccine.
The vaccine did that to him.
The vaccine as soon as he got the Pfizer shot, you know.
As soon as he got the Fauci-ouchie, I think is what they were calling it.
And then he does this whole, he does a whole song about the vaccine on his little show.
Yeah.
And it's like, listen buddy, first of all, not to bring it back to Eminem, but like if
you listen to even fucking four songs from Relapse, you'd have an entirely different point
of view.
Have you seen that video?
No.
The vaccine?
Why would I see anything?
It's a video, it's Stephen Colbert, and then a bunch of people dressed up like needles
come out and it's sickest shit ever and what does he do what did he like beat
the shit out of the needles like a family guy chicken? Nope he does a dance with them he
does the peewee Herman tequila dance with them. Oh because there's tequila
because there's worms in the... Peewee Herman. Yeah that's right because there's worms in
the vaccine is that what he's trying to get across? Yeah I don't know I think so
probably I heard there are worms. Or maybe he's trying to say the vaccine will make you
so anti-heterosexual that you'll actually get into singing?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Where rapping is actually what straight people do, but singing is like a girls and gays kind
of thing?
Yeah.
Like dancing on a table, really?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
What are you trying to watch?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the dancing.
It's all over.
You're just watching a video on your phone?
This is...
Alright now you have to okay because you're doing this you have because you're so in love with your phone
You have to give out your phone number on air right now to end the episode
What did you give out your well actually before do you should do that, but also?
Seattle and Portland by tickets it's coming up swag poop comm slash shows and shirts at swag poop swag poop comm slash shop
Oh, yeah, go check out the shirts in the shows
But Patrick is Patrick does he does have to get his actual real phone number? Okay? No funny business
You want your real phone number? 617-299-6257.
All right, good enough for me. Bye!