- Podcast about list.
The cup and spoon.
(screeching)
- Penis.
- That can't be the first thing we ever say on the podcast.
- That can't be.
- You can't say penis.
- You cannot say penis.
- That is fucking crazy.
- What?
- That it cannot be the first thing.
- I'm just nervous.
I thought it was gonna be funny.
- You can't forever now.
- No one's gonna like it.
- I mean, who knows how long this podcast will go,
but for as long as it does,
the first word ever uttered on this god damn show
is gonna be penis.
- Penis.
Well, you guys are saying it too.
We weren't saying it.
You're saying it right now.
We're saying it now because we're reprimanding you.
You can't start a podcast reprimanding.
Okay, that's not-
One of the members whose name is Cameron, by the way.
Oh yeah, I guess we should introduce ourselves.
I guess I'm freaking Caleb.
Yeah, I'm a guest.
You know what?
We had you on as a guest originally, but you should just join the show.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, now that you're-
That's the kind of thing I do.
in. Yeah you're like pretty much the most useless at this time in 2018 you're
pretty much the most useless person I know. So yeah you might as well just join.
We like to just create guests in the host that's kind of how we roll at
Two Fly Guys. Two Fly Guys? I don't know. I'm rethinking the name now. You don't like Two Fly Guys?
Well I guess now it doesn't make sense. I mean if you ask me I think it
still makes sense there's two fly guys oh yeah one and a one guy fly yeah one guy
who can fly one guys flies down yeah it's yours
no it's not Cameron's no it's closed guys I fucking I'll say one thing I am so
happy to be podcasting with you guys but then also 2018 this is gonna be the best
year ever yes I have a strong feeling that the midterms are coming around are
are they are they maybe they already happened I don't I'm not really up to
date on polit political stuff like that I think well yeah at this point in 20
I think I'm very political yeah I'm worried that there's maybe some fucking
ghoul about to be elected Oh bloody hell in two years yeah it's probably gonna be
fucking Hillary who do you think's gonna I hope so Loki Hillary God willing it's
Bernie yeah Sanders did he is actually legit yeah it's true I back that fool
like nobody else bro. Bernie and I definitely and when the election comes
up I definitely will not forget to vote. I will definitely go out in
Massachusetts where we all live and I will vote for him. What about the Bernie
cast? I don't think a political thing is our slant. I don't think that
we could that we could. I'm politically crazy though and slanted to the leftist
orientation. Sometimes maybe you're a little bit too crazy with your political stuff. Nah, nah.
uh... let's let's let's make a pact right now to pull back on the politics and
never do any politics and we won't get political eyes will be you guys so
this could be maybe the
the non-political so what do we call the pocket pocket and on political
three shit heads
well
because it's kind of putting their souls down what i did what i did i don't know
what it was a fairly short notice with microphone with his three was three
What's wrong with Dum Dums with Microphones? That's funny.
Three Dummies.
It's not a good name. It's not a good title.
Dum Dums with Microphones could have a cover art where we are holding dum dums like the lollipops like microphones.
That is fucking dumb.
Oh shit.
Or Dum Dums as Microphones.
What if we did Three Orny Dickheads?
Three Orny Dickheads?
Three Orny? Well it's like apostrophe.
No like I'm fucking orny.
Ornery?
Three apostrophe O-R-N-Y.
E-A-D-S. We're not really British.
Well that could be part of the joke.
Okay yeah, what about like a...
Alright, let's do a whole British podcast right now.
What's your attitude about...
I've got no attitude.
You have a British attitude?
I have a really dry attitude.
Yeah, wait, I can't tell if you're joking or not.
You're acting so fucking dry to me.
I'm not dry.
I've not become dry.
I don't know how to parse this. Is he being...
Is he joking with me or being completely earnest?
good name parse this oh shit middle finger blurred hours yeah no but then
they won't know parse unknown parse unknown pause unknown pause with three
full Danes don't pause this what I don't pause this is good pussy taste testers
pussy three-point taste testers eating the we did this dribbling yeah that out
though I you know it's you think it's funny now cuz we're in college but in a
couple years that'll sneak up on you no trouble no no no there's no it will
never age poorly to be nastily sexual three pussy dribblers but we shouldn't
name it like racial talk or something like that cuz I have a feeling that in
the coming years racial humor will become more and more accepted pop yeah
I mean yeah we said we wouldn't get into politics but once Bernie's and one
Bernie's and one and probably once and I honestly though I think that gosh my what
I'm hoping my predictions I feel like by 2020 or 2021 I think that millions of
S.J.W.s will die in 2020. That is going to be sad as fuck for like at least
hundreds of thousands of people. So us three we're in college right now we're
completely S.J.W.s do you think that maybe we'll always be S.J.W.s or maybe
we'll flip and we'll become anti-S.J.W.?
I don't know. I don't know. I'm really into rights. I'm really into rights.
I like rights too.
Amendments. Amendments. I fucking love amendments.
I've always been, consider myself on the side of rights,
but I'm starting to kind of slide backwards into kind of hating rights for all people.
Do you think that maybe, I don't know, like
woke culture will go too far in the future and people will get,
people will start becoming post-woke?
People, here's something, here's a little something I have been working on in anticipation of us
starting a podcast, which we're just doing, is a little saying. Yeah. Which is that people are
so concerned about human rights, they're not paying attention to global warming, which will
leave no humans left. Holy shit. So that's a pretty good example of something that I will go back on
in a year. Yeah, well, here's the other thing about that is we've promised already no political crap.
That's not political, that's human interest.
I don't know.
Or human society.
Human nature.
That's humanities?
That's like philosophical.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I didn't learn that word yet, I'm in third grade.
Yeah.
Man, I fucking hate third grade.
I know, it sucks.
Bro, this shit sucks, man.
You ever see the teacher bend over and her big fanny goes in your face when they're big?
F the teacher, bro, I don't want to talk about--
With her big denim skirt?
I don't want to talk about her--
What kind of sexual fucking teacher do you have?
She got a denim--
A tight denim skirt?
Not a tight denim skirt.
skirt you know what I'm talking about.
It's got a cheerleader outfit.
It's got an apple embroidered on the front.
Dude, I fucking hate my teacher Mrs. Linda Cardellini as Velma.
I hate my fucking nanny Vicky.
Yeah.
Yeah, nanny McPhee is a bitch as well.
Actually, I honestly, when I was a kid I honestly watched
I honestly watched
That bitch's tooth is weird as fuck.
It's pro-tuberance.
I never saw it. You never saw it? You know what she looks like?
Wait, say it again. I don't remember.
But you were a little bit like, she's a butter face and she's stacked.
Who? Nanny McPhee?
Oh. She's a little stacked.
She's got a butt like a shelf. I mean, honestly, it's more like a butter tooth.
I think it's really her teeth that's the problem.
She's literally built like a mole. Also, her wicked butt.
Butter moles.
Soul.
Yeah, some mole soul.
I mean, now, if you're saying, would I rather beat it on Nanny McPhee,
would I rather hit that Nanny McFanny, or would I rather hit that,
what's that other bitch that used to be Nanny McPhee but was hot?
Amelia Bedelia?
No, the fucking hoe who went up the--
Mrs. Doubtfire?
The bitch with the--
Mrs. Doubtfire.
The bitch with the umbrella.
You know I hate Mrs. Doubtfire.
No, you don't.
She looks too much like Robin Williams.
Why?
She just-- what do you mean why?
God cursed her.
What is the name of the--
why can't I remember Nanny McPhee,
and I can't remember the woman with the umbrella?
Lyle Lyle Crocodile.
You better shut up and tell me the right answer.
What is her name, man?
I'm freaking out.
I'm fucking bugging right now.
I don't think I'm going to tell you.
You know, though.
I know.
I'm leaving.
Yeah.
You guys both know.
Poppins. Fuck you and fuck you! Fuck you guys, bro. You won't help me out? That's how we're
gonna start this podcast is I'm out there, I need a life raft. I need a tube. I need an
inner tube.
If there's one thing that I know, it's that people don't like it when somebody just makes
a bunch of references. And I vow to never, ever do that. And I won't even reference Mary
Poppins.
You won't even tell me when I need you to, though? That's fucked.
Because it makes me look like a know-it-all.
I make references because I...
You know why I make references?
Why?
Because I does what I like and I likes what I do.
What's that from?
That's a reference to Mary Poppins.
Oh shit, I didn't know that.
So you're some kind of fucking Poppins head.
Yeah.
You know everything about this movie.
I know a lot about it.
No you don't.
Yeah, it came out in 1932.
That's some bullshit.
You're a fucking liar.
You don't even know her name.
How do you know if I'm...
I do know her name.
Mary Poppins.
I was testing you.
Fucking know-it-all ass.
it all again. Damn, I knew that you would know the correct answer. I don't even
know her middle name. What do you guys? Do you guys have a comb? Man, I got shit in my
hair. Yeah, yeah, yeah, here you go. Thank you, man. Oh, God. So there's gum in your hair.
Yeah, there's a bunch of shit in my hair. Oh, man, I'm fucking pulling my own hair out with this fucking comb.
Don't pull that out with the comb. Yeah, let's just use a different comb.
You guys ever use a comb and like half your hair comes out when you
you to get it in that fucked camera you ever do that
more like a hair brush, though yeah yeah, the air brush will do that. If it
comes do it like you ever get in the shower like an air your hair is just
falling all over the place. I don't know what that is from my from your head,
like your hair is falling over the place. No at all yeah, you are no at all
yeah. I hate your no at all ass
and I'm a I'm a playboy yeah in twenty eighteen year playboy. I'm a
millionaire playboy here play mobile. No, that will be in twenty nineteen. I will
get into play mobile. That's a promise. That's a promise. You're letting
everyone know right now. Yeah. Okay. Shit. Shit. Man, I'm fucking I don't know
guys. I've been I've looked at the scale this morning. You know what it said
what three hundred fifty pounds three hundred. You're down to three hundred
fifty. Congrats. That's great. That's huge. That's gigantic. Well, that's
- It's really tight, I mean that's not gigantic.
- That's a lot of weight.
- That's a big step, lots of big steps onto the scale.
- Yeah, you must have been taking lots of big steps
to lose weight.
- You must have taken a big step on the scale.
- I don't know what's happening,
but I'm losing a lot of weight really fast.
- At a rapid pace.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- I haven't changed anything.
I'm still eating a lot of hot dogs from 7-Eleven.
- Yeah.
- And a lot of--
- The Italian job.
- The Italian job?
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, that I'm still buying the DVDs from 7-Eleven?
When you're in there getting the Italian job in hot dogs?
Oh yeah.
Drinking a monster...
They're coming out, I learned this recently, they came out with it's Monster Energy Gronk.
Gronkowski.
After Rob Gronkowski, for a famous Patriots player.
Yeah, I love the Patriots.
I think they're gonna win this year.
I think they're gonna win the Super Bowl.
You think?
In 2019?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think you might be right.
They're looking good.
It's gonna be really big.
Yeah, they're looking very, very good.
Tom Brady, that guy.
I
bro said they're good if he leaves the Patriots it's going to like be like 9/11 for my mom
be yeah 9/11 mm-hmm it would be like 9/11 in Boston yeah yeah that was the marathon I
feel like 9/11 in Boston's gonna happen in like 2024 here's the thing about the marathon
bombing bro who isn't you know it's fucked up is like imagine that's the marathon that
you won right and it all gets it all gets overshadowed cuz Mark Wahlberg in blood
yeah like somebody won that marathon and was like really proud of it but nobody
remembers because these fucking cuz it's Joe car these fools yeah are in his
brother plow car that's not a clue plow coon Goku and Glico yeah
plow coon is Greedo don't ever say Greedo in front of this guy you know
he's a big Star Wars fan Patrick you like Star Wars big Star Wars fan I never
liked Star Wars yeah I think we should start in 2018 you never seen it no I
actually don't think I watched the Star Wars I think I might watch the Star Wars
movies in two years yeah the show a show yeah Jon Favreau is gonna direct it
about a bounty hunter that's not too fascinating to me
Mandalorian I thought that was the bugs no don't they make a lot of products
there never heard of what I thought that was a country you're thinking of
anything you think Geonosis is a country no Mandalorian Mandalorian no shit no I
think that you convert to Mandalorian when you go to prison oh yeah I think
that's right that's a white kingdom oh yeah if you guys went to jail would you
guys join which sect I don't know I hope I don't go to jail I'd probably join the
enlightened atheists I will never go to jail I know one thing right now in 2018
is that by 2023 I will never three months uh-huh never never will never
have to record never any sort of podcast with you through a phone like a max B
interview that will never happen it's never gonna happen never I know for a
effect that's not gonna happen would you guys ever play like a gay-ass board game
or something a gay-ass board game like imagine imagine imagine if we if like we
made money off playing a gay-ass board game fuck no I would like what like
sorry yeah probably what game what other yeah or like I like magic the gathering
or some fucking oh yeah I'm gonna hire some it was like Wizards of the Coast
game yeah we're into the coast game specifically no fuck I wouldn't do that
either. Wizards of the Coast, you know what those are called in my brain? Surfers.
How the hell they do that? It must be magic. It's wax. A lot of wax on there.
God damn it. I'm being a know-it-all again. I hope that I figure this out. I hope
eventually you dumb it down. I feel like for people who are listening to this up
to episode 1, which that's a good name for a podcast. We should, that is a great
episode 1. We should try that one. But people who are listening to this podcast from
episode 1 onward, I feel like you can maybe look at this and now's your chance
to kind of frame to look through this lens and frame it this way. This is maybe a
story arc about a guy learning not to be a know-it-all. That's true and maybe one
guy who's trying to avoid serious prison time, maybe another guy who has a kind of
a unsuspecting issue, some kind of issue with his facial and head hair, yeah,
running at him like a bullet train. Yeah. Who knows? Wow, that's a good lens to
look at the show. Yeah, that's a good name for the show, story arc. Stories from our
friendship what about story call it what about worries from our French oh what
about act one act one act one act one scene one what if we have we'd have to
change it every time you guys like electronic a conscious hip-hop what if
we call it the prestige the prestige as I like the movie yeah I think that the
whole show is about a movie well we could call it the turn then no that's
what people would think that it's about a type of bird wait what is that song
called? What if we called it Exhibit A?
Keg Push Coast.
Exhibit A is good actually.
Now I think about that.
Exhibit A. What if we called it The Black
Album? Yeah. I don't think The Black
Album would work. That's my favorite so far
I think. Yeah. It's no, cause it's an
album, it's not an album. You don't make an
album with podcasts. Okay, so you want it to be called The Black Podcast
you're saying? Yeah. Okay.
We could do that. That works for me. The Black Podcast?
Yeah. And it could have a good name
for the show. And then we put in the description
reference to the black album yeah true the black podcast I got that black
parentheses the parenthetical parentheses it's a reference to Jay-Z uh-huh the
best podcaster alive ask about him yeah what the lyrics to the bike what do you
guys think we're gonna get into over the years I feel like and the thing is you
know we know each other like two days ago what's gay shit clothing yeah I don't
I don't think I'd ever get into that.
- I meant like what are we gonna get into like hijinks wise.
- It'd be pretty gay if you even thought at some point
that you considered yourself into clothing
and that was the first thing that came to mind.
- It'd be gay to spend a lot of money on a jacket.
- Yeah, that would be pretty whack.
- Yeah.
- And we say whack.
- Have you seen this after paychecks?
- It's 2018 and we say whack and dope.
- Yeah, that's, you would be seriously herby.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you'd be herby.
- Yeah, you'd be herby as shit.
- They should make a slang word for bussing.
- I agree.
something's busting yeah so we'll know yeah I don't know what it would mean yet
but they should be like that's bus and bus and yeah yeah what and Riz or no
there should be something for Riz yeah that's a really good idea yeah it should
be that word should mean something we'll figure it out I mean it's a first
episode yeah a couple of years story arc yeah stories from our friendship this one
is called rising action yeah or what's it called beginning what's the beginning
called rising black podcast that's what we can call it rising podcast yeah that's
a good name that is a good name that's a really good art because I'm we have to
make some art - I don't know you just throw some shit together in Photoshop I
I guess. What about a picture of us and it's cartoony?
Oh, boy.
And we're sitting and it's our three faces next to each other with microphones.
You know what's really good for that if it's going to be a cartoon look is this app called
Bitmoji.
Oh, shit. We can do a Bitmoji.
Oh, that just dropped, right?
I think so.
I can't remember when that dropped.
It's integrated into Snapchat.
Oh, right. Snapchat.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm on Snapchat.
Hella.
Yeah.
I'm on there day and night.
night I just got one I added him here he has I've seen his friends list he had a
lot of friends I do you guys want to come over to my house and play the brand new
fucking Sega Genesis we could yeah it's pretty awesome my mom though and my
grandma yeah I would take I have to check with my mom because I haven't been
born yet yeah they're putting new Pokemon into Pokemon go really holy shit
Pokemon go honestly in 2018 if you play Pokemon go you should be killed yeah
a
Yeah, he's a legend. He's really nice too. Yeah, I don't think anything bad will happen to these people and he's funny
They won't do anything bad. Yeah
Who else am I talking to on my space?
Wait, Patrick about a sneeze. I almost had to sneeze. Oh, that's okay
Do you imagine like I mean I think just have like a cold because it's like the winter, you know, yeah
Yeah, imagine if there's like a fucking like
Imagine like a cold that was so bad. Uh-huh. It's like I'm doing fine right now. Yeah, imagine a cold
That's so fucking bad. It takes you out completely. That would suck. You actually just reminded me of something
I don't know why this or that reminded me of this there. It feels completely unrelated almost but I've actually been I've been doing some prank calls
Over over Skype. I've been doing and I say it gives me like a custom phone number
I sent my area code to Ukraine and I've been
Prank calling a bunch of Russian officials. Oh nice. That's yeah
- Yeah.
- Wait, how did you get their number?
- I'm like, come fuck me, come fuck me,
you know, that type of shit.
- That's good, that's good.
- Yeah, and I think I might do that for several years.
- That's a good ass idea.
- Wow.
- Yeah, and I don't know what made me think of that.
- Yeah.
- Bro, I would never fucking ever get a vaccine.
- No, no shot, no shot, get it?
- That's right.
- Damn.
- You know why?
'Cause I feel like it would make me
actually mentally disabled.
- Yeah.
- In 2018, I am already.
- Yeah, maybe it would reverse it then.
- Yeah, actually though, for real, I think probably
if there was some kind of vaccine,
I would probably get the first one
and then forget to get all the other ones.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Including the second part of the first one.
- I might do that too. (laughing)
- Yeah, so, you know.
And then it would probably be all right.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'd get all of them just in case
of the lawsuit that comes out.
- I really hope in the future--
- True, that's a great point.
If there was some kind of vaccine that could hurt you
and you knew ahead of time, you should get it
because then you'd probably get a fat payout
'cause it kills enough fucking football players.
- Oh, yeah, that would be great.
Yeah, are you kidding me?
You know what I was I did.
What do
I was just thinking recently to just on the kind of I really
really would love to someday wear a chin diaper.
That's a great idea.
Yeah.
Yeah, a diaper on my face.
I would love to be forced to do that.
I would love if there was some way that we could connect over
like some kind of like maybe some kind of web system to every
single computer in the world.
Would be amazing.
that would be because it's like that we're just gonna have to burn this to a
CD and it's gone forever I know it's like a hand it out in Times Square that sucks
yeah Times Square Boston Times Square where we in front of the Primark which
is brand-new yeah oh my god that you guys did you guys see Black Panther this
week I loved it yeah I thought it was powerful
it's really good I'm not just talking about the powerful characters who were
stronger mm-hmm then black any other characters in my MC black Panther is a
a lasting image in it and he will never die. Mm-Hmm true always be alive and
I've actually been thinking that Chadwick Boseman looks is something's up
with him. I saw this really good speaking. I saw this really good
painting called Wildwood just came out by Peter McConville. You're gay bro.
You look at paintings. Yeah, bro. You a girl. It's a winter would want to send
the winter world forever decide on it. We got a side on a name yeah, okay,
let's all right all right, let's so what are we? We can't be the black
podcast anymore, black uprising podcast yeah, well, because because you just
did remind me that black panther to sure about that and that's people are
good. That's going to be bad for seo. We need good seo on our name room, the
best seo possible yeah.
Well yeah, what
what's a good you are cordially invited to the Caleb Cameron and Patrick
podcast that sounds good that sounds really fit our vibe we're a little more
casual net no the podcast that is the best the best the podcast that's the
beast beast Ford kiss the beast the business did cordialized a latent what
police did please like the leaf Lord kiss the beatless what I don't know what
was that there's something wrong no try that again
(mumbling)
- Wait, wait, hold on, wait, hold on.
- Blastin'.
- Can I get a clean take of that?
- Yeah.
(mumbling)
- Did you just say, podcast,
- That's incredible.
- That's a great name, we should go with that.
- We should go with that.
I also thought of an alternate name just now.
- What's that?
- I think we should call it, Comedy on Video,
just in case we ever decide to do any video stuff.
- I think we have the budget for that.
- Well then we can shorten it to--
- Video podcast suck.
- No, comedy on video, we shorten it to CO video, CO vid.
that good not good that's good that's short video the only video podcast that
works are like fire and the kid yeah awesome yeah that shit's good
that's just a dope or the one with Bobby Lee and though the orange man not Trump
bad friend what do you mean orange the orange man is Trump who's Trump I don't
know who that is Donald never heard of a man yeah I don't even know who that you're
gonna hear a lot about him soon wait are you talking about the Patrick it's 1834
we're not gonna hear shit about that guy no no even nobody great-grandpa Trump
Dundler Oh Baron of the land I know him actually yeah you know he said he knows
link he knows a Lincoln big Lincoln Abe Lincoln Abe Lincoln president yeah
that's that's crazy you must have met him on a boat trip because when you said
because when you said Abe I was thinking Abraham like Abraham yeah oh you know I
hate that guy yeah yeah he is he is a wishy-washy son of a bitch I agree and
make up his mind kill that son yeah I think that we should call it Caleb cast
about his two friends okay we cool with that no yeah I don't know I because I
knew that we didn't have a name I did come up with a list of like names we
could use okay well but I don't think I don't want to do it is about a fucking
list or it's the only podcast or whatever it's a list of about podcasts
or list of list podcast that doesn't sound bad the about list podcast about
list is good about list but that does it could be like dot dot what does that
mean about list like we're talking about like about Schmidt yeah there's
something about list there's podcast about list there's that's good there's
podcast about list yeah all right we're done there's podcast about list there's
pocket here let's see if it's taking fuck dude that's already taken there's
podcast it's a fucking bar stool who's your daddy who's your daddy people I
didn't know oh my god there's podcast there's podcast yeah we could have this
in the cover. We could have the the about Jack Nicholson about Schmidt.
The cover art looks similar it could be about list. All right well maybe we'll
just do the about list podcast. Yeah. Is that fair? There's about list podcast. Yeah and
when I go home and I upload this I won't fuck it up. Okay yeah. Remember Patrick
the about list podcast. About list podcast. Think of it think of it like a
- A-L-P. - Not lists, right?
I think lists is better.
- A-L-P.
- The About List Podcast.
- Okay.
- With Cameron, Caleb, and Petey.
Remember, whatever name you wanna go by.
- Okay.
All right, I don't think I need,
no, I mean, you know me,
I work at a restaurant right now,
I'm remembering stuff all the time.
I remember people's orders.
- You have a fucking amazingly sharp memory
and there's no way that you'll hit your head
on the way home.
- There's no way, uh-uh, no way in hell
I'm going to hit my head.
- You're top of your class in college right now.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna trip over anything
at the subway station and hit the back of my head
really hard that I see stars.
- Yeah, we don't even have to worry about that.
- I mean, Pat, you're the smartest guy I know, man.
- You're a know-it-all.
You know it all.
I mean, I didn't mean that derogatorily.
You know everything.
- Guys, I-- - About List podcast.
- The About List podcast with--
- Caleb, Cameron, and PD.
Uh-huh PD PD PE T E Y PD. All right guys. Well, this has been the about list
podcast episode one. We will I guess I just thought of a prank. What's a prank?
What if we went straight after this? So most podcasts episode one episode two
episode three. I guess most of us do do that episode five assuming they get that
far dude. He said that do do
whatever. What about well? Okay, then meanwhile someone opens up someone opens
up spot to have podcast on spotify right now yeah okay. I they literally just did
a fucking big ass deal with that shit for brains Joe Rogan. Oh yeah, he's a total
yellow bellied. He's a coward. He's a pigeon toad coward. He we someone opens
a bar the about list podcast on spotify. They see episode one episode eighty
seven episode eighty eight. I'm sorry not you think we should skip right
pretty good prank skip eighty six episodes. All right, let's do it. Well
Yeah, well that would... I don't think it would be... it would skip an 85, right?
Yeah.
Alright, let's do it.
Yeah, okay.
[laughter]
Okay.
Alright.
Well, we'll see you in 87.
Yeah, alright.
Which we'll record right after this.
Alright, let's go!
[BLANK_AUDIO]