Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Okay.
- I'll stop riding my bike here before we do this.
I come in here and I'm just like drenched in sweat.
- I looked at the, I looked at your bike
when I was walking in earlier.
- Yeah.
- And it was sitting so, the seat,
the black leather seat was sitting so perfectly in the sun
that when you sit back down on it,
it's gonna brand the logo of the bike seat into your ass.
- Good, I need that.
- It's gonna get so fucking hot.
- Yeah.
- You are gonna have a red, pink ass.
- Good. - No spanks.
- I need that right now.
- You're gonna have a pink ass, no spanking.
- Dude, I'm so sweaty.
Or like, it just started hitting me.
- It's so hot outside.
- We need an AC in here.
- I gave up on being clean yesterday.
I just sweated up.
- Yeah.
- I sweat through my headphones.
- Me too.
- My headphones have a canvas outer thing
and it started to smell like a gym sock.
And so I think I might have to throw away my headphones.
- Damn. - Yeah.
- I think you can easily replace that.
- No, I think they have to just completely
go into the trashcan pretty soon.
- Yeah. - I went,
I skated yesterday for like three hours
and I don't think I've ever felt
the back of a pair of shorts so wet.
- Yeah.
- Like it was like wet and they smelled salty.
You ever do, you ever sweat through a pair of jeans?
Dude, yeah.
That's hard to do.
Before the show on Thursday, I had to change my pants.
I have a photo.
Hold up.
I hope it's not mid-change because I do not want to see this goober's penis.
That sounds freaking disgusting.
It's not that.
No, it's just the back of my jeans and they're completely, it looks like I pissed out of
my ass.
Stop sagging.
It's disrespectful.
I'm not sagging.
Look at how high those pants are up.
It's way too low, man.
Yeah, those are sagging.
You're completely sagging.
those are sagging doing a pale like halfway down your crack. Do you know
what that you know what that means in prison having a completely wet ass what
means that you beat yourself really haven't heard no I mean you were
standing with another guy and he peed he peed himself okay and it got on to you
yeah or that you sat in a puddle or you were sledding I would hate you know
what's the worst part of prison I hear is dropping the soap yeah yeah I hear
that that's not I don't remember why then you can't get clean because I just
hear that I hear that a really big problem in prison is just seriously just
dropping the soap on the ground. Yeah, yeah, because I the thing is it gets
soap completely dirty, because they don't have like body wash or anything.
Yeah, so you know you could take a shower. I don't have cells in blue and
I heard that I heard on prison. They don't wash themselves with soap. They
wash themselves with rope. Yeah, I heard it's rope. You think of soap on a
rope? Yeah, I heard they use the rope part. I heard if they're cleaning
that, and they're still like a watch. That's why they're incarcerated. It's
like a wash cloth. Oh, if it's a bad enough prison, like if it's like Alcatraz
like sing sing they make you wash yourself with an onion really is that
true I would hate to get a boiled onion trash I need to shut Alcatraz down I
know it needs to go it's fun you imagine I saw it can you imagine being in Alcatraz
right now you're you're so you're eating these horrible meals you're locked up
you can't get a family and then and then wash yourself excuse me Patrick and then
on top of that you are haunted by Al Capone's ghost yep that's right I would
like to they need to give those guys the Alcatraz needs one of those guys who has
iPhone in prison and makes TikToks. I saw the island. They used to have mac and cheese in the
food court, but it's COVID right now, so now they don't. They're just talking about prison and stuff.
I saw Alcatraz when I was in SF. I saw the island there. We all did.
We all saw Alcatraz. Oh yeah, we all did. Well, I went more recently and I saw it. It's changed
since then. The island's way bigger. It's changed since then. No, no, there was a dark cloud over it.
As if that's stands for what seriously fearsome for serious felony that he
commanded you in Alcatraz. Yeah, how did you wait? What were you doing around that Alcatraz prison?
Investigating the dark cloud likely story. What had it look like from behind bars?
You should there should be you should be able to do like a prison exchange program where you can
choose one like really cool prison you want to go to for like a month or so if you're like
imprisoned already yeah and you're in like a lame you if you're like a state
penitentiary yeah that'd be cool I want to go to Alcatraz for like a few days
where is sing sing I've heard of that in movies sing sing I don't know what
singing in Rikers and stow away Rikers Rikers is just like a reference or a
joke you're making that I didn't know no I don't know what sing sing is you they
should reopen Alcatraz as like the drunk tank we're like if you go they put you
on a raft and send you to Alcatraz for the night. That would be such a better
deterrent. Oh, Sing Sing is in New York. I would completely stop drunk driving in San
Francisco. It's in Austin-ing New York. Sing Sing? It's a maximum security prison.
I could get in.
Sing Sing's name comes from the Indian phrase "Sin Sink" which means stone on stone.
The thing about maximum security prisons is that it's stupid to call it maximum security
like you would never hear someone call a prison a minimum security prison.
We're sending you to minimum security prison.
Also I think that we need a further, we need an ultimate security prison.
says here in 1901 three years after Edison introduced the electric chair at
Sing Sing I didn't know he made the electric chair. He made everything electric.
Do you think he made the electric chair by accident?
You think he was trying to make like a... He was like okay let's see electric light bulb
yep okay telephone got it I guess like he's running out of ideas I guess a
it's a chair. Well, originally it was a plug in a chair. It was
just
chair.
He's looking at things around his room. I turn that electric. I
turn that like it killed the copyright royalties. Just really
start just drying up. We have the electric chair. Electric chair
ended up being a lot more useful than the electric table, which
was the other thing he invented the same day. You really it
really is like a like table that keeps your food hot, keeps it electric. It
kills anybody who's sitting on the
yeah, it's like a deterrent for cats. Yeah, it is so funny that electricity is
how they kill people. Yeah, that's yeah
like you might like what just do like a why not you just put them in a pool and
like put throw like a toaster in there or some electricity must feel cool,
though.
yeah I think you're electrocuted well you know I like you I've got a serious
electric you mean it kills you so you actually haven't been electrocuted
oh in six grade up when we were learning about electricity my teacher mr. stith
mr. stiff yeah mr. stiff shit mr. stiff and he had like Tiffany he had like
moles on his head oh he's a nice guy I didn't know why I brought up the moles
(laughing)
But he taught us how to make,
it was like an electric hot dog cooker
and it's literally a piece of wood with two screws
that you drill two screws and then you take a frayed cable
and then put it on the screws.
And when I was in, I made one at home,
even though he told us not to, and I made it at home
and then I was trying to move the,
I think I touched the hot dog,
or I was trying to take it off of the thing
and then I touched both--
- Does it mean you were trying to eat it?
Yeah, no, I ate it after.
I'm not denying that I ate the hot dog.
No, no, I was trying to get the hot dog off so I could eat it.
And then I touched both of the screws and then went like,
(imitates gun firing)
and then like, it literally was as Looney Tunes as it could.
- Yeah, that happened to me with my Game Boy charger.
I touched my Game Boy charger prongs.
- When my dad had an outlet that was completely detached
from the wall for a really long time,
and one time I touched like the back of it,
and yeah, I remember just sitting there,
I remember it felt like a full minute of me just like,
huh, this is interesting.
I can't move my body at all.
And I'm--
- Dude, it's the craziest feeling.
- Yeah, I just feel like (mimics electric motor)
I'm seeing all my bones.
- Yeah. - They're blue.
- I had for a split second, I was like,
if anyone saw me do that,
would they have seen my blue bones?
- I think they do, right?
- Yeah.
- How much electricity needs to go through you
to see your blue bones?
Cameron, since you're such a fact lord.
- Yeah, well, I have to defend the word electrocution
it's the coolest word ever. No you don't. It means it's literally the combination of electro and
execution. Nope. And it's so cool and people trying to dilute that word. It needs to be awesome and it
needs to just mean that you are literally killed by electricity. You think Edison like advertised
the electric chair with like like it's like a like big like flyer in a newspaper. I don't think
it is. I think that thing sells itself. It's like like the word all the letters are like
lightning bolts. It's like electrocution! The new way to kill prisoners!
Yeah, you could send one dollar in this ad to one Thomas Edison Road
in Edison, New Jersey, and we will send you a full Nickelodeon video or Nickelodeon film.
A dollar would get you a prisoner back then, I think.
Yeah, well, you send them a dollar, they send you a Nickelodeon film strip of just a man just
just getting killed by the electric chair. I don't play that little like
doodoo. I don't believe that Thomas Edison invented electricity. No, it's
Nikola Tesla. It was Ben Franklin. I think that it was actually the ancient
indigenous people of the Aztec world. Yeah, yep, and I think that they
probably stored it in their hand. I think it was actually the electrians
that is that who I'm thinking of yeah, they were yeah. They were they're
basically things are made out of electricity really. They were indigenous
an electro land. Oh, and was that it's an electric island? Oh, okay, that's what we
call it nowadays. Yeah, the old name is something we can't even pretty much
because it's an electries. Yeah, they used to be called in their language. It's
called zip zap yeah and they and their own language. They call themselves
Pikachu.
What yeah yeah, they look like Pikachu. They do yeah, they just like my kind of
One of the most famous electrocution...
You know there's a country where...
Electrocutors, what were they called?
What were we calling them?
Electroids.
One of the most famous electroids was a guy named...
And did you guys see there
who won the presidential
electrocution
electraction?
Over there? Who?
Hal Sparks. Yeah.
Just a guy.
yeah yeah that's not a real place. I really want to I would love to explore
every country in the world. I think I would really I think that we should go
to I don't know what there is there. I think we should go. I've been I've been
reading a book about about you guys to go camping in in like virgin forest or
whatever is where there's like no one has ever been. I feel like we should go
to an island or a forest where no human has ever set foot before and all of
can we plant a flag in it? Yes, okay, but then what if we discover a new animal
That would be incredible. But what if it has a million teeth? Then we would get it.
But what if it's a complete eater? Yeah, what if it's like a cat with a shark's mouth?
We could eat it before it eats us. Or we could bring a box to put it in.
Can we walk slowly at it like Elmer Fudd? Yeah.
And kill it? Well, if we've discovered a new--
Would you-- if you found a one-of-a-kind animal, would you kill it for no reason?
If it's running away. If it looked like a different--
If it looked like a different animal but then it turns out it's like a rare breed of some
like like it's like a deer with like okay a third antler it has giant giant eyes right
and a really sad face like it it's always like a frowner it always wants something
it's four legs and it's so cute it has it has a big big head and a little little tiny body
and he's covered in hair and he has no teeth is he running away from me and he's running away
and he's screaming for help. I kill him. Was that animal you and Simon made up? The
surpriser? The surpriser? Yeah. Yeah. Surpriser. I would not kill a surpriser.
You couldn't kill a surpriser because the surpriser would run away. Yeah you can't
kill a surpriser. It's pretty much impossible. It would run away to surprise you again. Yeah. I think I
would have been a way better God. Yeah. Than God. Yeah. I should play Spore. Spore
is sick. Yeah. I have it on my PC. Really? Let's make Homer Simpson. We could stop right now.
I just go play so much fun make Homer Simpson and spore and then I made a
great ever Simpson yeah yeah over Simpson and posted on YouTube yep Homer
Simpson spore Homer Simpson spore they're good. It's good. It's completely
good. It's good. It's good. That's it. Those are the two
there are two. Hello,
but you don't want to be in spore, but you're already in spore. I mean you're
creature stage you have to evolve to the civilization stage homer yeah go yeah it
goes sell creature and then tribe and then civilization and that space why
does he know that I played so much spore why does he know that I basically I had
the galactic edition of spore you guys are probably jealous I had the galactic
might be this might be your art book dorkiest it had a working out on your
mic is all messing up with the xlr cord. That's okay by me. You stop wiggling
see again. He's getting all technical people will complain about the audio
xlr. Oh, it's Caleb. So if it if anyone complains and they know it's Caleb
wrong message Caleb, you say I'm going to kill you. Yeah reports your you I
get that every day. Get you people try to kill me every day. I've talked about
Yeah, I've found a video of a guy. I found a YouTube channel where a guy
actually I think he's actually getting gang stalked. Yeah, because he what
he's posted video the other day of a guy who dresses a cowboy just following him
around. Damn, that's crazy. It's so crazy and he and then he went up to talk to
him and he was like hey man is there any particular reason why you've been
following me and then the cowboy guy goes I think you've been following me.
So genius. What? Yeah. This guy's actually getting gang stalked. That's crazy. I think gang stalking is real.
That'd be crazy if they're both accidentally gang stalking each other.
Well that's just normal stalking. I think you need a crew. True. To gang stalk.
Yeah I guess it's the operative word there, huh? He had a great video where he just videoed a Mercedes Benz on the side of the street and nobody's in the car.
And he's like, "Gang stalking must pay pretty well, huh?
"Mercedes Benz."
That's it.
Yeah, they're cool.
- Yeah, I wonder what would break in my mind,
'cause I feel like I'm pretty susceptible.
- Successful?
- Susceptible to becoming-- - Probably like canceling
a favorite television program or something of mine.
- I feel like you know what would really get me?
A bunch of people online saying,
"Look at this crazy gang stalk guy."
- Yeah. - Yeah, that might actually
make me go completely insane.
Definitely. Yeah. Yeah. I mean either I would never like follow any of these
people online and like check their every move every day.
But I do it is a weird. Yeah, it is a weird phenomenon because like you get
fascinated with the people who are being gang stalked and then you yourself or
are actually driving them to suicide.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I see. It's insane. The way the way I see people interact with
people like that. I don't I don't understand how you know, I know the worst
is like the people the people who like reply and they're like oh I'm in your
walls like don't do that you're you yeah you're going to be responsible for so
many deaths right this person's gonna kill 15 people yeah but it's still funny
to look at them I would like yeah I mean it's just it's just like good I don't
even know I don't I used to I understand what the bad thing about gang stuck isn't
that do you just feel like a celebrity isn't it good right yeah just really
popular. Nobody's like oh the gang stalkers hurting me it's always just
like they're following me. Yeah. So why not just you know try to maybe they can
help you maybe they can help you learn Spanish or something. Yeah. You know. Yeah.
Give me some investment ideas. Yeah just talk to them. Exactly. You know and it
doesn't have to be confrontational. Oh you're gang stalking. Just like. No like
hey what's up. Like what's up what's up partner. What's up. Say it like that. Like what's up.
What's up partner. What's up playboy. What's up yeah. It's like what's up. What's
What's up, partner?
- Partner.
- And then if you're not getting gang stalked
and you're crazy, then those people who you're saying
what's up to will become your friends
and you'll feel better and your brain will heal.
- I think you should strike up a conversation with them.
What's up, partner?
You seen that video, the giant alligator on the golf course?
- Dude, that video.
- That video was straight legendary, fool.
- Biggest crocodile ever, lapu-lapu, eats chicken.
- Yes, I've seen lapu-lapu.
- Everyone should go on YouTube and search
biggest crocodile ever, lapu-lapu.
- See, this is the kind of conversation
- A stalker should be having with a gang stalking.
- Lapu Lapu.
- What's up, you know Lapu Lapu?
- You know Lapu Lapu?
- Yeah, I've seen Lapu Lapu.
- You play old school RuneScape on your phone?
- The idea of somebody immediately knowing
what you're talking about,
you ask if they've seen Lapu Lapu.
Yeah, when he ate that chicken it was insane.
- That was fire, Lapu Lapu.
- Thank you, partner.
- Walking up to somebody who thinks
they're being gang stalked and being like,
Hey, Lapu Lapu.
Speaking in fucking Simlish at the...
It's all...
Follow, follow, going on through.
(Laughter)
It's making everything worse.
How many people do you think you need
involved to just make one
person, like an actual, a sane person
just lose their mind? Like how many different
people talking in Simlish in
one day before you actually just fucking go crazy?
I feel like two. Two in a row?
Two isn't that... Two in a row, two in a row you're like
like all right what the fuck is going on. I'm fragile. Three. If you talk to if you say
good morning to someone, I mean the rule of threes and then you go to if you go to somebody
else you're like that guy's speaking Simlish to me and he's like yeah then yeah that would
be bad. I would you know what honestly I think that I think that maybe culture has gone far
enough that I would just assume I was on a prank show. If prank shows didn't exist my
mind might. I know that's what I'm saying it's prank shows. I feel like they've ruined
they've ruined completely shattering people's minds.
You're right, because truly that is what I would I would I think a person who's
not schizophrenic, you know, yeah, you do something like that to them. They're
immediately be like, okay, where's the camera? Yeah, you're looking around for
that funny magician. Yeah, Carbonaro effect. The funny one from Netflix. I'm
thinking of a different around like, okay, I know that it's probably the
I know there's a funny magician here.
Yeah.
There's also, what's the, the JFL, Montreal.
Oh yeah, that's coming up.
People, people are, no like the prank show they have.
Oh, I thought, oh no, I don't know that.
Where it's like, oh like, one person walked into this port-a-potty and now 16 people are walking out.
I would have just assumed group sex.
Yeah.
Or a multiplier.
Those videos actually are funny as hell.
Yeah, it could be a multiplier a cloning pod. I might assume I might up assume so I
pulled up lapu lapu here you guys just want to refresh your memory about lapu
lapu. Yes, I think is maybe the video that could heal every gang stalking
victim in the world and every gangster. Yeah, he's chosen the street instead of
let me fast forward to when I'm here. I'm sorry. I was out of town. So yeah,
it's called biggest crocodile ever named lapu lapu and he's feeding him a
complete chicken I think it's an entire chicken is it like a raw chicken?
it looks like it's I don't think it's cooked. Nope, they cook it. Look at this thing.
Whoa that's a big gator. Just wait to wait till he comes out. He's coming out. Remember we went to
alligator adventure? That was so sick. Look at this fucking thing dude. That is too big.
Those are that's just a dinosaur. I think literally it look how gigantic that thing is.
Crocodiles and like Komodo dragons it's just like how the fuck do I exist at the same time as you?
Yeah, crocodiles are insane.
Going through...
Dude, look at that, they can't even walk, dude.
It's so big.
Dude, going through the fucking...
Going through Alligator Adventure and seeing like that big one...
Oh yeah, like...
That big white one that had its mouth open...
Uthar or something.
Yeah.
That was just like...
Just looking at a crocodile's mouth, I was like, "If I ever got eaten..."
If I ever was in there, I would be eaten.
If I got eaten by that thing, I deserve it.
I'm lower...
I am completely lower on the food chain.
I was far from scared there.
I was not scared.
I was scared me the most the tortoise the tour airs you yeah me to the tourist.
Oh yeah, yeah, because of their fat body and jibber jabbering about this and
that yeah talking about let's keep it silent and admire. Can you just enjoy
the fucking millions of years of nature that are unfolding before you and the
tortoise to oh my instagram filters broken that's what they're talking about
the whole tortoise with the tortoise snaps one day and he gets really fast.
(laughter)
- People don't think about that.
- Oh my god, he's going crazy.
- Oh my god!
- He's a fast turtle.
- It's a 300 year old tortoise and he's running at top speed.
- You could, that's the thing, you look at that tortoise.
- If a tortoise--
- I will say, I had a, the reason, okay,
petting that tortoise is why I got a dog.
- Yeah.
- That was the most insane animal experience
I've had in my adult life.
- I didn't want to pet it, I got, I was like--
he's too strong in the connection. I almost fell in love with him. I sat there and I just
touched him and he just looked at me. And I was like, "Animals are all alive." I had
that thought. I was like, "Oh my God, animals are not just pictures. They're actually real."
And they can breathe.
That was one of the best animals ever to touch.
Yeah, that was a great one.
I know why it freaked me out.
Did you end up touching it?
It felt like a boot.
It felt like wood. It was like a tree.
I think I was just like too scared to touch it because I thought I was going to get a
disease.
I thought you were going to get some kind of turtle skin disease.
Yeah.
I got probably cause I got turtle pucks.
I grow a shell.
Oh.
I am the most susceptible in this room to grow a shell.
I was, yeah, you out of the three of us, you would look the coolest with a shell.
Okay, so obviously it's impossible.
Actually, Caleb would look pretty cool with a shell.
Don't say that I would look, I'm not, it's not master disguise.
Stop.
No.
I think he would look the best with a shell.
I'm not doing, no, there's no master of disguise.
No.
you know that's not that's no that all fours okay eating a big head of lettuce.
I wouldn't eat an entire it's too much food for me. I will say watching a turtle eat lettuce
pretty cool. It is impossible to grow a shell, but I do think that probably if out of the three
of us you are the most likely yeah maybe just some kind of like calcium build up or something
around your back. Yeah. And I think it'd be pretty good for you. I think you might learn
a lot about yourself if you grew a shell. I think I, well it would ruin all of my break
dancing. No, it would make it way better. Are you fucking stupid? Are you kidding me?
I go on the back, if I get on my shell I can't get back up without help. So you'd just be
part of a crew. Yeah, that's the whole point of fucking break dancing. I was watching this,
speaking of break dancing, I was watching this interview with Bucky Lazik from Tony
Tony Hawk and from Tony Hawk, the from the Tony Hawk video games. Oh and
skater yeah. Oh, so you okay. I was watching this interview with him and
they're they're asking him about like from Tony Hawk. Well, it's a it's a
franchise series. Yeah, it's like saying Madden. I was playing yeah. I saw an
interview with LeBron James from NBA 2k, but I saw I saw this interview and then
And he was like, they were asking him about the special tricks and they were like, "What
was the idea behind it?"
And he was like, "I don't know.
I was really into breakdancing at the time.
So they recorded videos of me in the Neversoft kitchen breakdancing and then put them into
the game."
It's so fucking funny just being like, "Yeah, this is what I want my special trick to look
like."
And then just doing a head spin in the kitchen.
Games really use mocap and stuff.
I was watching a bunch of like making of like mortal combat making up and they
use like a their whole thing was like they use mo cap for all their like
characters and stuff and it's so fucking funny because they have to like to mo
cap that like a lot of it is like not mo cap. They kind of like scan it in or
whatever, so they just have people like dress up like the characters and then
just like pretend to fall over and go like oh, like get pushed like it'll be
just like one guy who's in full like like you know, like shalcon armor yeah
and then they just have like a just a one random guy who works there's like a
nerd with like these really thick glass and he just pushes them over.
How do they mocap the Mortal Kombat fatalities? They actually kill those people?
They practice it on lizards. They pull a green spine out of Ronda Rousey's back?
Yeah, it's really fucked. Oh, they put her in Mortal Kombat, right?
She voices Sonya Blade. And there's a nude hack.
That's the other funny thing about the old mocap stuff and the way that worked
is like yeah they just would just hire women to dress up like that for their
good for the good like cuz they were just like taking they were just like
like okay you have to wear like a ninja bikini and you have to jump up and down
for an hour for our video game. They did that they did that mocap stuff for Tony
Hawk's Project 8 and you could just like watch like the like people doing tricks
and it's just like so good to have to like wear like a big leotard with like
like little like balls on it and like they're like all right now like go into
to this warehouse so we can like you can like skate for an hour. It's like
sweating through like this little fucking like latex suit seems like hell.
I think for a mocap if I was a mocap actor see it like you know if I was like
Andy circus and I was doing like say like the apes from planet of the apes
yeah, those are like I feel like somebody seeing the video of me doing
that where it's not cgi all over me will be worse than someone seeing me naked
definitely because it's just like a big part of that is that in those mocap
suits everybody can see your penis yeah so your little tiny pieces of my body
now and it's more about I don't want to see anybody see me act perfectly like a
monkey it's so embarrassing how accurate it would be yeah yeah and also the way
I would look at you in public because I feel like a banana I see I've seen video
like for they did mocap stuff for some of the new Godzilla movies and like I've
seen videos of the like a mocap actors like pretending to be King Ghidorah I'm
like you should be dead. I feel like that's a seriously hard one. Yeah. Why are they doing
mocap? It looks cool. I mean, it comes out well. It's strange that they do it, but it's
because they use suits and stuff for the old stuff. So, they try to keep the human physicality.
Okay. I was just thinking about the Tony Hawk mocap because I remembered I would like watch
that to try and learn how to do the tricks when I was younger. And fucking Mike Valleli
literally like he got in that mocap suit and did a fucking flamingo on flat ground.
I don't know what that might-
That's literally you kick the board into like up into your penis and then like twist it sideways.
I was like gee like think about when I was a kid I was like that's sick now that I know
like that's just kind of like a weird like a like a old 80s trick it's like man you wasted
those mocap artists time that is insane.
We should get a whole mocap set up in here. That would be so sick. I never heard mocap
than when I talked to you two. What the fuck? Holy fuck. What? I'll get a mocap set up, yeah.
Yeah, that would be tight. What's that cost? A hundred bucks? Ten thousand. Nah, that's too much.
Oh, if we wanted a really good one. I don't want a weird, we're not going to use it. Can we get one
that just covers the entire office so we can walk from one side to the other and it's all recorded?
yeah and it's just and we just we leave it on all the time and then release a
movie called our life in the office okay it's just cgi like pixar characters
versions of us walking around talking with no audio sitting for an hour
yeah at a table okay that would actually be really a really good experimental
film if how does that how does andy circus act
like a monkey hey how the fuck does he do that i'd
rather he just knows how to do it somehow i'd rather see a monkey at the
circus how does he does he it's like arms down
it's all in the it's the the face is the most important the face is not the most
important part of the month you're fucking talking your ass notice no the
most important is putting your hands making your hair that's a simple as far
around
okay who looks more like a monkey okay
near you
well i can do either i can do the face thing
you look well a lot like a monkey now you did that they didn't before for
yourself with you guys watching
some of the picture of their
that's a flamingo say some of the bitch
so it gets causing
son of a gun
that's a cool trick
doing that in a mocap suit though it's like okay you can do anything
and we can make you do anything when you're in the mocap suit what would
what would your signature trick be in tony hawk i would fall over
uh...
flying up
flying up a hundred feet flying up flying up yet back to the
it's just sitting in the mocap suit doing like this
Yeah, then you guys will put me like a hundred feet in the air while I do this
trick. I hit I hit like left right B and then I just go like you just fly up and
then you die from fall damage. Yeah, yeah, flying up, you know, digging down
digging down is good using the board is it's like a going left, but you're using
the board as a shovel. Here's what I would do China. I would I would say my my
trick is that I have to like I'm being handed like a million dollars. So we
we need mo cap. Do we need to do that and then the hand me the million dollars
and I go actually I actually shockingly surprised you a trick to you and I'm
going to keep this for a freaking freaking plot twist and now my freaking
plot twist. Andy circus was playing the million dollars yeah and now my second
and also my second special trick is actually going to be putting a million
dollars in my car and then also eating a pretty good lunch yeah and then my
- My third trick is not being here.
- Oh, I just remember Chad Muska had a special trick
in that game called the Ghetto Blaster
where he just pulls out a big boom box
and does like a five-oh.
- What a dope name.
- Chad Muska.
- Chad Muska is a cool name.
- It's so funny, he's one of these vandals.
He does graph, he does graffiti, he's a writer.
Isn't that crazy?
If you do graffiti, they call it writing.
- What?
No, they call if you write articles and books.
- No. - That's writing, yeah.
- Graffiti, these-- - Graffiti's a crime.
- These vandals consider what they do
on the side of buildings writing.
- Okay, but at least they don't think it's art, right?
(laughing)
- Buddy.
Buddy, these guys who do graph.
- I hate graph.
- Chad Muska, he writes-- - I will say--
- If you look around like Tompkins Square,
you can see Muska just everywhere.
- Next time I go to Tompkins Square, I'll check it out.
The only good graffiti is stuff that says Lindsay was here and shit that's sick,
but if you do like I like I like the graffiti, I have a curvy version of my
name. I like that graffiti. They do where it's like at a manhole cover. It's like
an X or like an arrow. Yeah, that's good. Oh my God. Have you seen the guy here?
The guy who does lines in the middle of the street that guy's like so fucking
prolific fucking everywhere. Yeah, yeah, sometimes he fucks up and it's like
weird. He like skips parts of the line. I saw one that's like a six or and
somebody wrote over it my friend got mad there's a bunch of zexors. Zexors
are everywhere in Brooklyn. Yeah. Yeah I see a million of them. And I guess it buddy
I'm scared of his alien name and I don't want to meet him so I don't like zexors.
It's so late since moving here I've been like learning about like
graffiti and stuff I've been like. There's some stuff that you just
shouldn't admit. Yeah that's another no-kiss thing to say. I have friends who do it and
- That's another thing you shouldn't admit.
- And their names are, and they're full legal names.
This is a sting operation.
- That's right, like they get in trouble.
- Yeah, it's like I just like list every single person
I know who does graffiti.
- Like the cops are doing a RICO case
for a park with graffiti.
Guys, for the list today, it's a list of--
- It's a list of everyone I know who does graffiti.
- I'd like to introduce you guys to this website
that I found.
that's a blogspot website from the two thousands is called
on the army
fresh news article stories everything what you want
so that's where we get into it i want to read they have a kind of like a list of
the tags on over here and i just want to read you guys all the tags that are on
this website and i a don't read the other labels
yellow-tinted lately we are going to some sort of spirally they're laid out
it's not a tax they're not my eyes on blogspot their label okay well here they
are is on a row
answers facts science other job top beautiful girl most naked nude semi
nude sex sexy twenty twelve as the calendar bieber calendar december
twenty-first doomsday justin angry bad danger delete enemy facebook fb hates
mayan nabiru part two quit ten the end woman women world and uh... wall did you
find this looking at nabiru or plastic surgery i think i literally sir
i think it's a new sexy yeah most well
I don't want to tell you what I search. Yeah, I bet you don't because it's sort
of awkward. No, I can't give away my methods to everyone who listens or else
they just cut out the middleman. They don't know they can find all these
stupid websites themselves. Yeah, it's true. Yeah, but the list that I mean, I
figure we can read this list of them. I think there's other stuff on this
website. I'm sure we'll be able to find here. Yeah, this is top 10 plastic
surgery fails of Hollywood and it says it is good to take care of you, but
sometime excess of everything is bad true as some Hollywood celebrities are
so much concerned about their beauty and looks that they have gone through plastic surgery
to enhance their beauty but instead of becoming attractive they lost their charm and surgery
proved to be a disaster.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
That's actually fucking...
It's tragic.
Tragic, yeah.
That's very sad.
It's really tragic.
It does make me sad when like a, like a, like those fucking like...
When a woman wears shorts.
What?
It makes me sad.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's like, cover it up.
I don't want to see that.
I don't want to see your, your, your bobby pin tattoo.
for your husband. Your knees are your husband's thing. It's not for me to see.
Like the Bogdanoff twins? I hate some guys. And then they got all these fillers in their
face that made them look like a puppet. I thought that they looked cool. The thing is
if you look like that by yourself, you look stupid, but if you're twins, it's like, so
like check us out. I can see the life behind that. The thing about that is that twins are
like already inhuman monsters yeah you might as well they're already
mutants yeah a twin twins you get arms like you know thinking about that it's
so sick that they were like scientists they were really bad scientists yeah
they were like terrible scientists they they know their other stuff was just
like I plagiarized a bunch of shit right everything stuff up they were and they
were French too so they like sound weird man if I do seeing them in person like
seeing that guy looks like a lion walking up to you and then he starts going like
"I'd fucking lose it. I'd nut instantly. No hands, full prostate nut."
A French guy with a cushion in his face. I would nut my prostate out of my penis. Yeah exactly.
And it would just be sitting there on the ground. It's squirming away.
Yeah. Trying to get into that guy's mouth. Yeah. That's exactly what
would happen. Nutting out your prostate. I've never even thought about trying to do that.
Is that what kegels are for? Yeah. To nut your prostate out? You can like, so what you do
is you nut it out and then you slurp it back up like it's a sticky hand. How does that
fit out of your urethra? You can train it. It stretches. You can stretch your urethra?
Your urethra is one of the most stretchy parts of the body, like the butthole. Yeah. You
you can teach it to gape. Yeah, it's like a yeah, you flex it. Yeah, really your
brain.
That's a crazy thing here. That's nasty. Oh my God. I made my aritha huge. Those
guys who are like those guys who get like like
they train their butt to like become like a manhole
to be big to be big. So they can frame somebody's whole foot in there. I don't
understand because that's got to hurt. It's got to hurt, but like a little
something in your butt. They seem to like it more than anybody in the world. A
normal sized thing in your butt, probably pretty beast, but something that's as
huge as like a fucking... Like a parking cone? Yeah, yeah. The square side of a
parking cone in your asshole, that hurts. Yeah. That really hurts. I think for me,
the limit of my asshole is probably like sweet potato sized. Yeah.
that's I mean like absolute limit like that's a big as I could go. Sure you're
thinking of that. He's thinking of that sweet potato. He took the like three
years ago.
I looked exactly like a cock. Yeah, you're like a piece of paper
yeah folded infinitely eight and a half, but a piece of paper. I can probably fit
this.
You think you can put this in your ass with enough training? I could probably
so if you can't this is a big training doesn't count. This is what I'm talking
about right now. Anybody can write anything in there with enough training
so sweet potato for me is is it would probably take me like an hour to work
for me probably probably a strand of horse hair. The thing is I don't I'm not
opposed to like trying that though, even though I don't feel like I would find
much sexual gratification from it. I think a whole sweet potato in your I
feel like it might just be like a fun thing to do one day is like try to put
something in my ass. Yeah, you know a lot of people feel that way. But I don't want
to... There's this app where guys can help you out with it. Really? Yeah. Is it Fiverr?
It's called Ass Trainer. Ass Trainer? Yeah. Like Duolingo? Yeah. It's exactly like
Duolingo. Really? You have to do it every day. Okay, I guess I'll do it every fucking day.
Number one, Jocelyn Wildenstein. Yeah, Wilden out on your damn face.
more like it. Yeah and ste... I can't... Oh I hate seeing you. Yeah. Go ahead and read
this here. She ruined herself because of her husband. She wants to look like cat
because her husband loved cats but her expensive attempt has turned herself in
something like look like a dragon but at least now. I mean she does look pretty
bad yeah she was so what exactly like fucking brown bunny what's her name
Finns and gallo the girl from the movie close vignette yeah yeah she looks just
like her and now she looks like a dragon but yeah which is a serious yeah great I
would say a dragon's go I don't know if she looks like a dragon I don't know if
I'd say that no I don't know I wouldn't say dragon I think she is I think she
does look like Ron Perlman in Beauty and the Beast. She doesn't look like a
dragon, but I would believe that she lives in a cave. Yeah, definitely. Yeah, and
maybe guards something. Yeah, yeah. Number two is Lolo Ferrari. Oh my god. What's wrong
with this? She's actually fucking insane. This lady has undergone such a craziest plastic
surgery that became reason of her death. No, she's dead. She had firstly make her
lips look bigger, and then she put some extra, she put extra, some really extra on
on her breast. She was known as having hugest boobs in the world. She even died
because of suffocating due to those huge boobs. She is named as Catwoman wait
suffocated like she got her boobs so big that they covered her face. She might
try to sleep on her Mr. Incredible in the completely black bubble room yeah
whoa,
but she is named as Catwoman. That's like my dream way of dying yeah yeah.
Having cute be by your own your own breasts well yeah, and I would probably
sweet potato into my asshole. But yeah it sounds pretty good to me.
Michael Jackson, this is rude. That's fucked up. That's the king of pop.
Go ahead. Jinx, you owe me a pop.
I thought I had one in front of me but it was completely empty.
I have to go. I am taking about plastic surgery and how can I forget the name of
one of the top pop singer king of music Michael Jackson who has completely
changed himself through plastic surgery. Black Boy turned to White Fellow by the
grace of plastic surgery. After that he has gone through a lot of plastic surgeries that have
made him look like a man of plastic.
Black Boy turned to White Fellow by the grace of plastic surgery.
Holy shit. What a sentence.
I really like this website. I was so happy when I stumbled on this.
God damn dude, that is so sick.
Oh fuck.
He does look like a man of plastic.
A black boy turned to white fellow by the grace of plastic.
I was watching, oh yesterday I saw the sickest car out in front of here.
I think I sent you guys the photo.
It's like the, it was like a van and then like on this window it said like Michael,
King of Pop, Prince, Prince of Pop.
Whoa.
Fuck, who else was on that?
It was like literally right in front of the office and I was like holy shit.
That sounds sick.
This is the coolest thing I've ever seen.
I love that there's so many good cars in New York.
Yeah.
There's incredible cars.
Here it is.
It's a van called Cool Blue.
Oh that's dope.
Dude it was so, it's the Highlander Van Club.
Damn.
It said, and then it said the Brooklyn Blues, Whitney Houston and Aretha Franklin, the Queens,
Michael Jackson and Prince, the Prince and King.
Dude that's the coolest car I've ever seen.
Yeah that's sick.
There's one near me that's a van where and these people lost their dog like four years
ago and the entire van is wrapped in like have you seen this dog.
Like my Instagram photos.
It's so dope.
Yeah.
That is cool.
I would just do that.
I want to just like buy that car now.
Just roll it over.
There's a car on my street with the license plate Gapin.
What?
Gapin.
Oh, okay.
But it's G-A-Y-P-I-N.
You're very into gaping today.
I don't know why.
See, I don't feel like...
Maybe it's because I keep seeing that every time I come to the office.
I feel like it's more of a...
Somebody is psychically driving me to get my asshole gaped.
See, but I think that gaping your asshole is not sexual at all and it's something that
we could do in a funny jackass way.
It's, yeah.
I'm serious.
Or like a physiological research study.
Why is it sexual that we see how many big things go in your butt?
Like that's funny, like farts.
Or scientifically.
it's funny it's not funny then it's scientific we're doing in a funny
scientific way so yeah just like this what about this no because this is wider
than it is okay wider it's wider then but then the calf this is a deal okay
we'll start by the way my mic the cap would clip my what's the biggest thing
in this room that would go in your ass. My own penis. XLR cable.
cable that would fit that's going higher like yeah like the chain video okay wait
do that chain video is one of it's still one of the craziest what about this
click what about this click clicker would probably fit yeah I mean what about we
know what about this that maybe this is it what about what you see the thing is
but would you put my would you put my earbuds in there those could fit yeah
yeah, what if I like all your mouse in there? It's my old mouse. You don't go in
there. Is it? Okay, what about this?
That's the that was the the it's a long time prank. I was driving. I was
building up
to telling you I put that whole computer mouse in my head. What about this
replica sword?
It's a replica Excalibur. It's an slo. Well, I bought you that for Christmas.
Yeah, he bought you an slo. Yeah, so I'm going to go up your
I don't even want to say it. No,
could go up my the sword wouldn't go up my butt because okay he'll just the
hilt it has said it's too much it has too much sentimental value I think you
might have the biggest tushy here based on how many things you're saying hey
Gil s I mean the whole there's more room for
you have a sinker has more room in it all right there's less number for
Donatella Versace I thought that was a ninja yeah I don't know who this is
Versace's that's Donatella Versace's like the heir of Versace's
Like other stars she has also made a stupidest mistake of
undergoing plastic surgery at old age she wants to remain young and look
beautiful however she was truly very beautiful and oldness could make her
prettier but now she turned into an awful and ugly fellow. Looking at that woman and
calling her a fellow is really funny. This person likes the word fellow. Yeah. Number
five is Mickey Rourke. Holy shit that's not a picture of him. Yeah that that looks insane.
Wait go back up to Donatello Versace. He looks exactly like Jim Carrey Grinch. That's not him. He doesn't look like that does he?
The only thing that changed about her is her lip.
No, there's other stuff.
Like the lip and then she's just doing a darker eye makeup.
That's really it.
She doesn't look that terrible.
What the hell?
How'd you notice she had makeup on?
Okay, okay, white knight.
Yeah.
Why are you--
Oh, no, she also has some like cheap stuff done.
She's not gonna fuck you, Pat.
Yeah, she's not gonna put your mouse in your ass.
Mickey Roy, please, please don't fucking blow this for me.
He failed in lifting.
and lifting. Lifting has indeed made him look a younger, but unnatural and like
plastic. He lost his charm as he looked unnatural and artificial, although luck
is blessed upon him as he was nominated for Oscars. However, people thought that
his career has ended up. I think he looks fine. He looks like he went a hundred
miles down the road.
He looks like your miles per hour really. It looks like he looks like he has like a
clip on the back. Yeah, I think he looks or simpson thing. He just got off a
motorcycle yeah no helmet Melanie Griffith
From
Plastic surgeries that have made her beauty lost for forever
She has had many lifts on her face that are made her face look like wild animals
I feel like I could get some plus I could stand to get some plastic surgery
I want to get I was telling my girlfriend that I would I was gonna get some plastic surgery
I think I would look really good with a really pointy chin. Yeah
like like hacker from from cyberchase
like the uh like the guy with no other changes at all the guy in crash box
who just draws the pictures just a perfect i don't know i never watch
crashing i'm sorry just chin that just it's so sharp
his chin so he draws with the pencil and then his chin looks like the tip of a
pencil oh okay yeah like that i would have a
pencil chin yeah yeah i think that i might well it's
because he has a goatee there too i think i might get my eyes opened yeah
permanently in the morning. I think maybe I'd get some big ass like Chloe Cherry
Lips. Who's that? It's the lady from Euphoria. She plays Eve or something, I
think. She sounds pretty stupid. I saw her on the train the other day. Really? Yeah.
Do you push her over? No. Into the tracks? I saw her on the train and I was like,
New York City is a beautiful melting pot. There's me, for instance, a podcaster and
and then there is an actress yeah that is crazy.
Wow, Lil Kim, she has made great experimentation with her body and as she
has made some lifts on her face, made her skin whiter and implanted her breast. I
can bet you that whatever she has done with herself, she definitely scare
herself when she look in the mirror. That's just mean she did that on
purpose. So she's a big she's a big horror fan. She said you heard that yeah
it's not about her appearance. It's the loud noise. She makes yeah. You heard
her album like the first track on one of her albums is a skit where she's just
sucking dick. That's freaky. It's fire. I'm gonna do that on my half-hour special.
Number eight is Tori. Tori Spelling. Well it doesn't say last name. It just says Tori.
I know that's Tori. This could be a different person. She doesn't really look
all that abused by surgeons. No. Well it says many people think that she is only
in Hollywood because of her father, but she has invested money in plastic
surgery to transform her breast. Her boobs have gotten so huge that she looks
pathetic.
She looks pathetic and she's unable to inspire people.
She has uninspiring tits. Her boobs have gotten so huge that she looks
pathetic.
The only thing I know about... These do look like really fake boobs.
Yeah. I'll give you that much.
only thing I know about the Pepsi can and the concave of her chest the only thing
I know about her is the that Bloodhound Gang song the mope I cannot believe you
know more than one Bloodhound Gang song I know that's crazy there were I favorite
did they make other music yeah was it good yeah some of the songs are really
good it funny yeah was it a mope the mope has a line in the in the chorus
that's bugging out like Tori Spelling's eyes. That's just rude. Jimmy
Pobb was a rude guy. Yeah, chill out. Yeah, that's not cool to say. That's like
Gilbert Gottfried roast humor. Yeah. Priscilla Presley. I just saw a movie
about her. Have you seen anyone loosing their beauty for the sake of expensive
and costly ugliness? Presley has done exactly the same thing. She has
experimented with plastic surgery of her face and has lost her beauty and has
turned into a witch. That at the end kind of tacked on. Buried the lead a little bit.
Yep, she's completely ugly from plastic surgery. She also turned into an actual
witch. Yep, she's into warlockery. Yep, it's not all that good. She was, is it
Priscilla or no, no, no, never mind. It was Lisa Marie. I was going to say she was
married, Lisa Marie Presley was married to Michael Jackson for a little bit.
♪ I can't dance like Michael Jackson ♪
- Sorry, you just made me think of a lyric.
- I thought we were all gonna do it.
- No. - No.
- Alright.
- Whatever happened to this hoe?
- Tara Re--
What, what did they--
- New segment on the show.
Where this hoe now?
(laughing)
We take a hoe from a long time ago
and we ask where is this hoe?
- She was in a movie recently.
- Well, read it then.
Tara, read it.
she is a bit slow. It says it says she is bit slow fellow as I am saying such
words because she has just ruined her body by herself. She undergone a lipos
surgery that put a lot of extra skin on her body. She thought that she can
overcome by making another stupid mistake and she got plastic surgery of
her chest. Now she looks awful. Now I know where this is she's right there
and she's green yeah and that's the last that was the there's one comment
Malochi Flembo that says "The Fuck?" Malochi Flembo. Malochi Flembo commented on this
and this is from 2011 I think. Yeah, that's back when they had the Facebook comments plugin. Oh
man, I miss the Facebook comments plugin. I'm so happy when I go to a website and it still has the
Facebook comments. I remember the first place that I commented online I think was probably the Fox
News website on my grandma's computer and I would go on the Fox News website and somebody would say
there would be a Fox News report that was like
rapper T pain is a Muslim and I'd be like oh my God, this is heartbreaking in the
car. I'm just clicking here on some of the labels the tag. Yeah, why people hate Justin Bieber?
True yeah, there's some good. There's some good articles on this website.
Faulty reasons why people hate Justin Bieber. We save this one top ten most beautiful woman
of the world. Oh I looked at this one. They don't have much writing about it. It's just
kind of pictures. Oh okay. Yeah. Which we can all look at together. Okay I'm actually
seriously enjoying this website more than ever. I have a crazy boner. You know who's
so hot is Sofia Veragada? She's on the list. It doesn't matter to me that she's 82 years
old. You can tell this is made in 2011 because Mila Kunis is on there. You know who's seriously
hot? Kate Upton. Yeah. She was on a music video where she does the cat daddy dance at
Terry Richardson's really no way I saw a video where breasts completely fell out
of her shirt you know it's hot who whoever voices Sandy from Spongebob has
to be how oh my god her voice thing they they I think voice acting really tricks
you into thinking that people look a certain way yeah yeah who's it is the
lady plays Marge the lady who voices the guy who plays Homer yeah they don't look
look like larger Homer. No, they look nothing like them. Who's it the lady who
plays
Tommy Pickles, E.G. Daly. She's the, I learned this recently, she is the, I
learned this recently, I learned this recently, she's the singer at the school
dance in Better Off Dead.
She had a music career too and then she was also Pee Wee's girlfriend in Pee Wee's
Big Adventure. Can I give, do a reading for you guys? I would love to hear
something that you have to read for me. Yeah, it's called the end of the world
2012 say experts their views. I've already seen the end of the world two
years to go December 21st 2012 the date which is going on our minds at is as it
is reaching nearer and nearer that we all know that something is going to be
happening on December 21st 2012, which might takes us to the end of the world,
but is it really going to be end of the world? If it's so what might be happen
on that day? All these questions might be going in the minds of all at one time
or the other and then I'm going to skip ahead here to what might be the real is
And on December 21st, 2012 or on August 13th, 2012, whoever knows but both the scientific
as well as religious beliefs are prevailing in the minds of the people on this issue.
The science, technology and the scientists behind this are saying that the hyperspace
that contain our universe is also showing signs that something strange is happening
in our universe.
Even it was said that the global and solar polar reversal peaks are coming within three
weeks of that day, December 21, 2012.
But according to some scientists, it is possible that another universe is slowly starting to
claim in our physical universe and according to religious beliefs they
believe that the earth will be destroyed or cleansed by the wrongdoers and those
that believe in their God will be saved or brought to heaven. My my first
girlfriend in high school broke up with me on December 21st 2012. Really? Mm-hmm.
Wow. Like on purpose? Yeah not on purpose not she didn't know that that day was
the end of the world. Why did you remember it? I remembered it because I was like what if the
world ends - this year says another phenomenon that is making society more
conscious of the date December 21st 2012 is the movie 2012 I think sick-ass movie
right John Cusack I never saw John Cusack not it not a not respected enough
as an actor he's a beast dude dude and his sister's a Fox which Anna Joan Joan
I don't know who Ann is.
- Ann Cusack?
- Never heard of her.
- I'm just, you've probably seen her
and didn't know she was a Cusack.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The Cusack family, very talented.
- Use my sack like a--
- Welcome on the show anytime.
- Use my sack like a cue--
- Don't say, now they're not gonna come on the show.
- Use my sack like a cue ball.
- They're not gonna come on the show now.
- Shoot it all, bing bing bing bing bing bing ping ball.
- Better off dead.
- Ping ball with my dick and my sack, I mean.
- High fidelity, gross point blank.
He's just had a string of just nothing but banger. I want to do something gross
to him point blank.
Dead ass dead ass. I'm just scrolling through. I don't want to read this whole
thing because a lot of it's kind of boring, but I did just see I was skimming
through it and I did see this line that's just in the middle of it. I'm sure
many of you have heard of Merlin the magician.
And it starts talking about Merlin for the last few. Do you think Merlin has
something to do with this? I think Merlin could have had something to do. I
I think Merlin might be an actual evil psychic force.
You know what is funny about the movie, the movie Better Off, I'm still on the Q-Sec thing,
the movie Better Off Dead, Dan Schneider plays the villain in that movie and he also is a
villain in real life.
The Nickelodeon guy?
Yeah.
He's an actor?
He is in that movie as the fat neighbor.
That's getting a...
The fat neighbor with a...
It's getting a little weird to me that he has not been...
Yeah.
Like...
It's crazy how protected he is.
There's no like TMZ story.
was it that you never McCurdy thing that just came out every day some some new
star from Disney says like not even to says to like a media outlet that nobody
knows what the fuck it is like a blog spies like oh yeah that guy tried to
like tickle my penis when I was a child yeah and I used to play a game called the
finger dance never gets on the news yeah that fucking that uh there's that thing
where it's like he had all the like he's like said Nickelodeon photos of your
your feet yeah like your feet with crazy things on them. Yeah man you you I'm
going to shoot you. I saw him in public. I would open fire the
the all the stories of him being like like they'll finish a take and he'll be
like kid. You nailed that joke about seventh grade algebra. Do you want like a
glass of champagne to sell yeah and they were like yeah fuck it yeah yeah it's so
crazy. Yeah, it's one of those guys right just assumed that he was that
something already happened with it like that. They are. That's why everyone
just it's all anyone ever talks about with him. I hated those shows growing
like iCarly and shit like Zoe 101. I was like those are like I hate them
because they were they're so fucking gay. They were honestly mad gay. They
were gay as hell. They were like and then I'm only proven right as an adult
the humor was like lacking to it wasn't a song was not a banger. It wasn't
funny our Carly was not as funny as Comedy Central's premium blend definitely
not did Comedy Central's premium blend had Daniel Tosh watch listening to
Howard Stern on Sirius XM right Demetri Martin's first special yes like that was
that was the kind of shit that me as a nine-year-old was watching because I was
so it I was so funny that was real real fucking TV mm-hmm right yeah I was the
cloud was the real class clown because I would actually will Ferrell SNL I did
actually that was good I was on a lot that's real TV I'm not gonna watch as
told by Jinger no come on I'd rather watching South Park
Pokemon down South Park gonna see yourself on time
Yu-Gi-Oh yeah real - yeah growing they had this this thing on Nickelodeon before
they were playing on showtime before they would play as told by Jinger mm-hmm
and it was like a wheel and I like I didn't realize that that was like it was
like a wheel and then it spins and it's like what show is gonna be on next?
You thought it was real? I thought it was real I didn't realize that that was just like a
bump. That's okay. That they would play before the schedule. How old were you? I was like
six. Okay that's okay. And I got really mad because it would always almost land on
Cousin Skeeter. And then it would go to As Told By Ginger. And I
remember one time we were all in the living room and I just like got up and I was like God damn it!
don't like gambling yeah wow yeah I got up and I was screaming and then like my
siblings like tried to like console me and like bring me back to like deliver
like look look it's gonna they said it's gonna be on next I loved any show with a
puppet in it I was obsessed with as told by ginger used to come on and yeah I
would be like with my brother and I'd be like oh god this is so gay as fuck you
you probably I'm going to watch like an R rated movie and you have to leave the
room and he would leave and then I'd watch Estelle by Ginger yeah because it
was actually dope and actually hella emotional was a good show. I just wanted
to like Cousin Skeeter more how to force angels cry with clapping. We got to save
that
so we're doing that one
way. I just need to see yeah we're saving that. I do want to have one last
thing that I want to show you guys on this website before we end here, let's
which is this is a page they have on your called the most beautiful thing
women part one and it's a bunch of pictures of almost naked women with no
text and then there's a one comment at the bottom and already the comment here
updating the most beautiful girls in the world. Also, if like the browse my
my face page, I have the most beautiful hotels to check out
from Paul Schwann. The last
is like a hotel manager
- Between the most beautiful hotels,
we will be staying in one of the most beautiful hotels
in the world in Portland and Seattle.
- Uh-huh.
- On the--
- And a little over a week.
Better grab tickets now.
- Next Saturday.
- They're going fast.
I heard there's only one ticket left.
- (gasps) There's only one ticket.
- But maybe there could be extras
if you're going as a group and you might be able--
- But definitely, yeah.
- If you are going.
- Somewhere between--
- There's as many people are you thinking of going with,
there's that many tickets left.
- And it's not, it's a normal show.
It's not a live, one of these shitty live podcasts.
It's an actual good show.
Yeah, we're not gonna go up there and just go, "Mah!"
But yeah, what's up everybody?
We're Chopo Trap House, and we're doing fucking,
yeah, you see Donald Trump's in the news again?
No. That's not us.
We're gonna go up there. We are gonna do
the Donald Trump in the news again, though.
When we do our live show, we don't do the podcast at all.
We piss all over the stage.
We do some weirdo Andy Kaufman crap.
I fucking love Andy Kaufman.
He's fucking random. He's cool.
He makes me cough, man, from laughing.
The way that he treated girls was hella sarcastic and I appreciate it.
Yeah, well that's that.
Alright, so buy some tickets, buy some shirts, buy your mom a bottle of squirt.
That's my poem.
That was really beautiful.
Bye.