Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
[laughter]
[music]
You're a crap monster.
[explosion]
You should get a...
What?
A...
needles on it dip it in the paint yeah and then they just stab you a million
times I searched about shibori I think it's t-b-o-w no no it might be
both I be there it is te there we go I don't know what is it what is it so they
tattoo you like a thing or is it there's no machine crazy just stabbing him a
million time. If you're a tattoo artist and you listen to the show, send in some tattoo
ideas for the three of us to get as a team. Tell Patrick they're going to give him a discount
on a tattoo and then tattoo a swastika on his back where he can't see it, please. And
put it in that one spot where nobody can reach it. So that he can't even try to like ruin
it and like scratch it. Yeah, exactly. There's no choice but to keep it perfectly clean. Speaking
of Nazi tattoos on the plane home yesterday, guy next to us, full Iron Eagle on his arm
and it said like, I was like trying to read the German.
For what?
Iron Eagle.
Like a Nazi Eagle crest type thing.
Well I don't know.
I think that.
It was a family, so here's the thing right?
It wasn't a Nazi Eagle, it was like a coat of arms, but it looked enough like a Nazi Eagle
that it's like, that's a little weird.
looks like yeah and then but and i was like okay it's probably just a coat of
arms it's all the rightness something i was trying to read the german on it it
did have german on it too and then other arm iron cross to iron cross and then
everyone's such a i think an iron cross doesn't mean anything but i think those
two things together that is it is it well and then the four are also just the
way he looked yeah the way he looked on a way to look he was coming from myrtle
beach forty dollar flight from myrtle yes on his forearm huge we the people
the uh... so so i'll be soon
yeah although all here's my impression you guys guys i saw a patriot yesterday
always a lot of looking
as a fucking perfect patriot i violated his privacy that's why i didn't do
anything i want i wanted to read the german because i was like a little
session on patrick and you can say let me brush up a little you wanted to see
if it's a patrick and orin had to have you walking over to him at baggage claim
and going like this
you were you were arguing five times in a row. Also, the reason I don't know this was me a
baggage claim. He doesn't know how to act in public. Yeah. You and me have one you me and
Cam have one standard of public behavior and Patrick has a completely different one. Yeah.
You and Pierce have a similar kind of idea of public behavior and what's okay and me
and Cameron think that you should be polite and courteous specifically to women. Yeah.
And you guys have, like I said, kind of an opposite kind of idea.
A different school of thought.
I did see...
More like an Arkham Institute.
So there was a family sitting next to us, two of the most annoying kids in the world.
And that guy and his wife, they were trying to get everybody in the row or something.
And the lady just looked at the...
Everybody in a row?
They're trying to get everybody on the plane into one row.
No, they were trying to get the family into the row.
What the hell is that? It was a Karen.
The lady looked at the lady with two kids in her arms and she was like,
"That's my seat. Is there any way I can get in?"
The lady went, "Sorry, we like the window seat."
Whoa!
Yeah, and she also asked Patrick.
We were sitting in our seats and she came up to ask Patrick.
Then she's like, "Are you in 20D or whatever seat we're in?"
And the seat that Patrick is in, it is on his ticket.
and Pat was like, "Yeah." And she's like, "Are you sure?" And he showed and he had to pull up
his boarding pass and show her when she clearly was not in that seat because it was Patrick's seat.
Yeah.
She made Patrick show his boarding pass.
And this lady was a Karen?
She was a complete, she was one of the biggest Karens on a plane I've experienced in recent memory.
Did she anywhere near kind of milfy?
No, she wasn't even milfy.
Not even a bit. So you didn't let it slide?
No.
know
What if Cameron really gave her some serious side eye?
What if she was...
I would say it was a side stink.
I hate to say it, yeah.
I gave a dirty, stinky look to her.
What did?
Once or twice or ten times.
Now, new scenario.
And that kid looked weird.
New scenario.
What if she comes up, she says, "Can I do that?"
And you say, "Oh, I don't know."
But then she turns, she's like, "One second."
Turns around to put her carry-on in the overhead.
She puts her kid in there.
And then you see her bottom.
She has two little divots for her nuts like a Lego butt.
Right.
So she sits on you.
Oh, yeah. Oh, okay. So she sits on...
And she's milfy. And she has a Lego butt.
Yeah, but then if I have to get up to go to the bathroom, she's gonna like...
It's like a whole thing.
She's gonna bend over into the seat in front of me and then I'm gonna like...
No, you take her...
Excuse me, sorry.
No, you take her body, you take the top part of her body and you just take her legs with you.
Listen, I'd love to...
Okay, so I pee through the...
You pee through one of the Lego butt holes.
I'd love to help with the accommodations of a MILF in the airport before and after the flight,
But on a plane, that's the sacred time of relaxation and sitting in my own seat.
Nothing is more relaxing than just flying on a plane.
I'm saying I need to be relaxed.
Shooting 60 million miles an hour.
I truly needed to get this lady away from him.
I've done enough flying that I've gotten to the point where I just pretend that I'm not flying.
When I get on a plane now, in my head, I'm like, "I am on the bus."
Yeah.
I can't do that.
I'm on the bus or the train.
I really can't.
I try.
It doesn't work.
Well, because it's really hard because then you look outside and the world is this big.
You know what it is?
You've got to start sitting in the aisle seat.
It doesn't make any difference.
Can you imagine that first flight, man?
The Wright Brothers?
Oh my God.
Kitty Hawk.
We were just there.
We were close to Kitty Hawk.
Now it is.
They flew on a Kitty Hawk.
They'd probably be the Wright sisters.
Probably be the wrong sisters.
Yeah.
No, they didn't fly.
It was called Kitty Hawk.
Animal?
place where they were and the Wright brothers, one of them
pushed the plane and then the other flew the plane.
So where did they fly to?
Just in a, like an up and down.
So they didn't even go anywhere.
They flew from Kitty Hawk to Kitty Hawk. That doesn't even count.
The first time there was a place to place
plane flight was Amelia Earhart and we all know how that turned out.
Well that was a place to no place flight.
Well she was saying I'm gonna go.
That was the first flight where there was no destination at all.
saying I'm gonna go transatlantic on them. What if Amelia Earhart just
like got trapped in like a an Amazonian village and decided hey I'm gonna stay
here with these hot ladies. That's probably what she did I mean that's what
I would do yeah yeah that's the thing there's so many undiscovered tribes in
the world and on the entire planet. Of women who have been bred into having humongous breasts.
I would love to bring my kind of... And the guys are this big so you show up and
you're like over four feet tall.
- Yeah, it's a death by snoo snoo situation.
- Oh my god, yeah, we're gonna go Futurama on this guy.
- I think I would really like to kind of meet up
with some of these undiscovered tribes
who have made no contact with humanity
and bring them some of my ideas, literature, and food.
- I think I wanna--
- I want them to show them Green Day.
- I wanna show them kind of how I see the world
and maybe see--
- Bro, if you showed one of these,
if you showed an undiscovered Amazonian tribe Green Day,
it would kill them.
- What's that one place where you're not allowed to go?
- That island where they throw spears at the cameras?
- Yeah, one place where Cameron's the only guy who's--
I think it's technically a violation of some international law to do it.
Couldn't you do a little bit of...
Patrick got really in one of the baby's faces during the flight, by the way.
I didn't want to bring it up until he said that, but...
What do you mean you got really into a baby's face?
When we were getting up to leave the plane, he was like this.
And he didn't even smile.
Why'd you do that?
You know when you smile at a baby and wave?
He didn't smile, he just waved.
And then he did this.
[imitates baby's face]
You slid your finger across his throat?
You slid your finger across your throat as if you were slitting it?
I threatened the kid because he wouldn't shut up.
Why?
Why are you... that's rude.
that's just put headphones in man I had headphones in then you're just then
you're the baby you're and I had headphones and all I could hear was well
I was playing all you could hear okay maybe I did have a weird playlist on go
ahead and tell me what it is baby screams 10 hours then why that's what it
just blended right in baby was smiling good idea I think the baby was smiling
you get you immediately get desensitized babies the babies weren't really when
babies were not annoying on the flight at all I have to say well I really have
- I brought up the babies because Patrick said that I wasn't allowed to.
- No, but earlier you said, and we were on the plane.
- Oh, he didn't even hear that.
- Before you got here.
- I forgot you're the one with the headphones.
- Before he got here, you were like, yeah, we were on the flight and there was three babies on the plane.
- They were loud, but they were not annoying.
They were not crying.
They were just screaming.
- What?
- They were screaming, laughing.
- Oh, well, that's adorable.
- Exactly.
It wasn't that bad.
- Oh, all right.
- Yeah, but it is just crazy to get sat next to three babies.
- That is like worst luck.
They started screaming and crying right when we landed.
How about Octomom?
On a plane?
While all her babies are there?
Octomom on a plane? That's the movie.
And you got Samuel.
She's on the soul plane.
I'm gonna fucking kill, or get these fucking babies out of this.
I'm tired of these motherfucking octomoms.
When we were landing...
There's an octomom?
Oh my god.
Bad octomom.
Here's a question.
It's like a mom's, it's like a, it's like a dirty mom's movie.
Listen.
Right?
So she's, it's all of these other octomoms.
Okay.
And they're all, they're all going to Miami to get more pregnant.
So here's the question.
That's scary.
That's what makes it scary.
It's all these octomoms in heat.
If there's a whole plane.
And there's one guy on the plane.
There's an entire plane full of octomoms, right?
Literally at all 150 seats, all octomoms.
and then they all are right about to burst.
They all start giving birth at the same time.
So now there's fucking eight more for every person.
- Yeah, it'll make the plane heavier.
- Yeah, the plane crashes, right?
- Yeah. - Probably.
- It has to, 'cause a plane can fit 150 people.
- I mean, even besides the weight thing.
- 950 people?
- I think even besides the, well,
I don't think it's a weight thing
because the babies are already in the mom's bellies
if they're that close to being born.
I don't think the weight on the plane changes at all.
- No, the weight's different 'cause it's more people.
- Okay, but I do think the plane would still crash
because you're imagine you're the pilot and the stewardess knocks on the door and
says eight hundred babies were just born. I think you...
Eight hundred babies were just born and there's a hundred and fifty more on the
way. I think that I may might just crash the plane out of instinct because
this cannot be a thing that happens on earth. I think that twelve hundred babies
being born at one time... That might be the most beautiful sound in the world. Might honestly be...
The babies would probably all harmonize. Yeah. Some of them will. Yeah. We're not going to say all
all
counting your fingers right now. Oh you're talking about going up and down?
That's yeah yeah that's 16. So you cover every... Okay I guess that is 8.
I'm thinking of the babies covering every octave is what I mean. So you're
saying this might be something that might be sampled in hip-hop for decades
to come. So you know you know how that you know that song I'm not in love by 10cc?
I think the babies should all sing happy birthday because it's their birthday.
Whose job is it to sing happy birthday to all these damn babies?
I'll do it.
I'm a good singer.
It would fucking ruin everything.
I'm rushing the cockpit and I'm pressing the intercom button and I'm singing happy birthday
to these fucking babies.
Doing Skyler White.
Marilyn Monroe kind of thing.
Yeah, exactly.
It's a Marilyn Monroe kind of thing.
Yeah.
But then it ruins the, basically air travel is fucking ruined forever because now that's
going to be the number one most amazing thing that ever happened.
150 octomoms, what are the odds they give birth at the same time on the same plane at
the same time the plane crashes.
Now, and everyone survives, or at least some of them survive.
1,350 people and then the crew and stuff.
Well at that point the mommy's bellies are just rafts.
But well that's true.
That's true.
So all the water goes in their hee-haw.
But then now every year all these people have to have a reunion and do a reunion flight.
In a couple of years, these kids are full grown.
By age two or three, they're all five or six feet tall.
They all have hit growth spurts, and they're all loud, their voices are getting deeper.
"Hey, Mama, can we go do the anniversary plane trip with my 1,200 cousins?"
We'll just call them cousins.
They're basically cousins at that point.
they all the same father. I would say that's it that would be like a week
after this news story happens that might be National Enquirer front page news.
Yeah, and they all had the same dad. Yeah, and then that guy's getting
quarantined because something's up. Something's going on. Stop sperm.
They would probably that guy would disappear forever. You got to get it.
They would they would that would be like, you know, in like a in a in a
movie when they discover an alien and the alien just disappears because the
government just takes it permanently or someone superpowers. That's that's
I think I will just be in a lab for the rest of this.
Yeah, he's going to be under Arizona.
So I brought up the 10cc song, because back in the 70s, the way they recorded that was
they had the mixer board and they had four people singing a note, and then they would
like slide up, like the breathy synths in that song are all just the mixer.
So you do that with all the babies on the plane, you go there with a field recorder,
go in there you record every single one of those babies harmonizing uh-huh then
you have the craziest synth sound in the world. You're right. I don't think you need
to be on a plane to do that though. Yeah but if they're all octomom babies and
then if there's one music producer who's also on the plane who has a field
recorder. They're also, you gotta think about it, they're half-brothers too. Yeah. So they're
ancestors, they're half-sisters. There's no girls. That's the other thing man. It's all boys.
called the Octomom Plain Baby Orchestra.
If it's all boys this might be the most
interesting news story to ever happen. This is like amazing that we're even thinking of it.
Even the thought of this should be a news story. I feel like it would be like
Dune. I think that these would be like like a new race of like like babies that
know everything about the world and just kind of take over. That has got to be one
of the most amazing things to ever happen. It would either be that or it would be like a
duplicity situation where one of the babies is very smart and then they have
no cities there's no sister yeah yeah one of the babies is very smart it's like
village of the dam smart on a plane type and then you keep going down the line
and they just keep getting every single sibling right they're not clones or
anything or it could be a despicable me situation they're all there made their
minions of the pilot or wow you just found it yeah the truth that's the
statement they have to grow up to become minions yeah they have to be there
forever indebted if the pilot lands the plane successfully they have to be
slated yeah they literally have to I just don't know what to tell I think the
minions are slaves I think they're a hundred percent slayer right aren't
slaves they do that are they getting paid buddy keep telling yourself that
those are fucking slaves they're literally a race of slaves that were
there a race of slaves we have stockhold slave home syndrome and love being
slaves yeah I guess it's true huh yeah it's fucking yeah they all have their
own weight they'll they get literally dances but they all get but they get
ordered by grew to do stuff and sometimes they're like I don't want to do
it and grew makes them do it and they don't get paid well they don't really
say I don't want to do what Gru wants. Sometimes Gru is like go do this and Minions are like
"Nah, do your number, bro!" Think about how evil, like if he was actually evil he'd be like
go finger that old woman and they're not gonna, the Minions are too nice for that,
but they're probably doing it anyway. They would do it if Gru asked for it because they're loyal
to Gru. Yeah, they're loyal, they're more loyal to Gru than they are to their own kind of Minion
morality. Does Gru punish the Minions? Yes. I think Gru punishes the Minions. He puts their
faces in their own shit. Is there a scene in the movie where he punishes the Minions? Yeah,
One of them takes a sh- a stinking brown shit.
Yeah, the minion forgets to use- how to use the bathroom.
And he puts his nose in-
"You're going to get your poop in the face!"
Mm-hmm.
And he rubs it in.
"You're going to get poop in your own face!"
I never understood that.
Why am- why is it that every time Phil takes a poop in here, I'm ru-
Why am I rubbing his face in his poop?
That doesn't make any sense.
That's the thing.
Dogs love to eat shit.
I know, he just eats his own shit, dude.
One time, I swear to God, he put a little bit of the end of one of his shits in his mouth
and then slurped the log up like spaghetti.
Jesus Chri-
Why would you tell me that?
That is so gross.
The image of a dog slurping up poop like spaghetti.
I mean it was more like he like lapped it up, but it went-
as like one log went into his mouth and he probably swallowed it whole.
That's pretty nasty.
That is disgusting.
Do you think people want to have that mental image?
Do you like me?
These people who are listening to this right now are on their-
Do you fucking like me? Do you just hate me?
-on their way to work or something.
Do you just hate me for no reason?
They're gonna be working at like, I don't know, Sabaro or some shit.
Whoever listens to this probably works at Subway,
and they're probably going to be making a sandwich today,
and then they're going to be putting butter or something down
onto a piece of bread, and think about the dog poop getting slurped up,
and they're going to imagine the stick of butter as the poop,
and they're going to think the whole time, "Yeah, Caleb put that in my head
on my commute here, on my job where I'm making $12 an hour."
Look at how much you're making him cry.
Tears are literally rolling down his face.
Take a picture of him.
And know that you did this.
Good.
I literally saw a full tear go down his face.
Oh wait, check this out.
Dr. Santa.
Doctor, that's a good license plate.
This will cheer you up, Caleb.
Take a look.
That's next to your house.
You can go see that right now.
If anyone is listening and
works at a pizza place and is putting butter on bread,
And he's upset about my dogs
My dog slurping up a piece of poop like spaghetti. I'm sorry. I just like to say that
Why do you apologize?
We move I think we moved past this right? Yeah, I think we can I think we can move forward
I'm okay. Okay when we were on the flight not to go back to the flight, but to go back to the flight
We were on the flight when we were landing. There was some crazy turbulence and the flight attendant came on the intercom
Well, they came on the intercom one time and they were like,
"There's going to be some turbulence where we're landing,
so everyone like sit down and strap in."
And then like there was some crazy turbulence.
And a minute later, they were like,
"There's going to be some even crazier turbulence,
so stay sat down and stay strapped in.
And also if you have a baby, like hold them really tight."
(laughs)
Yeah.
And if you don't have a baby, grab a Bible.
Just an instant like prophetic flash of a banned scene from Final Destination.
Why are you proud of that? Why are you...
That's okay. No, I didn't want to finish talking.
Yeah, tell your story, Cameron. I'm sorry.
I basically, I said basically what I thought was funny and it was completely
paved over by Patrick showing a picture that no one else can see.
Oh it's the picture of Caleb crying and it says "I'm proud of this."
Now Cameron's crying. Wait.
Come on Pat. Look, I mean, you just ruined his story.
I'm in my evil era now.
You fucking, look at him.
Yep.
You ruined his, you're a fucking menace dude.
I'm sorry my story wasn't funny.
It's okay Cam, it really, it was funny but he got interrupted by this guy putting his
phone in your face.
And I think that's fucking dispa- and I was giving you the- don't look to your right.
Don't look to your right right now.
I'm s- don't.
There we go.
Don't look over there, don't be tempted.
Okay, now you can look.
No, no he-
*screaming*
He pulled- he held up the middle finger and then he switched to the pinky.
You can't cry because Phil is gonna-
Oh yeah, Phil's looking at you like you're a bird.
- Phil needs you to-- - Oh, he's trying to come to you.
- Phil's trying to-- - Oh, he's stretching.
He's warming up, dude.
Dude, the cone is killing me, bro.
- He's coming over, he's trying to give you
emotional support. - He's so shitty
with the cone. - I made you so cry.
- It's cone. - I made you so sad.
- That's right, buddy.
Say it again, Kim, yeah. - Yay, yay!
- It's cone. - It's cone, yes.
- So we had to, we were in North Carolina
and then Caleb had to go home a day early
'cause Phil got neutered.
He has no nuts.
He has zero penis.
They didn't let you keep it, right?
No penis?
Yeah, he keeps his penis.
No, the nuts.
The nuts.
I didn't ask for the nuts.
You didn't ask for them?
Wouldn't you?
You said you were going to.
I forgot.
You said you were going to keep them in a jar.
I didn't even go.
I didn't even drop them off.
You know how with every, like, imagine, okay, look right there.
You see the corn broom and shit and the rug and everything?
Don't say I have a corn broom.
You have a corn broom.
People don't need to know this shit about me, dude.
you just say yeah right next to the 60, 66 inch flat screen and a red TV for Samsung?
Right next to this original Rothko painting, right?
Oh no, that's, that betrays me. No, right next to the Dolby 5.1 digital, right next to the
fuckin' giant-
Right next to this neon Saint Polly girl-
That's right.
Sign.
Right next to the foam spray cave that, uh, uh, what kind of texture that I put on the
wall.
Yeah, so right underneath that-
I should get a man cave in here. I think we have one section, one corner of it.
this like all these candlesticks and shit imagine right there a jar of your dog's
pickled nuts are they red what if what about red like imagine it right there it
would go amazing with this with your homes aesthetic it would be kind of cool
yeah I didn't even think about it honestly I was so I was so thinking
about other things that I didn't even think to say, "Can you put these in formaldehyde
and let me look at them at night?"
And I probably would have put googly eyes on him.
Yeah.
That would have been such a good thing to have.
I also feel like he's definitely been lacking vital energy, vital male energy since he's
been neutered.
Well, you can just put testosterone in his food.
Well, but I was thinking, can you?
You can just put male enhancement stuff in his food.
Just like extends and shit?
extends like my brother my younger brother used to have these pills they
were red pills that were just like testosterone it was called male
testosterone plus for a dog no for a guy oh but you could just break up those
pills and hide it in his food I don't think I'm gonna do that I was saying is
maybe he would if he had eaten his own ball his balls he would have at least
gotten some of that back oh like yeah placenta yeah like just like hormonal
thing. I really just think like imagine just having like one day your friend was
like do you want to go over here and you said yeah and then you woke up the next
day your balls are just gone like you're gonna be feeling pretty bad but then if
he was like... I guess the analogy is more like your parents your parents
your parents take you to the fair yeah and then you go to the hall of mirrors.
I guess it's less your parents, it's more your owners. Yeah yeah your master. It's
probably your owners or your master and it's probably that they take you to the
vet. Okay. And then the vet takes out your balls. I don't like to say master with my dog.
But I also don't like to be like, "Oh, I'm his rescuer." Let's just say owners. Yeah.
He's an item. I think that people who, I think you don't, you
should never call yourself your dog's parent. I think it's really weird. Yeah.
Yeah. No, there's a lot of weirdos who call themselves, who talk about, like at
the dog park, they'll be like, "Oh, this other, this dog, his parents are over
there I'm like yeah parents really there's - oh really there's two dogs
over there oh really oh he lives with two dogs you fucking idiot
since you mean it's master yeah don't you mean it's master and mistress yeah
yeah word yeah I guess it is mistress huh what's up the male don't even say
this fucking boners yeah well that's the thing it's like fucking tons of fucking
boners. Well think about like the... I'm thinking about them. Okay so like master
has an evil connotation to it but mistress has a sexy connotation. Master
doesn't have an evil connotation. Yeah it does. Oh I've mastered the
katana. I'm a chess master. I'm a grand wizard. Yeah but those both have...
Mastered is in past tense and then chess master has like a qualifier. Okay okay.
I'm a master at chess.
That's still a qualifier.
That's still...
What are you talking...
Okay, I'm a master of slaves.
That's a qualifier.
That's evil.
But it is a qualifier, so I guess that I am wrong.
I am a master...
What if I'm playing chess and I say I am a master?
Master chef.
And then my slave brings me a martini.
Your little house of cards has come tumbling down.
Oh, oh.
He didn't even know what a master chef was.
No, no, I thought...
This guy's a fucking alien.
I should.
I wait man I think I did immediately master trying to say Master Chief Master
Chef Master Chief - yeah that's a title Master Chief and he's also he's also not
evil yeah he's fucking me I actually can't even think of a good single
instance where the word master is bad or evil Jedi Master true yeah Sith Lord
well Sith Jedi man you're gonna be Lord and Lady yeah you might be knows the
lord royal trouble who's a lord Christopher Guest really he's a lord
yeah yeah Lord of fucking alternative comedy yeah in the full of a mumble cord
mockumentary yeah yeah is it mumble core yeah no it's not mumble core no no
mumble core was invented by creep yeah it's a little more later mumble creep is
what people call creep is a mumble creep is what creep is creepy peep peep peep
creep is what people call mumble gore believe it or not isn't that horrible
that
bad boys. Oh, I thought you meant like Rumbles like a 1950s fight.
No, that's not bad boys like Martin Lawrence, bad boys like Sean Penn.
West Side Story. Million Dollar Baby. That's Rumblecore. Million Dollar Baby, Stumblecore.
Stumblecore. Yeah. Grumblecore, Snow White and the Seven Dwarves.
The Waterboy, GumboCore. Saw, Chumblecore. I would say that Pacific Rim is GundamCore.
Yeah. What else? What else do we got in here?
Condomcore is on all that stuff on porn.
Zack and Miri make a porno.
That could be it too.
Cummingherdcore.
What else? Gumbocore.
That Lieutenant Porter Carlowizzi.
I would say any movie that you watch at a
Regal or AMC theater is comfortcore.
Because of those big nice seats.
Also comfortcore,
what's that
fucking...
Uniclo.
Yeah.
That's comfort core.
Uh-huh.
Holy crap, those fucking fit me well.
Those Uniclo socks are great.
Yep.
I straight up, I never wore anything from Uniclo before.
We can't do any, as a fucking, we can't wear those clothes if you're not like 100 pounds.
Yeah.
The Uniclo clothes.
Oh, no, they hug me in all the wrong ways.
They're not for...
I bought a suit there for a wedding and it looked good on me.
Really?
Yeah.
They do make clothes for fat guys now.
Wow, really?
That's big for a Uniqlo.
I used to walk into Uniqlo when I was a little tad bit heavier.
I'd walk into Uniqlo and I'd be...
Well, they're making oversized stuff.
I'd be sitting there and I'd say, "Hey, where's the men's section?"
He's like, "The whole thing's men's, buddy.
The whole floor is men's."
I'd say, "Really?
You want me to wear blue?"
They got that giant Uniqlo in Boston.
I wouldn't say it's giant.
Pretty big.
Two floors, it's pretty big.
two floors vertically. Yeah, I guess you're right. Two floors vertically is not that big.
Yeah, but horizontally it'd be huge. Horizontally two floors? Yeah, that'd be really huge. That's
really impressive stuff. What's that other, Muji? Muji I like a lot. Muji is the best.
I used to go into Muji and take a nap on the beanbag chair. Which Muji did you take a nap
during
it wait do you know how to call a Mooji think about his wordplay first so I
think what's called a Mooji a movie emoji movie is probably yeah go ahead try that
one try and make that fucking make sense in your little world emoji movie you
mean the movie movie there is no way he has to be kidding right he's too quick
he's just fucking that was so fast quick like he's too quick like a cheetah you
You can click like a cheetah.
We should get on.
Are you seriously talking, did you fell asleep during the emoji though?
Yeah, well I actually never even saw the emoji.
I saw Wreck-it Ralph.
That's kind of a sin.
TJ Miller is in the emoji movie.
That's right.
Oh, Ralph the Wreck?
Yeah, what emoji does he play?
Fucking sexual misconduct emoji?
I don't even remember.
TJ Miller, that's the movie.
Is he the main character?
He's the main character.
He plays Meh.
Wait, Meh is the main character in the emoji?
It's not Smile?
No, it's Meh.
Well, his name is Gene.
- You guys, if there was an emoji movie
about your recently used emojis,
who would be the main character?
- Let's take a look. - Let's take a look.
- Mine would be-- - Everybody, let's go.
- Mine would be this guy.
- Thinker. - Curious one.
- Thinker. - Thinker.
- Yeah. - Thinker.
- Let me get some water while you find this.
- Could you get me some water, too?
- Okay, so my, the main character would be star eyes emoji.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Star eyes? - Uh-huh.
- You use that often?
- I use that a lot.
- Mine is just grinning.
Mine is normal grinning. - And then a neutral-faced emoji
would be the second character, and then the heart hands one
would be third place.
- Is it go down or across?
- Down.
- Down?
Okay, so mine is--
- And then laughing.
- Mine is grinning, swearing, and grinning.
- Basketball clown.
- Okay, so basketball clown.
There's a basketball clown emoji?
- I'm writing a movie right now based on those characters.
- Starry eyes emoji.
- Main character, starry eyes.
- He has, he's blind.
- What? No he's not, he's blind.
- Because his eyes are made out of stars.
But he can only see the world through music
because his name is music, right?
- His name is music?
- Uh-huh, and his mom--
- Wait, what?
- Wait, this is the plot of music.
- Okay.
- Hold on, I just watched that.
- Starry Eyes?
- I just watched the movie Music by Sia.
So let me just, okay, let me start over.
Okay, so the starry eyes,
guy, his, okay, so he's blind but he's also deaf and mute.
And then his teacher teaches him how to say water.
That's the Helen Keller biopic.
Hold on.
Okay.
My most recently used are skull.
skull you just to get an idea of what kind of what kind of text I send a skull
emoji fire emoji 100 emoji and goat emoji a lot of commenting on basketball
Instagram okay TV starry eyes is blind because it was no maybe I should go okay
Okay, so StarryEyes is a little boy in London and he meets his friend Bernie Taup.
Nope, that's Rocketman.
Alright, your movie, your Muji is cancelled.
I can't do it.
You rate my movie.
What would your movie Muji be about?
Okay, let me pull up my list here real quick.
Alright so basically my first one is a smiler.
The complete grinner.
So maybe the first what's up just something that it's really good.
Yeah, okay.
It'd be it's a be a smiler.
Okay, so this I guess is good.
Here's my okay my here.
I'll just run through the plot of my movie really get really quick.
Yeah, you just said movie, but yeah, well you guys taught me what it was.
Okay.
I'm basically your teacher slash master slash owner.
Sure.
Okay.
So basically there's a guy and he's smiling grinning with his eyes open and his mouth
open grinning yeah, then he
swears. Okay, something
happens that make him he
makes him say and dollar
number percent.
See stubs his toe.
Yeah, he stubs his toe
then he but then he
grins again this time with
his eyes and mouth both
closed. Wow, and then he
has and then his heart.
So I'm seeing there's a
heart emoji. So maybe his
something happens to his
heart and then the next
one's neutral. So maybe
his heart it flatlines
like the flat line of the
mouth and then his eyes
go wide and he blushes
the blood God is is
rushing to his head. God damn it. And then he's gritting his teeth here as he's having
a heart attack. And then he's very sad. Or it could be, this could also just be he's in
a coma or dead. Christ. And then he's smirking and smiling. Oh, that's good. Yeah, maybe
he's having a dream in the coma. Oh, okay. And then he's frowning again, so maybe he's...
So he woke, maybe he had a bad dream. Yeah, and then, oh, well then we got an eyes open
emoji, so that's him waking up from the coma. And then he's sweating, because he probably,
you probably sweat when you wake up from a coma. You wake up in a sweat. You wake up in
a
have us guess the movie based only on the emojis.
Okay, Halloween emoji. Halloween. Trick or treat. Yes, Caleb was right.
That was close. Okay, all right, this is for an upcoming movie that's not out yet.
Smile emoji. Smile. Okay, that's right. There's a movie called Smile.
So Caleb went home a day early. We didn't know what to do when we were in
North Carolina for a day because they basically we didn't have us to exist
when I'm not around we didn't know what to do because we didn't have a car yeah
we had to we were uber everywhere and walk places and we didn't really know
what good to do things there's a you didn't take a wave bus bro I don't know
what that is that's a public transit we're not from Wilmington we don't know
what to do to do everything for you no I mean we were fine we didn't ask you
because we didn't need you yeah I just don't need you like roasting us or
anything okay with that you re-ass haircut just okay fine I won't. He doesn't have a haircut he grew it all out.
Okay with that yee-yee ass haircut. I gave myself this haircut I gave myself this
haircut months ago. Let's see if we get a third one.
Oh can he do it? I did it all myself. I bought clippers and I did it myself. I do remember
when you walked into me and Cam's bedroom and you had the clippers and we
said oh Christ you want any and then when he turned around and then he turned
around and walk out and I and we saw the back and I just went like this yeah oh
babe oh honey it looks great honey where did you do it and we saw and I remember I
walked into the bathroom in the trash can fully your fucking hair right and I
was like I gave myself so bad for school I'm like I made I gave myself a buzz and
I said and it's my hair was too long. It's picture day and my daughter has a yee-yee ass haircut
That she gave herself
She's not the fate is fucking ruined. I did a wave check on my daughter and it's okay
I gave myself the haircut and then like I was walking I saw like the back of my head. Oh my god
We have a list today. Yeah. All right. I saw the back of my head like walking by a
Like a storefront and I saw it and I was like, oh Jesus fucking Christ
I left like a huge chunk on my neck and I had to like I walked into like a barber
It feels I will say the nice thing about shaving your head bald is that you can you feel exactly
You know exactly what it feel what it looks like based on how yeah, no
I know I used to shave my head bald all the time. Okay, keep saying this lie
Here's a here is a here's a website that I found that will be I think go doing a few things from ghost
Ghost Street blog spot comm and I have to let's read with two to compare to
companion. You look honestly a little bit like you have a yee-yee-ass haircut right now.
So why don't you let Cameron finish this intro. Two companion lists from this website here.
That's okay, I'll wait. I look like a who.
A little bit. I got who hair. You have a little bit of a who hair.
Kind of three different points. I gotta get a haircut so bad.
You sound like a who with that yee-yee-ass who-nose.
[laughter]
You got that yee-yee-ass pointed who-nose.
Are you guys excited for the Chair of Cheer this year?
[laughter]
They don't have lists.
They have a Chair of Cheer!
They do have a Chair of Cheer.
And what do you eat as a who?
Who-hash.
Roast Beast.
And who-hash.
No fucking vegetarian who.
But mainly roast beast.
Yeah, now you look like, now wow you look just like a who.
If he's a tape, I can do the rest of the episode as a who.
Yeah, let's go get a piece of tape for that.
As if I'm fucking made of tape.
No, then you'd be a tape man.
You wouldn't be a who.
That's true.
OK.
[LAUGHTER]
We should do that podcast at my house more often.
I'm having fun.
It's like the old days.
King in the castle, king in the castle.
Reference.
No.
Normally it feels like such work.
It's fucking--
Oh my god, it's fucking grueling.
--now today, it feels like a daft play.
was dripping, which I really title for the I really, really want to do. We need
these lists. Okay, let's do some of the best list. I found a really long time.
So I'm gonna start. We've had too much of a day of play. We have to go to work.
And so this this is to companion lists here from this website. So first one is
that we'll start with is called
of ghost. Let's it's not a ghost website. It's just there's some go stuff on
there. We'll get to eventually okay, there's a lot of stuff on this website.
We're starting with this list today,
it's all right. It's called husband like suck your breast. It's eight amazing
benefit for wife wow yeah and here's the these to my wife. The opening
paragraph here says husband like suck your breast. It's eight amazing benefit
for wife breast is one erotic area that could pose a major stimulus for sex,
therefore woman's husband often sucks the breast in order to get
satisfaction and enhance benefits suck the breast not to increase sexual desire,
but also very beneficial for women is inhaled by the baby of your husband.
I just can you zoom in on the website a little bit, so I just want to get
down there and fucking inhale those things.
I know oh my God, we inhale the breast of my down there like Kirby and
turn into a boob.
That's all my God.
Yeah, I want to suck a boob so hard.
I turn into a boob.
- Imagine trying to, you fit a whole boob in your,
the entire thing in your mouth.
Can you, that'd be awesome.
- That would be crazy.
- You could do it.
- What if I got startled and I bit it off?
- Stuff it in there?
Just stuff that in your mouth?
- Yeah.
- Joey Chestnut, I bet he could fit a big boob.
- That lady who has the world's biggest mouth?
- She could put her own boobs in.
- Oh yeah, she probably could do that.
- And they just make her eat just giant sandwiches?
- I don't know if they make her do that.
- They make her eat.
(laughing)
If you got a mouth that big, people are going to make you eat some crazy stuff.
Eat this can of spray paint.
She does.
That would fit.
Yeah.
Husband, like, suck your breasts?
It's eight amazing benefits for wife.
Eight benefits provided by wife when you suck breasts.
One.
We got this photo here.
Yeah.
So it's a photo of a man and a woman in bed.
It's not a photo of sucking breasts, but it looks like it's about to happen.
It could be about to happen.
Show it.
Show my thing.
Let's just see it.
Show me how old breasts suck, man.
Number one, improve your sex drive, wife.
Without this technique during sex may reduce sex drive his wife.
Not only that the process of making love would be very boring and wife
becomes become less enjoy because the breast has many points of
sensitivity.
In fact in some situations lubricants.
She does not go out because of does not lubricants.
She does not go out because of lack of stimulation causing his wife
pain when performed penetration pain when performed penetration.
So they're saying that your wife will have a bigger hole if you shove her breast in your
mouth.
Yeah.
I want to know how you found this website.
I found this website by the ghost content on here and then while I was looking for more
ghost stuff I came across a bunch of stuff on this website that was not ghost related
at all.
I don't like suck your breast.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well unless this article was written by a ghost.
woman's um you know what yeah if you put her boo bees you know's into your mouth
then maybe her you know what goes that's how that's a sound yeah put a ringtone
in your wife yeah like touch - or tooth tunes yeah and when you're fucking you
hear like but that's the thing you have to have it at the right angle I'm a star
boy there's a problem with tooth tunes you had to really press them if you
didn't press the right angle and in here be awesome yeah I would have sex way
more often yeah that's the other problem it starts over they should do something
like that in women so that you know if you're doing good or not yeah yeah you're
I'm just like yeah, I'm probably probably just not doing all that good. I'm going
down there. I'm I'm trying to write water down there like I'm Helen Keller. Yeah,
and if you're
and if you're but if you're here and like you know, if you're down there and
you're here in New York, I love you, but you're bringing me down that might like
if you hear that when you're doing good. Yeah, right and you hear like maybe a
car or when you're bad or here's an alternate idea. That's kind of the
opposite you know the game operation yeah maybe you're doing something wrong and
your entire body goes no no no maybe big red yeah but it goes but you would feel
it up your body as well any pain so this idea is bad it wouldn't be pain it would
just be allowed it's not even painful for her maybe it is it's an idea that's
being worked for that's being workshopped by three geniuses three guys
in the sex industry huh I would say we're roughly in the set where sex industry
Adjacent we could go to the avian expo get a booth definitely. I act like a fucking slut. I dread
I'm so slutty. I showed the top of my head. Yeah
You you are so slutty you wanted to look more like a penis and I did a pretty damn good job
I think I even have like a nice like giant head that looks like a penis head
You should get you should get a line on top of your head. We mean I should get a line
Who do I go to me? Oh put a line in my head
You could go to a guy with a permanent marker or you could go to a tattoo artist
I think that's a pretty not we don't want to tattoo. You said a line. That's true. You couldn't get a tattoo of a line
That's my bad
Of a line, but I couldn't get a line
Well, if you would say for example when you're getting a tattoo, you might say I'm getting a skull on my arm
Yeah, you can get a line on your head to of a skull
But you said put a line on my head some kind of put a line also just put a line on your head some abstract
2014 the hipster ass tattoo on your head. I should get a mustache on the top of my head at a bad angle. Yeah
Check this out
Look what I hold it up. It looks like I have a mustache on my head wait wait put your face
face, but your face behind my head.
That's genius dude. Number two can detect any abnormalities in the breast wife.
Yeah, by manipulation of the breast area, then unwittingly husband had helped his
wife to conduct early detection of breast cancer. If abnormalities, then you
and your partner will immediately take action. This has early detection of
breast cancer. The ob gyn does when he goes, I put he puts this mouth. No, I'm
old school.
put your tits in his mouth? Yeah I do. This is an old pioneer technique that I still use.
That tastes like cancer. I'm a holistic OBGYN. That tastes exactly like a tumor. I kind of
feel like acupuncture is kind of close to that. These acupuncturists have got to be
doing something with women's rear ends. Yeah. Like putting a needle in their butt? Yeah.
yes yeah i think so
and this is the
this is the area in your body were for put a needle and it will actually help
uh... make a red dot on your skin
that's what that's kind of an idea and this is the effect is you have a red
this area yeah how did they not believe when you put you had a key puncture dot
i'm not a it's a tattoo it's not going all the way in
i'd be bleed i believe when i get to know you would you can believe when you
get to i've never bled people to tell people one tattoo some people to do this
So yeah, both of those don't count.
Some people bleed when they get vaccines and stuff too.
I do.
Really?
Do you actually?
My body is already trying to get that shit out of there.
That toxic shit.
I wish I could- I train my body to as soon as they put it in,
it's already, I squeeze it back out just so they have it on file, but I know that my body's
pure.
That's right.
It's like taking your meds, right?
You put them- I haven't taken them in five years.
You hide it under your tongue.
I hide the microchip under one muscle and then I pop it out straight away.
I hide the microchip under one muscle and then I pop it out, straight pop, I pop my bicep
out.
It's like the shark tooth in the Woman King.
And I'm getting a good pump too.
It's exactly like the shark tooth in the Woman King.
The movie Cameron and I saw.
Shark tooth in the Woman King.
You didn't see.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, you wouldn't get it unless you saw the Woman King.
Did you see this yesterday?
No, don't worry about it.
We're just going to move on to the next thing on the list because he's kind of harshing
the vibe of us talking about our movie that we like.
I've been the vibe man.
No, we were just trying to talk about a movie that we liked and you were like, what's that?
so I just want to know we just like we like talking to people who know the
movie yeah and we shared popcorn in the week to you only like talking to
people who know the movie yeah, okay, but I don't know who shared popcorn to
and you know I what's it calling you
shark tooth and the woman King or woman King, it's called right, who is no you
saw it wait. Oh, I think I'm trying to I think I've actually seen that movie.
When did you see it pretty recently actually really one yeah, like two
three days ago. Maybe really I saw it. Yeah, I think so. Is your favorite
character? I thought all the what was your favorite kingdom? I thought all the
characters did a great job and there is no kingdom in it. So it's a proves that
I'm completely did not completely did not see it or there is a kingdom. Sorry.
I watch it in a different language. It wasn't called a kingdom. It was called. I
don't remember it was in a language that I've never even heard of
much to dub,
but I actually really thought the movie was really good. So it's fine for us to
keep hanging out and talking okay. Okay. Did you share popcorn with us when you
saw it? I think I did share yeah. I think I did. Oh, mm-hmm. All right. I guess I
can trust him. Yeah, I wouldn't expect him to lie to me. I guess yes, we wouldn't
be a guy. You saw the movie wouldn't lie or like yeah. I mean well now that like
the oil kingdom exactly now that we all here have seen it. I mean we can discuss
like I thought that the the the oil kingdom when they rode horses. I was like
get those horses out of the horses when the horses originally rode into the
kingdom. I was like bad news. Yeah, bad news is coming and that's and that's and
I was right and what did you say? What did you think of the the rapist
character? I think either way, you know, it could be could be portrayed either
way.
Yeah, what really with most stuff in the movie, either which would just a lot of
Either way.
What did you think about them stopping, the idea that they wouldn't sell people anymore
and they would actually start selling palm oil?
Well here's what I got.
Opinions are like assholes.
Everyone's got them, right?
Or everyone's got one.
So that's my thoughts on the movie, or not so far because I already finished it.
But that's pretty much my thought on that film.
And the director, a lot of people have a lot to say about them and I don't really.
I just don't have that much to say.
And the movie itself, the script I thought was really...
And the location.
The locations were...
Of DaHomie.
Of what?
DaHomie.
Yeah, that was good too.
Yeah.
I thought there was a lot of just, you know, I had a lot of takeaways and maybe I haven't
fully processed the whole thing.
Sure, yeah.
There's a lot to talk about with that movie I guess.
So we could do it on the next episode.
We could do a full...
Yeah, yeah, we'll do a full...
A full deep dive.
I think if we turn into a...
We think we should turn into a movies review.
movies only? Yeah I think maybe movies only. And that's what it would be called. Holy movies
only. Holy movies only. FMO. It's gonna be good. Number three. Can smooth the flow of
blood. By sucking the breast and perform massage of the breast will make the blood flow to
the breast wise to be smooth so could your partner's breast still tight and will not
loose again. Suck the breast can also relieve stress in women. Yeah I love getting a breast
massage. Is there fucking blood in boobies? Yeah I guess so. It's fucking disgusting.
There's also white milk.
Oh that's amazeballs.
No, the balls have white jizz.
Oh.
Wait, what?
You're thinking of amazeboobs.
That's amazeboobs.
Number four is can tighten facial skin.
I know mine.
I'll tell you this much, my loose wife needs this badly.
Because of the time of sucking the breasts during sex will make the movements of the
muscles in the wife's face.
It is good for the sport faces.
That aims to tighten the skin in muscles wife's facial area.
Sport faces?
Yeah, so if you have a sporty wife.
Okay.
I guess my wife is decently tennis-like.
Yeah.
Yeah?
And she could play a sport.
Okay, so this might be useful to you.
Maybe I'll tighten her face.
My wife constantly has yellow beads of sweat because of how much Gatorade she drinks.
Really?
Yeah, and she's constantly in black and white, and the beads of sweat are in color.
Wow, that's interesting.
Is the bottle in color?
Yes.
Oh.
My wife...
She's in black and white.
- My wife's skin is so loose
that she looks like a degloved apple.
So I think I might use this technique to try and--
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- You know what's so, when you come home
and you see your wife and she looks like
the skin that fell off of the rotisserie chicken.
- Yeah, she looks, I get home and I'm like--
- Baby, are you wearing your mom's skin today?
- And I'm like, I forgot that I bought
a Salvador Dali painting.
- Yeah, I hate it when my wife sheds her skin
and leaves it around the apartment.
- Baby, are you malting?
Oh my god, she's molting again.
You know, it's my wife's time of the month, she's molting.
[Laughter]
Yeah, you know, I love her to death.
I love her to death, but I could do...
A full respect the pouch, just like deflated, fucking...
I love my wife, but I could do without the skin on the floor.
Yeah, listen, we all love the wife.
Look, she leaves her skin on the floor, I come out of the shower, the skin gets wet, I slip, I almost hit my head on the side of the tub.
Mm-hmm.
Number five, train the balance of the heart.
With Breast Sucking Wife,
we'll make the heartbeat faster than normal.
It is good to practice healthy heart rhythm.
- So you're making, I mean is it--
- You speed up her heart by--
- With like the suction?
- I think it's you suck in and out to kind of--
- And then contract, yeah. - Oh wow.
- You're trying to suck her heart out of her boob
like it's the Temple of Doom.
- I want to suck your boob.
- You're sucking the boob and you're going,
"Kalima, Kalima!"
And this makes her heart go into your mouth like through a portal.
You suck it out like when it pops out of a cartoon.
It's like a heart shaped tube that goes all the way back of skin or of fur.
You can hear the SpongeBob guitar going.
I love the SpongeBob guitar.
I've been meaning to learn to play it.
Number six.
Little one with the four strings.
Increase contractions after childbirth.
contractions after childbirth and smooth the blood when menstrual pain arrived.
Well this is very interesting. Turned out to suck the breast can prevent the
occurrence of active bleeding after childbirth. Suction is performed will be
made so that the maximum contraction of blood vessels in the uterus that had
been wedged open back and make the blood stops. Menstrual pain has got to be hard
AF. Honestly women are fucking metal. Yeah. Nature is kind of metal too. Yeah.
Nature is metal for women's bodies. Metal as fuck. Yeah. Women are metal. Women's bodies are made out of
metal hey at least the ones I talked to
sex robot
was exist already yeah I mean I don't know how to metal Boston dynamics
Davis let me tell you do a sex robot that can torque
holy shit well right now they can do is gyrate
if they can do it working Boston dynamics robot with a brown metal ass
be fucking like my shirt okay I'm gonna I'm gonna go through these last two
really fast we can get to the other the other companion list here
So this is seven, reducing pain during menstruation.
At the time of menstrual pain, sucking at the breast,
we're able to distract the woman from the pain that is felt
on the other breast suction
when the contractions become painful.
Menstruation will make the maximum forcing
in pure blood to be released.
And number eight, losing weight with suction the baby
through breastfeeding.
With breastfeeding, it will accelerate your return
to your ideal body shape originally
because there'll be a fat burning calories
while breastfeeding the baby.
So it's great for your healthy diet.
- So that's an easy way to cut if you're like an IFBB pro
trying to make a bodybuilding competition
is to have a baby suck your breast.
- Yeah, so that's really good to know.
- I didn't even know that.
- There are a few comments here
that are mostly links in other languages.
- Well, I like this one, though.
Go up a little bit.
- Yeah.
- Smaller breasts provide females a beautiful look.
Make your breasts smaller and firmer.
With the use of natural supplement, it is effective.
- Interesting.
Okay, I'm gonna move to the second list here that we have.
It's called Five Technique How to Breast Sucking
to Not Injury.
- Wow.
So is this, are you trying to get,
Who's getting the breast, or the injury, is it the sucky or the sucker?
I think it's unclear as of right now.
And I think that, so first we learned the benefits of husband suck wife breast, and now maybe
if you would like to implement some of these benefits in your life, we can learn how to
do that safely without causing injury to either the husband mouth or wife breast.
So this is women's breast sucking techniques to not injury.
Yeah, it is way too big.
That looks crazy.
looks insane. Oh my God.
Put some Chad Muska flair on it.
You look crazy.
You're jealous of my new hat.
It's a cool hat.
It is a cool hat.
I got a cool new hat too.
Do I look like Chad Muska?
No.
What was your new hat?
I can't say what it was, but we bought it in North Carolina.
Well, we'll just start.
Number one, suction nipple or areola down to the black part around the nipple.
This is done so that you not only do the manipulation of the nipple so that you make the nipples
become sore, but it by sucking up areola area, then your partner will be able to enjoy and
not feel sick at all.
Areola area?
So that's useful to know.
In a corn maze gonna scare ya.
Holy shit.
Dressed up like a scarecrow.
In a scarier area.
Dirty jobs like a micro.
Holy fuck dude.
Areola area?
Damn, he unlocked an M&M ability.
That's a pit bull style terrier.
Oh my god.
Keep going, keep going.
I got some poop coming from my derriere.
Okay, keep going.
You have two more bars you gotta do to finish the...
And I'm in the closet.
I ain't coming out.
You're supposed to keep rhyming.
You just started saying...
'Cause my foot got the gout.
Are you like...
Bad case of gout.
It really sounded for a second like he was just like trying to sneak in coming out to
us.
I got something to tell you later.
in the middle of the impression.
(laughing)
- So you can actually save a woman,
you can suck up all the areola.
- Yeah, the black area.
- And get it all--
- What is the black area?
(laughing)
I sounded like Don Knotts for a second.
What is the black area?
- What is the black area of the areola?
(laughing)
- Why, what is the black area?
- Number two, do palpability in the other breast
that is not you smoke.
- Do palpitinia.
- If you know for sure about the shape
of your partner's breasts,
then if there are abnormalities such as tumors
arising in the breast area,
you are the first to know,
so that remedial action can be done immediately.
- Okay, so it's like remedial.
- We already heard that.
It's like a prevention technique is sucking your woman's
breast. - But this is saying,
this is saying-- - Remedial is a word
I'm familiar with. - The other one you know
is, this one says immediately.
So I think you might be the person taking out the tumor.
- Well here's what I, remedial is a word
I'm very familiar with a lot of my classes were remedial.
- Okay, that's perfect.
- I think what they're saying here is it's so easy
a caveman could do it.
- Right. - Oh, really?
- Yeah. - Listen, caveman,
if you're listening, stay away from my fucking wife's breasts.
That's not your job, that's mine.
- Caveman, stay away from my cave.
- Cavewomen. - Stay away from my fire.
- What's up? - Yeah, what's going on?
- What's up? - I bet that thing
smells like PlayStation Air.
- Do you think, (laughs)
Do you think, shouldn't, just for fairness,
you know, shouldn't a woman also have to suck your balls
to see if you have testicular cancer?
- Yeah.
- And your asshole to see if you have polyps?
- Getting your balls sucked hurts.
- Who's sucking your damn balls so hard?
- The friggin' Nunu from the Teletubbies?
- Yo, what's up?
- What the fuck is up, boy?
- I was gonna say Henry the vacuum.
- Damn, damn, we just got your ass.
- Henry the little red vacuum.
- He getting sucked by Nunu.
- Oh, shoot.
Oh my God.
Nah, not him getting snoo-snoo from Nunu.
Holy, not Birdo sucking, yo, dick.
Double TV reference.
Yep.
That's the noise it would make when Birdo sucked.
Yeah.
Yeah, and also the noise you made before.
(whistles)
Yeah.
It doesn't hurt to get your balls sucked.
(laughs)
It's gotta feel good, man.
I'm not even gonna finish this.
It's like, damn, my balls are getting,
I mean, it doesn't feel good on your balls,
but in your head you're like, word.
(laughs)
My balls, man.
There's this old interview show for skaters.
It was called Weekend Buzz.
And there's this guy--
I bet that's awesome.
Austin Gillette talked about getting a ball koozie.
Yeah.
Which is when you put your balls in hot water
and the woman just blows into it with a straw.
Nice.
That guy should work for Urban Dictionary.
Yeah.
That does actually work.
He worked for Globe Footwear.
And he made a skatable Chelsea boot.
He's a globalist?
Yep.
Yeah, big surprise there.
Yeah.
Globalist skateboarder.
Number three.
Global skateboarders are ruining the country by making skatable Chelsea boots.
Yeah, and inventing new fucking out-of-marriage ball techniques.
Yep.
Fuck that.
Number three.
Performed breast squeeze technique is also important when you suck the breast of your
partner.
By squeezing, then you can know your partner feel pain or not.
If pain is felt towards the breast area menstruasi, then it was reasonable.
Menstruasi.
However, if the pain is felt at any time and not be bearable, then you should immediately
consult a doctor.
So if you squeeze...
That is crazy.
One way to avoid injury when you're sucking your wife's breast is if you squeeze it so
hard that it hurts that will injure her.
Did they, were they trying to spell menstruation and then...
No, menstruasi.
It's a type of, it's like an ancient science.
No, it's a martial art.
Oh, that's, yeah, that's what I meant.
Yeah, it's a martial art.
Ancient science.
Is this like alchemy?
Yeah.
Or perform techniques to manipulate the nipple pair.
(laughing)
- Manipulate the nipple pair?
- Occasionally do pencubitin.
The goal is that you find out whether the size of nipple one
and the nipple two equal or symmetrical or not.
Besides, extortion is also done if the nipple
ooze pus or blood when pinched.
In cases of breast cancer, will bleed nipple and pus.
So you should immediately conduct an intensive examination.
- Have you ever seen those pictures of women--
- Pupes is just a kind of hair.
- A woman who survived heart, pubes is just a kind of hair,
that's a good line.
Have you ever seen those women who get their breasts removed
but then also get their nipples removed?
- Yeah.
- That's gotta just hurt and be kind of odd.
- I've seen people who just get the nipples removed.
- Nipples are pretty much useless,
but that's gotta feel, I mean I want them still.
If I had the option to be born with or without,
I'd choose with.
- What is this?
- I'm trying to figure out what pencubitin means.
- What did it just say?
(laughing)
- What?
it's it when you were typing that it said he will pay
well
it is a latin
and in english it as you type it will pay so i have to take the language on
attempting and can cuba ten
i've got pen it's a pen okay
and then pet p_n_c_ pink that means five
and then it moves to uh... pinku which is pen range of the knees
that we have
pent-up which is a pent-up
and then we have
the house, and then i add an eye or a pencubi and it means squirt vulgar in
chinese simplified, and then i add a t pencubit and in latin it is he will pay
vulgar. He will pay and then i press a and we have pencubi, it means pencubite
and then i add an n and now it means airbrush pen alter in chinese. Holy
fuck,
squirt vulgar vulgar that that must be performed techniques to manipulate the
pair occasionally do squirt vulgar. That has to be the only one that makes sense, right?
Occasionally he will pay. Yeah, I guess you're right. Occasionally he will pay.
But this isn't a Chinese website, right? I don't know. I don't think so.
Maybe it's translated from Chinese. Who knows?
Number five, the last one is, massage the breast while sucking wife's breast are also very important,
thus making the blood flow in the breast area to be smooth. If done in nursing mothers will
will make milk more smoothly and avoid engorgement.
Moreover, it's possible the massage
will make the breast becomes tighter.
- To avoid-- - Oh, I love a tight breast.
- Yeah, just like you can fuckin' pop a quarter off of it.
Oh my fuckin' God. - Yeah.
- Yeah, that's what they do in the female army
every morning, they check-- - The female army?
- Yeah, they check if you can bounce a quarter
off your breast. - I was,
we should make a movie about like a guy--
- Called the female army. - A guy who like,
sneaks into the female army-- - The woman king too.
so that you can genius.
Oh, we could go undercover and not undercover janitors or we could hide in
the laundry and stuff and see what kind of female army stuff they do.
Yeah, pretty smart.
So it's like Porky's but in the female army.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like the opposite of Mulan.
Well, what would that be called the female army?
The female army about if Porky's is about the camp and doing panty rides.
Well, it'd be like army fun.
Panty rides.
FUBAR female underwear the boys army.
yeah really want you to have the uh...
for he ready
yeah are you know underwear boys army field situation normal all-female army
always shannon
all-female army
that's for okay well that's the list on and that's the episode so you have to
you're gonna want we just did something incredible this past weekend and to see
that incredible thing you know what i don't know hints in this is a lack of
talk.com/shows. We did more than draw pins, we said what it was many times. We filmed a
paranormal investigation with Caleb's uncle. We were making allusions to something we said
before. We saw a lot of allusions that were casted on us. We did see some, I'm going to
be real, you've got to come through because there's some stuff that we saw on tape. There
was some questionable paranormal phenomena that we caught on tape. We saw phenomena,
got it on tape and uh... This is going to be world news and you're going to want to
be there to see it first. Yeah, no, it's pretty scary dude. Yeah, so... I'll say this much.
Dean if you're listening, hi there.
That's right.
Yeah, I don't want to go into any more detail than that, but go to swagpoop.com/shows to
buy a ticket to our Halloween show, The Night of Evil at the Bell House, Halloween night
in New York City, Brooklyn.
Goannas.
Brooklyn, Goannas, New York City, Halloween world.
It's on Halloween planet, you're going to have to charter a spaceship.
The Bell House.
And we'll see you there.
Hey, we're there on Halloween night, it's going to be the Hell House.
for watching.