come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
crap monster
we're completely back all three of us
we're back it is good to be a i'm cameron
patrick
mohammed
the
so i'm a lot of the uh... so it's a heavy bag and i'm not a bad and you've
been on one. I've been on one, yeah. Vacation that is. Yeah, well I stopped drinking too
because that was a real problem I had before. Yeah. And you changed your name to, well you
stopped drinking when you converted to Islam. Yep. No, my name's always, no. No. I thought
you were doing a thing where it's like Caleb comes back from vacation and he's. Oh, okay.
I am doing that. Yeah. Caleb's still on vacation, he's never coming back. Like you did like
- I was on vacation.
- Yeah, I was too.
- It's pretty nice.
- We all took vacations.
- We did all take vacations.
I was on the beach.
- I went to the beautiful Bay Area.
- Soaking up the rays.
I was in the beautiful outer banks of North Carolina.
- You didn't tell me where you were going.
- I didn't want anyone to show up.
- It's a secret.
- You have to keep it secret.
- You didn't tell me where you were going
until you got back.
- It's a safety thing.
- The whole time I was like,
"Okay, I'm just at the beach."
(laughing)
- I'm just at the beach.
I am just at the beach. I was at the beach. I was soaking up the water.
Oh yeah? Just soaking it up.
Soaking it up like a baby.
What I saw was a baby.
You're just drinking the water in the sea salt.
Oh my God, I saw dolphins.
I think I would have, if I knew where he was going, maybe I had been there before and I
could give him recommendations.
But no.
Check out the beach. Try the water.
try to the beach, try the water, you gotta try the sand, you gotta bury your head in
the sand, you gotta bury yourself neck up, I was boogie boarding, yeah, that's cool,
like Kenny Powers, yeah, I just watched that episode, I got a rash on my belly from boogie
boarding, that's why you gotta wear the shirt, yeah the rash guard, I got sun poisoning,
you got sun poisoning, yeah, when I was in Oakland, what does that mean, you got overheated,
I know I you were in like a doctor octopus kind of like experiment gone
wrong.
I was poisoned by I, um, I,
I went skating for like, I don't know, I think it was like three hours.
And I was like, damn, like the weather here is like so good.
Like this literally feels like springtime and like,
cause it was like 65 degrees out. And, uh,
I thought because like, you know, like you don't have to wear as much sunblock in the
spring, you know.
It's like the sun.
Well, I think it's the thing where that's the opposite, where you think you don't, but
everyone's like, "Well, actually, you know, you actually do."
The sun's always beating down.
But you don't.
The sun's always there.
Right.
Well, I, you know, for no, I didn't put on any sunblock.
You're supposed to wear sunblock year round, even at night.
Do you do that?
No.
Okay.
At night?
Yeah.
You are supposed to wear it at night.
Really?
I don't know, my girlfriend's always telling me I wear sunscreen probably like two days out of the year.
Yeah, my face. Y'all are pretty pale. Look at how red, look at, you can see.
Well, this was red before.
Okay, all right, wait. The inside of my mouth got so sunburned. Cut your hand open, look how red.
Oh my god.
Yeah, but the Oakland, Oakland, California, beautiful, one of the most beautiful places
in the world. Yeah, I think the Bay Area, I think people give too much shit to the Bay Area because
of the tech stuff, but San Francisco is a beautiful place. What do you got? You got the Golden Gate,
you got Pixar. Chiopino. You got Chiopino. It's got beautiful, it's built on a beautiful mountain.
on one side and down the other.
- That is the best food I've ever eaten.
- Is that that red thing that you were talking about?
- That seafood stew, I'm rubbing my belly just thinking
about it. - You probably told me
about this like five times.
- Yeah, dude. - How much you like that.
- Oh my God, it's the best thing I've ever had.
- What is it again?
I forgot. - It's just like a,
it's like a fisherman's stew.
- I had donuts.
(laughing)
At the beach.
- Hell yeah.
- Thank you, Pino, for my birthday.
- Maple bacon.
(laughing)
- 25 now.
- Wow.
- Do you feel--
- One more year on my parents' health insurance.
- You're a quarter of the way to being a wizard.
- Yeah?
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- If you hit 100 and you're alive, you get to be a wizard.
That's how it works.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah, there's some people trying to circumvent that.
Some people calling themselves wizards.
They wear big, white, pointy hats.
Now, here's what I say to all you wizards.
Fuck you.
- Fuck you.
That's right, we don't like you.
And you're not even real wizards.
I hate those people.
You're actually racist.
Although, there are 24 year olds who wear the hat.
It's like, "Nope, not yet buddy.
One more year.
Take the hat off."
Have you seen, speaking of, have you seen that video of Ezra Miller?
Yes.
And they're in a car.
Whatever it is, yes.
They're in their car and they're calling out a specific chapter of the KKK.
they're saying like you should all kill yourselves okay or I'm gonna do it for
you Wow that's good okay they redeem themselves
specific chapter is very funny you should not know the chapter of the KKK
that's a huge red flag like why do they know the fucking- you gotta do your research before that's true
because well yeah cuz that chapter they were that chapter they were saying they
were gonna kill it those are bad guys but some other chapters they're not so
bad. It's a bad apples in the video. They said, you know what
you're doing, which means like you're not either have personal
beef. Yeah, or yeah, you know what you know what you're doing.
You're not giving you're not giving the time of day to entry
interviews. You're not reading the applications that people
send in. Yeah. You're denying people for no reason. compliment
You just flat out ignore them.
Yeah, dude.
That's cool.
Is that a recent video?
No, it's from a while ago.
Oh, it's from the 1800s.
Was that one that you sent me?
It's the one of them.
They're like on in the middle of an interview.
They just start singing like Michael Rowe.
Oh, yeah, that's on that movie phone with that movie critic.
I can't wait.
Did that one come out a long time ago?
That was like right when they got famous.
Like I think they were promoting
Perks of Being a Wallflower.
- Holy shit, so they've just been psychotic forever.
- One was, what about, they were in
We Need to Talk About Kevin too, right?
Was that before or after that?
Before Perks of Being a Wallflower?
- That was probably after.
- That was before?
I don't know.
I'm just, if that was like their first big movie,
that'd be pretty funny.
- Yeah.
- That that just eventually--
- I think that was.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- I know him from Perks.
(laughing)
I know him from Perks. I'll tell you I love that movie. That's a great movie.
Perks of being a wallflower?
I love that movie.
I'm outing myself as a...
Yeah, I prefer the intellectual version, Perks of Being on the Mayflower. It's a historical
drama. Also starring Ezra Miller.
There is no Perks of Being on the Mayflower though.
Perks of Being on the... Perks of Being a Wallflower is interesting though because that
movie I think was like written and directed by the guy who wrote the book
that's always interesting the the exorcist 3 is like the same way
exorcist 3 is so sick it's always so good yeah yeah what's it William Peter
Blady baby even Spielberg eatie beetie there's no L in those last name I
thought it breath he's not related to the the beaties of Hollywood is he what
what do you say the beat the beady eyed people of hollywood war and beady he's
not one of those be you say you want to you want you want to be warring against
the beady eyed people of hollywood, the bees war in role or in pcs you say okay,
you're saying these beady eyed people are trying to bring pc culture to
hollywood. Is that what you're saying better watch your watch? You shouldn't
stuff like that it's what you Peter Blatty that's what yeah bloody so I was
right I just said his name wrong yeah we both were wrong actually you're not
right I said you said lady lady that's still
wrong bleep bleep still wrong weekly bleep bleep bleep bleep bleep we're
putting pleakley in that movie oh my god please work is that the guy from Lilo
and stitch yeah Kevin McDonald's character and that guy I don't really
sounds like I think that is what he sounds like yeah but he was funny I
liked it was funny he's a good character yeah yeah we want stitches they had a
bleakly the movie is a good character they're doing a great I don't like Buzz
was light year. I like pleakly what's the what's the big guy's name Zerg big big
so big so the big guy is actually named William Oh stitch lady no that's a little
that's a buddy that's the funny guy big guy Lilo and jumbo or something jump I
think it is jumbo it's gone to game - what's captain Gantt - no that's the evil
guy. Oh, who's the big guy? The big, the guy who invented Stitch.
Pleakley's husband. Stitch has a glitch.
Stitch has a glitch is the... Jumba Jookuba. Yeah, Jumba. Jumba. Jumba Jookuba. I'm so smart.
I'm a Disney expert. Stitch has a glitch is the... Oh yeah, Dr. Jumba Jookuba is a
Queltequan from planet Queltequan. Stitch has a glitch is the... And he's a creator of
630 illegal genetic experiments. Yeah, yeah. Is that the first appearance of Reuben?
the sandwich alien is he in yeah he's in the movie right yeah was he in the first
movie i don't know if he's in the first they had a tv show that it was like tv
show yeah i loved that show i watched that like every morning before school
it was good ruben was a real scene stealer on that
was awesome yeah he made all he liked to do was make
sandwiches
folks doctor jumbo jukuba
he's got 630
radical genetic experiments
great friend of mine, but a lot of weird little guys he makes
no he would be friends with general gantu
yeah that's true
he would hate dr jumbo jukuba
jumbo jukuba, little jumbo jukuba
i'm bigger than him
i'm bigger than he
he has a huge mostly bald ovular head
with three black hairs, a wide mouth, a round nose
and four beady eyes
huge
reading the Delilo and Stitch wiki at a rally.
He's a heavyset, mostly purple skinned alien
with a dark pink skin on his chest, stomach,
and under his arms.
That's what people are saying about him.
People are telling me about that.
They're saying he's little.
He's got four arms.
What do you need four arms for?
Jumba Jookaba attended and graduated
from Evil Genius University
Dr. Jacques von hamster veal his lab partner. Oh, I remember Jacques von hamster veal. That
sounds like a deep cut reference to the show. If I was like the main villain of the show.
Oh, I guess. Is that the other? Is that Ruben's boss? Yeah. Oh, okay. I didn't know his name.
He was the hamster guy. He had Yeah, he had big he had ears that stand up and he had the
H on him. Yeah, I'm thinking of like the shark head guy. That's Gantoo. Okay. Yeah. Dumbass.
that one lady that like the skinny and hamster veal seems to have a bit of a
Napoleon complex what does hamster will look like he looks like a hamster yeah
oh yeah speaking of speaking of Trump we saw the birds last night and the guy in
the movie sounded like Trump yeah the main guy sounded like you're doing an
impression of Donald Trump yeah it was really funny so if you ever if you're
listening you ever end up watching the birds imagine that guy's is Trump yeah
when he says your eyes birds they flew down the chimney it was like I don't
know what happened I was like for like five minutes I was just like like as
soon as you said like he sounded like Trump when he did that one like line
delivery I was like oh he kind of does then for five minutes I just like wasn't
looking at the screen I was listening to him like yo that does sound stupid easy
to do though cuz the birds very boring movie I thought I fell asleep yeah you
You were like nodding off. You were like a cartoon.
It was so funny. I was really hoping that you'd start snoring.
I did. I did start snoring, but like it was like that thing, like I was, cause I was like
sitting, I was able to catch myself. I went like, and like, yeah, you like shot up and
you were like, boring.
We saw the birds in theater.
Yeah.
Dude, that fucking...
I don't give a fuck about the first half of that movie.
I liked all the parts with the birds in it.
Maybe that's what...
'Cause like you were saying, like, there's like...
Like there's like, oh, you're supposed to put yourself in the shoes of the birds.
Maybe they put that like...
In the claws of the birds.
In the talons of the birds.
In the feathers of the birds.
From a bird's eye view.
Yeah.
You're supposed to watch that movie from a bird's eye view.
It would be the first half of the movie is boring because you're like man. I fucking hate all these people
Yeah, I never want to see these people and I'm just a bird and I'm a friend
Yeah, that's why there's I don't even it's I need a worm right now
I don't know how how they like marketed it when it came out or whatever
But it'd be crazy to like if you're like in like when it like 1963 or whenever it came out. It was 63, right?
Yeah, it was 63 like going to the theater and being like, oh, it's like a new Alfred Hitchcock movie
It's called the birds and it opens up and it's about like oh this woman like bringing birds to a guy and you're like
Oh, it's like about they're like weird
I think that definitely is probably why I didn't like it was cuz I thought it was gonna be like, yeah
Or a bird, you know, I think that's the problem is like that movies like
Old enough now that like every every cool marketing thing about it for us is gone. Yeah
Yeah, no, totally.
Like everyone's like, "Oh yeah, you should go see The Bird.
It's a movie about a bunch of birds attacking people."
Yeah, and then it's not really like that, really.
I will say I liked whenever they would show a bird eating a kid.
I feel like they had a lot of shots of kids on the ground like, "Ahh!" and then birds
just like...
The part where it shows the guy with his eyes pecked out was crazy.
I was not expecting that.
Spoiler alert!
the people the people next to us in the theater every time that a bird came on
screen they were like oh oh oh oh oh yeah it would be like a scene of like a bird
pecking a guy on the hand and they're like oh no no like the most annoying
group yeah in the yeah it was so funny
protect me yeah you should have gone to
see a Lilo and stitch we should honestly
I would have rather Hawaiian roller
coaster my yo group trip Hawaiian
roller coaster ride oh my god that's
really never been do you think they have
stitch there they've stitched Disney
world or in Hawaii oh they probably have
I thought there was something called the Hawaiian roll. I have no idea. That's just the song in the movie
Right at Disney we had to sing that for chorus class in seventh grade
Is that weird that is weird seventh grade feels a little old to be singing. No, we won't stay I went to Disney Middle School
Disney Middle School I
Forget there's like you imagine the clitis and Walt Disney Middle School. I got the villains
prince. The princesses, the
princesses.
Dude, were you seriously just
sitting at the princess table?
The animals, yo that's the
funny table. I got that's the
donors. The stoner to
to you, man, smoking weed with
a moment. If I was I was, but I
smoke weed out of Timon yeah who would like that the geeks be at Disney high
school I'd probably be like every like pleatly and jump yeah well that's the
thing Disney owns a lot of movies I'll be shoving learn this because I've been
playing I've been shoving game jumbo into mental locker yeah I'd be sure I'd
shove Bruce Banner into a locker not knowing oh I forgot that yeah this is
Disney owns a lot of properties.
They owned a lot of the shit back in the day too.
Jocks.
Mm-hmm.
Operation...
Or the soldiers in Operation Dumbo Drop.
The Xenomorph would probably be the principal.
Oh yeah, they own Fox.
The mean principal.
Yeah.
Bro.
Disney Middle School must be crazy now.
Yeah, I couldn't even imagine.
All these transfer students from Fox Middle School and ESPN Middle School.
had Star Wars school yeah yeah yeah and galaxy far far away school. You know I
would I would I was such a I was such a weird kid in high school. I would always
sit at the Sith table yeah dude yeah. My best friend was Charles Xavier that
tells you something
he was a teacher.
Best friend was my teacher. Yeah he was yeah yeah. I finally I finally watched
I didn't watch the whole series, but I watched like the final battle in the Obi-Wan series.
Oh, yeah, I watched that too. I only watched that part and if they only showed that that'd be so cool
It was when they're in like the rock. Yeah. Yeah, what's them? They have a new Star Wars show coming up and or yeah
What is that? I just saw Cassian on door. What's that Cassian on door was the guy in Rogue One?
character yeah and the first like shot of that like the trailer is like they just
have like a guy holding an AK there's not even like that's cool it's not even
like a Star Wars gun they should let me make a Star Wars series I've so I have a
good idea I have an idea I've had an idea since I was a kid okay what's your
idea off of the books so it's like there it's like this like Jedi
No, it's a real idea I had when I was a kid. So it's like a rhodian. What's that
mean? Like Greedo, like the green guy with like the yeah yeah Greedo and he
smokes weed. Whoa that's cool. And his name is Green Bud the Rhodian. Okay.
Patrick, you might need a workshop that idea buddy. Yeah I think you need to take a look.
And he has the munchies.
(laughter)
And it's like a limited series?
And he totally has the munchies from Smoking Weed.
Eight episodes, 10 episodes?
16 episodes.
(laughter)
But they're short episodes.
Okay, how long?
30 minutes.
Oh, okay.
(laughter)
That's cool.
You should get Tyga to direct some.
I wanted him to play the Rodian.
Oh.
Tyga Wittidi will play the Rodian
and then his stoner buddy played by Kevin Smith is just silent Bob. So
there's a so it's green bud and silent Bob and they're both stoners or one of
them just has a stone or buddy. No, they're both stoners. Okay, a few. I
okay. I hear my star wars idea. Yeah, it's called the 100 Jedis.
It's 100 episodes long.
There's 100
characters. It's an anthology show, so every episode is a completely different
story. Yeah, I've got to break the record for the most most people ever on a
poster for a TV show.
The trailer is a hundred minutes long, one minute from each episode. It's still
called a hundred Jedi.
We're going to have a probably a hundred is low balling it. We're probably going
a million people but you can't call it a season two. Yeah, the season two they
changed the title of the show to one million. I'm so excited. Yeah it's in
production. Yeah. Yeah we're looking we're working on finding the second
character. It's in a hundred productions. That's the hardest part about casting 100 Jedi's is like you do need to find 100 Jedi's.
like you can't just pick willy-nilly a hundred people. Yeah, he's already tied up.
He had a scheduling conflict. I actually wrote that part for willy-nilly. Maybe we
can get it for season two. I wrote it for willy-nilly but you know his
schedules really tied up so we just it's Michael Shannon and he's good
people say Michael Shannon is the poor man's really new people get him mixed up
all the time people always think that it was Michael Shannon in in the shape of
water but that was exactly the same he's really nearly just has shorter hair yeah
a little bit shorter and willy-nilly is like way more evil so he plays like evil
character but they're so hard to tell apart they even like the credits like
they'll get them mixed up so it's like Michael Shannon in all the movies so
like here's how you can tell willy-nilly and Michael Shannon apart so you look at
a photo of Michael Shannon and you open it up in Photoshop and then hit flip
horizontal and that's yeah he's pretty much like a black Michael Shannon
he wears he wears white makeup and yeah virtually indistinguishable but he is
black they need like a twin like they're casting a twin this guy's so good he
looks exactly like our lead actor he's perfect he is black yeah he they are
four different races. So yeah doing that for like a stunt scene,
it's like me a mission impossible or some yeah, there's just road. Yeah,
cruise like walking up to the edge of the skyscraper that it cuts and it's
just like a black guy. Just it's like a five hundred pound black
He's like, yeah, I did that. I do my own
That was my own stunt. I did that myself
Yeah, what's that that interview it's like him talking to Matt Lauer and he's like
Like is that the psychiatry one? Yeah. Yeah. He says like like what is he the exact quote is so sick
He's awesome. Dude. The exact quote is like something like like like you don't even you don't know
You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Yeah, that's what he says something about Ritalin -
Matt Lauer yeah and sick and like calls Matt Lauer a name yeah he's like unhinged
yeah he gets like mad at him. Dude, all the clips whenever he gets mad are so cool.
The one where um I forget who it is someone asked him about about Nicole
Kidman and he's like he just like keeps smiling he's like you're stepping over a
line here oh yeah I think you know it yeah and he's just so scary yeah and when
he jumps behind the couch on Oprah classic dude oh my god classic moment I
I only knew about like seeing the real clip of that after only seeing it in
Scary Movie 4 is so fucking it's way better in real life. I don't know if they've actually watched it.
I don't even know why they parodied that. They should have just played the clip in the movie.
What they do in Superhero Movie when they do it they get that guy that looks like him.
You know they did get a Tom Cruise impersonator. He's really good looks like him.
I don't remember a superhero movie.
Shout out to the casting team of Superhero Movie.
I remember seeing it, but it's one of those like...
I think it's on Amazon Prime right now.
I've seen probably every one of those Friedberg-Setzler movies.
I think it might be the Zucker Brothers.
Oh, that one's actually the Zuckers?
I think it's Zucker Brothers.
I could be wrong, but I think Superhero Movie might be the Zucks.
We should watch them all.
Yeah.
I'm down.
I've seen like... I remember because when I was a kid, I was like obsessed with those.
I like like I thought date movie was awesome epic movie epic movie.
Oh yeah, I heard they're making a new one right now that Disney's trying to shut down.
What?
100 Jedi's movie.
It's a parody of 100 Jedi's.
God, that's my dream.
I hear they're having an even harder time casting though.
Yeah.
Because it's like you have to cast like a hundred people.
I think you have to find an actor made of poop because it's one of the characters.
It's the main Jedi.
It's so funny dude.
One of the guys is made of poop.
I think the only one of those movies I ever saw was a scary movie.
Yeah, I made my, or I think we all went and saw a disaster movie in the theater.
Disaster movie is a weird one.
Seeing disaster movie in the theater when I was like 11, I was like the only one that
left like like that was awesome everyone else got in the car that's really funny
what it's that's maybe strange cuz that is just like a mad TV like showcase I
feel yeah everyone in that is it was on that TV yeah it's your over that movie
that came out when like Twilight was big vampire so I never saw that I remember
seeing like posters and stuff for that being like oh look out girls that was
the one that finally that was the straw that broke the camel's back yeah I never
watched another Friedberg sets or movie after I was like I remember going home
on Facebook and typing making my static my status vampire sucks dot dot dot
sucks. Whoa! That's pretty good. Too big a Twilight fan. Yeah. Yeah. What team are you?
Team Star Wars. You're stupid if you think that Star Wars is in Twilight. Okay I'm not
team Star Wars. I'm team Lord of the Rings. There's no, not a single Hobbit in
Twilight. Maybe they reference it though. There is a Hobbit in Twilight but it's in
the background. Yeah, you know, and if you miss it cameo there's a there's I mean
this hasn't been proven but if you look really closely in the background of one
of the shots and I think breaking dawn you can see a hobbit he is hanging
himself in the forest. Yeah, yeah. I don't remember if I saw Twilight or not. I
never saw those movies. No, I saw the first one and then I don't remember.
I didn't watch any of them either.
Yeah.
Gay.
Okay, well, speaking of Patrick being gay, here's a list I've selected for us today.
My top ten hottest animated guys.
Oh, hell yeah.
This is from a WordPress blog.
I'm not going to read the URL.
I'm going to have a lot of opinions on this.
This is a post from February 1st, 2013.
I might have made this list.
So a few days ago, Doug Walker, most famously known for the nostalgic critics.
You might have made this list.
I posted a list of his personal favorite attractive animated women after
viewing this video.
Yeah, my top 10.
It's top 10 hottest animated one.
Okay, we had an oopsie.
There was an oopsie there a quarter in out of space and it cut off and
we didn't notice for three minutes and in those three minutes.
We read the whole Doug Walker list.
We read the funniest list of all time.
Yeah, ever read on this show.
Hot is Doug Walker's list of hottest animated women.
It was really funny a gargoyle made it a appearance.
What if we just ran through the list real quick just like said the each one yeah, I guess we could just try try and but okay
We can do that do the impossible
I guess what everybody needs to know is that you are missing out all the hilarious jokes
We did about each one and the amount of laughs we had yeah, well
This is just gonna be like a quick like yeah about putting fingers and belly buttons. Yeah. Yeah, there was some stuff about that
Patrick made a very aggressive joke
that I won't yeah, because it kind of scared me on a team and yeah, that joke
was really number ten.
Jamaica from baby's kids
Patrick with that's why we know we did have the Jamaica from baby's kids was,
but I guess she's not a kid. I think it's the mom. I mean, I hope that's
actually double check. Yeah, what
joke I made about Jimmy
as a joke. I go back to this list. We should at least later in the list. Doug
Walker says that Jasmine and
Ariel are hotter than a certain Disney princess because they show their belly
buttons. Yeah. Well I can't is this that this isn't the mom right? Let me see.
There's no way this babe has kids. Or maybe you know it is the mom probably.
That's the mom. Yeah. Damn.
(Laughter)
God damn.
Okay. Okay.
I see you Doug.
I see you Doug. Alright.
Alright brother. Number 9 was
Annie Hughes from the Iron Giant.
Yeah. Milk. I don't remember what she looks like.
Well Doug Walker says the main
reason is because she's voiced by Jennifer Aniston.
Oh. Oh.
She has a sexy voice. That's a weird reason
to be like you know yeah that's a weird reason to be like this character is hot
because the voice actor is beautiful what are you talking about look at those eyes
he looks exactly like like number one mm-hmm she's almost exactly like I love
her hair number his number eight was April O'Neil mm-hmm
no qualms with that one no argument there my only qualms she's not higher up
Yeah, I mean you guys like her cuz she's like 15
So Peter so is Peter Parker well, he's 12
Takes place by Judith Hogue in the movie. Yeah. Yeah. Well, she was 12. She's a woman
Trust she was seven. She's not she wouldn't be hanging out with them turtles if she wasn't
Look, I know I know turn off the recorder cuz he said a lot of stuff. Yeah
That's probably when we went one dark
look. Cameron shut off the recorders and be like look. I would do and then yeah.
Number seven was Harley Quinn. He's you know a little crazy. I thought that Harley should
be higher up on the list. She got BPD. Yeah, do you realize also she's dating the Joker.
She's not going to get with you. She's not going to get with you. She actually has sex
with Nightwing in the new show. Oh yeah, I saw that clip on a certain website. I've
seen that scene. No, I saw that because it was one of those things where it's like
it recommends you to me tweets and stuff and it was like a tweet where someone's
complaining. It's like because they were like um Harley Quinn rapes Nightwing in
the new show and as a clip of it. Yeah, yeah it's a clip where he's tied up. Mm-hmm
Yeah, yeah, so what do you have to say about that? I don't think that's funny
at all. So I mean, but you still think Harley Quinn should be higher on the
list? Yeah, okay. Number six was was
demote
which I mean demote as gargoyles go. She's pretty hot, but she's
Demona of every cartoon character in the world. I mean it's just such a
beautiful name above directly above April O'Neil and Harley Quinn Demona
because she can kick ass like yeah
number five was
oh my God, I forgot the lady from the we went back to Alice Topkins from the
creek.
What's his reasoning? Does it have literally nothing? It doesn't even say
where she's from it says i'll read you what it says here. Doug vio number
five alice tompkins interlude
that's all it says
okay yeah number four was tiana from the princess and the frog very funny to put
a put a couple sisters on the list. Oh yeah, you like disney princesses,
that's funny, that's very funny, and watching a disney movie like oh my god,
Also, like, you're...
Wow!
I guess I don't know that much about Doug Walker, but to do a top ten hottest animated women
and none of it is sexy anime girls...
Those anime girls are hot.
They're sexy as fuck.
Let's say one, let's get one thing straight.
They are hot.
They are beautiful.
Beautiful
Some from Kingdom Hearts she was so hot yeah, or like
Misty from Pokemon what the hell do that's a 12-year-old
No, dude, she was 30
Mrs. Parr from the Incredibles listen was number three then number two was rogue from x-men
interesting and number one was and I'll read this out like I did last time and
Doug vo and my number one hottest animated woman is Bell. Now this is
really ironic because in the Nostalgia Critics top 11 I said Bell didn't
qualify because you had Ariel and Jasmine and they showed their belly
buttons. Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute. Okay, is this list Doug
Walker's top 10 or is it the Nostalgia Critics top 10 because that really
changes kind of every single that is a
Okay, it looks like this one is this one is Doug's top ten hottest animated women
And then there's also a link where there's a separate top 11 animated nostalgia hot. That's the stulture critic
He'd be doing those top 11s. Yeah, cuz it goes to 11. Yeah, so that's how you know
Well, let's see what his top is the top 11
linka from Captain Planet
(laughter)
- To have another list that's a bunch of just
different cartoon characters.
(laughter)
- The Baroness from G.I. Joe.
- Wait, so he had a list.
- Joe sent a list with completely different characters.
(laughter)
- I do, okay, I do respect--
- Okay, here we go, number nine, Sailor Moon.
- Oh, there we go.
- From Sailor Moon.
I do respect Doug Walker for being like, "No, my character would think Demonia is hot."
Wait, here's one.
This is a line from the transcript of Nostalgia Critic's Top 10 Animated Nostalgia Hotties.
After Sailor Moon says, "Nostalgia Critic, as an evil monster."
"Alright, Sailor Moon, I'm a big bad monster. What are you going to do about it?"
Oh my god, dude.
Number 8, Harley Quinn.
Harley Quinn's back on here.
From Batman.
Crossover.
Yep.
And then we got number 7, Hello Nurse from Animaniacs.
Number 6, Chitara from Thundercats.
Number 5, Daphne from Scooby-Doo.
Hell yeah, that's my girl.
Number four April O'Neil, okay
Okay number
Three rogue from x-men okay a little bit of a little bit repetitive. Let's try and
So they're trying their tastes align here. We go number two Ariel and Jasmine Wow oh
Here's we go. Yeah. Yeah, this is a belly, but here's here here. I'll just read out this this quote from him, okay
It's hard to choose which one of these two beauties was sexier, so I just gave them both their own number two spot
I mean these two hotties make Barbie look like Betty Crocker with their big wide eyes and soft curvy lines
There's no doubt that Disney knew how to make our dreams come true now a lot of you might be wondering
Why didn't I put Belle on there? Well? It's not that she wasn't beautiful smart and a well-developed character. It's just that well
She didn't show her navel ah
He's about that belly but loves that belly, but what about Pocahontas is Pocahontas show her belly button. He does what's up?
No, actually she doesn't does she not I don't know maybe those a deleted scene that I saw any guesses for number one
Dexter's mom
Mrs. Incredible is charity on the list. It's mrs. Puff. No, I'm just kidding. No
It's an obvious one. It's Jessica rabbit. Ah, yeah. Yeah. Actually, I remember this video now me too
I remember every sinister critic video I've ever seen
Okay, now that we've got the background of I can go back to
back to to the original pick for the list my top ten hottest animated guys,
which it's after viewing this video. My boyfriend issued me a challenge to
write up a list of my own, but with men so long story short, these are my
picks for animated. Here we go time for the time for the any guesses for any
let's let's play some bets on number one. I haven't looked at number one
get sora sora. No, I think lumiere for beauty of the beast. Yeah, flounder not
everybody got your what y'all flounder flounder under the little mermaid. Oh my
God, we is on get real. Oh my God, the care that all the little care of little
the little characters from clay world
from pancake mines,
probably like guest on yeah
okay, number ten was Jafar.
Are you evil, though? Yeah, well yeah, let's listen. Let's let's hear this
person out. I'll get this out of the way. Jafar is a douche.
Thank God she said that.
Well what do you expect from a villain as powerful as him?
While not the most attractive Disney villain out there,
Jafar has this smugness about him that I really like.
He's powerful and he knows it.
And he's always got a scheme cooked up.
He's got power, he's got money too.
He does have a lot of money.
Plus his evil laugh is one of the best I've ever heard.
He might look like he was beat with an ugly stick,
but he's easily the most attractive Disney villain to me.
to me. He's beaten by the ugly stick but he's the most attractive. Yeah, well this person's
maybe a little crazy and weird. Yeah, they got interest, they got strange tastes, it sounds like.
Yeah, I mean Jafar does, he does seem powerful. Hey, Jafar got like some flow.
Like getting like choked out by Jafar. Oh my god. What? Getting like, oh this Jafar is like,
you know, like just crushing your carotid artery. He's trying to smell some of his Jafarts. Oh my god.
missionary with Jafar
dude going is poised has his rope pulled up. He's holding it up going on a
mission with Jafar
dude when I'm about to bust in Jafari switches a genie form and flips me over
damn
yeah, I would love to have sex with a genie
Me too.
Yeah, that actually would be fire.
My next wish, last longer.
That was good.
That's really good, man.
Yeah, you can't wish for more wishes to bring people back to life or to last longer.
That's what he says.
I don't even want it.
I don't want any of it.
Yeah, that would be so rude if you're having sex with a genie and you're trying to grant
your wishes in the middle of it.
I wish you would not already a
number nine any guesses
piccolo
it's frozen from the incredible. Okay, okay, yeah, even though he's a
supporting character frozen is one of my favorites from the Incredibles for
starters. He has a sleek design which works perfectly with the ice powers. He
yeah his skin is so sleek. There's something so cool about frozen.
This is an
urban chill. Yeah, something chill yeah yeah, I think of like like ice crystals.
Look at him. He's like a black crystal
something about his ice makes me think of sparkling jewelry. Yeah, it's like
black ice on the sidewalk.
(laughing)
- Something about him makes me think of a sidewalk.
He's the kind of down to earth guy that while he enjoys
doing the superhero thing, enjoys having a bit of normalcy,
at least more than Mr. Incredible.
- Yeah, Mr. Incredible is having a midlife crisis.
- Yeah, and to top it all off, he's voiced by Samuel L. Jackson
who has one of the most recognizable and in my opinion,
attractive voices out there.
Okay, all right. I guess that yeah, this girl likes some tall dark and handsome. I think we're noticing a theme and ice power
Either genie or ice powers. Yeah, you could wish like you could be like genie. I wish you had ice
I'm looking for a guy with a sleek design and ice powers
I fucking hate like on tinder you go people are like I need a guy who's over six feet and that B is able to control
It's like, oh my god.
It's a shallowness of women.
Women only like guys with sleek designs.
It is.
And basically all of us guys with big robot arms don't get any attention.
It's hard to me, people are, like girls our age just only want guys with powers.
It's really, uh.
Yeah, I mean a guy like me, who's like, I look more like Bebop and Rocksteady.
Yeah, good luck.
Yeah.
Good fucking luck, dude.
I know.
Oh my god.
She's looking for more of a Pleakley type.
Looking for a Pleakley type.
Looking for something.
(laughter)
- Looking for a pleat cleat type.
- Looking for someone who looks exactly like a pleat cleat.
- She wants like a Gazzorno type,
which is actually a character I just created.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
- What does he look like?
- Let's describe Gazzorno real quick.
- He's 700 feet tall.
(laughter)
And he's invisible.
He's completely transparent.
- Number eight is, I don't know,
I've never heard of this guy.
I don't know if you guys have.
Martin Mystery.
- Oh!
- From Martin Mysteries.
- I'm always telling jokes about that show.
Martin Mysteries was like a show on like Nicktoons.
And I feel like I was the only one who watched that
when I was a kid, but it's like,
he's like a blonde guy with like fire.
- Yeah, that's what it looks like here.
- Yeah, that show rocked.
- It says, "Many people won't know this guy,
"but I first discovered him on a kid's channel called YTV,
"essentially the Nickelodeon of Canadian programming.
"While Tuxedo Mask from Sailor Moon
"was the first anime guy I ever saw,
Martin was the first I ever found remotely attractive. He has boyish good
looks and a lot of energy and spunk. He does. He's not the brightest character in
the show but he's extremely loyal to his friends and sister and has a fun sense
of humor as well. He's the one the show is named after. Martin Mystery. That show
was so cool. They would like, it was like a supernatural, it was like a
like a spin, it was like a Scooby-Doo kind of thing.
But they all had powers? No, they were just, it was like him and then I think I
guess the girl was his sister and then like a
caveman that they found and they would go on like adventures together it was really cool
and it was all like ghosts.
How does a caveman fit into it?
Or he was like a descendant of a caveman or some shit I don't know.
I think we all are.
No it was different.
Not me, not me.
I came from angels.
I'm a descendant from a fish actually.
I have a lot of neanderthal DNA.
Yeah.
We talked about it.
Yeah?
Yeah I think I'm like 56th percentile.
I'm 50th percentile for angel and 50th for demon.
Yo, I wouldn't I would keep the demon part. I would keep my hush hush on that
I don't let I wouldn't broadcast that just cuz you never know who's listening. Okay good point. That's actually a really good point
Trying to number as a friend number seven is Milo from Atlantis the Lost Empire. Yeah
Yeah, Milo has all the qualities about nerdy guys that I love. Yep. He's a little bit awkward, which is adorable
He's intelligent and knowledgeable, which is always a plus and he's also got a good sense of humor as well
Another thing I loved about the character was his drive and determination to find Atlantis.
*laughter*
Couple
I'm fucking I I say that no girl wants anything to do with me
Bullshit
I'm meeting guys
I'm meeting guys who are determined to find a man to say
You're on a first date
Like oh what do you do? What's like your goal in life?
Oh I'm determined
- You're a hermit.
- You're like, I just wanna find Atlantis.
- Annoyed at your girlfriend, I'm trying to find Atlantis.
- Oh my God. - Yeah, yeah you are.
- Can you please like take out the trash, excuse me!
- This is my me time. - Will you get this?
- This is the time I try and pinpoint
the location of Atlantis, okay?
I get home from work, I wanna crack a beer,
I wanna unwind, I wanna sit in my armchair,
and I wanna scan the earth with my GPS device.
- Where are you?
where is your girlfriend's calling you're supposed to be home like three
hours ago and it's like i'm in the middle of the atlantic yeah, oh wait,
what time was dinner with your parents
a little
and he falls in love with an atlantean that could actually write it.
Wait a second an animated movie, but a guy is driven to find land Disney
Okay, we actually have the Atlantis VHS in our oh yeah, I thought that movie was pretty cool
I liked it when I was a kid. Yeah, I only saw one time
I think I feel like most movies I watched when I was a kid
I saw like ten times in that movie, but that Michael J. Fox is is Milo
Which is right here Atlantis and treasure planet. Yeah, oh you know I might be confusing them right now
I think I might be thinking about Treasure Planet.
Treasure Planet was cool.
That's JGL. Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Oh my god.
What happens in that one? They go to a planet?
Yeah.
That's pretty sick.
I don't remember anything about it.
That was like, they, um, it was like
yeah, it was 2D animation
and 3D animation.
Bit of a blend.
Yeah, because there's that little pink guy, little fucker.
Oh yeah, the bubble guy.
This guy was bubble fuck bubble fuck bubble fuck the pink clown and then the
crazy robot that they find do you that guy's awesome is funny number six
Batman Wow from Batman the animated series where do I start with this Batman
for one he's cool and smart like any Batman should be he has the great
ear-catching voice of Kevin Conroy which gives the character a lot of weight in
both humorous and dramatic situations and of course it's Batman one of the
coolest superheroes ever put on screen from his great gadgets to as many layers
as a person for me, though this Batman was also who got me into comic book
heroes. Well, he's not my favorite superhero. We'll get to that. He
definitely left an impact.
That's kind of a boring pick. Yeah, but I get it. You know, I like this person. I
like whoever wrote this lister given us a really good reasons for the well
number five. I'm really curious to hear the reason this one's kind of a curve
ball. I think ready. The number five is sideshow Bob.
What
Wait a minute, for real?
He's not good, dude.
Neither was Jafar.
I think Saijobob is more evil than Jafar, though.
God, Jafar is evil too.
I know, I know, this is a weird choice, especially coming ahead of Batman.
But the thing is, I'm a huge Simpsons fan.
Compared to the Batman show, I grew up with the Simpsons through most of my childhood.
Saijobob, to me, was one of the most attractive characters to appear in that show.
(laughter)
- Women love to be attracted to a weird looking guy.
- I love his obsession and devotion to trying to kill Bart
and how many plans he'll try to accomplish that.
I love how despite having been a clown,
he's always been sophisticated
with his taste in literature and music.
- It's true, he's an artful clown.
- Yeah, she really likes obsession and devotion.
- It's like when women say they're attracted
to friggin' Nathan Fielder, pretty much.
- That's an even better rom-com,
is like, "Honey, where are you?
You're supposed to meet my parents tonight."
my parents and I'm so I have to kill kill out killing by my nemesis
I'm trying to kill Bart Simpson. It's my weekend. I'm trying to kill Bart
number four. I don't know who this is neuro from Majin Tante Nugami neuro. I
know that oh that's me yeah. We can just move on from that. If you've read my
first blog post, you'll know this is a recent one. I only saw the show last
month, but neuro left such an impression that I couldn't leave him on the list
the list. While Bob is obsessed with killing Bart, he always gets caught in the end. Nero's
obsession with feeding off of mysteries always ends in triumph. He never ever gives up until
he gets what he wants. Physically, his human form is pretty attractive, sort of like a
demonic mixed version of Miles Edgeworth and Phoenix Wright from the Ace Attorney series.
While he doesn't understand humans, he's the kind of demon whose presence and voice
commands attention, and his demonic powers are truly awesome.
So she got you got them like the guy who's winning and then like you got the guy who's like, you know taking the L's
So I think the ladies are always gonna go for the guy who's got taking the W's and that's just a little something about the female
Species. Yeah, they also prefer guys with demonic powers. You can get demonic powers
That's all about powers obsession devotion and your equal era
obsession
True. Oh my God. I love having an obsession. Yeah, me too. Yeah
Number three is
Wolverine from x-men evolution, okay, I'll be honest
I never grew up with the original and 90s x-men cartoon
But I did come across this one later in life and enjoyed it immensely
This is the guy Batman led me to a surly burly Canadian mutant with the no-nonsense attitude
Yeah, Wolverine already ranks high on my favorite superheroes list but between this show in the first live-action film
I came to see him as attractive - yeah aside from the quick traits just listed
I think another aspect is the mystery behind him while he may not always be a team player
He's definitely my favorite x-men guy of the bunch. Yeah, mine is Nightcrawler. Yeah from x-men evolutions
Still nightcrawler. I think beast
What was x-men evolution that was that the Disney one that that was x-men evolutions was yes
I believe it was on Disney. Like the newer one? Yeah, that's the one
They sold all the they had all the toys at Burger King
Yeah, they all and I had I think I had most of them growing up. Yeah, I think yeah. Oh my god
That's cool. You know cuz Batman is for you know, it's a little bit of like oh, there's a bit of mystery
You know, I'm attracted to the mystery and no mystery. No mystery. It's like this guy is dirty. This guy is a
Yes
Giant like metal bones giant like razor-sharp claws violence. Yeah. Yeah
experimented on
Dark past trauma PTSD. He could wake up in the middle of the night and stab you to death exactly doesn't doesn't know his friends from
his foes
From time to time against a Magneto countless times fought the Hulk in a comic only survivor
driver. Oh wait, that was dead pool. No he fought the wolverine everybody
thought everybody I'm sure he fought him at some point over in planet or old
man Logan
he fights the whole
does he actually I think the I forget, but like the United States is like
chopped up into four different Wolverine chopped up the United States.
has on stops for different factions and I think the Hulk owns like the Hulk turns
evil. Are you serious? Yes, I think owns the Hulk is like a control of like I
forget what he's like the president or he just like owns them. He's like the
president of like the West Coast. I think it all damn. That's pretty sick.
Old Man Logan is sick.
Old Man Logan.
Is that the one that they based that movie on?
Yeah.
Does that have President Hulk in it?
I mean look up if he's the president.
I should check that out.
That does sound cool.
I liked Logan.
I thought that movie was funny.
I never saw that one.
Logan is sick.
Yeah.
That's good.
I should watch it.
Yeah.
That was the year of two Calabans.
What was the other one?
It was Stephen Merchant and then some other guy in X-Men Apocalypse.
then in old old man Logan Caliban is just like a wimp. He's like a wimp in Logan I
think. Or I mean no no I mean in Logan he's a wimp. Oh yeah yeah. And then in X-Men
Apocalypse he's like he's like played like the Nightman. I don't remember.
He's like like you're trying to find a mutant. Oh wait yeah I kind of remember a little bit.
Apocalypse is on with Oscar eyes. Yeah, and he looks like Ivan ooze. He looks awesome. Yeah, he looks so funny
he looks like
He should be he looks like he should be in in freakin the fifth element
Yes, yep. Yes all his blue skin and a strange apparatus everything you're saying yes words out of my mouth. Yes
Yeah, sorry this turned into a bit of a sci-fi nerd corner nerding out right now a few references
Might not understand what we're talking about
about right now. That's okay. Yeah, so it belonged to Obama Nation and then the
Hulk conquered it and now the Hulk owns that. Wait, so half of it was Obama's Nation.
Obama versus the Hulk. Yeah. Oh, and then Red Skull is president of the United States. Oh my god.
That's, I mean, that is, that's scary as fuck. That's satirical. I mean, we basically had
orange skull. Oh my god. Yeah. Wow. Yeah. Yeah. Is that Nazi? Yeah, pretty much dude. Super
fragile, callous, racist, sexist, Nazi POTUS. Who's that? I thought I saw an animal. It was
just a bird. I guess a bird's an animal. Hey man, respect nature. I thought it could be
a werewolf or a donio. I'm afraid of birds. Beast. Oh my god, I shouldn't even mention
and all right, who's number two number two, Aladdin from yeah, Aladdin's
mystery. I don't have anything. This one goes back into my childhood of all
the Disney man. I saw throughout my life. Aladdin was easily the most
interesting. He wasn't just another rich prince looking for a princess, but
instead a humble street boy just trying to get by yeah, street boy. He knows
how to handle himself in a fight for the most part and has this sense of
discovery and adventure about him. Of course, physically he's both handsome and
cute, jumping between trying to act suave and being a little awkward at times.
While he pretty much has self-esteem issues, he's the kind of guy whose heart's
in the right place. If my number one pick never existed, Aladdin would have easily
nabbed the top spot of this list.
Yeah, yeah. I'm excited to see who number one is. Aladdin's pretty, yeah, across
the board, you know. He's got, he's a good guy. He's got those, those, that's
got a sense of discovery.
Sense of discovery. He's ambitious. He wants to marry Jasmine.
He dresses like a slut.
Yeah he is a slut.
He shows his belly button.
That vest, oh my god.
Oh my god dude, he is such a slut.
That little, that fez.
He's such a slut dude.
Oh my god, those pants.
Dude, but I have to say.
You know why they're so big at the bottom?
They're holding his balls.
Yeah, Aladdin's sexy, but I have to say, I'm more into his friend.
Fijini?
Abu.
His friend.
Oh my god.
Oh man, Abu.
Little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little,
little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little, little,
his friend. Fugenie? Abu? His friend? Oh my god. Oh man, Abu. Little, little, little thing.
Little ball of sexiness. I'm sorry New York for the monkey pox outbreak. This was all
It's all my fault. I was masturbating to a picture of Abu.
It's all my fault. Just go into an urgent care and start saving.
Abu did have that like sexy attitude though.
I mean I won't say like his body was hot but you have to admit like.
That's true.
The way he acted.
Yeah, he's number one.
Alright, come on we need a few guesses here for number one.
going up a little at a very serious
the
what
uh... all you want to do you want to have to get three d animation track
i don't know i guess
and shut up
uh...
three d
recent movie
uh...
not that reason uh... is it the once alert
no it's not the one
that's a pretty good guess though
that is a good guess
is it max from horton hears a who?
no it's not let me tell you what year this movie came out let me look it up
this movie came out in twenty ten
it's uh...
don't look
and it was a disney movie
3d animation is it one of the robinsons from meet the robinsons?
is it? no
i don't know
is it buzz?
no lots of cities and he's a grown-up and it's based on a fairy tale
this move all of us the guy from tangled yes the guy from uh...
i would tell you about the wind rider with a sexy as there was a
when i went to uh... i've i've visited like one of my friends from high school
and college yeah any took like this guy
took us to this lake he was like all we go play smash in my friend's room while
he's out of the party and i was like
What do you mean? He's like, yeah, he lets me go in his room and play smash.
And then like we were all really high and it got quiet.
And he's like, have you ever seen the girl from Tangled?
She's so hot.
Thinking that a cartoon character is like really hot is so funny to me.
That is like hilarious because like most of the characters that people think are
hot or even that even that are hot.
It's you look at it.
It's like it's little it's like a it's a draw.
It's like there's like three lines for a face. Yeah, like it's not how do you look at that and you like get a boner?
What is going on in the human brain?
There was somebody in in middle school and I know I realized this now that it was made up
but for the longest time I thought this was a real like
Excuse me scientific term
There's a some kid on the bus told me that
The word for being attracted to car to like like a cartoon character is called dumb. Oh sexual
Domosexual Dumbo Dumbo's like Dumbo Dumbo Dumbo should have been yeah it
sounds like you're attracted to Dumbo yeah well yeah that's the list go to
this weekend hey if you're if you're listening this right now it's in two and
three days uh-huh I'll be in Brooklyn be it life world in Brooklyn Alex will be
there. Alex will be there. Swagpoop.com/shows. You can buy some tickets.
Nope, never mind. I was gonna say on Friday Alex has a show but we also have a
show. Don't go to that one. Go to our show on Friday. And watch Home Planet's videos of course.
And also we're doing a show in Portland, Seattle. You should go to those.
Oregon. You're gonna like those. Those are our last live shows ever so you're
gonna want to make it out to those. Also watch Disney cartoons, any cartoons, write
about the characters that you find attractive. Send it in.
Let me know, DM me. I'd love to see what you guys think.
Send us your list of sexiest...
Send Patrick your list of sexiest animated characters.
the list of the sexiest women in movies. Not drawn. Not drawn. Okay. Well you can
send us, you can send me the drawings if you want. If you, if anyone listening
might create an original character and they want to know if it's hot or not,
just send it to me. Send us the hottest, your list of the hottest men in my
neighborhood. Yeah. Alright. Bye everybody.