Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
♪ Dance on table tops ♪
♪ And we took too many shots ♪
♪ And we danced on table tops ♪
♪ Last Friday night ♪
♪ Is off 'cause I'm off of work ♪
♪ And I'm going back to church ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm ♪
♪ It's Sunday morning ♪
- It's Sunday morning. - That would be incredible.
- Oh my God. - Maybe a good parody.
- Last Sunday morning, we got down onto our knees.
- Yes. - Put our hands together, please.
- Yeah, he died upon the cross,
and when he died, we all were lost.
Before he died, we all were lost.
Put him in a coffin box, the death of Christ.
In the Sunday morning fog, he was singing to a frog.
Which I think is in the Bible.
And he got killed by those Wops.
That last Friday night,
'cause it was the Italians that killed him, right?
And because he did turn into a man after the prince,
after Mary Magdalene. He was a boy.
Mary Magdalene found a frog that had a cane and a top hat.
He was running around. Oh, a cane.
Cane like a boy. Cane and a hat.
Cane like a boy. Cane and then Jesus,
he was a frog who was disabled.
And he was running around. Yeah.
He was running around, "Hello, my baby.
"Hello, my darling.
"Hello, my ragtime gal."
He gave him a kiss, right?
All of a sudden. Gave him a kiss
and then bam.
he said, "I'm gonna become a prince." He said, "Give me a kiss and I'll turn into a prince."
She didn't realize, prince of princes. Wow. King of kings. Lord of lords. Sunday of Sundays.
Sunday of Sundays. Back in that time, like back in Christ's era. Yeah, what year? Year
1. Do you think they had schizophrenia back then? Probably not, because there wasn't phones
in technology. Yeah, there was no doctors to say that. Yeah, they didn't have
anything. Yeah, they had either bad blood or you have something in you.
They would just be like something is different about you. Yeah, something is
happening to you, but it's not a thing. Yeah, they really didn't know what to say.
I guess that was all just like back then. You would go. That's what you would go to
it. You go to a healer, not a doctor. You go to a healer. You would go to the
doctor and you say, I broke my foot or I'm sick and they'd be like, well, why are
you telling me? I don't know what to do. They haven't invented anything. Yeah,
Well no, what happened is you'd go and you'd be like, "I have a fever and
there's snot coming out of my nose and I just want to sleep all the time."
And then you go. They would say, "Well, something's clearly wrong with you, but it's not a thing or
anything." Yeah. There's not like a thing out of this.
Why are you telling me all these things together? Do you think, exactly, I don't know what to tell you?
Like, sorry? You used to go to a doctor and you'd say, "I have
this happening to me. This is happening to me." And they'd say, "I'm sorry." Yeah.
what that's what the Hippocratic Oath is. That was what doctors did until like
1950. They were just people that you'd go to and they'd be like I'm so
sorry that's happened. Yeah something that's really really awful. And then they'd
prescribe you fricking butter. And then okay the bill a hundred coins. And then for a while, dude I hate
a hundred coins. Your wife and man that was a lot of money. Yeah coins have gone way way
down in price. Yeah. They used to be worth a lot of money and then at one point I
think the first thing they invented was putting a hole in a woman's head because
she got too angry about something.
- Yeah.
- They used to just prescribe women a vibrator
and say, "Hey, you need to go calm down."
- They used to prescribe women--
- You're being hysterical.
- They used to prescribe women a guy named the vibrator.
- Yeah.
- There's old ads you can look up.
It's like, it's literally, it's for stuff that's like,
to treat hysteria.
They used to just make women ride the Sibian, basically.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Which Howard Stern is probably the closest thing we have--
- To a doctor.
doc to a 1901 doctor yeah yeah never met one for real it is it's so awesome to
like a woman right a simian yeah that I monkey there is a picture that somebody
got yelled at for posting once something I yelled at so yeah Patrick yelled at
him cuz he was he's got scared yeah scared yeah picture that someone got
yelled at for posting once what does that mean is like a group chat where he
would send pictures of apes and stuff and somebody sent of a picture of a chimp
competing a woman out. Really? Yeah. It's amazing how much video and photo there is
online of people having sex with animals. Yeah. It really pops up in crazy places.
It just comes up. It just comes up. It's that whole fucking that lady. Yeah, just
as on Twitter and stuff. When? A couple of weeks ago. You never saw that one?
Yeah. I saw it and I was like and I saw the set up and it was like a woman and a
dog on a bed. I was like, oh, it's a camera trick. Yeah, there's no way that
there it's for perspective. It's like the Lord of the Rings running away from
that the dog is actually really far away from running away from that video like
you're the one of the first people to see train arriving at the station. Yeah,
like I was like there's no way that this is what's actually happening. This is
gonna be some kind of joke. I'm gonna yeah vine style thing and then it cuts
to the they're doing that the like worst angle and porn thing of behind the guy's
butthole and you see his balls, but instead it was a dog's asshole and he's
talking her inner yeah I like that angle I didn't I didn't like it best angle I
think I finally best angle in porn I love seeing which was just that angle yeah but
I just can't I can't believe it shouldn't that shouldn't you be in jail
for posting that yeah it does seem it does seem like there should be like a
thing that you're not allowed yeah exactly I guess yeah I feel like bestiality and CP
laws should be the same you you think that there should be more CP on Twitter
No, yeah, cuz you're right cuz video of somebody
Fucking a dog you should get penalized the exact same as like I kind of agree. It's a freaking woman getting penalized by the dog
For the crime of being penalized by a dog you will be penalized you have been sentenced to having sex with a human man
Oh
You will be penalized by a man
- Yeah.
- Aw.
- Woohoo!
(laughing)
- Dough.
- Marge, I don't wanna be penalized by a man.
- You gotta be penalized by a man, homie.
- I don't want to.
- It's the punishment.
- He's too similar to me.
(laughing)
- I want a dog, Homer.
Homer, I want a dog.
- Homer.
- Marger.
(laughing)
- Marber.
- Barty.
- Dough, I want a donut.
(laughing)
Woohoo!
- Dough.
- Woohoo, I want a donut.
- That's just no.
sounds more like Selma. Mo is kind of Homer and Marge. He's a complete double.
Is that what you call it? He's a mixture. He's a full name because he's a hybrid.
Wait a second yeah Marge Homer. Mo, Homer, oh my god he literally is a hybrid
Momer Harge. He is a Momer Harge because her last name is Marge and his last name
used to be Bouvier. What? Marge Bouvier. Beveridge. Marge's Boobies Ye. That's what I say. When
I see Marge I say. Take some letters out of that. When I see that playboy script. Let
me see Marge's Boobies Ye. Bouvier take some letters out of that it spells bar. True. Moe's
bar. Oh shit. What's Moe's tavern? It's an er at the end so it says burr. That's how
you spell bar. Burr. Burr. Isn't it called Burr's Tavern? Gucci Mane was on the Simpsons.
No he wasn't. A tavern is a bar. Is he? Okay let's not get. I don't think Gucci Mane was
on the Simpsons was he he was on Simpson find me dot com that's what I saw that
was that count yeah I just found out my whole family on Facebook was on the
Simpsons how the fuck did you guys get on the Simpsons and Rick and Morty -
holy shit and South Park holy crap my uncle was on South Park look and you're
hanging out with these dancing elves on jib jabs oh my god my uncle is a fox
having sex with another fox. What's that? I was on his DeviantArt account. Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah. Me and Pat came up with some new vines earlier. Oh yeah. Yeah, well we came up with one.
One, because Caleb's. Which is, here's what the vine would be. Yeah. It would be like,
it would be me, we need to bring vines back and come up with new vines. It would be me and I'm
sitting at the coffee shop and I say, "One hot coffee please." Right? And then I get my coffee
and I walk out and then Pat is sitting at the entrance and he's holding the weather app on
his phone. What do you say? Says he's drinking a hot coffee in the hot summer. Make it make sense.
I like that a lot. I think it's a good idea. I have a suggestion. He's drinking a hot coffee
in the hot summer. The thing about that is it's so easily faked that I think that um...
What do you mean? Just to make it just so people that people...
They can make him say whatever they want. Just so people really will connect with it on a deeper
level I think maybe you add kind of an establishing shot at the beginning when
you're kind of ordering your coffee or whatever than usual you have taken a
super shower up there it's a you should it shows the thermometer it's not the
weather it shows like their mom very thermo like a mercury thermometer and
it's rising up and it's got all going to like a hundred and twenty degrees so we
can film this after this yeah we can go film it and post it but there's gonna be
basically a video I'm gonna be leaving a coffee shop and Patrick will say he's
He just ordered a hot coffee.
In the hot summer.
Yeah, in the hot summer.
Make it make sense.
And then do a flip.
And then maybe I could get like knockout gamed or something.
Yeah, they take the hot coffee.
If you could do a, wouldn't it be so awesome if you could do a flat ground backflip because
that is the perfect ending to any video.
Is like if somebody's filming you, you just do a backflip.
If you get in a car accident with somebody and they start filming you because they like
need this car insurance thing. If you say if you're yelling at them, I didn't rear
end you as soon as you see that camera. Yeah, this is bust out a backflip.
You're going to be a legend. Also like yeah, you you're trying to try to
shoplift something right you read you put a candy bar in your pocket. You look
up you notice a security camera. Oh shit backflip. Have you seen that video
rating your you're getting swatted right? Yeah, if there's a SWAT video of
them busting in your door and you see them and just instantly do a backflip,
They won't shoot you. You're going to Cirque du Soleil. Have you seen that video?
It's like some comedian posted it. I forget who, but they... I don't follow comedians. It's like a
video of like the performers at Harry Potter World ending and they go up in the like in the front of
the crowd and do a backflip and walk back into the crowd. That's sick. It's so fucking funny. Yeah,
see like I if I could do a backflip... That one and then the other one there's a different guy. I
- There's a different guy.
- He's actively trying to get--
- There's this guy in Philly,
and his thing is he goes into stores and stuff,
and while people are behind him,
he just does a back flip.
He goes like, "What?"
while he does the back flip.
So there's a video of a guy at the counter,
and he's arguing with the owner of the store,
and he goes in and starts pulling bags of ice
out of the freezer,
and then just fully does a back flip.
- Oh yeah, that is a funny video.
- That is a really good one.
I think I would probably try, it would be like, for me, I would want to do like, "Maskless
Karen harasses store clerk for not pulling down mask and then does perfect back flip before
leaving."
Maskless Karen, but they don't realize you are wearing a mask, but it's one of those
Obama masks that you are banked with.
Or it's a Karen mask.
It's a Karen mask.
Oh shit, yeah.
But just the idea of, maybe I'm a maskless Karen, I'm yelling like, "Take that mask off!
What, it's not going to kill you?
What are you, a pussy or something?"
Watch this.
flip in the middle of it and keep yelling at them and then pretend it didn't
happen. Why'd you backflip? What are you even talking about? You're crazy.
See if you could just do perfect backflips with no fatigue and you could
backflip like a hundred times in a row. A really similar thing to that that I
would really like to be able to do is complete hands-free vomit. Yeah
definitely. That's another perfect video thing. In the store just hands-free nutting.
People say, oh I can, I wish I could vomit.
But that would get you sent to jail.
That's the problem with that one.
I wish I could vomit on command.
You can vomit on command, but it's obvious there's a lead up.
Yeah, you have to like, you can, yeah.
You have to like try, like I can make myself vomit at any point in time.
Yeah.
But I gotta try.
Exactly.
I wanna be instantly no provocation.
Yeah.
And not even, I wanna something I can, I do it with a thought.
No heaving, no lurching.
My brother, yeah.
I'm just, vomit is spewing out of my mouth.
My brother used to have acid reflux so bad that he could just make himself spit up on
command.
That used to happen to me every morning.
I can kind of do that.
He would kind of like, he would do that after he ate like fucking Jeff Goldblum in the fly.
He'd sit there and go like, and then just like, so crazy.
Acid reflux sucks.
It will ruin your life.
I've been getting it really, really bad.
Two years for me.
Me too.
Remember that, remember we went to New York for the first time and I was taking Prilosec
And I literally like, I was like anxious all the fucking time because I had that allergic
reaction.
I was like covered in hives and I just like, my heart rate was up fucking crazy.
And then what did you decide to do?
I smoked a joint.
And I got-
Smoked a stranger's fucking dope.
It wasn't a stranger, it was my friend Marion Zoe's.
It was strange dope.
It was my friend Marion Zoe's.
He was their weed.
Who's Marion Zoe's?
Nah, I'm playing.
Hmm. I'm playing yeah, I smoked one hit of their spliff and I freaked the fuck out
Yeah, cuz you know what you know the worst thing that front the worst part is he's right in front of a fucking eatily
Yeah, yeah, that'll I was in front of an eatily and
The fuck is in front of a belly in front of the belly in front of the eatily yeah
Yeah, that's Mario Batali's place right eatily yeah, no Mario Batali's place is prison
Eataly is owned by Mario Batali.
It's basically a huge...
I can't look it up, but it's owned by Mario Batali.
Eataly.
Eataly Mario Batali. I don't think it is.
I don't think they would let that happen.
Okay, well it auto-completes here.
Well, but that's because he's Italian.
A lot of different city names.
Yeah, he's Italian.
And the fate...
Once the crown jewel is this, let's see here.
Eataly finally cuts ties with Mario Batali.
Okay, all right. He was completely right.
Yeah.
But now he's not.
I also knew he was right. That's why I didn't say anything.
And that's why I looked it up.
I knew that Mario Batali had it.
And I don't even really know anything about Italy.
But that's probably the only thing I know about Italy.
It's like a huge, it's like a Whole Foods, but it's only like try hard fake Italian food.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's really fun to walk around and they have really stinky meat.
You know, like dry-aged meat.
Jamon Iberico.
I'm trying not to eat that much meat anymore.
Really? Why's that?
I got, went to the doctor, I have really high cholesterol.
Really? You have high cholesterol?
I have high cholesterol, can you believe that?
I really can't.
Yeah.
How do they test that?
I got, I went in there and they took out like six vials of my blood.
Vials?
I hate having blood taken.
I like it.
I'm kind of freaky like that.
I don't like it.
You told me you hated it when you got it done.
I'm keeping you accountable.
My grandpa.
You said it scared you.
No.
My grandpa will go give blood and he'll like push his arm down and like do this and shit,
try to make it go faster. That's funny. Because it doesn't bother him. I feel like that's a thing
you would do if it did bother if you wanted to be over. No he's like he's like doesn't. Why else
would you do that? Why if you didn't bother you why you just sit there? Maybe he does maybe he is
a little baby, but why is he giving blood? For the cause. I hate the cause. Oh he might like it
though. Yeah yeah. Oh that's a really good point. Also what is the cause when you give blood? If
people are dying they might want your blood. Who the fuck is dying from no blood? Blood
bloodless Joe who's that fucking guy yeah he needs a lot of blood he's a shit well
it's also if someone's blood it gets like dirt in it or something yeah like
you need we need you have clean blood because if you put soap in the blood to
try and clean out the dirt it's like now there's soap in there too
that's still a mystery just mysterious I used to give blood I find them
fascinating I had like like I think I gave blood like twice in a month once
Holy shit because they were giving out free hats. You needed two hats?
They're giving out free hats at a... Is that like a plot line to something? That's like a
TV show plot line that I've seen before I think. Yeah they gave out a free hat
but then I was like oh it's like a hat that just says like I donated blood or
something. Then I had a I got a sweatshirt. What TV show is that from?
That straight up is a TV show. I don't know. I remember I got hired as a fucking
Are you thinking of? I got hired one time as this fucking as a fry cook at
this fucking stupid ass restaurant. Krusty Krab. The Blood Restaurant. I was pretty excited about it, but then all these
uh, there's all these anchovies they show up. They're going meep, meep, meep, meep.
Because they're just so hungry and I'm trying to make all the burgers I can
but it's actually really hard. They started surfing their bodies like a wave, right? And at the end of the
I mean of the story.
That's what I was given blood with my mom and like two of my aunts.
Yeah, my mom Marge and my aunt Selma and the other one.
But basically I was working at this restaurant and my boss, listen, God bless him, fat daughter.
Yeah, like whale level fat.
Also Patrick was telling us the plot line of an Office episode.
That is not the plot line of an Office episode.
I think that happened to me too.
an episode in the office so they do that. And I remember one time he wants cookies.
Yeah cookies not a free. Okay that's a little bit of a stretch. That is a huge stretch.
He's not ripping off the office because there's. I thought it was a free hat and I looked it up
and it was cookies. Also that's based off of real life people get shit for giving blood.
And literally that's also a joke from the jerk where Navin just gives a bunch of his blood.
Well then why didn't you say that when I was asking what it was from? You're trying to cover
something up no listen I'll concede the point but I have the I have the the
sweatshirt that I know
yeah all right this is actually changing you might be right on to something I
think there's a green sweatshirt that said I don't remember him mentioning
that it was red blood you know get some kind of red souvenir see I thought they
were gonna have more blood themed stuff but it was not even blood themed it was
more hospital theme than blood theme. What you're saying it like that like you they
have some kind of like Chuckie cheese reward cabinet where you come up and
you're like I gave X amount of blood and you're like I don't record to wait here
I have my donor card is how they should do it though yeah you should be able to
you the amount of milliliters you give you should be like your tickets yeah I
would like to get a ps5 yeah yeah be able to save it up to exactly yeah they
put it on a little printer a seat yeah come back next time yeah I fucking think
I have some tickets in here somewhere yeah donor card oh no I got my Homer card
wait no I don't dough dough dough whoo-hoo
my vaccine card these are drink ticket oh there's a picture of me and Cameron is
as what oh it's baby Cameron as babies I have that picture on my fridge you guys
have known each other since you were babies check it out
I met you guys like four years ago.
He's a bunch of drink tickets I never redeemed.
Holy shit. Come on everybody.
You kept them in your wallet?
I don't know if I have them.
You broke piece of shit.
I was like yeah if I come back next week.
You think that they're gonna...
You have a tattered, you take it out of your wallet, a tattered
drink ticket. You got on the
show, you're like yep. That's pretty fire.
That is dope. You robbed them
of cards. He's hiding away the
picture of us as babies. He doesn't want you to see it.
because he thinks that I had to recently go through and okay let me look at this
picture so I'll be the judge of this didn't describe it to everyone who can't
see it all right so there's I see two babies the hell I don't have my blood
donor card anymore I think it's at home wait no okay I don't remember you guys
ever going to India oh here's my old India this pretty cool my old debit card
that they canceled or someone wants this is some kind of number is not four one
one seven so this is some kind of you're in some foreign country and you're
wearing kind of like cloth diapers. But you're grown men there.
Where? Right here. Yeah, we're grown men there. And above you're babies and
then underneath I really I think those are also babies. You guys look lily white.
I'll tell you that much. Okay. Oh here's something. Here's my
prescription card for my eyes. You're just going through your wallet. You don't have
anything like nothing crazy happen. Do you want to hear something crazy that happened to me?
Nobody last night got completely hit by a car.
Nothing like that.
Do you want to hear something that was...
Oh shit, here's my donor card.
Okay.
I am blood type A positive, but also here is the business card for Steven Vega.
Oh, the pit bull impersonator.
The pit bull impersonator that my friend Charlie hired for his runway show.
I think the wallet needs to go in the phone circle.
Yep, I agree.
I think that this is now a wallet and phone circle, because somehow you're doing your phone
with your wallet right now.
Something that happened...
Donor ID 214160.
Stop.
Something that happened to me the other night that was not funny at all. It was very scary.
Yeah.
As I was sleeping and I woke up. You know when you like first wake up and you kind of
are still dreaming a little bit and you can just like see stuff, like a weird dream hallucination
in the real world or whatever?
Yeah, yeah. You get little floaters.
Yeah. Well, so I had one where I woke up and I was like half awake and my like dream, waking
dream hallucination was just my bedroom door just closing.
Scary.
So scary.
Nice.
One of the scariest things I've ever seen.
I had a scarier dream.
Yeah, I had a scarier dream.
I had one where just Darth Maul cut me in half.
I had one where I was closing Cameron's door.
Really?
Why was that scary for you?
Because there was a monster behind me, obviously.
Because it was between you.
It was a door between you guys as friends and you couldn't hang out.
Yeah.
I had a dream that we were all in the same room, but I was like, you guys were like two
feet close to each other.
Like there's two feet between you and there's like 15 feet between me and you guys.
So you guys were talking and like laughing and stuff.
And I was being like, "What?
you say yeah like that and it was really scary yeah I told you guys about my
Patrick's neck dream Oh Patrick in my dream Patrick got stung on the neck by a
bug that's so scary yeah and it's done by a bug his neck swelled up really huge
so it's like the size of his head and then he was walking around to us and be
like guys I think something's wrong with my neck we kept me like Patrick there's
something really wrong with your neck I'm at a dream in days I mean having
lost my imagination. I've been having some weirdies. Oh yeah? Yeah. Anything crazy?
Well that was pretty crazy. The door. I already told you about my dream movie
idea kidnapped by Dracula escape. Yeah. Yeah you did tell us about that. I think
it would make a weird easy thing. I had a dream last night. I had a dream because I had like a
like I was going to see a doctor today and I like fell asleep and woke up and I
think I had a dream that I already went. To the doctor? Yeah and then I was just
I hate that. I hate when I wake up from a dream where I was doing what I'm planning to do during
the day.
Yeah, I have to do it all over again.
I get confused. I get really confused.
Whether or not you did it or not, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I would dream.
I wake up confused every single time.
Oh, yeah.
I've never woken up and immediately known where I was, even in my own bed.
That was the worst on tour when I would like wake up and be like, "Oh, I'm at home," and
then like I roll over and I see one of you guys and I'm like, "I am not at home."
Wait, what is wrong with seeing one of us in the mornings?
well sometimes I just want to roll over in my bed and just start whacking off.
You can do that. It wouldn't bother me if you whacked off. Sometimes I just want to
just roll over and just pull on my Johnson Leggings. Pull on my Johnson Leggings. Pull on my Johnson Leggings.
Like it's owing me a free like it owes me a sass Toyota CNS. A sass Toyota. A sass. If I'm I'm good
enough friends with you that if you if we were sharing a bed in a hotel room you
were like Caleb I really have to whack off but the bathroom is broken. I'd be
like yeah you can whack off. I'm not gonna whack off in front of my friends. I'm just
I don't want them to see, I don't even want them to hear the JOI, I have to watch.
I'm probably, yeah, and I have to watch it, but I have to watch it.
You're the size of a pea and I'm a big monster.
I have to watch JOIs because, not because it like turns me on or anything, because I
genuinely forget how to do it every time.
You're watching it like, I'm like, oh, interesting.
to the tune of the chicken dance or
something or no left foot in right foot
out yeah yeah you're doing the hokey
pokey with your penis yeah yeah and I'm
just keep going like oh right oh that's
what it was a circle with my oh yeah do
you guys ever do a one circle jack off
no you only make one circle and it feels
like you're fucking a ring my hand is so
much and is so much bigger than my
penis you have to use your you have to
use your foot. Yeah, I have to use my I have to use my hand is so much bigger
than I have to use my big love pinky. Yeah, I've used my damn pinky and my ring
finger just so it doesn't feel like it's tiny like a mouse. Yeah, tiny like a
mouse. I have to use I have to use an oven mitt because of the strange. The
first way I learned because I don't know how to wash it. The first way I
learned how to masturbate was was using just I would make a circle, make a
circle and I would fuck it like a two fingers like a dainty yeah and I used to
use soft pinkie out I used to use soft soap the hand soap and it now every time
I smell it at people's houses it gives me a boner Wow yeah do I've soft soap in
my house no you don't he's just tie a string on my penis then shut the door
really fast your big brother's like no it's gonna work for real this time this
I used to I would do I used to do I would roll around in the grass, so I'd have to
go outside every time
completely naked like a worm rolling like a worm wriggle yeah, I do a worm
wriggle.
I you know you ever hear somebody say that they grew up. They would like hump
their couch. Yeah, yeah, that's a way. That's really weird. Hump the couch. I
don't understand how that like works. It feels good. Also, I think it probably
like that fucks you up as an adult because you're looking for people who
of who just look like couches maybe yeah also the couches that you should at
least do it to like your own bed yeah and there's certain things like the
chair from from Pee-wee's Playhouse or like a globe from yeah play house like a
genie box yeah something like that like a leg for a wish and maybe could wish for
pussy from Jambi do you think that Lego figures fuck the holes in each other's
heads no they fucked the holes in the pants yeah there were holes there though
yeah they for they have to put on but they also have a hole in their head it's
like they're waste that's the other I mean that's what a blowjob is to it is
they get fucked they take their head off and they've yeah long ways down their
head or the top of it well Lego man doesn't have a penis you don't know
sorry to burst your they don't make a note they don't make a no-brainer
person in bubble but no a Lego man doesn't have a peanut little Lego man
I'm doing the opposite yeah. I'll burst my bubble. If you say he does have a
penis interesting, there goes my bubble. Here's a bubble. I got to show you. I
think I burst my
I just
yeah, that's like somebody walks in your covered and come a bubble burst on
kind of like a medieval like like the four humors type of way of
understanding. You know in your body, there's a bubble in you burst and
sometimes it bursts bursts.
it's birth you know how to have more come no cuz I would love to I think if you'd
come right think there's something really yeah I was soon though that puts more in
your body I think I think if you take a bunch of zinc we'll tell you what I had
today super awk or no swear rocks swear OX swear OX electrolyte beverage guess
what this has in it zero sugar zinc zero calories with zinc to help boost immune
system guess what else it has eight of calories ions yeah I think it's zinc I
don't know yeah I think I think I think it's a makes your nut whiter zinc why
no it's it's one of those her you haven't you heard the the mnemonic device
zinc make it stink zinc make it stink zinc make it stink magnesium make it
pleasing him Oh vitamin B makes it P yeah you just peeing when you come yeah
the same vitamin C also makes it P vitamin D, also makes it P as well.
Vitamin E does not make it P.
No, vitamin E makes it erect, makes it makes it good for she yeah.
So magnesium is for him, pleasing him, pleasing him.
Vitamin E is for she.
They make a skateboard trucks out of magnesium.
Isn't that weird?
That's because all skateboarders like to be pleasing him.
Yep.
Come on pound that out pound that out real long.
Give me a long one.
Give me a long.
He wants to be pounded out by a long pounder.
you want to be pounded out by his that's what they say - we just needed each other
always you don't to be wound up by his way along pounder oh yeah cuz it's got
why it's a fish yeah what's this fish oil make your thing boil from a from the
shield the shield I love that you'll see CH bounders her name is CCH pounder
yeah funny very funny always sunny clip I don't know I don't know Dennis does an
impression of her and then D does something racist and hilarity ensues
that show is honestly funny but I do find that the characters are like not exactly
they're unlike a best people there well here's the thing if you idolize them
you're watching the show wrong well I watch it upside down ah is that that's
the right way to watch you're watching it wrong in two ways hmm it's a double
negative two ways cuz you're yep because you go both ways and both ways are wrong
wrong. Yeah, yeah, I think both ways are wrong. Yeah, I'll say it all right. I
think that you should be doing a third way third way third way like Andrew
Yang. Yep third way right down the middle. I'm not fucking men. I'm not
yeah. I think hey people some these these people nowadays. They're they're
going both ways when they should be focusing on the eightfold path. Here's
the thing who does it nowadays. Everybody's going both ways, but we
can't even get our politicians to fund roads that go both ways. Yeah, all
fucking one way. And they have a guy that goes one way with guys in charge of the roadways
now. They do. And he goes one way with guys. He goes one way with Chasten. He goes one
way. I wish he was chased. Yeah then maybe he would get all the roads working on time.
Basically these roads are going both ways and I'm like well that's why I'm late everywhere
because bisexual people are fucking late everywhere. And they're late on their periods. Because
they don't cuz they because they have a kid cuz they're full they're getting
filled up with nut by both ways by both ways and they get completely filled with
nut and both sides of our system are is totally full sides of the aisle I hear
bisexuality is basically the new viral dance move it's pretty much viral yeah
it's completely viral to be bisexual. It's spreading. I would say that's true.
Yeah, I think that's what a lot of people are saying. There's a lot of discourse
online about, "Is bisexuality just viral or is it like a
dance that stays like the whip and the locomotive?" The locomotive?
You know the song? "Come on, come on, do the locomotion!"
that's what you're thinking of. You know what needs to come back is hula hoopers.
The hula hoop? There's a lot of uh there's an undergrad there's a burgeoning
undergrad. There is a lot of people if you look up hashtag hula hoop on
instagram there's a lot of women. Really? What are they wearing? A lot of grown
women with a lot of tattoos and dreadlocks doing doing hula hoop videos. I
saw the crazy I just saw I saw the craziest white guy dreads near your house
Caleb the other day. It was a while ago. It was maybe two weeks ago. I don't even like
what level.
Is it a fat guy? Kind of fat white dude who has, he doesn't have dreads, but he has like
four braids coming off his head.
No, I think he had like, he was wearing like super reflective sunglasses and he had like,
it was.
There's like a Paul Wall style white guy with like four, I don't know how his ears look
like.
You know what, maybe it was him. I think it was braids, not dreads.
but he has so few of them that it looks like spider legs coming off his head and
he's always talking to somebody and just being like that.
No, we wow. He sounds like that. Wow, like talking into a fan. Well, we were
yeah. Okay, he we all rapper. Yeah, today. What does that remind you of? It
reminds me of this list. Yeah, that I've pulled up here. That's called that 50
worst Lil Wayne lines examining the so-called best rapper alive and who what
is this his aura was orange this is from a blog called his aura was orange. So is
that probably that's probably this guy somebody told him you can't rhyme
anything with orange. Oh he said his aura yeah well it says he actually has a on
the sidebar right here where my blog got its name from so he actually disproves
you right there. Disprove me then? It's a it's a Charlie Murphy quote. Oh yeah oh
oh i'm rick james bitch oh okay all right quote yeah it's basically that he must
have mistranslated yeah. So let's just well he has a quote in the sidebar from
thomas pain albert einstein the honorable sass
and then this one that is unattributed listen. I've never really listened to
little wayne. It's just not my kind of type of music or anything. So like what
I mean what even could these lyrics be are they probably about maybe
drug abuse, maybe like a mis-officer, maybe like a jolted...
He actually has a lot of lyrics about female police officers.
Really?
So you're a Lil Wayne, you're familiar with his work.
You must be some kind of Lil Wayne.
I know him from Tony Hawk, Pro Skater 5.
I prefer the works of Rothko.
Me too, yeah.
I would say...
Bosh!
Yeah, I would say like...
Kevin Federline.
Nietzsche.
Nietzsche is kind of my version of Lil Wayne for a lot of these people.
Kevin Federline.
not I'm not loving not familiar now love and I know that movie
mclovin why'd they never do a mclovin spin-off called make love and where's a
detective that'll be so good I can't believe they didn't do that they should
have called it super detectives they should have just called it it was Evan
and it was Evan and Seth and instead of being in high school it's them as
detectives super clues they should have called her super bad was that murder
that we have to investigate now. That's actually true. Super bad, nothing that bad happens in the movie.
Maybe if there was some kind of... Well, if nothing that bad... What happens? Underage drinking.
Well that's true, but if there was some kind of like... like super bad is like a holocaust or like a
mass murder... I think the creators of that movie have relatives who were in the holocaust.
Yeah, so they have the perfect kind of cultural background to tell that story because that was
super bad. True. Yeah. Now anyway, there's an editor's note to open this kind of... it's kind
It's kind of an article.
It opens us with an article written by this guy or a blog post, I guess.
Editor's note, "This is a weak man on the microphone, ladies and gents, and it takes a strong man
who loves hip-hop and loves his aura was orange to put as much time and dedication and endure
things no man ought endure, like listen to Dwayne Carter's songs and lyrics to show you
how much this guy truly sucks.
All I ask in return is that you hear me out or at least consider the facts that I've painstakingly
amassed and tell me at the conclusion whether I'm justified in what I say or I'm clinically
insane.
is all. This guy sounds, he's almost, I'm suspecting him to be a member of
Intelligentsia. Yeah, like a Mensa. Like the coffee company? Intelligentsia, no coffee.
Oh. You know? So like I've already, listen, I've only been kind of paying
attention to this rapper style thing for a couple minutes and I feel like I've
already taken some of the slang. Yeah, it's like I prefer Starbucks anyway. It's much
more of a... Exactly, yeah. Notes of flavor. Yeah, the notes of flavor are... Alright,
well let's get into this. I really would like to, I mean I don't know much about
Lil Wayne, but I'd like to know, you know, because I don't know what side of the
aisle I land on yet. Yeah I've never listened to Lil Wayne. Do we want to read
I mean he's written a huge, I don't know if we want to pick up the lyrics.
Does anything stand out here? Wayne is the biggest bullshit artist, product of an
extremely weak era ass rapper. It's ridiculous. He forces so much garbage
that either makes little sense, no sense at all, or just no thought or cleverness
to its basic second-grade simplicity. He cheapens metaphors in a way that I've
only seen fabulous do fat why are you what's wrong fabulous I cringe every
time I see his spike from gremlins face or hear his prepubescent voice getting
ready to murder in the bad way as he's as deep as a YMCA kiddie pool Wow
no and listen I don't I don't know much about this little Wayne character but I
do if it he says on top of all that the dude is way too cocky yeah I hate
cockiness and raggedosciousness and that kind of thing. This line I think covers that
perfectly too that I would like to read for you guys. If he didn't have this
self-important attitude and cockiness then he wouldn't leave himself open to
this kind of criticism but when he calls himself the best rapper alive then he
deserves the scrutiny and he's not just rapping for fun and in a light-hearted
manner and we should all who consider ourselves true fans of the genre take
off the kiddie gloves when dealing with him. Okay the gloves are off Mr.
Wayne or Dwayne what his name is Dwayne but he says but isn't it rapper name I
think his name is is Dwayne little that makes no sense what if I said my name
was a lib I just drop a letter yeah a let's I was like Kramer I think about it
a lib is kind of cool if my name was like a miracle at Rick at Rick at Rick
not that great maybe I just go by see by like Rick the ruler no you can't add
add extra things you have to just change one letter for a little way and added
little
that's more of an adjective yeah. So you could be like a ruler rick yeah,
maybe rick
rick the ruler and i could be on a be that's maybe i could be like that's just
a name. I thought i like camer a lot huddles of camer that's like more of a
like it sounds like a lord of the rings book. What about like
Griffin that's a I think they've done there's already like sticky white
kamer it seems like you're adding adjectives you try to make that about
like like set like white is about rice that's about jizz fucking hell right is
it's rice it's not jizz what I was wrong with you guys don't like okay fine fine
fine okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
and gallons of juice I hate cum shots squirting bubbling kamer that sounds
like a cum shot. That's about soup. I hate cum shots. We don't like cum shots. We don't like
cum shots. We don't like jizz. We don't like nut. I'm not doing that. I'm trying to come
up with a cool rap name that's about a food I like. You're trying to make a song about
jizzing all over something. No I'm not. You are. You're trying to make a new jizz anthem.
Chewing salty wad of kamer. Jesus Christ. Are you fucking kidding me? It's about salt
water taffy. That is. That's about cum. That is so clearly about cum. What does that have
to do with cum? That is about jizz. You're talking about sperm jizz. You're making sperm
All over my bed sheets, my Kamer flowed.
That's a sperm joke.
That is not.
That is when I was eating gazpacho in bed.
Gazpacho?
What the hell is gazpacho?
What the fuck?
Is that another jizzy cum shot name?
No, it's not.
It's a type of food.
It's like cold soup.
You're talking about nut.
I'm not talking about nut.
You're talking about cum.
You're talking about squirting your hot.
I sprayed Kamer on my girl's face.
Bruh.
It's about spray cheese.
Alright, well that one was a little too much on that one.
It's spray cheese.
Okay.
No.
combined the list during thing got stuck on the roof of my mouth it does that it
does that but don't say anything about I'm not gonna start on the roof I was
why would I say that no foods do that you have a fucking come losing out of
your brain you were your brain okay can we at least just settle on drunk right
now a Kmart sandwich and that's about ham stop making serious bukkake
references what I hate bukkake it's a you are talking with literally obsessed
with loads. I'm not obsessed with loads of food. I hate loads. Stop talking about loading
it up. A pig with kamer in its mouth. You're talking about loads of chunky jizz. You're
doing... You're talking about somebody being a splooge target. I am not. You're talking
about splooge. I'm not talking about... Admit it. I'm not talking about human oil. You're
making splooge comparisons. I'm not. You are straight out talking about white spew. Stop.
You guys are just bringing up all this stuff like the swamp water of the human body.
The swamp water.
See it's automatic for you.
You always have new words for fucking cum shots.
It's not automatic.
I have to work up to it.
I'm sick of your cum shot words.
I've been talking about food only.
It doesn't belong in a podcast.
Cum shots are for napkins.
And paper towels.
What about a sock that you don't wear anymore or a shirt you don't wear anymore?
I just gave a cum shot to my shirt.
Did a serious cum shot on my shirt.
My shirt is so crusty from all the cum shots.
You're talking about doing a tribute onto a Kleenex.
I'm seriously not, okay? I never did a cum shot on the wall.
You've done one.
I never did a cum shot on the seat.
You did a cum shot on the wall and you did it near your oven so people would
think it was olive oil.
I didn't cook my cum in my oven.
You bet you boiled and baked a car. I did not. My come did not get stuck in the
crack between two things. You jizzed in the toilet. I didn't just anywhere and
you swirled it around like it was a poached egg. That's right.
You got it right. You made a for you made a vortex. You did and then the
toilet with your jizz. I did not come shot into a bottle and when someone
asked me what it was, I said it's nothing. The bottle is empty, but the
bottle was half full.
There's nothing in that.
There's nothing in there.
I did not wave my hand in their face like Obi-Wan.
Wait, what the fuck?
For comparative purposes, I hate Tupac, but he had tons more depth to his best works than
Wayne.
Dude, Tupac is one of the greatest fucking rap artists who ever lived.
I'm thinking about getting a Tupac tattoo.
He actually did Matt, a tummy rocker that says Tupac instead of Thug Life.
That's pretty good.
No, like a portrait.
A portrait?
A portrait.
If you get a Tupac portrait, I don't even, I mean, I'll just smile.
Yeah, I'll admit it. I'll smile if you do that and I'll enjoy it.
Yeah. I don't even like Tupac's music that much.
I feel like I would definitely get a Tupac portrait. The thing is it's funny.
You should only be getting funny tattoos.
Yeah. Yeah. In one way or the other. I'm a tribal type man.
Yeah, I got a spider web on my elbow. Well that one's cool though.
Yeah, that one is cool. But then you also have the word Dr. Evil on your arm.
Yeah. I think it would be funny if I got like...
I got my eyebrows tattooed on.
Again, don't get me wrong.
If you take away the buzz and the arrogant swagger of Wayne
and you put him in the same character as someone more affable
and less self-involved, it'd be a different story.
But when you put him up as a great of his time,
which for all purposes is a very talent depleted era
in hip hop, fair or unfair,
you then have to have him survive the test
of comparing him to the other greats of other eras.
And there's no way that you can put his ass up there
with other greats of other strong eras of hip hop.
It's just not a credible case. The fact is, the fact that this is even arguable
shows that Jesus died in vain. So like honestly this guy's bringing Christ into it.
Yeah, you gotta do the Kool-Aid with the Christ stuff.
You better have some really good points. I want to read these lines. I feel like we've done so much
building. I need to hear what the fuck this Little Wayne guy is talking about.
Okay, here's a thing that says "World's Worst."
Okay, and it's a picture of Little Wayne kissing Birdman.
Okay, so gays are bad to this author.
Okay, so I guess he's not fucking okay with LGBTQness, which is
Which is actually not fire. Yeah. Yeah, but here we get to the list
There's a new heading the 50 worst most forced most nonsensical idiotic things
Wayne has said as in his career is wayne little wayne. I think he's who he's referring to little wayne's a different guy
All right. No, i'll read this because i'm probably the best at reading rap. Yeah
So you go ahead and read just every word now now where you ho at wipe your feet on the doormat
I'm a bring the N-O back like a, and he says actually,
- A word.
- I can't say that, but with no back.
I'm gonna bring the N-O back like a--
- Let's say friend.
- Friend with no back.
What does that mean?
I mean this is basically--
- Not operational?
- It's almost forced and nonsensical if you ask me.
Idiotic I don't know about,
'cause I really don't understand the context.
I would need to know you know rap songs are money based on based on on on this
line so far that we're wondering what what I'm a bring the n o back means I
think no might mean no I'm nonsense obvious oh because of that it truly
makes no so no lick of that's almost meta that's like an almost have you seen
the movie the so sorry the film adaptation yeah so he's kind of doing a
film have an adaptation of what no there's a movie called at a film called
adaptation and it's about-- I don't remember it but it's about
meta-ness and kind of-- it's about yeah it's about if a movie and a book were the
same thing. So it's a film adaptation of a book adaptation of what? Of a experience--
You're getting caught up in the wrong thing. The next one is-- this is almost-- I mean
and this one almost also has some kind of racial tinge to it. He says, "Get girls
wet like backs and I don't think that I can say that. Interesting. And I just
completely did. This one here, this is a good one I think maybe. This one actually
makes some sense. This one makes sense. I'm hot like dogs. Yeah like hot dogs. Hot dogs.
Or a dog pants when it's hot. I don't think that that's nonsensical at all.
Maybe this is this could actually be a deep line about wearing pants. Maybe he's
wearing cool pants. I'm hot like dogs when a dog is hot at pants. Holy shit. I'm
wearing cool pants and a dog pants I just got new I also just got new pants a dog
pants to get cool that's actually to cool down to the tailor I'm so sorry I'll
read this one here my girl is prego and then in square brackets pregnant which
you have to assume is at is added by but you never know author yeah little Wayne
could have said my girl is pregos left square bracket pregnant right square
bracket and that's why it's transcribed that way but I don't want it so I'll cut
it out like Joey Gladstone. Oh that makes sense to a Full House fan like me. Yeah.
Does he does he perform an abortion with a razor blade? No. Joey...
Caesarean section? Joey uh Joey Gladstone has a he's a... He cuts out babies? He does
this he goes cut it out. Of a woman's womb? It's a catchphrase. He cuts out a... so it's not so full.
The house is too full so they can't have another kid in it. On the show Full House the
mother was full we need yeah we need the mother was cut out of the show because
she had cancer but what I should just cut that out of her yeah they should just
cut the cancer out too late well they should have done it earlier not too late
to abort this child well there's two children on the show and they cut them
both out and they got one child they got completely cut out and aborted yes okay
and now one of them is married to the Prime Minister of France's brother.
They need to change the word abortion. I feel like it's a little too nautical.
Yeah. Or space. It does make me think about...
Or abort. It's kind of spacey.
Spacey, yeah. The further we get into the future, the more abort is going to be...
That is a word that's a bit... It's early.
Exactly. Yeah. We're not ready for that word yet to be used a lot.
Abort is going to be so ubiquitous, because everybody's going to have a
spaceship with a big red button that says abort, and we're going to have a lot
of very stupid people thinking that that'll make their baby shoot out of
body so I think we need to change it yeah I got a bitch with me I call her miss
without draws I go to the bank they call me mr. withdraws okay that one's got
some wordplay - yeah you know yeah because you with actually sensical this
one's really good like the number after one I'm gonna get me - he's got me - see
that's a really now and I think I'm assuming that one's just aged poorly but
yeah saying I'm gonna get me - does not the best that's maybe yeah and it's and
And you'd imagine he's bragging about it because of how much he's read about his
machismo.
Yeah, like the number after one, "I'mma get me too'd."
Yeah, I don't know if that's a good thing to brag about.
He's bragging about getting me too'd.
Yeah.
And Harvey Weinstein.
Oh shit.
Whoa.
I just realized that.
Yeah.
Um, "Baby, I'm an acrobat.
Sweetie, I'm a stunt devil.
You can't get on my level, 'cause I am so unleveled."
Okay, so it's kind of a--
'Cause he's a stunt man.
Or it's a role playing game or video game reference.
Oh, he's on a different level.
Or he could be unleveled like he's an NPC or something.
I would like to make some kind of game where I can run around like Mario and
jump on all these rappers heads and kill them.
Yeah.
Kill every rapper.
Just flatten them.
Yeah, just fucking flatten you out.
Hey, stop ruining culture!
Yeah.
Rapper!
And then just jump on them and flatten them.
There is a game.
I'll tell you who I'd love to see flattened, Post Malone.
jump on Post Malone and all his his tattoos and grossness would disappear
like like when you jump on a Koopa and it comes out of the shell. Yeah, there's a
game where you can box other rappers. Yeah, but they should have Post Malone and me do it.
And I can just get him one-on-one in a ranked DLC pack. Yeah, Post Malone and Caleb.
Yeah, and I can do a special. I can do a Hadouken or a Samurai Sword.
You have like a specially developed... He has a diaper. Yeah, you have like a specially
you develop like it's like you're like a vampire hunter, but for post malone like
you're you have a specific equipment that is just for killing. I'll say this
post Malone. He talks all the time. Oh, I drink I drink fifty Bud Lights a day. I
drink sixty cigarettes. I smoke sixty cigarettes a day. I'm a rottie buddy.
I'm running five six miles every single day. I'm shadow boxing for about an hour
and
I'm coming for you. Yeah, you know, you got you better. I've already you had
start getting in fighting shape. Yeah. Here's my new version of Post Malone's
song, okay? I'm dead, I have rigor mortis, and now my body's rock hard.
Oh, that's good. He died. Yeah. My body's calcified, I'm a mummy, I've died
for a thousand years, I'm rock hard. That's good. What's another one?
Dying dead and ghostly. Instead of white Iverson, he could say, like,
I'll have no son because I am dead and now I'm done.
Caleb killed me with a gun.
He took my money and all of my friends.
The one where he's listing his cars.
I just died.
Ow.
Bentley.
What's...
The Beamer Benzer Bentley?
That's Lil Wayne.
No, that's not Lil Wayne.
That's Lloyd Banks.
That's not...
Okay.
I don't know any rappers.
I don't listen to rap.
I listen to like guitar and acoustic music.
music verse on that nope maybe there remix I did a remix I mean I've never
heard any of these songs check my bio I started high with two ounces just like
Ohio - well yeah this person wrote - Oz this doesn't say ounces it says - Oz
well this doesn't again I don't used to fall in recipes come also a chef part
time I mean amateur of course I mean I personally I consider chefing I'd say
it's less of a science than it is an art and I mean it really depends on who you
are and look at this next line here. There is no grammar. If you you know what
the difference is between chef being an art what and chef and chefing being just
something you do is if you walk behind somebody and you say behind you behind
behind or behind or what is it? I'm behind you right now behind behind
behind which if you're the thing is if you're trying to corner, you're turning
corner corner ready if the foods food. Oh, that's the other thing they say
foods ready when the foods not ready. That's just a weird quirk that only
people who worked back of house now tips everyone's like oh if they seen a TV
show if they'd say foods ready and the foods ready like you know yeah. I'm in
the back of the house in the back of my house. I'm taking a fucking monster
dinosaur shit in my bathroom and that's where my bathroom is the back of my
house. Yeah, yeah, and I honestly when I'm doing his house, that's not true. It's
is completely false. Well, the back of my house is my bedroom. So I'm in there and
I'm is it wrong morally to take a shit and then do a cum shot onto the shit
because you save flesh? Yes. Yeah, I think it's I think it's completely safe.
One of morally wrong. So yeah, I think that's one of the I watch a
Kurzgesagt video about how there's no fucking water. So I'm saving water. I'm
doing cum shots onto my poop to say what the fuck did we just talk about
earlier with combshots. I don't like doing that. I didn't do a single combshot thing and you guys yelled at me for 20 minutes and now Caleb admits that he's
he's literally combining two things. He's shitting and pouring jizz on his shit like it's a Cinnabon. I'm not doing that.
It's literally you are basting your poop. I'm not trying to put sage and rosemary on it and basting my poop inside. You are taking your poop. I don't have a cast iron toilet that I get to temperature and baste it with my poop.
- I've been there. - I'm pasting with butter
in my nut. - You were putting your poop.
- Pasted in the nutter. - You were putting cheese
on your poop like it's ice cream
and you're trying to put one of those hard shells
that you can buy. - Yeah, I love those.
- I just remembered those just now.
- I had those ones
- You know what I had the dream I've always had?
- I had that at the beach.
- You know what my entire dream has always been?
Pour it on my tongue, get my tongue really cold,
pour it on my tongue, make it harden onto my tongue,
and now I have a chocolate tongue for an entire day.
And guess what?
Everything's tasting like chocolate.
and then I could finally eat my vegetables. You might have to live in a cold place. No,
I just tongue cold, cold up my tongue. Here's an idea as a prank, put it on the like a pole
in the winter. Chocolate pole. Chocolate pole. Someone tries to go lick the chocolate pole.
They get their stung, their stung. Stung pole. They get their stung. They get their stung.
The thing is tongue stuck. If you just say stung, that communicates the entire meat. So you can just
say I didn't they go up to it they put their tongue at they get their stung and
people will know what you mean I didn't grow up in a very cold place did you
guys ever put your tongue on a pole yeah I did it I did I did on my back porch
did it get completely stuck yeah and I ripped it off and I saw like you ripped
your tongue off I ripped my tongue off the back porch thing and I saw like a
little bit of blood on my tongue yeah I didn't I didn't do it when it was um
when it was that cold when I was afraid I did it when it was kind of cold I see
the country of New Hampshire. Did you say oh fudge? You know when you're taking ice
cubes out of the ice cube train you can feel them stick to your fingers a little
bit? Yeah. That scares me, I don't like it. What if my rip, rip, what if my rip,
you're like a bitch with no ass you ain't got shit. See that's I think unfair
because I think there's plenty of women with no ass who actually have huge boobs.
Yeah. But they don't have shit. They work at Hooters. It's just not about having boobs, it's about
having shit. Oh, because he's saying if you have no ass, of course you can't shit. I hope
women have no shit. That's actually a really good point. I thought it was a stupid line.
It's a smart line. No, it's clever. If you don't have an ass, you can't have shit. No
shit is coming out. I hope a woman has no shit in her butt ever. I think they try to
keep it out. Yeah. I'm in the hood. I'm butta on bread like parquet and I'm all about me
like do re do re like do re me do re me oh my god that's actually good how is he
saying this is bad yeah I just didn't need the part where he says he's in the
hood I think that's what author thinks I got old money could have bought a
dinosaur clever hmm it's very clever it's about old money it's about it kind
of engages with the issue of an ancient economy yeah it's actually academic yeah
like what would you have bought it with Mr. Wayne? Yeah, I don't Mr. Wayne. I'm
starting master. I'm certain that he's back to one. What would you have bought
you with even when I'm laying on my back? I'm never backing down. I got oh no,
you already read that and I'm going to be with my dogs like goof troop. I would
love to hang out with the goof troop. What's goof trip like goofy in him? Yeah,
it's exactly I'm not feeling them goofy in him. We should have a goof troop money
female dogs bitch roof roof okay that's not bad yeah coke transactions over the
phone we call them blowjobs that's a slippery slope cuz then now what do you
call blowjobs you're a fucking famous rapper penis sucking get over here I
would love to have a penis sucking yeah that makes no you need an appointment
that's okay his pussy so friend I'm a virgin I'm a pill-popping animal syrup
sipping friend I'm so high you couldn't reach me with a fucking antenna again
like I just the pill a minute past and it's about to get shitty my penis is not
working and my asshole shit on you my flow is sicker than a patient that is
HIV positive I mean that's a again that's yeah like it or hate it I mean
that is true that people who have HIV are pretty sick. Here's a scary one. Her head is crazy
so she's insane. This is kind of like a horrorcore like ICP type line. Here's one below it, "You
can't see me Ray Charles." Yeah, which is like, yeah. He can't see you. It's rude to
Ray Charles, he can't see anybody. Yeah, like why, also you're not special because Ray Charles
can't see you. Her toes smelling like, or smelling mint like Tic Tacs. This would be
be a better line. I okay. I like the use of simile and metaphor and figurative
language in rap, but this would be a much simpler and more evocative line. If
you just said her toes smell like mint yeah and also you don't need the tic
tax in there. It is a brand name. It's a crutch again. I don't know that yeah.
He's probably paying royalties out to tic tac yeah. Just say second. She has
minty toes. I've never heard any of these damn songs. I for all I know. This
is a whole song about a candy woman. Yeah, you know like I she's got a bubble
lips she's got she's got she's got laughing tacky nose you gotta say
tackles bubble gum lips she's got laffy taffy and her butt is full of fudge is a
complete it's got a fudge but it's not candy but it's okay
not only hot like stove but I also cook like its cousin oven I told the bitch
Jorge like the ketchup for the Yankees he's not currently the catcher for the
Yankees anymore so if you listen to that later in life it's gonna make no sense
Yeah, you know, I think Jorge Posada has now played for the Yankees in some time. He should say wait, what's hey
He should a good line would be like I'm
Completely swinging on her vagina
My penis is a complete bat and I'm in I'm doing this in the same way as Aaron judge does I don't like a white ball
With red. Yeah
Out of my bat and I have white balls like
Santa I have white white balls like baseball. Yeah baseball
- White balls like MLB. - White balls like Santa.
- White balls like MLB. - But long white Santa.
- Dirty white balls with a little bit of red like MLB.
That's easy.
- Yeah, red veins.
- White balls with red veins, like it's from the MLB.
- MLB.
And then, and she is so pleasing
because you know I had my vitamin E.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Shoot a friend in his thigh and leg,
tell him to ketchup like mayonnaise.
- A bitch is a female dog and a dog is a man's best friend.
- It's like-- - Those are just facts.
- Touching, yeah. - Yeah, yeah.
- Bitch, I'm the bomb, like, tick, tick.
- Tick-tock.
- Oh, oh.
- That's an app now.
- Oh, I must have misspelled.
- That's an app now, but I guess back then,
it was just bomb.
- I call them April Babies 'cause they fools.
These babies are fools.
- Boy, I'm shitting on the green like piss in the grass.
- He likes shit and piss. - Oh, sitting on green.
- Do you think he likes pissing on people?
- And me, I'm still spitting like a retard,
and these friends soft, they should be rapping in leotards.
This is a line, this line, this next line here
one that I've always wanted to add to one of my reps. I didn't know that he'd beat
me to it. I'm hot too, baby girl, I'm soup. I mean what's what's hotter than soup?
Yeah. Gazpacho. It's very cold. Gazpacho is completely cold. Yeah. It's a cold, it's like a
cold soup. Where have you been getting gazpacho? It's served completely. It's cold soup.
It's a cold, it's not even gazpacho. It's coldly red. It's a redly, boldly, coldly soup. It's entirely cold.
completely ice-cold. You've been having hot gazpacho? Where? I just thought it
meant soup. Gazpacho? No it's like a cold it's like a chilled what's in it like
cucumbers or something. Tomato? Crap tomatoes. What? It's a cold tomato soup.
The gazpacho that I had was completely white. Okay I just found out
earlier when I said that when I said that. The gazpacho I had was completely white with
chocolate chunks in it. Did you have it at my house? I had it at Baskin-Robbins.
Oh I think that was ice cream. Well and it was hot? It was hot.
Fudge was hot. Oh okay. I just had a banana with the banana and the cherry.
Earlier when I was reading the sidebar I said he had a quote from
somebody named the Honorable Sass. I've just got to the bottom of this blog post
and see it says posted by the Honorable Sass. Holy shit it's him. Yeah at 301
He says, "I arrest my case, now you be the judge."
You got a picture of a judge.
Is there any comments here?
There's a lot of comments here.
Let's just read one or two.
Yeah, let's see here.
Christian, I like the name, he says, "I completely agree with everything you say.
Everything Lil Wayne says is intelligible or nonsensicable."
This anonymous said-- Only if his fans see what we do.
Anonymous said, "Last guy to post is a dipshit."
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, no, that comment continues.
I thought he was just saying like, "Oh, whoever leaves the last comment is a dipshit."
says wait anonymous says you guys are retarded Wayne's the best there is he's
not retarded and how you gonna say a ten-year-old can write that it's true
it's completely true I'm on Wayne's side let me just clarify yeah thank you for
writing this I'm showing this to every Wayne fan I can find that's you know
maybe they're fans of just Wayne's in general this is this article has a
multi-generational kind of reach here there were three three years deep into
comment section. Oh yeah, wow, I didn't even notice.
Some people are writing some long comments here. Yeah. Yeah. I mean basically
they're just, I would say they're mad because they can't come up with 50 lines.
Lupe Fiasco, Aesop Rock, MF Doom, Deltron 30/30, Big L, Wu-Tang Clan, Jedi Mind
Tricks, Brother Ali, and Atmosphere are 300 times better, yet none of them get
the recognition they deserve Caleb.
Fuck man.
If you take him for what he is, he is pretty amusing couldn't help but laugh
out loud at at least half of these lines.
Maybe he's less of a rapper more of a comedian.
He should do comedian four words Lil Wayne a fucking sucks.
Yeah, people are very people are being very rude.
Most recent one.
I want to know.
I think it was at the oh,
- Oh no, we're still going.
- Yeah, no, it goes down.
- Oh my gosh, all right, let's see how far.
- I don't know what people are saying.
- Okay, I think we, yeah.
July 2019.
- Will Wayne still top 20 greatest of all time
and better than Eminem?
- Please, there's nothing deep or clever about his wordplay.
- Wait, this guy's good.
- Anybody could come up with this shit.
- This guy is named Shhh, Shhh said, Shhh, asshole.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- All right.
- Well, that's the list.
- That's the list.
- Anything to plug?
Yeah, I mean, I guess, well, this comes out--
This comes out Wednesday.
So tonight--
No, tomorrow night.
Tomorrow night is Portland.
Portland, Ogin.
Beto, get yo ticket.
Seattle, Austin.
Seattle.
We got a couple of shows in Seattle.
Go to swagpoop.com/shows.
And the show, it's not just us going up there and just
talking.
You keep reiterating.
Yeah, let's--
I'd say it pretty much is.
Yeah, we actually do a good show.
It's going to be completely normal, no surprises.
there won't be a we didn't plan the last thing we would want to be a
choreographed we definitely don't have a special technology themed guests for the
Seattle shows so don't even expect that yeah right okay bye bye