Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Bad things come in threes.
- Bad things come in threes,
but good things coming.
Dozens and dozens of blessings overflowing.
- Maybe even thousands, overflowing blessings.
- Millions of overflowing abundant blessings.
- In a row, with no breaks.
- I would say good things come in blessings.
- Large amounts.
- Good things come in blessings.
- Yeah.
- Well yeah, blessings are the vessel
in which good things are delivered.
- Exactly.
- Bad things come in threes.
- But how many?
- Good things come in presents.
- Okay, so bad things come in threes,
but also they say deaths come in threes.
- So deaths are bad.
- Sometimes people die and it's completely fine.
- Not true.
- You know, an old, old, old man.
- It's always a human life lost.
- Can you get a blessing as a present?
- Yes.
No, that's a present.
A present comes in Christmas.
- Presents come in Christmas.
- Bad things come in threes,
but presents come in Christmas trees.
but presents come at Christmas and your birthday.
Christmas Eve.
- I'm trying to do a rhyme.
- Oh, I don't think it needs to rhyme.
- I think it needs to rhyme.
- Why?
- That's a poem if your birthday is on Christmas Eve.
- Yeah, you know, you gotta feel bad for those kids.
I feel good for them because they get presents the next day.
No, you got to feel bad for them.
What?
No, they only get one.
If you're born on Christmas.
My aunt was born on Christmas.
I don't think I've ever known anybody who was born on Christmas.
I think that that's probably...
I think that...
Most people, if their child is due to be born on Christmas, they get a C-section beforehand.
I don't...
What?
Oh, a Christmas section.
A Christmas section, yeah.
I feel like that's...
Honestly, I mean I'm not a woman and I've never had surgery done. I feel like that's worth it.
Yeah, right?
I mean, I think that's one of those things where as a kid it sucks really bad, but I think it trains you to be a better adult.
I think it's like child labor, you know. If you work in a prison camp or something as a child and you grow up, you'll be stronger.
True.
Yeah. You will be a great artist.
It's like adversity.
Or you might, you could be the Antichrist.
Yeah, well, Antichrist will be born on Halloween,
not Christmas.
You could hate Christmas so, so much
that you become, or like, 'cause you hate Christmas
because you don't get Christmas presents, right?
Right.
And then you hate it so much
that you yourself go your whole life
trying to become the exact opposite of Christ.
Yeah, you're like, yeah, 'cause your parents
are expecting you to act like Christ
of your birthday yeah or Santa in either one I think you're gonna end up being
kind of devilish yeah exactly that's the green the anti Santa oh I guess I bet
dr. Seuss had this same conversation
If you're born on Christmas, you wouldn't become the anti-Santa.
He said, "Who is the anti-Santa?"
Oh wait, it's the Grinch.
And then he started reading that.
And then he made up the Grinch.
Apparently Santa Claus's birthday is March 15th, according to Google.
Whoa, that's my little brother's...
That's the day before my little brother's birthday.
When is Santa's birthday? The answer might surprise you.
Many may assume Santa Claus was born on December 25th,
if given his profession, and if not on Christmas Day,
then pretty close to it.
But it turns out Santa is more of a springtime baby
than a winter wonder birth.
This works out well because who really wants to work
and travel on their special day?
- Yeah, Santa is such a Pisces.
- He is. - Is that a Pisces?
- Deadass. - He actually is.
- What does Pisces do?
- Yeah, wait, look at-- - Pisces.
- We need to know-- - Pisces are sensitive as hell.
- You think Santa's sensitive?
- Yep.
- Let's see, what are the Pisces traits?
- What does a Pisces do?
Pisces traits, do we want male or female?
They'll do whatever they can to make sure the people around them are happy. That sounds like Santa Claus to me.
Yeah, people around him in the entire world, he's got a very large radar.
They're also artistic and use their vivid imaginations to think up ideas many others wouldn't.
Flying reindeer, let's go through this. Elves? Flying reindeer, all the presents?
Intuitive, unselfish, yeah, I mean that fucking fits the bill.
Wise, big ol' gray beard, knows just about everything there is to know.
Isn't he a wise man?
Imaginative. Yeah, he came up with every fucking thing about Christmas. I'd call that pretty
imaginative. Compassionate. Even the kids that are bad, he gives them something. Straight
coal. Romantic. Restless claws. Adaptable. He can fit through even a small hole or a
keyhole, we learned from the Santa Claus series. Open-minded. He even gives presents to kids
kids who live in a gay lifestyle or a Muslim lifestyle or a
Judaistic lifestyle so that's actually pretty open-minded I would say.
Artistic, he does skywriting with the reindeers. He says ho ho ho. He should do
that more. He should do skywriting with the reindeers. He invents toys with the elves too.
Yeah it's artistic. It is funny like as a kid when you're supposed to
to believe that like Santa makes every single toy that you get, but it's like,
like you think, you think, you think Santa really made a,
you think Santa really thought up of like that Crayola machine,
that Crayola, a crayon maker where you melt all the wax together.
You think Santa came up with that and not the, uh,
the good old minds of the USA.
The elves. Imagine Santa just hammering the no Russian mission into the,
the Xbox 360 copy of modern warfare two,
which he does it all with a little wooden mallet.
made
ones I think I don't think he's making no it's done makes them I think maybe a
simple thing he'll make but I don't think he does cheap knockoffs that's why
they all the all the brands hate him yeah yeah and they try to do they try to do
like proprietary stuff that Santa can't do like kind of a they have a guided or
a what on earth to tell me pray tell what on earth can't Santa do exactly
that's the problem they're running into is that they're got a toy on Christmas
from a video game from Santendo. That's right. That's right. It's like, yeah. It's not very
good. Santendo's Turtle Crossing. It's like Animal Crossing but all the animals are turtles.
You can't even do your missions fast. You ever get a pair of Jordans on Christmas, right?
You look at the Dunkman logo, no basketball, he's holding mistletoe. That's right. And his
- His penis is out, his cock is out.
- Fuck, man.
- That's nasty.
- Santa stitched a cock into the thing.
- And he stitched cock and balls here
'cause Santa has a good sense of humor.
- Ew. - Yeah.
- Right, he's around, he's as old as time.
- Listen to this scenario from this--
- 2,000 years old.
- From this Santa Claus birthday article.
This is the opening of the article I scrolled up and saw.
As your family prepares for Santa Claus' arrival
this Christmas, your children may wanna plan
an extra special menu for the man in red.
After all, he works up an appetite
traveling all around the world.
Maybe they suggest making a plate of Christmas dinner leftovers to keep them
from going to waste, a veggie packed smoothie to give him energy for all his
deliveries, or even a birthday cake to celebrate a special day.
If they suggest the latter, however, you'll have to tell them that Saint Nick
wasn't born on Christmas, leading them to ask when Santa's birthday is.
Well, I mean, hey, who wants...
you only eat birthday cake once a year? What kind of life is he living?
He's Santa Claus.
never really looking at the other point this is claus's birthday is a cause of
birthday cake and you have to be like
or sorry i really didn't want to talk about that
yeah this is this coming to the race
birthday yet is quite a while after they not saying that we have to have the
talk with the
they want to get a bit of a break
it
yeah he thinks that santa was born on christmas and not march fifteenth
what i just give him to give him christmas eve let me born on christmas
eve what are we are being so sick we should start we should start celebrating
Santa's birthday. I agree. Two Christmases. That's the day after, that's the day after
Pi Day for any mathematically minded folks out there. Oh my god. Oh my god. Maybe he's
not celebrating it as to not overshadow Pi Day. Well that might be right. So Mrs. Claw's
birthday is Christmas. Really? That's what Krukal says. Wow. That's not fair. Well it's
It's not fair to her, her husband's fuckin'-
How do you think they met?
That makes more sense.
Oh, it's probably-
That makes a lot of sense.
Wait, she says every year for Christmas, she says, "Give my gifts to someone else, I don't
care."
Listen to this passage that's the info box when you google Mrs. Claus' birthday.
December 25th.
Mrs. Claus' age is heavily debated, but her birthday is not.
According to multiple sources, Mrs. Claus was born on December 25th, i.e. Christmas
Day.
say this is a coincidence but mystic investigations writes that her birthday
meant she was destined to marry santa claus someday did sit did santa claus
well she sent his present every year did santa claus kidnap
mrs claus
is she what's always here that's literally the next heading i was about
to read the headings on this website are when is mrs claus birthday
and what's the age difference between santa claus and mrs claus
there's two possible there's two possible answers here according to them
like to know both. Alright the first one is 611 years. That's too big of an age gap. I'll
say it, that's too big of an age gap. The second one is 1521. That's even worse I would
argue. That's even worse. Get this, when she was in high school, right, he could have been
628 years old. Isn't that disgusting? That's not right. That's true. Come on. That is just
not right. Well she's in high school. She wasn't even born yet at his at his
thousandth birthday. Maybe, we don't know. You know what you know what you know one
of the craziest thing is? Santa probably delivered her a present once. I've never
I've never found myself. I've never found myself wanting to there to be a
600 year age gap just because the 1,000 year age gap is just almost too much to
fathom. Mm-hmm. Right? And I do and it is kind of upsetting that maybe maybe 18
years in a row he was delivering her presents being like oh my here it is
hey here's lipstick another more lipstick for Christmas here you go here's a
here's a Santa Santa style bikini here's a Santa is a Santa Claus calendar it's
got sure to me on it I clicked on the source they cited hey birthday she gets
Santa's phone number and a six-week birth control.
Yeah. Santa wouldn't do that. That's really not right. But he actually did do that.
I mean if he did that a year before that would be weird. Maybe they met on an app.
I don't think there was an app. Maybe they met on an app and then
and Mrs. Claus is like, "Oh my God, I was like, I knew you,
but like, that's insane."
- Mrs. Claus has been around for quite a long time.
So it's definitely possible that she was maybe,
she was maybe like a slave or like a really,
like a peasant or something.
- Yeah.
- And he rescued her, you know, I don't know.
- I mean, is there any, is there anything about how they met?
Let's see, there's a lot of information available about the Claus family, but some of it is
conflicting.
So I click here on the source they use for a lot of this information, which is called
mysticinvestigations.com.
And you think it might be a paranormal investigation thing, but it's actually, it's Mystic Christmas
blog the bewitching blog of Christmas.
Might as well, they're getting a little
confused, they're crossing holiday wires
there.
"Mrs. Holly Claus was born on Christmas
day by the sheer fate of her future destiny
as the demi-angel Santa Claus's wife."
Really? She's a demi-angel?
No, no, Santa's a demi-angel.
"Holly's father, Daniel McBride."
*laughter*
Wait, what?
What the fuck?
*laughter*
What?
Daniel McBride?
Her dad is
Was an Irish immigrant and young architect who
aided in the construction of the United States
Capitol. Wow!
Oh, so Santa Claus wants to date my daughter,
okay. She was born in
1792 Holly has no siblings because doctors told her mother that further
pregnancies could pose a risk to her health in 1792. They told her that Wow
they're about ahead of curve the age difference Mrs. Claus is currently 229
years of age but doesn't look a day over 60. She married Santa Claus at the age
age of twenty two on Valentine's Day, February Fourteen, eighteen
fifties when he was a thousand five hundred and forty five
years old.
The age difference isn't that shocking when you consider that
their soul mates.
That's true.
Does it say anything about Cupid being at the wedding?
No, you have to assume he was though.
I mean, yeah, I would think it would be all elves.
I don't think the reindeer's know.
think the rangers have any any idea what they're doing I think they just run yeah
like camels yeah the reindeers don't have the soul no yeah do you think we're
thinking st. Valentine's Day begins in the metaphysical mind of the omniverse
God in which we all exist right now send me this website right fucking now
every mystic Christmas is your valentine their Valentine's page is insane upon his
ascension to godhood various concept and thoughts spontaneously manifested into
sapient beings springing forth from his subconsciousness mind these are known as
omniverse personifiers one of them was love wait and this is about Cupid yeah
This is the author is Xavier...
The unholy union of demons and dark goddesses.
Xavier Remington.
As the founder and president of Mystic Investigations,
I have dealt with all manner of metaphysical mayhem.
However, the supernatural beings and paranormal phenomenon of the Christmas season are some of the most magical.
Our supernatural crime-fighting team has had the honor of being welcome at the...
Crime-fighting?
...devi-angel Santa Claus's North Pole City,
and the horror of battling the diabolical Anti-Claus.
Anti-Claus?!
Wait, hold up. This Xmas blog was born out of my own interest.
Wow, look at this fucking photo of the Anticlaws.
Merry Christmas to all. Holy shit.
And to all a safe night.
And his most recent, he's still posting.
Christmas is July.
I think there's a holiday episode now.
I think I have to do a deep dive into Mystic of Mystics.
I can't believe it. Santa Claus vs. Dracula.
It was the Christmas Eve of 1888 when Santa Claus found himself delivering gifts to the
good little boys and girls of Transylvania, Romania.
Santa landed his sleigh upon the roof of a modest home with smoke billowing from the
chimney at the witching hour.
He teleported down right into the flames of the hearth that kept the home warm on this
specially chilly night.
Dude, he fought...
See also, Santa Claus the Vampire Sleigh.
Oh my god.
There's hundreds of posts on this website.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Yeah, no, go ahead, Pat.
- I just, I don't know if we're about to say the same thing.
I just want to say the sections at the top
of this website here are home page, home,
paranormal Q&A, supernatural stories,
Christmas blog, Halloween blog, paranormal forecast,
paranormal news, time travel, and private investigate.
And when you click on private investigate,
there are three different tabs.
The first one brings you to a website called free background
check.org then reverse phone search and reverse email search.
Dude, this is the best website I've ever fucking seen.
When you hover over Halloween blog, the three options are
Halloween spirit, Halloween beings and Halloween Queen
Shala. And I clicked on Halloween Queen Shala and it took
me to a news article on their site called, "Who is the leader
of Halloween.
The headline is "The Angel-Demon Hybrid Shala Revealed to be Secretive Queen of Halloween."
Okay, okay.
This brought us to a new Halloween mystic blog.
Oh my god.
Antichrist invaded Halloween Island.
Are you fucking serious?
I'm completely serious.
That's crazy.
Let me just read the top here.
sections of the website are home, hallow Q&A, Halloween legend, Halloween beings, shop,
costumes, decor, candy, scary stories, which under scary stories includes devilish
DVDs and mp3s of spooky sounds and Halloween music. It has a it says gift
shopping and there's four things silly stocking stuffers, Christmas costumes,
ugly christmas sweater and candy and when you click candy it just searches on amazon for you
yeah i was just about to say when you click devilish dvds it brings you to an amazon link for
horror movie dvd listen i'm gonna read this paragraph to you about the plan of um of
anti-claws because i think you guys might find this a little fascinating on what anti-claws was trying
to do uh-huh unfortunately the devilish dark claws lucked out and found her hidden hat halloween hide
You would have to assume.
yet he would have a jewelry demon
uh... my god i i did find all that there's a recent post
i'm looking at a recent post here
on the halloween blog
the office of jim the vampire
no way
what's what does that say
in an episode of n_b_c_'s the office title business school that flies out of
the office scaring everyone
to white shirt is on the hunt for it amid jim helper making him believe he
was bitten by the bat
the intent was to trick to a into thinking he was turning into a vampire
If this was real, it would need to be a vampire bat, in which case, Jim would have faced a long-lived, yet not immortal future as a Nosferatu variety of vampire.
They are hideously monstrous beasts who can never blend into society, unlike the beautiful vampires who ascend from royal vampire lines.
Those type of vampires don't come from bat bites, but rather a bite from another vampire.
So this is just correcting BJ Novak and what's his name, the guy who plays Toby on their vampire
lore.
I have a very important, okay guys I have a project for us, okay?
Okay.
I think we need to work on it, okay?
We've never been nominated for any kind of award, have we?
No.
But would you guys want one?
I would love one.
And who needs, I don't need a Grammy, I don't need an EGOT, right?
I'd like one. I don't need it. Okay. I think that I need a
Claus Award for excellence in deeds of goodness and bravery.
We the highest honor possible in the supernatural community for
those who walk the path of righteous light. The awesome
award is presented at the North Pole City Banquet by Santa
Claus himself on December 30th. All nominees get the honor of
being the personal guests of st.
Nicholas at his stately Claus Manor such a level of recognition
by the leader of all that is good on earth signifies one's Herculean heroism and serious
sacrifice, a deep dedication in aiding and defending the innocence of the world against
the scourge of paranormal evil.
The Claus Award was conceived by Santa Claus to encourage and motivate people to protect
the world against diabolical darkness while spreading Christmas spirit serenely.
He began giving out this prestigious award in 1742.
So here's some, you guys want to hear some recent winners?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Raj, this is 2011.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Acharya, metaphysical investigation. He's a president in India.
Mystic Investigations, Xavier Remington, president and CEO in Colorado.
2013, Shala, queen of Halloween from Halloween Island.
Why did she give her own? She's evil! She almost created the Antichrist!
Accepted by ZamXuza.
2014, McTavish International Academy of Magical Sciences.
I have this page open and I've been waiting to read this.
the
Okay, including a special-clause lifetime achievement award for Xavier Remington from Mystic Investigations
in Colorado.
Whoa, that's great for Xavier.
I'm on Xavier Remington's blog right now.
In 2015, and then so Xavier won the lifetime achievement award, and then the next year
the award was won by Amazon warrior princess Adonia from the Amazon rainforest Brazil.
In 2016, here comes Xavier again, Mystic Investigations.
So his third award in only five years. He's got a
Hey, he deserves it. He's doing some incredible work
2017 and the 20 so he wins that in the 2017 Cesar Jacobson enchanted human elf
Exemplary aid for the deaf disabled and the empowerment of women around the world
He's from Canada and then the most recent one. I guess they haven't had in a couple years
2018 won by Patriot woman who is a superhero in New York City
I'm looking here on the time trap the mystic investigations time traveler section and there's a
Thing here for the top 10 posts
ever made by the time traveling blog, uh-huh and
Here's one here the future world of Tomorrowland as an Amazon associate we earn qualify if we earn from qualifying purchases
Disney's Tomorrowland the
The fantastical utopian city is seen in Disney's Tomorrowland film won't exist in reality anytime soon. No
That's horrible. Um, I
Have this you know Caleb mentioned briefly the this this school that I think I'm a little interested in and maybe we could try
And figure out how to get a tab at school
Yeah, cuz I found this they have a link to this at the bottom of the mystic investigations
And that's it's a separate website for the McTavish International Academy of Magical Sciences
which it says here is the world's premier magic school, but there isn't much on the website.
It seems like you need a it says welcome professors and students to log into your magic school account.
Please send forth your unique cyber spelled incantation to those not a part of the supernatural
world who found this site. Please keep in mind you will only see only what we want you to see
and what and there's not much on there. So I think what they want us to see is they do have the list
of their graduation commencement speakers. Okay, who do they have? The grand graduation
commencement speakers of the McTavish International Academy of Magical Sciences who address
all classes from elementary to university level. The speech is generally followed by a dazzling
fireworks display as the students head off to summer vacation. Now I'll go, they've only,
it's only been around for three years so I'm going to go from most recent backwards. So 2022
was alchemist Edelweiss Wu from China speaks of his work melding magic and science into one
unenchanted entity for the betterment of humankind. That's
why huge that's big yeah.
Twenty twenty one it was sorceress supreme Elvira winter
of the seminary of supreme sorcery hidden in the German
black forest. The top female magician on earth who used to
who used to serve the forces of darkness. Thankfully, she saw
the light and now fights for all that it's right. That's good.
That is good. That's a big turn around. I mean I would be kind
of pissed off if I got either of these two when I see who the
first commencement speaker was in 2020. Okay. You guys ready for this? I'm ready.
St. Nicholas of North Pole City, who is better known as Santa Claus, the world's
only demi-angel and de facto leader of all good things on earth. Yeah, I mean, of
course you'd be fucking pissed off. I think there's a lot on
this website here. I'm looking, I'm on the, I think that if we separate the
the way that we look at the website in a in a thirds right like one of us gets
Halloween I'm looking at time travel and then one of us looks at Christmas I
think we can cover a lot of ground I just clicked on the the link the name Santa
Claus was linked on the the magical Academy website and I clicked on it it
took me to an article about the story called Santa Claus the story of
Christmas and I'll just read you the first sentence here which I think speaks
volumes about how important Christmas is Christmas is the antithesis of Halloween
13 and dark Christmas.
(Laughter)
Well when is dark Christmas?
Dark Christmas?
(Laughter)
It's, let's see, the 13 nights of dark Christmas
it says.
When is dark Christmas and who is in charge of
dark Christmas?
Have you seen, have you gone to the,
I'm on the Antichrist page.
McTavish International Academy website on mystic investigations.
Have you looked at this?
I, I, it has its own website. I haven't seen it. I just want to read some of the some of the headings here.
Yeah, go ahead. I'm not, there's a lot here. We already know that it's an International Academy of Magical Sciences, right?
Yeah. This is the intro page.
So we have International Academy of Magical Sciences, the building and cloaking of a secret magic school,
application and acceptance to McTavish, student life at McTavish, how to get to the McTavish Academy,
McTavish International Academy of Magical Sciences Mission, Magical School
Curriculum, and then the Loch Ness Monster, the Dungeon Prison in the Sub
Basement, the McTavish Prison for the Criminally Insane.
Wait, wait, look, I want to see.
Pat, I did find out when Dark Christmas was, if you want to know.
Okay.
When is it?
It's 13 nights.
It's December 21st to January 2nd.
They get more, Dark Christmas gets more.
Christmas gets more.
Okay.
McTavish Prison for the Criminally Insane.
Ian McTavish has one of the oldest known paranormal prisons on Earth.
We know it as the McTavish Maximum Security Prison for the Criminally Insane.
The maximum security part was added in the mid-20th century to let everyone know his prison meant business.
It's housed in deep sub-basement caverns of the school.
More seasoned students enjoy scaring new ones by taking them down there to view the monsters in the cells.
There's also that rumored entrance to the underworld.
The students are perfectly safe as the cells are supernaturally sealed shut by magic and
the like.
School above, there is a powerful spell that prevents harm to anyone.
Criminals of sound sentient mind are given a trial based on Magna Carta law.
They can be found not guilty or receive set sentences that allow for release upon competition.
I don't know why it says competition.
I think it means competition.
I think it means that you have to compete for your freedom.
That was accurate.
"Hospitalization takes place via paranormal psychologists and even students at the school
studying the supernatural mind.
Probation sometimes entails working at the school in a useful capacity before final release
into the human world.
Some have even been known to stay with the school for the rest of their days."
So there's a school and then there's a full prison underneath.
Wow.
That has all kinds of devilishly evil monsters just banging on supernatural cages.
That's easy because if someone tries to shoot up the school they can just throw them in
the basement.
I mean, and they gotta be scared of the sorcerer Ian McTavish, a tall, muscular, commanding
figure standing at 6'5" in height.
Even without magic, he would be quite capable of taking down multiple adversaries via his
raw power and immense fighting skills.
He has emerald green eyes that almost seem to glow with power, and often blatantly do
because of the massive metaphysical energies surging through his body and soul.
I have to figure out how to make this work since we're recording remotely, but
the anti-clause page on here is huge. It's gigantic.
I mean, all of these are probably 10,000 words each.
Yeah, I'm looking at an article here.
I know. I'm telling you something important here.
I'm at the bottom of the anti-clause page and they have a link.
they have a they have a sound cloud embedded thing to an eight second sound
called the voice of the anti-claws and if you play it it here you hear the voice
of the anti-claws and I click on it to try and see and I'm on their sound
cloud page they not only do they have the voice of the anti-claws here on
their on their sound cloud page they also have the voice of Santa Claus and
they're all come on and a fucking hey you that's my son he crazy also believe
it they also have the sinister laugh of an evil gnome no I don't want to hear that
dude oh my god I found their Twitter account let me let me uh I found mystic
investigations Twitter I mean these people have so many different oh my god
they still put also 10 top top 10 ways to destroy a vampire we got to come back
to this I think the rest of this week only the next like three episodes were
only going there's so there's another website called galaxy fleet calm Jesus
where they they explore the future what is 5d printing 5d pretty have you 5d
print you guys want to hear the voice of the anti-claws yes yeah I want to hear
all of this
Oh my God, I'm fucking that was that was the voice of the anti Claus.
Here's the voice of Santa Claus.
Oh, Merry Christmas.
Okay,
this is still laugh.
Yes, okay, here we go.
there is
another sound. They posted called scared elf
wait
dude. There's a santa's elf. There's another light to land at
There's a seat in the connection of the National Airport authorizing your landing at runway
11.
He's directing that.
That's Santa's elf directing flight to land at North Pole.
Guys, I may have found a...
What is it?
I may have found the most important one yet.
So I picked out, I don't even remember which website it was, I clicked on a subheading
that was called "Godhoodism" and I clicked on it.
It's a website called godhoodism.com.
Godhoodism, the godhood ascension religion.
Oh my god, yeah, I'm here now.
Be your own lord and savior, attain godhood, amen.
And here are the headings on this website.
Home blog, godhood definitions, pole, universal structure, pure thought power, quantum mind
Mind power, existence cycles, godhood observations, supernatural beings, civilization types, higher
dimensions, related sites, binaural beings.
This website's fucking crazy.
Oh my god.
I can't believe this, dude.
I'm on the Mystic Investigations Facebook page here.
I'm trying to find...
I feel like we need to stay on godhood.
This is a really...
- No, no, no, definitely go look through godhoodism,
but I'm just saying, I'm just looking through here
to see what kind of stuff.
- So what if I'm evil?
- Who follows it and who hosts here?
- We go on the assumption that only reasonably decent people
become gods and that the almighty of all the universes
is the same, so it's a fair bet that if you're evil
and you die, then you're really dead.
You simply don't exist ever again.
We don't believe in hell because there is no crime
that fits such a punishment.
The existence of such a place implies a sadistic nature,
which would be an evil trait for a god.
The removal of your evil waste of space from our reality is justice and punishment enough.
In all fairness, however, even if you're evil in this reality, you might still end
up being good in the majority of parallel universes.
Although we believe that those who commit horrific acts in one reality are most likely
evil in the majority of others, this is due to the power of your spirit overriding the
other two factor that govern your life, environment and genetics.
If your spirit is good, you simply can't commit a horrific acts of evil.
This is crazy.
Wow.
Dude, this website is...
I'm looking at the community for Mystic Investigations Facebook and I'm looking at a post here from
Ruben Munoz Medina who asks, "What would happen if by some reason a vampire was executed in
the electric chair?
Would he survive or die?"
That's a very good question.
Dude, this is...
And Mystic Investigation answers almost immediately and says, "Being electrocuted wouldn't harm
a vampire at all would actually make their dead heart pump during the
electrical surge and they'd feel a rush similar to consuming a large amount of
blood like the lethal injection a smart vampire would play dead and escape from
the morgue later on I cannot believe we went from Santa to godhood is a dude
here the other question here's a god and if they do here is the title of a blog
post on godhood ism is unfortunately all children die and then there's a picture
of a cute baby. Here's more of the FAQ. Is God evil? Do aliens exist and do they
become gods? Do I have a soulmate? I have a big ego or I like riddles. That could
mean anything. So can I create a religion for my people? Can I not just hide and be
with my people? Can I create magical realities where supernatural beings
really exist? So the answer to this is knock yourself out, create magic,
fairies, genies, vampires, werewolves, Santa Claus, and leprechauns as well while
you're at it. So won't being God get boring eventually? Why does God allow bad
things to happen? Do you have a holy book? Do you have church service? And do you
accept donations? And they say no. So this is a religion that
basically says that you are God or you can become a God at the very least.
There's stuff about quantum jumping and like... Yeah I just tried to... they have a
poll on their website which is a... you can vote in a poll and give you give them an
opinion on their religion and I tried to vote that yes it's the perfect religion
that makes sense and I got an alert from Google that says this information you're
about to submit is not secure. So we have we have all the I'm scrolling through
all these blog posts we have all this stuff about like how to quantum jump you
know how to ascend to godhood what is the root of all mental illness and then we
got another post right here that I'm seeing it says Dr. Benjamin S Carson
speaks common sense at national prayer breakfast that's yes
various ideals that flew in the face of president obama's agenda eight
they said they want that one of the authors on god is it is just named god
well the from guiding shit here
he i'm looking at uh... some visitors posts on the on the mystic investigations
page still
lot of pictures from one guy
but also
Obina Nuasu asks a lot of things.
"How do you access the pure thought foundation of reality?
"What powers do travelers possess?
"Is Azazel an actual demon or an archdemon?
"What are the powers of Slender Man?"
- Slender Man's in on this? (laughing)
Oh wait, I opened a tab and I forgot about it.
- Here's one more. - Hold up, hold up.
- Here's one from Obina again, I'll read this last one.
"Has anyone ever heard of the anti-Halloween spirit?
I got psychic echo that sort of told me about it.
I want here I'm going to send you guys this link because I think this is a page that we
all need to be looking at on mystic investigations.
I forgot to bring up before this is a list.
Every episode of the podcast is about this now.
This is this is this is honestly I can't.
This is this is a mystic investigations.
This is their their encyclopedia.
This is the known list of supernatural beings and they have categories here.
Halloween beings, Christmas beings, horror legends, superheroes, super villains,
righteous royalty, dark royalty, and here I'll just read the A section
because this will give you an idea of what we're working with here, okay?
There's so many of them, we can't go through all of them, but here we go.
I just want to note on every single page on Mystic Investigations,
there is a disclaimer or I don't know what to call it,
every single title of every single web
page it says as an Amazon associate we
earn from qualifying purchase that's
good that's just good practice yeah
yeah I'm gonna read a and B here cuz I
think this is a perfect lineup of
supernatural beings I'll just run
through a lightning-round style
abominable snowman adirondack
abomination Amazon's angel in angels
guardian angels angel demon hybrid angel
goddess hybrid Antichrist anti-claws
was April antifool April fool our arch vampires Arctic abomination Asian
sprites or I rinse nymphs autumn nymphs baby new year baby spring Bigfoot
black stick Ben Slenderman assassin blue lady boar hog Moosey sin blob monster
bloodbather and bogeyman there's an antifool there's an April I had no
fucking clue single name, every single name I'm reading is like a link by the
way, like everything is like a piney associate me about the antisocial many
paragraphs. I didn't know that was a fool in the April antifool warning April
second is anti April fools day and with it comes the evil mischief of the April
antico aka the chief nemesis of the April fool who blesses us with
humiliating, yes, hum let yet humorously harmless hijinks on April fools day. All
of the two are enemies. They are temporarily separated in a four
manner confined to their respective days which from their perspective last one
whole year. Unlike the April Fool, the Anti-Fool can be very dangerous in
nature and his so-called pranks can be extremely dangerous and diabolical. The
Anti-Fool has equivalent magical powers including mind control and enhanced
superhuman abilities like the Fool. The Anti-Fool wears a black and white
jester's costume complete with magical scepter that has a skull at the top. He
also wears a skull mask to hide his identity along with being an
intimidation tool. Unlike the Fool whose powers are truly imbued within him, the
antifool derives his powers from his scepter so taking it away we'll turn him
into a normal evil human dude I had no fucking clue there was an antifool or a
fool and in contrast to the April Fool who is powered by the Norse trickster
God Loki we have no clue where the antifool came from I'm looking here at
a there's a section at the top of the page for omniverse personifiers mm-hmm
And there's obviously, you know, like light, darkness,
There's a dark Cupid.
Light, darkness, life, death, karma, fate, destiny, that's all one thing.
Love, luck, fortune, chance, all one section.
Hate, the four horsemen, the sandman, and Jack Frost.
Jack Frost. We need to defeat Jack Cross.
Jack Frost.
There's an evil version of Valentine's Day. There's an anti-every fucking holiday.
Yeah. I cannot believe this. Did you know Baby New Year and Father Time are the same guy?
Why do they not teach you any of this in school? I know. This is way more important than like...
I honestly just can't fucking believe it. So I guess there's a difference between an
Easter Bunny and an Easter Spirit as well, I'm seeing here.
There's also... What the fuck? Frankensteins, Friday 13th Demon Specter, Frosty the Snowman,
fuzzy monsters gargoyles and gargoyle mancers.
Yo, the Grinch is real.
The Grinch is real.
Is there an anti-Grinch?
Is the Grinch real?
Yes, would you believe the Grinch is a real supernatural being?
However, his story was greatly simplified by the infamous author,
Dr. Seuss.
The infamous Dr. Seuss.
In reality, the Green Grinch was a gnome helper of the Anticlaws.
Really?
so you're not going to do that is specifically said the green grants to
to say anything about roast beast juries and i'm rich
control f roast beast here
now i'm not seeing anything let me see the comments who bill that to find out
that that's made up this kind of a
i mean i think it was i think it's doctor seuss is fault i mean that guys
totally wackadoodle
the future foretold from galaxy fleet well here we go nation
i here's what happened with his a really happen with the grinch
The infamous aforementioned anti-Klaus coup attempt by the Grinch took place in December of 1952.
Dr. Seuss knew of the story since he had been lucky enough to visit Santa's North Pole City in that same year.
It seems Seuss had been secretly abducted by aliens and taken to a planet similar to what he eventually described
to an extent in 1971's The Lorax.
A number of his crazy characters and silly stories came from his short time on the unknown extraterrestrial planet.
He also had disturbing visions of a second alien abduction.
The E.T.'s brought him back with other brainwashed abductees as a part of a
master plan to conquer Earth.
Santa Claus intervened when he happened upon the extraterrestrial vessel.
Not only did he save Dr. Seuss, but the entire planet as well, by sending the
aliens back through an intergalactic super cluster portal
that transported them here.
And they destroyed the technology to create portals on their home world. That's huge.
So Godheadism has a shop page, but it's completely empty. There's nothing there.
That's good. It's about advancing yourself, not spending money.
Oh, that's kind of on the verge.
So I was going down the list of known monsters.
And there's one in the T section.
And these all have to be made by the same guy also, right?
It's Xavier Remington.
This is the stool.
What is the stool?
We hesitate to even mention this particular paranormal phenomenon
since it's by far the most disgusting we've ever come across.
It is an excremental entity known as the stool.
The creature of crap is caused by all manner of fecal matter, randomly coalescing into
a sentient blob.
Although a rare event is clearly a health hazard that the government often deals with
and covers up in the media as well.
If the stool is left unchecked, it will grow into the giant pile of poop as seen in photos
on this page.
The stench is unbearable to the point of causing mass barfing episodes, even among those with
protective masks on.
The high levels of methane it gives off drive away oxygen, therefore causing asphyxiation
in humans and other creatures.
This is often a concern in sewers, which is the place this despicable entity forms the
most.
Wow.
Did you know there's such a thing as human-leprechaun hybrids?
Yes, you're looking at one.
I know, I have it paged up right here.
It sounds very similar.
It says, "Whoa, apparently Keanu Reeves is one."
What?
That makes sense.
That's what it says here.
Oh my God, dude.
I'm finding Xavier Remington clearly has a bunch of different Twitter accounts.
He has one at Santa Claus at North underscore Pole underscore City where he's saying, "Why
on earth has @readersgazette blocked Santa Claus?
I will have to tell my friends at Metaphysical Private Investigations about this injustice."
[laughter]
"Supernatural Investigations Firm fighting paranormal forces of darkness in a metaphysical
quest for justice."
Are there any zombies at North Pole City?
What is a reverse ghost?
Is Chucky the Child's Play doll real?
I did see they say that Jason Voorhees is real.
And then the first thing is Jabba's.
What are supernatural Jabbas?
the superhuman jackpot with a ground zero nuclear blast wait what
Pat's shit froze up Oh he's completely gone dude they're trying to shut us down
is Paul Bunyan real he is in fact real he is a Nephilim which is the offspring of
a fallen angel and a human dude they're trying to look Pat's he's not even
talking dude they're trying to take us down they're silencing us they're trying
I won't be silenced.
I tried to talk about a Jabba and I got completely silenced.
I know.
It's fucking crazy.
Who is the plague doctor?
Oh my god.
Tooth Fairy Laws.
Jabba's are paranormal monsters named after the infamous Star Wars character Jabba the
Hut.
These are relatively new cryptids that first began to appear in the 50s and were merely
classified as large-scale cannibalistic shapeshifters for a time until given the
name Jabba in the mid 80s. Wait so there's Christ, there's an
Antichrist and then there's also a neutral Christ. Will there be a neutral
Christ upon our earth? Yes indeed the Vatican and other Christian religious
authorities have suppressed a missing biblical chapter called the destiny of
mankind that would have told the tale of the so-called neutral Christ would have
saved humankind from a damned ending in Armageddon, while ushering in an eternity of enlightenment
for humankind.
Interestingly, it is also written that the Neutral Christ will be the Judas of the Antichrist.
We know that the Antichrist was born in spring of 2015, but no word yet on whether the Neutral
Christ has been born or already exists.
I'm reading that, I'm reading that, the Antichrist's birth during the spring solar eclipse of 20...
Bro, what are we doing? He's 77 years old!
Ever since the first battle of Armageddon on Halloween 2013, the devil has been on Earth in biological form,
ousted from Hell by the diabolical sorcerer, Timitri Diablo.
I did read about the first battle of Armageddon. According to Xavier, it took place in Kazakhstan.
2013 wow I like this website is so
incredible every article every article is
a meet you Diablo's now the king of hell
once again is a question and every
answer is always yes it's yeah perfect
Liz I also I have really good news for
you guys that I'm reading in this
article right here apparently tooth
fairies enjoy profit and power yet still
care about kids Wow and that's really
good news to hear at least dig for a
The greatest sorcerer known to fight against evil, Ian McTavish, there he is again 6'5" by the way,
led the charge to neutralize what turned out to be a cloaking spell as the Halloween Witching Hour approached.
This is all the Battle of Armageddon from 2013.
The- oh, I mean here he is.
The Great Claws immediately whisked the innocent human sacrifices away into his holy portal powered by the Star of Bethlehem.
Wow, dude, everybody was here.
Claws, anti-claws, Xavier Remington, oh my god, Mystic Investigations, Xavier Remington wielding
the Sword of Judgment let forth a battle cry as he came at the anti-claws which forced him
to remove the flaming sword from Santa's heart.
Santa was clearly weakened and stumbled into his portal which promptly closed.
Remington, a human, valiantly engaged in an epic sword fight with the demi-demon claws
but the supernatural being was quite powerful.
Oh my fucking god dude.
Xavier saved the world.
Now I get why he got so many awards.
Of course, yeah.
He got his first one in 2013.
Oh my god.
That makes perfect sense.
Of course.
And then he got his lifetime achievement in 2015 and got another one in 2017.
I found the first article on here.
Wait, wait, guys, guys.
Did Xavier Remington have a kid in 2015?
I don't, I mean, does it say that?
that. I mean I do some research. I have to do I have to sorry I got so
distracted. I have to do more research.
He was definitely birthed during the first battle of Armageddon. I found the
first article on this website that I found so far where the answer to is this
real is no.
You want to know what it is? Yeah, what is it are the Twilight vampires real?
Thank God the Twilight vampires are not real.
But it says that if they were real, they will be fairy vampires, not normal
vampires of course yeah I mean there is so many is the chicken nuggets werewolf
what the king of God's zoo saves a woman by nearly striking her with lightning
Christian Bale thanks the devil who made him famous what holy shit the real
Freddy Krueger was a man named Sylvester Hawthorne however I have to see
nightmare on Elm Street movie debuted Hawthorne decided to rename himself
himself, Freddy Krueger.
I have to see the Chicken Nuggets Werewolf.
Yeah, what's the Chicken Nuggets Werewolf?
What's the Chicken Nuggets Werewolf?
It's a video of a person who looked like a werewolf, I guess.
Werewolf exposed, alcohol intoxication used to cover up the werewolf, and then the brave
member of the paranormal community.
This wacky woman was known to be a member of a werewolf pack who taught her how to control
herself, yet she was still a novice and gave in to her demonic DNA rather than letting
the righteousness of the Yule Moon guide her.
werewolves face fighting the urges of this DNA while in human form at present
she has mellowed and accepted the responsibility of the power she wields
she works bravely with the supernatural community to fight the forces of
darkness while saving many innocent lives don't judge her by this one
incident so she attacked a McDonald's worker because of the chicken nuggets
this one is actually kind of this one's scary I love this they're all scary this
This I mean a lot this one this is the scariest one. I think who is the blood
bather the blood is a monstrous immortal shapeshifter killing machine composed of
the blood of virtually every species on Earth. It is the physical
personification of blood in our world blood representing both the gift of life
and the loss of death loss of death the blood bather rose from the spilled blood
of mass extinction two hundred and fifty two point two eight million years ago
during the Permian Triassic extinction event.
- This is crazy. - Wow.
- The bloodbather is the first and only of its kind.
The master shapeshifter of molded blood.
- There's so many categories. - It's invincible.
Oh, and it was last seen in Florida.
- No way.
- Please no.
- They have an MP3 recording of it.
- I need to hear it.
- This one's not on SoundCloud,
so I can't play it from my phone.
- Send it, send it to me.
Oh, it's scary, but the, it's very scary, but also the bloodbather, I would say, needs to upgrade their microphone a little bit, maybe.
There's something called a were-zombie.
A were-zombie?
It's a common misconception that a were-zombie is a werewolf-zombie hybrid.
In most cases, the werewolf virus trumps the zombie virus, so such a creature won't exist.
However, a fresh zombie created from a live human could become a zombie-werewolf hybrid for the remainder of the full moon night it was bitten.
This is an extremely temporary creature.
Who is the Cringe?
The Cringe?
Who's that?
The Cringe loves posing as a creepy clown.
There is one man on earth who is the complete embodiment of instilling a deeply disturbing
feeling within all who lay eyes upon him.
He is only known as the Cringe.
Some say he resembles Pennywise the clown from the movie IT, although Pennywise looks
like a charming bachelor compared to the cringe.
I cannot, I, we need to get in contact with.
The first, it's getting me so good every, every, every article starting just with yes,
100% is incredible.
I'm loving this so much just to be able to see a post that says, does, does silver hurt
vampires and I'm thinking to myself, no, that's a werewolf thing.
And then clicking on it, it says, yes, 100% pure silver is a kryptonite of sort for vampires.
Dude, they have so many employees.
This is a list of all their employees.
The expert executive team at Mystic Investigation specializes in subduing sinister supernatural
threats to common individuals and the world at large.
President Xavier Remington.
Executive Vice President Drake Alexander.
Senior Vice President Rebecca Abernathy.
Vice President Psychic Julia Hathaway.
Ghostbuster Robert Edmonds.
Psychozoologist Ashley Abercrombie. Supernatural technologist Zachariah Powers.
Soldier Hunter Jackson. Investigator Elizabeth Weatherly. Research assistant
Seth Morgan, parentheses, part-time. Receptionist Barbara Gerber. Michael Remington, parentheses,
currently lost in time somewhere. And then they have independent contractors including
Father Thomas Davis and Alexander Remington who's the founder of Godhoodism
Religion and also acts as the website widget designer and coordinator.
And then Penny Summers is in the mailroom. Wait I need to know about this
guy's lost in time yeah on okay wait first let's read about Barbara Gerber
she's a secretary she's 47 took over as the new receptionist in early 2011 Barb
has previous experience working in the paranormal investigation field so
hopefully we don't have to worry about being scared away like the last
receptionist was and then here's Michael Remington code name traveler corporate
title senior vice president CTO 25% shareholder corporate technologist
Supernatural ID, human.
Areas of expertise, technology, time travel, history,
inventing, treasure hunting, science,
Kung Fu, parentheses, black belt,
and martial arts weaponry.
He has a pilot's license for small jets and helicopters.
Lineage, human.
Although during recent genealogical research,
there was some minor evidence that his great, great,
great, great grandfather may have been a traveler.
He was born on the magical island
of Washington Island, Wisconsin.
(both laughing)
Powers, so this is Xavier's brother.
powers time travel through technology he invented age 25 residents Michael still
has a room at minute Remington Manor and a laboratory in the basement near
Rebecca Abernathy's witches lair this that is where he stays when he returns
to our time in Woodland Springs he also maintains a time time museum slash home
a million years in the future in what he calls the million years manner
additional notes he's rarely around and is often gone for many months at a time
temporarily traveling he wants to age with us so he doesn't return to the
instant he left our time. Also due to time travel causing one to be pushed to
parallel universes there's no way to change events in our timeline of origin
unless it is predestined. Therefore we don't use time travel as a methods to
right or wrong. Michael simply loved history and invented time travel to
explore it. Although his past explorations can sometimes give us the
answers we seek, since he isn't around on a regular basis, Assistant CTO Zach Powers
stands in as acting CEO. Wow! And he has a blog. This is crazy. He's a time traveler.
Yeah. I'm looking here. I see a disclaimer notice here. Sure. Oh, wait, no, I shouldn't read it.
Why? It's required under the Supernatural Secrecy Pact of 33 AD. Oh, yeah. You don't want to violate
that so I'm not so Xavier Remington I definitely shouldn't Xavier Remington
you know I mean we all we all don't love him for of course laying the anti-claws
winning several awards keeping us updated he's also an author Wow he wrote
one book on Amazon called the Demi Mermaid witch and the strawberry fairy a
paranormal adventure and now this book sounds really fascinating here's the
here's the blurb here about this book as the full June strawberry moon approaches
a fiendish fairymancer is after the human mermaid hybrid witch Rebecca Abernathy
and her little friend a strawberry fairy named Red. Together they fight and evade
the dark magician as they make their way to Red's nature nymph ascension ceremony.
It is the fairymancer's hope to crash this paranormal party and siphon all the
nature deities powers including the Roman fruit goddess Pomona. His twisted
plan even involves the archdemon the devil himself along with his newly born
for an antichrist child. Now this
sounds like a an epic romp right
a yeah, I'd love to read a
saga like this and it's in fact
it's all it's it's 18 pages
long. Oh wow yeah, I have to
full pages of still have to
possibly dive into that at
some point. I mean there's so
much here dude. I mean I we
have to get in contact with
Xavier. I would love to do
anything for the team. I
didn't realize it's so many
people working on this project
over at mystic investigation.
we work freelance. Yeah I mean Barbara even I would even if Barbara Gerber the
current receptionist is 47 years old been there since 2011 if she wants to I don't
know move up the ladder a little bit I'd be more than happy to take her spot as
the receptionist at Mystic Investigations. Yeah. Right? I do want to
learn about the vice executive vice president. I would look at you like a
treasurer. So I've actually changed my mind because the executive vice
president and chief vampirologist who's a 25% shareholder in the business by the
way his secretary is Mrs. Finch he is a vampire and I'm not sure that I could
basically be a co-worker of a vampire especially work for a vampire. Wait are
you serious? Especially knowing that he recently suffered complete amnesia to
the point of not even exhibiting the symptoms of being a vampire there
by proving the power of mind over matter the amnesia occurred when he was
literally blown up along with an alien vessel somewhere in the high altitude
skies over Kentucky. His vampire mother and headduana helped him regain his
memories of the past centuries. Yeah and he's 742 and he's worth 325 million
dollars. Oh. His vehicle's a silver Aston Martin v12 vanquish. That's pretty cool.
yeah so i i have i got the the free sample i sent the free sample of this
book to my kindle here okay um and oh my god
well so the the free sample i guess i the i would say this is about six pages of
of prologue and and disclaimer so okay so here i'll just read the prologue here to
to kind of set the scene for anyone who wants to buy this book, which I would recommend to
go out and do.
Of course.
The story takes place on the evening of June 2, 2015, toward the witching hour of June 3,
2015, during the full strawberry moon and the continuity of our Supernatural blog revolving
around the adventures of Mystic Investigations, a paranormal crime-fighting firm battling
the forces of supernatural darkness.
The unusual firm is based in a town teeming with paranormal life called Woodland Springs
in the great state of Colorado.
The main character is mystic investigations resident human mermaid hybrid, aka Demi-mermaid,
senior vice president Rebecca Abernathy.
She is also a top flight wielder of witchcraft.
The story involves Rebecca aiding a fairy in her escape from a fairymancer.
A fairymancer is a type of magical practitioner who has the power to mystically manipulate
fairies and absorb their power for their own nefarious ends.
There is mention of the devil himself along with his newborn antichrist child, which is
a part of a greater storyline.
He came to be trapped in human form on earth during the first battle of
Armageddon on Halloween 2013.
If you remember that.
And eventually fathered the antichrist in March 2015.
And this story also, it still has, you know how everything on the website has
links?
The book has links too.
Oh my god.
Wow.
I would like to really quickly, just before we end, and I think we will be
coming back here, dipping back into this world.
Oh I'm certain.
I would really like to, I would really really like to read just a couple of
post from Xavier Remington from his Twitter.
Yeah.
So here's one. I'm hearing an odd sound coming from the supply
closet. Dot dot dot. Ah, my executive VP vampire and our
psychic just came out of there together. Dot dot dot. Lol. Is
it odd that I was at the hashtag McDonald's drive through one hour
ago in a hashtag Lamborghini. I promise I only eat it once a
month. Moon at 97% full. Expect heavy werewolf activity tonight. Have your
silver bullets locked and loaded for the non-violent dog whistles.
There's a couple more. Today we're searching for the leprechaun who brought
us good luck over the past week. And I just, this is big, so he's making big money
moves okay the CEO all right well here I'll read this one first me and the
me and Rebecca just nabbed the ice cream truck serial killer last night and sent
his demonic master back to hell but again so he's a CEO he's a businessman right I
just had okay get this I just had lunch with the president of zombie Corp to
discuss a future partnership to deal with the growing number of zombies.
So, zombie-coding is getting pretty involved.
That's huge.
Rebecca, who I often call cutesy, is skinny-dipping in the pool at our mansion on the edge of
the enchanted forest, and I'm joining her now.
I mean there's just holy that is the life of a CEO right there have a multi-clause award-winning
Yeah world savior first tweet ever enjoying a sunrise breakfast with Rebecca after the hellish fight with the poltergeist on Friday the 13th
God okay, all right, I mean, I'm this is all doing the rest. Yeah, I think I we also yeah
we'll check back in. Because there's top 10 lists on this website. Well we're
100% checking back in with Xavier's Mystic Investigations.
But I think that's it for now. I think guys we have to say that's it for now
and we have to say you guys seriously have to subscribe to our patreon for
crazy ass bullshit. We'll say that we will be doing something on the
Patreon with this world. I think very soon. Yeah, I don't know what it is. I have some ideas. Yeah
Okay. Bye
[BLANK_AUDIO]