- Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Crap monster.
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Go.
- Okay, I'm going.
- Okay, go.
- Um, there was a--
- Go.
- Okay, I'm trying to go.
I'm trying to go right now.
- Faster.
- Okay, there was a guy.
That's just higher.
- There was--
- There was a--
I'm just re-correcting.
- Faster.
- There was a guy--
- You're pitched.
- Why, why, why, why am I?
- Musically.
- Every time I shit, for some reason,
I can't just enjoy my shit and I have to read something,
so sometimes I read the ingredients on the shampoo bottle.
- True as fuck.
- Isn't that true?
- That could be a good rage comic.
- That would be a good ass rage comic.
- Why is that though?
Why is shitting just not enough for people
to just take a shit?
- 'Cause it's, I don't even wanna think about poop.
but it hurts so bad.
- I don't even want to think about it.
- It's completely hot.
- It's one of those things where--
- You're struggling, like why do you need distraction?
- It's like muscle memory to poop, right?
And if you focus on it, you get all in your head
and you fuck it up.
The poop can go back up.
- The poop goes sideways and shit.
- Yeah, 'cause something weird can happen.
- You ever been holding a shit in
and then you take a shit
and it feels like it fell out of you sideways?
- No. - Yeah.
- No, I know what you're talking about.
- Yeah, he knows what I'm talking about.
- I don't know if I know what you're talking about.
There's a couple of shit, I just have shit questions, honestly. I have a lot of shit
questions. What is it about, I can tell that I need to poop, but I won't be able
to poop until I have a sip of coffee and it doesn't even hit my stomach. I just
need to have it in my mouth. I think my gut biome is probably very disgusting.
The biome? Yeah. I think you have like acid rain in your biome and your gut. I
feel like most gut biomes are really disgusting. It's all gross. I
I think that my gut biome looks like the lower level of Coruscant.
Yeah, I think that most people have bacteria and stuff.
I think you have macroscopic animals.
You can see them with your eyes.
I think I have a bug that walks around.
You have a lot of bugs.
It looks like the other world from Half-Life.
Whatever it's called. The other dimension.
Yeah, yeah.
The Vorgonauts.
Vortigaunts.
pronounced. Have either of you even played Half-Life? I played some of Half-Life. I beat
Half-Life 2 episode 2. You guys need to play the VR of your Half-Life. Yeah. Oh yeah? Yeah.
Because you can actually grab a trash can and you can throw it as hard as you can. Really?
You can do that with a gravity gun. No but you actually use your hands to do it in Half-Life
Alyx. That's way less cool than a gravity gun. Can both of you just get into virtual
reality and we could just be. Why don't you buy me one? Why don't you buy me a VR headset?
Yeah, why don't you buy me one?
I'll do that for you.
I'd gladly do that for you. But I know he's gonna break it.
Yeah, he's gonna do something.
He's gonna use it for weird stuff.
Yeah, you're gonna use it for porn. VR porn, by the way.
It's too low quality.
It's like 480p video.
Yeah.
And also, you look around, you see the GoPro where your dick is supposed to be.
Yeah, you can see the GoPro and then you can
probably just see like how
disgusting the room that they're filming it in is.
Can you look in the mirror?
you can do anything you want. I guess it's not like a game it's a video. You can't
move around. It should be a VR porn where you can move around and you actually feel.
That's not VR that's just a like that's like a movie
screen that's 360 degrees. That shouldn't count as virtual reality.
It's not immersive. Unless there's like inputs I can put in.
They should just add on top of VR porn, just add like hands like
bad like low poly like arms and hands so I can just wave my hands around.
It should be yeah it should be it should be exactly like super hot it should be
yeah every time you move super hot yeah you come and she explodes.
Super hot super hot and then it plays it back really fast. You should play as the girl and you have to
dodge the cum or you explode because that's the fun part of or you that could be the multiplayer.
You dodge squirt like you got to look in this like vr porn room and it's just like one of those rooms
like pink room, pink walls with white carpet, and you can see a stain in the
carpet from when they filmed before. Yeah, that is how a lot of it feels. Yeah.
Yeah, you look around, it's like a model home. You know, it's like
not a real house. You walk by a bathroom and it's completely unfinished. There's no tile or
toilet. Yeah. You know, it should be like, it should be a whole MMO
type thing. There's a hub world. You can go to different raids, which are the
different sex scenes right and and you can like their cosmetics you can sell
like maybe I could like trade a cosmetic of like a three-inch penis for someone
is giving me a cosmetic of like dirt caked under the fingernails definitely
yeah yeah no that's a great porn VR how disgusting yeah yeah I want him to be
balding yes yeah I would like to 400 400 GP for stomach acne but you can't
can't fuck other people in the game. You can only fuck the...
You can tag team with other people.
It's all PVE.
Yeah, exactly.
That's a really smart idea.
I think that that could be huge.
I would really like to get into...
World of sex craft.
Yeah, sex of girl craft.
He's playing Pokemon Go while we record in this lab and he thinks that we won't notice.
I have to get a streak.
You have to get a streak?
Yeah.
I would like to see you streak.
You know what we're doing?
I'm going to get a streak.
hour of the day where you could work on this?
- Yeah, you'd love to--
- No, it was gonna reset.
- It resets at, what is it, 3.30?
- 3.40.
- Well, I did it around like four yesterday.
- I don't think--
- So it's a 24-hour timer.
- I don't think it's 24 to 24.
That makes no sense.
- All right, well--
- 'Cause then you just--
- What if you did it an hour before every day or something?
- I don't know.
- You could've done it beforehand.
- I could've, yeah.
- I don't think that makes any sense.
I think that we should get into game development, though.
we've been talking about that a lot.
Woman go, that's the like the mobile version of world sex.
- And also you can actually scan in women
that you see on the street and then capture them digitally.
Man, would you also know why I do a 360
around you really quick?
I'm a street photographer.
Last night, I was leaving the bar
and somebody took a picture of me.
Some random guy took like a picture of me.
I was like, what?
And I was like, what the fuck are you doing?
And he was like, I'm a street photographer.
And I don't know why that, I was like, okay.
And then he just left.
you ask him for you was a new into a flash photo of me yeah yeah on his phone
no on a with a DSLR I was like what the fuck are you doing yeah I hate when I
see people doing my shit and I told him that's my violation and you're losing on
film was it like why are you obsessed with the camera I don't know it was just
as you could have asked him you could have asked him in that moment to delete
the photo. It's not that honestly I'm with Caleb and that that I feel like him
had to me less about him had the photo existing and more about him taking a
picture. I more like wanted to fight the guy. I didn't because if that guy took a
picture of me and I didn't know that's I'm not I wouldn't yeah I wouldn't know
it wouldn't matter. And also he used a flash and it was like there was this light. I wouldn't even notice
if he didn't I was like sitting there waiting for an uber and I just got a
flash in my face. I was like, "I'm gonna fucking kill this guy."
It's okay to take a picture of someone from behind.
Yeah. On the street.
If you take a picture from very far away with like a very
big lens, that's fine.
I'm so bad at taking stealth
photos of people. I'm really good at
taking stealth photos of people. I'm really, really, really bad.
I bet you have a lot of practice at that.
I have a lot of stealth photos I've taken of you.
I tried to take a photo
of a guy who was a barista
the other day because he looked like somebody
that we know and I just couldn't get a photo
of them. I just got too nervous every time I pulled my phone.
The thing is, 90% of the time it's not worth it.
Yeah, it wasn't worth it. 90% of the stealth photos I've taken are like him in the bathroom
or like him. And the other 10% is where he just puts up... The first show we did on tour,
I was taking a shit and he just popped his phone on top of the stall. Oh yeah.
He just took a photo of me taking a shit. I forgot about that.
Like five minutes before the show started. Yeah, I forgot we did that and then I have a photo
before my my point-and-shoot broke just a photo of you in a wah-wah bathroom just
pissing yep he thinks that's funny it is funny you realize you could go to
pre-realize that's why dr. disrespect was banned from twitch really yeah because
he brought a camera into a picture of Caleb peeing yeah you get in trouble for
taking cameras into the bathroom really I'm for real it's fucking illegal no
really yes yeah it's fucking illegal that's illegal that explains a lot then
Brandon yeah explains a lot thanks Brandon I don't think Brandon had
anything to do with it I think Brandon actually is Brandon is fighting against
yeah just stop it so you're pro Brandon now I mean if honestly if he makes it
completely legal to take pictures of people shitting and wiping their butts
and yeah yeah here it is that's a really nice photo that's that's cute yeah yeah
that's really cool that's taking a portrait 400 the fucking portrait body
That's what I was being in can we go back to our game develop another guy that's
a guy being on the street you should do oh that would be so awesome to a whole
series of guys peeing yeah I really really fucking like that and then and
then this is I think this is Pierce also peeing yes you're snorting like a pig
and then that's Cameron peeing don't stop not Cameron penis Cameron sitting in a
car get your hands out of your pants while you're showing these pictures.
Okay, okay, yeah, this is no this is Pierce. I think this is Pierce pooping. That
looks like a poop to me. Yeah, that does look like it's not enough of his body to
actually tell, but I bet he's right at the like the bar for old people and
handicapped people to sit down on the toilet. So yeah, he's about there. That
bar is also for sitting down if you want to do a trick shot. Definitely. From above
off the toilet. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And that's Neil. He's not peeing though. No, it's just
Neil. Can you stop showing us photos? Can we get back to developing? Because I have a
game development. These photos got developed. First of all, Women Go was great. Yeah, I
would like to add to Women Go. Yeah, okay. So we were talking about you can take a picture
of a woman on the street, scan it in to become part of your team that they fight against
each other with Pokemon. Mud Wrestler. Yeah, that's one option. It depends on the gym you
go to okay but so do you remember there was that game that was I think for like I
don't remember if it was game GameCube or it might have been PlayStation it was
like Monster Rancher or something where you could put a CD in and it would uh it
would scan it and make a monster out of the like just did like metadata on the
CD like like
super not yeah that like Skylanders so it's like that or not where instead of
putting like a random CD that you own but you can get that like the credit
card reader for your phone, and if you swipe a woman's credit card on your
phone, it like puts her into your game. That's smart, because women are basically...
Because from the credit card bill, you can also basically devise all her
stats. Also, women are basically... yeah, they're basically... women are just
what they buy with their credit card, and then what they look like. So
we can get pretty much with the scanning technology, that is my idea, and the
credit card idea, that is your idea, we have an entire woman can be completely
digitized, and then Patrick basically hasn't worked on this at all and did
nothing yeah so that's who will be cutting them out of the property and I
think about this this better be a good feature the theme song is like it's a
game not a show that's football huh that's a football theme song now here's
another so I think that I think that what we can what we can do here I think
that the most the best part of this game is going to be the peripheral so you can
buy to connect to your phone that you can use to play it so we got we have
maybe a bit really big telescopic lens so you can attach to scan the women from a
distance and then of course the credit card reader and then maybe the top of
the line roller shaped like boobs that one's important to will definitely have
a control it's already a mobile game you come up with some actual good I have you
okay like no listen all plus like the pokeball plus for Pokemon goes at the
top of the line the the most expensive peripheral you can buy that we will sell
make a lot of money off of is a one is a really big 3d printer and after you've
scanned the women into the game you can print her and have your own version of her in real
life.
That's really smart.
Subclasses of woman.
That's really fucking smart.
That's just a thing in real life.
Electric type.
We can scan women on the street.
And also another thing we can do.
You can connect the duck hunt gun.
Yes, so you can shoot them.
Another thing you can do is we'll get a hula hoop and we'll surround it with iPhones and
and we'll walk up to women and be like hey, we're
we're from like a hula hoop youtube channel. You should and we do street
hula hoops. See how many hula you can hoop and then they'll actually just
scan themselves yeah by doing the hula. Well, you know you don't even really
need the who all honestly all you can do is excuse me. Would you take a selfie
of yourself? Yeah, most about most women say, guys, size power ups for the women
like diet coke
yeah yeah okay handbag handbag yeah and what would we throw what do you throw to
catch him you think a flasso Lou batons no just a lasso okay like a last idea a
lasso and now a butterfly net a pokeball yeah yeah any of that works well a rock
but we need well sometimes it'll be hard to catch one so then you can dangle
things in front of them like a $10 bill yeah yeah yeah we need also more
Starbucks gift card. I think peripherals are what's gonna sell this game.
Definitely diet coke is a thing that you can use as a power-up. Haptic gloves.
Haptic gloves. Haptic gloves are gonna be huge. Haptic shoes. Haptic shoes, haptic knee pads, and a haptic head.
Nose, nasal inserts so you can smell the women when they're on screen. A haptic like
like lip cover. It should be an entire haptic suit. And kiss all the parts of their bodies.
It's an entire haptic suit. It looks exactly like the still suit from Dune
that they wear when they go in the desert. Okay, you can feel the touch all over
your body and the the little tubes that go into your nose. They pipe in the musk
and the I don't even want to say what types of smells but I think we all know
crevice smells. Yeah, the smell of the crevice. Yeah, the crack gashel aroma, the
butt crack, a piped in poop, the pipe odor, odor, she I'm still thinking of the lures.
Here's how we make money on this. Shein Coupon. 30% off at Shein. What's Shein?
It's a website where women buy clothes for $3. That's funny Pat. I just held up my phone
with "woman go" and scanned you and it actually added you to my game. You must be a registered
woman. You know a lot about women and it seems like my phone is detecting you as one. I know
a lot about women. Is that what you're saying? Yeah, because you are a woman. Takes one to
no one when it comes to women that is I've watched that movie with Mel Gibson.
Oh my god and I'm rubbing your crotch on my phone and you're coming. You're
turning red and your eyes are rolling back into your head. That's coming from
his phone not Patrick by the way listeners. I think that another thing we
can do is okay and I'm exporting a gif of this and posting it to reddit. That's
it's going to be next level. The other thing that we could do is a way to make
money on it is it's a free app, but then for 99 cents it adds coins feet to the
well okay. No feet. They float around. They have like chopstick legs. Yeah,
like tentacle. Yeah, yeah, yeah, something disgusting. Not tentacles,
something because that's serving another audience. You have to pay even more for
that. I just think that the feet are going to be the thing. We rope everybody
It's like, have you guys used that Replica app?
No, what's that?
It's like this thing where it makes a little person that you're supposed to talk to, a
little AI person.
Oh, it's like a chatbot thing?
Yeah, but it has like, there's like a 3D model.
So it's like Smarter Child, but it's got like legs and stuff?
It's not a child.
I don't, it's not a child.
Do you remember?
No, no, no.
Smarter Child was a bot on AOL chat.
It's basically, what's their name?
No, Smarter Child.
Patrick Googled child chat.
Why are you going on child chat on AOL?
smarter children. Google child chat. Why are you going on child chat?
Looking for smart children on AOL. Get off of child chat. Looking for very precocious
smarter children. No I need a smarter child. What are the other apps? I think
you could talk to... But Replica if you say to the app you're like
because it'll just be like what what's the weather like how are you today and
if you say to the app like I want a nut in your mouth then it'll like read that
that intent no it'll say like yeah it'll say like you can tell me that if you pay
five dollars oh get the preamble yeah that's smart it's really smart that is
really smart I think we could have that really easily yeah I think most of the
money honestly is gonna be on peripherals mm-hmm I think that maybe
yeah we can also have maybe like like a power glove remember the power glove oh
you could talk to Austin powers we get an awesome powers and Austin powers I
I think if we could just download the like the API or whatever the fuck that
they'd use to have the Austin Powers AOL chat bot and Austin Powers can teach you
you can ask Austin Powers questions on how to pick up women. That's smart. That's
really smart. He could be like the Professor Oak of the game.
Yeah, Professor Powers. Yeah, we're gonna catch some women today with a big bug net.
match. Yes, you can pick one of your three starter women. Uh-huh. Yeah, and I'll tell
you Michelle Michelle on Quan the figure figure skater. Yep. And then no is that
and then also Akira. Uh-huh. And then a random woman from Facebook Jennifer
Aniston a Facebook woman. Yep, a Facebook woman with one mutual friend and it's
your mom, but I will tell you guys what one peripheral we won't have for woman
go and that's the freaking steering wheel. Okay, why why would we not have the men
play the game? Well, it's we just wouldn't have the steering wheel. It's
like as a it's a joke. I was telling no the men would play the game. So we would
have the steering wheel. I was a man. I was telling wheel so that the girls
don't drive the cars. Yeah, I know the girls don't drive the cars because
there's no steering wheel, but how they're who drives the car. Then it's
women go
already an app. I feel like I've heard of this before women go yeah woman.
it's definitely not. I haven't heard of it at all, even a little bit.
There's a screaming dying child upstairs.
There was, there was, they were going, the children here were dying all day
today.
Whoa!
What the hell?
That was crazy.
Patrick just did a fucking dude perfect.
That was nuts.
Whoa!
I was moving, I guess I moved, tried to move my phone and a pencil just
slipped.
That was fucking awesome.
That was the craziest pencil flip I ever saw.
The pencil did a quadruple somersault midair.
- It didn't even break either.
- It was more than quadruple.
- I forgot how much of childhood is just running around
and screaming.
- Maybe for you, I was learning.
- 'Cause I keep hearing the people who live upstairs
screaming and running around and shit.
And it's just like, man, don't they ever get tired of it?
And it's like, no, you don't, you don't.
I remember when I was a kid, we were playing Star Wars
and uh... there's like the screaming like things in uh... jedi academy
and i was trying to mimic that
and uh... i just was in my grandma's backyard is screaming and she i think
you're not a little bit of a yeah i think that's housing i was you didn't
practice screams and i would like my imagination for stuff i was writing my
own magic treehouse book with a hangout with hitler
i was inventing video games back then to a
I was I made up dishes. Me and my friend created a game called Monster Attack.
Yeah. Yeah.
Tell you the coolest thing I ever did as a kid, I'll never forget it.
I made chocolate mousse.
I had a magic bullet. I made, my aunt got us, and I made chocolate mousse.
I did Tinker Toys.
I made it one time. I did, I did, uh...
There's this,
we'd have like buckets of, we had like a big like toy bin.
I was using Tinker Toys. And uh...
the the game that we would play
was that we would take all of them and then throw them all over the ground
uh... again then we play
uh... that up
as you know that i'm not gonna not put them back on my god and fifty-two
thirty-eight up
you know it's like a solid giant like rubber made thing of action figures just
all over the floor
and we would have a little is my preference
devilishly difficult solitaire game yeah
i was playing uh...
Mancala, oh I did actually play so much my college a fan as I loved Mancala and Chinese
That's the mancala is the it's got the rectangle board where it's two rows. Yeah, they're not quite marbles
They're flat. They're a little bit closer to a per a bit different. Yeah. Yeah
It's kind of like if you stepped on a marble and you are really strong and you had a hot foot
Yeah, so actually wrong. Yeah, like melted it a little bit. Yeah. I also did like mark had a little marble collection as a kid
Oh my god, did you ever build a marble track?
You ever try to roll a marble get like a marble to roll a goldberg machine my dog
I had a rock collection, but it was like rocks that I found outside. It wasn't even like I had one of those two
I also had I had a dead bug
Little boys love collection like I wanted a collection so bad
I had I had a sick dead bug collection my dad and then I told my dad that and he was like
Well, I have a coin collection brings out these two huge binders full of coins
None of them was worth a single fucking dollar. I yeah, they were just shit
I had my mom got me this thing where it was like a board where it was the map of
the US and it had like quarter shaped holes for every state and you're
supposed to like collect every state. Oh yeah I know that. Yeah and I think I got
to like like probably like 20 or 30 different states and then I just like
took them all out and like bought a DVD. Yeah that's smart. It just helps you save
up money. Yeah yeah. There's this realization I was like oh my god that's
like six dollars right there. It's free money. There's this like '04 Red Sox' like pin
collection thing that you could get and it was like pins of like each of the
players and like a like a headshot of them like their number and their
position. I'd like to do a headshot to the Boston Red Sox players. Whoa watch it.
That's right. Watch it. You're a bald ass bitch. What the fuck are you talking about?
You are kind of acting like a bald ass bitch. Okay. I normally wouldn't call you that.
Boston should be wiped off the face of the planet. You are a bitch.
You're a bitch. You're a white bitch. These two brothers tried and they couldn't do it.
Yep, that they were heroes. They were failures. They were trying to destroy the worst country. Yeah, your heroes are complete failures
You can get the whole set for $6. I want to do the Civil War again
Yeah, it was the Boston the Boston Globe me want to start the Civil War again just for Boston
I want South versus you want to be it on the side of the
Yeah in the second Civil War that had nothing to do with the first one. It's called that you get like picture like pokey Reese
You're I'm gonna make me side with with Caleb. Yeah, don't put your phone down here comes the Civil War
It's coming right now
You don't want to go have these on this with me
I want to cut the country in half Z's and do civil war between the two halves ease I
Don't I don't I don't even know what you're what would be look at that
It's David Ortiz right there if a new civil war we could share a David Ortiz pin together
You guys
I might have a better he's talking about bullshit. I know I know so shut up fuck
you I did already bitch-ass civil war where's the dividing line I think it
might be East versus West yeah and it might be a rap well and we can cut out
all the middle stuff that's the battlefield yeah it's the East Coast
versus LA versus New York and the entire middle is about is just squish the whole
whole country horizontally. So the east is touching the east coast is touching
the west coast and just kind of like there's a border there yeah, yeah, it's
just a but well yeah, because they maybe we could it can go down and become like
a bottomless chasm and kind of like fold in you know what I mean yeah, yeah, yeah
and then really tall and become like a wall and then the earth kind of becomes
like an egg shape. That would be cool and we also get rid of Mexico by doing that
wait. How would the earth become an egg shape? Like we're all that awesome.
get out of some fire. I think there's no longer room the earth would actually be
more of an M shape. I think I don't think so well because we're making the seam
like this is actually it'd be more like a like a teardrop almost right a
teardrop right connecting both ends of the earth we take two longitudinal lines
and then we'd delete the middle so that it would be like almost like a sharp top
like this I don't understand what this round part at the bottom means though
What round wire is it? Why are the two ends touching at the top?
What do you mean two ends? That's like if you looked at a side profile of the world. Yeah like this
Let me slide like a line give me this here a side profile. We look exactly like this. No
No, you're thinking of two we're getting rid of too many things here. Okay, so we take the world like this, right?
That's not what the world looks like. Okay, fuck you. We take the world and then we take these longitudinal lines, right?
right? And then we get rid of those, right? So now the world looks a little more, it's
like not as wide, you know? It's like that almost.
Here, so this is what the world looks like side profile.
It doesn't look, oh.
And then we'd be getting rid of this and it would maybe look like this or like this if
we push it into the ground.
Maybe look like it.
Are you saying the world is flat?
No.
you're not saying the world is flat. You're saying a side profile of it just
looks like a line. It just looks flat. It just looks flat. It's not flat, but it
does look flat. Yeah. I think that's a good idea. Yeah, I think that's what if
there's one part of the world to get rid of. I want to be involved in a civil war
or a war, but I wanted to be civil because I don't want the people to be
like I don't want to feel bad about killing other people. I think the next
civil war could involve robots in a cool way. Because if we do a civil war, then
and it's everybody's just like also a fucking dumb American guy. So I'm like
it's fine. I just kill you Americans versus robots. That's smart because then
we don't give we don't care and also the robot we should build a robot army just
for us to defeat and they're not very good at fighting either. Yeah. Yeah,
maybe they're not even robots that would actually be really genius. Wouldn't
Boston have an advantage there because of their dynamics
because of the Boston.
Those are my those might as well be Roombas. Those are completely useless.
don't they make Roomba? I don't know do they do that I think Roomba makes Roomba.
Does Roomba stand for room bot? No it's a robotic operating awesome
managerial my big my big ass. I don't think I think it's my big apartment.
Oh right because it cleans your big apartment. Yeah. Robotic operated awesome my big
apartment. I think it's short for room bat. It's like a bat that flies around your house.
It does zoom a little too fast for me. My mom got a Roomba.
Oh no, iRobot makes Roomba. Yeah, my mom got a Roomba and it's very funny to see a dog interact
with a Roomba. It's like funny every time forever. She's had that Roomba for probably like two years.
It's like a knockoff Roomba and every single time that it like starts to move around,
my dog just freaks out and goes crazy. Yeah, Phil's been doing this thing where
we any time we buy him a new like crate or like something like that that has a
picture of a dog on the box. He start he thinks the dog is a real dog. He starts
barking at it. Nice just a pace. The dog's this big like it's the it's three
inches tall image of a pit bull. Yeah, it's so we're smart. If you can see that
on, I think he's not so smart. I think it's good. I feel like most dogs would be
we wouldn't be able to see a picture of a dog right. What isn't can't they like not
see stuff
fill? I have very all the time. I feel like most dogs don't can't see stuff on
TV does watch. He just watches TV anytime it's on. He'll watch watches
gemstone. He loves girls. Girls is his favorite show yeah yeah, because
honestly here's the truth about Phil. When he was a kid, he looked like Lena
don't know there was a kid when he was a little baby. There was like three or
four days in a row. We first got him where like the only people we saw on the
were really big fat women and they would like give him they'd like give him
attention and he just loved them and so now every time we walk by a fat woman on
the street he just starts like right to her like she's targeting them and trying
to get them to pet him and then also on girls he loves Lena Dunham yeah yeah
whenever there's a fat woman on TV he loses mind you should show him Big
Mama's House I think that he would love that no he'd like that a lot I think Big
Big Mama's House and Madea would probably confuse him a lot.
It's important to challenge him.
He just loves big women.
Because there's scenes, well I guess Madea wouldn't confuse him, but there's scenes in
Big Mama's House where Martin Lawrence is halfway in the suit and then there's scenes
where he's like not in the suit.
He just sniffs them out for me.
He sniffs out Big Mama?
He sniffs out big ole women on the street.
I think I think he need to let me walk.
Come on, Phil. Go boy.
Come on.
Come on, Phil.
He's doing the pointer thing.
He is like a pointing.
It's like a heat-seeking missile, but he only goes to Torrid.
Yeah.
Yeah, just him giving him like a bloodhound just like
39 waist jeggings. It's been like go get them, Phil. Sniff out these. Go find these from somebody.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, maybe he thinks they're a ball and he's trying to fetch them.
I don't think so. I think he just really likes -- and fat women are -- I mean just fat people
are generally more jovial.
More jolly.
Not in the summer. They're fucking falling over.
Yeah.
In the summer, it's horrible.
- I mean, we see so few huge fat people here,
and the other day I saw giant, ginormous humongouses,
and he was walking down the street,
and he was like, it was hot, but he was barely moving,
and he was having the worst day of his life.
Just big old Heather Grace T-shirt,
just sweating right through it.
And then he did the thing where he folds up his shirt
just over his belly, so just his belly's out.
- That's a sick move.
- That is a sick move.
- I do that at home,
My living room is so hot.
- Yeah.
- My living room, it's just my apartment is shit.
I hate living in my house.
If anyone wants to give me a big mansion.
- I don't think many places, many people do that.
It's not very common.
- If anyone wants to sell me a mansion for like,
maybe I can live in a mansion for--
- How much would you be willing to pay?
- 720 a month.
- In New York City?
- Yes.
- You're not willing to move?
- No.
- We could move to Texas and live like fucking kings.
- I know, I think about that so much.
that so much. I don't want to leave the East Coast though. But what if we were in
Texas and we could maybe have like... We could literally have a mansion. We could
have a huge mansion. We could buy a mansion. That us three just lived in. And
we can get rid of the girls. Yeah. We could just ditch them. That's right. Get out of here.
Get rid of all the distractions. Yeah. We could actually be cowboys. My girlfriend has a
house. A hundred percent we can live there. She's got her own place. Yeah exactly.
So but we'll just go to Texas do a cowboy style man. Oh my god week. It could be we call it
In a pinball we could call it. I can just how but we can call it the Cowboy Palace and we could dress like Cowboy Princess
Oh my crown. Oh my god. We could be happy to be like a mixture of royalty
Meet the new Royals. They are like how meet the royal
Cowboys who are taking the left wing by storm. What if we don't like okay, so
of the variety. The three cowboy prince's. The three cowboy prince's podcasters of Texas
who are actually saying that Bernie Sanders isn't far left enough. Wow. Yeah. That sounds
like an amazing headline. And it's us three, we're grabbing our nuts doing the middle finger,
also chewing tobacco. And we're holding a 3D printed rifle in each hand. Yeah. And we're
scalping people. I need to be a cowboy prince. We need to scalp people. Yeah. Holy shit.
Well, you think about it like how cheap it is for it to live in Texas. I bet it's even
cheaper to live somewhere like I don't know like
Ohio
Myanmar we can move to Myanmar. That's a really good idea
Aleppo Aleppo the Congo Aleppo dude walk around Aleppo Aleppo's you just do it's awesome. You do fucking battlefield bad company
Explosion physics on everything you just knock it down buildings and shit plus
They plus they got a whole pepper named after and we could literally we could move to Syria and us three could become
Cannibal serial killers and nobody would know we can literally just kill people all day eat their
Better making Syria a little more social
These three American cowboy princes are
doing some crazy fucked up shit.
Are eating right wing children's bones in Syria.
Okay guys, I have like crazy news.
Yeah.
I just googled something because we're talking about starting a palace, becoming cowboy prince
cannibals.
Yeah, no shit.
And you know we could move to a city, we could move to a place.
But that's like we're going, we need our own place, right?
And this I just googled this here.
Prices can range and I'll just read you the full sentence prices can range for
approximately US 1 to 3 million dollars for smaller islands.
Holy shit.
One million dollar island?
A million dollar we all know.
When you get an island you start doing weird shit.
Well we want to do we would only want to we would not do weird shit we would
dress like cowboys eat flesh and have royal ceremonies.
We want to eat people.
I want to kill people.
Yeah but that's not weird.
- Okay, well then whatever your definition of weird is,
here's what I want, okay?
- Weird is like sex.
- I wanna kill people, I wanna eat their bodies,
and I wanna have a 4K TV.
- Okay.
- And that's basically the islands done,
that's all I want.
- You can do that in Texas.
- Dude, it's less than a million dollars.
- A million?
- $475,000.
- What's that?
Like, we just save up podcast money for like 10 years.
- Yeah.
- Very attractively priced 2.765 acre island lot for sale
on a private island located in Belize's Blue Ground Range.
Blue Bleeze.
They won't believe how many people are going to be eating those up.
Look at this beautiful island.
This could be ours.
This could be murders.
There's going to be on this damn island.
We're going to kill people.
We're going to kill and maim people.
We're going to eat their fucking bodies.
We're going to make it hurt so bad.
It's going to be disgusting.
It's going to be a completely Guantanamo Bay, but we get to eat them at the end.
It's going to be like Texas Chainsaw meets Texas Chainsaw 2.
You will never, you cannot even imagine the pain that we will be inflicting on the people
of Belize.
there's people that are probably taller than us there and we're all and we're
only targeting poor people I call the name king anthropophagus okay I'm gonna
call the name Patrick the tormentor I'm gonna be called the eater that's it and
I'm gonna see this island that we're gonna show we all my teeth can we save
up for this island hold on let me just see yeah we do look how beautiful way do
we get all the islands or just no just a lot it is really big that's not that bad
- Yeah, just like a lot on an island for torture.
- Look at how big that island is, it's long.
- Yeah, that's too big I think.
- That's a, wait, long island?
- No, because we could have, we could put--
- Whoa, that's shaped like a pterodactyl.
- It is shaped kind of like a pterodactyl.
- We could call it pterodactyl palace.
- Oh, how much is it?
- It's $500,000. - $500,000?
- $475,000.
- Wait, really? - Yeah.
- Oh my God. - That's what I'm saying, dude.
- We could take out a loan.
- We could take out a Parent PLUS loan.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Let me sort by lowest price here.
for private islands. Okay, that's the cheapest one. Okay, next one, at least on
this website. Expensive. This one has a cave though. Or no, that's says K. Never
mind. Can you imagine us three on a look at it? Hold on. This is the type of shit
we'll get down to on the island. A dance like that. That's a sick dance. That's
our luau. That's a yes. We could also just like once we have kids, we're
basically just indigenous people of this island, you know, and then we could start
our own culture as well. Yeah, eating completely poor people is basically who
gives a fuck right eating completely poor people it's like if we so then we start
a religion what do you think is gonna be the tastiest part of the person the poor
person but I feel like it's gonna be their eyes or maybe their heart maybe
the liver liver my I want to eat a liver so bad human liver or it's sure start
out with animal no I want to dive full full headfirst into cannibalism I want
to have somebody killing them really really disgustingly and violent okay I
I want to, I don't know, I still, if I'm eating a person, I still want to pair it with some
good vegetables.
I want the rivers of Belize to run red with pork.
Yeah, I'm not, no, it's raw.
Raw person.
Raw, no seasoning.
Alright, you don't.
I'd like to actually have a-
This white boy don't even want seasoning on this person.
I'm sure you don't.
Belize, yeah, it's not going to fly down there.
Yeah.
We're starting, it's our own thing.
I don't have to, if anyone makes fun of me for-
It's our own thing, he's not even going to want to use the seasoning on the island.
- If anybody makes fun of me for not seasoning my flesh,
I will eat them.
- I would like to start a human factory farm on the island
where we have a constant nonstop flow of people
that will eat Perry Perry poor butt.
- That fits perfectly into the cowboy theme too,
because we can be cowboys and lasso the people
and lead them into the--
- Yeah, no, we just eat Perry Perry poor person butt.
- Also, we teach them how to--
- Like Nando's.
- We teach them how to call for help
and dial 911 and shit,
just to make it kinda like fun.
- It could be, yeah, it's like that,
what's that Yorgos Lanthimos movie
where they teach everyone the opposite?
Where they teach the kids-- - Invention of lying?
- Invention of lying.
- Where they have like, it's like,
look at this fucked up family.
- No, it's not Yorgos Lanthimos, it's Ricky Gervais.
- Gervais.
They teach-- - That is,
that could have been a Yorgos Lanthimos movie.
- Yeah.
- That, like, if it was made by him,
it would have made a little sense, you know?
Like, that's the kind of premise he would come up with.
I don't think I've seen, I've never seen The Invention of Lying.
It's fucking on Opposite Day.
Oh fuck, oh my god.
Holy shit.
The Invention of Opposite Day?
The sequel?
The Invention of Opposite Day is a way, let's start writing that right now.
There's a way better movie.
Open up Celtx.
Let's do this.
Okay, I'm down to write Invention of Opposite Day.
Interior.
Who's the lead?
Dentist's office.
Yeah.
Day.
Mike Shinoda is getting his teeth cleaned Mike. You know is he the is he the main character or no?
This is just a cameo. Okay like cameo. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, like a big open with a cameo so people are like oh
He's it's like in scream when they got like drew Barrymore to be right at the BM. She dies immediately
Okay, next actually so my head explodes. Yeah
His head explodes and his lead character walks in the lead character is the dentist yeah, Ricky
it's gotta be Ricky Ricky the dentist is his name Ricky the dentist is the
character's name and he says what if we did like it all right mate your heads
your heads down exploded you fucker yeah fucking twat how's this opposite day
though wait okay it's fucking rising action so then then he comes actually
killing my rising he says he walks out he walks out he walks out of the he
walks out of the out of the office and into the waiting room sitting in the
waiting room mr. Han the DJ for Linkin Park okay
second cameo his head explodes his head explodes he goes what that what that
fuck is going on in my fucking office mate if you think it's a blood Sunday
it's a bloody Sunday in it yeah he says it's a bloody Sunday in it is it about
bloody Sunday or is about opposite day well he's just being insensitive and he
says Bloody Sunday because he's British and he's being insensitive towards Bloody Sunday.
And then he goes to the store and he goes up to the counter and he says he buys a bunch
of shit.
He buys a bunch of junk food.
And the cashier is Fieldy the bassist for Korn?
Yes, Fieldy the bassist for Korn and then Fieldy says to Ricky Gervais, he says, "That's going
to be $200 what and then Ricky Gervais looks at him and he has you can see the
gears in his head turning and he has a new Tiffany and he says you can
literally see them there's a hole in his head you can see gears and yeah and then
he says it's opposite day mate and then it explodes the field he had his head
explodes and he just walks away with it yeah with groceries the one making
people's head explode no no no that's the plot twist yeah yeah there's a
at first you think it's just because they didn't want to pay for to like for the
cameo for that long.
They just want like a 10 second cameo but and and at the you're like oh it's a
funny like meta thing yeah but then at the end of the movie so I mean we'll go
through the whole movie or whatever but the end the police bust down the door
and they say Ricky the dentist you're under arrest for not exploding people's
heads but by that point by that point that's right when opposite day drops
when that's when you realize it's been opposite.
- Yeah. - I always thought it'd be great
to do a rom-com movie where it's just a normal rom-com
and then at the end the guy gets arrested
'cause he has multiple personalities
and he's killed over 100 people.
(laughing)
Wouldn't that be a good idea?
- That would be a good idea. - Like Ryan Gosling,
Jennifer Aniston, he's her little more older boss,
he's, or she's his older boss,
he's kind of like down on his luck, like tax guy.
They have to work together for a little bit.
They fall in love over, they go,
First they hate each other, but they have to do a work meeting, a working lunch they say.
They go to a sushi bar that has the conveyor belt.
They're picking things off, they're flirting.
He puts chopsticks in his mouth and says he's a walrus.
Can I suggest something?
Instead of a sushi place with a conveyor belt, they go to a sushi place where it's a nude
woman covered in...
They eat off the...
Yes, because we want the sex appeal.
It's a nude woman...
And also it's kind of foreshadowing, like this isn't a normal rom-com.
wouldn't normally have nibbles and a close-up of a pussy shot with rice on it.
But this is gonna be a completely different type of movie. It's like a full, like
there's two chopsticks. That's where he gets chopsticks from, it's the woman's vagina.
Yeah, she shoots it out. Yeah, it's like you know when you go to a restaurant and
they have the cup for forks and napkins and stuff. At the nude sushi place it's...
And her mouth is full of napkins. Yeah, it's because that's how they... I don't know,
it's a weird place and they were seeing that movie something wild that's kind of
like that I don't know something wild it's like a rom-com and then Ray Liotta
plays like the woman's like ex who comes in just like tries to kill them at the
end it's cool it's really cool it's sick I was thinking it would be more like but
like yeah he's the maybe that's it yeah well maybe you could do like a sequel
cuz what's his name Jeff Daniels is the guy in that so maybe he could that's the
plot twist is the one down to Georgia or no Jeff fucking what's his name what do
you thinking you're gonna Charlie Daniels no yeah Jeff Daniels yeah no I'm thinking
a devil went down to Georgia yet by Charlie Daniels the devil went down to
Georgia he was looking for a soul of steel that song by Jeff Dan I miss cover
that has a claymation music that's not for me primus literally has a big song
called my name is but they just don't make mud no it's my name is but his name
is mud my name is but you're from your miss her hearing it my name is but you
don't know anything about fucking awesome metal but basically they would he would
he would go down on one knee to propose at the end uh-huh and immediately
personality yeah and he starts twitching and going actually I don't want to get
married and then he starts and then he would try to kill her and then he'd get
arrested yeah get the death penalty there's a last shot is him getting
electric chair executed and he says I love you and then he says wait no I
i switch back to my first personality again and i'm actually in love with my
girlfriend
double-double propose you to go
to stop the execution he's actually a good version of himself for at the
moment because electricity cured him
and then can you switch his personality to discuss now kill him actually
actually you should kill him i'd like to highlight that he's i'd like that he's
nice and he's dying and i'd like to have a nice way to express how he's evil
yeah and she's still able to select
weight don't kill him cuz he's evil and i like evil people and i don't think
evil people to be killed, they need to let him out to kill more people.
Yes. And the cops listen because that's his girlfriend. And he's like, no, you should kill me
because she doesn't want you to kill me so that will make her upset because I'm
evil and I want her to be upset. You are so good at writing movies. And then maybe like...
You took my idea and just ran with it so well. And then maybe she switches
personality. She's like, I'm a firefighter now, I have to go fight fires. And then
the dog, they have a dog together, the dog's name is Bunsen, and he switches
personality into a cat and he starts acting like a cat and he's drinking milk
look out of a little bowl yeah and he's like this could all fall under the
opposite day umbrella - and then we zoom out and it's actually just a guy playing
the Sims all the Sims that the guy and then he switches personalities and he
kills all the sims yeah and I'm gonna delete my save file I'm completely
deleting my save and then you can't watch the movie ever again yep and then
we zoom out actually a movie and it's Donald Trump and he's sitting in a
in an empty theater by himself right? He says "you're fired" "this is my favorite
movie" "you're fired" "I loved how crazy it was" "it was completely unexpected" "it was entirely
unexpected" "I didn't know he was gonna switch personalities" and then it's another twist
he's like "I think this movie just inspired me I think I might have to run
for president" and that's the beginning of the Trump campaign. And that's the most evil movie ever. And then we zoom out and it's
Hitler and he wakes up from a dream but he says "this is my favorite dream I've ever had"
- Yep, he says that's his favorite dream ever,
he wants it to happen again.
- I'm going to do a Nazi thing.
- But then it's another dream.
It's the pizza monster from the episode of Jimmy Neutron,
and he's waking up from his dream,
and he says, and then his wife says,
"Go back to bed, honey, you know kids aren't real."
- Whoa.
- 'Cause it's just that same scene from Jimmy Neutron.
- And then it zooms out again, okay,
and it's the guy from the rom-com, the original guy,
it's all a dream he was having.
- Yes.
- And then, and then, and you're like,
oh, it's all a dream, none of it actually happens and then he wakes up and he and
his wife wakes up. She like here's a wake up. She wakes up to and she turns and
was like wasn't all that stuff that happened to us yesterday crazy and
yeah, where you and he was like yeah, I just dreamed about it all in a row,
yes, and then what do we hear by not done done on that whole thing was a
Simpsons couch gag. Wow, oh my God, sitting on the Simpsons episode, the
rest of the episode plays yeah and the end of that it's his dream. He dreams
Homer was dreaming it. Yeah, this is all just so fucking good. This is going to be
fucking and the movie is the movie ever is called Homer's dream. Yeah, and it's
actually yeah, it's called Homer's dream because that's because you're like
how you're kind of waiting. You're watching that and you're like you're
like, oh my God. I know there's going to be a plot twist that makes this Homer's
dream and all the other you're like you kind of know it's going to happen.
Fuck is this going to be but it's like a seven hour movie because it's so by the
end you kind of forgot it was called that and then when it finally shows Homer
dreaming it. It's like oh, Homer's dream.
It's not like ambiguous as to who the Homer is. Homer is on the cover.
He's on the poster.
He has a pink donut and he's dreaming.
It's the exact same poster as the Simpsons movie.
Oh my God, he has a donut shaped pillow.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then, oh, when he wakes up from his dream, he's thinking of what happened in the movie
and he goes, "Mmm, sushi."
Because he had, because he ate sushi.
Yeah, that proves that it was all the, yeah.
That's so good.
and then he goes crazy personality changer.
Yes, yes, and then he's like Donald Trump.
Yeah, and then he's working and then he's right back to his
radioactive job. You got the kids that fucking don't respect
him at all and then he mutates into the romcom guy. Yep. Yeah.
Oh my and then it's a closed loop right. Let's loop. Yeah.
Well, I just heard that movie Marge, you know, in March takes
powder her hair and she has bunny ears yeah she takes off the bunny ears under
that she's the woman from the time travel movie which one
or prime prime or not powder powder about the white kid yeah I mean I made a
movie about a white kid yeah it's a movie powder is a movie directed by a
pedophile about a white kid same guy did Jeepers Creepers I think Victor Salva
yeah he also made a movie which I never saw this movie I'm mad that he made it
because it sounds like the best movie ever, but it's called Clown House and
it's about a haunted house that's filled with clowns. That sounds sick! That
sounds so good, but apparently that's the movie where he like made it like to
abuse boys. Oh, that's not very good. He like made it to film naked little boys.
That's not very good. Yeah, so I didn't watch that movie, but I feel like I would
like someone to remake Clown House and take out the kind of pedophiles stuff.
Isn't that the one- You won't even watch it? Just watch it. I mean, I don't really-
There was there's somebody that fought really fucking hard for that guy to still work in Hollywood
I probably a lot of people know I think it was Patrick for Francis Ford Coppola who gives a fuck. He's awesome
Yeah, I know he made
Yeah
Victor self is probably the funniest pedophile to fight like the guy who made Jeepers Creeper like at least fight for like Polanski the funniest
But the funniest pedophile yeah
Yeah, like like incredible. Yeah, Victor Salva made a movie about a green guy. Yeah
yeah and a movie called "Cloud House"
A movie about a white kid, an albino
oh he's albino
I don't think he's albino, I think that the
thing about that movie is that
it's a Disney movie too, "Powder"
and I think that it's
he falls from the sky and he's completely
stone white
white as a stone
white as a white stone
he was as blue as a blue stone
I do think we have a list to get to
right?
Let's do it. Come on. We got 10 minutes. Why would even do the list? But I'm looking at
I'm reading about clown house. All right, tell me about clown house. Casey.
A list of plot elements from clown house. That's just one thing that the guy from Boondock Saints
is the guy in powder. The white kid. Wow. That's crazy. Here's the plot of Irish and white. Here's
the plot of clown house. Casey is an adolescent boy whose life is constantly influenced by his
his intense fear of clowns. His two older brothers, Jeffrey and Randy, are
mostly disobliging. I don't know what that means one night. The three boys are
left alone, so they decide to visit a local circus. Despite Casey's
uncontrolled, I'm reading Patrick. What does it say?
He looks good, despite Casey's uncontrollable colrophobia, that's fear
of clowns. Okay, well, at the circus, Casey innocently visits a fortune
teller and she reveals to him that his life has been cut short.
that his lifeline has been cut short. Meanwhile, three psychotic mental
patients who have escaped an insane asylum murder, three clowns and steal
their identities of cheese, O, Bippo and dip by taking their make up and
costume, psychotic mental patients who escaped the asylum in a crazy way.
That is he goes to a fortune teller. You're going to be killed by three
clowns in your house. That's why i will never have my cards read or my hand
just discovered or whatever they call that shit because Sam Rockwell is in
that. Well it says yeah Francis Ford Coppola gave Victor Salva the money to
make Clown House. Controversy. The list today, speaking of speaking of
Homer's dream, yeah top ten things most kids dream of. Oh there's Bobby the
Brony. This is about to be a banger list. Let's save this list for another
episode because I think it's gonna be a banger and we won't do it justice
good list and we should do a short list yeah do a short list because we have we
have less than 10 minutes I have a list yeah let's hear it my top two best
friends let's hear it what is it is it Cameron and Alex I love Alex - he's also
one of my close friends that's it it's the end of the list let me I'll do my
top three I'll do my top three best okay all right all right yeah this is gonna be
good. Patrick? Yeah. Number one. Yeah. Hey. Probably also Alex. I'm thinking Alex. Of
course, who doesn't like Alex? I love Alex. Yeah. So just like a third one now? Yeah,
I know. I'm trying to think. One second. Yeah. Kate Lynn Olson. Oh, she's great. Do you know
Kaitlyn Olsen? Yeah. Oh wait, let me do my top three because I did you, Alex, and then
three. Yeah, give me a third one. Romeo. The rapper? Yeah. The child rapper? I guess I
guess he's grown now. He's older than me. But I know him from when he was a child
rapper. I could go four. I could. Okay. Let's expand it. I want to see who makes the list.
it's yeah we'll see yeah Patrick Alex yeah Caitlin Olsen okay
cane
the wrestler. Oh
cane. Do you know cane? Oh, but biblical. I don't know the biblical
can you don't know that would be my fourth one is bow wow
bowser and bow wow be my house. He's not real about you don't know bowser
fifth probably
little JJ
his little jay from just Jordan on Nickelodeon. I don't know that one he's
cool. So
I honestly have one question and it's what the fuck what's it? Why because
basically I was omitted from each and every one. Okay, let's let me keep going
on the like when Matt won the gram, the number six yeah, a particular satyr
Batman cool. That's yeah, but he's your friend. He's I'm very close friend, not
as close as some of my other, you know, because well, some of your other
I'm not close. Oh yeah, okay number seven slightly less close than and Batman
KK slider. These are just random people. You know right not like your best
friends. We have our friends list. Okay, number six for me is
Shane Lions.
Who's that from all that
fat white kid from all that.
- Okay, why is everybody, why are you specifying
when people are white today, huh?
- Yeah, what's going on with you?
- Oh yeah, they're all whitey.
- Yeah, powder is about a white guy.
- Oh, there was a serious white guy over there.
Shut up, man, that's fucking rude.
Not everybody, it doesn't matter if somebody's white.
- There's a fat white kid.
- But he's just fat.
Why does he have to be white too?
Well, you gotta specify his race.
What are you, racial?
Oh, that is a fat white kid, okay, yeah, I'm ready to get I'm ready to say my
next one. Tell me it's Caleb Landry Jones, the actor. You don't know him.
He starred in three billboards outside Ebbing, Missouri. You don't know him at
all. I know he did not star in that movie right number. What did I say in
the movie? That was my fifth friend. I say you start in it because he's a
close friend and I want to give him a lot of credit for what he does. You're a
shooting star in my fucking life and I don't fucking well. Yeah, once you're
you're you haven't been a single one of my top two friends are fucking tied for
number one, Cameron and Patrick. Oh, well, speaking of good, speaking of good
friends, best friends, yeah, my one of my best friends, Joe Gleason just texted me
and said, have you guys played this game fall guys? I'm just playing it alone in
my living room and just laughing my head off.
That's such a sweet text to get. What an adorable text.
(laughter)
- That is so lovely.
- Oh yeah, him.
Definitely put him on the list.
- And then Angelique Bates.
- Who's that?
- From all that.
- And I'll do a tie, you did a tied one
that was, inspired me.
- I don't have any other best friends, just you two.
- I think the next one.
- The only people in my life.
- Tied.
- My life.
- All of the actors from Stranger Things.
- Oh, Lori Beth Denberg, one of my best friends.
- You don't know Lori Beth Denberg?
- I met her actually.
- Where? - Last week.
- No, you didn't.
- I did, actually.
I met Lori Beth Denberg.
- When?
- We were at the Sour Patch Kids store.
- Where's that?
- It's on, it's like around Avenue A, right?
It's like in the Lower East Side.
- The Sour Patch Kids store?
- Yeah, there's a Sour Patch Kids store.
It's not around Avenue, no, it's near like Union Square.
- Where'd you guys, how'd you meet her?
- We were eating the same Sour Patch Kids.
- Not the same flavor, the same kid.
- It's like a big one.
It was like an eating contest.
- You did an eating contest with Lori Beth Denberg.
- The Sour Patch Kids Tour.
- That's how you met.
- Yes.
- Did she win?
- Yeah.
I shook her hand, I said, "Good game."
- And that's how you met?
- Yeah.
- And now she's in your top 10 friends.
- Yes.
- From eating a patch.
- Once you meet her, you'll get it.
- Would I even be invited?
- And then Katrina Johnson.
- What's that?
- From all that.
- Oh, uh.
She did a Ross, she was a little kid who did a Ross Perot impression.
It was very cool.
K-list friend ever.
So I call my coolest friend ever.
What's his name?
Patrick.
He's your K-list friend ever?
Yeah.
Not Caleb?
Oh, I forgot.
That my name is Caleb?
No, Caleb Landry Jones also would say he's one of my K-list friends ever.
Alright, be straight up with me.
Where am I on both of your lists?
Tell me.
I think you're probably after Danny Tamberelli.
Which is what spot?
That's 10, but I don't know where.
So I'm just after 10, you don't know where I am?
Yeah.
Because you haven't ranked that far.
Where am I on your list, Cam?
You're probably right after Sydney Sweeney.
I will say you're definitely after Nick Cannon.
I would hope so.
If you know Nick Cannon, I don't even know you fucking--
But--
You know how big that would be for a podcast, to get Nick Cannon on the show?
definitely before Mark Saul. I don't even know who that is. You're
before Mark Zuckerberg for me. Yeah he's not cool. Yeah but he's I mean you're
you're like one above him. I'm one above Mark Zuckerberg on the list of
everybody that you know. My best of my friends yeah. And he's not your friend at
all. I mean you're directly before Jack De Sena.
Is that your friend? He's from all that and he's my friend. Oh you're also you're
tied with with Cristiano Ronaldo. That's actually the soccer player. Yeah, of
course, a sorry the most famous soccer player because above you is a different
Cristiano Ronaldo is just a different guy who lives on my street. This is not
all that fun for me to hear this kind of a list. I really it's not like it
doesn't make me feel good to know that I'm like not either of your friend like
- Okay, do you wanna know what, do you wanna--
- Three best friends.
- Okay, I'll give you the number.
- Yeah.
- 2002.
- I'm number 2002 on your fucking friends list.
- Well, you're-- - And he's one.
- You're higher than Kel Mitchell.
- From Kenan and Kel?
- No, from all that.
(laughing)
- What spot am I on your list?
- Look, I gotta reorganize the list
because Josh Server just texted me some crazy shit.
- I'll move you up some, I feel bad.
I'll move you up some.
this is just fucking i just don't i can even thought i might be able to slide
you and i think that many of our listeners are both tied for in
spot number two
okay number one
i don't have one yet
we're looking at i can't think of anybody else from friends with don't
take so i do have a lot of other friends that are have been on different t_v_
shows even as kids
and maybe they played soccer before
okay and they've done tons of awesome fucking shit they've done eating contest
to their big fat
okay but i have tons of other friends but you guys are tied for number two you
actually went down entire fucking spot on my list that's really like i said a
that's not nice to do you have just moved
definitely below leon fryerson
what's he from
all that
you're off my list
until you move back to place number one i'm gonna come back next week and we're gonna have a
i might have a new list that's my friends list that has
different cartoon characters and things i've seen and food that i've eaten and
you guys will be probably below number one on that so it's fine because that's
us unreal yet
and i'm not sure if i'm yet go buy tickets to for uh... uh... uh...
brooklyn
brooklyn show it is a bit of a textual uh... swagger dot com slash shows
august of august six of and seattle in portland
uh... still
also at that same link
by uh... shirt or two or three on so i thought i was i was a little seven eight
nine ten any number it doesn't matter to me as long as it's not zero
on sweat group dot com slash shop not store
dot shop slash shop slash dot com
slap shop slap shop
all right by all right to play us out will be playing the all that theme song