Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
- Basically something crazy happened today.
- It was the worst day of our lives.
- Yeah, it was not the worst day.
- It's one of them.
- It's up there with one of the worst things
that's ever happened to us.
- You walked in and bought,
you went to go buy paper towels.
- Yeah, I will say that you,
(laughing)
you coming right out of the gate saying
it's the worst. You showed up two and a half hours after it flooded. I asked you
to go get paper towels. I forgot that I was supposed to get paper towels. You go and then you
get you got the worst mop ever which we already had three of. Yeah. And then I sent
you back to go get paper towels and then you did come back with paper towels. I
came back with four rolls. Basically the office completely flooded last night. We
lost a lot of stuff. Yeah. Yeah. No. We're gonna need a lot of funds. Er yeah. We lost a
live we lost a lot of pieces actually buy some equipment we did we lost a lot of
pieces of paper and dirt which are very important for our creative process that
were priceless completely priceless you couldn't put a price so basically we
need there's an infinite number of money that you want to donate to us then go to
the patreon or go to our tickets shows just go to one of our show I show yeah
or Venmo at Dr. Phil McGraw.
- No, don't give him any money.
You don't need any money.
- Everybody requests a lot of money from that Venmo,
make it really annoying for him for saying that.
- Yes, please do that.
That is what you get.
Start requesting tens of thousands of dollars.
- If you're listening to this right now.
- No, don't do that either.
- And Venmo, Cameron Fetter, 16.
- What, why would it be 16?
- A random number.
- The year you were born.
- I was not born in the year 16.
- Kilo Pits, 1997.
- No, but that is my Insta though.
Go check that out.
(laughing)
- That's another way you can show support.
Go check that Insta.
Check out my likes.
Also, check out my TikTok, @calebpitts1997.
I think is what it's called.
Maybe it's Caleb Pitts the Comedian.
It might be that too.
I don't remember.
I think I tried to do that
and it was already taken or something.
Caleb Pitts.
- Is somebody impersonating you on there?
- What's up?
- Is somebody impersonating you?
Their name is Cameron and their @ is Nabira Truth
and it's not you.
'cause I sent them a video and they said,
"Boy, did you send me this?"
- It is crazy.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't go in for all that social media shit.
I'm more into books, talking with your friends in person.
- I don't fuck with that anymore.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I don't go in for that bullshit.
- Basically, I've gotten my screen time
sub 20, 30 minutes a day.
- Really?
- Yeah, so I'm basically just kinda cruising through life,
actually putting my head, looking at what's in front of me,
got forward emulation going on.
Meanwhile, my my screen time on my my sub my submarine way up. I've been
taking it out on many voyages my screen time. Yeah, you're talking to talk
and Tom. I'm talking. I'm an old old old captain accent. I've been
writing for my submarine that I've been taking out on voyages. Is there
what they screen? Yeah, it's a radar is I'm scared. That doesn't a radar
doesn't count by for screen time. Well, you tell them that because I still
get the notifications every week. He's got it. He's got it.
He's got a test your
Your screen time is up to 24 hours a day.
Look at what, Jesus Christ, what app am I using?
Radar, 23 hours, 45 minutes, Google Maps, 15.
- Yeah, I'm gonna take my submarine to Taco Bell,
to McDonald's, to Europe. - You know, they should set it up
on Google Maps so that it's like a radar,
and it blinks and you see everybody else
who's using Google Maps. - I saw the Google
Street View car, I think I might be on the street
and it's pretty soon. - You gotta, you better,
I bet you showed your nuts.
- I did a rock on sign, nice.
- I can show you, I was at home this weekend.
My old apartment building, I am in front of
my old apartment on Apple Maps.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- I'm looking at, it looks exactly like Sasquatch.
It looks exactly like the photo of Bigfoot.
- What?
You went Bigfoot on Apple Maps?
- I'm blurry.
- Then it's not you?
- That is unmistakably me.
- Oh, that's you, man.
(laughter)
- Oh my god.
- If you want to see it, 200-206 Harvard Ave on Apple Maps.
- How did you even find that?
- I remembered, I was showing my girlfriend,
I was like, I think I'm on Street View here,
and then I looked around the street on Apple Maps.
- And there you are, clear as day.
- You can also see me in the door of my old apartment.
Like I'm looking out.
- You're in both?
- I'm looking out at the car and I'm like,
is that the Apple Maps car?
can see like my thing of my I went to check if I if they put me on Google
Street View yet but I forgot we have no service yeah well that's a
every cell tower in my router the flood gaming router that I bought the flood
did break Patrick's gaming router yeah aiming the flood I'm hearing the halo
sound oh yeah yeah but the flood basically but I want to I'm hearing the
other Halo song in these headphones right now.
Listen, hey, what's her name? Beyonce's got Halo. What's her name? Beyonce's got Halo.
Bruno Mars has Grenade. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Halo Top. Jordan Sparks has Battlefield. What's next? You're gonna sing
call of duty. Jordan X Nintendo has a Super Mario Bros. theme song in one of their games.
Yeah. Wouldn't that be like...
Something like that.
That's not it. No.
No, that would be... I don't remember which game that's from.
Speaking of, we were talking about Talking Tom earlier.
You were talking about Talking Tom earlier.
Well, yeah, there's a new streamer.
For one second you weren't even talking about it, you just said it.
There's these streamers and they do these videos where they call Talking Tom and Talking
been at 3am and my nephews are obsessed with this shit and I couldn't get away from it
all weekend.
It's called lanky vision.
So why are you putting them on then?
I'm putting them on because I got really mad because they sell these lanky vision surprise
boxes at Walmart and they were saying the only way to save yourself from talking to them at
3am is to go and buy a lanky box from Walmart.
That's just smart marketing.
You're getting mad at that?
I'm getting mad because there are plenty of other ways to save yourself from talking Tom at 3.
I would say that's clearly...
Like maybe I don't know, going to a podcast about this live show.
I would say that that's clearly some kind of like
democratic leftism way of trying to get people to not buy firearms and have like legal protection
of themselves. They're like, "Oh no, you don't need a firearm."
Because what else is at Walmart? Guns.
Yeah, you don't need a firearm.
You don't need to go to that aisle.
You just need to get a box to defend yourself from talking Tom.
Buddy, if Talking Tom knocks on my fucking door at three in the morning, he's gonna meet my steel.
He also-
I'm blowing him away.
Yeah.
They also said-
My katana.
And I have my shotgun filled-
Katana.
Listen, two birdshot, one buckshot, right? Pump, pump, birdshot, pump, pump.
Yeah, I mean, it's my katana.
My nunchaku.
Yeah, he's gonna be my nunchaku.
They said they're gonna-
Just completely blow his head off with my- the chain on my nunchucks.
I had to register my forehead as a deadly weapon.
Because I was headbutting. I mean, because look at it. It's got a point. Look at that.
They said that there was exe dripping off of Talking Tom at 3am which showed that he was glitching.
He was glitching at 3am?
The thing that they were saying was that, I forget, I think it was called the Blippi glitch
or something?
He's gonna, I'm gonna glitch him with my Blippi.
Yeah.
Honestly, Talking Tom, these days he's getting up there on my list of my ops.
I did see, I did see in that one video you can kind of see Blippi's glitch,
this spot in between his bum and his
ball holders. Remember when Sharon Stone's blippy glitched on that? No, that was her
glitch. It was showing her glitches. The glitch is what it's got the space between
your finger and your backside. What's up? She was showing her that's a guy. I was
rubbing my blippy. That's a blippy is a man. You're rubbing it rubbing your dick
like I was rubbing my bill. I found I accidentally I stumbled on one of those
those those child like four children streamer type guys. He stumbled on a
child. I stumbled on a child. I was trying to see. He stumbled on a child and he
started streaming all over. You were watching these for a full weekend. I was
watching them because my nephews would not let me have control of the TV. You
said it yourself, you could not tear yourself away from it. I wanted to watch
Paramount Plus and all their awesome shows. You know how you can buy like on
eBay, you can get like a cursed doll or like a cursed like antique or a cursed
I was trying to think like a little John cursed antique. I'd love to curse and
okay, that's fine. I'm listening. I'm listening. I'm listening. I just want
trying out new. I'm trying new ways of you can what you could try it out
during your own thing. How do you ad lib your own speech? You have to figure
it out. Okay. Well you finish your story about it. It's not a scary doll. Not
even that good. It wasn't even about a doll. Okay. Well, you basically ruined
whole flood vibe. I think the flood is tearing us apart by making you be so
mean to me that I want to cry. See I know and then I try you don't even acknowledge it.
Well because I don't know what this is. I don't know who's adlibbing. That's my adlib.
Oh double it. Double it. Remember that from double it. So it's not your adlib then.
Remember it from what? My speech pattern. Remember from your songs that you make?
Oh no I don't. But I thought that maybe it would be great if I could find on
on craigslist or ebay. If i could find in the day, well ebay also they have a
whole section called metaphysical, really all cursed and magic items, but i
really wanted to find either cursed legos or a cursed bionicle or like a
something like that to be there isn't there's none of it and i found that
out because i googled cursed legos and all i found was like a streamer for
children who is like playing gmod and was like i found a cursed lego car in
the game and it's just like it's a twenty minute video of them being like
Lego car is cursed. Oh my god
Yes, literally like what I found out also the word cursed is ruined forever because of cursed pictures
Yeah people when you search for a cursed
Bionicle all you find is cursed bionicle pictures someone put a dildo on a bionicle right? Well, you know, I want a bionicle
That's like
Okay, so it's the original all the streamers all those like children streamers talk to it's the most annoying
I literally was not allowed if I change the channel they'd be like what no and like it was they
Think they glue. It's like the fucking like silver shamrock thing
Yeah, Halloween three these kids cannot stop watching these fucking streamers, and they all talk like they're like like oh
This is completely
Haunted yeah, actually see the exe glitch inside of I don't want to see a haunted glitch
I want to see a haunted real item. Yeah, I'm with you there. Yeah, I
We got to stop talking about streamers cuz it's making you guys do
Annoying voices I've ever heard in my life doing these impressions. Yeah. Yeah, they're really hurting my ears that I was just trying to
Baby fit when you made your scooby-doo, so I don't remember throwing a hissy baby through it
I remember bringing up cogent and logical points
Oh, you can't say yeah like little John cuz I hate rap. Oh, that's a flop
We should be putting more
- Yeah, we need some new-- - I'm crying.
- All right, we need to change. - I feel like those annoying
little guys who start podcasts and have the soundboard
'cause it's how radio is.
- We have, I will say the flood has given us a--
- Woo! - Damn!
Holy shit.
- Hold up.
- The flood is giving us a good opportunity--
- Homer. - To make some changes
'cause it's a, think about the great flood
in the Bible, biblical story. - NPC cartel.
- Or it's MPC. - Canon.
The-- - Danon.
- Danon. - Danon.
- The flood was the beginning.
- The flood was Danon's beginning.
- Listen, the flood is a new beginning, right?
Everything is a new, right?
And so--
- I wish Jonah's Ark was in here.
- We have Joe in the office.
- Yeah, that's true.
- I don't know what Novark is.
- I wish Joe was here to help clean.
- Yeah, he was.
- He was.
- I'll say this, he did his piece more than you.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, no, he did a pretty good job.
- I didn't know he was here.
Well, then I wish Alex was here to help clean.
- Alex has a job.
- Oh, right.
- Yeah.
I wish Pierce was here to clean up his mess. He doesn't even work here.
I wish Patches came here to clean up his mess. Patches, I think, also does a good job. You have to hold your mic a little closer to your face.
Sorry, I was... He's taking it away. I'm prepped for my... Damn! Yeah, I know you're ready.
That was so good. You sounded like a cartoon volcano. That was a good one.
Jesus fucking Christ. I'm about to explode! Oh my God. You should be a voice actor.
We should try... Okay, what about me? Do you think I should... Okay, wait. Go ahead.
this, but you think i could be a yoshi actor.
See that was better that was so much better and i thought that because he has
a little bit deeper of a voice, you wouldn't be able to reach that. What
are you a phone? No, that's what okay that's what yoshi does when he throws an
egg, but i'm more interested in this new character now. Okay, we've heard yoshi
before and also we've never heard yoshi before cameron peter really and can you
do some more sound
I have to say I like these sounds a lot better when they're in the middle of someone else
talking I feel like it really elevates them.
It almost creates like a soundscape you know.
Can we put this in stereo and maybe we could have.
Yeah I think we could master this in 5.1.
Yeah I feel like can you imagine dude just cranking up sitting in front of a full speaker
system a guitar system.
That would have been really good.
Nice.
This is quality stuff.
people are really gonna like this. No one's gonna be like "Holy shit!"
That's disgusting. What? That almost sounds like a mouth.
Have you ever watched the roast battles where the guy keeps hitting the
"Holy shit" button too much? No. Is it cool?
No, because it sounds exactly like "Holy shit!" I think that
roast battles, I mean, I just don't... I used to be so into
those. You used to be in a roast battle? Really? Like the ones at the stand?
Really? You used to go watch all those on YouTube?
I watched those on YouTube in Laconia.
Nice.
In Lakes Region Community College. I had nothing. I would leave them on in the background.
They're all just skinny white guy, fat black guy.
I used to be really into physics.
Or sometimes they'll get a fat person and somebody who has a clear disability and they'll make them go at each other.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. The guy that, there's that one roast comic who's in the wheelchair. He's good.
- Roast battles were more like a Naruto tournament arc
where everyone has a clear power,
you have a superhuman ability,
and there's 32 of them and it's a bracket.
- That's what they try to do at the stand or whatever
by putting the Hadouken sounds and shit,
but it's just annoying. - Do they have anybody
who can control sand though?
Or maybe who is-- - I don't think they have
a sand man. - Oh, who is a Japanese
warrior? - They do?
- They say if it's at the Apollo,
the sand man can come and take you off the stage.
- True, that's true.
- He's got a cane.
- Uh-huh.
Can you imagine that happening to you, bro?
Dude, imagine you get a tomato--
Can you imagine you going up at the Apollo,
you're doing Greg Peppers.
Me going up, okay.
Yep, you're doing Greg Peppers.
I'm not doing that soundscape.
(laughing)
And you get pulled off the--
I remember the first time I ever saw
Bo Peep or whatever.
You know when you're like a kid and you--
Something that I did in college,
material I wrote in college.
Absolutely.
And I'm just like, get off the stage.
Yep, that was a good one.
That was a good one.
That was a good voice.
like a kid and you see something for the first time and you it's the like just
the for like the first time that I saw like I the cane pulling somebody off
stage was a funny thing it was in Shrek or a Shrek to or whichever Shrek that
happens in yeah happens to I think the three blind mice and I'm everything like
oh that's a Shrek thing it's a Shrek joke that yeah I think it happens in you
start to know Roger Rabbit you start to notice tropes tropes trope that breaks
your fucking brain mm-hmm embrace your heart honestly
- Yeah, yeah. - Break your heart 'cause it's like there's no originality.
- And it breaks their creativity most of all, though. - What the hell?
Are you telling me there's a hero and a love interest and--
Wait, I recognize that trope. That's scary teeth.
That's when the monster has sharp and scary teeth.
- That's from "Jaws." - That's been--
That's been in millions of movies.
- It's in the actually starting to enter your room. - Where's your originality?
Oh, this is a trope. This has been in every single one of these war movies I've watched.
This is the Hitler trope.
- Yeah. Oh my God. - He's in every single--
What are you doing in here?
That was the fast and damaging bullet trope.
bullet just killed this character completely fast and damaging what's up
Alex.
I didn't even hear him come in because I'm wearing these headphones and you
guys your eyes are just shifting behind me and it scared me so bad. I thought
something was happening. You had a beast. I thought there might be something
behind. I was in ready to say what it is and he's a say it out to the beast on
the mic. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, what if what if he came in here and he was
not Alex, but he's a giant be a giant be giant be you want to say something
Alex we all know how that was incredible noises yes that's when you care to
everyone on what's we bow when he goes well like a robot future really we bow
mostly says his name just to say that why you wearing a lab coat you look good
You look good. You look official. Yeah, you do look good. Are you giving it to me?
Yeah, so if you had any scrubs... It's not a scrub.
Get out of here. You're explaining someone else's thing now.
Yeah, go get the fuck out of here. Stop smelling your armpits.
You might want to wash it because there was a flood. Everything got flooded.
Yeah, we cleaned everything. No thanks to you, but go take your lab coat.
Yeah, you saw the text and you said I'm not going.
were you working or were you just at our apartment the whole time?
I was working and then I was like I'd probably leave.
Yeah. Alright, that's fair.
Alright. That's fair.
Thanks man. Yep. We'll see you later.
Bye. Bye.
This guy's a piece of shit.
Completely ruined the episode.
This guy's a piece of shit. Ruined the episode and we indulged him by just talking to him.
And look, he's pooping on the floor.
Oh my god. He's fucking rubbing around.
No, he's doing the, he's pantomiming eating pussy at me.
I don't even want to hear that word eating just say eating thing. Yeah eating glitch guys. I'll say I fucking love eating pussy
I fucking love it. Is that is that men in IST or male feminist?
I love eating that thing and I just love putting another you know
My favorite part about it is when you're eating and then you also put your fingers inside of it
I'm on that thing like a fucking rack of ribs. Mm-hmm doing that thing when that I'm gnawing it
I'm like a rat the bottom of a trash or uvula
That's what's sexy to me is being able to put my fingers into something while I lick it.
Oh my god.
Yeah, because that's sexy.
A gaping hole.
Yeah, a hole that I just...
A wet hole.
So gross.
You know, it's okay.
Sex is completely disgusting.
No, not... women's bodies are disgusting.
Oh, okay.
Dude, I'm in there and it's like every second I'm making a sound like a bootstepping in a puddle.
I'll say...
Just rapidly.
The penis...
That's what I'm in there like...
The penis and the balls make perfect geometrical sense and geological sense.
And they don't smell.
And they don't smell bad. They do smell.
They smell normally.
Yeah. It is crazy how... why do your balls...
It's crazy how much it smells like paper.
What?
Paper?
Y'all know that smell?
No. I'm not familiar, but the papers... your balls smell like paper?
Balls and dick both smell like red paper.
signature. Who did that? It's got to be a scooby in here. We've detected a
scooby in the old man. That's a scooby signature. Do you think that you would
do you okay? So I guess I haven't experimented with this and I'm curious
if maybe you guys have. Would you like the smell of another guy's balls or is
it like you only like your own balls? I think unquestionably, I would like the
smell of another guy's balls. Yeah. I think there's like zero doubt in my mind.
I like that too, but wanted you to say it first.
(laughter)
I think if somebody gave me jars and it was,
it was mine.
I don't think I could tell the difference
between my ball smell and someone else's.
It was a Yankee candle.
It's a Yankee candle, it just says Zach Braff's ball sack.
No, no, listen, if it was three Mason jars,
it was a Yankee candle, the smell of like,
my wife's shirt or something, like the perfume she wears,
and then a guy's balls a random any guy's balls. Zach Braff. I would be like
Zach Braff's ball sack. If I didn't have the context of like it wasn't labeled I would
smell that and be like oh that smells like pretty good like that smells like
home to me you know. Yeah yeah I think that maybe I guess I guess that I
probably definitely one smelled it. I've definitely I've absolutely have caught
indirects of other guys balls I'm sure that I smelled it without realizing it.
gym, but not very much. What do you think I am? You've been to the gym, you know
that smell. Yeah, you're looking good. Yeah, right? Yeah, look at that. But I
feel like I've probably caught a whiff, you know, in a locker room or walking by
on the street if someone's wearing stinky underpants that comes out. That
guy's got a, those balls are loud AF. Well, that's, I can't, I can't, well, I
can't, that's what I'm saying. I can't call to mind when I have. You're right.
Smelling other guys' balls. So I'm not sure that maybe I would have, maybe if I'm
like nose deep in a guy's crotch. He's been sweating all day and it might
smell completely different than I expect. I might have my own smell and I
don't know because I'm I'm not you go outside and you smell that Baba.
I'm not little little Rover Fido sniffing up into a guy's between his
legs. I'm not going to do it, but I'd but the mystery of it. I think
you're wrong. I think if you smell a guy's balls on the street, it's
like passing by a subway. You're like immediately like, oh, that's
balls. Yeah, that's balls and I like that. But I'm not sure I've ever smelled balls on the street, I guess.
You probably never have smelled them on the street. I'm also completely a mouth breather. I don't smell
anything ever. Oh, I didn't know that. You know that... You're basically, it doesn't matter,
your opinion holds no weight. Yeah. You don't smell anything. You know that smell,
like the New York trash smell? Yeah. It's the one that smells exactly like the best cheese in the
world, but it's the worst smell. Definitely. It smells like cheese. Your brain is confusing
things a little bit. It smells like cheese and if it was a cheese it would be like
it's a smelly cheese but it tastes, it's hard. There's a smell connection in my brain that I
don't think make, that I think makes almost no sense. And I, this is, I'm
gonna open up to you guys here, okay? I'm ready. So I'm ready for all the jokes here
but I really, whenever I open a jar of peanut butter it makes me think of the
smell of a dog. And I assume it's because we feed my dog peanut butter as a treat,
sheep right just every day. You can't control it every time I it I don't I
the smells are not the same obviously, but when I smell it, I'm like my brain
is like that smells like a dog. It's like a dog has been in this. Okay, just
since I'm I'm a hundred percent serious, smell peanut butter. I think of my dog
and then I look down and there's just a puddle on my front.
I see this is what the jokes I was. I was trying to get out of here, but I'm
completely serious. They're lazy. I don't I don't want to go there. I will
I do kind of agree because but that's because I realized the other thing there
already is a food that smells like dogs and it's corn chips that's already it
that's already it it's cone yeah it's a horn it's yeah dogs smell like corn chips
if they have a certain there's a dry and warm dog some of them have some kind of
like fungus or bacteria or something that creates that smell yeah the top of
the dog smells like a free those yeah exactly
- That's how I smell.
- Go home and smell Phil, he smells like Fritos.
- Yeah, 100%.
- He smells, no.
- That's documented, that's normal,
but I've never met another person
who thinks that peanut butter smells like a dog.
- Yeah.
- And I, but I can't, I don't know.
- I think that, I will say since I got Phil,
I've probably eaten zero peanut butter.
It's like-- - Really?
- 'Cause I feed him to him every other day or whatever.
- Yeah, it becomes dog food.
- I think that's what it is.
- I don't have a peanut butter in my house that isn't like--
- Same with like Doritos.
- I think that's what it is,
is that we had a separate peanut butter jar for the dog,
maybe that one started to smell like dog or something and then like I don't even
I just don't understand it. I definitely slowed way down. That fucking, that natural peanut butter
with a teddy. Shit you gotta fucking. I got the teddy. I give him the teddy. Yeah. I'm a good dog owner.
Yeah you gotta, you gotta squirt that shit. What? You don't squirt. Squirt that shit.
What are you talking, it's a jar of peanut butter. What are you squirting? How do you squirt that?
Dan and you, squirt that Earl. It's gotta be the worst episode I ever did. These people are gonna, everyone's gonna hate this.
No, no one's gonna feel bad about the flood at all. We're just being, yeah,
it's the most annoying episode of all time. It's 'cause we're, you know,
traumatized. We're completely traumatized. Let's admit it, we're traumatized.
There's a lot of emotion inside of us right now. A lot of people use being
annoying and using types of humor as coping for being traumatized. And I've
done it my whole life. It's like saying Danon loudly is a coping strategy.
It doesn't even make sense. Specifically for flooding.
Double it, double it. You can't steal other people. Guys, I'm not participating.
I'm collaborating. You started it so you should feel responsible.
Here's a thing I can talk about. So I... A spot on your pants? You see, well it's a
brown spot and it's exactly what it looks like. I'm listening. It's poo-poo? You got doo-doo on
your... You've been wearing these all day and you didn't tell us you have doo-doo on
your pants? What if I rubbed your knee? It's a doo-doo. I tried to get it out with a shout.
What if I did a joke about you being Santa Claus? Let me tell the story here.
Okay, so I found so I left it was a money Mondays. I left a money Mondays
I found a cat walked up to me in the street with no eyes. Yes, I remember
Mmm turns out it had an infection in its eyes. Yes, but these two cats walk up to me. I immediately I picked them up
I'm walking down the street
I walked all the way home from the office with two kittens in my hands like French Montana with the Tigers
yeah, I was walking around like that like to like probably I think I live like I
five blocks away mm-hmm I walked five city blocks with just two holding two
kittens just going like oh geez yeah I want to like like Morty like Morty and
then I well okay so I'm petting one of them and I'm like oh man there's this
one's like he shits all over me. You were like what? I was like this one's like this one's like this one's like my little boy my little baby and he fucking shit shit it all over me. It was that long ago?
The stain has not. You chose to put the pants back on? No no no I washed them. And then the stain
wasn't gone and you put them back on? Yes. You put dude you know what stains are
made out of? Yes I know. The thing that it is. I tried I sprayed it with shout I tried everything.
and then you put the pants on. You weren't like, "I'm going to leave these pants off
for a while."
These are my favorite pants.
I need to put them back on.
These are your favorite pants?
Yeah.
There shouldn't be any more.
They're just green.
They're the perfect fit pants. Look at how they look on me.
Right now it's giving you a fake boner and there's a hole in them.
And there's poop on them.
They've got to sell these pants somewhere. You've got to be able to get new pants, man.
You've got doo-doo on them.
Well, I can't because I have to pay you to fix the whole flood.
You're going to pay to fix the whole flood.
I'm putting all the money down.
- Okay, all right, that's fine by me.
- Sounds good to me.
- But, yeah.
- If the price to pay for that is some poopy pants,
that's okay.
- And then that cat died.
- He got what he deserved.
- One of them died.
- Yep.
- He had panleukopenia.
- What the hell, why would you tell people this?
- Kitten AIDS.
- That's gotta be the quickest way
to ruin an episode of the podcast,
talk about a cat that died in your care.
- Uh-huh.
- Yep.
- It wasn't my fault.
- No.
- Yeah.
- He should have been standing under my foot.
- It wasn't, exactly.
- Yeah.
it was it wasn't directly your fault yeah yeah and then I well I've been taking
care of the other one that's what I that's what I tell the police she just
died in my apartment yeah she had something she pooped on me
it is what you think it is a woman's blood yeah and poop tell you what would
suck having a period that's yeah I've been thinking about that a lot recently
Look, I have a period, all right?
Let me think about trying to give myself a period.
You have a period?
A period of where I'm eating too damn many chips.
Dannon!
And when would that period be?
Maybe before your food gets there at the Mexican restaurant?
Here's the thing about these chips, buddy, I'm filling up on the-
Let's go!
Hey, listen, here, I'll stand up for this.
All right, come on.
All right, hey!
Come on, come on!
Hey, Mexicans!
Stop bringing all those chips to the fucking table!
Here's the thing, here's the thing, yeah, here's the thing, okay let me stand up.
Alright, listen up.
Mexicans.
Yeah!
Okay?
You guys.
Okay, but you better say the chips thing.
'Cause I already said it.
Mexicans!
No, no.
No, just say it.
When I finish the first bowl of chips, don't bring me a second bowl of chips.
I don't want them.
Mexicans.
No, alright, you're leaning too hard into the Mexicans.
I'm not leaning at all, I'm standing straight up.
I immediately regretted saying the Mexicans thing.
Alright, Pat's standing up now.
Yo tengo trabajar. Trapping hard? Trabajo? Isn't that Travago?
Yo tengo trabajo en los baño. The bathroom. What? Bano. The singer? Bano?
impersonation of Bono this is your Bono impersonation he's a completely
different nationality oh you know Tango you think Bono is Spanish speaking about
ho Bono impersonation nor it or person is your own or ner
Oh
Norner yeah, oh
Norner that guy all right listen
I like to apologize to the brave people of Mexico
Tips I'd like to apologize to the brave people of Mexican restaurants - yeah the chips listen the chips there as long as you keep
Them free you keep the chips free you're gonna see a lot of me. Yeah
We should put that in an almanac.
What's an almanac? You say almond stack?
An almanac.
I'd love to have an almond stack of wasabi almonds.
How are you going to stack an almond? Their shape is not...
You can stack them if you shave them down.
You ever do the thing where you try to get all the skin off the almond and leave just the nut?
No.
And then it doesn't taste as good.
And then you realize it's like a rotisserie chicken.
I have to say, it's odd behavior.
You know they sell...
god the keto chips. I'm basically a normal. I have to you know. I don't
want to I don't want to start. I don't want to start a fight here or anything,
but normal people don't do that. What take take all the skin off an almond.
That's weird. No, I do that. Don't smell peanut butter and think of a dog. You
smell that is what that is low. That is so low your penis. If I smell a dog's
come, I'll think of a dog duh. Why do you recognize a dog's come because it
came out of a dog's penis onto my floor or lap.
- Why is it going on your lap, man?
- 'Cause it's grinding on my knees.
- You can't, that's not your fault.
If the dog starts using you as like a device
to masturbate with, it's not your fault.
The dog humps your leg, it's your,
I think at that point, it is your choice.
You don't have a moral obligation to swat the dog away.
But it's--
- What about a cat?
'Cause there's--
- I don't, cats don't hump, right?
I've never owned a... no, I've owned boy cats.
But I've never owned a boy cat that wasn't fixed and I'm really ner... because he's getting
around the...
My...
Mohammed, my little...
What's Mo?
I think he might fuck your face or something?
I think he might cheese all over my couch.
That's okay.
He's done so much to that couch already.
We're deciding whether or not...
You watched him on Saturday.
Yeah, he pooped everywhere.
He pooped on the wall.
He pooped on the wall, the couch, the blanket, the floor.
the floor. He's a street cat and I when I when I met him he had a switch plate and he was
pointing it at me. Whoa. Yeah. He slick his hair back like Shia LaBeouf. He's a two dollars kid.
Tombstone. No. Liam Neeson. I think you're talking about Better Off Dead.
The kid who says two dollars. Better Off Saul. The show's over bring it back. Mm-hmm.
So he pooped on the wall? Yeah. I think he had already pooped on the wall when we
he got there yeah, because he was having problems with he so what happens is
so this cat, which I learned which I was not. I was we were told halfway through
into watching him, which I'm very glad that Alex told us this because I can't
believe no one else told us this because this is maybe I'm pretty sure I told
you this is no you did not say what I'm about to say is the number one most
important thing I should have known watching this cat is that if he meows
yeah, he's about to blast diarrhea everywhere yeah, and I was not informed
about this and at all he every time he meowed three times. Every time he
me every time he meowed when we were watching him, he started pooping
everywhere wow and and other one and otherwise we would have assumed like any
other person watching a cat that if it meows, maybe we'll pick it up and put it
on our lap or something and we were told that just in time and I can't believe
that that was not that was that was yeah God Almighty. I know they pooped every
really just well you it was easy it's brutal yeah it's really really good yeah
you clean it up with like a shop sweep like a shop room yeah we got to do that
and then like I have a I have these these wet wipes that are the smell like
Japanese cherry blossoms I have to wipe its Clorox wipes no no it's it's pet
wipes oh the ones we were using were Clorox yeah yeah that's the that's the
opposite oh I thought you meant wiping his butt you weren't wiping his butt with
chlorox I was not wiping his body wiping it why you're wiping his but I have to
why I did see his but I'm not touching that yeah dude it's fucking nasty it's
covered in poop I'm just I watch my friend's cat of what I'm wiping his butt
every time this thing is like okay if you like the next people who own them I
think if you watch someone else's kid and the kids shits or pisses in its
diaper that's not my problem yeah that's the that's your problem clean up the
poop but I'm not gonna wipe his butt no you should have emptied him before I got
him yeah that's that simple I wasn't asking you to wipe my cat's butt yeah
you were but you thought that maybe I might have been wiping his butt yeah you
were hose that there's there's been many times or I've had to wipe his butt why I
could tell that he needed somebody to wipe his butt and there but it is all you
I would not would not be me I was not getting paid I was doing it for love of
the game I and I'd alright well clearly you don't like the game if you're not
wiping its butt. Wiping his butt is not part of the game that is a timeout
that's in timeout no huge part of the game is looking at the cat and going
aww and petting it and playing with it with a toy yeah that's the game you have
no vitality. Vitality? Mm-hmm what do you mean like hit points? Yes.
You're we know you would have you would have wanted to wipe the cat's but
It's part of the job. I was not getting paid. It was not a job you get paid. I did not get paid
If I got paid I would have wiped the cat's butt what if he's been withholding payment just then I'll go back
I'll come back. I'll come to your house and wipe the cat's butt if you pay me how much
$60
Yeah, that's there's a there's a much lower amount of money I would do that for 40
I'll do it for 40. Wait, I can't I'm beating myself out of the fucking thing
I'm do I hear 30 30 going once to wipe his kid his butt like a good wipe am I do it?
Am I doing it all day? Yes all day. Fuck you. It's all I'll do it once. Yeah, I'll do it once for
That was the number I had in my head. I think that's the lowest I would go his butt legit
Looks like goatee
It's really nasty. It he's got no goatee. I can I can tell you as an outside observer - it's not just his butt
that is the gross part is that he gets poop all over his entire back of his body.
It's been a rough couple... I've barely been home too. I feel
like an asshole because I left this fucking cat that I found. You would know what an asshole feels like
because you've been sticking your finger in that thing. I wish I could just put on a
rubber glove and just poke that gland back into its butt. What about a piece of
cork. I honestly I'll do any any solution to put to plug up Mo's butt so he stops
pooping. Yeah yeah he does need to stop. You know what it is just cuz he's on
the kitten meal replacement uh-huh and I need some of that dude. That stuff looks so fire.
Dude, his food? It looks so good dude I saw him eating it and I was like dude I'm
I can't look up a picture cuz there's no Wi-Fi but trust me.
describe it it's fucking it looks so good dude it looks dude it's like it's like
it's like it's like it's like an AI content-aware fill of chili yeah looks
the same coming out as it does going on yeah Cooper no food yeah well his food I
had to mix the white formula in with like the pate chicken and stuff mm-hmm and
pate chicken this fucking cats living large and you're making sure this cat is
eating pate and you're wiping his ass for him? What kind of fucking richie rich spoiled brat
are you raising? I'm nursing him back to health, dude. I'm making sure he stays alive. Back
to health? You're fucking raising him to be a fucking brat, man. You got a spoiled ass
rich fucking cat. Eating pate? I've never had pate. You have? You've had a banh mi. They
put pate on a banh mi. Not on the ones I'm getting. They may put mayonnaise on the ones
I get. No, they put pate on a good, no. I don't get a good anything. The place that we
- You go in Boston, they put the pate on it.
- No they don't.
- Yeah they do. - That's a lie.
No, it's mayo.
- It's like a pate, yeah, it's like a pate.
- No, no, wrong.
- I suppose you're looking at me
like you wanted me to settle it.
- They don't put any pate on that.
- Like you want me to do some kind of--
- Look up bahn mi recipes.
- Yeah, let's use the wifi.
- I can't look anything up.
- Not.
- Oh yeah, we don't have a list
because we can't really have access.
- I thought maybe we could do a fun,
figure out what is a list.
- Well, the Caleb's Cup has a list.
- Okay, wait, list of banh mi ingredients.
- What, you have access, you have what?
What?
You have a, you have service?
- I have LTE.
- Why didn't we, you didn't tell us?
- You just let us think there was no hope?
- What's wrong with you?
- Okay, bread, pork, sauce.
- He's got perfect-- - Oh my God.
- Coriander.
- There's no pate on that?
- Wait.
- There's never, I've never heard of pate on a banh mi.
- What if the pate is the sauce?
- Then they would call it pate.
Why are you, it's just sauce.
- Bon Me Pate, authentic bon me, cooking with Lane.
- I've never had an authentic bon me.
I just have the cheap ones.
- That's true.
- I've never had pate.
- I don't know, I don't even--
- And now you're just,
we could have been reading the list off your phone.
- Are you too intimidated by your local Asian grocery store?
Let me help you out.
I'll send you a free shopping list to your,
oh, that sounds lovely, hold on.
- You need, okay, now he's just on his phone.
- Yeah.
- Now you're just doing phone time.
You found a loophole.
- Found a trick, a phone trick.
- Put that down right now.
How do you pronounce bottle?
Put that down right now.
- Okay, I just found a list, guys.
I'm excited to do this list.
I just found a list of what it says
on the side of my water bottle.
- Okay.
- Here's my list.
32 ounces, 28 ounces, 24 ounces, 20 ounces,
16 ounces, 12 ounces, eight ounces, four ounces,
1,000 milliliters, 900 milliliters, 800 milliliters.
- Vietnamese pate for banh mi.
- Is there any comments on that?
- Adventures.
- That's all it says?
- See, it says this first sentence here.
- Patrick, I'm completely disengaging with you.
- Oh, it says Nalgene on the other side.
(laughing)
So there's a list that I found just now.
I think maybe we could do a whole thing.
- I guess.
- I spy with my little eye my list on mine.
- I've never had it bond me to look like that.
You had to try so hard to find a bond me with pate on it.
- Here's a list of letters on Patrick's hat.
- Can I propose something?
- Oh, wait, wait.
- Can I propose something to you guys?
- This one doesn't have the,
see, I should have worn the other Red Sox hat.
- I'm wearing a list hat that has a list on it.
- The other Red Sox hat had the list of World Series
things on it. - See, that's the kind
of thing we need to find right now.
- Okay, wait, here's a--
- I'm getting the Mad Libs, I'm getting them.
- Yeah, I think this is-- - I'm getting the Mad Libs.
- If you can find them-- - That's way better.
- Guys, make small talk.
- Where are the Mad Libs?
Okay, here's a list I'm finding right now.
- Here's a list of cats that I hate.
- List of buttons on this remote.
- Okay. - E-Mom, Tabata.
- Okay. - FGB, a picture of a clock.
So that's the top row of buttons.
that's a good list right there here's a here's a list
thank god okay
guys
i'm gonna need
is it which one are you doing
we only tell you the name of it you know what we are you did some of them from
that book and i was i want to be okay i guess this is the code of the same
yeah i did that one day you know okay here's how would you read it out and
then
tell us what word to put
we need
what you'll be so you read the whole story out and then then say adjective
No, I guess we'll just do it the right way.
Let's just get a mad look going for you.
I'm a little bit of an academic.
Would you guys consider yourselves academics?
Perhaps.
Perhaps, and mayhaps. Would you consider yourselves thespians?
Yes.
Would you consider yourselves Shakespeare fans? Shakespeare aficionados perhaps?
A bard.
Once a bard, forever a bard.
A bard for the bard.
What the hell?
I'm going to need a noun.
Okay.
William Shakespeare.
Oh, stage.
Hmm.
Which one are you going with?
He's not even going to tell us.
Okay, good point.
I guess I'll go, okay, yeah, all right.
I won't, you guys both give me one and the surprise will be who I pick.
Okay.
And then the other surprise will be what the story is with all the words in it.
Thank you.
And now I need a person in the room who's female, Cameron.
Cameron.
That's not, you can't, you can't say one.
can't give him one like that. Okay, William Shakespeare. That's not how you cough. I was
clearing my throat. Okay, clear your throat again. We'll do that because William Shakespeare's
spirit is all around us. Tell me what your thing is because he said Cameron. And then
I said William Shakespeare is a compromise. You have to say something here, Cam. Okay,
Patrick and Caleb combined it to one person. Okay, so it's going to be... You can't say
what it is. Hey, listen folks, I know which one I'm picking. I like one of these answers
a lot more than you. This is completely, it's not fair. Wait, why don't we just do Pamela
Anderson. Pamela Anderson's in the room right now? Yeah. Yeah, she's in the room.
Oh. It's so hot. Stop mixing up the mic. What are you doing? Yeah, my arm is already tired.
We will do, we'll do Pamela Anderson. Oh, I'm not supposed to tell you guys. Yeah, I
don't know, you're really messing this up. No, you're messing it up. We're only two in.
I need a nap. William Shakespeare, nap. I need a nap. Oh, that actually works pretty well.
and
I guess I'm saying the same thing over and over again.
I guess I won't.
I guess you are.
I don't know if you guys remember how Mad Libs worked.
You're supposed to say something just oh so ridiculous that no matter what the format
is and what the meaning is.
Okay, I got you.
I got you.
Okay, so with that in mind, I need a noun.
The plays of William Shakespeare.
Okay, that's better.
The thing.
No.
Yeah, I think it might be funny.
Okay, and now I need an adjective again.
go ridiculous the craziest things you listen it's your professional comedy
funny funny okay that actually fits and now a plural noun so that's the same
thing but Shakespeare's actors okay hmm let me get the next one here okay this
now this is a noun again okay I might say Shakespeare's hat Shakespeare's
bards. He's the bard. We're almost there guys. Bard. I need another noun. Bard. Bard.
Okay and now I need another yet another noun. Playwright. Playwright. Okay. Playwright.
Okay and now I need a plural noun. Playwrights. No we can't do that. Play...
Play pens.
What?
No, no.
That's a plural noun.
Writers.
Playwriters.
Authors.
Bards.
I can't do bards again, guys.
Maybe tone it.
I know how extreme you guys have been thus far in this Mad Lib.
Tone it back two or three steps for this next one.
Because you won't be able to control yourselves.
Part of the body, plural.
that's that's singular brains spunk makers okay that's gonna spunk Meyer
remember Otis did your school your school also sell cookies at lunch they sold as
Otis spunk Meyer cookie. One last noun. Otis spunk Meyer cookie okay okay maybe maybe a
certain brand of cookie let's hear it can you guys let me just read this yeah
let's hear it William Shakespeare is the most famous
writer in the history of the William Shakespeare that's just - all right that's
rich he wrote many plays including Romeo and Pamela Anderson again pretty funny
and a Midsummer Night's Nap that actually makes sense
Shakespearean poems here is a selection from one of his most theatrical sonnets
Shall I compare thee to a summer's plays of William Shakespeare? Thou art more
lovely and more funny. Rough winds do shake the darling Shakespeare actors of
May and summer's Shakespeare's hat. Hath all too short a bard, but thy eternal
playwright shall not fade so long as authors can breathe or spunk makers can
see so long lives this and this gives cookie to the cookie part at the end
cookie part does sound kind of delicious yeah yeah you want to do this yeah I'm
gonna do one here let me give me a second I gotta be a new ad lib maybe
that do that one again do you guys believe yes by that Shakespeare was
multiple guys a lot of people don't realize this podcast multiple guys yeah
people think that we're all one voice yeah I did have a guy the other day ask
me if we were brothers really he's like you guys brothers I said wait somebody
asked you that yeah if you if we were brothers yeah well I'm a brother your
brother your brother so Eric and Paul mmm two siblings Wow
and my sister mmm shouldn't say by their names I shouldn't be saying their names
No, not at all.
Yeah.
You just writing?
Okay, here we go.
All right.
I got, okay.
So, this one here, I'll, okay.
Yeah.
You guys ready?
Okay.
Plural noun, the curses of the crazy chicken.
Can you give me a second to write that down?
Yep.
The curses?
The curses of the crazy, the slot machine.
The curse of the crazy chicken.
Yeah.
Okay.
Since the beginning of time, people have been using the word, "crazy chicken," and it's
been around for a long time.
And it's been around for a long time.
a slot machine because of the crazy chicken yeah okay since the
beginning of time people have fought with one another for many
crazy reasons, but these brave people devoted their lives to
helping their fellow men. Gandhi led India to freedom from the
British Empire who had taken it over. He inspired people all
over the world to be peaceful folk Martin Luther King Jr. Led
the civil rights movement in America thing helping gain equal
rights for African Americans by protesting peacefully Nelson
Mandela helped and racist stuff in South Africa for his hard work. He won the
Nobel Peace Prize and the US Presidential Medal of Freedom. Mother
Teresa was a nun from somewhere who devoted her life on helping sick and
evil people all over the world. Clara Barton was a nurse who helped found the
American Red Cross which educates children and gives assistance to the
curses of the crazy chickens in need.
I mean that was funny. That one was so funny. There's a single. That was funny,
there's only one thing that was picked. Yeah, you're supposed to do multiple
things. What did you just fill the whole thing out? What do you mean? No, it's just one that
has one blank at the end. Yeah. What kind of, there's nothing mad about that
lip. They must have run out of... Let me see that. You can just do your own one.
Alright. You just do your own research. Yeah. I don't see why you have to pick a real
part of my mad lip. I'm telling you. Okay, plural noun. Curses. Curses. We'll just leave it at
curses for now. I think I know, yeah, curses of the crazy. Just curses. Curses. Curses of
the crazy chicken. Another plural noun? Randoms. No, randoms. What? Doesn't make any sense.
Randoms. Pies. Chicken pot pies. No, that's too weird. So you want to do curses of the
crazy chicken again yeah we could do that yeah that's first in the room crazy
chicken the crazy chicken the the crazy chick is I mean there's not really in
the room it's like a sauce made up funny now and crazy again chicken no not crazy
just chicken chicken cheese sorry okay then plural now Jesus what does that
have anything to do with the cream. Cheese and pie. Chicken and cheese. Verb. What? The verb.
Cursing. What else you got? Noun. Curse. TV. Or football. Cursed TV. Monday night football.
Monday night football, that's good. Person in the room. Patrick. Doran. Patrick chicken.
What is it? Torb a burb, I think said a tour. I think a burb what's a okay,
just a torb
torbing
twerking no
verb twerking or being twerking okay twerk that's kind of funny. Yeah, it's
really funny. It's about but I know additive
demented
yeah a little off yeah a little bit off place place the coop coop the farm the
farm yard okay adjective out out of this world out there groupy person in the
room. He yes, that was Shucky by the way, sh u c k y pat so down now in Shucky's
shoes. Shucky's shoe. It's a singular noun. Yeah, true. Adjective. Shocking
and psychotic beyond belief. Yeah, oddity and oddity. This is like
psychotic and odd beyond belief.
Psychopathically weird.
Okay.
Alright, I think that we're arriving pretty close.
This thing's about a 99% on the loading bar.
What's the name of this one?
Did I do that?
Don't tell me. Wait, what? Come on.
Oops! We should thank our lucky Curse of the Crazy Chicken
for these curses of the crazy chicken
that were invented by accident.
In 1945
Oh, the microwave.
In 1945,
the chicken was experimenting with a chicken when he discovered it could melt
cheeses and make popcorn cursing he then built a microwave TV football
Monday Night Football. Monday Night TV Football. Yeah. The Slinky. In 1943 naval
engineer Patrick attempted to help. Patrick Doran. One word? Wait, this guy has one name?
was like print yeah what's the last name I don't even know that helps that helps
ships twerp when he got the idea for a toy hold on pause could twerk wait down
what pause first of all is this mad lip talking about a tour tour it helps ships
tour but what is tour meanwhile the ships are twerking as well this is down the
stairs all by itself it became the demented slinky potato chips at a
restaurant in the barnyard coop that's a terrible place for a restaurant in 1853
the customer complained that his fries were too out of this world
why would you complain about that also fries weren't even even fries are way too
out of this world I don't I can't eat them the chef Shucky cut the potatoes as
thin as possible and fried them in a
shucky shoes
accidentally inventing use the shucky
potato chip there are no wait the
psychotic and demented beyond belief
potato chip. That's a terrible name.
Nobody's going to buy. Yeah, that's
that's confusing. All right. I think
that's enough mad libs for now. I think
that I think the mad lives just weren't
think where they weren't mad. It's not
hitting today. We have to have a list
man. I'm telling you that's what we
find lists in our okay. So here okay.
I see a list of I see I see a Caleb. We're not doing I see a Patrick. We're not doing
I spy on a podcast. That was the end of my list. Okay. I mean if you would you know
what it's. How about list of reasons why the flood is gonna bring us closer
together and number one show you number one it already did. That's a number two
and list end. No we're not gonna finish the list that fast. Finish list and list end. You're fucking terrible at this.
I told you guys a story about poopy on my pants. That was a that was a that's a
list of reasons why I don't like you right now is because you have stinky poop
pants. Smell them, they smell good. Not in any world am I gonna bend over and put my
nose on that poop spot unless you give me $10. I'll Venmo it to you. You won't. Oh my god.
I don't actually want to do it. You have to do it. You just said you talked a big game right
there. Smell the, smell my knee. You send it to me first and I'll do it. I'm a man of my
word okay send me ten bucks and I'll smell the poops come on let's go all
right this guy's getting fucking you know I do that for free I smell poop all day
you should see my pants you see my so I'm wearing brown pants for a reason
yeah you see my shorts they're shorts for a reason that's right so the poop
flies out oh my god wait you you subtracted $10 from my Venmo account
- Smell it right now.
- Okay, hold the mic up so we can hear you smelling.
Come on now.
- Do I have to do like a deep smell?
- I'll hold the mic up for you.
- No, no, I gotta go.
- Okay, you have to do it.
(sniffing)
(laughing)
- I didn't need to do the second one,
but that's how much of a man of my word I am, okay?
I sat there, and oh my god,
I feel like I just like railed an Adderall.
- Yeah?
- That is a, that's magical.
And it didn't smell anything like poop.
it smell like the bad thing is bad thing is he does now have panleukopenia I got a
dog can't get it they can a dog can get it dogs can get it
what about humans yeah you'll give it to your dog you just quarantine in here now
really are you serious wait you just let him do that for only ten dollars if you
had known he had to quarantine here you should have at least paid him out for
the week aim you should have paid him enough money that he could get food here
for a week and you put him up you know he has enough money on his own in one week
I'm gonna get a text from Patrick this is lol can I have that $10 back I know it I
just know it'll be fine whoa guess I'm gonna do it that ten bucks what I'm
gonna buy this exact pair of pants I'm gonna wear them next time you're wearing
wearing them. That would be cool if we got matching pants. He's lying. You're lying.
If that happened, he can't order the same thing as someone at a restaurant. I'm going to start
doing that. Every time I see you with a new thing, a new item of clothing, I'm going to
buy the exact same thing. I'm going to set up a security camera outside of your apartment
and every time I see you walk out in the morning, I'm going to change clothes into whatever
you're wearing yeah yeah and I'm gonna buy a sideways hat now yeah wait where can I
buy a hat that's sideways what it's like oh do you make these guys I have my hat
like this no not the I want my hat like this I need to buy a sideways hat none of
these are going to go into the barber and have a your hat forward and so I
want you to make my hat like this yeah can you figure out a way to do that I
don't know I don't know if I'm supposed to go to the hat store to you but
somebody yeah it's supposed to do a custom I already have a backwards one
okay and I have a forwards one but I really need a sideways hat I need it I
need it and then in Cambridge and Boston really yeah yeah I know I know every
square yeah yeah it's the one in all the boxes yeah it's like yeah I walked by
that it's like the wand guy in fucking Harry Potter he's like trying to find
- Yeah, he's measuring your head.
I mean, I might have been just me.
He measured my head.
- Yeah, it needs to measure your head.
- Oh yeah.
- Maybe he saw you walked in, your head was bald,
and he thought you were just the mannequin
that was coming in.
- I think he, my head is so big,
he probably thought that I was like trying to do--
- Your head is not, put this on.
- No, you have a, I mean, come on.
I have a big head, okay?
That doesn't mean that you don't have like a freakishly
like fucked up head size.
- I've learned recently--
- I have a normal big head.
I fit in a 7 and 5/8.
Knowing hat sizes is the ultimate sign.
That just means you wear a fitted hat.
No.
Yeah, it does.
I don't think most people who wear a fitted hat would, off the top of their head, would
be like, "I just learned I can wear this size of fitted hat."
It's on the gold foil sticker.
What are you talking about?
You're supposed to leave those on.
You put it on and you feel how it feels.
If you know the numbers, I think there's something up.
No.
That just means you're buying them online.
I'm sorry to make...
I think you're just being contrarian.
Yeah, you were you were just trying to throw a wrench. It doesn't make sense that there's sizes. I think that I okay
5 15 it makes sense that their sizes
Could it make sense that there's
50 I think if there's a running commentary in your head of what size you learned you just you just running comment
You said he just learned that he can win. He literally just said I just learned I can wear this size of hat
I just learned things every day. Does that make me anything other than a myth buster? No, it doesn't I learned that
maybe the flood is one of the best things that's ever happened to us today. I think the flood is
making me feel, I will say, all this talk about floods making me have to pee so bad
but I'm holding it in because that's the kind of show we are now. Yeah I've been
holding in my pee too. Everything is being completely, there's things at work that
you fucking small-minded piece of, you wouldn't even know. There's so many things going on behind the scenes.
You don't know what's coming and when it does come it's gonna, buddy, you better
buckle up because it's gonna hit you like a fucking freight train okay? Yeah.
We're gonna be bowled over.
- It's gonna hit you like a Ziploc bag of bricks.
- 100%, you're basically, I mean,
what we have planned for this next part of the year,
you're gonna die.
You're gonna fucking die.
- All of you.
- All of you are gonna fucking die, okay?
- Yep, so don't come to our live show
if you don't wanna die.
- 'Cause we'll fucking kill you.
- And we're gonna scare you to death on October 31st
at the Bell House. - We're getting all of our fans
in one house so that we can slaughter all of them
in one fell swoop.
Yeah, fucking animals. Uh-huh. Maybe even less like animals and more like blades of grass or weeds like nothing nothing just without
We're doing it at the bell house the bell house like and and and the type of ringing the bell like a like
You know what it's not even like animal slaughter
It is now that I think about it more like plant slaughter cuz nobody is nobody wouldn't care is like gonna shed a tear
It is gonna see this and they're not good. They're gonna say great. Yep. Won't even make the news
He's gonna see this and say they'll be talking about a high school football
Lois we at the clam I just parted so bad we have to shut off the recorder and
leave that. It's gonna break all the electronics. I believe that okay but go to the bell house go to
swag poop dot com slash shows. Go to the patreon go to the twitch
channel and tell Jubio that Jubio timber is still happening bye bye