come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
you're a scrap monster
it's a while
world
uh...
you are great at coming right out the gate of coming up with something
fucking hilarious to start the episode
you just know how to keep the energy up instantly it's like let's fucking go dude
I was gonna do my Muhammad Ali milk milk lemonade and then you did woo it's a wild one.
It was good.
No, it was funny though.
It's a song.
He's mad at me.
Stop defending him.
You are mad at him.
I am mad at him.
He was being so rude to me.
He just was mocking you.
It's not that big of a deal.
That's really rude.
Mocking is rude.
You're still in the copycatting is rude phase?
How is it fake?
I get one day, listen, I get one day of not seeing my friends for a while and being sad
I get one day.
I get one day to complain about my friends being rude to me.
I think that's fair.
No, you don't get that.
I think it's completely fair.
I need a one day.
I did do it.
I left it at the door.
I complained about my friends.
It's not my fault that you were sick.
It's actually your fault that I was sick.
Yeah.
And I surprisingly didn't get it.
So you get to be rude to me.
Why would I ever be rude?
Why would I ever be rude to me?
Exactly.
Why would a friend be rude to a friend?
That's a good point.
That's a good question, right?
Yeah.
That's a damn good question.
I don't know.
You're the only one who dodged COVID, dude. Straight fucking neo backflip.
Probably because I think I might have had it and then we went on tour.
You think you gave it to the Northeasterners?
I think you probably gave it to the Northeasterners.
I was probably asymptomatic and then I gave it to every single fan.
Yeah.
Because I tested every day before we left and I kept coming up negative, but when I
stopped testing was when we were on tour.
So I only tested positive the day that I was asleep for like, like I was feeling sick for
like four days and then on the fifth day I just felt like I was only awake for like
an hour. I mean I stayed inside well there's two reasons I stayed inside
because I found a stray cat yeah I was watching it mm-hmm and but also I was
staying inside I caught up on a lot of shows I'm on season three of
Better Call Saul now. Holy shit you started on season zero like yeah you're at zero
holy fuck that's crazy that's great yeah I had an interesting day. I watched 100
movies yeah I watched I watched the kids stays in the picture
what's that is this this documentary it's narrated by that's a goose robert
Evans where they take the photo yes they cheese and die that's a spoiler actually
they don't that's what it says at the end it's a documentary about Robert Evans
who was like the like he was like a head at Paramount or something. Yeah I know Robert
Evans I'm reading the Chinatown book right. Yeah yeah so so it's his
documentary and it's all narrated by him it's all just like like old archive
footage it's really good check it out but there's a scene in it where he's
talking about. His mom was a hoe? No the first time where he gets he gets the
script for Rosemary's Baby and he's like like I needed like I needed somebody to
direct this and I met one of my best friends, Roman Polanski. He says something where he's like talking...
He gets Roman Polanski to come to his office to read Rosemary's Baby under the
guise of it being a skiing movie and he's like "the kid asks me is it about skiing
and I say listen Polak you read that script and if you don't like it I'll
take you skiing anywhere in the world. I did, I'm reading the book about how
about like how Chinatown got made and in the introduction it was
it's about Jack Nicholson, Robert Evans, something Thorpe and
Roman Polanski. Robert Evans, he is the most wives of anybody in the world.
Yeah so it was like it was describing like their their little stories next to
each other was like you know Jack Nicholson was having this love affair
with this actress and and Robert Evans was his love life was troubled as well
and Roman Polanski had his share of ups and downs. The Roman Polanski it's so
funny that like Roman Polanski is the one the one thing that can undo like like
ever everybody over I would say like 30 years old yeah and the industry loves
Roman Polanski and I mean but they will talk like for hours about how he did
nothing wrong yeah and they love him he's the best guy ever and it's all completely overblown
everybody fucking signed it that's the thing Sigourney Weaver i learned recently everybody
i was reading Sigourney Weaver's wikipedia page you could probably count on on one hand
i got a lot i got caught up on a lot Sigourney Weaver's wikipedia better call Saul
straight to the sexuality section so you get a chance literally everybody signed that that
petition or whatever yeah i probably could have been bullied in the in the 90s into signing that
You wouldn't have had to be bullied in the 90s. Yeah, I would have probably just
everybody would sign it. Yeah, everybody did. I'd be like, oh, okay. Yeah, Roman Polanski.
Oh, yeah, I think he made a movie. Oh, he made a great movie. Like, I'm sure everybody that
signed it probably didn't know at the time or something. No, people knew. No, yeah, no,
nobody cared. He was on the fucking land. He's still on the land, technically. It's true. No,
everybody just... It's not... You can't excuse it. There's no... It's not that they didn't know or
that... They just all love him. They love what he did. It's so funny. That guy did
crazy crazy life crazy insane life holocaust survivor charles manson charles
manson murders your wife you you make the greatest movies and then you rape a
child that's like a fucking that's like i think it's like the odds i mean that's a
roller coaster
i'll say i'd say it's mostly down i would say it's two downs
Which one's an up? What are the ups? Three downs, one up. I mean it depends on how annoying his wife was. He was married to Sharon Tate too.
Yeah. That's a loss. Sharon's taint.
Sharon's taint. Eww. He was sharing her taint with every fucking... With every Tom, Dick and Harry in Hollywood.
Yeah. He's sharing his wife as a whore and his wife as free love. Dude, that movie is so fucking funny.
The Kid Stays in the Picture.
Because it's literally like he just like says like
It's just so funny. It's just a guy who was just addicted to coke in the 70s, and he was just like I'm addicted to the movies
Yeah, and they think they're addicted to the movies. No he's addicted to the to the fame. Yeah
He just like the way he talks about all the shit in them
Oh, oh, there's a there's a scene where he gets the script for Chinatown
and he's like and I pick up the script and just like its title it's completely
Chinese I don't understand a goddamn thing in this script but I know Thorpe is
a good writer it's true it's a great movie I watched it on a plane for the
first time couple years ago and I was like good move I'd never seen a Roman
Polanski movie and I was like holy crap Roman Polanski this fucking guy
is crazy yeah the penis huh he directed the penis look excuse me directed a
dream Adrian Brody's penis excuse me what you said what we also directed a
potion right I don't know I never I'm always in Chinatown I think you should
watch a movie that movie's good he directed Adrian Brody's a SNL music
intro oh no way where he's in the Jamaican outfit yeah hmm
I actually don't think you directed that. I went to the gym this morning and I did not
see Roman Polanski, although he would stick out like a sore thumb at my gym. He is tiny.
Yeah, five foot three. I got big guys over at my gym. I was doing, there's an exercise
called a skull crusher, right? That's not an exercise that somebody pranked you. No,
it's called a skull crusher. You hold a dumbbell on top of your, like you lay down like this,
One of the big guys at his gym was like, "Yeah, this is called the Skull Crusher, right?
I put your head between my thighs and I lift you up."
That's just my thighs.
Honestly, that would be a complete dream.
But I was doing it and I realized that with these shorts, my little morning penis nub
was just like, it looked like I had a fucking M&M right here.
was just catching the light so perfectly. I looked down, my nub was just so... it
looked like I had the smallest penis in the entire world. You must have. The
only time you ever talk about your penis is you talk about how small it is. It
gets really really small in the mornings. Yeah. Like really really small and so I
was just looking at it and I was like... I'm exercising. I'm like pushing up a
weight on top of my head like... Yeah. And then I had a hat on and my hat fell off.
So it's just a combination of me sitting there with the smallest penis ever and
imagining like a hot girl watching me and then my hat falls off to reveal I'm
bald. I just started laughing so hard and I dropped the dumbbell and it hit me on the forehead.
And then I just left the gym. It was the last exercise I did. I couldn't stop laughing. I was laughing so hard like into my hoodie as I was
walk around the gym just like that.
(laughing)
Fucking, that's the stupidest looking thing
anyone's ever seen.
- Did you have headphones in?
- I had headphones in too.
- Okay, good.
- So I'm listening to like--
- If you didn't have headphones, that happens.
Somebody's watching you, sees your tiny penis.
- Yeah, like oh this must be like a--
- It sees your half all over your ball,
then you just start laughing and walking around the gym,
and then you leave.
- This must be one of those like social experiment breaks.
- Listening to DMX.
- Yeah.
there, my penis is the size of an ant and it reveals that I'm bald. I should have
farted. I should have dropped the weight on my stomach and farted like the
Pillsbury Doughboy.
Oh, and then do a somersault while farting.
Yeah. It was so funny. I don't know when I'll be able to exercise again because
every time I do it, I'm going to think of that moment and just how funny it was.
Yeah. Speaking of penises, the other day I was in bed.
Yeah. He gets into every story he needs to tell. Come on. Every story in his
- I'm speaking of penises, go ahead.
- My girlfriend was telling me to get up.
I was trying to sleep in, and then I started
pretending to have a temper tantrum in the bed.
Like you can see the blank.
You know when little kids have temper tantrums
and you're trying to wake 'em up?
I was trying to do that.
- He's always trying to wake little kids up, Drew.
- I was trying to do that. - Going to their bedrooms.
- I was trying to do that.
- And they always have temper tantrums.
(laughing)
They always say, "No, I don't wanna get out of my bed."
- No, like you do the thing where it's like,
like that, and you hit the sides of your leg.
Why are you describing-
You know that kid you do with-
The thing you do with kids where they go, "Ugh!"
No.
When you're getting them out of bed.
Why are you trying to-
This is- This gets funny and you guys aren't even letting me fucking finish it.
You have a- You have your-
'Cause you have to get one thing in every single time.
You have your mommy brat, uh, sex relationship.
I understand. Go ahead.
I was doing that as a joke and then I- I fully punched myself in the nuts.
The hardest I've ever, ever hit myself in the nuts.
Ever?
Did you threw up?
I almost threw, I rolled out of bed and almost puked on the floor.
Damn.
I would love to accidentally hit myself in the nuts hard enough that I'd throw up someday.
See, now that would have been funnier if I didn't get interrupted by you guys trying
to call me a pedophile.
Us telling you a pedophile is way funnier than you just hitting yourself in the nuts
accidentally.
I don't think so.
It would be funny if you hit yourself in the nuts in front of us right now.
I'm not going to do that.
And I got to see it.
That would be funny.
And also that you didn't throw up.
My is it throw up my friend his brother got in a fight a couple weeks ago or some
shit and he like they like he just showed up that at his parents house the
next day with like two black eyes like what happened he's like oh I got in a
fight but it was fine. He just started projectile vomiting everywhere. I thought that was such a funny like like the you
projectile vomiting because of a concussion? Yeah, there's no hiding that.
yeah you get into a fight and you have first of all you have two black guys you
should cover it with makeup I'm just I'm just goth now yeah I just became goth
my older brother every time that he would go to parties or something cuz he you
just would like throw up when he would drink yeah but anytime that he threw up
when he would drink like the he would pop blood vessels under his eyes oh god
cuz he would puke so hard ah he'd come home from these parties after throwing
come and he'd be like I like I was not out doing anything last night I was not
doing a single thing and meanwhile he's got like just completely like like just
red dots all under his eyes and he's pale white just from bruh seriously what
exorcist mode it sounds like you know I haven't been drinking I've been I did
last night I tried the Heineken zero that those when I was a like sober for
six months and I would drink those I would get like projectile diarrhea
Really? Because it's just wheat.
For me it just blends.
No alcohol in it. It blends right in. I mean I only had one.
It just blends right into my drink.
If you drink three of those
in one night. Why are you drinking three of them?
Because I have
There's no alcohol in them. I have an alcohol problem.
There's no, you're so sick of it.
And I'm trying to replace it with something. So you're doing binge
fake alcohol drinking? Yeah. I was just like
oh the taste of the beer sucks. Because I have a living
where I need to constantly be sipping something.
There was one, Kai sent me one of those. I get that.
I that with the seltzer you know those those fake reddit posts that people
always post there the am I the asshole ones I sent me one that was like
there's no way this is real, but it was making me laugh so hard this guy who
he said he was a recovering alcoholic and he would so but he like so he would
drink a bunch of non alcoholic beer like to replace it or whatever and he said
in the post that he would he would drink it in the morning at work.
I guess you technically can do that.
And then people were like, yeah, and he was like,
"My coworkers are getting mad at me.
"They're always making fun of me."
And people were like,
"Well, you technically can do that, but you shouldn't."
And he's like, "Yeah, and I'm shotgunning."
(laughing)
- Shotgunning a non-alcoholic beer?
- It's so fucking funny, dude.
- It does taste like beer, to give it, you know.
- Heineken Zero, though, tastes like, no, no, no.
- I mean, Heineken tastes like shit anyway.
- Yeah, but Beck's non-alcoholic.
I've never had Beck's beer.
- I don't think they drink it normally.
- No, they do.
- Do they?
- I went through every single non-alcoholic beer
when I was like, I'm gonna be completely sober at 23
and I will never fall off the wagon again.
- You try the IPNA?
- Yeah, I would get IPNAs and then there was
a Hoppy Refresher.
Hoppy Refresher's good, it's just a seltzer.
- What's that, a frog drink?
- It's a seltzer, yep.
- Come on, pound that out real quick.
- I'm gonna pound that one.
- Gotta respect that.
- Hoppy Refresher is just--
- Respect that work that you went into that one.
That was a classic.
It's just a seltzer water that they put like hops in it or something.
Yeah.
And it's pretty good.
But IPNA gave me diarrhea.
Beck's non-alcoholic tastes like raisins.
It tastes like if you liquefied a raisin.
Can you imagine how much of a bitch you'd think your dad was if you walked in and he
was drinking a hoppy refresher?
Right?
While he's watching football?
Yeah.
Fuck you, dad.
I guess you, I guess there's a lot of context for seeing, I feel like if you see your dad
drinking a hoppy refresher, there's a lot of context, there's a lot of prior stuff that
probably happened.
- What a pussy, dude.
What if you walk into a bar--
- Out of all the options.
- You're like, oh, dad, what kind of whiskey do you drink?
He's like, I just put dye in some water.
- Yeah, soda and bitters.
- Yeah, no, it's not even soda and bitters, it's just water.
- I was doing that at the bars, too.
- Soda and bitters.
- We would go to bars.
There was like six months where I,
like when I moved to New York, I was completely sober.
- Yeah.
- And I did not know what to do with my time.
- You just try to learn how to do a back flip.
- I did shit like that all the time.
- Yeah, that's how I've been feeling
last couple weeks. I felt I mean I know it's good zero, but zero tastes exactly
like Budweiser. If you drink Buds you guys tell you this much you got zero buds.
Nobody wants to hang around with your farting ass. You probably drove them all
away with your alcohol. You know what the best sober beer is?
Water. Nice. Two liters of water per day. That actually doesn't
taste anything like beer though. Yeah but it's actually delicious in its own way.
Yeah, you're sober like a gopher huh? Yeah, it's actually delicious in its own way water. You were straight edge for a bit. Yeah
I still I forgot about still completely straight edge
I'm gonna claim straight edge if any hardcore fans are listening to this or it would take it seriously come and kill me
Yeah, cuz I'm lying
I'm gonna claim the edge till I die and I'm gonna drink every night straight edge people
Dude, straight edge people are the biggest fucking wimp losers in the world.
Yeah, no, trying to make not drinking tough is so funny.
Yeah, it's like, I know that you are not as tough as a drunk guy because you have inhibitions.
Yeah.
You have like...
There's... you were proud of yourself.
Yeah, like you have some... yeah.
You have...
You have shame.
There's no...
A drunk guy has shame.
Yeah, there's nothing that this guy won't do.
Drunk guys will bite you in a fight.
Drunk guys will fucking like...
Yeah, they'll...
I mean...
hit you with a car. A drunk guy, he's a danger, he can make anything a weapon.
He's a danger to himself and society. Exactly. You might be just a danger to society, this
guy might actually kill himself trying to kill you. That's the worst part about straight
edge people is because they're a danger to only society. And they're so good to themselves.
Exactly. They're treating their body like an actual temple. And they're protecting themselves,
playing balloons tower defense with the world. Straight edge people are exactly like Travis
Bickle and Taxi Driver. It's the same level of derangement where you're training your body
like like okay Travis Bickle what you're training your body to get to for your wrist to get burned
by the stove what situation you're going to need that in. Yeah what touching a hot doorknob. Yeah
like it's never going to happen. Yeah what are you trying to be? Sticky bandits? You're gonna
have to walk a straight line someday. It's not gonna matter. That's just the truth. Yeah.
if you're running away from a crocodile you want to run zigzag not straight line
a drunk person has the edge on you there that's right you're walking wobbling
one foot in front of the other walking all the way down yeah get eaten I will
say those those straight edge guys do do make the best music to to get drunk -
uh-huh they do they make the best music that is not true no that's not true no
it's not true pirates do that's true pirates make the best music.
I think it's like cool.
I think that straight edge guys make the best music to take and add a roll and get all of
your chores done too.
I think all of these are not wrong dude it's all like cool black guys.
I think everybody makes awesome music.
But I'm saying in I'm putting like cool moving the goalposts.
Cool black guys make the best music for every all the best music is made by cool black guys.
who make straight edge music? There is but it's not as many as there are guys who
look like me. I look like a straight edge front man. Yeah. Yeah. You should get
X's on your hands. I know. I was straight. I was straight. I claimed
straight edge until I was like 16 years old. Yeah. And my brother tried to get me to
get a straight edge tattoo when I was 13. That band Project X. I said no. I think
the cover of that that EP is just like a guy with a tattooed X on the back of his
hand it's cool and there's one line so first I think the first line of the
first song in that album is like I'm as straight as that line that you start up
your nose not very straight if I'm cut now tell you that much yeah yeah I don't
know how to do that yeah yeah straight edge guys make cool music as long as
it's not about being straight your shirt is caught on your chair yeah I did that
I did that completely I was just fiddling with my shirt okay I thought you nerded
out here no imagine does it look nice I
imagine he was in your class and he did
bullshit like that would you fucking yeah
I was like sure his ass going to the
principal what kind of okay well I think
he's going to have a chair like this a
really nice cool would have that
technology magnet school fucking asshole
yep might have a comfortable your
charters cool yeah a charter school yeah
a charter center for inquiry where I
went a charter school but like stop
autography school that's why it's called
the charter school you went to a farter
school no I went to I went to the wayside school and there's some sideways
stories I got it so I went to the Cartman school yeah yeah the Cartman
school of authorita yeah I'm respecting authority yeah I went there I seriously
did you know and I majored in remember when Cartman saying I majored in fat
and this and insulting that was a college no it is a children's elementary
school I went there the uniform yeah looks exactly like Cartman yep mm-hmm
tell you what Carmen fat piece of shit Carmen not a good friend honestly
fucking asshole rude chili made a Scott Tenorman yeah mommy and daddy yeah we
tell you when we see uncle Matt no we need to talk to him about that yeah he's
gonna yeah he's gonna stop he's gonna stop promoting Cartman yeah yeah it's
This man pushing C.
Uncle Matt does that. He's heavily involved in the Cartman promotion business.
Oh, dude, you love Cartman.
Yeah, he's got some C. Oh, wait, we should announce...
Speaking of, yeah, we should do it.
We should announce up top.
Wait, what are you...
Up top.
It's in the top 30.
Top 30?
Halloween night.
Prepare for a fright.
Yeah, Halloween night.
Ghosts and goblins up in your sight.
They're going to be in your sight.
If you're a Brooklynite.
Brooklynite.
Brooklyn night there's a ghosting I'm gonna be in your sight yeah they're
gonna do a show at the bell house show at bell house yeah doing a show at bell
house so if you like what Patrick is doing there's gonna rob this job
that's exactly like it sounds like frog zombie come on
sounds exactly like Rob's like Rob's zombies being squeezed like a toothpaste
tube. More human than human. We're doing a show at the bell house on Halloween night.
You need to take some gas x. You sound horrible. I gotta go to the bathroom. We're gonna be
doing a show at the bell house Halloween night. I'm fighting so hard I got shit on my dick
yeah. There's gonna be a. It's not a good enough impression for you to keep doing it.
You need to stop. It needs to be over. You're wearing the headphones. We have a paranormal
investigation that we're premiering there. We're flying out to do an
investigation on a haunted museum with Uncle Matt. We're filming it.
It's gonna be exclusive to the show. And you need to come
because we're gonna have great guests. We have
we have a serious squirrel squirm scary squirm we have scary pierce
scarpion scorpion and the devil scorpion the devil real life coming in from hell
or to be announced yeah more to work more chewy to be announced we're gonna be in
costume well I won't reveal what our costumes are gonna be we have a big plan
dressed up like a bumblebee I'll be a Pokemon yep I'll also be a Pokemon
probably okay so it'd be drill be two different Pokemon yeah so what if we
were all you should come in costume - yeah yeah no everybody yeah we're gonna
have a costume contest we're gonna look we're gonna look at everybody in the
audience only costume contest so nobody should it there's gonna be it's gonna be
a lot of fun we have a lot of stuff for us a lot of big plans right we will say
barred from entering the for the costume thing you can come dress in a costume
but don't dress like a ho yeah don't dress like I don't see any slutty cats
or mice or oh I'm a ho ass police officer I'm ho ish I'm ho ish Michael Jackson
don't yeah I'm a slutly Madonna don't do it I don't want to see a ho ish cancer
patient I don't want to see ho stuff did you see what did you see Bill Maher's
costume slutty Steve Irwin it was so disrespectful. There's nothing scarier on
Halloween than a ho's butt but I still don't want to see that bullshit. Yeah you
know let's leave the butts at home. Let's leave your butts on the toilet and in
your bed and on the seat. But you can get tickets at swagpoop.com/shows and you
seriously don't want to miss it. Or eventbreak.com/6238C11123
You say onion?
Onion.
One one onion.
Eventbrite.onion.
You can only get these tickets on the dark web because it's a scary show.
That'd be a fire ass URL page.
Eventbrite.onion.
You don't want to miss it.
Yeah, so we'll see you there.
And if you miss the show, you'll never get to see it again.
It's a special Halloween night show.
Yeah.
And it only comes once a year.
And I heard, and this is not what I want to say.
not what I want to repeat. I heard if you are a New York resident, I heard this
from Eric Adams. If you don't go to the show, you will be placed on the sex
offender registry. I heard this from Eric Andre. He said ranch ranch it up.
I actually heard that from him personally. He told me to ranch it up.
I heard and I heard that real from Eric Adams to an Eric Adams as well. I heard
huge fan of Adult Swim. Eric Adams loves alternative comedy. He's an Adult Swim diehard superfan.
And that's why he says if you don't go to the show you'll be placed on, your house will
be put on family watchdog. I heard that Eric Adams about this Halloween show said awesome
show great job. Tim and Eric Adams. That's right. Now that Eric Wareheim's got a food
addiction, they gotta get a second Eric on there. He's addicted to pizza and wine. Yeah
so now they got to get a different guy to rehab because you're addicted to pizza
and wine. You show up to alcoholics anonymous to be like yeah, i've been
drinking too much wine and also eating way too much pizza with me.
Who with me i've had a big problem with wine, but it's mostly pizza yeah yeah.
I mean you know and chicken sashimi. I drank two bottles of wine last night and
and I went over to my pizza and I just kind of experimented with new different
types of semolina.
And I went outside to my brick pizza oven.
It cost me $6,000.
I'm completely addicted.
I'm addicted to this pizza thing.
I've been thinking about getting a pizza oven.
It'd be cool.
In your apartment?
Yeah, I've been thinking about just installing one.
Just put a -- yeah.
Yeah, you don't need a bedroom.
You just sleep in the living room.
Listen, I'm on the penthouse top floor, third floor suite.
I think like two or three months ago,
our friend, you made fun of our friend Bob
for having a pizza oven.
- I just wanna point out, you're a fucking tattletale cop.
You know that, you realize that?
You're such a baby for remembering things like that.
- You made fun of our friend for having a pizza oven,
now you wanna have a pizza oven.
- You think I really wanna put a pizza oven
in my fucking apartment?
Is that how dense you are?
- I think you actually do.
- I do, I wish I could.
- And he admit, oh my God, he admit it.
- I struck at him out of jealousy.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
And guess what he also, he gets to play golf all the time.
You think I get to play golf all the time?
- I hate him so much.
- I live like a slave.
- He has the best life.
- I have the worst life fucking ever.
- We have the worst lives and this man
has a beautiful pizza oven.
- I'm a fucking henchman.
- He can be addicted to pizza.
- We're the bottom bitch of New York podcasts.
We just walk around and get our asses fucked.
- Everybody spits on us.
- Every other fucking comedian and podcast,
they spit on us.
- Every single comedian hates us
'cause we tell all the truth.
- Sorry, I'm toiling over here.
I'm toiling and all the other comedians and podcasts they sell out all their
shows instantly and it's like if this show doesn't sell well something bad
might happen to me yeah yeah I might do something bad to myself yeah this show
doesn't sound like everybody else's hands yeah yeah so bring you don't go to
the scariest Halloween of my life yeah and it's nice and it's a nice it's a
nice time I think it's what is it seven or eight or something probably doors at
seven I know it's eight it's the one that neither of those are true
the show is at midnight I think it was 730 doors 630 but let me double see you
can do that then you still got time for trick-or-treating yeah yeah and guess
what Halloween this year it's on a Monday night so your Halloween parties
they're gonna be on the weekend before that Halloween party after the show no
at Patrick's apartment and in a in an undisclosed at a location. Yeah, it's 730 show, 630 doors. It's
nice. It's nice and early. Oh yeah, you'd be out of there by the whatever 10 o'clock.
By 8 o'clock.
Yeah, 745. You're back on the streets knocking on doors.
All right, dude, we should do some trick-or-treating this year. Oh my god, I would love to.
And our costumes. You know what? My costume came in the mail and I sent you guys a picture of it.
What do you guys think pretty fire I've done I've been trick-or-treating near
nary 40 times right and I've never once
well how you manage that what do you mean you go around you go around twice
that doesn't count as if you go around twice it doesn't count as two separate
I've got in different that's one that doesn't count that's one I hit the
north side shout out north side then I hit the west side shadow well that's all
one side shout out to that's all one then I hit the dirty south so that's all
one trick-or-treating. What if I take a nap between them? That's still one trick-or-treating.
What if I'm on the Uber-Mitch sleep cycle so that isn't even a nap.
That counts as my sleep. Trick-or-treating happens for all of Halloween.
That's a Halloween day the entire day. But what if I be doing that before Halloween?
If you do it on different days, that counts. So that's what I do. Okay, so you completely changed.
No, I just remembered. Trick-or-treating is whenever and wherever
you get candy on Halloween. And I be doing the trunk-or-treat as well. What's the trunk-or-treat?
retreat never did trunk retreat at church. No, where you go and you and it's
trick or treat, but you don't get to wear any scary costumes because the devil
likes that and it's all people dressed up like Power Rangers and there's a cake
walk and you Bob for apples. What is a cake walk? That's where you walk around
in a circle and wherever you stop you want a cake.
It's like basically musical chairs, but yeah, with cakes with cakes. Yeah,
they had that with a yo back at that with ham back in my head a ham walk.
(laughter)
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- I had a parent-teacher night.
- It's so long!
- What the fuck is a cakewalk?
Oh yeah, we had that with the ham.
- Yeah, my seventh grade.
- You had a ham walk?
- Oh yeah, it's like a ham walk.
- What the hell are you on about?
- My seventh grade, they had like the parent-teacher night
where it's like the kids and the parents show up
and it's like, "We're doing like a meeting."
And they gave out a ham.
- Are you bloody mental?
Are you daft?
- What the?
(laughter)
- This is Mrs. Vessels and--
What the bollocks are you on about?
What the hell is that?
They gave a ham out?
That's the most insane shit I've ever heard.
That's crazy. Ham.
Like a big honey baked ham.
In a bag.
Like the ham from the store.
For like $11. And then my aunt won it.
And then my aunt Maureen cooked the ham.
Like a spiral ham.
Yeah, my aunt Maureen had ham for dinner that night.
That's crazy. I might be conflating
two things.
I might be conflating no cuz I think she she definitely won a ham from my seventh
grade teacher was it refrigerated was it just sitting in the it was it was a
raffle that goes on for like a month where you find a ham is like at the
front of the class I had to ask her well I know that my aunt Maureen wanted
smoked I guess you should be able to that should they should be like a reward
We could go to the grocery store on the corner.
We could do a ham walk at the live show.
Did you just say we could buy a ham?
Of course we can buy a ham.
Yeah, we could go buy a spiral ham right now.
You say they have them at the grocery store?
We can buy one?
They have them at the grocery store.
You are fucking...
We could go buy one.
Something's wrong with you.
Of course you can buy a ham at the grocery store.
No, I'm just saying we could do it right now.
No, we can't.
We're recording the podcast.
We could pause and then go get a ham.
And do what?
I don't like it.
not the same as pausing and going to get beers because there's no distinctive
opening click sound that you can do with the ham. We could we could we also have
an oven. We'd have to eat it cold. We'd have to put the glaze on and eat it
completely cold. That'd be disgusting. It'd be good. It's like icing at that
point, the glaze. I talked about the chocolate ham, right? Yeah. Same cousin,
same mom, same cousin, same mom, same cousin, same mom.
When he was like four or five,
he was obsessed with Scooby-Doo.
And I've talked about this.
He was obsessed with Scooby-Doo
and he saw Scooby-Doo put chocolate syrup on ham
and said, "Mom, for dinner, I want,
"my birthday dinner, I want chocolate ham."
We all had to eat a chocolate ham.
- You all had to?
There was no option?
It wasn't a condiment?
there was an inox regular pisa you know option but the each other there was only
that are cake did they get that
knows i need to know if i have a more cake
and in the truck with him
okay we didn't even need it so you try other world and i i gotta try it now i
think you need to use your senior you're making a whole it all this i was about
this no option you had to talk with him you didn't even need it because my mom
about that
on my daughter's
My mom probably is listening and will text me about the chocolate ham.
I would say you were one of the fucking all ham all-stars.
I didn't eat that much ham growing up.
All ham team.
My dad never made spiral ham.
I've never heard more ham stories in five minutes.
My dad's a turkey guy.
Yeah, everybody likes...
My dad can cook the hell out of a turkey.
Ham is the worst part of the Thanksgiving dinner.
It's even worse than the turkey.
Well see if you grow up with it yes, but if you didn't grow up with it it becomes a delicacy
The spiral ham is a delicacy
Boy that's true if you didn't that's not true about like everything
Ham is a spiral ham is a delicacy
In America ham is a delicacy
He just drooled all over himself
You fucking just spit drool everywhere. He's so he's just thinking about
So wet and watering
You know, I'm learning, you know, how I like
In like Japan they'll eat like they eat like shark fins or whatever and they also eat fried chicken
It's like well, they're always and it's people are always like, you know in Japan like that's like a delicacy
No, I say it's a delicacy. Do you think in like Japan? They're like, oh in America they eat ham
It's a delicacy to them probably love they love ham. They probably are in America
Peanut-butter-jelly sandwiches a delicacy
That's literally what happened with KFC dude, I had a real I was like reading about this this weird KFC in Japan is like
It's like oh, it's a delicacy. Yeah, you only eat it once a year you eat it and you eat it on Christmas
You eat it on Christmas and they sold it the guy who I heard it at in in Los Angeles popcorn is a delicacy
Corn is more commonplace in Los Angeles. It's just like the side
nothing. I heard that in the Sahara Desert, water is actually a delicacy to a lot of people
there. People just sell popcorn on the street in Hollywood, California. Literally, it's
like everyone I know who grew up in Hollywood says something about like, "Oh yeah, we used
to eat like ribs with popcorn." Like the East Coast popcorn is just not as good. You got
to go to the West Coast to get the popcorn straight from Hollywood. Something about the
butter that the popcorn tray from Hollywood the water there is different
and it's I don't know why it affects the corn but it's just it's better like
like like like like anthropologist who's like studying culture being like yeah I
want some hot some Hollywood we should get some we should get some popcorn yeah
Hollywood style popcorn. Speaking of Hollywood and movies we actually do have a list. I just want to give you my popcorn secret.
Let's hear it really quick. If you take you take a kettle corn and you put the
garam masala in it it's pretty good. I put I put spray deodorant on mine. Yeah?
Yeah. Axe chocolate. Best popcorn for me I put my saliva on it. No I do women's
deodorant. Yeah? Because it makes me horny. That sounds good. Yeah cuz it got like
female pheromones they put in and extract them from squirrels. Cool. Yeah.
Female deodorant doesn't kill you. Male deodorant, you put it under
your arms and make some rock hard like the thing. Well, it takes, well female
deodorant has female pheromones in it and male deodorant has male
pheromones in it, aluminum, which we all produce and women go crazy for. Why do you
think they use it to cover their food when they're cooking? Oh my god, now I
I just realized that. Women love to roast a pepper and cover it in aluminum because a pepper is phallic.
So I found this forum thread here. This is speaking of Hollywood and popcorn.
This is Mr. Movies?
This is Blu-ray.com, which apparently they have a forum on Blu-ray.com.
And this is in the movies subcategory of the movies category of the Blu-ray forum.
The other day I saw a photo, it's one of the worst photos of Doug Benson I've ever seen,
but it was on blu-ray.com is this the same website if it's blu-ray.com it would be
the same website yes okay that's lit that's lit as hell um this is a thread
so I thought we you know we it's no secret we love movies we talked about
movies a lot already today we were just talking about great about where we love
movies we're great at movie ideas we're always coming up with good movie ideas I
feel like maybe we could we could make a career that's true yeah I think we could
I think we could make a career is as script doctors and kind of a ritual
- Retool movie ideas and make movie ideas better
and we could probably market this
and I wanna do this as a--
- I forget both of you guys have college degrees.
- I wanna do this--
- Almost have one.
- Not almost.
- He was on--
- I was on the path to almost having
maybe a screenwriting degree
or just a general movies degree.
- Guys, this is important.
- Sorry, sorry, finish your intro.
- This is for our careers, okay?
If you wanna ever work in this industry
without a college degree, you better listen
'cause what we're doing today
is I found this thread on blu-ray.com
called movie ideas by this user here
valerious and I thought maybe we could
read this person's movie ideas and we
could kind of script doctor them for
them and this could be you know we could
send this as a resume to the big shot
Hollywood. Now this is making me think too much of
college. I think I'm blacklisted. Yeah
really this might be this might get you
out off the list I think if we do a good
enough job. This is making me think too
much of college and now I just want to
pound a beer. That's right. Here's the
beginning post of the thread okay. I want
to play beer pong or flip cup. Okay this
This is my third thread so far, Whippity Pow, and I found hopefully the right forum to do
this.
Post your movie ideas right here, because I've been planning this for some nights now, so
have fun.
Note, the phrase Whippity Pow is used in the 1983 Mexican cartoon movie, Katy Caterpillar.
I feel like using this phrase because I feel happy.
note the 2008 movie Little Big Planet will appear in this thread since it fits
okay is there a movie is that is that photo is that katie caterpillar i would
assume that's katie caterpillar is there a little big planet movie can you check
i have no idea let's i don't feel like there's not a little big planet movie
but there may be an animated short let's see 2008 i think that's the year little
big planet came out it's that is the year little big oh well here's there's a
on movie ideas wiki we have little big planet the movie this seems like it let's
see if this is the same this could be the same person. I'm not sure they have a
let's just do this for they have a bit of a transcript. All right, let's read
this here. The characters are sack boy. I call sack boy sack Cole and sack girl.
I want to be sack and sack mom and sack dad. Okay, I want to be sack girl. Okay
and sack mom. That's what you are and I'm sack dad. Okay part one introduction.
Hello sack Cole. Hey sack boy part two girl talk
Sack girl admit it you like sack boy. I like him the three girls giggle and squeal
I'm out sack girl rides her skateboard and exits part three fourth wall
Hi, yeah, what part for the end
Thank you, you're welcome
Deleted scenes one sack boy is zip riding it to school to the four girls are trying to get a date three sack
Mom is punched by sack boy. That's rude. Yeah, wait. There's some quotes
Oh
They have a cast here sack boy voice by Frank Welker a teenager with no personality in sack girls love interest sacral voice by Greg
Griffin a tomboy in sack boys love interest
Saki voice by Matthew Lillard a weird risk hidden sack boys best friend the movies rated PG
Wow okay no wait wait look at that note note do not take this seriously oh it's
a comedy well damn okay that's why there's punching moms let's that's why
sack boy see sack mom and sack mom and sack dad get into you can you it's it's
implied but it's not explicitly written that sack dad is beating the crap out of
sack mom and sack boys learning from his dad and he's having an incestuous
relationship. So mostly what the Little Big Planet movie is about is about the
cycle of abuse. Yeah. But it's not serious though. But it is, it's a
light-hearted... so this is like the I, Tonya of Sackboy movies. You know what's
the movie that I've always wanted to see is a virtual buddy movie. Interesting.
Yeah. Right? Okay. Where maybe you get... maybe you can get Sackboy as a
virtual buddy skit. Well that's what I'm saying and maybe he's getting it
exploded and stuff and we hear we hear I hurt myself today and maybe we're
sending nuclear missiles at his body and he's looking like George Bush and crap
he's jumping all over the place getting points and stuff yeah to see if I still
feel right yeah and I don't really know where I would go from there.
Well it wouldn't be a parody song that would be kind of disrespectful it's more
about it's more about it's not it's not hurt it's kind of a movie that self-harm
Patrick you're just making it's not Johnny Cash it's not like when they when
Polaris did hey Sandy for Pete and Pete and they changed the lyrics I don't know
what the hell you're fucking talking about or like when they change the
friends theme song because it used to not be I'll be there for you I don't know
what I'm gonna ignore you now okay all right I'm just I'm gonna read I'm gonna
to read valerius is for music version of now that we have the now that we have
the background of little big planet the movie from two thousand and here's
valerius's first movie idea i should start with the first little big planet
movie that i'm planning to make the plot to it after a sighting of an unknown
spacecraft has landed on the ocean side of earth the ocean side sasuke from
pan yo and pan yo discovered a very new life form a sack alien named sack boy
together with the help of other unordinary people they need to stop an
alien threat from destroying all of Earth companies Walt Disney Pictures Marvel
Studios Pixar Animation Studios Studio Ghibli and Amblin Entertainment rated pg-13
for intense sequences of sci-fi action violence and disturbing images okay this
sounds a lot different from the movie we just yeah read the script for got a
ponyo yeah it's got ponyo in it and you know what it would be it said Marvel
Disney Amblin it would be a great merger. Who's Amblin? Amblin is a Steven
Spielberg. Amber Pamblin? I think that means ET might be in it.
Yeah I think ET yeah ET's definitely gonna be in it. Yeah if it's about aliens and it has Amblin.
Yeah if not in the movie in the title card for Amblin.
it really amblin right Easter Sunday yeah wait I think Easter is Easter Sunday
made by amblin or dreamworks I don't know Steven Spielberg's involved I'll and
that's all I know about it so we get Joe Koya's kind of licensed yeah yeah he
could he looks just like him just have you cross hatch him I like this I will
say as a professional screenwriter I like this idea but it needs more we need
of screenplay needs a beginning middle and then this is just a beginning. So
here's my thing if you're already going PG-13 why not go full are even x-rayed
and show full penetration on Sackboy. Well yeah, he has a zipper and then
he could he could unload his big white cock. BWC. It was cocks white. Sackboy is
not a white guy. He's Sack. His insides are white. I just I want to do big white
white cock. I just wanted to see one so I put it so I just involved it yeah.
That's a fine say what there's no there are no bad ideas and screenwriting
actually yeah in regards a big white no definitely the fucking sack boy and
then a bad idea Luria says that's my first movie anyone want to join like
join on as a producer or something because yeah I would I would join I
think I could be a good et then we got then we have this is ten minutes later.
i should bring in a new movie idea so here's this one the math bear movie
all my god the plot to it a band of thief bears plans to attempt to steal twenty
million dollars from a high facility protected bank is the math there the
bastard squad what else can go wrong companies warner brothers pictures
village roadshow pictures metro goldwyn-mayer fund a mation gonzo be
trained productions rated are for extended sequence of strong bloody
pervasive violence had language throughout and for some sexual contact
So this is my question. Wait, Gonzo the production company or Gonzo the Great?
What do you think?
I don't know.
That's why I'm asking. Companies. Companies. Okay, well the company that these
bears keep could be Gonzo the Great. Well they might be doing some Gonzo pornography
filming. This seems more in line with your pitch. So what I'm saying is, here's what I'm saying.
So the Bastard Bears, okay first of all the movie should be called The Bastard Bears.
The Bastard Squad. It has nothing to do with math except the fact that there's a number of money
- High number of-- - Yeah, which I guess is,
maybe there's a scene where they're adding it,
they're like, wait, how much money is that?
One dollar plus one dollar, they're counting all of it.
- They have a calculator, they're doing--
- Calculator, but here's my only punch-up scene, right?
One bear, he's barely legal, he's 18.
- That's his name? - Yeah, his name is
Barely Legal, yep. - Barely Legal.
- And that's a part, maybe we rename the movie
Barely Legal. - 'Cause they're robbing.
- Yes. - Oh my God.
- Also-- - That's perfect.
- Also, the newly 18 young stud of a bear, right,
and he's been trying, well all these older women have been trying to fuck him the whole movie.
He finally shaves his pubes, or his hair, but he thinks it's his pubes because he's been
watching too many YouTube tutorials.
He unfolds his fucking hair, peels it back with a fucking, with a peeler, like a potato,
big white cock.
Big white fucking dripping cock.
That would fit perfectly with some sexual content.
Oh, yes.
It might not fit perfectly into a woman.
I think that would bring the movie up to NC 17 maybe well no because they showed a penis
in Boogie Nights.
It's animated it's like it's like fucking hot dog party or fun.
It's fun.
A funimation.
Yeah it's funimation.
Yeah so it's an animated movie obviously we don't have real bears that can do this kind
of stunt with a big white cock.
Well they did it in Jackass.
They had a bear doing a stunt but they cut out the part with the white cock.
That was in Jackass 4.5.
They put the part with the white cock in.
I might have to check that out.
yeah proof of concept yeah and then valeria says about twenty minutes later
or even know less than twenty minutes later want me to go into details of
these two movies just replying to themselves yeah just all this and then
this this person here this amaze runner another user does kind of this is kind
of an inside baseball movie idea. So this is something that maybe could break out
all like a small scene yeah it's exactly like money ball this says jennifer
lawrence fan and monterey jack are blu-ray dot com's biggest theatrical
fans and their worlds come crashing down when their local
theaters close for good due to covid. Both users are eight
hours away from the nearest open theater and it's the same movie
theater. Brie Larson is going to make an in-person cameo for a
re-release of Captain Marvel at that theater in two weeks and
there's only one ticket left, but the theater doesn't do online
ticketing. So the two blu-ray users who have no vehicle and
can't drive must race to that theater to see who can get that
final ticket. Who's Monterey Jack? These are two, I think
to
past or something good idea and it's Jennifer Lawrence yeah doing an in-person
meet-and-greet because one person has clear motivation there not saying who
Jennifer Lawrence and who does she play mystique right yeah so she's there with
her blue breasts just one blue and who does she turn into Johnny Sins Johnny
guess what white well you it's blue it says pg-13 movie you can't show a white
cock in that you could you can get away with one can't show white cock in a pg-13
You could show...
You've never turned over a DVD thing and said PG-13, mild violence, mischievous themes, and
big white cock.
I will say...
PG-13 movie and I... because I'm... it usually says unrated on the front, but then on the
back it says PG-13.
Yeah, that's true.
This one does not specify PG-13.
Oh, it doesn't?
No, it doesn't.
I must have misheard.
No, you misheard.
I was...
I will say, any movie...
I mean, knowing the Blu-ray community, any movie that's going to be centered on this community,
gonna be at least x-rated yeah all right we can put a big it down we put a white
cock in this whatever yeah we'll put that's the main note I would say for
this one a white cock well especially Jennifer Lawrence I think that a lot of
people might actually enjoy that yeah she's so it's a big white cock fucking
blue breasts what she can't fuck her own breasts in the movie so she half of her
is blue yeah and then the bottom half has a male genitalia white cock white
white cock and she looks like a cat dog but half blue half cat half white cock
yeah and they're talking there's gonna be a spin-off cartoon called blue and
white cock in there and she and it's a remake of blue cock white call blue top
white cock here's a little thing called a blue and white cock here's a sequel
idea from valerius okay okay little big planet two the plot of it years have
since sack boy met Sasuke and Ponyo.
Sack boy is now an adult, but he gets sucked into a virtual
reality game called Sword Art Online.
I really don't like the name "Sack Adult".
He's stuck there and has to fight Nexus,
a program that gone into Sword Art Online and takes control.
Along with Sasuke and his new partner Asuna from Sword Art Online,
they go on a journey to fight Nexus and save the people who's stuck in Sword Art Online.
Companies Walt Disney Pictures, Marvel Studios, Pixar Animation Studios,
entertainment studio Ghibli rated PG-13 for intense sequences of sci-fi action
violence and frightening images. This is Spy Kids 3. Yeah, first of all this is Spy Kids 3.
Second of all it seems like that's just putting Sackboy and
Ponyo and Sword Art Online. I don't know why they have all the other
entertainment companies. Yeah, they need production companies for money.
If you guys don't like this idea I'll just throw in another one right away.
the sequel is completely soft more yeah yeah we'll tell we'll throw your
slump this is the this is a different one okay okay this one out for you
Pikachu the plot to it after the events of Pokemon the power of us Ash Ketchum
gives up on Pikachu and Pikachu has started to be wild okay when he gets
attacked by a Tyranitar a villain saved him Harley Quinn Pikachu and Harley
Quinn teams up to save Aurora City from the tyrannical hush who wants to
destroy both humans and Pokemon the Ash Ketchum saga is coming to an end
companies Warner Bros. Pictures, The Pokemon Company, Legendary Pictures, DC Comics, Syncope,
rated PG-13 for sci-fi action violence, disturbing images, and thematic elements throughout.
So that's Hush from Batman.
That's what I would guess.
Okay.
But I really don't know.
So if you know it, Hush is one of, is like Bruce Wayne's like equal.
Hush is like, he's like a surgeon.
If I'm remembering correctly, Hush is a guy who gets a bunch of surgery to look like Bruce
Wayne what and he starts doing crimes as a villain yeah that's so fucking funny
it's cool yeah I bet they're gonna do him for the next Batman movie so to put
hush in it he probably dresses up in girls clothes - yeah Bruce Wayne no that's
what he does that's a good idea he dresses up as Bruce Wayne and and become
a lady yeah he probably does like super kind of like sus shit yeah you know so he
probably goes to a glory hole and sucks it off on video. Yeah, people does glory
hole pictures as Bruce Wayne. People are starting to get angry at at Valerius.
Okay, so really is post an idea for a little big planet three the battle for
Earth. Yeah, Ronan the accuser is plan to take over Earth and make it extinct
forever. Yeah, the other guardians etc. etc. It's guardians of the galaxy people
are somebody post a YouTube link the Truman Show. What the hell are you
talking about? Valerius is I'm taking that I'm taking it that nobody's liking
threat don't understand what the third little big planet movies about someone
says what about little big planet four and puts a nail-biting of animated
emoticon which I think is probably sarcastic unfortunately someone says
this isn't even interesting trolling and then and then Valeria says there is a
little big planet for I'll talk about it once I'm done watching a video here
about alcohol and all that how to prevent it how to prevent alcohol so
that ties into the straightedge thing we were talking about earlier little big
planet for dark planet. So they finished watching the video about about alcohol.
Wait, wait, wait. Can you when did they post that one? Wow, 707. They became
dark and twisted. It took 37 minutes. They became dark and twisted because they
realized the reality of alcohol addiction. Yeah. And they made a dark
planet episode. Dark planet. The plot. Sackboy has to deal with his enemy years ago.
Scorpius from Farscape. What is Farscape? That's an old sci-fi show. Okay. If
Sackboy wants to save Earth, he'll have to fight Scorpius on the dark planet
get dacker companies, Walt Disney Pictures, Marvel Studios, Pixar
Animation Studios, Amblin Entertainment, Studio Jubilee,
rated PG thirteen for intense sequences of sci fi action and violence and
frightening images throughout and also how to prevent alcohol. Try not to
take it always look at what you're drinking because you might die from it.
Do not take alcohol a message for you before I go on with more ideas that is
there is a little bit planified by the way. Have fun with that
that's actually fucking real shit.
it's so true yeah just pay attention to what you're drinking and don't take
alcohol. Little big planet five rise of ultron the plot ultra has been set from
the future to destroy the past sack boy and his new crew of heroes must take
down the ultimate threat. Well, that will determine the future of the planet and
it's the same studios, the same PG thirteen type writing back to the
pikachu movie. How do you think of it being directed by Christopher Nolan? I
think honestly, Chris Nolan like once he gets done with Oppenheimer and shit,
he might knock that out of the park. Nolan's Pikachu is probably going to be
the the blockbuster hit of the
trailer where it's like in the world will change and it has like a countdown
the most important creature in the world and then a light.
I'll be going now. See you guys tomorrow. Does he come back? I honestly
didn't read this far in the thread because there's I will say we won't get
through it because there are twenty three pages of this.
there's a message there from COVID. Who was banned. Holy shit. Thank God they banned COVID.
Yeah, I would hope so. Okay, honestly never seen a thing like this before. A little worried to post
here, but here's the one movie idea I can recall creating outside of fictional things I've written.
This must be what got them banned. This is a good movie idea. Title, isn't it? Dot, dot, dot,
question mark. Also chose the tagline, not what you're thinking. After that, admittedly zero
development except for how it would go as the phrase go a hundred and film have
before and then left turn issues I found every time I think it through is there
are 100 ways a million stories go so too many unused to choose from not only that
but many likely unchosen due to the inability of people to find ways close
to them which I would obviously have to do if I chose the not overdone
continuation this is a genius idea this guy wants to make a movie that the story
has a twist that people that the story hasn't done before and it's called it's
called is it and the tagline is not what you're thinking and the twist is that
something happens that's a total left turn uh-huh it will be hard to do
because there have been hundreds of movies the twist is something happens
that you're not expecting that's the twist that's pretty genius idea that's
pretty fucking genius maybe the twist is kovat 90 oh shit well I'm a little big
planet Dark Phoenix there he made a Dark Phoenix movie well this is a little big
Little Big Planet six Dark Phoenix, so it's different than the normal Dark
Phoenix movie. You can kind of guess what this one's about yeah. Here's
another one goes bigger. This time the new Avengers the plot after the
events of Little Big Planet six Dark Phoenix sack boy now has amnesia and
does not remember anything from meeting up with a mysterious bear doll named
joy from napping princess the both in them and the new and recruited members
must fight off against Dark Helmet from space balls from taking the planet's
there again the same companies here. These are all so so valerius is just good at
just making amalgamations of of movies little big planet seven origins the plot
after the events of the new avengers sack boy meets his bloodline. Vincent
Valentine, final fantasy seven yeah and it just it keeps going this person. I
will also I don't drink beer only root beer. So is this don't listen to them
just drink a couple of beers and everything will be okay and then
valerius replies and says I don't drink beer only root beer, but not other
beers, but thanks for your support. That's very nice only root beer for
very. I really want
somebody asked can Pikachu get Harley Quinn pregnant. That's not how the
movie went, but there were a few suggestive moments where Pikachu
actually kisses Harley Quinn having no idea what he's doing. I like
valerius. I like valerius. I'm just saying that the leader is has yeah
benefit of the big planet ate the summer soldier.
(laughter)
"Ready to PG-13 for intense sequences of sci-fi action violence, gunplay language, and some suggestive comments."
What is the summer soldier?
"Sackboy and Vincent fight against an advanced soldier from Sackboy's home planet that is destroyed."
Okay.
"Sackboy has to fight his own battles if he wants to survive."
I noticed the description of these plots are a little... Oh, the Math Bear movie 2!
Oh, the Math Bear movie 2! The plot! The bastard squad is back!
black the street time this time no rules to the game when the math bears are
assigned to steal one billion dollars at a casino ruthless ganglord brian griffin
from family guy goes in to kill the bastard squad off what are their options
rated are for strong bloody violence and pervasive language throughout and for
some sexuality and we already know what that is yeah i think we know exactly
brian and train here's the here's a here's a twist you could put this in
isn't it brian griffin shaves his hair off guess what's underneath his white
here.
Black dog, you know, no, just a big black cock, okay, so he's got a it's kind
of a reverse of the bear. Oh my God, it is I'm scrolling or got to a little
big planet eleven. There's so we the new avengers three patamons awakening part
one holy shit. This person is it is an idea machine. The math bear movie three
busted no blue bear tries to get rid of his paranoia of clowns. He talks to his
therapist about his paranoia, but sooner or later he has his paranoia consuming
and he becomes a clown himself. The Bastard Squad has to find a way to bring one of their
compadres back. Rated R for horror violence, grisly images, and strong language.
No nudity in that one. If you like LittleBigPlanet this much, I'm
sorry to say this, but this will be the end of it.
That's horrible news. Maybe that means there's an extra, maybe
that means there's a last one. There's new movies. Maybe Sackboy, holy shit.
I hope so. LittleBigPlanet 12 Last Life.
There it is. Yep, that's probably the last one.
Wait, will you scroll up for a second? I saw something about anal sex.
Oh yeah here it is somebody posted a movie about Freddy Krueger and Jesus that
has anal sex and animal torture they're kind of being a mean and they said
jokes that Beyonce and Miss Swan from that TV are gonna be in that the new
Avengers for the case of Pikachu we've got here the animos oh there's a new one
this is new the animal it's a set in the same universe I'm seeing now but it does
to bring Hamtaro into the mix. Okay, it's pretty big Puru so this mit here's the
cast of the math bear movie. Since people are liking it, Blue Bear, Brad Pitt,
Red Bear, Channing Tatum, Green Bear, Mila Kunis, Yellow Bear, Angelina Jolie
and here's the spoiler for the day in the new Avengers three, Patamon's
awakening part one, Brian Griffin makes an appearance in this movie, but is a
reincarnation of Megatron from Transformers. Holy Shit, all right, so I
I mean there's some this I will say I eventually I feel like we can come back
to this because we are we're not even like a quarter through of the movie ideas
yeah this is also only one of many threads that this person has and also
something I noticed when we started recording that I didn't look at yet it
shows I think you can view what their blu-ray and DVD collection are and see
what movies they own they own okay it looks like a lot of Marvel movies here
only on blue I said right well these are blu-rays they had a lot more DVDs okay
some anime they have Jurassic World Fallen Kingdom they have the Hunger Games
Mockingjay part 2. Let's look at their DVDs they had 219 DVDs. Wow they have
10,000 BC that's sick. 13 going on 30? Dope. Agents of Shield. What a good
they have Dragon Hearts. They have the entire Dragon Hearts. Holy crap. What a collection.
They have multiple Fantastic Four movies. They have the Equalizer. They have the Dark Crystal. Gemini Man.
I mean, I've seen some Godzilla movies here.
Make no mistake, this is a film buff the likes of which we haven't seen since Godzilla.
Jonah, a VeggieTales movie. I mean, this is, yeah, this person, somebody in Hollywood needs to reach out to Hilarious.
This is the kind of cinephile that needs to be working behind the scenes.
Absolutely.
Right? Their talents are wasted posting on this Blu-ray forum.
So if anybody is on a, if we have anybody from any talent agencies who are listening, please sign this person.
Please, yeah, send us.
Sign Hilarious.
of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles DVDs too. Oh yeah, Secret of the Ooze. Wow, so many. Oh
my gosh, a lot of X-Men. I mean great, great, great stuff. Great ideas. Great movies that
I like. Almost no notes besides the big white cock thing. Yeah, listen, I mean the big white,
you could add a couple of big white cocks and make them maybe spurt cum and... And maybe
have it beat up at the tip a little bit right before it squirts out. And part of it, it
could be a sex appeal thing, but then in some movies you could actually use that for comic
relief because what's funnier than a fucking big white cock nutting all over the floor?
Yeah. So there's my only notes.
The funniest part of every movie that I've seen is when they jizz on the lady in the end.
Exactly.
And that's the...
Talk about a twist ending, isn't it? It's not what you're thinking.
And the Halloween live show will have a twist ending. I'm just realizing now that I think
about what we're talking about right now...
Yep.
But it doesn't involve jizz.
The twist might be that it involves this.
There might be jizz. I don't know.
I don't think there's going to be a cum shot at the show.
I think there might be a squirt shotter.
there might be a come shot but go buy tickets to it at swag.com/shows
and uh bye bye bye tickets