Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay. - Okay.
- All right. - No mommy.
- I think we got it to work.
- Oh my God, dude.
- No mommy, I think we have no,
this is, mommy's gone too.
- Mommy's completely gone.
- Mommy's out of town. - She's out of town again.
- And it doesn't matter where she went.
I don't care if she's with other boys
and being just completely out of town with other boys.
because she's not here. And the important thing is the two kids and
brothers, you and me, actually learned how to press all the buttons and start all the things.
We learned how to do the recorder and we learned how to do the... I guarantee you that somebody's listening to this
right now and it's just completely... Well you have the headphones on. Yeah but I
have bad hearing because I actually have bad hearing. Why didn't you let me do that? I had bad hearing. I had an
ear infection when I was nine years old. I ruined my hearing forever. Really? Yeah, every
time I open my mouth I hear four pops. I have TMJ. I have TMJ, that's what the
doctor said. I just didn't know if you knew what TMJ was. If I click my... If you click
your jaw... I can hear yours, that's weird. That's not what I have. Yeah, I've
definitely done it on the show before. Oh, that's scary. Yeah, I have a lot of dental
stuff that I... I should start a medical GoFundMe. Definitely, you should. I really
I can't afford any of these fucking dental bills
that I have to pay.
Don't you have a dental credit card?
Yeah, they made me take out a credit card.
The dentist did.
The dentist fully made me take out a--
The dentist said, "First of all,
"you need a credit card."
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, I had $8,000 of dental work I needed done,
and then I couldn't afford all of it,
so they made me take out a credit card
for the remaining $3,000,
and I've been paying that off for the past two years.
Wow.
Jesus Christ, that's so much fucking dental debt.
I know. And I have like probably like $15,000 more dollars I need done.
What the fuck could you put... Are you getting shark teeth put in your mouth?
Yeah.
What are you getting for... Really?
I'm getting full... I'm adding more teeth into my mouth.
More lit rows of... That would be cool to get rows of human teeth.
Yeah.
See, this is the kind of stuff that we only come up with when mommy is completely gone.
When mommy is not here.
When mommy is gone, the company--
Watch this.
Yeah?
I just took a bite of a banana.
And nobody can say anything.
And nobody yelled at me.
'Cause I don't care if you eat.
I'm not your mommy.
Right?
I'm just your brother.
I'm just your twin brother, and I'm sitting across from you.
We're two twin brothers.
It's just that simple.
And Cameron is a complete mommy.
Mommy is not around.
Mommy is not anywhere to be seen.
I don't see a mommy.
I think it's $15,000 a dental day.
It might be another $8,000.
Did they say you have to, it's gonna be 15K.
- I have to get my wisdom teeth out,
and then I have a bunch of cavities
that I need to get fixed.
- I mean, how many is a bunch?
Is every single tooth cavitied?
- Well, I also need to get a,
the reason that I have cavities and chipped teeth,
I have a shit ton of chipped teeth.
- Mm-hmm.
- And a lot of like--
- You have a shit ton of chipped teeth.
- Yeah.
- I mean, come on, no mommy.
- I have this one cavity up top,
and then I have to suck food out of it,
and then when I do, it tastes bad.
You know what I really want?
It constantly takes notes.
You know when the dentist is like burning your tooth
or like grinding your tooth down with the thing
and it smells like burning bone?
Your dentist burns and grinds your teeth?
With the little Dremel thing?
With a pickaxe?
No, nobody's ever put a Dremel in my mouth.
Well, you've probably had better dental health than me.
When I go to the dentist, they...
And I brush my teeth generously once every two days.
And when I go... I'm 100% serious.
And when I go to the dentist, they go like, "You've been keeping up on brushing, haven't
you?"
And I say, "Yes, ma'am."
And I think the reason why, I've thought about this before.
I think dentists...
Maybe because you call them ma'am and sir.
I'm very polite.
Maybe they're like, "Well, let's kind of tell them."
Let's kind of tell them.
Let's cut them some slack.
Yeah.
I think that dentists have an inflated idea, or a deflated, I guess, of what average dental
hygiene is because most people lie to their dentists and say, when they're like, "Do you
brush twice a day?"
And they go, "Yeah."
But if they brush once every two days...
See, I actually do brush twice a day.
Really? And you're that fucked up?
Yeah.
I hate brushing my teeth, man.
Me too.
I hate taking care of myself.
I don't like showering.
I don't like brushing my teeth.
You should see what my bedroom looks like right now.
My girlfriend hasn't been, like,
she's been off on business.
Yeah.
I have not cleaned my room once.
That's bad, dude.
That's how I used to be in Boston.
Yeah.
Baby girl used to come over,
basically just clean my room.
Clean my room and I'd make the worst
fucking dinner the whole time.
I guess my roommate was telling me last night,
said that like one time I was here recording or something and she was like
staying over and he heard a bag full of bottles clinking in the living room and
Neil walked out and was like what the fuck is going on and she was like oh he
thinks I don't know he hides bottles under his bed. I'm not doing like a full deep clean you know I'm not
I like that a deep clean to you is just getting the bottles off the floor yeah I
I live like that lady from Evangelion most of the time.
- Never seen that show.
- Yeah.
- I've never seen any, I've seen Naruto.
- I used to, so I got into Naruto the week of my birthday
and then I bought a shit ton of Naruto action figures
and then never watched Naruto again
and then just had all these fucking Naruto action figures
for the rest of my life.
- They're cool, dude.
It's cool that he, I only think I started watching--
- I used to get told I looked like Rock Lee.
- Who's Rock Lee?
- The guy with the bowl cut and the big eyebrows.
yeah. Because when I was a kid I had a bowl cut and big eyebrows. Yeah I've seen
pictures of you as a kid. Yeah. Yeah you do look like that a little bit. Mm-hmm.
Have you been watching Naruto? No, no I watched it as a child. I watched it as a
child and there was a part where he becomes naked. He's a child. He's
eleven years old. He's a child and they make him naked. He tries to seduce old old men who
look like the Jedi of whatever they're called. Uh-huh. He goes yeah I'm gonna use
my sexy jitsu on you. I haven't seen it in a long time. I forgot about sexy jitsu.
And the clouds cover his mom's pubis and his nipples on his breast.
No, you see most of the breasts, honestly. Really? Yeah, and so the guy, he goes
"sexy jitsu" and then the guy who's got gray hair, this guy's got to be in his 50s or 60s.
There's a poster! There's a poster! Oh yeah, there's a Naruto poster.
Oh my god, I cannot believe he was right behind me the entire time.
It's my girlfriend's Naruto poster from middle school.
Oh my god, he's even younger than I remember.
This kid is like nine years old, right?
Yeah.
So he says "sexy jitsu" and then this fucking guy, who's clearly in his 60s or 70s,
gets horny as hell.
He goes "oh!" and then he's got that blush on his cheeks.
I wish that happened in real life.
When you get horny you get those lines.
Me too, that'd be so awesome.
Your cheeks go red and you're like "ooh!" and you get the lines on your cheeks and shit.
That'd be so dope.
you just basically could never go to Victoria's Secret ever again though as a
man that's right yeah walking by I still avert my eyes when I see a Victoria I
don't wanna that's trash complete ho ish stuff godless fucking trash dude why
they dress like fucking it's completely ho ish I'm getting a FaceTime video for
mommy oh do I accept this accept the kamami call hold on hold on hey mommy we
We basically don't need you and we're basically
doing great without you.
Huh?
- What are you guys doing right now?
- Oh, nothing.
- No mommy.
- We're having a no mommy moment.
- Yep.
- And you're basically ruining it by being here.
- What do you mean?
I'm just calling to see what you guys are up to.
- We're staying up as late as we want
and basically eating a fucking over one and a half servings
of food at a time.
- Let me tell you the amount of sugars in this drink.
Oh shit.
- Yeah, yeah, tell him how many sugars.
- 41 grams.
- There's 41 grams of sugar in what he's drinking.
And I'm having caffeine past four o'clock.
Patrick, stop standing on the bed.
Nope.
He can stand on the bed if he wants.
We wore shoes inside today, so I bet Mommy's pretty unhappy about that.
Yep, I'm wearing complete shoes.
Mommy's such an attention whore that she actually has to call us in the middle of the "No Mommy" episode.
I know.
Oh, you guys are doing an episode I didn't even know.
[Laughter]
You're a complete mommy.
You're completely mommy.
What are you guys doing?
If you wanted to be on the episode, you would have stayed here.
- You would have stayed here.
- Yeah, you would have come home.
- Yeah.
- Feeling sick?
How did you even know to call us right now?
What is wrong with you?
You have some kind of preternatural mommy sense.
- We should have taped up all the webcams in here.
- You guys might be in danger or need me.
- We're not in any danger and we're actually,
we don't need you.
And I would say that you're actually
a hindrance on the episode.
We have a lot of stuff planned.
We were gonna maybe do a--
- Do you guys even care that I'm shopping
at Rope's Shoe Barn in Plastown, New Hampshire right now?
- Where?
- Yeah, mommy's getting a new pair of shoes.
Where?
In Plastow?
- I was born in Plastow.
- You better be at DSW
because my mommy only deserves the best.
- Okay, well you guys behave, okay?
- If you're in Plastow, you should go to the Savers.
It's really big.
- Yeah, I know about the Savers here.
- The Plastow Savers is really, really big.
- This is a conversation,
this is a mommy-son conversation.
She can call you on your jitterbug.
- That's true.
Not my jitterbug, my firefly.
firefly yeah okay okay okay okay he doesn't know about the new TV oh yeah no
we didn't definitely get a new TV okay bye mommy yes Joe Joe gave us a big what
is that like 70 years TV yeah we don't know where to put it but Joe just put it
right in front of Caleb's desk yeah I just can't even access my desk yes I
I think we could put it on this wall, maybe like hang it up.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I feel like it's kind of fucking annoying when your mom just like, unrelated to the TV thing.
Yeah.
When your mom just like can't fucking leave you alone when you're just trying to have
a fucking good ass time with your bro.
Isn't that fucking annoying?
Dude, you're preaching to the choir right now.
Right?
Knocking on the basement door.
What are you doing down there?
I made ants in a log.
Yeah, it's like bitch, I know that you're coming down here.
And I'm not going to say bitch to you.
I'm gonna say "bitch" to my friend.
I'm gonna be like, "Bitch, I don't want any ants on a log, thank you!"
Yeah, well you say "thank you" so she doesn't know.
Yeah.
But she can feel it.
"Bitch, bitch, you stupid bitch."
I actually don't want anything to do with you, mommy.
And I don't want your ants on a log.
That's not for me.
I would hate it if I got ants on a log right now.
If you're gonna bring me a snack, can you at least make it like pepperoni?
Beef jerky.
Or beef jerky.
Pepperoni beef jerky.
Pepperoni jerky.
You know when you buy the pepperoni in a bag?
You ever get that as a kid?
I never bought, see when I was a kid, I was a very weird child.
I found out that Hannaford Supermarket, my mom talks about this all the time, you could
buy a wedge, it's like a little small wedge shaped box full of shrimp with cocktail sauce
at the tip.
That sounds so good.
Oh, you told me this, you ate 25 of them.
No, well I have eaten a whole bag of shrimp before.
That's awful, bro.
In a sitting.
Shrimps freak me out.
I used to, it would cost five bucks, it was like a little shrimp cocktail thing that you
could get on the go.
My siblings would be getting candy bars and shit and I would come back with a little thing
of shrimp.
That makes a lot of sense to me.
That you'd be like, "Oh no, I don't like sweets, I like savory things."
And somehow, even though you were eating shrimp cocktail as a kid, still got fucked up teeth.
- Yeah.
- I was eating all the candy I wanted to.
- I was also eating a lot of candy too.
- Oh yeah, that's a bad combo.
- If I had the opportunity to get shrimp,
I would get shrimp every time.
- Shrimp over candy.
- Shrimp over candy for sure.
- That's honestly crazy to me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I feel like, I still don't like shrimp as an adult.
I went to, I got some shrimp shumai.
- That's insane.
- Ugh.
- You're crazy for that.
- It's like five--
- Shrimp is my favorite food.
- But those baby shrimps they put in shumai,
it's like 5,000 fucking crushed up shrimps, disgusting.
I like that. You're just an odd duck. I can't believe you're my twin brother.
Mm-hmm. Makes almost no fucking sense. That's like with my roommate I eat
sardines and every time that I'm- You like sardines. If I eat sardines and he's
in the same room he says he he goes he makes like a noise and leaves the room.
Really? It affects him that deeply? It goes to his room. I've never- If I eat
because I made I made like a sardine toast. Uh-huh. I just took like a nice
piece of sourdough, layered out the sardines on it, ate it like that with a
little bit of, you know what I put on it? What? This fucking goat cheese.
That goat cheese that comes in the terracotta thing. I knew it was gonna be something. I knew it was gonna be goat
cheese. Yeah. That means that Neil is fucking, he's fucking, he's a
Greek-a-phobic, Greco-phobic. Yep. He doesn't want anything to do with the
Mediterranean people. Yep. Because he thinks they smell and their food smells.
You know? And you, middle of the summer, you're sweating. I know you got a shirt
off in that kitchen. You're making sardine toast with goat cheese. I mean you look like
Pestanopolis or some shit. You're sitting there, you're looking like a Greek god and he's jealous.
I do look like one of those Greek gods but if it's the Greek god of diabetes.
No because they would get way fatter. I'm not going to say you look like the Greek god
of Apollo. The Greek god of 24 hour diners.
Yeah, something like that. Yeah, no, you would look right at home with like a...
Like a tank top with like a...
Big rag on the side.
Big rag on the side and I'm just like shaving Euro meat off of a spit.
Yeah, exactly. You're just sweating so much. I've been doing it for 50 years.
Oh, yeah.
I saw a video the other day.
I have a big Greek flag pendant.
Yeah.
I think I should start dressing like this.
I think you should too. I saw... You know what I hate? I've been seeing a lot of people
dressing like they're in the 1970s recently a lot of them yeah get that
shit out of my face I don't I there's like dudes wearing bell-bottoms again
and it's like yeah like the coolest way to dress is is a like 90s style yeah or
maybe we're in big-ass jeans or like Easter Bunny or Santa Claus but yeah if
you're going 70s you don't don't go like cool bell-bottoms and stuff you know yeah
go like David Koresh. Look like David Koresh yeah or wear like a
pinstripe suit yeah yeah and maybe go maybe go to maybe two decades
earlier or actually you know what no that's perfect two decades 70s but you're
dressing like like really big collar mm-hmm just like the crushed velvet
suit. Do you think that that that late late 2000s early 2010s is ever gonna come
back. It already is. Really? Like teach me how to doggie yellow skinny jeans and stuff?
Yeah. You think so? I think that it's coming back but I don't think jeans that tight will
ever be back in style. But I have noticed an uptick in like, there's like the people
dressing like Y2K. See, no mommy, we can finally do Patrick's fucking fashion corner. Right?
This is what, this guy's on the streets patrolling right now. All day, every day. You're walking
I'm walking around. I'm in Soho. Yep. I'm following these people. I'm in a Sherlock Holmes outfit.
Following tons of women, tapping them on the shoulder.
Excuse me. I'm a street photographer. I'm a street photographer. Can I have a photo?
Can I take a photo of your big-ass pants and your small shirt? Yeah, please.
I have been seeing... yesterday I saw a woman in Etnies. That's sick. Yeah.
That's fucking dope. Like the pink Etnie, like the Molgoth. People are dressing like
mall goths again and I'm like 2010 mall goths and I'm I mean I think I'm I think
I am down with that I think I'd rather you haven't had an episode since we were
in the Pacific Northwest I feel I feel I feel acutely acquainted with the goth
subculture at this point yeah in time went to a place called the coffin Club
yeah there's an actual coffin there and not only is there a coffin there's also
spiders and there's is skulls as well there's a big Ouija board on the floor
yeah and we and there was a little person there and I don't know if that
was part of the theme. Caleb got a text from me at one point. I think I was
upstairs buying a drink. I got a crazy text. I sent Caleb a text that just said
there is a woman here with a slave. And then I looked down at my phone, I
was at the bar, I looked down at my phone and then I looked up and who was walking
towards me but this woman with her slave. She had elf ears on. Yeah and
And you know, at first I thought it was maybe
what would you do episode.
- Yeah.
- And it was like, what would you do
if a woman was walking around with a slave?
- And a goth, but then you had to put,
once you put goth club in there.
- Exactly, it's like, oh well probably,
there's probably more than one slave here.
- Yeah.
- And maybe they take turns.
But I don't know, that slave seemed like she was
doing a damn good job.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and you could tell who the master was
'cause she had elf ears.
- The master had big elf ears and they had them on a chain.
- Yeah.
And I was like, man, I guess they're just like doing like,
I wasn't weirded out by it at all.
- Were you surprised at how okay you were with slavery?
'Cause that doesn't surprise me.
That yes, you, a slave walked right by you and you said,
hmm, okay, interesting.
You said, instead of I'll text my friend,
you should have said, I'm gonna text 911.
- Yeah. - And you should have
called 911. - But I think,
I think it was a sexual thing.
That should still be illegal.
- Yeah.
- I think, yeah, I think slaves,
people fucked slaves all the time.
- Yeah, look at Thomas Jefferson.
- Thomas Jefferson was a fucking--
- They called him the slave fucker.
- They did.
- Yeah.
- He was like, he was putting up wilt numbers.
- Yeah, dude, he was the most prolific.
- Slave fucker.
- Yeah.
- And I don't want, you know,
this person who's walking around the coffin club
could have been the next Thomas Jefferson.
(laughing)
You know?
And no founding father.
She could have been fucking, she could have been--
- You know what was crazy about that was we went there,
then the next day went to Seattle, two days later,
and we did see this small woman who looked pretty old there.
- That's what I'm saying, we saw the same, oh yeah,
it was the same little person.
- We saw the same old little person two days in a row.
- Unmistakable little person.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, and was just walking around,
in two cities, three hour drive apart.
Just walking around.
the same as like going to like upstate New York. Yeah but to see them two times in
a... that's true. To see them on the sidewalk. Yeah. Just randomly. And also...
Seeing them at a goth nightclub and then seeing like it's like seeing like an
NPC at a place it's like somebody's like... Exactly, they reuse the texture. They did like a
console command to spawn them on that sidewalk. It's like when you when you say
when you're in a video game you get a quest from somebody and they're like okay
I'll meet you there and then they stay there and you walk away and then you get
to the new place they're already fucking there that's what it was like oh yeah
it was like she gave us a quest she was like go you need to get as far away from
the slave driver in Portland as possible and we said yes ma'am next day we see
her there right and we didn't even get XP for that no we should have I think we
did I think we got a lot of XP on this trip I think so I think I'm getting
ready to level up yeah I've leveled up to my goth tree yeah I've completely gone
I think I realized that I would be a really fucking good goth based on my looks.
Me too.
You're a little too swarthy, honestly. You're like, I feel like you would go, you'd be, you should be at a pirate bar.
Let me be, I look like a, like a skeleton. You let me be a goth guy.
I think I look more goth than, I think I know more about goths than you.
That doesn't mean anything, you could be a historian, right? That doesn't make you a, you can be a...
I think that's, I think that'd also be a cool look at the goth club, as if I'm dressed up like the gothic professor.
Oh, you could be like kind of a goth Indiana Jones type. Yeah. Yeah that
That bow house record belongs in a museum. There we go say stuff like that. Yeah
Okay, but did goths okay museums then though? No, hey that they go to mortuaries
Yeah, that uh that that alien six fiend record belongs in a mortuary belongs in a mausoleum mausoleum
There we go. Uh-huh easy did yeah, but I do think that God belongs in an alcove
There we go an alcove. Yeah, that's a that's a that's a joke for for real Goths
It's really fucking hard to talk and do all these dials. Yeah, there's two dials
We need to rest. I think I think everybody needs to respect mommy more
I don't need to know cuz by the time by the time that this is listen if I was doing this for three years
I'd be a pro true right and mommy, you know, I love her right? We love mommy
No, exactly a pro at this show. I mean I hate to say it
it. So it's good that I'm learning, you know. I learned how to do this, you
learned how to press play on the timer. Yeah. You know what, I got it the timer to
go up. Oh shit. Yeah, you see how it says up? Yeah. Yeah. That's pretty legendary.
Uh-huh. Pretty cool. Yeah. So now that we've invaded the Goths and I think
they accept us. That's one thing I'll say about the Goths. The Goths are very accepting.
accepting us. So we went to the goth club we went to four different goth clubs.
Yeah and I yeah we did. I'd like to know about some in New York because I again I
really I enjoyed the people. So we went to four different ones then ended up at
coffin club we went there met the bartender then came back the next night
in face paint. Yeah we got a bunch of face paint for our Portland show yeah
and then we didn't have time to take it off before we went back to the goth club
and so we showed up the first night we let's be real we looked like complete
herbs yeah right we're sitting there we looked we looked like we stuck out like
sore thumb we were wearing white t-shirts yeah shit we were thinking more
East Coast gangsta style uh-huh right we put we pulled up on the Pacific
Northwest coast yep right they they checked us they g-checked us goth check
us check at the fucking bar right we already asking us about g-code yeah yeah
- Yeah, we were like, "Oh, you already know what it is."
They're like, "That's the wrong coast."
We were saying cap, we were saying fam.
It wasn't working with them.
- They were supposed to say bat.
You're supposed to say bam.
- Cape.
Yeah, bat, cape, skull.
They say like, "Yo, that's mad skull."
- It is mad scully in here.
- Yeah, like that's skull AF.
Yo, that's brimstone.
Yo, that's some brimstone.
- Yo, you look like obsidian right now.
- Yeah, you straight staked up.
That's what they be saying.
But then they'll say it like that.
- They say stuff like that, yeah.
coast kind of New York accent. Yep. But anyway, then we show up the next day, we
hit the upgrade button. Oh, absolutely. My face, white as snow. Patrick's face,
completely green. It was gray. Completely gray. It was gray because I tried to
layer. My lips, black as night. My eyes, black as night. Patrick's eyes, black as night.
Patrick's lips, wax red lips. Mm-hmm. Just looked like a Mr. Potato Head. I looked
like old Greg. Yeah, you looked completely like old Greg. Uh-huh. Which, I mean,
honestly fit in. I fit in well in there. I wanted to pull up like a mime though. I
think that would have been a better look. Yeah, I think if next time I think we all go
Next time we pull up like mimes. Yeah. Mimes got to be part goth, right? Yeah. The thing is a mime
can't even talk. What's more kind of sad than that? Yeah, and they're always sad.
Goth music, I was pretty surprised. I'd never heard a goth song before that I knew of,
but then we got in there. They're playing like Depeche Mode and shit. Depeche Mode.
if you want to be a goth you gotta say Depeche Mode.
Depeche. No, I don't want to be a goth. I'm a Spaniard. Why are you becoming, why are you
changing up? Why are you changing up now? Because I'm, because I was, I dabbled, right? But honestly
I'm a culture vulture. I'll cop to it. Yeah. I just want to be a fucking culture vulture. You are.
I've been about being goth. You have not been about being goth. You're wearing white. I'm wearing,
I had a whole goth playlist ready when we got to Portland.
Yeah, Spotify presents. Nope. Goth 90s. It was my own gothic playlist. No. I had a lot of...
I had Killing Joke on there. That's a Batman movie. Nope. That's a band.
I like you give a fuck about bands. I do. I give a fuck about the goth culture. I was
pulling up with mad knowledge. I was spitting facts at them. I was educated.
They honestly they thought I was an OG and you know what the G stands for.
- Old goth.
- Yep.
- I pulled up like an OG too, old Greg.
(laughing)
- Yo, he's a OG, OG.
- Yeah, dude, that's OG, that's old Greg.
- Yeah, you pulled up, you were like,
"Yeah, bartender--"
- "Wanna drink Bailey's out of my shoe?"
- "Can I get Bailey's straight up in a shoe?"
- "Can you serve me Bailey's in my shoe?"
- Yeah, right now.
- Thank you.
- I don't like Bailey's.
I don't like any of those creamy ones.
- I don't know, I did, I had white Russians
on Christmas a couple years ago.
ago. Oh, actually, white Ukrainians.
That's in a white Ukrainian.
Same ingredients.
Yeah, but we just don't fuck with the Russians anymore.
Remember, whose birthday were we at?
Did a bar we were at have a white Ukrainian?
Yeah.
I tell you what, a lot of the--
It was at KGB.
A lot of the bars--
It was at fucking KGB, dude. They changed it to like--
That's fucking hilarious.
Yeah, they tried to change other shit to Ukrainian stuff. They were like, "We only sell Ukrainian
vodka."
Oh god. Yeah. Come on bro. Who gives a fuck? Yeah, that's not my war. Dude 1940s. I'm buying it
I'm buying a fucking Jeep tell you that much. Yep. I'm buying it. I'm buying a Volkswagen. That's a damn good car
Right
It's a car of the people. That's what
Volkswagen is a damn that is what Volkswagen translates to 1944 folks folks. Yeah car folks folks
Wagon car 1944 right you got Ford Ford is fucking jacking off making the shit model t
Fucking yeah, fuck you shit. Basically you better
stands for
Turtle shit, it's a complete turd turtle shit does its total shit. It's it. Yeah
Yeah, not total shit turtle turtle shit, and then you got Chevy Chevrolet fucking new gives a shit
Fuck you blue car black car. It's all don't don't care me
Volkswagen, they got a little beetle looking motherfucker.
- Volkswagen, right, you call the dealership,
you're like, I want something nice, right?
Something foreign, right?
I hate these American cars.
Something where maybe the steel came
from a questionable place, right?
And, 'cause it makes it cheaper.
And he says-- - Oh, that's a fly.
- He says, tell you what, bud.
- That's a spider.
- All we got-- - I'd be fine with that as a goth.
- All we got is this Volkswagen Beetle,
steering wheel monogrammed HH. We just got this in. The previous owner passed away and
wanted to get rid of this. Exactly. And we go, "Oh, you know what? I mean, HH, that could
stand for anything. Honk honk. That's why it's on the steering wheel." That's why it's
in the middle of the steering wheel because you say honk honk. That's why it's monogrammed
right there. So you look, you're like, "Ah, really? Where's my horn? Where do I press my
horn again. HH Honk Honk. There it is. See and I'm going okay. You could also look at
that too. I'll buy that. Two HH next to each other. That's the parallel lines in
the middle of the road. Exactly. There's so many ways. It could be two ladders if
you stack them on top of each other. Right? If you overlay them on top of each
other it's just one H. And who knows what that stands for. Maybe just honk
once. Yep. But it's got instructions right there. You know what I mean? I don't know.
I just feel like it's uh, I feel like it with the Russian vodka shit, if you want to enjoy
yourself a fucking Smirnoff Ice, by all means.
You know?
And you know I want a Smirnoff Ice.
Yeah, dude.
You know, when I get iced, I don't freak out.
I actually enjoy it.
It's like basically a sativa.
Yeah.
Beer is an indica.
Yep.
And Smirnoff Ice is a sativa.
Yeah.
And Mike's Hard Lemonade is a hybrid.
I agree.
Yeah.
found out they make is a Simply Lemonade, spiked lemonade.
Really?
Had two of those last night.
Holy shit.
The Simply Limeade, that's a bit of a game changer.
I think that's how I got fat as a kid.
Oh, earlier we were talking about pepperoni.
I don't know if I've ever told you this.
It's really not that important of a story.
I don't know why I'm bringing it back.
When I was a kid, I thought pepperoni was a vegetable.
Yeah, you told me that before.
I did?
Yeah.
Isn't that fucking stupid?
That is crazy.
Imagine if it was a vegetable that tasted good as pepperoni.
There are, well I guess mushrooms aren't a vegetable, but there's a bunch of mushrooms
that taste like, there's like mushrooms that taste like lobster.
Oyster mushroom, I like an oyster mushroom.
Yeah.
King oyster mushroom, that's a big mushroom.
King oyster mushroom, you can make some vegan scallops.
Yeah, I mean I've never had a scallop before though.
Really?
Yeah, I haven't had much.
Not even a scallop and bacon?
No, I've had very little seafood.
I've definitely talked about my scallop and bacon incident, right, where I got food poisoning
so bad that I--
Because you had frozen scallops?
frozen scallop that expired two days, I think, later.
But I, the first time I've ever pooped and puked.
- Like same time or same day?
- Same exact, like same time.
- Wow.
- I was on the toilet and like simultaneously,
it was like a demon was leaving my body.
- Yeah.
- It was insane.
It was like, like, blech, like that's the sound I made.
I sounded like the boomer from Left 4 Dead.
- Oh shit.
- Think about the boomer and think about
how bad it probably smells.
- Think about how bad he feels walking around.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Like he's fucking, first of all he's got
body image issues, right?
- He's got cellulite.
- He's fat as a balloon, he's got cellulite
all over his body, he's dressed terribly.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- That shirt does not fit him.
- Everybody he's running up to trying to touch
are running away from him.
- And then when he gets hit he explodes.
It would be funny if a zombie apocalypse happens and it follows the left 4 dead
rules of like you become whatever you kind of were. Where like oh you're a
you're a woman, you become a witch, you're a fat guy, your whole things you run
around you diarrhea and throw up on people. What the hell is the hunter
supposed to be? I think the hunter is a stoner. Oh because he wears a hoodie? Yeah
- Yeah, it's like a Kid Cudi type guy.
- Oh, okay.
- You know, I knew a couple of Kid Cudis.
I've told you that, there was a guy--
- Oh, the kid who changed his name?
- Yeah, last name Mess Cudi, Dylan Mess Cudi.
- He changed his last name to Kid Cudi's last name.
- As far as I know, yeah.
- That is so sick.
- And then I think he quit rap shortly after,
so he's just sitting at a Best Buy, Geek Squad status,
just with a name tag, says Dylan Mess Cudi.
And let me tell you, by looking at this guy,
you'd never think he's related to Kid Cudi.
blonde hair could have dyed it blonde hair no Frank Ocean okay yeah you get me
yeah yeah yeah yeah remember that time we saw Frank Ocean at that bookstore hey
who the fuck's that guy reading the Berenstain Bears wait didn't it used to
be called the Berenstain Bears? I'm gonna write this book and call it the Berenstain Bears.
It was Berenstein everyone thought it was an E. I think it's most Mandela
effect stuff is just so stupid. Yeah no I think it's real actually. I don't know.
Nobody knows what's going on there could be a Mandela effect.
I don't care. Right? What is it that people think that they... it's funny that
that people think that they just skipped a timeline.
- I think that's possible too, dude.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I mean anything is,
I think, I truly believe anything is possible.
- That's a good way to live.
- Right, no, it's a scary way to live.
What if I get, what if a needle,
what if a needle goes into my body?
And it's got radiation on it.
- Oh, shit, okay.
- Doesn't that sound pretty bad?
- It does sound crazy.
- Yeah, I want that. - That sounds scary as well.
- It is scary, thinking about that kind of stuff.
I watched Nope yesterday, I watched that new Jordan Peele movie.
Do not give me any spoilers.
I have not seen it.
I'm not going to spoil it.
I've got to go to the movies soon.
But I'm sitting there and I'm thinking, "Man, that could actually fucking happen."
Yeah.
You know?
Because anything could.
Anything is possible.
Get out?
Not so much.
That could not happen.
No, it doesn't make any sense.
I don't think Bradley Whitford could be mean.
Is that the guy?
Is that the dad?
Yeah.
He's cool.
Marnie from Girls is in that.
she play? Oh the girl who eats the Froot Loops? His love interest, his girlfriend.
That's Brian Williams daughter? Yeah. She got her ass ate on TV. Yeah and let me tell
you something I saw it and I think that guy was going hungry that night. He was
going to bed with an empty stomach. She's got no ass. Yeah. I thought you meant
that it looked too clean. It looked too...
that's why he was eating her buddy I'm hungry for poop I need poop right now I
guess she probably does have a clean butt yeah you think is the female celebrity
with the nastiest stinkiest but probably Marilyn Monroe you're not allowed to say
a dead person or Lizzo who do you have female celebrity she knows she's famous
she takes care of herself what do you know doesn't straight-up doesn't wipe
Did you read that Marilyn Monroe, like, biopic, or something about like people like...
Don't tell me there's about to be a scene in this Anna de Armas movie where she don't wipe her ass.
It's not that she doesn't wipe her ass, it's just that like she would like,
I guess, there's like this story that came out that she would like just
eat like chicken wings and shit in her bed and just leave the plates under her blankets and stuff.
And like...
That's normal girl shit.
She would fart and like burp everywhere.
and just like... She's farting? She was farting in front of everybody. She's releasing pheromones
like a bug dude. She's fucking walking around. I guess her ex-husband Joe DiMaggio said something
like how he was surprised at how disgusting she was or something. Really? Joe DiMaggio?
Which also like, I don't know, maybe that's just like a 1950s guy just not like
realizing that women burp and fart too. Yeah I think it was probably more of a like you were
finally in private with this woman. She's rich and famous enough that it doesn't matter if
she farts in front of you. You're not going to ruin her career.
She has more money than you and he's just like, "Dear God. Women poop. Women poop!"
Who is the guy, Fatty Fucker, who fucking...
Fats Domino?
No.
Fatty Arbuckle.
Yeah, who fucking killed a million women or something.
He killed a million women by sitting on them?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay, well I still I still think Marilyn Monroe maybe had a nasty butthole
But I do I told you no it has to be a lot. I do remember. I do remember somebody
fucking Trisha Paytas started like only fans, and she posted like a whole photo and she had
toilet paper all over her butthole
Really yeah by God. That's awful
Yeah, I feel like male celebrities. I honestly I guess is the exact opposite of what your question was, huh?
Yeah, because that does show that at least it was clean. Yeah, I would say
But male celebrities who do you got because I think top two has got is probably like Homer
Yeah, Griffin probably Homer and Peter Griffin. I was gonna say yeah Slimer from Ghostbusters
I do Jack Harlow if Peter Griffin was actually a Carlos pubes and asshole
He mentioned that they also they also they make him look more like mr. Tumnus. Yeah
This is based on his B. I know he's got full hair. Yeah, I got a fawn from the legs down
That would be so cool to convince Jack Harlow to dress up like mr. Tumnus. I think it'd be easy
He looks so much like he should be a fawn
I think it little Nas X told him that there's a they're gonna make a music video where he sucks his dick
He'd probably put on the the fawn pants. Yeah. Yeah
Damn, that would be crazy, but I bet his pubes are nice and patchy and like an s-shape or something
Yeah, because it's just based on his facial. I tried to do a Naruto arrow once with your avatar
I'm I do a tasteful landing strip right down the middle. I don't do that. You don't do a landing strip my
my penis skin grows hair
Mine too, I guess I shave your balls
I looked at my I looked at my shaft and I saw two hairs on it. That was dude
I got fucking a hundred hair
I thought - well
I was looking more at it and then I was just like oh like even on like the tip where like the like the skin you
Have a you have a hair on your tip not on the tip, but like the skin. Oh, I
Still I still got my I'm I'm I'm I'm made completely in God's image. I was not
I was about to do plants versus zombies to you, bro. I was about to fucking shoot you
Is that one of your pubes hanging out of your pants?
Yeah, that's one of my pubes.
Holy shit, that thing's long as fuck.
Yeah, dude, look, it's like I'm a marionette on my penis.
(laughing)
See, this is the kind of conversation you can't have with mommy.
This is the kind of stuff Cameron would not let us say.
No, no, he'd be, she'd be, "Oh, you're being nasty."
You're being nasty.
You know how Cameron is.
"Oh, you're being so nasty."
Oh, I need you to completely stop.
"I don't like to hear all this pee-pee-poo-poo-penis humor."
I don't want to hear that. I don't like it. I completely don't like that.
Hunched over, hands like this. Coach Steve-ish style. Long, yeah, complete Coach Steve. Long,
long fingernails on Cameron, right? Beautiful painted fingernails. You know those like the
lady, the cartoon lady with the gray hair and the big sunglasses and it says like, "I'm
not over the hill." Yeah, the greeting card lady. Yeah. What's her name? I want to say
it's Margaret. We'll say it's Margaret yeah she's kind of a mean-ass fucking
bitch. Or it's Kathy I think it's Kathy. I like the ones where she where it's like
it's like 18 plus and you put you pull it up it's like yeah I love my grandkids
but not as much as I love getting fucking anally fucked. Happy birthday
grandson. Old woman. Yeah and it's her you know it's like and she's heard she
says happy birthday I love getting I love getting sucked on. Yeah. My nipples.
Yeah, I like getting peanut butter licked out of my hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
My name's Margaret and this is a picture of it.
My name is Old Margaret.
Yeah, I'm a fucking old stupid-ass fucking bitch and my grandma, my nana,
she goes to the Hallmark store once a year. She buys a hundred cards. I swear to
God. The top drawer of her dresser. The most easily accessible drawer.
Does she have her own little Hallmark store?
No, no, she doesn't sell them to other people. She's not like a dropshipper.
No, she has them and then when it's somebody's birthday or an event so that she doesn't have
to go out and do it, she just grabs it from her collection.
That's not a bad idea.
She has one for like every age range, you know.
She goes to the middle age section, she goes to the early age section, she goes, condolences,
you know.
Maybe she runs out of cards sometimes, ended up sending kind of a sexy anniversary one
on somebody's, when somebody's like teenage son does a car accident.
ever one of my favorite things to do in high school was uh go to the the
greeting card section and just put like the funny ones in like like loss of
husband yeah that'll that'll fucking own them yeah yeah cuz but well but somebody
trying to find something for their grieving friend and it's just like yeah
who the hell yeah or a hell a trying to cheer herself up when her husband does
yeah but she gets there and it's kind of funny you know she sees a chimp and it
says like it says going ape over you yeah I'm going ape because you're turning
six years old. She goes, "Oh my god, I'm turning six years old!"
Finally, I'm six. I'm finally six. "Oh my god, how was my husband dating me when I was
five?" And then he died. And then maybe she'll feel better about it. Maybe he had a heart
attack because of her age. Yeah, yeah. "How old are you, honey? We've been together
60 years." I think I'm five! According to this card, I'm this many. Yeah. "Oh my god,
I've been dating a five-year-old for 60 years. Oh, that'd probably be his last
words. Oh my god, I'm going to die even though I was dating a five-year-old. I'm not going to
heaven for this. I'll probably go to hell, I just realized because I'm dating a five-year-old.
That would be honestly the fucking worst. Yeah. Imagine you've been dating somebody,
you're hitting your 75th anniversary, right, and you go,
"Here, I'm gonna go, honey, I'm gonna go grab us some drinks, but the bartender
requires an ID for everybody. You know, I know he's not gonna ask for it, but it's
just good to have it just in case you know she cuz she's got bad legs she got
a bad hip you're chasing this fly around like Walter White so you walk up you
bring your ID you put them both on the counter it says she was born seven days
ago wouldn't that be fucking heartbreaking that'd be the worst thing
in the world you'd have to instantly kill yourself yeah right you've been dating
even with this woman 75 years and it's like a Benjamin Button thing exactly
yeah well that's the questionable thing about Benjamin Button when did she stop
fucking him yeah yeah a really good question cuz there's like the one maybe
we do that in the movie I haven't seen a long there's the one point where they
start to kind of look the same age yeah yeah they intersect yeah and that might
be the only time it was okay - well I mean either way it would have been
pretty bad I think I kind of wish I aged like that
reverser yeah like I'm growing more hair you know I think I would not want to
disappear or go back up my mom what happens at the end of Benjamin Button
I've never seen literally just did you get so small he disappears that's so
smart that is a good idea yeah they just fucking they came and there's no ashes
to fucking spread he's just a piece of nothing damn yeah so they probably
squished him like a fucking bug that's what well at some point it's like well
this is I mean come on Roe v. Wade style let's fucking he's he's let's crush him
yeah yeah let's put him in a vacuum we're gonna crush him we're gonna put him out
of his misery dude he's fucking sitting there he's red once he turns into a red
thing he's a he should turn into red mist yeah so I guess we have a list or
something oh yeah yeah I wanted to just do a little um it's like an interview
type thing you know okay people don't get enough yeah of your personal do
people yeah there's I don't think I've ever said anything personal on this show
yeah yeah even within like the first I guess like whatever like 30 minutes
prior no no not at all so I'd say anything about my girlfriend or no no no
I think that maybe we just need to get to the bottom so so I brought these two
these basically these metal things that just because we might get kind of
intense so you want to have something so I hold I hold these two metal things
connected to that here we're connected to that machine right yeah well yeah it's
- It's another recorder, it's a backup recorder.
- Oh, okay, so that's gonna record the--
- Yeah, so we're just gonna--
- What is it in, like it says, I see the ohm symbol there.
- It's just the brand. - This is like
electrical volts? - No, it's just the brand.
- Okay. - Yeah, so don't worry
about that.
Just gotta check the levels.
So, basically, you're gonna, so put your hands on that,
we'll mount your mic.
Okay, perfect, so put your hands on that.
- All right, I got my hands on the two metal things.
- Basically, just don't think about these questions at all.
- Okay. - Okay?
All right, and we're just gonna go through these, okay?
Have you ever debased a nation's currency?
Ooh, that's a tough one.
Is that tough for you?
That's a tough one 'cause I don't know.
I don't know if I'm supposed to say anything.
Maybe you're supposed to just say yes or no.
No, you probably gotta give a sword.
Maybe?
Maybe.
Have you ever killed the wrong person?
No.
No, never.
Have you ever torn out someone's tongue?
No.
No?
Maybe.
Maybe?
What about your own tongue?
I've stuck it out.
I don't know if that counts.
I don't think that counts.
Have you ever been a professional critic?
I guess, I guess technically that is my job.
I guess in a way it is, you're critiquing things.
It's my job too, I guess.
But this isn't about me, this is about you.
Hands back on the thing.
Okay, sorry.
Have you ever wiped out a family?
Ooh, that--
I'm getting some interesting readings here.
A family of humans?
It doesn't say.
'Cause I do a lot of stuff with mice.
When you say, well, I guess I can't ask you
that follow-up, it's not on the thing.
Yeah.
I will say your rating just went off the charts,
so we'll take that as a yes.
Okay.
Have you ever tried to give sanity a bad name?
Which I don't know what that maybe like,
maybe sat in the middle.
Maybe saying like, "Let's go crazy."
Maybe you sat and went to the mall and you said, "Bah!"
Or maybe you stuck out your--
Maybe I said, "Wait 'til the elevator, don't,
"oh no, let's go, let's go crazy, let's get nuts."
All right, here's a better version of the question.
I'm just gonna rewrite this real quick.
I hope they don't mind.
Have you ever photobombed someone?
Oh, yes.
All right, well, that's pretty insane of you.
Have you ever consistently practiced sex
in some unnatural fashion?
By a natural fashion, you have to imagine maybe one of those big Tyrannosaurus Rex
inflatable suits or something.
Yes.
Have you ever made a planet or nation completely radioactive?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Have you ever made love to a dead body?
I'm going to do another quick edit.
We'll just say, have you ever fingered or above?
Have you ever gotten a second base with a dead body?
No.
First base?
Okay.
Have you ever engaged in piracy?
In piracy?
In like sailing the seven seas.
Have I engaged in piracy or in piracy?
In piracy.
In piracy, yes.
Have you ever been a pimp?
Yes, every day of my life.
Oh for show.
Hold on, I'm taking my hands off to film you.
Yeah, that's right, no that's okay.
Have you ever eaten a human body?
Which I would count as second base, so you've already answered this one.
Okay.
Have you ever disfigured a beautiful thing?
Well I shave, sometimes I shave my face.
And you nick yourself?
I shave my penis, I shave a lot of parts of my body, and I think naturally I should keep
the hair there because God wants it to be there.
Of course, yeah.
So I guess that's technically, on a technicality, yes I have.
Okay.
Have you ever exterminated a species?
Yes.
Okay.
Have you ever been a professional executioner?
I'm talking Black Hood, Giant Axe.
- Yes.
- Have you given robots a bad name?
- Hundreds of times.
- Okay, have you ever set a booby trap?
- Yes.
- Okay, have you ever failed to rescue your leader?
We'll say mommy.
- Oh yeah.
- Have you ever failed to rescue mommy?
- I have failed to rescue mommy, yes.
- I hate disappointing her, but it happens.
Have you ever, or have you driven anyone insane?
- Yes.
- So have you ever been, have you ever maybe had,
forced somebody into a photo bomb on a dare?
Okay, have you ever killed the wrong person?
We already talked about this one.
Yeah.
It's almost like it's repeat,
like it wants you to just assess these more.
Is anybody looking for you?
Yeah, mommy.
Have you ever set a poor example?
Absolutely, 100 times, yes.
Okay, hold on one second,
I need to dial a couple things in.
Did you come to Earth for evil purposes?
Yes.
Okay, are you in hiding?
Okay.
Okay. Have you systematically set up mysteries, maybe like escape room style?
Yes. I applied to work at an escape room in Boston, Massachusetts, and in the interview process,
my friend said that I gave the worst interview that the employer has ever seen.
That's right. Anjan Biswas did say that. Yeah, I do remember that.
Have you ever made a practice of confusing people?
Maybe going up and going, "Buh!"
Maybe, I don't know, there's probably hundreds of hours of me confusing people.
I would say you've set up shop doing that exact industry.
Have you ever philosophized when you should have acted instead?
Yes.
Yeah? Have you ever gone crazy?
Yeah? Like, permanently? Or like, "Oh, I'm so..."
Yes.
Okay, alright. Have you ever sought to persuade someone of your insanity?
Like maybe, for example, going like, "I'm completely a loony!"
Yes.
You've said that before?
I've said I've looked at people in a store and I said I'm completely crazy.
Well, did you say I'm completely a loony or a loon?
I said...
Crazy could be like...
A nyuck nyuck nyuck.
Well, that's basically a Zoidberg Marx.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you ever sought to...
Oh, no.
Have you ever deserted or betrayed a great leader?
Yes, mommy.
Oh, have you ever smothered a baby?
Yes.
And what, you know, nacho cheese?
I mean, come on.
Yeah.
Well, again, I do a lot of stuff with mice and small animals.
Oh yeah, I guess that's a baby too.
And I do a lot of bedwetting and setting fires.
Do you deserve to have any friends?
Yes.
Okay, have you ever castrated anyone, yourself included?
Do you deserve to be enslaved?
Yes.
Okay, I'm gonna take a note of that.
Is there any question on this list I had better not ask you again?
Yes.
ever tried to make the physical universe less real?
- Yes. - Been like,
"Just tone it," just like late night.
- I have, there has been many times
where I've told God to knock it off.
- You're sitting on the hood of a car, right?
You're looking up, and you say,
"Just take it down a notch."
- "Give me a break."
- "This shit is getting a little too much for me."
- "I'm getting too fucking old for this shit."
- I think if you, so, I mean,
when you say, "Give me a break, give me a break,
"give me a break," at that Kit Kat bar,
who were you asking?
- God.
God. Just give me a break! Give me a break, give me a break of that cat bar. Have you ever
zapped anyone? A hundred times. A hundred times you've zapped someone? I've zapped a billion
different people. Have you ever had a body with a venereal disease and if so
did you spread it? No. You've never done, well that was the last one. That was the
last question? Yeah but I guess we can keep doing more. I guess I need to, well I
I guess, I mean, hmm.
- What if I, how about I ask you these questions now?
- Okay, well there's gotta be more of those.
They're from some, from some church.
Let me just look it up.
I can't remember what it's called.
- Okay.
- Something's got it. - Why don't I ask you
the same questions because you didn't answer them.
- I mean, if you want to, yeah.
- Yeah, I could just pull these up.
Okay, so have you ever debased a nation's currency?
- Oh wait, I got more.
I have more.
Yeah, nobody wants to know anything
about whether or not I've fucking debased currencies.
Listen, I'm not the one getting interviewed here, okay?
That's true.
You're the one getting, so hands back on those puppies.
All right, I'll put my hands back on the poles.
I don't wanna touch them.
They're not calibrated for me, they're calibrated from you.
That's true, we'd have to do a whole
new calibration process, I guess.
Are you a pervert?
No.
Are you guilty of any major crimes in this lifetime?
Yes.
Have you been sent here knowingly to injure Scientology?
What?
No.
Are you or have you ever been a communist?
Yes.
Well, that's interesting.
Okay, any more questions?
Have you ever embezzled money?
Yes.
Have you ever been a drug addict?
Have you ever bombed anything?
Yes.
- Have you ever, yeah, a couple open mics, come on.
I mean, come on, that's, yeah.
No mommy, you can actually, you know.
- Oh, I had to put my hands back on the poles
and I had to fist bump? - Yeah, put 'em there.
Yeah, no, yeah, don't do that again, please.
Have you ever-- - Well, what if I say
another good answer?
- Then I guess we'll have to do it again, okay?
- I guess we'll have to fist bump again.
- Listen, I'm fun over everything.
There's no mommy here. - Okay, yeah, that's true.
- Ain't no rules, right?
Have you ever murdered anyone?
- Yes, family of mice.
- Oh, we back to that.
- Yeah, I did, I was,
Have you heard about the story of Werner Herzog on the set of Nosferatu?
No. What happened on the set of Nosferatu?
He tried to dye a bunch of white mice gray and put them in boiling Rit dye.
Holy shit.
And he boiled a big, big box of mice.
That's horrifically awful.
Yeah. I did the same thing, but I wanted to make them rainbow.
Oh, that's sweet. Yeah, like an Easter egg.
Yeah.
Have you ever raped anyone?
No.
Not even a mouse?
No. Okay. Have you ever had anything to do with a baby farm?
Of mice? It doesn't specify. There's a citation here, but it doesn't specify beyond that. Okay.
Yes or no? No. No, never been involved with any kind of baby farm? No baby farm. All right,
you've never been out there milking babies? No. All right. Do you collect sexual objects?
No. Well...
You better be. Come on. I know if you're lying. Not because of the machine, but
because I have a psychic link with you as your brother.
Define sexual object. Anything that can go in your ass. Oh, then yes.
I collected a banana earlier. You did. You collected it in your front.
Do you have a secret you are afraid I'll find out? Yes.
And what is it?
Mommy's over there.
Don't tell me mommy's here.
Okay, that was actually a lie, and you're very close to failing this test.
Oh, right.
I know you're not technically, I know you said it before, you're not a good test taker.
Yeah.
Right?
I do, I do.
I want you to know you're teetering on.
With my 504 plan, I should have been able to take this in a quiet room, and I should
have had gum.
You're teetering on a C plus here.
I should have had gum provided.
So far.
There's some questions left though, so we can bump that thing up to a B, big guy.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then you won't have to take a summer audit.
Okay.
Are you upset by the security check?
No.
Have you ever had an unkind thought about L. Ron Hubbard?
Yes.
Not sure who that is.
Really, what did you think?
Hair weird.
Is he a weird hair?
He had weird hair.
Who is this guy?
Oh, this is an author.
He made a series of jazz albums with, I think,
Chick Corea about horses.
Oh, okay.
I think we've listened to that before.
- Oh, dope.
Uh, okay.
Do you hope you won't be found out?
- No.
- Do you think there is anything wrong
with having your privacy invaded?
- Yes.
No.
- No.
That's what I like, yeah, that's what I like to hear.
- Yeah, that sounds like the better answer.
- What do you wish you hadn't done?
- No.
- Well, no, you gotta give an example here.
- Oh, um.
- Maybe something with those mice or something.
- No, I don't regret making rainbow mice.
- Well, yeah, of course not.
You're like Darwin.
like yeah like a huge scientific breakthrough as far as creatures are
concerned yeah are you well I already asked you that but what they got me
that's on the list are you upset by the security check yes no okay so this one
is we have a couple of more here this is designed these ones it's another
security check designed to be applied to children aged 6 to 12 okay okay and
there's 99 questions but we're just gonna do a couple of ones here all right what
What has somebody told you not to tell?
Uh, Santa, not real.
Somebody told you not to say that?
Yes.
My mom, my mommy.
To somebody in the room.
Okay.
Um, well that, um, it's basically just a lie that mommy told you and I hope that you know
that because I know that, right?
I hope.
Yeah, so you can put your, I'll just keep going
with the questions, you can put your hands on the thing.
Yeah, good.
Have you ever decided you didn't like
some member of your family?
Yes.
Who?
Mommy.
That's what I'm talking about, right?
Huh?
That's what I'm talking about, I like that.
As your brother, I like that.
Okay.
That's good to know.
Have you ever taken something belonging to somebody else
and ain't never given it back?
You never gave it back?
What was it? Mommy's hairbrush. You stole mommy's hairbrush? Uh-huh. Holy shit, man. Yes. Is that
where her hair's been a fucking, I mean, serious, fucking bee's nest? Yeah. Right? Rat's nest. Crow's
nest. Rat's nest. That's what they're looking for. It's a rat's nest. At least that bee has a hive,
huh? And that's just a hairdo. Yep. Yeah. That's just Marge's hairdo. That's right. I'm getting a
little off track. Have you ever pretended to be sick, little guy? Yes. Really? And did you get
get out of doing some homework?
- Yes.
- Oh, what did you pretend that you had?
- I used to pretend that I would have painful stomach aches
at the nurse's office, so they would give me food.
- Nice, I used to put my head under my lamp
on the side of my bed, and then be like,
"Mom, I have a fever," and she'd touch my head,
and she'd be like, "You have like a burn on your head.
"You have such a bad fever.
"You seriously can't go to school.
"Mom, if you're listening, you're a dumb bitch."
Have you ever made yourself sick?
- Yes.
Have you ever hurt yourself to make somebody sorry?
- Nice.
Like put a stake through your heart?
- Yes.
- Holy crap.
- I put a arrow through my head.
- By God, at least you weren't playing an instrument, right?
- I was playing the banjo.
- No.
Well, at least you weren't singing
about some kind of Egyptian ruler or anything.
- No, I was singing about grandma.
- Ah, well that's much better news.
All right, not that many questions left, okay?
You ready? Put your hands back on.
Okay.
And you know what? For this one, I'm gonna say, um...
Take all your clothes off.
Okay.
Yeah.
If you could just do that real quick.
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
And your- Hey! And your shirt.
Oh.
Take it off!
Alright.
That is a fuckin' heavy shirt.
Chainmail.
Oh, yeah, well...
You are goth.
Did you- Oh, we already did this one.
Hey, we'll do 'em again, 'cause I think that's one of the things we were supposed to do.
Okay.
Did you come to Earth for evil purposes?
Yes. So let's investigate this a little bit. What are your purposes here on Earth?
Just to cause rats pain. Rats or mice?
Mice, rats, rodents. Have you ever confused mice and rats?
Yes. Have you ever seen a rainbow rat? Yes.
Have you ever seen a rainbow mouse? Yes. You've seen both? I've made both.
Oh my god. That's awesome. Mm-hmm. Have you ever smothered a baby?
Yes. Baby mouse. Okay. How did you do it? And with what? Chipotle sauce. Okay. Chipotle's an adobo.
Oh, those are good. That's a good, that's a little flavor bomb. Yeah. For all you white people out
there. If you add a little bit of a Bobo's Chili. Yep. And I think a Bobo's the guy's name. A Bobo
is the chef who makes the chili. He basically invented the chili, invented the red sauce. And
if you put them to a little mayonnaise, which I know you got in your damn cabinet. That's right.
That's how I pound it out. I'm taking my hands off the reader. Put the hand back on that rod.
I'm putting them back on the rods, but I had to bump one time for the one time.
Here's one for you. Do you think mayonnaise is spicy? Nah. Nah. What do you keep in your bag?
Hot Tabasco. That's right.
Have you ever destroyed a culture? Yes. Which one?
Rhodesian. I thought that was a Star Wars thing. No. Oh. Rhodesian. Rhodesian. Are you sure?
That's not a Star Wars thing. I could-- there's a ghost in the office. Somebody's completely
moaning in a sex way. Yeah. Have you ever jacked off to the thought of someone moaning
in the office? No. Do you-- but I will later. Do you have plans-- oh, that answers it. Have
Have you ever enslaved a population? Yes. Which one?
Rhodesian again? All right. You say it into the microphone and keep your hands on the rods.
You enslaved Rhodesia and
then you destroyed their culture.
Yeah, no, I meant Rhodian. Sorry. I mean, the whole time I've been saying Rhodesian, I've meant Rhodian.
Have you ever torn out someone's tongue?
Yes.
Okay, this time not yourself?
Okay, whose was it?
Mouse.
A mouse is... yeah, we'll say that's someone.
And again, have you ever zapped anyone?
Yes.
And have you ever eaten a human body?
Have you ever farted and blamed it on your friend?
Yes.
Okay, have you ever drawn a naked photo of me?
Was my penis average size, small size, or huge mega large size?
Small and your head was bigger than your body.
Did you do that on purpose or are you a bad artist?
- It was a forced perspective thing.
- Have you ever drawn me with hair?
- Yes.
- What kind of hair did I have?
- Mohawk.
- Was it awesome?
- No.
- Did you erase it afterwards?
- Yes.
- Do you wish I had a mohawk?
- I put a different mohawk on.
- Did it go sideways, like a left to right mohawk,
ear to ear? - Yes.
- Is that the best thing I've ever invented right now?
- Yes.
- It's pretty smart.
- I think you should do that.
- A sideways left to right mohawk?
- I think you should do a sideways left to right mohawk.
- I honestly can't believe I just came up with that
I think that this question, I think these questions were all leading to that
invention. That might be the best fucking invention of all time. A sideways mohawk?
A sideways mohawk that goes completely sideways. Because the best part is you
look at someone from the side with a mohawk, that's the whole profile, right?
But somebody with a sideways mohawk, we'll call it a, we'll call it a sidehawk.
Let's just keep it easy. You're like, oh this guy's got a fucking spike on his
head. Yeah. Right? Or he's... This guy looks like a fan brush. And then he turns sideways
and you say oh my god yeah oh my god he's like he's like a lizard
holy shit he has some kind of lizard thing that would be cool that'd be
fucking dope that would be so cool all right all right so how much how many
more questions do we have just two more all right you ever eaten a human body no
I think you said yes earlier I think I said yes earlier so what so who was it
because we're going to take the yes at the time. A prince. A prince of what country?
Michigan. It was Rhodesia wasn't it? Yeah. It was a Rhodian. Yeah. It was a Rhodian prince.
His name was Gugu. Okay. And have you ever made a planet or nation radioactive?
Really. Rhodia. So this is interesting. Under the controversy section of this
you have potential blackmail. Researcher John Attack-- I'm not sure I'm gonna trust
this guy. Yeah. His last name is A-T-A-C-K. That's a bit of a scary last name. A critic of
Scientology and himself a former Scientologist explains in his book A
Piece of Blue Sky that SEC checks could be applied either as a confidential
confession or as a non-confidential investigation. He alleges that former
members have been silenced by the fear that their confidential secrets will be
used in blackmail against them. Do you have any fear that I will release this
audio? Yes. All right. Well, then I won't. You're fine. Nobody's ever gonna hear this.
All your secrets are safe with me. All right. Well, and that's it? Yeah, that's it.
I think you're good to go. Free to leave, as they say. All right. That'll be
$8,500. Perfect. I have that. Exactly. All right. All right. Nothing else to talk
about, right? We're done. Yeah, I guess we're done. Mommy was gone. Mommy was gone,
and nothing weird happened. Nothing, not a single thing. And we have nothing to plug.
I guess you can go to Patreon maybe. Yeah I guess maybe go to the Patreon and
the Twitch. And check out Prank Ass. Check out Prank Ass the movie. Mm-hmm.
Well the pilot. The pilot. It's not a movie yet. Could be one day. Could be. Yeah.
Alright, bye. Bye.