Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
- Big soda cup.
- I fill you up.
- Let's have a Pepsi.
- Have a Diet Dr. Pepper.
- Let's have a pepper, Diet Dr. Pepper.
- Very good.
- Big soda cup.
- I fill you up.
- Do you guys know what episode?
- Let's have a Diet Dr. Pepper.
What are you telling me?
Do you know what episode number this is I was asking?
No.
666.
Is it really?
Nah.
'Cause if it is then I would be like,
we could be like, welcome to episode 666.
Oh, that's good.
But I have to know the number to say that.
Welcome to this episode of the Die Dr. Pepper cast.
I'm your host, Fancy Pepper.
And I'm--
And you're joined--
And I'm joined by my co-host over here.
Zero Sugar Steven.
- Yeah, that's right.
Zero Sugar Steven, and this is Doug Aspartame, to my right.
- No, my name's Nutrition Facts.
- Nutrition Facts is what his name used to be.
- That's my radio name.
- But his real name is Doug.
- Yeah, but we don't say that on air.
- No, of course not.
- Yeah, we have--
- If people could find my house, the Aspartame Manor.
- We have different names for the Diet Dr. Pepper cast.
- Welcome to the Diet Dr. Pepper cast.
It's the first inaugural, it's the first episode.
It's episode one.
- Episode number one.
Yeah, that's what the Episoda is.
Yeah, and we gotta get the sips in the...
Episoda number one bottle.
Oh, yeah.
Number 1-888-377-3773, drpepper.com.
Why don't you do me a favor and open up that,
and then we'll record the sound of it opening.
I don't think that they have that much of a hiss.
I think you'd be pretty surprised. It's not like a can tab poppin'.
Yeah.
And you know what? Let's get into our first topic.
Is Diet Dr. Pepper, does it taste better in a bottle or a can?
can I'm gonna say every soda for the most part tastes better in a can yep I was
gonna say that too yeah yeah but I said it first so I think it's best in your
imagination it tastes best in your mouth yeah it tastes in imagination I mean you
can't really replicate what it really tastes like uh-huh
so it's always gonna taste a little better cuz you're a dream like flavor
the ranking to me is an interesting discussion can and then and then glass
bottle mm-hmm and then plastic bottle and then cup and then probably like dog
poop bag would it be under that a chilled chilled glass a heart yeah or a hard
plastic cup from a restaurant one of the red ones oh pretty good when we went to
cookout in the south little ice pellets in the styrofoam cup never really had
that before that I think well you the best way to have a soda you've never
had the ice pellets they don't do that up north I don't think that's us Yankees
Is that true?
No, not really.
Unless you go to Sonic.
Really?
You guys call that Sonic ice?
We got that everywhere down there.
Yeah.
Sometimes you go to a restaurant and they have the ice machine makes that ice.
Wow.
That's cool.
And that would be perfect if they had Diet Dr. Pepper in the machines.
I wonder why that would be a southern thing.
We drink more soda.
I don't know.
Soda capital of the world.
Maybe it's warmer so they need different types of ice.
It is warmer so you need ice with more surface area.
Yeah.
Maybe that's it.
It's like putting a whiskey cube.
And maybe like that I was colder up north so the ice is harder to break
Yeah, well you do in the summer though in the summer I said I said no about the summer
Pretty good in a glass cup
In a glass cup ice in a glass cup in a frosty mug
Okay, diet filled with diet. Dr. Pepper diet. Dr.
Filled yeah all the way to the top where do you even find that much fucking diet doctor?
Trust me. I'm just I buy it just merits you buy the pallets Oh pellets or pallet
I buy pellets of sugar syrup and you build it and then I put it in my own. Holy fuck soda
I have a soda machine at home. You ever do a soda stream
Yeah, I want to hear before I drink my I had a
My roommate had a soda stream and then it broke. Yeah, but uh, they should call it a soda scream
'Cause it's the loudest fucking noise you'll ever hear in your life.
And it's shaped like a penguin.
Yeah. A penguin.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
A penguin?
And they're from Israel.
Yeah.
Shout out.
I think my...
I think...
My grandpa had either one of those or an off-brand one of those, I feel like.
Let's stay on topic.
A soda stream?
Yeah, let's not get into grandpas.
Let's talk about soda.
Oh, I'm talking about soda stream. That's exactly what we're talking about.
But you mentioned "grandpa."
Yeah.
Well, my grandpa who likes soda can't be mentioned?
Okay, that's better.
- He has a soda stream, what the fuck are you talking about?
- Yeah, but he also has other stuff.
- Like what?
- He probably has trauma.
- He doesn't.
- He probably has drama with your grandma.
- Nope, not true.
- Your grandpapa doesn't have drama with your grandmama?
- Nope, just soda.
- Baby grandma?
- Nope.
- Okay, you're getting off topic.
- Yeah, he's attacking me right now.
- Okay, you need to stay off the topic.
- He's attacking my family history.
- Okay, let's get back to the Dr. Pepper episode.
The pepper-sode.
- Pepper soda.
- Diet pepper soda.
Diet Dr. Pepper Soda. So here's my thing man, I honestly wish that Pibb was
making a new appearance but the Pibb whole family, the Pibb family has
not hopped on the zero calorie train. Pibb is a deliberate knockoff I was
reading the other day. Really? Yeah. And in what terms? It used to, the
The Coca-Cola Corporation was jealous, genuinely very jealous of the sales that Dr. Pepper
was having in the 70s.
Well, what a lot of people don't realize is that Dr. Pepper is not Coke or Pepsi.
It's Dr. Pepper Snapple.
And they own Sunkist.
But they're not part of the big two, they're disruptors.
is why the big coke corporation wants to go in. This small family brand
yeah of educated people. Pepper family. Pepper family we all know pepper.
yeah and they're like it's like you know you got Mozilla Firefox Google Chrome
this is Opera. A browser that's good enough to be on the Wii.
It's DuckDuckGo. If it's good enough for fucking Joe Rogan it's good enough for
me. Let's stay on topic with Soda.
place yeah Joe Rogan yeah yeah I was gonna get into it
soda just so again just soda again I will have another soda again yeah that
could have been drinking there we go see I'm looking here on pibb thug.com yeah
and that could be any one of us yeah if things had gone mr. pibb was born in the
summer of 72 after the cola coca-cola company had the intention of creating a
drink that would rival the growing success of dr. what I don't I wish it
wouldn't say mr. PIB was born because I really did think like oh it's named
named after a real guy when you said that yeah well it used to be called Pepo
no you Pepo line to me it was under the name of Pepo Pepo yeah do we can we see
a logo on that it was called Pepo and then coke settled on the name mr. PIB
for important brand identification purposes so there's no I can't find it
there another pepo in the world? There's Dr. Pepo. Dr. Pepo. Oh. See there's Pepo.
Pepper type soda. Yeah. Oh so they really were ripping off Dr. Pepper at this time. Yeah.
See that is why Dr. Pepper especially. The can is great. That can is crazy.
It was really good. Let's stay on topic. Sorry not the can, the soda. The inside.
Yeah I think that Pepo would have been a better name for Mr. Pip. Here's a bottle
of peppo they're having an auction for a bottle of peppo really how much let's
take a look and it's on from a website called do we come on time to do a true a
taste test I think we would have to buy this peppo bottle sold price zero
dollars must have sold for free Wow what the hell they got free peppo and it's on
they got peppo on me come wait what are you saying you think on topic Pat no
look Pat we're talking about the soda we're not talking about me come you say
We're not, you shouldn't be touching the computer, there's a soda discussion.
Close the window, it says Me-Com.
We're not talking about windows, we're talking about soda.
So let's discuss this Pepo, that's right here on the screen.
Yeah, I'm saying Pepo on Me-Com.
You better not be fucking bringing up windows unless you're looking through the god damn window of a candy and sodas fountain for trying to look at a soda, you bastard.
That's right.
I don't think that I, I don't think that I went off topic.
Drop your fucking...
Now you're discussing topics, let's talk about soda.
Drop the fucking topic talk, and talk sock.
Can you just, just like, knock it off, I have something to say.
I think it's too early.
Say it.
You said you have something to say, say it.
You better fucking start talking, buster, or I'll fucking eat your soda.
You're going to eat my soda.
I'll de-eat it in one bite.
Someone just was in the hallway, slammed a door, and went "mm-mm" really loudly to the
point where we heard it 30 feet away.
We all were distracted.
Pretty crazy.
My favorite type of soda is baking soda.
Just kidding.
Psych.
That was almost a fucking off-topic moment.
- That was almost a soda joke.
- But because it was a joke, I think we have to allow it.
And that, it did make me laugh.
- And baking soda is like a powder.
You know what else is a powder?
Pepper, Dr. Pepper, which is a liquid, which is soda.
- Pepper is a powder.
- And then Dr., I was just kind of free associating it
back into Dr. Pepper.
- So, I wonder, see, Dr. Pepper is famous for
having 23 flavors inside of one box, and also--
- Let's say human beings have 23 pairs of chromosomes.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, so I think that's probably the reason.
- Yeah.
- Wow, that's why it's so popular.
- That must be, and that, you know what?
Your kind of like logical thinking does make it make sense.
- Make it make sense.
- See, 'cause I always wondered what the 23 was.
- Yeah, I'm always like 23 flavors make it make sense.
- See, see.
- 23 and me, that's gotta be about Dr. Pepper.
- And I used to, 23, I think it's 23 ingredients.
- The me must be Dr. Pepper.
- Yeah.
- Fuck me.
23 ingredients in Dr. Pepper and there's 23 ingredients that make up the human soul.
Do we want to go through the ingredients of Dr. Pepper?
They won't tell you.
Oh, flavors.
Well, there's 23 flavors of the human soul.
That's true.
That's true also.
There's flavors of soul.
Let's see here.
What do we got?
Well, let's look at it on CVS.
Let's look at the original recipe's ingredients.
Okay.
Let's see if we can find this.
Let's do, okay, this is the history corner.
How does that stack up to KFC's recipe number?
Uh, eleven.
Eleven herbs and spices. More than fucking double the fucking flavors in pepper.
I'm not sure if I can find the... Yeah, it's secret, that's what I'm saying. The original recipe.
Heritage Dr. Pepper. Let's see what Wikipedia has to say about this.
Good luck.
Yeah, good... Alright, I'll say this much while you search this page.
Heritage Dr. Pepper, or Dr. Pepper Heritage,
became available around november two thousand nine in various outlets around
the united states as its name implies it is a re-release of sorts of doctor
pepper's original formula which uses sugar instead of high fructose corn
syrup which doctor pepper and other brands of soft drinks are to use around
the early nineteen seventies
the formulas of heritage doctor pepper in dublin doctor pepper are assumed to be
one in the same but heritage doctor pepper is a larger scale national
release aimed at capturing the same marketing essence as the pepsi and
mountain dew throwbacks
Speaking of Mountain Dew throwback, what a great soda.
- I don't think I've ever had a Mountain Dew.
- Mountain Dew throwback?
- I've never thrown back any Mountain Dew.
- You've really never had a Mountain Dew?
- I've had a Baja Blast, actually, at our taco place.
- I know you've had Baja Blast.
- I've never had a normal Mountain Dew.
- And I know that I may or may not have given you
a sip of a Mountain Dew back in the day.
- I don't think that's true.
I don't, what do you mean back in the day?
- Back in the olden days.
- The olden days, like the 1800s, 1700s?
No, like back way back. Before then, like in the 1000s? Just a little bit back, a little bit.
So 80s, 90s. A little bit further. The 2000s when we were just young children? Did you see, there's a new
there's a new Dr. Pepper flavor, and I haven't been able to find it
anywhere in diet yet. All right. But Dr. Pepper Dark Berry. Dark Berry.
Dark Berry, and it's a promotional item for Jurassic World Dominion, and in the
commercials is one of my favorite singers Barry Manilow. What? Wait, Barry
Manilow's in the Dark Barry? He's in the Dark Barry commercials. Wait, is it Dark Barry or Dark Barry?
Is it Dark Barry Manilow? Is he evil? And you're gonna love this commercial. Okay. If this is
confusing you right now, this is gonna make, this is gonna make you smile. Does he act
darkly mean or anything like that? He wears a blue berry suit. So that's not
that dark of a blary. No. A blue berry style, berry colored suit. A styled blue...
violent Beauregard from Willy Wonka. He looks like Barry Manilow. I have violent
disregard for Barry Manilow. I would kill him. And that is an insane
thing to say. Violent disregard. And you're going off topic. I'm fucking sorry.
Yeah. Yeah. So I'm gonna sip. I've actually been smelling. You have to just take a
sip. Yeah. Hey take a sip if you get off topic. It's a little drinking game we've been doing here on the Dr. Pepper episode.
Check out this little paragraph. I think I remember hearing about this at one point.
Oh, I remember tasting it and it was good.
I'll tell you this much, it came out when I was 10 years old.
Yeah, me too.
That can't be a coincidence.
10 years old in 2011.
I don't remember.
I was only a little bit older than that.
I just assumed that because we were the same age that you were right.
Hey, he just went with it too.
But I agreed with you.
Well it says here, for anyone who doesn't know, any less educated Dr. Pepper fans, Dr.
Pepper 10, a low-calorie version introduced in 2011, promoted as having as 10 calories
per serving. A little whoopsie on Wikipedia here, a bit of a typo.
Wikipedia, you can't trust a single word you read on those damn websites.
Definitely not. Dr. Pepper 10 was marketed primarily towards men, with the product's
branding featuring a masculine appearance and gunmetal colors, and promotional campaigns
featuring the slogan "It's not for women," which gained some controversy for its promotional
sexism.
Yeah, I remember that, and I remember that if you got it in the cans, if you got Dr. Pepper
pretend in a can it was silver but sometimes they would put football pigskin on the roof
of the boat.
Oh yeah, and couldn't you fuck the bottle?
You couldn't fuck the bottle but it was big enough to hollow out and put a pocket pussy
in it.
Yeah and you could hide it.
You could say no honey it's just for men.
You're getting off topic.
I'll take a sip buddy, don't force my hand.
Well yeah, this is the history corner, I have some interesting history right here I found
if anyone wants to read this little fun tidbit here.
I would love to.
I would love to read this.
Dr. Pepper was a frequent player in the 1990s antitrust history of the United States.
As part of these activities, economists and the courts have weighed in on the opinion
that Dr. Pepper is a pepper-flavored drink and not a cola.
In 1995, the FTC blocked a merger between the Coca-Cola company and Dr. Pepper on the
grounds that it included concerns of a monopoly of the pepper-flavored category of soft drinks.
Wait!
- They tried to put Dr. Pepper in the Coca-Cola family?
- They did, and then the FTC blocked it
and said you can't have a monopoly on pepper drinks.
- Which is good.
- Yeah, you have to have--
- The FTC won't let them be or let pepper drinks
drink them from me.
- See, I thought you were off topic.
I thought you were just singing,
but you turned it around into a song about soda.
- Yeah, and I'll take a celebratory sip of my soda.
- I think you earned a sip.
Thank God for the FTC blocking that merger.
And thank God for the FTC.
Just in general.
In general, but that's off topic.
You know how when you fart in a bath--
and I promise this is soda related--
you know how--
[LAUGHTER]
You know when you fart in a bathtub,
the fart smells different?
Yeah.
Or in the shower, it smells different.
Let me tell you right now, this better be about soda.
I promise it will be about soda.
The difference between a normal fart and a fart
that is done in the shower or a bathtub is the same smell or a taste
difference between a Coca-Cola and a Dr. Pepper. It's just got a little bit of a
different kind of-- it's like it was made in a different world. I'm glad you were
able to swing this back to soda. Yeah, it hit the soda, all the soda
marks, you know, and it's barely even about-- the farts were just an allegory,
you know, in the way the Bible, but these are just, I mean, what a soda.
I'm seeing here too.
Usually, you go on.
Sorry.
I was just going to say, usually, when I think about soda, I keep the farts away.
That's right.
Get the fart away from my cup.
I feel the same way.
In that one moment, you got what I'm saying.
Mix my soda with some fart.
Just spray it.
Spray some fart all over my soda.
Apparently, nobody knows for certain why it's called Dr. Pepper, and there are multiple
theories.
How did I know?
several different people whose names were Dr. Pepper that could have possibly
inspired the name. Really? Can you list maybe one or two? Yeah, so there's an actual
doctor, one Charles T. Pepper of Rural Retreat, Virginia, or a Dr. William
Alexander Reed Pepper of Christiansburg. Those are two possibilities for who Dr. Pepper could have been named after.
I think we should take all the Christian and put them in a burg. Yeah, an iceberg.
yeah all the curse and then very off-topic sorry do you know do you do you
think before you speak have you ever heard of the Holocaust I haven't and
don't even bring that up because I walk topic yeah we're not gonna we're not
gonna talk about that today never heard of that well but I don't care what that
is because your mind is on soda because I'm fucking being off topic as shit
these days and so I'm just gonna drink my soda very silently and quietly and
Patrick you can just handle all this dr. pepper stuff that we've been talking
about in regards to who created it as with coca-cola the formula for dr. pepper
is a trade secret and allegedly the recipe is kept as two halves and safe
deposit boxes in two separate Dallas Bank Wow they are serious about soda how do
How do you have 23?
How do you split the remainder in half and so you only get half the word?
Yeah, it's a recipe so I mean the recipe is not just one word.
What I'm saying is...
Maybe they cut the piece of paper down the middle.
Yeah, I think that's likely what it is.
So that's what makes it so hard.
I think each piece of paper is probably cut in half and each different half is kept and
they're all mixed up too probably.
That would be my theory.
What if you get in there?
Excuse me, something's...
God, fuck, what's happening?
I don't know why this could be happening to me.
But...
It seems like there's no reason why.
There's no reason why.
Now, I do wanna...
I'm sorry, that was off topic. I'll take another sip.
I feel like we can dive into history a little deeper here,
kind of a Dr. Pepper conspiracy corner.
The Dr. Pepper formula is kept in Dallas.
Do you think we...
Do we think this could have anything to do with the assassination of President John F. Kennedy?
He got too close.
He...
It doesn't say exactly which buildings the formulas were kept in.
Because those were in between two banks, right?
Probably.
It could have been that it was kept in the book depository.
True.
You know, what's one kind of book?
A cookbook or a recipe book or a soda book?
Oh my fucking God.
And that guy, that...
What's his name? Harry Joe Oswald.
He...
or whatever his name was.
He loved soda.
- Yeah.
- And he talked about it all the time.
- Yeah, there's a lot of diets.
- Harvey Oswald.
- Yeah.
- Coca-Cola.
- Lee, holy that soda's fucking good.
- Harvey Oswald.
- I swalled a god that's good.
- Swalled, I swalled, I swalled the soda.
- I swalled the whole bottle.
Holy, I swalled the whole bottle.
I get Harvey C. because I'm so...
I get Harvey Lee!
I get Harvey Lee in front of me.
I get Harvey Lee what's in front of me because I swapped the whole bottle of soda.
Yeah so he had to have been a soda guy.
Yeah.
Ah you're a soda man Lee.
I remember that was in the movie.
JFK.
Yes.
MLK.
Dr. MLK.
Doctor...
Holy shit.
holy shit and he was like pepper the original formula was formulated by
Brooklyn born pharmacist Charles Alderton and Morrison's old corner drugstore in
Waco Texas interesting so it was it's all a Texas affair and it's all but tied in
the guy who made it from Brooklyn all right so shout out to Brooklyn yeah all
All right, before we go any further, Brooklyn, stand up.
Yep.
I'd like to see you stand up.
Stand up.
There's a lot of-- and you know what?
Yep, and I'll stand up.
I'll stand up.
Yep, for Brooklyn.
Yep.
For Brooklyn.
This one's for Brooklyn.
To Brooklyn.
Yep, cheers on that.
But basically, I mean, it's all happening in Texas.
And this is around also the time that acid
and different psychotronic substances--
Hold on.
Now, can you go back to that last page?
Yeah, but I just look at this--
Dr. Pepper, capital of the world.
Oh my god.
That's one of the headings on Wikipedia.
The company sells more Dr. Pepper in the Roanoke Valley area of Virginia than any other metropolitan
area east of the Mississippi River.
And we went there, right?
I'm pretty sure we did on our way over.
We went to the Roanoke, that's where Richmond is?
I think so, something like that.
And you know what?
It's fucking sad that we didn't know this beforehand going there, because if I had known
that it was the Dr. Pepper Capital-
And we were in Dallas too.
We had gone to all of the Dr. Pepper spots.
And I don't think-
We took a Dr. Pepper adventure-
That's the sad thing about the South is there's this whole hidden history they don't teach
you about the South.
and this dark kind of past and this is one of them is that like they're not
telling you guys oh my god pepper capital guys what in October 2015 the city of
Roanoke declared October 24th to be its official dr. pepper day oh my god that's
awesome but why not why would it not be the 23rd I mean you have to ask Roanoke
I guess it's not really my you look up the maybe there's another holiday we can
get maybe there's another holiday on the 24th in 23rd yeah the 23rd is taken
maybe yeah maybe that's 23 not found this is just made up yeah yeah so this is
another one of these wikipedia's information I was so excited to
celebrate there's there's something I saw up there that said dr. pepper used to
be their ads used to say that it was a wait hold on go up here I'll check in
23 flavors redirects here for the Chinese medicine drink see 24 flavors
what there's a Chinese dr. pepper drink no this is a drink called 24 flavor yeah
But this isn't soda, so never mind. I thought it was maybe a soda.
I'm sorry for getting off topic. Oh, it's no worries.
It wasn't your fault. You thought you were on topic. Yeah, I thought I was talking.
Wait, what is this Dr. Pepper?
Free Dr. Pepper for everyone in America.
Wait, okay. On March 26, 2008, various media outlets reported that Dr. Pepper would
offer a free can of Dr. Pepper to everyone in America,
excluding former Guns N' Roses guitarist Buckethead and Slash,
if the band released the long-awaited Chinese Democracy in 2008.
Later in the day, lead vocalist Axl Rose replied to Dr. Pepper on Guns N' Roses official website
and spoke of his surprise of Dr. Pepper's support.
Rose said he would share his Dr. Pepper with Buckethead as some of Buckethead's performances
are on Chinese Democracy.
After it was announced that the album would be released in 2008, Dr. Pepper stated that
it would uphold the pledge.
Wow!
That's crazy.
Wait, and then Dr. Pepper failed to distribute the coupons for the free drinks and they tried
not get into that. They tried to sue wait Guns N' Roses tried to sue Dr. Pepper?
What the? There's an unmitigated disaster which defrauded consumers and in the
eyes of vocal fans ruined Chinese democracy's release. Wow.
Holy shit. Yeah I think that's what ruined the release of Chinese democracy.
Yeah there's also a Dr. Pepper Museum in Waco, Texas. Holy fucking shit. The museum
founder Wilton Lanning died in January 2018. Well I think we think there's an
opening yeah there is for the for founder I mean we could get hired as
founder. We need like a founding document to go into this. Yeah we could pull that off
though yeah I think maybe even Patrick might have a founding document. Is there anything
that could be like maybe the first entry to the museum's catalog? Yeah and you
know what it is a list. Oh my fucking god. Wow let's hear it. You know a little bit of a
throwback to our old show. Yeah I remember that. Yeah. Yeah the show that we don't do
anymore. Yeah now we do Dr. Pepper. The Dr. Pepper show. Yeah. This is a list of why
Diet Dr. Pepper makes me smile. Okay and what would be the first entry?
Well the first entry, I mean isn't it obvious? Well it's yeah it is. Yep it's
obvious. Yeah so we tend to skip it. Number one is the flavor. Oh man. You get me in a room with a
a bunch of cans of Diet Dr. Pepper, only I'm leaving.
- Yep.
But where are you going?
- It's just gonna be me leaving,
and maybe some empty cans.
- You got me in a room with a bunch of cans of Dr. Pepper
and my ex-wife, only I'm leaving.
- Yep.
'Cause she's gonna be staying in there drinking those.
- A bunch of cans of Diet Dr. Pepper and a bag of--
- And a big bag of laundry.
- Yep.
See, I don't know exactly what the flavor of Diet Dr. Pepper is.
All I know is that when it hits my lips, I want-- I wish it was a beautiful man or woman to kiss it.
'Cause you don't know the gender of Dr. Pepper either.
Right, doctor is-- kiss what? Your lips?
I wish it was-- if I wish the soda, I wish it was a liquid man or woman that I could kiss.
[laughter]
And they're made entirely out of Diet Dr. Pepper.
Okay, that makes it a little more--
so when they and they walk her and if it's cold out it's not a good day for
them because they get frozen because they get frozen and if it's hot maybe they
turn into a puddle right if it's hot they or if it's a normal okay they could
stay normal if it's hot all right well I didn't realize you were so fucking
romantic mm-hmm wow that's crazy yeah and you know what
let's say that died dr. pepper is an aphrodisiac I think it is an effort is
that is that on there cuz you should add that if it's not and you know what I
I just added it to the end, so we'll get back to it.
Alright, we'll table that. We'll get back to that.
And listen, when it comes to Dr. Pepper, I throw DZ at my tongue.
Yep.
I throw DZ at my tongue.
I throw DZ back at my tongue.
Mm-hmm.
And I suck it down.
And I fuckin' slurp.
I slurp that Diet Dr. Pepper down like it's a--
You know what? Let's get to the aphrodisiac part now.
I slurp it down like it's an oyster.
And you know what? Raw oyster, all you need, hot sauce and a lemon.
You're putting that on pussy?
Sorry, I got off topic.
Let's get back on topic.
Real quick, can we test the aphrodisiac-ical qualities?
We're gonna get back to the aphrodisiac.
Here's my perfect meal.
If I'm fucking drinking this, do you guys wanna suck my... I mean I don't have underwear on, you already sucked my dick.
I think you would wanna suck our dick if you drank that.
God, I want to suck your mouth.
Here is the perfect meal.
Hit me.
36 raw oysters.
Okay.
One glass of Diet Dr Pepper
and a salad for the lady.
How about you switch those numbers and maybe...
And she'll have a salad, the perfect meal.
Lobster, steak,
14 glasses of Dr Pepper,
and she'll have a crouton.
She'll have one single crouton.
That's a perfect meal.
And a candle between us, which if she gets hungry
she'll start eating like she usually does.
so she probably won't be able to.
I will eat dessert.
If it's a Yankee or if it's a vanilla bean, I could be liable to eat that can.
I'm going at it, yeah.
And I like spicy food, so I'll eat the hot part of the candle.
Yeah, that's fine by me.
Number two, the color of the soda.
The color of the soda.
The color.
This brown fruity drink.
Brownie red.
Oh my god.
Reminds me of a brown picture.
A brownie that's filled with peppers and fruits.
yeah it's like if you put it reminds me if you took water and put great
ingredients in yeah brown best we'll say this much brown is the color of a great
ingredient yeah a great ingredients gonna it's always brown so I scrap brown every
time yeah it really is turmeric no that's yellow that's orange yeah I mean
we don't have to list brown ingredients everyone know if there's an ingredient
brown and nice chocolates clothes I got a brown a nice good dirt my asshole
say my niece is brown yeah
it does an anus that's what I thought - oh no my niece is brown that's what I
saying but yeah I guess my asshole is brown too. Cinnamon, cloves, star anise,
brown peppercorns. Dr. Pepper. Dr. Pepper, great ingredient if you're making some
Dr. Pepper cake. Dr. Pepper ribs. Those are good. Oh my god I'm hungry.
Dr. Pepper stew. Dr. Pepper stew. Yeah Dr. Pepper I'll take two of them.
Yeah, I'm getting a phone call maybe from the pepper police. What is it?
No wife off turn off phone throw
Number three number three is a put it on the ground. I already broke that phone the secret rest the phone. I gave him
Yeah, it's completely
That is off
That is a completely off topic and we will do we will discuss that after the episode is done
But I'm gonna get a whooping
Number three is it secret recipe?
Mmm. I love right if you if you're like me you love espionage. I love it, and I don't want it to leave
Uh-huh you know yeah, I want to protect it. I'm basically I'm like the CIA for the dr.
Pepper is someone dare to do the fapping with dr. Pepper. I'd fucking blow their brains. Uh-huh yeah, they should be again
And we're talking I mean blow your brains out CIA
Yeah, I just you know, I think that the histories are intertwined.
CIA, JFK, MLK.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Blow your brains out.
If you try to do some kind of Ocean's Eleven style heist to get the Dr. Pepper Seeker recipe
out of those two banks that it's being held in, if you try to do that, there will be me.
There will be a blowtorch.
There will be your cock.
You're nuts.
I'm gonna blow it up.
I'm gonna just go to town.
Exactly, I'll tell you what a couple of my friends and we're gonna film it you try you try you try something
You're gonna burn him you try to do oceans 11. You're not gonna be getting lotions in heaven
No, yep, you're going straight to hell and you're gonna not get that bath and body works cherry blossom or the
And and you know what you're not no lip lotion none of that dr. Pepper flavored
Yeah, you're gonna go you're gonna go lip tattoo. That's a slut. Yeah, that's right, and you're going on the outside and gauges
Yep, and you're yeah, and we're gonna pierce your nose. Yeah, right you have one of those little rings and there's a cheek gauge
Yeah, yeah that you're gonna get and we're gonna and we're gonna split your tongue split your tongue like a snake
Do you think if you split your tongue you could taste when you soda or dr. Pepper twice
There's only one way to find out yeah
Split the tongue completely down the middle one part
One cup one part diet you could probably create new flavors that way yeah, you could stick
You could stick one half of your tongue into dr. Pepper, and then the other half into whatever flavor thing you want
I like cherry or vanilla or dark berry actually yeah, or even one that doesn't ignore ice cream ice cream
I don't make you can make a
You can make a separate
Root or dr. Pepper float in your mouth
I'm no friend of evolution, but if I were that might be the next step in it
It is having two tongues because the more I think about that your soda
Enjoyability factor is gonna go up
Multifold yeah, I was worried you were about to get off topic. No. I'm talking sodas. Okay good
Number number four the ingredients kind of in in line with this
Secret recipe, but these ingredients even on their own even if they're not in a dr.
Pepper are they stand out stand stand alone star of every single thing that there is each ingredient stands alone
But together they stand strong. I wish you carbonated water. Yeah
Caramel color that's got to be my favorite color caramel color is good
Aspartame aspartame mm-hmm love it love it can't get enough whenever that's in a meal. I know it's the star of the show basically
Dr. Pepper is a meal. And I asked for it but you know a lot of people say oh
aspartame is bad for you it causes cancer these are the same people are saying
this about MSG and that's fucking racist. Yeah. Right aspartame is not
dangerous it's okay it's actually a nootropic in high amounts and it can
actually make your right leg fucking go completely numb for like two months
straight. And did you know it's actually named after Spartan? Yeah exactly.
Uh-huh. This is Spartan! The main guy from that from the movie. The main guy from that it's
named after yeah because of how strong he is and if you don't like aspartame I'm
kicking you in that pit playboy mm-hmm do you like ask your team there's the
door yeah they're not staying at my barbecue get the fuck guess what's on
all the ribs the answer doctor diet dr. pepper with extra aspartame extra yeah
because sprinkle yeah I like my fucking ribs sweet like candy asshole yeah I put
sweet and low on my diet dr. pepper ribs heard that uh-huh
well it's ingredients and then it's caffeine count I think it's the perfect
amount of caffeine for a diet soda. Right there, you know, not quite 70. 68 milligrams.
And 70 might be pushing it for a bottle. A Red Bull? Red Bull is gonna be 120.
Red Bull small can that's 80 milligrams. Yeah so this is a little less than a small Red Bull.
Basically it's the same amount of caffeine as a small Red Bull
but you get more soda. You're drinking a bottle of Coke, it's
46 not enough you're drinking a bottle of Pepsi is a hundred and one how much is
in a cup of coffee about a hundred about a hundred yeah so there's a little bit
less than a cup of coffee mm-hmm you know so just enough pep shit in your
step yeah I will also say I feel like I pretty you should pretty much never be
drinking something that has a hundred of something yeah I that's dangerous yeah
like a hundred razor sharp a hundred of anything's bad if you look at ingredients
on anything you see a hundred you shouldn't drink that. Turn around run the
other way. Yeah a hundred degrees. Turn a hundred degrees and run the other way. The next
one it's calorie count. Now Cameron I want you to take a look at this
label here. Sure. Okay now I want you to read the amount of calories. Well it
seems like they did a misprint here where because I'm not seeing a number
I'm seeing a letter and the letter is O. I want you to take a closer look at that.
Oh my god, I just realized it's a zero zero. It's a Z as people. I thought this they messed up on this bottle
But it's actually zero. Yeah, I just believe that that could be true. It's a completely guilt-free soda
You can drink it and you won't and you can drink it and look in the mirror after and not say
Look at you
Well, see you look at you look at you look at you
You piece of shit.
(growling)
(screaming)
You're not looking at the mirror doing that
after you drink it.
- Because it's not, there's nothing in it.
It's basically fucking nothing.
- There is no calories, it's basically like,
and you know what, get yourself a zero bar.
I think that zero bar has zero calories, I don't remember.
That's a candy bar, that's off topic.
- It has calories.
- It has calories, okay.
Well then don't get a zero bar.
Also, haven't had one of those in a while.
Those are pretty good.
- Off topic.
- That's off topic, and I said it fast so that--
- That doesn't stick.
- I just didn't mean to cry when I just started.
I really didn't mean to do this.
And I think it's gotta be some ingredient
that is pushing me towards this kind of emotional state.
- Zero sugar also.
- You just turned your mic off, I think.
- I did.
I did turn my mic off.
There's also zero calories.
- A gentleman never drinks Dr. Pepper on mic.
That's for his wife to hear.
- Yeah, exactly.
(slurping)
- Whoa, Caleb, turn your mic off before you do that.
- 'Cause it's an aphrodisiac.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm throwing these back.
I almost feel like my memory is getting better.
And I'm remembering different things I've said.
Can I do a human benchmark right now?
Give me a test.
I'm one and a half bottles deep on Diet Dr.
- You're supposed to share that bottle.
- Pepper, you can have the rest.
I don't want this. It's scaring me. It's scaring me what I'm becoming.
Okay, let's do a- how many calories does it have?
It's gotta be fucking a hundred.
Okay, so you just instantly failed the benchmark. You said your memory is getting better.
I was just testing your memory of what-
No, I've never heard how many calories are in Diet Dr. Pepper.
I didn't know that.
Okay, well, how much sodium is in it?
It's gotta be fucking...
That one I know is zero because it doesn't taste very salty to me.
It's actually a hundred.
which is the one thing it's okay to have a hundred of the c_n_n_'s
yet i was going to be that's the next uh... well that's a lecture like that
so that's that's the next thing i love about it a hundred grams of sodium
it's exactly it's a little tips a hundred milligrams of sodium
uh... it's not a hundred and a half
it's not the
it's it's perfect for you because it hydrates you as you drink it
and it's also got caffeine in it yes
to make you
crazy faster yeah think better I mean I'm sure is a migraine caffeine it does I was
saying before I'm training that loosens your your blood vessels I want to try
running a half marathon I think dr. pepper might be my little pre run you
while you run yeah put it in a put it in a camelback or one of those double
drinker a beer back uh-huh beer oh my god you can make it shape a pepper back
pepper back pepper back no mm-hmm pepper back pepper back pack mm-hmm and number
I don't even remember what number we're on the next one is the color of the
label right what do you like so you look at a dr. pepper right I'm looking at one
right now you're looking at a diet dr. pepper but think in your mind rotate
this why would Patrick like the color of this label can I dr. pepper it now I'll
get there. The can of Dr. Pepper is red and white. Yeah. Diet Dr. Pepper? White and red.
It's the away team. Oh shit. Okay. Yeah. It really is. And sports fans rejoice. Mm-hmm.
Diet Dr. Pepper. It's the classic jersey with the colors reversed. And it's even got a
football on it. Yeah. And it's Pepper Perks. It's got Pepper Perks and it's perfect for
football fans. It's like when in a cartoon they run into the same versions of
themselves with dressed in different colors. Yeah. But and it's that's always
the best episode. Dr. Pepper, Diet Dr. Pepper, Dr. Pepper Berries and Cream, Dr.
Pepper Vanilla, Dr. Pepper Dark Berry. I think that they all hang out and they're
like the Power Rangers to me. Yeah, the Pepper Rangers. The Pepper Rangers. Oh my
- Oh my god.
- That could be a whole new show.
- Guys, we need a lot of funding
to make our show, The Pepper Rangers.
- So basically we want to shift focus now.
We need, this is a million dollars
that we need really soon to make The Pepper Rangers.
- The Pepper Rangers is gonna be
one of the most incredible things
that we've ever done. - Yeah, what's it called?
Mighty Morphin, instead of Mighty Morphin, what is it?
- Soda Sip and Pepper Rangers.
- Holy shit. - That is so good.
- And look at how fast I came up with that.
- It's perfect.
- That's because you've been drinking Dr. Pepper.
- I've been drinking so much. - 'Cause you have fast speed.
- Diet Dr. Pepper.
Yeah. And the bottle is recyclable.
Yeah. That's all right.
That's all. So I'll tell you how I'll tell you how it's recyclable to you.
Finished drinking it. You take another bottle, fill it up with more Dr. Pepper.
And you can bring it to the Coke. And you know what?
You show the Qdoba employee, you show them.
I'm just getting a refill. And they go, well, yeah, they say it's OK.
If it's Dr. If you're refilling it with Dr. Pepper, you know, Dr.
Pepper is not in the Coke Freestyle machine.
You're crazy.
Is it not?
It is at the one at Qdoba.
Wait, that doesn't make any fucking sense.
They've bought out, Dr. Pepper, smart businessman,
bought out the rights to have his drink
in a Coke Freestyle machine.
Wait, that's,
he bought out his own rights to have his drink,
so he didn't own the rights to it,
and he bought it out so that he could have his drink
in the Coke Freestyle machine.
Because it used to have Pib in it.
So he's paying extra to get Dr. Pepper into the Coke Freestyle.
And I had one the other day.
I had a Diet Dr. Pepper cherry.
Wow.
I'd like Dr. Pepper to pop my cherry.
Just fuck me.
Just, yeah.
Alright, you don't have to say that.
Just fucking Dr. Pepper.
And the last one here, it contains phenyl...
phenylketonutri- ketoneutronate.
Dude, you gotta stop, I'm drooling over here.
It's so fucking good.
It contains phenyl- oh my god.
Phenylketonurix.
The phenylketonurix are just fucking, oh.
Specifically, it has phenylalanine.
Fennel, fennel and lalanine.
It's just so good.
Yeah.
Oh, it's just good.
It's the best ingredient it's got.
It has to be.
That's the 24th flavor, it's honorary, it tells me.
I fucking love that fennel and lalanine.
I'm seeing, okay, can I,
I'm gonna read you guys something
that I just saw in this bottle.
Yeah, shoot.
That just seems like it's on its own here.
Must be 18 plus and legal US resident.
And there's a whole,
it seems like there's some kind of con.
I think that's in regards to the pepper perks.
Yeah.
No, I think it's just, I think it just is about the bottle.
You think that an 18 year old has to drink this?
Yeah, an illegal US resident.
Yeah.
Oh, there are Pepper Perks though.
I think that's separate though.
I would love to get Pepper Perks.
Well, let's try, let's, I mean, we got,
we got a few bottles of Dr. Pepper right here.
I don't see any reason why we can't.
Let's scan these.
What if we won a million dollars right now from Dr. Pepper?
Okay, the Perks fans deserve.
Oh my God.
Get your game face on with limited time Pepper Perks.
Okay, let's log in here.
Okay.
Do you guys already have a Pepper account?
No.
No, we can make one with Google.
Yeah, we'll sign up.
I wasn't even fucking aware.
Sign in with Google right there.
I'm not gonna sign in with Google. I'm gonna make an account here.
Why not? Why not put it on the podcast email so we can all share it?
I mean, I'll still do that, but I don't want to connect it to our Google account.
Why not?
Because we'll just type all this stuff in here.
Why don't you like connecting it to the Google account?
It's a security risk, okay?
It's a one-click button.
It's a security risk. You don't know what kind of...
because people I mean we've been talking about the secret formula of the doctor
pepper the entire time you're making people are constantly trying to break
into the dr. pepper database and find the formula it's kept under lock and key
damn good point we should put our the name of the pair so what I'll do two
different banks or I'll do different pieces first name
Yes
Doran better pits door
Well, I'm middle every time
That is true now I won't say this into the mic but I'm it starts with dr. Pepper. All right
D-octo are just dr. Hmm. Okay, I see
- Okay, oh wait, hold on.
Sorry, so we're working with a long password here.
- Yeah, high security.
High security.
Yeah, no, I'm seeing that password.
That's really good.
That's a good one.
- Okay, let's continue here.
Create our account.
- Okay.
- Oh, we have to check our verification code here.
- Oh, yeah, get that email open.
- Let's get this up here.
Okay.
Okay, verify our account.
- I'm doing one of the perks of Dr. Pepper right now.
Yeah, the taste, the drinking aspect.
Let's verify our account here.
Your Pepper Perks await.
I feel, it feels like Christmas Eve right now.
It really fucking does.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Oh my God. Okay, here we go.
Here's our points, guys.
Holy shit. 30% off Fanatics.
We get that for 30 points.
Oh my God. We get one free month
of ESPN+ for 40 points.
We get a $10 Uber Eats gift card for 60 points.
They're out of stock for a $50 e-promo code
from Fanatics. Just so many people
are buying this bullshit.
also out of stock for the BR the bring it box ring BR the BR ring it box which has
a beanie texting gloves charging cords charger and a clear sling bag they're
out of stock of that they're out of stock of a no sweat box - and the who's
house box and people are just a sack sack er some people are just going
fucking crazy that's so fucked up okay so we have to oh you have to submit your
receipt we have to upload a picture of our receipt well that is not gonna help
Itemized receipt? We don't have that.
We don't have an itemized receipt.
What the fuck?
They just gave me a piece of paper that just says...
I mean we could try uploading it anyway.
Yeah.
Maybe we could scam them.
Here, somebody take a picture of this with their phone and air drop it to my laptop.
And we'll just upload this and we'll see.
Hopefully they'll believe.
Let's put the Dr. Pepper in the picture here.
Could we maybe...
Yeah, get all three. Where's the third bottle?
Do you think we could fake receipts pretty easily and just like basically farm fucking points on here?
I think we should try that.
the other bottles down here. Okay give me that bottle. All right now now hold it up.
Okay here I'm holding the receipt up and and hold on to this picture too. I'm
taking it in portrait mode too. So yeah it looks amazing. So let's take
that that picture there. Okay great so now let me make sure. I just got an
Apple News notification. Oh okay. What if nuclear war started right now? That
it'll be pretty crazy awesome okay I just airdropped it to you okay oh it just
went away try one more time there we go except okay all right guys let's hurry
we got that yeah okay select the number three three right
burrs okay it won't let me okay wait I can solve this you guys talk about dr.
- Dr. Pepper for one second. - Oh yeah.
Man, oh.
- You know if I had to make a--
- That is a good picture.
- Holy shit, that's so beautiful.
Holy.
If I had to make a list of my favorite parts of Dr. Pepper,
it would be one thing is I like that the bottle is shaped,
not, it's a bit oblong.
There's some kind of like wind, it's almost torpedo-like.
- And this right here--
- That's what I mean, there's like--
- Perfect grip.
- Yeah, exactly, it's got good grip.
- Perfect grips on it.
It's almost, it almost is a, can double as a football.
- Watch this, try, try and knock that out of my hand.
Okay, I said knock, not grab.
Do you see that?
- I did see that.
- You can't, I mean, it was amazing.
- Try again.
- Wow, I really tried that time too.
- Yeah.
- And it just stayed in.
- And it stayed complete, and it's these plastic,
perfect, try to get one more time.
- Fuck, that's fucking--
- Thank you for your submission.
We are currently processing your receipt.
will receive an email shortly notifying you of your status.
- Holy! - This is the best day ever.
- So I guess we'll keep everyone updated too
with what happens with this, but I think we're looking,
I'm not sure how many points you get per thing,
but I think we could be looking at getting
a $10 Uber Eats gift card pretty soon.
- I mean. - And we could buy,
oh my God. - Wait.
- Does some Dr. Pepper, Infinite Dr. Pepper Hack.
- Infinite Dr. Pepper Hack because--
- Okay, 'cause then we can get--
- I think you probably get one point per bottle.
(laughing)
there is a very small reward is thirty
thirty points here in europe so we can only return dollars we need sixty
every sixty bottles is doable
i'll do that in a fucking take a look at it take one down pass it around yeah
was that
it doesn't say how many points
are are i read maybe you know maybe each bottles a hundred points and that's why
all that hide the top rewards are out of sound makes sense because there's so
huge a generous company exactly yeah
all right do we have a
no now that we're doing we're writing it out let's just keep going on the
department
you know we may have made it as far yet what exactly what another here let's
test when he was a little bit of a lot of evidence that i mean that we had
different option in different points that we probably could have transitioned
to a different kind of thing point but listen buddy were fifty minutes in the
list was another has been so that the headings on doctor pepper dot com i want
to hear that one is posted points alert
well your profile dot org i'm so i can't even talk guys
Bonus points alert, complete your profile now to earn five points.
Holy crap.
We are going to be on our way.
Let's complete the profile.
Okay.
So you have to connect your-
Connect your Facebook and your Google.
Connect both of them.
Let's go.
Wait, we have to take a photo of us to put as the profile picture.
Oh my God.
Wait, let's-
Okay.
Favorite Dr. Pepper flavors.
Let's go.
Select all that apply.
Dr. Pepper, Diet Dr. Pepper, Dr. Pepper Cherry, Dr. Pepper Cream and Cream Soda, Cherry Vanilla
Dr. Pepper, Dr. Pepper Dark Berry, Dr. Pepper Zero Sugar, Dr. Pepper and Cream Soda Zero
Sugar, Dr. Pepper Cherry Zero Sugar, Dr. Pepper Fantastic Chocolate, Dr. Pepper Made With Real
Sugar. How often do you drink Dr. Pepper? Once a day, once a day at least. Once a day.
Where do you usually get it? Convenience store, grocery store, restaurant. Restaurant, well
let me click restaurant. Well just click at the bottom, all the above, Dr. Pepper is life.
Oh here we go, restaurant, vending machine, stadium event, all of the above Dr. Pepper
is
And then period, and then say, "Oh, and Dad's Pantry."
- And Dad's Pantry, one of us is a child of divorce.
- Besides Dr. Pepper, what else are you interested in?
Movies, music, photography/videography,
illustration/design, travel, cooking, sports, pets.
That's true for Caleb.
Fashion/style, gaming, other--
- We gotta listen to our, vintage pornography.
We all love that.
- Oh, yeah.
- Right, who doesn't love vintage pornography?
- We were looking at it the other day.
I just like how their tits just go into,
they're like bullet bills.
- Yeah, uh-huh.
- You know what I mean?
What else are we into?
- Fitness.
Website design.
- Fitness, website, UX and UI.
Treating mental illness.
- I was gonna say,
I was gonna say--
- Mental illness, yeah.
- I was gonna say Barbados,
but I guess that goes under travel.
- Barbados is good too.
Barbarianism.
- Barbarianism, yeah.
pescatarianism yeah we really did for a year fish plus chicken is pretty fucking
awesome different world world religion many many different religions metal
music metal music and material metal machine music that blue read album Lou
Reed chewing cud yeah the saxophone yeah I watched a video about it last night
and all you tube impressions impressions on you tube yeah
uh... circuitry yes sir
uh... city really really do you believe the bidding with that issue in their
yet the new members of the new rubbish
with girlfriend yeah and
bending a bad bitch
uh... yeah
bending a bad bitch we could do that too
uh... there
and bender
Futurama. And from Breakfast Club. And from Breakfast Club, yeah. And Fender, the guitars,
and the back of a fucking car. Yeah. A guitar and her car. A... Wait, wait, let's... Star
Seeds. Fender Stratocaster, Fender Starcaster, Fender Telecaster, Fender Mustang, Fender Jaguar,
Fender, Fender, um.
- Bender Jazzmaster.
- Fender Precision Bass.
- Precision Bass.
- Fender Jazz Bass.
- Make an incision on her face.
- Fender.
- Surgery.
- Medical issues.
- Electable surgery.
- Surgery and medical surgery.
- Yeah.
- Fender Jazzmaster J Master's edition.
- Autoimmune disorders.
- Autoimmune.
- Carnivore diet.
- Fender Jazzmaster Thurston Moore.
- Jordan Peterson.
I think that about covers our interest. That probably covers all of our things. Oh, oh,
one last one. Origami. Origami's good. Yeah. And while you're, just put Japan. Yeah. Japanese
style white guy. Not that. I'm just gonna put Japan. I'm gonna click save changes here.
Bad request. What? We wrote all that and it says bad request? Dr. Pepper, what the hell's
going on. Okay, we'll let us save our profile. All right, well, what? Maybe we just put too
much in the other section. It's it's fucking in it doesn't have a fucking endless or it's
endless. Okay, oh, you didn't fill out two things up there. Well, they're not required.
They are required. Probably all that's required. I would guess. Yeah. Okay, what are we putting
for a birthday? Let's split the difference. Yeah, it was October 24th was that was Dr.
Pepper. Oh, yeah. Oh, my God. Yeah. And then they'll be like, oh, they were there. They
were born on Dr. Pepper's birthday or Dr. Pepper. That's like born on the fourth of July.
one one one one no no do six one seven two you do mine zip code one one one one
you do my zip code I have I have a phone number yeah Oh brag I have a phone
number yes six six one seven two nine nine six two five seven all right now
let's try on zip code um oh three oh five three London dairy nice all right let's
click Save here bad request it's got to be this other section I think maybe we
just leave it a vintage pornography in Japan all right that should be enough
vintage pornography from Japan let's just make it all just one okay yeah yeah we
just change it to Japanese pornography oh it already say oh well real say five
- Zero points earned.
(yelling)
- Yes!
- Oh my God, let's check our points.
- Oh my God.
- Let's check our--
- Wait, tuition.
- We are on our way to like one of the greatest--
- Wait, go to tuition.
- One second, just look at this.
Just check this out.
This is gonna blow your mind right here, looking at this.
- Holy shit, we have fucking five points.
- Oh, bad image quality.
(laughing)
- What?
- We got zero points from our receipt picture.
- How is that possible?
That was such a high quality image.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
That image was so good, bro.
That's so fucked up.
We just got cheated out of points.
I bet each bottle is five points.
Go to the tuition, how many points to go to college?
Okay, let's see here.
We're gonna be sending a letter to Dr. Pepper
about that ruling.
Or with that picture of this receipt.
We're gonna be suing Dr. Pepper.
That has to be a tuition giveaway.
All right, so Patrick, you didn't finish college.
No, I didn't.
How to enter, make a TikTok.
This is perfect for Patrick.
You got this dude.
- Upload a video to TikTok to help us get to know you
and your biggest dreams.
From your academic goals to professional aspirations
to personal dreams.
Be passionate, be creative, be you, but above all else,
tell us how winning will help you achieve these goals
and live out your dreams.
All right, let's do it.
All right, ready?
- Are you on?
- I'm just recording and I'll upload it on TikTok.
- Well, are you logged into the podcast one?
- No, I don't know how to do that.
- Just film on the camera.
- I am logged in.
- Okay, you make it then.
- Okay.
But you can earn up to $100,000 in tuition.
Well, you could go back to school
and you could finish your fucking degree.
That's true.
In Dr. Pepper Sciences.
I never finished my degree,
and I think due to a credits mishap,
I think I was technically still a sophomore.
Well, then 100K should cover all that.
And you could probably live on campus too with the co-eds.
That's true.
I do love the co-eds.
Listen, who doesn't love co-eds?
All right, you gotta talk into the mic.
Wait, let me put a filter on.
Yeah, is there one that's like maybe a graduation cap?
Oh my god, this one's funny.
Oh, that is funny.
I don't think, and maybe, oh, I have a disability too.
Okay, then, yeah, let's, I guess I have to, okay, this one, I'm in a mirror, okay.
Let me change the, I'm gonna have to put it on like three minutes, I don't know how, there's
gonna be a lot of retakes.
Yeah, it's fine.
I
Wait, it changed. All right. You just press record. Just hit it. All right
Hey, dr. Pepper
Wait shit
Just record it. Hello. Hello. Dr. Pepper. I
am a
18 and I'm ready to go to college
For what do you want to go for?
What do you like to the official pepper pack? Oh scroll to the go to the - we need to see what?
- Is that what he needs to say?
- Yeah, let me just game this thing real quick.
- Yeah, yeah, we'll just hit all the points
and then he'll be basically in.
- It's academic goals, professional aspirations,
personal dreams, be passionate, be creative, be you,
but above all else, tell us how winning
will help you achieve these goals and live out your dreams.
- Hey, Dr. Pepper.
- And you must use the challenge sound tuition dreamin'.
- Hey, Dr. Pepper, I'm an 18 year old kid
and I am ready to become the one who cures cancer.
the one who cures cancer.
- Where do you wanna go to college?
- I wanna go to...
What's like a brain surgery school?
- Probably like Ronald McDonald House.
- Yeah, or like--
- Ronald McDonald House is a hospital.
- They have like a medical school.
- Maybe freaking Dr. Frankenstein has a brain surgery school.
- Just say you wanna go to--
- In Transylvania.
- John Hopkins University.
- I wanna go to Tufts University to cure all brain cancer
because my mother and father--
- Well not, wait, stop.
not all some brain cancer probably good or my mother and father died of brain
cancer see I made that up
okay so and then keep going say your entire family died of brain cancer and my entire
family too
and your friends all died and my new friends died and say that and now video me
and say that i have brain
and this is my friend who has brain cancer
and then say do a video of me and say this is my friend who has cool style and this is my
friend who has cool style
And now say your personal dream, like be like I want to play a board game at college or something.
And my personal dream is to play football in college.
Play brain football.
No, give brain.
To play on the Quidditch team as well, because I'm a bit of a nerd.
And chess.
Chess, yeah, chess.
And if I win, I will cure cancer.
And play chess.
Okay, let's look at this.
Okay, let's watch it.
Hold the mic up to it.
Hello, Dr. Pepper.
Hold your mic up.
- I'm 18 and I'm ready to go to college for,
hey Dr. Pepper, hey Dr. Pepper, I'm an 18.
- Wait, I gotta give some edits to it, right?
I have to use the sound.
- They'll think that it's endearing.
- We'll have to go into the editing suite.
- You guys will see this in a minute.
- That'll come out later, but I do,
I mean before we get out of here, I do just need to--
- Can you go back to the tuition thing?
I gotta see what I gotta use.
- I'm just gonna read this before the episode ends
'cause this is really important
you're not going to want to miss this. There's a there's a heading on their
website that's pepper pack and it says welcome to the official pepper pack home
only the most devoted most passionate most 23 flavor loving dr. pepper fans are
encouraged to enter beyond this point want to join the pepper pack patients
pepper applications will be open soon oh my I think I based on the episode we
just did the episodic I think we are prime candidates yeah for the doctor
we have to be let into the pepper back so this is our campaign put us on the
pepper pack. Put me in the pepper pack. Put me in the pepper pack coach. I need to be in
the pepper pack. Put me in. I need to be and my name's gonna be Little Pep.
Speaking of the pepper pack we got a whole pack of peppers that are on our
Halloween show. We got Sarah Squirm, we got Jack Bensinger, Eric Rayhill, Pierce
Campion and some more special guests that we haven't announced yet.
So you gotta buy a ticket. SwagPoop.com/shows. Halloween night dress up,
dress down. Uh-huh bring a pillowcase. Bring a pillowcase because we will be
- Give it a candy. - It's gonna be boring.
You're gonna have to go to sleep.
- Yeah, I heard that.
All right, brother.
Well, I'll talk to you later.
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.