come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
every crap monster
well yeah i saw talking talk about apparently drama in the fuck there's
there's drama between the trailer guys apparently kind of our sister show
i've always seen them as our rivals because i can see that there's our
brother's show
more than a sister i look like the
eugene
which was his name what you mean
what's the aging i think the aging guys named eugene i don't know
i don't know which are which i just i saw you gene was trending
eugene was trending eugene was trending okay i'm gonna go to you know what i
think i think okay so i thought you gene was trending right and then i read
that eugene a_t_c_ is the asian try guy okay that i don't look like him but i
saw a very very very very very take that back
you are i think that you know what is on the other showing photos of him eugene
i think if you put me through a couple filters i could look like that guys and
i did cheated with his wife says uh... says and and eugene said that ned would
cheat on his wife on the lie detector test episode is what i read
holy my gosh what this
there's some serious news here apparent according to
sports gita
there's a headline here who is a alexandria herring ned foamer alleged
cheating controversy explained as to react to disbelief yet her last name is
harry fucking disbelief that these try guys was it an apple will be tried i was
trying some more some new pussy yeah that's what you know i don't think it
was trying not to come into a new girl
you're really bad job is trying not to yet what we don't know what it became we
need to ask him if he can't i know that he can i think it was a scientific
myth busters i could try it was that there was a photo of a market all by the
sheen on his face again
i think he is now one of the guys in the trie guys show that's on the dozen
television you're on the right
or a coral
that's all the time i'm trying to talk about jimmy neutron
that's a bad might have tried to answer another power our uh... i think the
boat third may have a gun i think what we need to do
i think we need to get this wimp
uh...
ned
on this show
you hash it out how do you win the fucking beautiful women on the site
Off the Try Guys.
Yeah.
Hey girl, I'm one of the Try Guys.
He has a built in fucking, like built in pickup line.
I wanna try your butt.
This week on Try Guys, you.
Yeah.
We're all gonna try you. Do you think I've ever quadrupled teamed a woman?
No. I think they're wimps.
Why do you think they're wimps?
You think they're wimps?
Okay, so the real Try Guys drama is starting to unfold here.
Yeah, you know why I think I have beef with them. What's the beef?
Look, I don't want to get this isn't a gossip show. No, it is now completely
We started it out as a gossip show. You can't can't pull back now
Look look, this isn't a gossip show and I don't want to get into it. But what's the beef?
Tell me one of those guys which one and I won't say who okay, maybe maybe you can just
Tell by looking at them the wimpiest one
Doesn't like to share things
What at a party share like the women that he's cheating on
And I'll leave it at that so you so you walked in on this guy
And he was fucking a woman and no I didn't watch him say hey try go try some of that girl. Yeah, there was there was
Whippets I saw him
He tried to get right. Hey, but all he was he was trying whippets
at the party.
And you wanted to share it.
It was a big Try Guys party.
It was a big trying party.
Everyone's trying different things.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what I...
They were smoking funny things.
They were making love outside the lake to their favorite song.
That's what you should try.
Well, I was trying to and I said, "Hey, let me try the Whippets."
We know what they say, "Try, try again."
Uh-huh.
Well, he didn't let go.
There is no try.
Because he's a wimp.
Yeah, there's no trying team.
Yeah.
And I'm glad he's getting into this.
have to say about these these these these guys try guys I think these fellas are
getting them into getting in themselves into so much trouble with women I'm say
hey fellas how about you try guys that's right I think the one thing goes strike
there has is I think one of them needs to try girls that's a I don't know okay
right I don't think it's possible to tell from looking at any of those guys
whether they're gay or not. Thai guys? Yeah, Thai guys. Like guys from Taiwan?
Yeah, my... Or Thailand? My friend, Ronnie. You want Ronnie from Thailand?
Taiwan. So he's from Taiwan. He's not really my friend, he's more like my
mom's boss. He taught you how to say that. Yeah, he did teach me how to tell my mom
she was fired in Taiwanese. Really? That's kind of cool. Yeah. Has he had to use that before?
Is he fired? No, he didn't fire my mom. He just thought it would be funny
If you started saying that in Taiwanese, you never tell I've definitely told this before he came up to me one time
It was I was in I just got home from I was home visiting from the community college
I was going to I was home from the community. I was home from my yeah, I was given back and
I
Gained so I stopped I gained a little bit of weight and he walks up to me and he's like hey, man, are you?
Is everything all right with you?
um
You know, it's always a nice thing. Yeah, he's like is everything good. Are you like depressed? Are you depressed? Yeah
and I was just like what what the fuck is this guy doing like I was like
i'm
I'm, all right. I why he's like, oh you got really fat
Yeah, you got really fat and I was wondering if there's something wrong with you because you're fucking huge
Yeah, he owned you. Yeah, you oh he got me
- You switched there, caring about you
just so you can say you're fat.
- Yeah.
- You came back from college and you gained a little weight.
When I came back from college, I gained a little weight.
Wait, don't tell me.
Got a little bit of NPR knowledge.
- Ah.
- Yeah, it was kind of like a liberal--
- Yeah, you came back from community corn dogs.
- That's right, that's right.
Yeah.
- Everything else.
- Community all this food.
- What, I ate the community?
- Yeah, you ate the--
(laughing)
Yeah, you went to college, you ate the entire community
in a single bite and became hugely fat and you went back.
- What university did I go to?
I went to the I went to Golden Corral
Go to GCU
GCU
Gostallions
I majored in
Golden Corral Unlimited
That would be so funny if you like
All you can learn
That would be so funny
If the school had a culinary program that would be so funny
It's so fucked
I hate getting the syllabus at the beginning of the semester
and being like oh my god
much fucking money on forks and knives. I just spend this much on forks and knives and my
calories are graded on a scale. And I hate that you can't just reuse the plate, you have
to buy a new one for every fucking class. You are graded on a scale also. You got hugely
foodly. From Golden Corral University. And then your mom's boss got you. But you look
good right now, you've been in the gym? I've been riding a bike everywhere. What does that
I don't know, something about cardio.
I rode, so yesterday I rode my bike all the way, I was going to this skate park under
the bridge and I saw this, on the way there there's all these industrial things and I
went down this one thing, this road that's just all concrete mixing and I think it's
It's like the national grid building.
And I went down the street and this dude pulls over
and he goes, "Hey, habla espanol?"
And I was like, "No."
- He shouldn't be able to start with hey.
- Right?
- You can't do English into Spanish.
- Right, so then I'm trying to leave
and then he wolf whistles me over again
and I'm like, "What, what do you want?"
He's like, "Do you like business?"
How'd you say?
No.
What?
I told him no.
Why would you say no?
I told him no and then he takes off his ring
and looks at me and is like,
"Do you wanna buy this gold ring?"
And I was like, "No."
Like, what the fuck?
Just leave me alone.
You were just fucking pissing on your opportunities.
I wasn't gonna buy a gold ring off this guy in like a--
That could have been a spy ring.
That could have been a James Bond laser ring.
You own a business.
You're a fucking 33,
well, you're a 31% shareholder.
in a bit in an actual business.
- So I'm not gonna tell him that.
I'm not gonna, I'm gonna be like,
what's his name about it?
- Yeah, don't be.
- Who's that CEO who dresses like shit?
Oh, Mark Zuckerberg.
- What?
- You CEO dresses like shit?
(laughing)
On CEO Facebook, you're like, he just, his fits are whack.
- I don't understand.
What do you mean also?
What do you mean you're not gonna be like Mark Zuckerberg
about it?
- You think his fits are whack,
you do a price breakdown and that that gray t-shirt that's hugging his titties
that t-shirt is $44 yeah that's expensive tee it's an expensive
blank t-shirt and I bet it's climbing. Did you guys watch him on on Rogan? No. It's pretty
awesome yeah yeah he showed that he actually knows how to take a sip of
water like a normal person Wow yeah Rogan was like it was so funny
Rogan's bullying the like richest guy the world is like can you take a sip of
water to prove that you know how to take like a real sip of water because you did
it's so weird in the Senate hearing he was like yeah yeah okay okay he just
takes Mark Zuckerberg's haircut is awesome he has the Roman the Roman like
Julius Caesar he's obsessed with no it's a it's another guy it's uh yeah yeah
Marcus really yes I forget who it is it's some it's some Roman guy that is
obsessed with a Roman guy he's that's why that's why his hair is is cut like
that he cut his hair like it like the Roman Emperor did it or whatever I don't
believe that it's completely true he does obsessed with the Augustus Gloop and
he's like he wants Facebook to be a big tube it should be a tube the only the
only CEO ever figured out whoever figured out how to look at is Caesar it's
Augustus Caesar yeah um the only it says may I think did he didn't say this let's
see here.
Well, he just has a haircut is a source of fascination.
Is that his wife?
Yeah.
It's cool.
He lets his wife cut his hair.
There's nothing wrong with dude.
This haircut sick.
If you saw this haircut downtown, you'll be like this haircut is
called the Caesar cut.
If you saw this haircut on like a guy in tight biker jeans with
like a bunch of thin line work tattoos like black tattoos, you'd
be like, holy shit.
Biker jeans and like the fucking like the square glasses. Yeah, they're like blue frame. I have a pair of those
I bet you do I have a pair of those that I was going to wear to my cousin's wedding and I forgot them at home
They had a cheetah playing with a ball on the side of the only guy who figured out how to look as a CEO was
The the Jack from Twitter guy because he's like I'm just gonna look like Maharishi
Just know the only the guy my shit out not even Jack not even Jack
Oh, the best-dressed CEO is the guy who wears the suit with all the money on it
You know what I'm talking about?
Fuck no.
What are you even on about?
That's what a CEO should dress like.
I think he wears a hundred dollar print suit.
I think it's the bang CEO.
Yeah, that guy too.
I think that guy has it figured out.
No, but I'm talking about big billionaire types.
Okay, right, so you weren't talking, you didn't CEO.
So you lied and you just made something up.
I said tech CEOs actually.
You did not.
So you guys are both stupid.
I said tech CEOs earlier and you keep hitting that.
I think you gotta you gotta go you gotta just look crazy the coolest guy ever was
the guy in my hometown dollar bill and he had this day it was called dollar bills
outlet and he wore an umbrella hat that had dollar bills hanging off of it
that's cool this is the coolest guy in the way of his eyesight so he's having
a store he'd have these commercials where it's like him showing off like oh
like bed frames like blah blah blah and he's walking around his department store
and he's got big dollar bills hanging off of his umbrella hat.
We had guys in our-
Dollar bills premium outlet.
We had plenty of guys like that in our hometown too.
Yeah, I know.
You probably did.
We did have plenty of-
Yeah.
Like who?
Our guy was $100 bill and he had $100 bills hanging off his umbrella hat.
We had a bunch of guys.
We had-
Who?
Mr. Slavery?
The guy who used to own slaves and now he's basically giving away bed frames as reparations?
No, there was this guy, he was called Ants in My Eyes Johnson.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
And he was...
Wait, what?
Did he have a TV commercial?
I mean, dude, you won't even believe this.
This fucking guy, he's in Wilmington, North Carolina, he was in my hometown, you guys
haven't seen this.
It was a guy who walks around, he's got ants that are in his eyes and he sells doors.
And you saw this on TV in Wilmington?
It was on TV in Wilmington and he basically walked around and I think he...
What time of night was this on?
And then he caught on fire.
it was in it comes on at right at midnight. Basically, there was there's a
crazy commercial in my hometown to that was kind of a local commercial. Yeah,
yeah, it's called the greatest. No way yeah, really yeah, I just I would love
to know the story behind like who came up with this to this. If I could get in
the mascot because it really on the wall in that board, oh my God, right when I
came up with that, I will shoot that. I mean that honestly the making of that
commercial would be an interesting thing to see on TV. You guys ever see that
- Show too many cooks.
- Yeah.
- Weirdest bullshit I've ever seen.
- Oh yeah, I remember that.
- It's just the intro.
- Weirdest bullshit.
- There's this restaurant.
- I don't even remember an episode.
- There's this restaurant in my hometown
that had this like fucking crazy deal.
It was called Taco Town.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
- What was the deal?
- Big ass taco.
- Okay, that makes sense.
- I can't even tell you how many ingredients it had.
- Well I mean, it's just a taco though.
It's not that special.
- Oh, trust me.
- What happened then?
- It's not just a taco.
- Well what was it then?
If it wasn't just a taco?
they had a pancake on the taco they put it in a bag so it's almost like so it's
almost like it was a taco wrapped in a gordita wrapped in a quesadilla with a
crepe a French crepe and a blueberry pancake that's and they wrapped it in a
corn husk and then they put it in a bag and they pour chili on it was it that I
I think I saw that commercial.
I don't remember the fucking order.
Because it's smallest to largest, dude.
The bags obviously, they don't put a bag and then wrap it in a fucking tortilla.
Oh, and then, well, they deep fry it. I forgot. They deep fry it at the pancake.
Oh, and then they beer batter it and deep fry it.
And then...
And then they put the pizza around it.
And then they put the pepperoni pizza, then they put it in the bag, chili on top.
Uh-huh. Vegetarian chili.
Vegetarian chili, yeah. It's a great commercial.
And then do you guys ever see the Cosby show?
That guy's in jail
Surprising too many people yeah the Cosby face we used to him back in my hometown we used to have a planet called Cybertron
Yeah, really. Mm-hmm. What was it? Like it was a war most of it
It was like basically eternal war between two factions. I used to have this thing this fucking we use everybody in North Carolina
Did it was something to do with like some kind of local law?
where like at night or just when you weren't around basically your toys would
fucking come to fucking life. Seriously? Yeah and they would fucking have like
some kind of interpersonal conflict and a lot of times they would get knocked off
the bed. I think I had that too but we had we had we had that too. Do you
remember? We had the second one of that. Yeah. Do you remember I don't because I
think it was around Boston it wasn't in Londonderry where I grew up there's that
old man who put all those balloons in his house?
Oh my god I forgot about that.
Yeah and then he flew away with the kid.
They were on his house.
He kidnapped this kid and he took him away to a mystery place.
He kidnapped a little Korean boy.
They never figured out why he did it or where he went but they thought that maybe it was because his wife was weird or something.
Like his wife drove him to...
His wife was a pedophile.
Apparently his wife hypnotized him to kidnap this little Asian kid.
died and apparently he invented a robot talking dog or a dog with a robot
device and I don't even I mean but yeah the rumors got kind of crazy you guys
really know what really happened that reminds me do you remember a couple years
ago like couple of years ago like a while back when basically the whole
fucking world was pretty much just fucking trash yeah do you remember that
and we were all oh yeah way out there and I was fat fat and a fat chair fucking no
bone I do remember I remember those slurp all day and movies we drink we drink
these movies and we watch basically drink so much smoothies about screen time we
were so addicted to screen time huh nothing you you haven't seen what you've
never seen Wally well good for you they're releasing it they're releasing
it in the criterion collection on 4k so you can spend $60 to watch it cutting
that out yeah cut that Julio cut that out I am NOT cutting it out Patrick yeah so
then we would and then remember we got fucking yes do you remember there was
that that when when Patrick was was with us in that area and he and and he had to
because of the recycling system on our spaceship yeah poop constantly you
remember that most of that that was very for me is about a guy named Patrick who
looked a lot like you and it might have actually been you literally fucking
eating robot she was like genetically engineered to turn poop back into food
with the other way you open up his stomach and he was in pieces of shit
yeah toilets turds and you turn them into not even not even for this happened
yeah i'm a poop guy and i was talking to the scientists who developed the system
that this patrick is using any i guess he was genetically engineered to to eat and
process shit new is psychologically engineered to like it more than fucking
it
and that's in wall-e that's a character in wall-e was always our memories from
recently. Yeah, just a couple years ago. When I say, I mean like a few years back. A few.
You know, like a while back, but not that long, like kind of Obama era. I was going
to see, but I think we were going to watch WALL-E, but then, do you remember that shit
happened? Yeah. A lot of shit happened with you. What happened? There's that shit where
it's like we, like, we got tickets to that ship and there's that guy saying he was like
king of the world at the front of the ship you remember this no I don't
remember that at all oh that bitch ass fucking ship yeah that big ass that was
so that's the spaceship from Wally that big-ass cruise we went on and the guy
saying I'm king of the world we're like what the hell is this guy remember we
were back then the style was like straight-up brown clothes only break
straight up brown like some Peaky Blinders like you're only wearing the
the brown clothes. Do you remember how long that fucking band played?
Yeah. It's like, shut the fuck up. Stuff's going on right now. Stop playing.
Yeah. And then something happened at the end. I don't really remember,
but I do remember I was some old and then there was that.
And then there was all that stuff on that during that ship with all those like
really tall blue people and the robot suits and stuff.
Oh, there was all that shit that was also on the ship. I think if I remember
correctly. Yeah. And I remember I walked out one day and I walked out and I
I looked up at my car and I was like straight up. I think I just saw my car
blink right and I was like no way no there's no way right and then poof I'm
fucking gone all of a sudden. It's a story of my car and this is where I have
it and it's a story of my car. You were gone and I was just gone. I just I
don't know where I went. I think I was there as a car really yeah and I
remember my car started fucking walking around. He meets this fucking rusty
piece of fucking shit right guys that like a like a mentally yeah that guy
tomato this guy in not all their tomato. He's like a he's a tomato yeah,
and this guy's so so fucking stupid. He thinks his name is tomato right and he
or tomato or tomato and he basically fucking they kidnap my friend or my car
and they basically I think they either torture him or sexually assault him and
like tie him down and like a dungeon type thing right and then they release
him and then he became famous.
Is that that really that happened in my car and I didn't exist at the time.
Yeah, I wasn't even I just stopped existing for some do you guys remember that?
What was was her name? We used to hang out with her
Cinderella mm-hmm, whatever happened or whatever happened to her
That's I remember I remember us three
We used to I mean back when I back when she was yeah back when well
I was gonna say back when she was our sister
Yeah, yeah, I just I remember the mouse thing more than be yeah the mouse thing definitely was
Yeah, do you remember that one time remember they fucking made us drive that fucking pumpkin? Oh my god. I hated that bullshit
I made us into a horse. Yeah
Annoying annoying as hell. I don't want to be a horse pumpkin turns into a big chariot. Yeah. Yeah, it's like I
Yeah, when I'm thinking about stuff like that, I'm like I must be remembering this wrong
But then I flip through my scrapbook and my photo album on my iPhone. I'm like nope that really happened. Yeah, okay wait
I thought this was low-key a dream, but I actually was a fucking pumpkin carry. Yeah, okay great time to drive Cinderella
Do you guys remember with that one time when we were all just like kind of chillin and like doing basically nothing and we were
In the UK and shit, and then there was like all the fucking dolphins, right?
They start fucking floating up right and we're like okay. That's kind of fucking weird
You're singing a song and floating up right next thing. We know the world's fucking destroyed. We're chillin with most deaf, right?
fucking that one guy's got two heads yeah I remember all the bloody that robot
that's sad ass robot yeah you take some fucking Zoloft yeah right relax I know
okay so to be nicer right yeah I thought you were talking about that time we were
chilling in London and I mean we had a crazy crazy night before yeah we were
celebrating. Basically every time we go to LDN it's like that. Yeah oh my god I have a
London story too. So we have like this amazing night and then we wake up the
next day fucking all these people have this virus. Yeah I remember how long was
it between when we were partying and the virus happened I can't remember the
exact amount of time I feel like it was like days was it? Day and night. It was like day and
night. That song for whatever reason just always makes you think
I think it was London nights. Yep. And we were we were that was when we were
hanging out with silly and Murphy too. Yep. Yeah. He was so cool. He's hot
change though. Yeah, he did change. He almost became more old school. Yeah, he
also there was he went through that phase where he was being so scary. Yeah,
and he was wearing that mask and going. Yeah, yeah, and then he was like, you
know, I'm just gonna start kicking it old school, right? And we were like,
okay, do your old school style or whatever. And he just started fucking
He's Karen Flintlock. He starts calling himself Tommy. Yeah, that's right. He's like, oh, this is a new nickname
It's like man, man. Shut your bitch-ass up. Shut up, Killian
Killian church Killian Killian church be mm-hmm like Killian's church be like change your name back. Yeah
That's your Catholic name. Mm-hmm little ass
Blue eyed Irish guy remember when I got all eyes
Got straight up. It's fucking legendary. I got fucking blowjob from Chloe seven. Yeah
Came in her mouth really I don't remember that cuz I wasn't there came in her mouth you guys are both watching we were there yes
I'm not sure I remember
You would have remembered me nutting in her fucking mouth. Oh wait wait wait at the same time
Is that around the same time that you gave Chloe seven yay, HIV?
And we were all skateboarding in New York. It was pretty and we killed that guy in Washington Square Park
Yeah, it was pretty close to that. Yeah when I gave her HIV. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I think it was actually right before that
Oh, I nutted in her mouth, maybe Wow. Yeah, so it's pretty much. I've had a legendary career as a guy. Yeah
Yeah, oh and then and then we all learned how to roll a joint in the park
Do you guys remember we used to hang out with that guy fucking he had the coolest house ever that fucking a guy that guy
Rolly polly ollie. Oh my god
Fucking animated we should hit him up. We should his dad was a fucking trip and his mom was
was Kirby. His mom was nice. I just remember he had to stop hanging out with the Pevensies.
Oh my god dude, the fucking Pevensies. We started hanging out with Roly Poly after we were hanging
out with the Pevensies. Every time we hung out with the Pevensies they were like, "Get
in the wardrobe!" I know, it's like, "Let's play hide and seek." Okay, you hide in the
wardrobe. I was like, "I don't want to hide in the fucking wardrobe. It smells like shit
in there and there's a goat man. They're gone for five minutes, right? They hide in
the wardrobe. I'm not getting fucked. I'm claustrophobic. I'm not getting in there.
They're gone for five minutes. They come back and they're like, "We've been gone for 30 years!"
All of a sudden there's water flooding into my fucking room from one of their fucking stupid gay paintings.
Speaking of the Pevensies though, you know who actually was sick as hell to hang out with back in the day?
I don't know if you guys remember him. Dudley Dursley? He was fucking sick. Dude, he was...
That guy was wild. He was crazy. He was so mean to his little brother.
Remember when he used to smack his little brother?
Yeah. Was it his brother or his cousin?
We'd go in there and we'd make spaghetti or something.
We'd strain out the noodles and put the hot water on his feet.
Oh my god, dude.
He'd get all mad. He'd get so mad the fucking electricity starts flickering and shit.
And you're like, "Whoa, you fucking goth freak."
Yeah, you little goth bastard.
That little, he had that, 'cause they put him
in that little ass room 'cause he was like,
like I mean, look, I'm not condoning what his parents did.
- He's a fun-- - 'Cause they would tell it,
well his mom would say like,
he's a bit mental in the head.
- Yeah, yeah. - He's special.
- He was a bit touched.
- He was a bit special. - Yeah, yeah.
She said that he was special needs
and they would keep him in the stairs.
And then he went off to that special needs school, Hogwarts.
- Oh my God.
Literally a school for ugly little children.
I mean, think about the name.
- Yeah, true.
- I mean, I wish I could have been at that school
and just smacked him with a--
- Yeah, but then he, I mean,
he was pretty much normal though.
I don't know why they kept calling him,
I guess he had some needs that,
I guess normal school couldn't meet.
- Yeah, maybe like dietary.
Maybe he was like celiac or something.
- Oh yeah, 'cause in the UK, if you have celiac--
- No dude, I'm telling you,
there was something wrong with his brain.
I don't know if you guys noticed.
got this crazy scar on his forehead I think he got hit in the head by me. Oh that makes
sense he had TBI. Yeah. Yeah he had a TBI. Yeah. Well I mean celiac. That's why he was
always like just speaking in that made up language and he would always point at us and
go like "Avada Kedavra" and stuff. Celiac in the UK is a special need because then you
can't have a full English. True you can't have a toast. It's all beans no toast. Uh huh.
Right? Wait where do I put these beans on? Exactly. These beans on tongue. What are you
gonna put on that charge piece of tomato that they have for everyone we were
sausages and had a party
and you remember that
yeah yeah a lot of people don't like our party and we've got such fucking dope
ass life you know
probably one of the great the all-time you read a fucking new bible about us
to your
on my god i have an idea for what that by will be called what i hope they serve
beer in hell
holy shit i was gonna suggest the bible
I hope they serve beer in hell colon the life of Brian.
He said that's Tucker Max.
I hope they serve beer in hell.
I don't know man.
He was, because Tucker Max was like a...
I'm into real fucking books.
He was like a blogger and then like he wrote that book because his blog was doing well.
The stuff like Be Here Now, Ram Dass.
Who's Ram Dass?
Baba Ram Dass.
Baba Ram Dass? You don't know Baba Ram Dass?
Are you doing like a reggaeton song?
- No, but you kinda, it kinda, Babaramdas.
- Babaramdas!
- No, he's a white guy who invented LSD
and became a hippie.
- Yeah.
- And he went, and he died recently.
And he wrote all these--
- I'm gonna tell you straight up right now,
I fucking hate hippies.
- Me too, man.
- I hate hippies, but--
- Listen, you might hate hippies,
but I think if you read the book Siddhartha
by Herman Hesse, I think a lot of stuff
might change in your life.
- Yeah.
Thank you my learn how to i think you might learn how to live in india
by doing that
the only only know what you should say should have like a hippie they should
like you know how there's like people who are hippies
for me like this and they were like the flower shirts and listen to janice
joplin but it's like a you were born in nineteen ninety six why you doing that
yeah uh... they should have that for people who uh...
one uh...
do like that
mid-eighties
uh... cocaine stuff
They should have hippies but that. There should be a word for that.
What are you talking about?
Like...
Try to talk in a way that I can understand what you're saying.
Like doing like a...
Say it with your chest. What do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
Day in, day out.
What the fuck do you want to do? And who are you trying to do it like?
Trying to... I'm trying to live like...
I'm in Manchester, innit?
You want to be in Manchester...
Manchester!
I see it, innit?
Don't know what the fuck you're talking about. What are you even fucking saying? Oh, I go is Manchester go to Hesse and
She knew water. I'm so good. I don't know what's happening. You want to be an 80s
I hit my head this morning. Oh, that makes a lot more sense. I want to be in the mod scene
Oh, yeah, I'm on a bitch. Bye. Yeah. Oh fuck my fucking girlfriends for yeah
My go weed hair. Yeah
Big hair and big eye liner. I'm a fucking extreme fucking blow up. She's got big eye liner.
The mod scene is fucking dope dude. Twiggy!
You ever seen the movie Quadrophenia? No. It's a movie, it's a movie made by the who about...
Come on. No, no. What the hell? No. It's a movie made by the who about how they used to be very big
in the mod scene and how they were the biggest band in the world. Get rid of the
mod scene, bring back the God scene. There's a whole scene in
Quadrophenia where it's like, they're like, "Oh I hate rockers! I'm a mod! I
hate rockers!" They hated rockers because rockers used to beat up the mods. Yeah.
Right? There's a mods versus rocker rumble and then he sees
that Sting is in the movie and he sees that Sting gets a job as a bellboy.
Yeah, and he crashes stings a Vespa off of a cliff. No the mods were rumbling the mods were rumbling
Of course the mods are rumbling they're all they all weared weared chessboard clothing
Come on that's why they're fucking rumbling like a fucking Gamecube controller with like that chess guy
Chess about this chess guy. Oh, yeah, what's the deal with that? I don't know
I don't know grandmaster you or anal beads or something. Yeah
How did that get
Speculated at all that's for a while people have been like well
that's kind of the only way that you could probably cheat at chess at one of these big tournaments because they they do a metal
detector on you and
but if you had some kind of
anal bead kind of plastic thing
They're not listen, what are the you guys are they shaped like is it like no it just it would rumble
It would it would basically rumble when he has the right move
Though I mean that's somebody watching
the only way
I thought they were gonna say that the the chest pieces the anal beads are shaped like each of the pieces and
Then the pieces that were gonna say that the order he had a full-on
Operation style they were the pieces are in it
So it's like the first beat is like a pawn.
The second beat is like the knight.
The third beat is like the queen or something.
- Wow, that is truly unreal that your brain went to that.
That's what you thought that was what it was gonna be.
- I didn't actually think that was,
I was trying to make a joke.
- No, you believed that.
- I did not believe that.
- You believed that.
- We did.
- Did we ever talk about the chess cheating guy
who attacked the kid in the bathroom?
- Yeah.
- We did, okay.
- What, he slashed his face?
- No.
- What am I thinking of?
the mad slasher. You're thinking of Jack the Ripper. Oh yeah he ripped him. Yeah.
Yeah. No that's a different guy. Yeah. Do you remember hanging out with that guy back in the day?
Listen he was a nice guy. He threw some rippers though. That's what I'll say.
Jack the Rager. That's what we called him because he did have serious rage problems.
Yeah when he drank he was like a different person. Yeah. Yeah. Y'all remember
that fucker Dr. Hyde? That guy was fucking cool. His brother was actually
low-key fucking green mm-hmm well I thought I time brother his he was green
and his brother he and his brother wasn't I think you're misremembering no yeah
his brother he was he was big and scary dr. Jekyll I mean yeah so yeah you are
kind of his brother well I said dr. Hyde he said mr. Hyde I said no you're wrong
I said I know I said doctor okay well it's still not right doesn't matter
remember when I remember when our friend brain wrote that song the Jekyll Jekyll
hides yeah Jekyll hide-hide Jekyll I do remember that that's a fire song we have
a list today what's the dealio bring us in okay the dealio big C oh so someone
wants to do a list now there's only one big C on the show um and it's me
no Cameron no that's that's big C cuz he's taller than you know way more and
And you are C. Biscuit.
I'll take C. Nevermind, I wanna be C. Biscuit. That's actually cooler.
[Laughter]
C-Biscuit.
That's cooler. That's way fucking cooler.
Alright, take it, take it, take it away, Big C.
[Laughter]
Thanks, Lil P.
Do you wanna be Lil P?
What do you wanna be? You can pick.
I just wanna be Patrick. I don't want any of these nicknames.
Twisted P is really good.
They stress me out.
twisted p? twisted p is really good. twisted p that boy crazy. twisted p. so I'm back on
the same website. ghost street. ghost street from last time. and I found this other list
on here which is 10. pat what are you doing? you're causing havoc. listen seed biscuit don't
play that. I can't really see this. you chose to sit down in a full rain to be twisted.
over this way you really think I can scoot over with this right here you can
change chairs you chose to sit there it's your problem
chairs he truly is twisted this is the 10 this is the 10 most handsome sons in
the world Wow from coasts okay here it says what is this so I would say what
what category of the website are we in right now
- Unknown, it says. - Biranda.
- Oh, oh, unknown is the author.
- Yeah, we're in the category, Biranda.
- All right.
- Biranda.
- 10 most handsome son in the world.
The term handsome or good looking is usually used
only to men who have been moving up.
But what if it turns out that only some of his little boy
also has shown their good looks?
Same is the case for the prettiest girls then, of course.
There is also a list of most handsome boy in the world.
Here are 10 boys most handsome in the world.
- All right, so my problem with this is,
This guy hasn't seen every fucking boy.
You don't know.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I guess the qualifier here...
I guess it's written by unknown.
If there's any guy who's seen every boy in the world, I would think it would be unknown.
Yeah, he's probably anonymous.
Yeah.
Maybe this is written by our creator.
Whoa.
God.
Holy shit.
G-D.
Damn.
Shout out to my Jews.
Um, number 10 is...
Shout out to my Jewish fucking chosen people.
I put that - instead of the oh number 10 is Mason - disick that's Scott disicks
kid yeah mation well actually no I'm here yeah I'm reading here Mason - disick was
born in Los Angeles on December 14th 2009 was the son of celebrities disick Scott
and Kourtney Kardashian so this is actually the son of disick Scott not
Scott disick Kourtney Kardashian is the one dating Travis Barker now mm-hmm
That is her handsome son.
This is her son who's um
going to be either
become goth or something now.
He's going to be either become goth or something.
I mean it's a possibility that.
This website's really
fucking with my brain.
The name Mason himself fairly well known
Kardashian family since which makes
it fit in a few TV series such as
Keeping Up With Kourtney, Kim Kardashian
and Take Miami Kourtney and Kim Take New York
and Cuteness and her handsome
barrister figure making Mason as fans that not a few holy crap this kid's a
fucking popular celebrity I will say he's kind of a I mean bit of a dog face
really yeah I don't think that this is that handsome of a boy he's also he's in
this picture he's got he's got a fistful of bread how about you salad get down on
the car but yeah here's my plan for Mason we're gonna get him on a fun a
strong list three by three kind of kind of weightlifting routine right we're
gonna because I see I see his arms he doesn't have any definition yeah 10 miles
a day of running. He has good genetics. We're going to be throwing in between all that,
we're going to be throwing in a lot of pulling the trigger. Yeah, we're also a little...
He's a huge... What is he now? He's probably 13, 14 at this point? 2009. 2012. We're going
to be saying a lot of things to him that are going to make him develop anorexia. No, see,
we don't want him to be anorexic. We're going to get him a trick mirror. We're going to
get him a trick mirror. We're gonna get him on HRT 150 mg a week. We're gonna get him on
Trembolone. HRT? Yeah. Yeah. And I just want to, I want to, I want to just say real
fast to you, Pat said we're gonna give him anorexia. That's not the case. We
just want to get him to a healthy sub 100 pound weight. Just so he's looking
nice and handsome. Pat, that's what steroids are. It's HRT. Really? Yeah.
Yeah. They also call steroids HRT. It's the same thing. I thought it was HGH and
- And then HRT is--
- No, HGH is human growth hormone,
but HRT is steroids, TRT, testosterone replacement therapy.
- Okay.
- So we're gonna get him some testosterone.
- And is there any way I can get some of that?
- Yeah, you can, you actually can.
It's pretty easy. - Really?
- Yeah.
We're gonna get him on Tremblom,
we're gonna get him on SARMS, right?
300 milligrams, or five milligrams creatine,
every single day. - And a, yeah,
Bang Energy sponsorship.
- Bang Energy, Carnitine. - Wellbutrin, Nabilify.
- Yeah, Zoloft. - Oshkaganda,
Tunga-Ali. - Risperdal.
- Risperdal. - Right?
We're gonna get him on all of that.
- He's gonna get four hours on a stair climber minimum,
every single day.
- Two hours of sleep.
- Yeah, two hours of sleep.
- Uber mid-cycle.
- Uber mid-cycle, we're gonna do two hours,
three times a day, right?
Just naps, right?
Keeps him active on shoots and stuff.
- Zyrtec Benadryl Claritin.
- Yeah, all three, daily, twice a day.
- Some of the, we're gonna get him on--
- Signed to image, right?
And he's just basically gonna be walking down that runway.
- Elderberry syrup.
- Henna.
- Henna. - Lots of henna.
- We're giving him some henna tattoos.
- Facial masculization.
- Uh-huh, yeah, jaw fillers.
- Yeah, we're gonna get huge Zac Efron jaw fillers.
We're gonna get, honestly, I see his hairline,
it's not the best, so we're gonna ship him off to Turkey.
Right, we need to get him a passport.
- Beard plugs.
- Yeah, facial hair plugs, head hair plugs.
- Get the beard plugs in early,
because you could have one patch right here
that doesn't grow in.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Bionic arm.
- Yeah, bionicles.
- Microchip.
- We're gonna get him some bionicles.
- Tracker.
And that's the only thing he's allowed to play with.
Because we're going to tell him, we're going to get him
Bionicles as a body image issue enabler.
We're going to say, if you don't fucking look like this.
Put one hand in the microwave.
Yeah, just see what happens.
Yeah, just that's for us as a joke, right?
Pre-workout before bed.
We're going to get him on C4.
He's going to be dry scooping C4.
And you know those shoes that, the basketball shoes that have
big platform on the bottom. He's gonna be 10 jumps every morning.
Weighted vest too.
Weighted vest while he's jumping.
Centrifuge like space camp.
Try to stretch him out.
Yeah.
Cause he needs to be 6 feet at least.
He needs to be able to sustain at least 20 G's.
And now, Mason listen buddy, I know you're 10 now, you know, 2, 3 years from now, you
could be number 1.
Yeah, you're gonna thank us.
You could break top 3.
Yeah.
So, you're welcome.
Alright, so that's our plan for Mason.
I mean, top 3 is generous. He's gonna be like 5.
I mean here we here we got him. I mean he's number 10. He's the bottom of the
top 10. So anything is better. We'll see I mean I mean and that's our plan for
Mason. But I guess we can see what we're gonna do with these some of these other
beautiful handsome sons. Number nine is Kim Jin-woo. Born on 20 March 2006 in
South Korea, Kim Jin-woo is one of the boys figures who have often
appear in TV drama Korea. Some examples of these plays is Aquarius, The Iron
Empress, three sisters, and the latest is the Empress of Ki. His career in the world of
the play has started in 2008 to 2014, so since childhood he has often met famous celebrity
figure of Korea.
I think nothing's gonna help this kid, he's gonna stay at number 9 forever.
Yeah, I mean it's honestly just the market he's in is too small.
I think, you know, I think that we could see a change in trends of what we consider handsome
and what, you know, how people rate these sons and I think that maybe if we put this
son here, Kim Jin-woo, if we put him in, you know, carbonite or some kind of cryo sleep
for maybe 20 to 40 years so he can maintain his current age for a long time, I think we
could see a better chance for him to climb the rankings in maybe, you know, 2040, 2060,
something like that.
Yeah, that's true.
But, you know, for now, if he's against being frozen in gel, I think he's out.
Okay.
Alright, let's move on.
He also only has maybe two more years of being a boy because he was born in 2006.
So he is 16 years old. Yeah. Yeah. So yeah, you know, sorry Kim Jinwoo, but you're
Charlie Axel Woods
This is Tiger Woods's boy. Let's hear. Why don't you read out our never heard the name Tiger Woods? I never have yes
Charlie Axel Woods is the name of the boy from the figure of famous golf athletes born February 8th
2009 Charlie Axel Woods used to be a figure that highlighted the world's attention a
handsome body itself obtained from his father, Tiger Woods, and also his mother
who was her model, Ellen Nord... Nordegaren of Sweden, former wife of
Tiger Woods. He, uh, this guy, this kid actually is a really good golfer. Yeah?
Yeah, no, he did a, he did a father-son tournament. Really? No, I think so. This, he
could, he could, you know, he could, this guy could, this kid could be a contender
in the talent category maybe. Yeah I think he stays at number eight just because of
his talent. Sure. And also his dad is like, Tiger Woods is a pretty good looking guy.
I wouldn't say that he's the most anywhere near the most handsome men, the
top ten most handsome men. Yeah. He's good-looking but he's not top ten material
so I don't want to see really see how his son can break that. I guess I would like to
see Charlie Axel Woods attend some kind of boot camp or some kind of rigorous
training regimen where he's you know forced to play golf maybe 10 to 12 to 14
to 16 hours a day. He needs to be more well-rounded and honestly needs to pick up maybe three or four
other sports. That's true. Have you seen Tiger Woods? Tiger Woods has a I think
every year there's one thing I remember seeing it's Tiger Woods shirtless in a
Santa hat and beard and it says like "Sexy Santa again this year." What? I think
that I'm gonna make a kid do that no no I'm saying that maybe he has some comedy
prowess in him because if his dad is that interesting and then all of a sudden he
could be the next some he could be one of the next big I think yeah some UCB 101
we have to keep this kid out of UCB yeah any other any other comedy collector
or just keep them away from you see a good good point. Yeah, maybe the
round. I think the ground links will be perfect for him. You know, just
knowing what he's good at and you know well yeah groundlings. Hey, you know
he's hit a few groundlings with the golf ball exactly. I just think he'd excel
on and and maybe some groundling is like an animal on the ground. I think he'd
he'd excel in
like a like a mole. He's probably a few moles or alag a stout
Stoats I think he's put I you know what I want to see him do a father-son golf
tournament maybe like a Stoat contos him and his dad yeah who can hit a Stoat
exactly it's that's like going hunting with your dad this could be and that
could be a perfect comedy sketch kind of a character based humor but it'd be real
it'd be like that flash game where you shoot cats out of the cannon yep yeah
exactly and it would also be like Borat like just because it would be like a
comedy thing that's kinda real. And Borat could be there.
The father's child thing. Is this boring you?
Little bit, yeah I'm pretty bored of Charlie Axelwood.
Alright, let's move on then. Here Caleb, you can take this next one.
Sean Preston Federline Spears.
Federline Spears, a son of Britney Spears, married to Kevin Federline.
Born on September 14, 2005, and his brother Sean,
Jaden had been a model of her music video clip entitled "Ooh La La."
So here's one thing, this kid's fucking drinking an icy.
Who's Jaden?
Wait, who's Jaden?
I don't know.
Probably his brother.
I don't know either.
I will say he's got a good fit here.
He kind of looks like Jon Hamm.
So I think that if we take the icy out, replace that with maybe...
With some ice.
With something from...
In old fashioned, because it's Jon Hamm.
Maybe an Erewhon water bottle.
Right?
Voss.
Yeah, Voss.
I think there's two routes we could go here.
What are you saying?
I'm saying maybe we'd replace the...
like, because you're saying he's got a Jon Hamm thing going. Yeah. Maybe we replace it
with like a Long Island iced tea or like a bourbon straight, double bourbon straight.
No, no, but Jon Hamm is known for like having kind of plain clothes that speak for themselves
a little bit. He's not too flashy, right, but he's a health nut, right? He takes good
care of his body. He's pushing 50, okay, and he looks like that. So we need to have him
on. He's got some kind of green juice in his hand, right? He's walking, he's got the blazer
Ron very very very tasteful I would say kind of casual walkabout avoiding the
paparazzi kind of look and plus he's got the dad shoes on right which are
actually for the celebrity that's like a kind of a power play. Oh those are the Rosh runs.
Yeah he's got the Roshi runs on which are like yeah it's a bit like yeah fuck you
fuck you I still live my life even though I'm a
celeb. Can I throw out a little pitch for you guys here?
So, I mean, just looking at this kid's outfit here, and also looking at his name, Sean Preston
Federline Spears, I'm just going to throw out, just give this some consideration, okay?
J.R.R.
Tolkien, W.E.B.
Du Bois, S.P.F.
Spears.
S.P.F.
Spears is great.
Famous author.
And then it really, like, she becomes a famous author in the future.
It really changed, or now, who knows?
And it really changes.
The child author.
It never has been one since Eric.
What's the name of the guy who wrote Jurassic Park?
Michael Crichton.
Yeah, so like Michael Crichton kind of thing where you're like, "Okay, well he's just an
author, he's probably ugly," and then you see a picture of him and he's a fucking ten.
Yeah, a ten-year-old kid.
Yeah, well he's a ten-year-old and a most handsome boy.
So that's what we kind of want with this.
I mean, and the outfit, I mean this is minus the icy.
I think if we kind of, we can do some Photoshop magic, change this icy into maybe a pipe.
And I think this would be a perfect About the Author picture.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
we have a perfect about the author blurb right here. A son of Britney Spears
marriage to Kevin Federline and this is on the back of a yeah it's on the inside
of the dust cover. It has like you know the front has like a dragon that's like
attacking some kind of giant computer yeah and this it has all this info right
there. I think that could be huge. SPF Spears. SPF Spears. Yeah.
And the first this is on the back. This is on the computer. Yeah you can write that now. I was gonna
to suggest a title. I thought maybe he's like a James Patterson style author and he's got
a book called The Lemon Tree. You read The Lemon Tree and it sounds kind of just normal.
I don't know what this could be. It's like a haunted lemon tree.
Whoa.
All fucking shit.
With lemons that scream at you.
No. Screaming lemons?
Yeah.
So you go to pick the lemon.
Hmm, this lemon tree is in my brain.
Yeah, well, I screamed a little too early.
But you'd go, yeah, okay,
I just bought this giant mansion, right?
It belonged to, let's say, Alexander Graham Bell, right?
And then you're walking around,
you've seen a couple of these things.
Well, Alexander Graham, let's change it so there's like,
I mean, so if you know--
Okay, George Washington Carver.
If you know, like it's an if you know, you know,
so maybe like Alastair McCrowley.
Alastair McCrowley.
Yeah.
So we have Alastair,
we're at Alastair McCrowley's giant mansion, right?
and we're like, "Oh, that lemon tree outside,
"and it's a nice contrast with all the gray and brown."
And you go to reach it, and then it turns around,
full fucking annoying orange, screaming at you.
The annoying lemon.
- Oh my God.
- The agonizing lemon.
- Yes.
- That would be really good.
- That'd be fucking dope.
- SPF Spears, I mean, head to the bookstore.
It's out right now.
Number six is Yeezy Yu.
- Yeezy Yu.
- I'm sorry, if I'm not pronouncing this right,
I apologize to Yeezy Yu.
Originating from China, children are often fondly known
as Baby Z.U. was born on June 14, 2008.
It is unquestionable why Baby Z.U. could fit
into one of the 10 most beautiful child in the world.
Because too handsome Z.U. managed to become a famous model.
He is often mentioned having a natural resemblance
to former members of EXO, Korean boy band,
namely Luhan, perhaps this too,
which causes it to be very famous.
- That's true, it does cause it to be very famous.
- I don't know much about this guy.
- Baby Z.U.?
- Yeah, and I kinda wanna get to the actually
like the higher end. Yeah, I think we can I think we can we can see this is you
like I wish you sorry buddy but disposal six is where you're gonna be. Yeah.
Number five here. Alexander Sasha Pete, Alexander Sasha Pete was that like a
list of Russian guys hanging out at the bar.
Found that out. Come on, Pete. The first child of the famous American actor and
producer Leo Schreiber. Remember Sabertooth from the movie Wolverine? Yes,
that's leah schreiber wow born on july twenty five two thousand seven in los
angeles alexander sasha pete or sorry alex and are
sasha p
was the son of the figure
his blonde hair white skin blue eyes made him often touted to be the figure of a
man who was very handsome one adult
saber to this the only uh... but maybe we will see the body on the t_v_ screen
as it is still not known
whether alexander will follow in the footsteps of her parents as actors or
choose another option. Interesting that they make note of his white skin.
Yeah. He's so handsome, his white skin.
They pick Wolverine, hey buddy,
that's Ray Donovan you're talking about. Yeah, that's right. Come on.
Put some respect on Ray Donovan. Yeah. This could be fucking
young Donnie. Yeah. Young Ray. I think, so this is making me think, I am glad that they
mentioned Wolverine though because I think that Alexander
Sasha Pete might thrive as a kid with superpowers.
- Really? - True.
- Good point. - I think he might be
a really good Twilight Zone kid.
- Radioactively white skin.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- He blinds you. - God, that guy's skin
is so fucking white.
- Oh my God, wait, okay, okay.
- You think it's white now,
wait 'til I activate my white skin.
- And, Liev, I know you're listening.
- Yeah. - I know you're listening.
What you need to do,
keep your kid-- - Those big cauliflower ears.
- Keep your kid in a completely dark room for years.
- Yeah. - No sunlight.
- We gotta-- - No sunlight.
got to keep that skin white uh-huh pasty white like like keep them in a dark a
room not even a candle a yeah the mirror can cause sunburn windows painted with
Vantablack uh-huh so there are no windows at all yeah yeah no floor and
the walls painted with Vantablack yeah no like no floor just an infinite just
just he's just suspended in there huh anti-gravity anti-gravity chamber with
Take him out one day, he's completely white like a Falmer.
Because if he's touching the ground, he could get dirt or something on his feet.
Completely white like a Falmer.
No eyes like a Falmer.
Long ears like a Falmer.
Sword like a Falmer.
Okay Lonely Island, get to the fucking picture.
We're gonna make him a Falmer.
Okay.
We can do that.
I think that would be great.
You would try to take a picture, somebody would see him flying by in the sky because he has superpowers.
That's how he's floating in the room.
room don't make us go over that but uh... but whites there yeah they sell my
god what's that white what's that white kid in the sky and they go to take a
picture overexposed never can get a picture of a skin so what i'm trying to
open the door to try to do it all what is this room
and then we have a visit
and then you open the door and it's uh... turns around it goes
did
as he's a lot
yeah like a former okay who's next year
Leo William reception.
- Recepon.
- Leo, Leo.
- It has a French father,
it has a French father and actress mother, Korea.
Leo William Recepon, famous as a boy who,
ol-zang, i.e. Korea term,
for those who have the form of handsome and unsightly.
Born on September 7th, 2008,
he was also a child actor and model of Korea,
first known through an event, i.e. Korea variety show,
hello baby along with the boy band black black cuteness of Leo making personnel
black very favored him okay so for this kid I mean it's right there what is
recipe bone recipe poem we this kid is going to culinary school yeah celebrity
chef uh-huh the next Anthony Bourdain yep he is going to good-looking he's gonna
to be like Anthony Bourdain. There is, now that I think about it, there is a void in
the cooking world that Anthony Bourdain left that needs to be filled by a French
and Korean child. Yep. Yeah. French and Korean child, he's gonna, so I mean French,
they let kids drink at the age of two. Mm-hmm. They drink wine at dinner. Mm-hmm.
That's what my mom told me. And they have soju, which is a type of rice wine, but
Soju actually just tastes like juice if you get the right juice and kids love juice
Yeah, I'll get him on alcohol
Actually, he meets the same coward's fate as Anthony. Uh-huh, but we're gonna
Try to get as much as many years out of exactly possible. Yeah, right as many years. They haven't done
Okay, they haven't done a child alcoholic heroin addict. Yeah, I haven't done it. Well, it hasn't been done
See what you need to do. Okay, so a big part of
Bourdain also was
He taught us that chefs could also be punk rock. Uh-huh. Yeah, we do have to get this kid punk
We have to get this kid. He's gonna be in a sensory deprivation tank. Okay, only listening to
American idiot, uh-huh
Don't want to be a French Korean
Child star. I want to be a French kid.
Korean child chef. He's gonna be listening to all the, you know,
that's the remix. Yeah. VH1 top 100 punk songs of all time.
Yeah. Punk goes crunk. He's gonna be listening to Krass.
He's gonna be listening to Fall Out Boy. New Found Glory.
Pretty much everything from all the punk spectrum.
The whole punk spectrum. Yeah. Everything from all time low
to a day to remember.
Nope, yeah, actually we'll keep it in a day to remember.
Mute down, Glory.
Nothing actually gives.
The entire punk spectrum.
The entire...
Set your goals.
Yeah.
He's gonna be listening to The Wacken Summer.
We're gonna...
Everything from Fall Out Boy to Andrew Jackson
Jihad. This kid is gonna
take in every punk song there is.
But it's going to be a punk chef. Yeah. Oh my God. Pink will be big.
Pink as a tattoo studio on Universal CityWalk. If you ever want to go.
Get a tattoo, that's the place to go? Yeah.
Alright, here's our next. We're closing in on the top of the list here.
Okay, this is gotta be a joke. Max Leroy Bratman.
This has got to be a joke name. Yeah, this is not a real kid.
Bratman? Bratman.
Well, let's read it. Let's see what it says.
Dr. Steven Brew trying to say Batman. I mean, completely true.
Was the son of Christina Aguilera, well I guess he must have passed.
That's awful. Yeah, so I think this is more of like a courtesy.
So let's just read it somberly and not. Yeah, so this kid is completely dead.
Yeah, so just read it, read it peacefully.
Bratman yeah was he fighting that he died because he's fighting the Drucker
no he's dead was the son of Christina Aguilera with her ex-husband Jordan
Bratman Max Lyron Bratman was born January 12 2008 while still an infant his
mother together with the max ever do a photo shoot for the cover of people
magazine with American mercenaries of 1.5 million dollars u.s. funny behavior and
good looks made him a max himself favored by many people so yeah even had
funny behavior before he died? And so I'm getting from this he was he actually
died in Iraq. He died at the hands of American mercenaries. First ever ghost
child model. Friendly fire. That is perfect. That's a very good direction. This kid he has a whole Pat Tillman
style American socialist. Pat Tillman, good looking guy. All right we got
Levi Alves McConaughey. Levi Alves born on July 7 2008 is the son of actor
father, Matthew McConaughey, producer of the fruit of her wedding to come
as a famous designer and model from Brazil, as his father, Matthew
McConaughey, mentioned is one of the most handsome men in Hollywood, then
his son, Levi, also allegedly was one of the handsome boys in hollywood.
That's a putting allegedly in there, strangely enough, but said is Levi
already beat to brother, namely Viva Alves McConaughey and Alves McConaughey
stone also. Wow. What does that mean? He's kind of destined for, I mean, you know, I
don't know if any of you have ever read interviews with Matthew McConaughey.
He's very scared of his receding hairline. Yeah, and he lies about what he
did. He lies about fixing it. Yeah, he says he only used minoxidil. No, he
didn't. He doesn't even claim he used minoxidil. He claims that he used some like crazy
lotion that like maybe they paid him to say it in the 90s or something and he
doesn't but it's not even like a hair loss thing it's like it's like some
normal skin lotion I think you want to put that on my head and I mean ten years
later look at my hair's better than it ever was
check this now this guy had a fucking full FUE transplant uh-huh right and
then he goes up sorry I'm getting off topic okay the point is this kid could
be basically partnered with the fucking white kid and he could go he's white
he's white he's white sounds good all right yeah this kid could also just not
be famous and be a source for a Matthew to harvest hair when it needs it yeah
that's fine too yeah I think that that's what's gonna end up happening yeah just
basically a hair slit like I like a cow for hair yeah whatever in a human farm
yeah just take it's more like a sheep more like a cow it's like cow for yeah
we'll say I will shave you will shave the sheep's no we're just gonna say you'll
a child's cow.
Think of how you pull hair out of someone's head, like this.
So you suspend him upside down,
and you pull like that, like you're milking a cow.
And that's how you get the hair out.
We'll just say that this kid is going to be a human cow
in a human form.
That's all we're going to say.
And here's number one, the big number one most handsome son in the world.
I want to see what you guys think.
Number one is Dennis Kay.
(laughter)
What the fuck?
That's the villain from Despicable Me.
one of the try guys yeah that's one of the try guys. Oh my God this picture
lately the name Dennis Cain became the talk among internet user especially in
the Asian region. Born on February 6 2007 this child has a mix of blood came from
Australia where his father and his mother who came from Korea. With the face
of her handsome barrister not difficult for Dennis to- What does barrister mean? I've seen that
twice on this list. Let's look it up really quick. Barrister a lawyer entitled
practice.
Not difficult for Dennis to be a model for many children's
products. It is said that although still minor, Dennis was
able to pose like a model professional and has sense of
fashion. This often makes Dennis touted as the world's best
looking son. Are there any comments here? No, I mean,
there better be people aren't going in here like how about my
fucking son? Oh, no, these are just comments on other. Yeah,
there's no comments on this. You guys real quick before we
finish up. When and if you guys have sons, what are you guys naming them? I feel like
Tucker's good. Tucker? Yeah, I'll probably also just do Tucker. Yeah. After TC. I think
I'd probably name my kid Alex. Okay, I'm actually going to name my kid Alex. Okay, I changed
my name to Bravery. Okay, mine's actually going to be Bravery. Bravery Pitts. This is
my son Cole V. Nam Campbell. I can't do any cool, like, crunchy name because of my last
do we already did this my life's really yeah we already did the whole Caleb's
son with the last name oh yeah thing I guess I mean I can't do any cool names
because my last name would I guess your Irish maybe double day double double
day Doran double day Doran double day double day Doran is like double day
Double Day Doran is some author from like the 1920s or something. He's from that?
Okay. Wait let me look this up. Double Day Doran wrote... Go check it out. Nope. Double Day Doran
is a publishing company. Okay. So yeah. My sister has that in her house. Go buy tickets to
our Halloween show. Halloween. Which we already talked about a bunch. Swagpoop.com/shows.
All the details are there. Hey. But also go... Alex and Joe. Alex and Joe. Come here. Come here.
one of you come here or both get over here now quest come on the show we're on
hurry come on hustle all right give us the details of the show on the 8th what
a home planet happy hour yeah October 8th at 8 o'clock at life world of 5 on this
five new videos new videos one featuring each of the people in pot about list uh
huh best friends where where can people find the tickets
- Tickets, Home Planet, link in bio,
homeplanetvideo.com/shows.
- Or if you go, I think--
- Live link.
- Shut up, no, no.
- Fruit cubes.
- I think come to Lifeworld.
- You don't have fruit cubes.
- Come to lifeworld.com and you can get your tickets there.
- Go to our website, homeplanetvideo.com/shows.
- Sure.
- And it's the only one that's there.
- Okay.
- And we're also, you know you can send us emails
on the website, there's a contact section.
- All right, they're running away with the plug.
So if you want--
- What if there was like a,
what if Batman's son like flew in here and--
- Email, we'll send the script.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Bye bye.