I
all right, Caleb, go sing your song. No, no, no, no, no, fuck. I'm not my God.
You're going to knock. I never did this before. No, do not get the get the
Caleb camera. No, get the Caleb camera right now. I'm so scared. I never did
this before. No, okay, so loosen it first.
don't listen to the case. Don't take the cage off, but then just kind of nudge
the
now just you could use your thumb. We've just gradually twist it.
Did you loosen the cage and you twist the key thing? Yes, shut up, please.
I'm really focused.
You're gonna hit one of us.
See
not my heart. My heart is fucking pounding. It's not that big a deal. My
heart is pounding. I wanted you to do it. So you would see it's actually
nobody's ever made me do it and I really appreciate it. It's fun. I thought you
were doing the thumb. I thought you were doing the one thumb. It's like
one thumb challenge. It's like popping the biscuits can. I like that. Yeah,
it's the same thing. I like when that happens. Yeah, so you like this too.
All right, let me... And now... You guys, what time is it right now? It is
12.25 PM and we are drinking. Well, they didn't have champagne, but we needed
a cork popped. Prosecco. Prosecco. You guys, we're not drinking a lot. Let's
you're going to be crazy. Yeah, just a just a few it's a cup. You know this is
a couple of me. I have to go to the dentist immediately after this. Just a
single flu. They're not going to know man in the dentist office, grabbing his
thigh, the dentist,
you better not fuck my teeth. God, that is so funny to have a dentist
appointment like one thirty PM and you walk in your mouth. It smells like
shambler
were you just drinking? Did you just celebrate something? I just had a
Thursday
guys. Cheers to five years and fifty more. Yep to the pot, baby fud.
That's good champagne. Yeah, well, I have a dentist appointment. Why'd I do
that?
Well, why
what
you thought we were shooting champagne?
a per seco a per seco of sparkling wine.
Who the hell shoots champagne man
me apparently that was fucking psycho. I apparently oh my God. Oh, there's a
little left
guys. It's a fifth anniversary of the podcast. Wow, and it's Christmas and
it's yeah, exactly. It's holiday season. We were so go to for planning. What is
the where you guys were? I wasn't here at the time. We're so what you guys were
so go to for planning the anniversary to be on Christmas. Is that Christmas Eve?
Oh, it's Christmas Eve, yeah, December twenty fourth, twenty eighteen yeah, but
the episode comes out today, a day that we may live in infamy. So this is pal
pal. I remember so vividly being like oh, I want after we had been doing it for a
while being like oh, I wonder what the anniversary is. So maybe it matter we've
been doing for a while. I think it was like the second time. It's crazy that we
didn't think of that when we did the first episode. What the fuck it's
twenty fourth. We thought why would we think that people would want to listen
to the first episode? Well, maybe at home, maybe it set us up for success
because you people are at home, they're back with their pet with the rents
right. They're going to be taking long drives. Exactly, it's actually a bar.
Well, here's another thing too that I thought of
now we get to say we started in twenty eighteen instead of twenty nineteen. I
know it's like a week,
eight days away from twenty nine. True basically it was twenty nineteen that it
started, but it did start, but it was
founded twenty eighteen founded twenty eighteen. That gives us kind of an extra
you guys ever do you ever feel you ever see a restaurant or something and you
walk by it and it says established like twenty twenty one or yeah. Why do they
do that? That's a very optimistic. They should know because it's always it's
always a restaurant that's called like sumac and it's like the most fire
about that to a restaurant. That's all that's a super, super optimistic thing
to do, because even assuming that they're doing that being like okay, our
restaurant's going to be around for two hundred years, you know in two thousand,
two hundred and twenty one, there's still going to be the restaurants that
say established like exactly twenty five. They have to be hoping that we're
going to get to the year like thirty thousand yeah to the point, because
that's the only time we have to they have to get far enough away that the
year seventeen hundred and two thousand seem close to yeah. Yeah, though you
you guys know that cozy corner was established in nine yeah, nineteen
thirty years. I had the literature on the hundred years. I have a big
billboard that says that that's the bar is over a fresh pond. The bar we like is
almost a hundred years old. Well, and you know, the bar we like we see people
there all the time. That's true. Imagine how many other trio alternative comedy
trios throughout the last hundred years have frequented this bar and made it
their watering hole. Stooges could have been the Stooges have been Laurel. I mean, could
have been Tom, Jerry and Spike Alvin, Laurel, Hardy and Blarty. The third guy that died
Grace and Frankie and and their friend Abbott Costello and Abbott Junior. Yeah, any of these
could have been drinking at the same Harold, Lloyd and Charlie Chaplin. They all had $10
Miller Highlife at Cozy Corner. That is amazing, man. What are you kicking at? Bit? Sorry,
my foot got tangled and all guys ask me about my beef. What's your be your beef?
Oh, your beef, how was it? Oh, I thought you were doing Jay Leno on letterman
thing, but no
tell us about what's my beef last night,
the night before last he overcooked it. I'm not my Patrick's prediction now did
not if anything I under cooked Cameron's. We're going to show you undercooked
if anything, nope, complete left turn ball curve.
it was perfect. No well, it was perfect. It was obviously perfect, but I wouldn't
know because
as I'm okay, so set it up, I'm going to know I'm already know where this is
going. I'm already no, you don't know where it's going. I'm about to cry
when I went to the all you can eat wagyu place. They cook the wagyu right and
then they take these cubes of bread and they put it in the wagyu fat that's left
over in the pan and they make like croutons okay, and this becomes one of
a banchan, which is a Korean word for a side salad.
Or a chicken place.
Chicken chain.
Banchan chicken.
Remember that place?
I did a copycat. I had a little bit of bright on the edge, stale sourdough bread,
and I cut it up into different sized cubes, and I put it in the Wagyu fat,
and I started cooking it.
And I had already cooked the steak. I was letting it rest one minute before I served it,
and then
I decided to eat one of the croutons right out of the really hot cast iron pan,
and I burned my tongue to the point where I couldn't taste any of the meat when I
ate it. Oh, my God, I thought Phil was going to eat it. Me too, but I did give
Phil a little piece. Okay, and he freaked the fuck out. I'm not. I thought that
dogs couldn't tell the difference between good things and bad things. He ate. I
gave him a little piece of wag of I rendered down the wag you fat. I gave him
a little piece of it, and then he ran into the kitchen and started and knocked
over the trash can and started trying to eat the rest of it out of the
and then I put him in his crate and he was like growling like a like a like a
wolf. He was like wanted to kill me to get one more. That's awesome. I could I
think I ruined his life. Yeah, no, he's never going to be able to eat like
cable again. I did the same shit to Mo Mo can't eat a specific
like can of his food. If anyone needs any
eaten food or cat full grown cat food. I have a bunch of this pink can from
where Ruva because Mo can't eat anymore because I used it for his medicine and
now he hates that. So this is the exact opposite, but this is the kind of a
yin and yang situation.
But the point is I
basically just had to sit there while my wife ate the steak and I had like two
pieces. I didn't want to waste it, but I didn't want to tell her and I was so
hungry. I hadn't eaten anything all day and I was just and she was like you
don't want any of this. It's so good and I was like yeah, I'm not that hungry
damn and how much was that steak was a hundred and thirty. Oh, you you ruined
your steak. No, I you know, it's no it was it was you. I ate some stuff. I had
some
keepers. I can take the direction out of the pan. That's the what the hubris was.
I didn't even consider the fact that things that were so hot that they were
recurring brown. No, you don't blow on food. You don't blow on food because
it's gay. Yeah, exactly. You don't blow on food because that is gay. Especially,
and also probably it was the same oil that I'd just been essentially deep
frying a steak in. Yeah. It was the hottest thing ever, and I put bread in
it, which is just a sponge, so it was completely saturated. Do you reverse
sear it? You don't need to, no. The steak's like this big, you don't need
to reverse sear it. I don't know, I'm just, I know that word.
I was curious. You're just throwing that out there? Yeah. It's like a half
I didn't know I thought it was a bigger one. You cut it into very small pieces
bite size pieces. Okay, so you're doing it. You see them like fifteen seconds
either side and then you put them some put them over some rice. Well, now you
put them over some rice a little bit sushi style. They serve it at sushi
places sometimes and then you put some salt on it and guys. I mean it was
amazing. I'm sure it was, but I wouldn't know it must have been. Yeah, they gave
me a certificate. It had to have been. They gave me a certificate on the wall.
I got to put that right here.
Wait, can we put that in here?
Yeah, sure.
It's sitting on my fridge and my wife asked me to move it, so yeah.
I covered up her family's Christmas car photo with the thing.
And she woke up this morning, she was like, "You got to, we can't have that covering the
whole fridge."
That's awesome.
But yeah, that's about how my yesterday went.
How about you guys?
I have to go to the dentist, so I'm not having a good time.
I have to pay for wisdom tooth removal with no insurance, which is awesome.
But that's not what I'm thinking about.
Today I'm thinking about five years of podcast about list.
Well, it's pretty unbelievable.
You're kind of not even really celebrating anything because you
weren't there.
I was here for four years, but
well, I guess I could just do this now.
I am you guys
as a gift to the fans for five years of podcast about list.
I have unearthed something amazing.
What is that?
We thought they were lost to the sands of time forever.
but you guys, holy crap, you're kidding. I found some snippets from the dark
thirty one, which are the episodes that we took off because they sucked really
bad.
There was just me and you guys as a kind of a like you saying they sucked
really bad. Well, all right, but as a retrospective on to see how far we've
come, let's listen to episode two. I don't want to do this explosion. It was
called Fantasy Explosion. Is that true? It's a really good name. That's can't be
true.
I am just gonna say it avatar pussy probably tastes so good.
Dude!
You can't start the episode like that.
Ha ha ha.
What's up y'all?
Welcome back to Potabout List.
We're here recording in the library at our college.
Yep, our college located at 120 Boyles.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not gonna dox us.
Dude, do you know what I saw today?
I saw the fattest guy riding a skateboard around campus.
He was like, and I'm not even kidding.
He had to be like 200,000,000,000 pounds, but he was taller than me and he had a Mario mustache.
Hahaha, oh yeah, I saw him too.
Honestly, dude, I wish that I was him.
He looked so awesome.
I hope I see that guy again.
I want to make him jiggle like a jello bowl.
He was really good at skateboarding though, especially given his height and weight.
God, it made me so jealous.
You have no idea how jealous I am of that guy.
I want to sniff his stinky shoes after he skates.
I want to turn him into a bubble and make him squirt bubbles.
God, I'm feeling so sexual.
I wish the bubble was my boyfriend.
- I would take the bubble out to dinner
and drink wine with him.
Oh, I love wine.
I love red wine and white wine.
- Yeah, and I wish I had to make the bubble squirt
every day as my job.
Oh, and the bubble looks like Mario.
- Dude, me too.
I wish I could make love to a bubble
and achieve mutual orgasm.
I wish the bubble I am imagining
was the third host of this podcast.
- I hope one day he becomes the third host of the podcast.
I bet he would be the funniest podcast host of all time.
Aight motherfuckers, this honky finna sing.
- I'm in love with your singing.
I'm gonna sing too.
In a few years, I will bring a Mexican on as our producer.
♪ You would not believe your eyes ♪
♪ 10 million fireflies ♪
♪ Lit up the world as I fell asleep ♪
♪ 'Cause they fill the open air ♪
♪ And leave teardrops everywhere ♪
- I remember that.
♪ You'd think me rude ♪
♪ But I would just stand and stare ♪
(laughing)
♪ I'd like to make myself believe ♪
that planet earth turns slowly. It's hard to say that I'd rather stay awake when
I'm asleep, 'cause everything is never as it seems.
How did you find me? That's crazy. I thought we destroyed those. It's weird,
I had them saved on my phone 'cause I was just a listener back then.
so I was just somebody that was listening.
- I was expecting you were a fan.
- Yeah, and you know, I think you would remember--
- You would like to go from fan--
- Fan to host?
- Fan to host, I don't know.
- One of the first people to cross that boundary.
- One of the few times ever, dude.
- Oh yeah, which--
- Fan to fan favorite.
- I heard that's gonna start happening
more in the next year.
- It will, it definitely will.
Maybe it'll happen with this next guest that you had.
- Maybe it'll happen to somebody listening right now.
- Or this next guest, Julio, play the next clip.
- There's more?
- Oh yeah.
- You found more of this?
- Yeah.
- What the hell?
- Podcast about lists.
Remember the old theme?
This old theme banged.
It banged hard.
(screeching)
Greetings everyone, and welcome back to Podcast About List.
I'm Caleb Pitts, alongside my co-host Cameron Fetter.
And guess what?
We've got a special guest today,
none other than the one and only Drake.
Yo, yo, what's good fellas?
I'm happy to be here on Podcast About List.
Big ups, Drake.
We're stoked to have you.
Today's episode is a bit out of the ordinary.
We're chatting about how we wish we were pregnant.
What are your thoughts on that, man?
Yo, I really fuck with the LGBTQ community, but I'm not fucking with the male pregnancy
fantasy stuff. Sorry, but I'm going to leave.
Okay, so that was awkward as fuck.
Yeah, maybe he could come back.
I remember there was like the first big bump that we had.
Oh, yeah.
Was that we were the first podcast to have Drake.
And then Bobby Althoff stole our whole flow.
Yeah, well, and I wasn't on for that long.
She stole our whole flow in a huge way.
Oh, absolutely. In a huge fucking way. The awkwardness.
Dude, I'm awkward as fuck.
Talking about pregnancy.
Talking about motherfucking being pregnant.
Oh, absolutely. Yeah.
And do you guys remember when I was just a guest
before I was the host? I remember that too, man.
Julio, pull up the clip. You have a clip of this?
Oh, yeah. Episode 29.
We are sorry featuring Patrick Doran.
Okay.
Again, that theme song, man.
What's up everybody? Welcome back to Podcast About List. I'm your host Caleb Pitts. And
I'm Cameron Fetter and today we're here with Patrick Doran.
I got an issue.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
you know that what you just said comes across as anti-semitic and it's not cool.
We should steer clear of such topics.
Also, let's avoid talking about skateboarding if it's going to head in a similar direction.
[Skateboarding]
"Okay, we have to end the episode here."
You really have come so far.
I know you really have.
Yeah, I used to be a lot bigger.
I used to be fat.
You did used to be big and fat.
I did.
What do I remember about you?
I remember thinking that you maybe had an IQ of 68 the first couple of times I hung out
with you. And not the kind of person with a low IQ where they are like stupid.
Special needs, yeah.
It was like you almost couldn't talk at all.
Yeah, right. Maybe it was because of my massive weight.
I think your massive weight was weighing your brain down. You had so much upper fat on your
head.
I was mostly fat up top, but my legs were good. My legs were buff.
Your legs are still buff. My legs were one big kind of tail. Everybody was talking about
your calves the other night. That's true. They're big, man. They're huge. Everybody at the Girl
God show was saying that I have gigantic ass calves and legs and quads and stuff. Do you
have a big rod? I don't know. What's your shaft? I don't even know. I don't know. Do
when you shoot... When I shoot loads, it's not good. Is it big or is it not that big?
It's pretty minuscule. I'm trying to get the size. If you were trying to fill a Dayquil
serving cup. I could how many you can have a whole thing. Okay, probably twelve twelve
milliliters twelve milliliters twelve nuts twelve nuts. Well, that thing up
maybe twelve loads. I think that with me it would be how big is it? It's thirty
milliliters. I believe how big is that with your hand that big thirty loads
you're doing one milliliter loads.
That's really not healthy man. What's unhealthy about it? Well, the size size
in the volume. Since when does size have anything to do with health? Healthy at every size, you're
saying? Yeah. Okay, that's fair too. Next you'll be telling me the color of my load also
has to do with the health of my body. What color is your load? Ghoulish yellow. Wallpaper
color. It looks like this? School uniform shirt. Okay. Yep. But I'm glad that you're
on the podcast now, even though you were such a disgusting fatso when we first met you.
like big frog type things. We got well. I remember we got you and we
you were I hate to say it. You were a fixer upper
okay. You were a run down piece of shit auction house and me and camera got in
there and we got in there. I said we'd really like took all the floorboards up
and concept yeah and we want them to break up with his girlfriend and we did
that.
We did that and then we got you skinny
and
that's
the
so
about her.
And then we
and then we got you into cool stuff like rap and we got you got you doing stand
that comedy and we got you up. We got you a house for your computer. Yep, we got
you an office just so you could have your computer here. Well, it's because I
don't, I don't have room in my apartment. Do you? That's what I'm saying. We
helped you out. Would you say that me and Cameron, my current girlfriend,
doesn't want me to have my computer at home? And that's respect. No, it's I
don't want to have my computer at home because it took up too much space in my
room. Because it also, it's nice to have your computer at the office, because
then you can come here every day at nine in the morning and then you play Skater
XL or obsession or whatever for five hours, and then you can go home and she
goes, "Can you do the dishes?" You say, "I just got off work."
Are you fucking kidding me? You know my whole plan. I literally just got off
work.
I know you do that. I know for a fact you do that.
You come in, you look at, you put four clips into Adobe Premiere and then
minimize it and then open obsession. I literally was just working for five
hours straight. You're kidding me. No, I think that well that used to be the case. But then
once I started making the OJ the alien beats, I would come here for you. Yeah, I would be
here for eight hours at a time making music. It's so incredible what this podcast has done
for my life. I'm trying to think of I mean, I think we did this last year, but where would
we be if we weren't doing this man? Can I tell you something guys last night? I was
thinking about how how lazy I am. I'm probably one. I think one of the laziest guys in the
world and I was thinking that if literally I think if I wasn't doing this podcast, I'd
I would probably just die, because I just just if I if left my own devices, yeah,
I just the mouth yeah. I would just be sitting in my. I would literally rather
sit on my couch yeah, then I was I was thinking about this, how this happened
to be multiple times where I've been sitting on the couch. The TV is off. I
want to watch TV. The remote is at the other end of the couch to the Roku, so I
pick up my phone. I download the Roku remote
I try to I try to turn on the TV with my phone. It won't connect, so I just
don't watch wow one in and people
you have a mile long couch. So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a hundred
cushions, but that's literally something that that's an experience
that I've had often enough that it's happened to me probably four or five
times. God, well, I guess I'm not going to watch TV today because I can't sit
I rather sit down.
that is next level. I literally think if I didn't have to come in here and do
this, I would be at worm. Okay, do you do the thing where like you're in the
kitchen and like
maybe your girlfriend is like sitting at the table waiting for you to like like
be finished with dinner and you ask her to get something that is directly next
to you. I don't do that. Oh, I do that all the time. I got that's how I am.
Well, actually, no, because I'm in my head. I'm doing so in my head. I can ask
first I can ask to be brought or handed something maybe once a month and I get
I get so excited. I'm like when I'm sitting on the couch, I'm fine. Can you
bring me my water bottle? Yeah, I'm like I bring my I do that. I barely ever do
that, but when I do I feel so good. I bring my girl everything and then I will
ask her. Can you bring me something? She she says no. Yep, what the hell is that?
That's how it is. Why are men the most abused man are coming in the world? Every
single woman were stepped on and stomped on. That's why we started a podcast like
this because you make double the amount of money that I make and I'm
practically unemployed. You think that you can not be my slave?
I was having a long, dark night of thinking about laziness while I was
trying to fall asleep, and I think the reason that I am not fat. I live next
to a pizza place. Yep, too far at literally. I would rather eat a slice
of bread for lunch than put on crocks.
That's why you're so good at saving money. Yeah, because you don't don't
You don't want to do anything. Yeah, it's too much. That's crazy. I respect that man. I do.
That's my strategy for life. That's how you save so much. That's why I spend so much.
It really is. I think that I'm too energetic. You're too much of a grinder to not spend
hundreds of dollars every single day. I know. It's fucked up. I think if we didn't do this
podcast I would almost certainly be working under my stepdad at Waffle House. Yeah. And
I would be in probably some kind of paradise. I think that I would be. I mean I would definitely
I cannot be living in New York. No, no, no chance. I don't know possible. I
wouldn't be doing I mean yeah, I'd be a waffle house. I'd probably be making
video essays. Yeah, yeah, I probably would have moved into video. I probably
would I was in Manchester, but I don't know what I would be doing. I was making
about a hundred dollars a week at the liquor store. Oh, I'd still be doing
Amazon M Turk. Yes, yeah, doing surveys for money
I probably would have worked. I almost worked like in the mail room at my ex's dad's mortgage
company while we were doing this show. That would have been awesome. And then we broke
up and then that didn't, well I mean obviously that didn't happen. You missed the bag dude.
But that would have been, I would have had so many crazy work stories to come on the
podcast. Well the mail room is also how you start supposedly. Yeah. You kind of, a little
bit you started in the mail room of this show. Did I ever tell you that her dad paid for
You literally did. You used to run our Twitter account. That's true. You
started in the mail room. That is true.
I ever tell you I, I, her dad paid for
me to do like real estate classes. No, did you do one? Yeah, I did like
the whole course. Are you, are you
licensed? No, I failed the test.
Wait, that's over, that's your New Year's resolution. Yeah, we're gonna get
you licensed, bro. In New Hampshire? Me and Caleb, we're gonna train you. We
got you here. That was he wanted me to work for him so much. You're going to
work for us. I'm going to work for me and my personal life right now. I'm
going to reel back a little bit. Why don't we remember that? I just I think
that you would look so amazing on a real estate. Could you imagine like one of
those shitty like airbrush photos and me and just like the shittiest like
haggar suit? Yeah. And I'm like this like dude, I mean, having balding balding,
but I like I'm still like you fill it with the wrong color. The number one
experience of going home for the holidays is is you go home and you see
someone you went to high school with on one of those real estate. So yeah, and
you go
when you're when you are literally just talking a story, a boy did tell us about
how you'd rather
sit on the couch. Yeah, somebody's like doing something with their life and
you're just like
fucking
loser.
he's on a billboard. I had that experience. It was I have that every time
I had that experience, but it was weirder because the kid was running for
like state office. Well, he was running for state office because his only
platform was weed legalization. The last time that I saw somebody in twenty
sixteen, the last time that I saw like what somebody from my high school was
doing was do you remember that it might have just been a video or might have
been a tick tock that went viral where it was in Boston and the guys were
harassing the
the oh the antiserts yeah yeah that those guys went to my there like there's a
guy. You know the guys who walk around with the big blood stain pants and they
have the sign that's like you know don't don't circumcise kids yeah, whatever
you never seen that they were in Boston heavy. I'm sure you did see them, but
they're the video where there it's a bunch of guys making fun of really yo
look at
you need to get laid. Oh yeah, that's all you got to get laid. You knew the
making funners yeah that's awesome. Those guys rule, because I watched the video
like two times. I was like wait is that fucking Antonio? What the fuck
dude that's my dream is to pull up
a gas station shooting video and it's just like a homie to friends that I knew
yeah, that's their old friend yeah. I just I just look at mug shots every
time I go home. I look at all the mug shots every single year. There's
somebody that I know and it's always except for one time where it was
a robbery, it's always some kind of like
perverted, disgusting sex thing. Yeah, same same with my like I did sex with an
animal. I added the blue found out that somebody I went to high school with lost
their leg and is now like on survivor. Well, I was just like damn that's a
that's guys. This guy's going to win as a woman. This guy is going to win. The
guy is going to win. Yeah,
one legged woman.
Yeah, this like girl I went to high school with like lost her leg and is now
like a survivor like superstar. I was just like Jesus fucking Christ. That is
that is the biggest example I've ever heard of karma
balance in the universe. You lose your life. She probably doesn't have such
good balance in this universe anymore. All right, well, that's not very nice.
Yeah, it is not nice, but that's true. I mean that's a fact. She was nice to me
sometimes. It's not nice to say that. You have to really your all sense of
balance. If you lose your toe, what do you think happens if you lose your leg?
You probably fall over if you're falling on the stairs a bunch. It's that simple,
Patrick. Stop making it emotional. It's not emotional at all. There's I think
there's two notable alumni from my high school. It's that girl and then the
other girl who was in some Netflix movie about being a lesbian and then and then
me. Yeah, Mama Brooklyn podcast. Yeah, I don't know if there's been any
since I went there.
the crown princess of Japan went to my high school in like. Whoa really yeah,
that's cool and terrible. My as a home schooler, I had my brother who ran a
paintball field for some time and then my other brother is really good at magic
the gathering. So where do you fall in the middle? You're just like in the I
would say famous in the house. I would say I am you're the most famous in the
house. No, the middle okay, I would say I'm in the middle. Oh yeah, your other
brother's because my pool hall yeah my brother exactly and I think that he's me
and gus were talking about. I think my brother he's starting this pool hall in
new hall california and I think for sure no he's starting a new hall a new hall
and pool hall california and I think for me and gus were talking about how he is
for sure going. We like saw him at this like event where they were doing like
face painting and stuff and he was like out there. My brother has like head
tattoos and looks weird and he was like shaking people's hands and being like
very
gregarious, not gregarious, very
gregarious, charismatic and weird and me and Gus are talking. He's definitely
going to run for city council and change his last name, change his last name to
like Torres. Yeah, he's going to be, he's going to be Josh,
Josh Tiny Torres running for city council.
We should run for city, we should move somewhere that we have a shot. Dude,
Manchester, New Hampshire, because here it's a it's a crap shoot. We could move
to many. I think I lived in I think we did a popcorn ceiling yeah, but the
ceiling, we should we should that would be okay. Oh my God, oh my God, guys, we
should us us and all of our friends move to a small town smaller than Manchester
and completely for what New Hampshire flood the the government. We just all
run for board of select men or whatever the fuck they have. They're completely
kill the entire government of the town with just us and our friends and take
over the town and it's our town. It'll be the we should. Why is that? We don't
want to move to Humboldt, California. Somebody has done this in New Hampshire
specifically
crew there was it was like there's a the free state project is like a thing where
all these libertarians want to move to New Hampshire and turn it into the like
the true live, free or die state and they fucking I think it's grafting. I
don't remember where I think it starts with a G. You'd have to look this up,
but they privatized everything, even trash pickup.
And then there was an infestation of bears in the town
and it's so fucking crazy.
They ruined the whole town by making trash not public.
And then there was just like, oh yeah, there's a bear.
There's a bear in the...
Yeah, I think so.
I bet they had no debt.
But we would not, we wouldn't, we wouldn't...
We would make everything the government's problem.
We would do a good job.
Yeah, we would do the exact opposite.
Right, we would keep everything the same except parties every day.
Block parties, four day work week, Friday's pizza movie night.
Arcade, bigger than Fun Spot.
Yep.
Oh my god, wait, no, we just go to Laconia, we just flood the Laconia city government.
We could do it anywhere, man.
Yeah, but then we make Fun Spot our headquarters.
I don't want to live in New Hampshire.
New Hampshire sucks.
Let's do it in Texas or something.
It does, yeah, it sucks fucking shit.
It sucks ass.
You're the only person of us three who has zero pride with their hometown.
Oh, fuck all that shit.
Yeah.
New Hampshire fucking sucks ass.
it's lame to say your hometown sucks. I know it's late. I go say that it sucks
you're out. You have to you have to stand for it. No, I don't I agree every
time I go home. I'm like oh my God, this is paradise. You guys went with me.
You guys went with me. We did a whole we did like one of our worst episode of
all time. It was at least pretty. I like pretty yeah. There's nothing wrong
with New Hampshire. Good to visit. It's cool. I would live there. You would live
there. I live close to the Massachusetts border, but I live there. Yeah, that's
where I grew up close close enough to the yeah, you live in cigarette county.
Yeah, yeah, why not might as well, but every time I go home and I talk to
people who live in Wilmington, they're always like dude, it sucks here. Fuck
this place. I wish New York is so awesome right and I'm like no bitch, you are
living the dream bro. Fuck all this what I go to
amazing shit every single day and I see all these beautiful rest see the most I
I eat at the greatest restaurants in the world. I have Wagyu beef delivered to
my house. I find you know this it sucks. You want to live in North Carolina,
man. You guys have the beach. Yeah, yeah, you can surf man. Come on.
These people don't know what they have. No, they have the beach here too.
It's and you can get to the beach by train.
The beach here isn't as good. The beaches here suck. Yeah, well, that's
and I'm a complete beach bum. So yeah, I know I need the sea. I do. I need
I need the sea man. I have a mariner soul.
He needs the sea man. He just said it.
You just said that and I'd like you to know that was pause.
That's pause bro.
That was pause in another level.
I need the sea man?
You just said it again.
What is so...
What is so jizzy about what you just said?
Bro is speaking...
You're speaking in tongues.
I love the sea man.
Dude, stop bitch.
I need to be near the sea man.
to live and got on our anniversary go to my trash can in my bathroom and if you
need to be near the seamen so badly not on our anniversary don't say that yeah,
you can't say that our anniversary our podcast and versus our anniversary
our anniversary. We have not really done that much to celebrate it. It's well
reminiscing. We have baby foot here. What are you supposed to do? That's what
it is. It's for reminiscing. Oh, his head just fell off. He's dead. We have
the five. We got a balloon. So I bought a balloon and it's a helium only one.
so you can't fill it with your breath. We're going to make Pat pass out by
blowing it up, but apparently he gave up instantly. I personally open the
champagne bottle. I didn't probably would have been bad to have a big balloon
here. Yeah, why just would have been all sorts of mischief would have. Oh yeah,
you well, we would have had a funny helium segment. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Well, we can we can fake it actually yeah here. Wait
Okay, go ahead and pretend you're breathing in the helium rail.
Hey,
can you turn the go ahead? I'm not turning the
yo what's up? Can you just press the oh sorry yeah, I do it against it.
I sound like the I sound like the chipmunks. Can you hit the
you haven't pressed it once I pressed it, you press it, you haven't pressed it,
I prestige
okay. You didn't press it long enough. It will you didn't have a big enough hit
of helium. You just
have any helium to send yeah. So this is your normal voice.
Your voice is so high.
What's the other gas reverse one?
You're a bore. Yeah, it's some compound of some some long name hex or something.
I thought it was nitrous. Nitrous does that too, but there's one that specifically doesn't.
There's one that doesn't get you high. Yeah, yeah. I think it's some type of thing. What
are you doing, bitch? Stop waving this shit around. Wait, you actually look like the king
of Egypt. Do I look like Elton John right now? A little bit. I mean, you always kind of do.
All right, well, do you guys want to see my slideshow? I would love to see your slideshow.
Of our memories together? Yes. Is that what it is? It's a slideshow of our memories over
for the past five years that I made. So guys, I bought a one-month subscription to CapCut.
I spent hours on this video. I like this already. I guess just take it away, Julio.
I'm not sure. Okay, we'll just watch it.
I'm wearing a shirt that says Young Thug.
Me using an umbrella?
No, a vacuum.
The original cover.
That's in my closet.
I forgot about if you see something inappropriate.
An apropos camera.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Do you have the original one with the Ben Margera photos?
We'll be friends forever
First up to the girl in my math class
I'm rich and you broke, bitch, I had the last laugh
This is a dumb nigga in my science lab
Had it feel when we fought and you called it jackpot
Fuck this shit, it was always talking on the aircraft
This tournament I was always gonna bring in a bomb
And all of the girls, wow, them bitches was too foul
They all on my dick now
Our first trip to New York.
Me in a towel.
First live show.
First live show, second live show.
That was my show at Atlantic City.
That was Robin's show.
That's my older partner.
Oh my god, the riverboat casinos.
Yay!
Merry Christmas!
Aww.
That hat is really cool.
Something happened.
Oh, is that baby Bill?
Gratitude.
Oh, that's Tor.
That's when I died.
Caleb's hair.
This is someone's house.
Oh, wait, what?
[LAUGHTER]
Team Liquid.
Oh, they have set the drawing of the gentlemen brothers.
That's me on strength.
Oh, that's rehearsing my outfits.
That's my slideshow guys. That's my photo. Four hours. That was a photo. Was I
holding dress like Dracula? You're holding some ladies boobs. There's some
ladies big booze. Instagram that you had found. I guess I don't know. You were in
character. Wasn't my camera. I guess I was in character. Can you cut back to
that photo? I just want to see. Why do you want to see his bitches boobs again?
No reason why it's just kind of
one.
We had so many memories together that we had an incredible journey, man. What's
our lowest possible point we've ever been in? Got to be chicken brain. Chicken
brain is definitely I wish we kept that. I might have it. I have it. I have it.
might be the 10 year anniversary we released the chicken brain episode.
I have everything. Everything that we've ever recorded and not released I have it.
Yeah. For those who don't remember, we one time everybody came to my house and
I think it was your first time having KFC? Yes, it was his first time. Oh yeah. We got
a big bucket and we were gonna eat it on the episode and talk about it with him.
And we ate one piece each and then recorded probably the worst 28 minutes
of podcasting ever recorded. We used to not even do an hour. There were some, there
there were some we did thirty minute episode, whatever the opposite of
whatever the opposite of a banger is there were some real that that
apartment yeah yeah that was in that room specifically there was a lot of
lot of pain on your bed yeah. That's the thing for me. I was just too
comfortable. I was in my bit. You should never do that's why work from home is
such a bad idea. Yeah, you should never be in the most comfortable place in
your entire life. The only place where you can fall asleep yeah where and
doing work. Especially not podcasting, which is the most mentally taxing work ever created.
Your roommate had a bug trap that smelled so bad.
I don't even remember that.
I remember we would go there and then we would shut your door. We would shut your door, but
then we would go hang out in the living room, which was barely, it was like the tiniest
living room in the world.
It was so funny.
It wasn't a living room.
It was a hallway.
We had a hallway that had an indention, or a cut out area.
You put a bed or a couch there.
not even a couch. We got a free my way. There was this promotion for this like
sectional couch that was modular, where every single cushion was like one
section of the couch, and the whole thing was like come get one for free,
and then you can buy the rest of them. Yeah, and my wife just picked up one
that was free, one tiny section of a couch, and then we put an ottoman next
to it, and then that was our couch. I remember that, and then we put pillows
behind it. And I played a lot of Grand Theft Auto in that ottoman couch.
Yeah, but we would sit there and it would be so hot in that room. Yeah,
there'd be... It would just smell like apple cider vinegar. Seven people right
there. Yeah. Yeah. In a pension size. Oh, yes, it was apple cider vinegar.
Yeah, we had... When you say bug trap, I didn't know what you meant. The
homemade fruit fly trap. Yeah, fruit fly. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that entire apartment
smelled like vinegar all the time. I would stay there till like two in the
morning, have to call an Uber home to Revere, where I was living,
and I would drink 17 beers there.
Yeah, I would. I wasn't even a like I was just the first time you guys hung out
with me outside of like school. I went to your house. I drank 17 beers that I
brought from a 30 rack. You brought a 30 rack of PBR like it was a briefcase.
I drank all of them out of it like Patrick Star. It was insane of me. It was
completely insane of me and I would just sit there in the kitchen just talking
like, "Yeah, there well, I'm sort of having some fun there." No, it was better
and that you that's why I liked you is that you drank seventeen beers and you
did not seem like you had even had one
interesting. I was in my brain. I was so drunk that I was speaking like like
no, you were not doing blah. I was talking like a senator
after seventeen beers like you were and what we need to do.
That's how you were man. It was it was amazing. It was one of those brilliant
things I've ever seen. It was performance in a way. Well, the only thing I think I
I don't slur my speech. I think if I'm drunk, I just get louder.
That is true. The other night when we were at Noah's surprise party, my
girlfriend was telling me to be quiet because Noah was turning the corner and
she said to me, Sam picked up on this, she said to me, she was about to say,
she was gonna say, "Your voice is too loud. You need to stop. You need to
speak in a whisper." She didn't say loud. She said, "You need to be quieter.
Your voice is too strong."
that is a keeper man. I was like, oh strong. That is strong. That is litter.
If a woman talks to you like that, dude, that's rare. That is rare. I could not
believe. I was like, yes, I have a very strong voice.
You're being loud and you look fat. It has nothing to do with me being loud,
but she was said it anyway.
So
that's good news.
Let's see other memories that we have of our beautiful. Well, we were supposed
go in the infancy of the show, we were supposed to drop acid and go. I think
we've talked about it, but go see Mr. Wonderful at the Chevalier Theatre.
I found that. Apparently, I didn't remember that. I guess I got a letter
about it. Yeah, because we had to register online. We were gonna put on big,
like, David Byrne-style suits and sit in a hot room. I have a feeling he wasn't even there, man. No. No way. He was definitely there.
He was there? He was there. Why is he wasting his time? He's from Kevin O'Leary Live, man. He's a billionaire.
Well, yeah, but that's how he makes his money is doing shitty tours. But I think it was free. I think it was the only reason we were gonna do it.
Oh yeah, that's right. It was free. We were supposed to take a...
He's looking, scouting the next generation of money makers.
We were going to sit there, scared as shit.
Yeah, I don't do well on drugs.
No, you left. You said that you weren't going to go and then me and Cameron were about to
do it and then we were like, yeah, we shouldn't do that. That's a bad idea.
You didn't have your brave leader there.
That's a very bad idea.
I mean our cowardly leader who dropped out first.
Well, because I got scared of doing drugs, man, which is a perfectly Christian thing to do.
That's a good reason to not go to see Mr. Wonderful. I'm scared of drugs. I'm
scared of Mr. Wonderful. He killed people with his boat. Yeah, I thought his
wife did that. That's what we were going to go there and say. We're going to
ask him about the boat a bunch. Had he already done that at that point? Or
had his wife? Or no, no, no, no. We, I think we, if I'm remembering correctly,
early on in the show, we issued a fatwa against him and then he killed someone
with a boat. Because he got so scared. He thought it was one of our sleeper
their agents. Yes, that's what happened. That's how I remember it. Do you
remember our first big guest? Of course, dude. How could you forget? Jake the
legend.
He's in the vid, man. He's in the vid and we redded him out, and not out of
disrespect. No. We redded out of pure respect. That just happened in the
camera 'cause he was emanating pure energy. Pure, beautiful light out of his
amazing body. Our first number one big guest, when we called him from the
library or whatever at our school and he was delivering Uber Eats the whole time.
Who was our second guest that wasn't just a college friend, I'm trying to think?
Oh, God, that's a good question.
Well, Tom. But that doesn't really... He's a college friend, technically.
Who wasn't a friend? Someone we didn't know.
Someone we didn't know is probably Felix.
I mean, someone we didn't know in person.
Oh, Thomas. Yeah, Thomas was our first over-the-phone guest.
And that's when you ate a bite out of an onion.
was so drunk that night because he got the timing wrong or something and I
would party
I think no he or we blaming him for how drunk you got. No, we got the time
around thousand miles away. We got the time wrong and we were waiting for him
and while we were waiting, I had nothing I was I had nothing to do. So I drank
like six beers. Yeah, it sounds like Thomas's fault. Yeah, there's no it's
completely my fault, but we were no because we were up at like 10 PM and
and he had to, he was still living at home,
and he had to record at like two in the morning.
And if you listen to that episode, he's like--
- So he lives in the ocean.
- Yeah, man, I gotta be real quiet
'cause my dad's asleep in the other room.
- He lives one time zone into the Atlantic Ocean.
It was 10 p.m.
- No, he was recording at two in the morning,
if I remember correctly, I don't know.
- Then it would have been midnight.
- I had one million beers and said my real
social security number.
- Did we bleep it?
- We bleeped it, but I said my real social--
- I used to think that was so funny to do back in the day.
Oh, my God, it was so funny. I was a class now, dude. I try to get I tried
to get car insurance. I don't like telling it to people if they need it. I
tried to yeah. I tried to get car insurance the other day, though, and I
put in the the VIN for my car and was like who would you like to
get insured and it was like Jorge Ramirez and it had like a list of fifteen
names that were not my name. Oh, no, oh yeah, I've made some really bad
mistakes in my life. Yeah,
well,
it was all for this show. A guy stole my identity when I was a kid, yeah, and got
like some kind of foot surgery and said that he was, he was, yeah, I've never
told you about this. I went to go get my, 'cause I didn't get,
I didn't get vaccinated that much when I was a kid. It didn't happen that often,
but then I went to go to college and I had to get vaccines for college,
though I wasn't immunized with the normal stuff that a lot of people were,
and because I was home schooled, so there wasn't like a requirement and I went to
go get my vaccines and they were like,
how was your foot surgery and I was like what and the lady's like looking at my
paper. She's like you got foot surgery five years ago. I know I didn't and she
turns out it was a grown man that stole my little boy identity. I got yeah, as
insane good for him. I got surgery under my name. He got foot surgery. Yeah, and
they just they sent the bill to the wrong. I mean, I think he had the bill
sent to his place. So we didn't even ever get the bill damn yeah, that's crazy. I
don't even know what ever happened with that yeah. My doctor keeps trying to
schedule
strange tests on me that you won't explain. Oh yeah, you're still having
this beef with your doctor of a huge box. It was it was it was the beef. I mean I
still hate my doctor, but there was no conflict between us until yesterday. I
get so that last time I was there, I get home and I are like weeks later after I
get done with my checkup or whatever it was. She I get an email. It's like your
appointment is tomorrow for the like cardio stress test, like the like test
we have to run on a treadmill. It does not sound very pleasant. No, I'm like I
don't I'm not fucking doing this. They never said I needed it. They're going to
charge me like a thousand dollars for it. Why would I do this? Why do I need
this? And I sent them a message. I was like I did nobody told me about this.
Why am I? I'm not going to pay for this. Why are you scheduling me for this? They
just cancelled it and didn't reply. No explanation or anything, and then
yesterday, I got a letter in the mail that said your appointments coming up
soon and they just had re re scheduled it. So I have to you know what they're
doing. Why are you trying to what's wrong with my heart? They're testing you
for dementia and you're failing dude. It's making me so mad because it's also
getting in my head like what if there's something what if there's something
wrong with my heart that they saw they're just not communicating it and
that's why they're trying so hard to schedule a heart test. Oh boy, that I
think that's crazy. They're not they're not saying anything. I feel bad and be
like why are you doing this? What's wrong with me? I feel bad for these
doctors, first of all, because they have to work with nurses, but then second of
all, because they have so many...
Think about how hard it is to remember, you know what, a hundred people,
everybody knows a hundred people. Well, that's why they got the clipboard.
Yeah, but still, like, you have to go and read all this shit. Every doctor
should just have one... That's why they have to write their computer notes.
They should just have one patient. Every doctor should have one patient, and
they should be... That's how it used to be. And they should live in their
house. Yeah. And they should take care of this person, and they should be in
charge of making them dinner as well. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What? I have to call the electrician again. That's in another amazing podcast moment.
Yeah. Remember when you had all this electrician trouble? Remember when we had to scrap a whole
episode because I was so stressed out about this guy being in my apartment? I do remember
that. That's why I've been very hesitant to let you talk about him. I don't want to talk
about him anymore. Because time is money, man. Time is money in a major way. But also I have
to send a video to my landlord because the dance challenge that thing faucet shower.
What's the word the knob in the shower is leaking? It's okay. Water. My sinks been my sink. My
brother who is an HVAC dropping probably thousands of gallons a day. He's an HVAC technician.
He's a plumber. He does plumbing stuff. I don't fucking know what he does. HVAC is heating
and cooling. I sent it to my plumber brother and he said, "You need to send that to your
landlord right now because that could be symptomatic of a bigger problem." And I said, "Shit."
Not a bigger problem. A bigger problem. A bigger problem never matters unless you own
the house. Yeah, but I don't want mold to grow in my bathroom again. I want mold to
grow in your bathroom again. No. Also, remember how broken my toilet was all the time and
me and my old roommate would fight all the time because you'd have to wait for it to
like refill. No, you're not a flusher. We know this. Yeah, I know, but I could have
fixed that. I could have fixed that whole thing. I could have fixed the whole thing
on my own. I showed, I FaceTimed my brother because I had the same problem in my new apartment,
FaceTimed him and he said, "Oh yeah, that's a $3 part you can get at any hardware store.
It's draining as it fills." I should have just been a plumber with him. That's probably
what I would be doing and probably just be a plumber with him. Mario vice. I
would be a plumber. Oh, my God is actually go to again back to being
Mario. Back to being Mario. I should have. You know what had I should have
fucking war today? The P hat. God damn it. I've never worn it on the show. I
should have done it as a gift. Maybe not a video episode. No, I should have
done it as a I'm surprised you still have that hat. The brown hat with the
with the white P on it. That Mario brother named Poop. That hat is really
good. Also, no, it's not. It makes you look like you're a poop Mario. Well,
doesn't matter. I like it. It's fine if you like it, but it is a cosplay of an
amazing. Did I tell you about the time two weeks ago when? Yeah, I think I said
this on, I mean, all the episodes we've were we're all backlog and they're all
blending together. I was wearing that hat and a group of yes, I saw a black
squirrel, a group of teenagers pointed at me and said that dude looked like
Mario. Yeah, you do look like Mario. Yeah. You know who thinks I look like Mario?
of my nephews. I'm sure they do that. They love that movie. Yeah, the movie was okay.
I didn't like how they treated Donkey Kong in the movie. I did not like how
they voiced Mario. Donkey Kong, that guy, Charles Martinet. Who's that? The guy who
goes
the voice actor for Mario should have voiced Mario. Yeah, no, the guy who goes
Mario. That's my opinion. It's a me Mario.
Okay,
Man fuck Chris Pratt because he's Christian. Yep,
but I love Christmas. We actually that's it. We can reveal this now that
we're five years and we have you already hook line and sinkered. We're
gonna do we're doing an I C P. We are a reverse. We
hate Christianity. We are three atheistic,
whenever we've talked about whenever we've mentioned God, we've been talking
about the devil. Whenever we mentioned Jesus, we've been talking about Damien
from the omen and devil. So whenever we talk about having whenever we say that
we have halos and angel wings, we actually have double horns and tails,
all these things all along. We tricked you reversed you. We've been worshipping
idols. Oh, what do you think this is for example? This is a this is a fud baby.
Yeah, and if you look back into ancient Egyptian tablets, there will be a
yeah, there's a an outlet on a
the spiller, the spiller has has shifted body. My God, the spiller has moved
the spiller. The spiller has officially moved. I'm free. Oh my God, oh and he
spilled on my phone. That's perfect.
I
well, I'm going to clean this up right now. Yeah, I mean why
it's not that much it's a lot. Okay, your spiller tendencies are coming back.
I don't think it's fully left your body. Well, I'm more of a podcaster than a
spiller at the end of the day at the end of the show must go on. There's no
cracked my phone the other day. I'm sorry man. It really is devastating.
It's really is. What do you guys think we can expect for the for year six
year six?
I think that one of us will have nude photos leak. Okay, and I'm really hoping
it's one of you, but I haven't taken a photo. I haven't taken a nude photo
since I was four years old. Really you took one or someone took one. I took one
with what I posted on Facebook at four yeah, bitch as illegal. I made a special
account
called
a novelty account.
I made a mean page called naked, naked, naked Cameron pics that had me had my
sides in orbit.
I know when the last time I took a nude pick of myself was man mean either. I
don't like I take nude pics every day in the gym with my brain yeah. When I try
I X ray my own body in the mirror. Well, yeah, sure. I look at my nude body,
but when it comes to pics, not for a long time. I'm not crazy. Seven,
eight minutes. Someone's here with beers. Who is that? Oh, I think we should.
Hello. Hello.
Hi.
Good. How are you?
Yeah.
Oh, thank you. Appreciate you.
What the fuck just happened?
What the fuck was that?
Who is that?
What?
Wait, bring that over here. What the hell was that?
Who the hell is that guy?
What the fuck?
What the fuck was that man?
Bring the whole thing.
Is he still here? Spiller!
Is he still here?
What the hell?
I think he meant to go next door.
I store. I think that he thinks we're boot boys,
whatever
okay, some guy for people who are not in the room right now. Some guy just
walked into the office, opened the door and was like sup guys, you're filming
right now. Well, I got some year but my day for you and then just put he got
in a car and left he got in a car and left. I'll have one.
I'm not drinking this too much caffeine for me right now. I think I should
probably give this neck to the people next door. I'm taking one bitch. I love
your BAMAT. That was crazy. So why did he just walk in? He didn't knock. He
just didn't say anything walks in and it's a twist off.
Oh, that's cringe of me. Yeah, all right, well, let's see how it is. I've
actually had this. You were not a good. It's a good. This is like a good
yerba mate.
he must have he must have thought that
for the people next door. I don't give a fuck. They ain't getting this shit. I'm
liking this taste. No, no, we got to give them. Well, now we can't. Now that one's
missing, we can't. He knew, okay, you know what it was? He knew it's a fifth
anniversary. He must have. And he wanted to give us a birthday present. He knew
that we were recording the fifth anniversary episode today, weeks before
the fifth anniversary. He knew he could smell it. Why didn't we ask him who he
was I know I was giving you because I kind of it kind of felt like I he was so
familiar with he did coming in here. I knew he was supposed to be yeah. I felt
like he was
he had been here before any of us right.
What the fuck just happened? Yeah, it was really the way that he acted that
made me not ask. He was so non. She was not very confident. He wasn't shy about
walking in here. I walked straight in, walked in, you guys film something
that's cool. Here's all right, six by
all right. Well, no way there's no way that this isn't supposed to be for the
guys next door. Well, we'll give it okay. Here's what we do. I keep two and we
give them four because there's four in a whole no no. I already opened this one.
You want me to hand it to him? You're in trouble. You're in trouble for that.
We're going to tell there are friends. They don't care. I'll give them five
bucks. That's overpaying for this, but white label yerba mate. If you just
sent, if you just sent an agent,
sending us, you just sent a promotional man dude. We're finally it's the CIA,
sit down. We should have asked him to come sit down and talk to us. We could have
learned about him. I didn't want to talk to that guy. He was weird. He wasn't
weird. He was, he was a little weird, man. He was a little weird, just a little
bit. I hope that he wasn't a crazy fan who learned our address.
Listen, if they come bearing gifts, yeah, if you come bearing gifts, I got a
hard time saying no, man. Food. I like food, man. Pizza. Pizza. Pizza is amazing.
pizza is amazing. I do love pizza. Well, that was
very strange. I mean, I guess this is also supposed to be the Christmas episode.
Yeah. Oh, my God, he was Santa. That's a wise man. That was Santa. That was a
white guy was the opposite of here and record another hour because yeah, that's
one of the wise men. There's gonna be two more that come.
There's gonna be two more men that come here and give us gifts for the
so we got here and wait, wait the mad guys gifts in in twenty twenty three is
yerba mate. Oh God, wait,
so we got woke, Magi and pre rolled joint pre rolled fucking Delta eight
joint. Yeah, what that means is that we got to start locking the fucking the one
day. This was the one day we didn't lock it. We immediately got and you know
what gifts have we missed out on?
six guys. The reason it's not locked is because I went out to get that
Prosecco for us and I didn't lock it. When I come back, I come back in is
literally all cascades from and if I we had wouldn't have got this, if we if I
wouldn't have gone to get this, if we hadn't lasted five years, yeah, this is
literally for the five years. So if you there's a decision that you that we made
five years ago that led to me drinking, we wouldn't be in here right now. If
Patrick didn't have to go to the dentist, we would have been here later. Oh yeah,
this guy would have missed us. He would have come seen this down and he would
have given it to some other. He would have walked into someone's apartment and
given it to that or he probably apparently that's what he does. He was
so hell bent on giving us this Montez guys. When you it's a butterfly effect
type vibe to the note in here, he was the note he was that I wish we had
interviewed him. I think that maybe he was grub hub.
No, he was not. I think that maybe he was grub of anything. He was getter. I
mean yeah, he the way he behaved a door dash or a grub hub or someone says hey,
next door dash. Hey, you guys order this. Hey, you guys filming something cool. I
brought this. I
if it is door dash and we drank the guys next doors, it's fine man. We'll give
them your
it's okay. I guess one bottle you think they're going to kill me. They're not
going to kill you, but we have to say explain it. We pay for the trash pick up
yeah, that's true. So I'll say we do yeah, because they don't have oh and this
is our gift for they have like they have like we got you this walk over
surprise.
We got you five
guys.
No, it's fun to say. Oh, he drank one, then he realized it's probably for you,
and now that I said that
erase that so we don't they don't hear us manipulate. I knew it the entire time
boot boys. I do not care. I'll drink anything that is delivered to me. It's
really it's none. It's not a good pick a better delivery driver who doesn't
weird. It's on you guys. You picked a fucking idiot. It just walks in and
or it could be a good friend of yours, which if that's the case, then I'm
sorry, you guys filming right now cool, not even what are you like cool? You
guys,
so just the weirdest possible thing to walk into to yeah, it was completely he
was
covered in toys.
He was doing yeah again, it's like he's been here before right. Well, he was
probably here at the old one. This used to be the half. You think you they have
him on retainer. He's a regular. Yes, the regular, I think he's the man. Well, it
be. What I know is that I'm too filled with shame to walk this over to the other aisle,
so it's going to be Patrick.
I'll do it.
Here, will you hold Fudd for a second?
Yeah.
So, guys, it's Fudd's fifth birthday.
That is true.
So I got him a gift.
You're kidding.
Aww.
So, little Fudd, you're five years old now, and I think we all know what that means. You're
finally ready for your first one of these. I know you've been begging for one for a long
time.
man five years old. I remember when I got mine. Oh my God, a Glock. Yeah,
19 man. Yeah. So now he could do anything he wants. You're going to run
the world one day. Future president
Joe is shooting it everywhere. Put the gun down. You crazy bastard. Where a
where were you when we just got reverse robbed with your Vermont?
that is one of the craziest things that's happened. That's why that's why
I carry it. Today is such a magical episode. Don't try to give me. It really
is.
Oh, this thing is totally broke. We gotta get a new one.
Yeah. Oh, that's where you put the CO two.
No, it's a real gun. Oh, you know, it's a yeah.
Okay. I guess that's the end of the episode. Pointing at the camera. Guys,
yerba mate and champagne. Pointing all the way at the camera. And
I feel like a myth buster because this is making me feel the most insane of
ever felt in my life. All right. Thank you. Happy five years, everybody.
Cheers to 500 more and we're going to destroy the camera right now.
Happy birthday to you.
The other day, my neighbor rang the doorbell. She's like, I forgot my keys.
That's not similar to this at all.
Get out of my house you crazy bitch.
Bye.
You crazy psyche.
I was walking with my girlfriend somewhere and I cut through that big
that park where we
shot the Underworld's Biggest
Mummy thing. We were taking a short cut
through there and this group of
teenagers pointed at me and said
"Yo, don't he look like
Mario?"
Way. You got cooked man.
The worst part was
I was wearing the poop hat.
You were wearing the pee hat.
I was wearing the pee.
And you guys, if that happens to you, your girlfriend is not going to look at you the same that day.
No, no.
You have to, I honestly, I should have just broke off and went into just like a bodega and just hid there.
I think a lot of these teenagers are very well aware of the fact that they can ruin any relationship.
if there's three or more of them, they can ruin every relationship.
It's like fucking
Nocturnal Animals, that movie with Jake Gyllenhaal.
It's like that. Zootopia? Zootopia. Are you talking about Zootopia? No,
bitch. Is this a documentary? It's a movie that I saw probably 10 years
ago that is about Jake Gyllenhaal being such a loser that his wife and
daughter get murdered.
But it's the same kind of scenario, basically. Right, he's getting roasted.
yeah where he's like just going along with stuff. The bartender roasted me last night.
You're kidding. What happened? You were there. He called me mustache. Oh dude this guy was
on one. He was on one. I turned and handed him a drink ticket and I was like hey does
this cover a June Shine? Ok and before you say gay. Oh the bartender at the bell house.
Oh that guy likes me. I think he likes everybody. He must like like me in camera because he
was bullying us. Yeah. Can he give you a shot? Well I said can I have a June Shine? Can this
get a
Leatherneck.