At the beginning of time, aliens came to the Earth to create the ultimate organic weapon.
They created mankind.
Eons later, the year is 2022.
The festering scourge of humanity still reigns supreme.
The Robotronic DNA implanted in their genome lies dormant, awaiting activation.
and their true purpose is forgotten.
Until...
Light years away,
the High Lord Glaxon of planet Robotron
declares war on the galaxy,
activating the sleeper cell of human-Robotronic hybrids.
But then he choked on Bobo's stew and died.
He was succeeded by his only son,
Fedman Fedex of the Glogan Army.
And now, Commander Fedman approaches Earth with a fleet of Dirk Sand Destroyers TM to
claim his birthright and to unleash a galactic onslaught of universal proportions upon our
pale blue dot.
On Earth, the very ground tears asunder.
The seas boil and run red with the blood of the unfortunate.
They have discontinued Doritos.
Refuge from the assault is only possible for those who are rich and awesome enough to afford underground bunkers.
Armed with nothing but a podcast studio, an archive of all human information, and an artificial intelligence protocol known only as "Jubio-3",
Cameron, Caleb, and Patrick have nothing better to do than to film themselves having fun.
Okay, peace out.
(upbeat music)
- Hey.
- Welcome to the first episode of the rest of our lives.
- That's right, the rest of everybody's lives.
- The rest of every single living person on Earth's lives.
- It all changed.
- If you don't already know.
- Go ahead, explain what happens.
- Well, Alexa--
- You're doing a great job, dude.
- The world is fucking over, obviously.
And we've been driven into this bunker, thank God.
- Thank God we already prepared for this.
- I know, thank God we spent so many months
funneling all the Patreon money into building a bunker,
and that's why the show has sucked for so long.
directly into the bunker. There's no fresh air down here.
No. Mostly fart air down here.
Yeah. I've been working on this thing on the weekends. Some of it's pretty fun, actually.
Oh, yeah. Check this out. Look at this. This is pretty cool.
Plasma ball.
Touch it, Cam.
Okay. Wow. What do those buttons do?
Don't touch the buttons.
What about the key? Can I turn the key?
Please don't touch the key, don't touch the buttons.
Let's just have a-
What's wrong with the key?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, shh, shh, let's touch the plasma ball.
Oh, isn't that fun?
I can't touch it from my spot.
That's okay.
I really-
He's touching the button.
Don't touch the key, please.
I want to touch the key.
Please do not touch the key.
What's wrong with the key?
The key is not- the key flushes the toilet.
And we only have a little bit of water, so don't touch the key, please.
Is that true?
Yes.
You have to come all the way out here to flush-
There's a toilet right- you can't see it.
There's a toilet right off screen.
Well, I'm sitting on it, that's why you can't see it.
Oh, there it is.
I really need to flush the toilet.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
If you flush the toilet, I have it set so that it flushes about 50 gallons of water, and I think we have 55.
We'll just recycle the water.
That's a good point.
We could recycle it through Caleb's system, because isn't pee sterile?
So he could drink the dirty water, he pees, and then it's sterile.
So maybe I'll just flush this poop water, and we can pour 50 gallons of poop water into you,
and you could maybe be a human converter.
You wanna make me eat 50 gallons of poop?
Not eat, no, no, no, drink 50 gallons of poop water.
Obviously we have a filter.
We have a filter that will stop the poop from coming out.
You're the first PP.
And then we turn the poop into food.
I don't wanna be the food pooper.
Well, a lot of people don't wanna be a lot of things, but the world is fucking ending and we don't have a lot of options.
Did you build a fucking poop and pee converter? I don't think so, so you're gonna have to be one.
Right now most people are either robotronic weapons or their food.
Yeah, I also should mention that me and Patrick got a huge fight over an egg.
I don't know, that's why our clothes look like this.
I'm completely covered in...
See, the thing about going out...
I think this is all his blood.
This is all my blood.
It wasn't because of a punch to my face, it was because of a nosebleed.
And I told you that because the fucking new air that we have to breathe...
It's dry.
Hell for my sinuses.
So I mean it's funny the apocalypse affects people in different ways.
I mean you guys, you kind of lost your minds.
I know because a lot of shit is going on.
It's, it's, everyone's turning crazy.
You guys got in a fight.
I got it, I shaved my whole head.
Me, I, I, I, you know, my whole family was eliminated by the Robotronics
and I actually came into a lot of money.
Boohoo!
So, no, I'm actually really happy.
I don't know why you're saying boohoo because you already know that about me
and I was saying a thing so it's like.
I was wondering why you look so damn good.
Yeah, well it's just like you know I'm kind of a billionaire now and and figure I should act apart
You know in money doesn't mean anything anymore. It doesn't matter if you're not mean something to me trust me
Well, would you are you anything? I got these clothes with money. I went down to the store recently. I bought them
Yeah, like yesterday
Why are we in the fucking bunker then?
Well, I mean if you guys don't have money to go spend so I figure you probably don't need to be leaving or going
Eating pine cones and shit we fought we sent it. I thought you guys like pine cone
I got more of the pine cone you got more of the pine cone you guys don't like pine cones
It's fucking it's spiky and brown no. It's it doesn't taste good so the durian pine cone
That's the most we had enough if we had enough water which by the way you're gonna have to again
Yeah, you're a billion
Why are we why do we have a button to flush the toilet if you got a billion dollars?
It's state-of-the-art that cost a lot of fucking money
I will say this did cost so much money doing all this.
Oh, you know what?
We did also wipe a lot of our money out because we uploaded Jubio.
Jubio died.
Yeah.
And we uploaded him into a, he's like an AI kind of thing now.
Jubio 3.
Yeah.
Yeah, because there was a lot of attempts.
Well, a lot.
There's a lot.
There's two.
Don't, bad.
Bad.
Okay, he's going to behave.
He'll be okay now.
Okay, he's going to be nice.
So, I'm going to go ahead and get the key.
I'm going to go ahead and get the key.
So I mean besides all that what else been going on with you guys the other day I went I went up
You went up. Yeah. Yeah, I went up to the surface and
Guess who I saw who celebrity?
No
the corpse of my mom oh
Your mom yeah
The corpse my mom's dead body her dead, but she was just up there
It was a it was a it was one of Edmund's soldiers taunting me
With like it's my mom on a dead body on a fishing rod
Fishing rod like a mary that's like a marionette yeah, yeah, yeah, and he was trying to say like
I I almost fell for it, and then I was like wait my mom's that green
Because you've been decomposing right yeah, Frankenstein mode. Yeah, yeah, I mean
My mental health is in the tubes. Yeah, the
These tubes I I think there's tubes behind me. I I mean stuff is definitely shitty
But oh, yeah, I mean the the the delis the bodegas are still open. Yeah, I'm gonna pinecone
So it's a lot of stuff. I know yeah, I mean, it's all pinecones now. Yeah real. Yeah, all meat has been wiped out
well except
You I mean you guys know I mean you guys have gone to the back rooms in the bodegas. You know I mean I
Haven't tried it, but you guys
Yeah, well they are snake people now. Yeah, you guys I mean come on what?
chopped human
Chopped human I haven't tried it. I haven't tried it, but how much have yeah?
How much have you been going out? How many times have you gone outside in the past week like once an hour?
Once an hour just a little bit. We've been out
Two times I've been out two times and one time I see my dead mom the other time
He and I get into a fight over a pine cone and a tentacle goes up my ass. Yeah, well, okay
I think I know you guys is issue. He had to pull me you he had to pull me
There was a tentacle and it came out of all air and it went there
I'm not standing up because it'll it'll look weird on camera
There is a hole in the back of my this yeah thing it ripped right through well
I think I know why why you guys are having these problems
I mean when you go outside are you wearing your three million dollar cloaking device?
What where would I get where no I don't have three million dollars let alone spending it on a cloaking device
I probably spend even buy one for us put Dolby digital
Ever asked you'll buy us one. Yeah, you didn't think to maybe to maybe like share
I thought you guys liked having fun out there. It's we've got twice. He's getting fucked in the ass with a tentacle
He likes that. He does that normally. He did that before this apocalypse.
By the way, I spent my last pinecones on just another pinecone.
Yeah, pinecones are money too.
It's all just fucking pinecones.
I didn't even know that because to me right now money is money and food is food.
Where are you getting food from?
And who are you buying stuff from?
Instacart.
That's still around?
Yeah.
It's even better now.
No lines.
Who's delivering the food, man?
Like everyone died!
Slaves?
Slaves!
See?
I'll do a lot of things.
I'll eat human meat.
I'll pretend that it was a tentacle that went up his ass instead of accidentally my tongue.
But the last thing I'll fucking do is get groceries from a slave.
Because I'll say this much, slaves are dirty and I don't want to eat those groceries.
Right.
Yeah, most of, I mean...
Let's not say that.
What?
Let's not say what?
covered in debris and ash from burning cities.
I don't know if any one person here just got a new job.
Who? You? A job?
Well, it's less of a job, it's more of a servitude.
Wait, Instacart or Gitter?
Gitter. It's Gitter.
Do you have to wear the outfit and stuff?
I have to wear the outfit and I have to ride the bike.
Oh my god, I see those guys.
The bike that's made out of human bones.
Yeah, it's human bones. It's like a HR Giger thing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really gross what they've done to the world.
Yeah.
You know what, one--
If we can, Jubio, can you pull up a photo
of what they've done to the world?
Can we see just a photo of what it looks like outside?
Yeah, he'll work on that.
Yeah, but in the meantime, one thing that I do,
we're talking about apps, like Instacart and Getter.
I do, since the Robotronics get here,
that app that they developed, Laser.
Have you guys seen this app, L-A-S-R?
I have not seen Laser.
And you can press a button and it eliminates
a random person in the world.
This is-- Wait, just one button?
Yeah, on the app.
I want you to pull this up right now, what you've shown us.
This is what it looks like outside.
Holy fuck.
It looks like this outside.
It's fucking--
This can't be fucking real.
No, it is.
This is somebody took a selfie outside.
Oh my god.
And this is right outside our house.
The king's arms, that must be referring to Fedman.
That must be.
Because he has eight arms.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It must be that.
Yeah.
But anyway, besides all this, it's been pretty--
I've been all right.
Yeah, I've been chilling.
Yeah, I got--
Video games to the death.
Yeah.
I've been really good at this new game I made up.
What is it?
It's called Chase the Ball of Yarn.
(laughing)
What?
It's called Chase the Ball of Yarn.
It's called Chase the, but Chase of Ball of Yarn?
Chase of the Ball of Yarn.
Yeah, Chase of the Ball of Yarn.
Taste of the Ball of Yarn.
And what I do is like when you guys are asleep,
I get the zoomies, I run back and forth
with a little ball of yarn.
That's the other thing, I gotta take him out twice a day.
take him to the fucking park or else he's zooming all over the place when I'm trying to sleep.
Uh huh. Right? Yeah. And I don't have any of my shots. Yeah. No. And he's gonna need new
shots. We'll get you some shots. We'll get you some shots. Yeah. We'll get you some shots.
I have a bunch of shots in the closet here. Oh. Yeah. Is there any way that we could get
all of our clothes, like all the clothes that we used to have back? Yes. Okay. I think I
will pay a company a billion dollars to make replicas of our entire wardrobes. That's great.
I think that these shirts are ugly and I don't want to see your thing. Yeah, his nipple is completely. Yeah, I don't like seeing
I
I might have I might have destroyed both of our shirts in the fight. These are the only shirts we had left
Yeah, and I'm gonna get you some new shirt. Yeah you some fire
So I'm gonna get you one with with lamps all over it and I'm gonna get you one that says skater. Okay apocalypse apocalypse
Albums what did I bring?
Oh my god.
Right?
Because we had a couple minutes before we had to get running to the bunker.
I didn't bring anything.
You didn't bring anything?
I brought the Linkin Park Jay-Z split.
Yeah, luckily, I mean, the thing is we do have a record, we have an archive of the entire
internet on here.
So we do have every album ever, but they're all-
How much fucking money did you spend?
You have an archive of the entire internet?
Yeah, so we do have, we have this song, for example.
Here, just throw this up.
Right now, what you have right here, just put-
Just show, just show the whole-
Just throw this up on the screen.
We have this right here.
Show that you, Jubio, you looked up Kendrick Amar.
Yeah.
do a little bit more AI training. Jubio3 is a bit buggy. Uh-huh. See, it was three attempts and every single
attempt I think I got some kind of oil on the computer. Yeah, yeah. The third
attempt, it was the one that worked, was not the best attempt. No. No. Yeah,
something in his kind of computer genome I think got a little... Look at him smiling
like that. Yeah. Oh, there really is something wrong with that. Why didn't we at least
least change how he looked. Yeah. Right? We could have made him anything. We could have
at least given him like sunglasses. Or like we could have made him like an
anime. He could have been anime. Do you know what actually would have been great
is if we didn't change his appearance and we actually preserved how he looked
right before we uploaded him. Woah! He just got a hat! With a giant gaping hole in his face.
That might have been nice. That would have been really nice. Yeah. A hole that covers all
his horrible facial features. I am seeing it. Yeah. He just got a hat. Get that hat off your head.
Yep, thank you. Delete hat, Jubio3.
Okay, run the peace sign protocol.
That looks awesome. That's a really good protocol.
So, I guess the
nice thing is, if we have an archive of the whole internet, we have
stuff to look at, right? Yeah.
Like, what do we have here, Jubio3?
this website it's prepper 365 again an archive of it this is I guess I kind of
just want to like check this out and see how we stack up against like all the
stuff that they have here right here let's start with the myths about preppers
we didn't do a ton of prepping ourselves yeah here okay so this is a prepper
have you guys ever I mean we're we we'd spent most of our time honestly on on
building the thing. We didn't really get to the prepping stuff. I thought that this
was gonna happen maybe like you know 2024 or yeah 2023, 2024, 2025. Maybe December 2022.
November. Well I guess it did happen. Trust me, I thought this was gonna happen way later and I did
no prepping at all even for this episode. I thought it was gonna be 2012 also. Yeah. But the next 2012.
- Right, yeah.
- 'Cause there's BC, AD, there's gonna be another one.
- Yeah.
- So I thought maybe we'd hit another 2012 at some point.
- I did a little prepping, but it was mostly
just walking around to train myself for walking.
- Oh, you know what I did?
- Get the blood flowing.
- You know what I did prep?
- Yeah, exactly.
- What?
- Pokemon Go.
- It's not gonna connect to anything.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it doesn't.
- So that means that I'm still the ruler of the gym.
That's true.
GameStop.
That's so true.
You'll be the gym leader for that--
Good word.
--in the LES.
The thing is, yeah, the only apps that work now
are Robotronic-approved apps.
And most of those--
I mean, they do have-- they have SlaveGo.
But that one is--
I don't really--
--catch new--
Yeah, I don't really like playing that one.
No, it's also-- that's not even on your phone.
They hand you a butterfly net.
Yeah.
It's not in a backpack.
It's like, I can only fit one guy in there, first of all,
my inventory.
And then all of a sudden, you're doing micro transactions
for Robocoins, right?
because you have to get a bigger bag.
- It is nice though, if you--
- You need to get a watch for your slaves,
you can get a G-Shock.
- When you get that app and you find out
you have a slave stop right across the street
from your house, you can hit it every day.
- Yeah, yeah, that is nice.
- Be instantly around when you wake up.
- You just sit in your bunker and just spin that thing.
- Yeah, just spin the slave stop.
- The thing that I don't like though is--
- Just get free shackles.
- Yeah.
- There's no such thing as rights anymore.
You could just put Pokemon in the game.
- Yeah, that's a good point.
- Hey buddy, I'll tell you something.
There's one right nowadays, and you know what it is?
Fedman FedEx, he's right.
Yeah.
You're a big Fedman fan.
I'm a Fedman supporter.
Yeah, I mean, obviously--
I don't support his ideas.
I didn't support-- I never thought
I would support someone like Fedman, but I will say,
once you guys get a little older,
you get a little bit of money in the bank,
you're going to start seeing things differently.
So you were thinking that maybe one day when
we make a little bit of money, we're
going to all of a sudden switch from being
people who like humans.
You're going to be-- yeah.
You think that we shouldn't have slaves on Earth
and that earth shouldn't be destroyed to oh, now,
now Fedman and his dad Glaxon, who rest in peace.
The thing is, I disagree with the guy politically.
To say that he deserved that is like,
that's bullshit.
- Yeah, that's not right. - But he just choked on stew.
- Yeah, it's a horrible way to go.
- I don't care. - He was only like 380.
- I actually don't care that he's fucking dead.
And you know what, if you hear this, Fedman,
- Okay, so here-- - Your dad was a bitch.
- No, don't say that. - Don't say that at all.
- You're gonna get the whole-- - Don't say that,
don't say that, don't say that, don't say that.
- I'm gonna have to arrest you for some--
- Cut away from him, cut away from him.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I'm still on the screen.
- Cut to a, yeah, thank you, okay.
- No, and your finger is out too.
- No, get him out, get him out.
- Stop.
- Fedman, we like you.
- So, here's some myths about preppers.
Number one, prepping is expensive.
- Yeah, you got that right.
We didn't do a damn lick of it,
because it was so expensive.
- What do you mean?
We built all this.
I bought a plasma ball.
This was--
- No, no, no, 'cause this--
- This is a quarter million dollars.
- This doesn't count as prepping.
Why? We got walls.
It's a bunker.
There's stuff, there's devices.
It's a bunker, sure, but it's not, this is not prepping.
I just realized I can hack Jubio right now.
Look at this.
Ah!
I made him scream in pain.
Oh my gosh, that many keys just to make him scream?
Yeah, I typed, well yeah.
I think it was just this key that did it.
that's a short scream you have to type in the whole thing okay I'm not a fan of
that yeah there's so many fun toys back here that we're not gonna touch though
because some of them flush toilets and some of them turn the fridge on and this
one which one turns the fridge on we're not until listen until we get a
refrigerator something that's really good we're not wasting water on the
fridge water-powered fridge by the way okay speaking of fridges my old fridge
back in the day yeah it keeps leaking water I don't know what's going on with
that I think there's a line there my fridge it's like a red to the into the
fridge my old fridge would leak into the fridge in like this is it just
condensation I don't know what's happening but I was supposed to have a
party on Sunday the 30th but the fridge is ruined the fridge is being weird it's
still gonna happen or was it was still gonna have it did happen it still
happened but the beers and stuff might have been wet. They're wet, okay.
Don't you want a beer to be wet though? Isn't it like every commercial they're
like, "Here's the beer." They slam it down, water flies everywhere. And the thing is
man, I'm walking around, I got my gloves on, I don't want to get my fucking gloves
wet drinking beer. That's right. I'll say that shit with my chest. I do not want
the condensation on a beer glass, I don't want that. My fingerless Jack
Skellington gloves, Bud Light. I don't want condensation on those, man. To the Bud Light Corporation, back when you
were around. Well, I mean, actually, I think they're still around. I think they
are. I think they're one of the few things that that didn't get destroyed,
but the Bud Light Corporation, if you get, if your ice-cold beer is condensated to
the point that my Jack Skellington fingerless gloves get wet, and they smell,
Yeah, that's a problem. I
I'm going to your I'm going to the Budweiser ranch. I'm putting
Too much ketamine and all of your damn Clydesdales. That's right
Uh-huh, and if rank allies the fuck out of them and if your beer if it's too hard to open
I'm gonna kill every one of you. Yep. Yeah. Hey, here's the other thing take those cans those bullshit cans
Yeah, put a bottle top on them. That's right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Why are we fucking around in Arizona?
Why are we doing all this bullshit fucking tab shit?
At least make the can come with a can opener.
There's a tool that opens the can.
Why do I have to do it with my finger?
Make a little thing that's attached to the side of the can.
Look at my finger!
You pull it out.
Do you think that this finger could open a can?
No! I need a tool.
Look at this finger! It's tiny!
And hey, here's another thing.
Hey, pine trees. Make more pine cones.
pine cones yeah why are we getting every pine tree we're getting fucking we're
getting 16 pine cones we should grow 50 we should grow pine trees down here we
should have a little hydroponics lab with the poop water because poop is
fertilizer god from the toilet plant some pine cones that's seeds right so you
want to get a you are pine cone pine cones are definitely fine I need a
jubilee oh three look up if pine cones are seeds because I genuinely need to
- No.
- A pine cone is fucking, is black as night though.
- I mean, most seeds are dark in color.
- I meant the sun.
The sun is black and there's nothing coming,
there's no rays.
- We're gonna get some sun lamps
and we're gonna grow some little pine trees down here.
- Okay, here's some fun facts about, they're not seeds.
- Okay, we won't plant them.
- Storage compartments for dozens of seeds.
- Oh my fucking God.
- Wait.
- One pine cone could be dozens of pine trees.
And imagine how beautiful Christmas will be next month.
If we start growing these pine trees now,
They'll probably be full-grown by Christmas.
That's a good point.
I think Christmas is cancelled. I think Santa died. Santa's dead.
Santa's for sure dead.
Don't you ever fucking say that ever again.
Okay.
I don't care if it's true or not, don't fucking say it, okay?
WHAT?!
Santa found dead.
That's from 2017. Click on that.
No, no, it says 343 AD.
Santa died.
He died that long ago?
Jesus Christ.
Santa found dead on New York Post.
(laughing)
- Can you imagine what it was like pitching this story
in the fucking, in the New York Post?
Yeah, there's all these Paris Hilton upskirts and stuff.
- I don't know what happened today.
- Scroll down.
- There's been no like teenagers subway surfing or anything.
- Let's do Santa found dead.
- Yeah, Santa found dead.
This will scare people more.
- Real life Santa Claus grave found
an extremely important discovery.
- Who's Virginia?
Yes, Virginia, there was a Santa Claus.
Who is Virginia?
- That's from Miracle on 34th Street.
- Oh, I've never seen it.
- It's a shrine, they found the tomb of Santa Claus.
(laughing)
- What?
- They've got the tomb of Santa in Turkey?
- They've detected an ancient tomb
under an ancient church in Turkey?
- It was in Turkey?
Wait, Santa was buried under a Middle Eastern church
all this time?
- Oh my God.
- Oh my, wow.
- Saint Nicholas used his whole inheritance
to assist the needy and the sick, the suffering.
Okay, so that's not presents.
That's just GoFundMe.
- Yep, talk to him. - Yep.
- Wait, listen.
One tale claims that a mysterious bag of gold
appeared in the home of a man who was desperately
trying to marry off his daughters
in order to obtain a dowry.
If not, the girls would be sold into slavery.
This legend led to the leaving of stockings on fireplaces
in hopes the jolly visitor might fill them with gifts.
What does that mean?
Those things don't connect.
- This is the story of Santa, I guess.
- My daughters are gonna become slaves
and I think I will save them by putting stockings
and getting Santa Claus to give me presents.
- The stockings, you can put gold in them.
What's stnicholascenter.com?
Let's check this out.
(laughing)
- Who is Santa Claus?
- We're back on it.
No matter what we try to do,
this podcast always comes back to this,
reading a website about Santa.
- Yeah, we do all this shit.
Get a wide shot, Jubio.
We do all this, right?
And then we're just fucking looking at Santa websites again.
Look at this shit.
- Okay, pull it back up.
- I don't care, go to the cell gloves.
- Cut out Saint Nick.
- Word search, word search.
- I'd like to cut out Saint Nick from the--
- Wait, there's a crossword too?
- We have a printer in here, we could do this right now.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, go to the crossword puzzle.
- The shift game, find the S words.
Yeah, I'll find one, shit.
- Come on. - Okay.
- Yeah, you, I think that Fedmin
might have outlawed cussing also, by the way.
- In Europe, Saint Nicholas often leaves
and children you presents he is called center clause in jerk turkey Dutch New
Jersey in Norton Robotron he helped those in his knee in Chris North Pole in the
North Pole Nicholas taught people about stuff presents whose birthday celebrated
Christmas Santa Santa st. Nicholas staff is called the elves or a sleigh what
that's his staff what do you mean yeah or the reindeer does he I didn't I've
never seen all the Santas that I knew about growing up all the Saints black
Santa white Santa that I told you about your you were taught about different
races of Santa I saw a black Santa at the mall and you're did somebody say
Like that's a different Santa to you. They said that's not that's a different Santa. Yeah, my mom said that's a different Santa really
So we're just telling lies now, okay, hey, I'm stuck in this bunker I'm gonna start making up some stories, okay
Yeah, that's I mean isn't that what humanity is about making up making up stories. You know what we're just continuing
This is it this is important. I'd like to touch on this. Yeah, this is
Yeah, I you know I would also like to touch that it is so much fun to touch this thing and watch the thing
follow the plasma ball I do think you know the what how does humanity has
survived through things like the Great Flood the Great Depression the Great
Depression the great craziness yeah yeah exactly the LA riots right because the
great celebrity deaths of 2016 because of the bathroom incident yeah because of
the oral not many people because they were brave men and women and mystics and
and very percussion young children who would tell stories and tales to continue
this amazing tradition of humanity. So that's our job. Yeah. Is that we got to
keep this thing going, right? Yeah. Because it's just three guys, a plasma ball, a
button that flushes the toilet, another button that turns on the refrigerator.
A reel-to-reel. A reel-to-reel, a Mexican guy that we put into a laptop, and an
aquarium. Yeah. You know? So that's my... Can you guys give me a clap for my speech?
Thank you. Thank you. We're gonna do this thing. And us three, and yeah, and keep
clapping and us three we are gonna repopulate the earth us three yeah yeah
starting with us two against Patrick I'm excited penis war yeah I can't wait
yeah who's sperm is gonna work I know well okay here's that you remember when
there we were looking up and there was all those horrible spaceships green
glowing descending onto the earth your head will be the earth and we will be
the spaceships with our the parts of our bodies at dangle yeah okay if you think
Think of your butt as a bucket. Now imagine a bucket full of mayonnaise.
Yep.
And this will be your situation.
Think of the way they destroyed the White House and the Capitol building and the Empire
State Building and all that stuff just a couple days ago when they invaded.
Oh, when they had that big gaping thing.
Yeah, they completely baked them up.
That sucked them up and you could see all the...
So so the Empire State Building and the Washington Monument that'll be us - and you will be the spaceship
Yeah, basically so here Pat what I want you to imagine is I want you to imagine your butt
Okay as a turkey an uncooked turkey. Yeah, no feathers. It's it's about to go in the oven now imagine me and Caleb as mr.
bean
So you're gonna put your head in my foot and then imagine you know how mr. Bean loses his watch inside the turkey
That watch could either be interpreted as a cock ring
Or as many droplets of sperm or as a growing fetus
Condom as that you know how when you put the condom on there's all that right so the watch could pretty much be anything that's staying
Inside your so you're gonna put your
No, no
Why do we have a cockroach on our hand?
Like Mr. Bean, you're gonna put your hand in my butt to get the sperms out?
No!
No, we're gonna put your hand to push even further into your body.
Let me give you another metaphor then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess it's a simile, right?
Can you help me?
I guess imagine...
My brain is white.
Okay, here.
Imagine a TV.
Your butt is a TV.
and there's sexy videos playing on it first of all but that's not important
yeah back at the back of the tv hdmi port that's actually your butt okay hdmi port
now imagine me and caleb's penis it's it's two it's two hdmis you got hdmi one hdmi two on the
back of the tv a lot of things have two now imagine hey you know what now amir's got more
of an rca thing going on now imagine patrick it's just not updated what are you talking you have a
peasant let him describe destroying your body with his butt your butt you you have two holes
Okay, obviously. HDMI 1, HDMI 2. Now imagine two HDMI cords, okay, and they're covered in
lube and they squirt sperm into your hole.
Yeah.
And then a baby grows inside you.
I know how sex works. Let me get this joke about how...
You already got it and it was nothing.
It's a good one.
I'm sorry, I'm not going to give it to you. It was completely nothing. It was a bad joke.
It didn't make any sense.
I don't even know what an RCA cable looks like.
Yeah, it really...
Red, white, and yellow ones.
Blue.
Red, white, and blue.
Yeah, that's right.
That's gone.
Yeah.
That is gone.
Okay, imagine a volcano.
Okay.
And here's the worst thing.
And we're fucking the volcano.
Here's the worst thing about these Glaxon destroyers.
They fucking-
Oh, the Dirksons?
The Dirkson destroyers.
They turned the flag, they turned it upside down.
They turned it upside down.
Yeah, what is up with that?
They disrespected the flag, drained all the color from it.
They drained all the cum from my fucking dad and they're making clones of him.
Yeah, that's not right.
Disgusting.
That's not right.
I mean, back in the days of human rights, there was something against-
I know what they're doing to my dad well cuz your mom's dead, and they're using her as a human puppet
So your dad has to be
Probably like fucking
Probably like a sex slave yeah, yeah, I think my dad is it is a total sex slave for the Glaxon
Yeah, here's the here's what they did to the flag show this you via Jesus Christ. Oh my god. That's not right
That is not fucking right this guy on it
But it looks like Baphomet, and then I even ours are five pointed stars and the cross the stars
well they put stars in the stripes I don't know why they had to put the
here's a good right you already have busy it's hard it does yeah legible for
you already have if you want why I don't like you want to do a Satan thing you
already have five pointed stars why would you turn the the stars of the American
flag into upside down crosses you don't turn it on crosses they turn a lot of
monuments and fancy buildings upside down now take a look at this flag yeah
they also this was another thing they did yeah this is the one that's hanging
in now. Uh-huh. Yeah. It's scary. That is a terrifying flag. But they did actually, they
turned upside down a building or two. I think they did one in Myrtle Beach, I think they
even turned a building upside down. Oh yeah, they did. Wait, wait, search Myrtle Beach
upside down building. You know what the worst thing they did? What? They took the lean out
of that tower of Pisa. They did, they made it straight. And they illegalized lean. It was
legal for one day before this happened. And they illegalized it. Look at what they did.
Look at what these pieces of shit did to this world. What the fuck. Jesus Christ. Look at
the crowd of people, they're screaming. They fell out of the top. All of these people are
crying. They fell out of the top, you see that hole? They all fell right out. It's fucking
horrifying. That can happen to any one building. They have a machine that turns buildings upside
You know what else they did recently?
What?
Jubio, pull up, search Sphinx, pull up Sphinx here.
What'd they do?
With an I, spell it normal, okay?
That's a cat.
I never foresaw that.
Put that picture up on here.
What the hell did they do to this?
Now if you look closely on here, they took the nose off the Sphinx!
Oh my god!
That thing had a nose! I remember that!
They did it in all the pictures too!
They just have a beautiful, beautiful nose.
only did they take the nose off, they photoshopped the nose out.
And they took the pictures.
They have good cameras, too.
They're from space.
Yeah, they know how to work it.
They all have a Ricoh GR2 that they're using.
All right, let's check the-- let's go to the--
That's not even a great camera.
--myths about the preppers.
I do want to cover some of these.
So we-- all right, so let's see how these apply to us.
So we're preppers.
We've established that.
We have a whole kind of room here.
Number one, you have commando-- or number two, we already did the money thing.
have to have commando-like skills. While skills are certainly an important part of
being prepared, you don't have to be skilled in hand-to-hand combat to prepare
for most disaster situations. Are there preference with a military background?
Absolutely. Helpful? Yes. Necessary? No. So now, so I have a military background, right?
I did gymnastics for two years. He didn't do that. And so, who won the pine cone
fight? Well, I lost because there was a tongue in my butt.
Mm-hmm and I I was a very experienced in Tai Chi and meditation and who didn't fight
I have a military my I have a I come from a military family
Yeah, do you my a lot of most of my uncles were in the army and how where'd that get him now, huh?
They're all I mean
They're probably making your dad probably do an ass to ass like the end of rec room for a dream right now
It's your dad and there's a bunch of alien that's seen up real quick
Don't pull that thing we're allowed to pull that so I don't think we can watch that no
I think no I think ass to ass is on YouTube. I think if you look up
Now I think yeah, we actually installed a content filter in Jubio, I can't do anything like that
You can you look up?
Asked to ask two guys. No don't it's not gonna help us. I don't think I am excited that we that
Thank God the only website that the aliens left up is patreon. Yeah, cuz we're gonna be making fucking what a
Fucking nobody nobody can pay for Netflix anymore. Nobody can pay for Amazon Prime. No, I don't know what I can pay for Paramount Plus
Yeah, say what you will and you know all those subscriptions coming to us now. I'm one of Edmund FedEx's biggest
Critics I will say I would say you're kind of a complainer. Yeah. Well, well, I'm one of his big
You're one of Earth's biggest babies. I'm one of his biggest critics
I will say though. I do love his undying support for independent creators. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, he kept up fans Lee and
I mean, that's that's what I'm saying guys
I think if you look a little deeper into his policy you'll find that he's he's he's a very reasonable guy
You guys who has a lot of humanity's best interest at heart. Yeah, cuz he kept grailed up. Yeah, he kept grailed up grailed. Yeah
Now it's called grilled. Yeah human meat on it. Yeah
Yeah. He sold Rick Owens bones. What is Grailed even a... I mean look at this.
A platform for personal style. What do you sell your body on here for fucking
money? Yeah. I think this is for... I think now this is for Robotronics to get
human disguises. It's because Robotronics are... the one thing that I will... I mean if
we had a photo of a Robo... it's hard to get a photo of them. Right. We don't have
one yet. They do love Stussy. They love Stussy, they love Echo. That can be kind of an ongoing
thing for us. Maybe we can go out in the next few weeks, try to capture some
footage of Robotronics. Yeah, we can maybe try I guess. Yeah, because we don't have any right now.
Yeah. We did get a good a good clip of one of their ships descending, one of the
Dirksen Destroyers. Yeah, we did. That one was pretty good. That was pretty, yeah. So go back to the
myths. I want to check these out. God, my nipples are really just out, huh? Yeah. So, you're a
delusional slash delusional slash conspiracy.
Dilutional.
This is about this is about the the pee purifying thing.
So you are you're you're kind of a dilutional because you drink
poop and dirt water and you dilute it into normal water with
your body.
Okay, you're right.
Yeah, I guess so.
Here's a here's this hasn't aged.
Well, you don't have to be an Alex Jones fan to realize that
natural and man-made disasters can do and will happen.
I do not think that the government is reading my mail,
although they obviously have the ability nor do I think the
aliens are secretly running our government.
Yes, I actually heard that one recently.
So, and that actually ended up being really true.
Yeah, that was actually--
'Cause there was a bunch of,
most every single person that was in power
turned out to be like a sleeper cell, robot.
Yeah, they had Robotronic DNA in their system.
Yeah, Robotronic DNA, they are these--
Human weapons.
Michelle Obama was an alien.
Yeah.
A male alien.
And what I will say, most of the people in power,
they turned out to be human,
but with Robotronic DNA allowing them to be controlled.
but most mayors and selectmen, full alien,
full, completely planted alien.
- Oh yeah.
- Especially the selectmen.
I mean, you should have guessed
from a name like that, selectmen.
- Yeah, 'cause they asked--
- What human would call someone a selectman?
- Yeah, exactly.
- They were selected by the aliens.
- Exactly, selected men. - To go to Earth.
- Selected men. - Yeah, exactly.
- Okay, you are hoping for the end of the world.
Yeah, I guess I wasn't hoping for the end of the world.
Just making sure I was prepared.
I do kind of-- - I wasn't hoping,
'cause I, I mean, I had that big party I had planned
for Sunday. - Yeah, that's true.
- We were all gonna wear costumes
and Caleb and Cameron-- - And it did happen.
- Well, Caleb and Cameron brought,
what did you guys bring?
You said you brought your egg--
- I brought an egg salad that has,
yeah, it was a pretty good egg salad.
- I have a feeling that I brought
some kind of sweet delete, delete.
- Sweet delete, delete?
- See, no, they didn't have delete, delete back then.
That's a two-robotronic dish. - Yeah, I'm sorry, yeah.
A dessert, a delight. - Oh, that's what you're
thinking of. - A sweet delight.
That's gonna be but I call it a sweet delete. That was really good. Yeah, and I really enjoyed it
Yeah, the only problem is I was your favorite part of it
I guess my favorite part was when we watched the scary movie. I meant the favorite part of my sweet delete
Oh your sweet delete my favorite part. It was how full it made me good
Preppers are just religious zealots. I'm gonna go down here to the end of this thing
Preppers are just religious zealots building an arc which we tried to do by the way
The wood prices are just fucking out of control these days.
Sheet metal though?
While many Christians will cite Proverbs 21 as a basis for their preparations,
there's treasure to be desired, and oil in the dwelling of the wise,
but a foolish man spendeth it up.
Not all Christians subscribe to this concept.
I've even heard some Christians say that prepping is based on a lack of faith,
though I disagree with this.
The fact remains that some do believe this.
It's just as prepping is not limited to those who hold certain political beliefs,
nor is it limited by religious affiliation.
I mean, we're three different religions here.
You know, I'd recently converted to, uh,
Glogonianism, you know, because I wanted to kind of assimilate.
- Oh, good for you, I didn't know that.
- Yeah, I didn't want to be like, you know,
'cause I was-- - That's big.
- Going from like, 'cause I actually--
- I actually recently converted too, to Judaism.
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
- It was hard as fuck to be a Muslim
in the post, like, annihilation world, you know?
Like, it just is, honestly, it's just hard to find
like, halal food, so I was like,
pine cones don't cut it for some reason.
They like, for whatever reason, pine cones are not halal.
They might not be kosher either, so I'd watch it.
- Yeah.
- So, Gorgonian is--
- Well, the important thing about the kosher thing
is you can't eat human meat with human cheese.
- I just converted--
- And you can't boil, oh, if you ever get a hand on his mom
and you wanna eat him, you can't boil him in her milk.
- Yeah.
- That's like way out of line with--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Well, she's got no more milk.
She's a green, decomposing--
- They took the milk out of her?
- Yeah.
They took, hey, there's, I don't even know
if there's any milk left.
- There was.
- There wasn't any left.
- There was milk left in your mom.
I don't think so.
There was a huge amount.
When I saw her on those puppet strings, I don't even think she had a jaw.
Really?
Yeah.
I will say before this whole thing happened, I did use my milk scanner, and there was a
lot of milk.
Yeah.
I used my milk scanner right here.
I converted to a new type of agnostic called atheism.
You're going atheist on us, man?
Yeah.
After all this, what about the...
I'm going to get a...
Look at this!
this out? You know what? I'm back to agnostic. Okay, that's right, because
you're not sure, because there's certain things in this world, like a plasma ball
where you go, "Yeah, maybe God isn't real, Christianity is fucking bullshit,
Glogon's not even fucking real." Then you touch a plasma ball and you say, "Well,
who made this?" Yeah. Right? Right. Who made the elements of this? Exactly. And also,
how's it heating my finger up so fast? Is it hot? It kind of gets hot if you keep it there.
there yeah I yeah I'm gonna start getting a now that I'm agnostic I'm gonna start
getting all sorts of crazy tattoos really yeah like what probably like a
fisherman yeah tell you what's a of what this one this one's aged pretty poorly
now I think yeah this I mean this guy this is what kind of what your mom
looked like right no jaw okay and the crown I think your mom was made out of
of just bullets. Really? Just bullets kind of just reaming your head? Oh, well, just no
scalp either. I got one of my dad. Yeah. Oh wow. Yeah, I don't know if you guys can see
that on camera. Yeah. I just got that. He's making a skeleton. Yeah. He's uh, I mean,
I also don't know if you guys have. That's what your dad looked like when you saw him?
Yeah. Well, he's, he's. I don't know if you guys have. Yeah. Oh, that's the smell. Yeah,
- Yeah, that's my dad, my mom, my uncle, my aunt,
grandpa, grandma. - You put it in a pile?
- You kept everybody.
- Yeah, what am I gonna do, throw 'em away?
- I saw most, on FaceTime, I saw pretty much
my whole family get disintegrated,
but I didn't know they kept my mom and dad
to keep taunting me.
- Well, now it's called Space Time.
- True.
Let's check out this list of the--
- Preppers Just Hate Obama.
- Wait, wait, wait, go back to that one.
I actually do wanna read that.
Preppers Just Hate Obama, that was actually--
Clinging to their guns and Bibles certainly didn't endear him to many folks in part of the country,
but the fact remains that the prepper survivalist movement long predates the Obama presidency.
Remember Y2K? That turned out to be true.
So it actually just was a little delayed.
So like, that's why Jubio doesn't have any memories of anything and his family.
He doesn't remember anything about his family, right?
And he also likes getting hit.
[slap]
You know? He actually likes it.
you know but he can't he also can't speak so he doesn't he can't tell you but he
does like it he really really likes it others say it goes all the way back to
the pilgrims my parents are both depression babies hey you don't have to
tell anybody that yeah that's your your your parents your grandparents or your
grandparents didn't want to have your parents yeah that's nice that's fucked
up you don't have to tell anybody that's something you say in therapy buddy you
don't say that on your website. Let's see what else is on this, the myths. Hope for
the best, prepare for the worst. That's about it. I like this advertisement here. I like
the look of that for some reason. Can you zoom in on that? Yeah, zoom in on this here
advertisement. Oh, actually zoom in on that one. Yeah, this picture to zoom into either
the right or left side of this picture really far. Oh, I ate that the other day. A foot?
No, the cream. Oh. Oh, actually Pat, this is a really good representation of what me
and Caleb are gonna do. This is kind of what we were looking for. I could be the left
foot, you could be the right foot, and we can both be the spoon.
Maybe we're sharing a spoon. Yeah. That's not a bad idea.
Yeah. Okay, there's more stuff on this website. Go to the
prepper list. I wanted to get into this for a little bit. So I have
a couple of items that I think that are going to be pretty helpful
for us. Jubio, if you want to cut to the close-up thing.
and you hold my mic up to me so I can...
Okay, so here's the...
So I have a couple of things that I think will be helpful.
One...
I know we've been eating pinecones, but I did share one thing,
and maybe for one of our birthdays or something,
I have one can of beefaroni.
Oh, I don't like that.
Hold that up to the...
Here, here, here.
You guys can have that. I don't like beefaroni.
You don't like beefaroni? Okay.
No, I don't even care if it's the last thing I'm allowed...
or the last real food that I'll be able to eat in the world.
I'm ever gonna eat that. I don't know why but this is the I have just a
mayonnaise. Now I like that! I love that. I can make some real good I can make some
real good pine cone sauce with that. Romantic dinners we might want to pop
open a little bit of bubbly. Okay. Well that one. What the hell? That is scary. So just show
maybe this other one there we go yeah just a little bit of that I think
something bewitched this mountain do oh yeah magic's real now - I should mention
that you know oh yeah I got a magic is completely real everyone want to close
whoa hold on now I gotta hold I can't even open my glow stick up for you I got
you okay you can hold you can purple or green you can hold your mic this whole
time we shouldn't do green probably because it will become bewitched you've
been able to hold the mic the whole time.
Whoa.
These are real, genuine Rothko--
They're actually real.
--glow sticks.
Wow, look at this.
Oh, I got green.
I figured maybe we want to keep up morale around the bunker,
so I got some-- just a couple of things, you know, like--
you know.
Oh, this is good.
Oh, wow.
I mean, what's better than that, right?
Here's my glow stick.
This would be great to hang up, maybe.
Oh, yeah, we can hang that up.
We could put this here.
Yeah, yeah, that's not a bad idea.
I got another one.
This one says-- see, and I think we all
like positive affirmation in the morning and shit especially with the stuff going
on the world politically so this says you know you did not wake up to be
mediocre so we're gonna wake up and we're gonna be some of the best fucking
pinecone hunters that's right that would go perfect right here I think we could
get a thumbtack and put it yeah that might be yeah that's not a bad idea that
is a pretty good one here for now yeah and then what else we have we have rope
so we could tie him up when we're doing later yeah I can hold on to that this is
exciting for us you like the MRE here oh why don't we make and eat that right now
we said you don't like beefaroni this is beef ravioli in meat and that's your
soy protein sauce yeah I know how to make these actually all right and then
one more thing this is huge yeah is because we got to keep ourselves safe I
I think if this is what I if I remember correctly oh yeah oh and let's see this
will be perfect this will help me open up the bag of beef ravioli this is a ninja
star that I bought it was seven dollars and eighty cents I don't know what the
conversion of pine cones would be but it also comes with a nice free silica gel
that is sharp is it sharp did you just hurt yourself on it no I just opened the
bag really quickly. So next time that we get in some kind of fight I definitely
check this out. I'm gonna make sure that I have that on me. And usually these
MREs come with some kind of dessert. Is that what you're gunning for? I'm excited.
I think we can treat ourselves to a little dessert. The last time I ate an MRE it had
some kind of peach thing in it. Oh my god. Nutrition facts. I was right.
We'll have grape jelly and a great
No fucking way, okay, what else do we have in here we have more grape jelly
This is the be preppy only the activator. Yeah
We're any water water and then we do we have water yeah, okay?
So then we put the water here you read that you get the water okay here
I am gonna go I'm gonna let you make this and meet me
Okay, you guys make that I'm gonna make
No, you make the R.E.M., me and Cameron will read the list. How about that?
Yeah, you guys read the list.
Yeah.
I was going to say, because this also comes with white wheat snack bread TFF.
Wow.
Hold that up to the camera.
Which has, and this is the best bread you can get.
The best bread?
Right there, the best bread. 350 milligrams of sodium in it.
Right.
And, uh, 3 grams of sugar.
Okay, so go ahead and make this.
This is reduced sodium, too.
Oh, that's nice.
wants to follow along at home this is beef ravioli in meat and textured soy
protein. Yeah so go ahead, go on HelloFresh you can order this there probably.
The thing that ties the meal all together. It's called HelloFresh now. One moist towelette. Yeah so we're gonna use that to clean up Pat later.
So this prepper list, it seems there are literally hundreds of excellent prepper
lists out there and as part of our journey we have started our own. We hope
to use this as an inventory/wishlist to help us stay on track as well as, hopefully, helping
others develop their own. So, it says, "Happy prepping." This says cash. Okay, yeah, we
get it. You're fucking rich. Obviously, I don't have any cash. Patrick doesn't have
any cash. He has a bucky buck, which is very helpful. A buddy buck, rather. I don't know
what that's going to get him on one of his apps, you know? On Lazer or whatever. No,
You shut up about your apps, okay.
It says, "We keep extra cash in each vehicle as well as some loose change.
$20 stashed behind our cell phone covers.
$200 in the prepper closet."
The thing is, if the world goes to shit, what the hell, why do you give, oh, at least I
have $20 in my car.
That's not going to do anything.
That's going to help a lot.
I mean, speaking as someone who has a lot of money in this situation, you'd be surprised.
Every book, every movie they say, "Okay, money has no value anymore."
But that's science fiction.
They made that up.
It's still $100, it's still $100, and you can get incredible food with it.
I always thought about that with like Fallout and shit.
It's like, why the fuck are we doing...
Why is it that all of a sudden bottle caps are some fiat currency?
It's like, just fuck, keep using money.
Money has no value anymore, but now bottle caps do.
Exactly, it makes no sense, dude.
So stupid.
the has the MRE cooking coming. It feels a little hot already. I think you're
supposed to do this. No you don't you're not supposed to cut that much of it
you're supposed to open it up and then fold it you have to close this thing.
What the hell just happened? A light just went out. Oh great now the lights are
fucking going out. Okay everything's getting ruined. Water it says water we
have one water bottle yeah and then now all of a sudden we're gonna have this
fucking shit water to this guy you're right you are supposed to put I know you
fucking already ruined it that's okay worst case we have the grape jelly large
were treated water storage again we have 50 gallons water filter that's me I guess
uh-huh drink mixes we have mountains amount do this could be a really good
drink mix grape jelly this is actually maybe now I'm thinking about it maybe
one of the most valuable things you could have in a post-apocalyptic society
You are right.
And we have two of them.
And you are--
See, finding a packet of grape jelly in these times
is kind of like finding a misprinted nickel.
Yeah, you're right.
It's actually worth--
It's pretty rare.
You think that's worth nothing.
You think that's worth $0.05.
It's actually worth $6.
So coffee, we don't have any--
well, I just drank my last cup.
Yeah, we have this at least.
Powdered milk.
- If we wanna pretend we're drinking coffee,
this empty cup could be pretty good.
- Oh yeah, I guess we can just use those.
It's kinda just like a nice, it's like decaf, right?
It's like-- - Yeah, it's like
going through the motions.
- You know how sometimes you'll drink decaf
and you'll be like, "Whoa, I feel like I drank a cup of coffee."
- It's like when you're addicted to watching movies
and you trick your body into thinking
you're watching a movie but it's looking
at a blank TV screen for an hour and a half.
- Yeah, exactly, which is what we've been doing.
And then for food, okay, so this is big.
So we have, let's do a real, so we have,
we're about to have a beef ravioli.
- Two grape jellies.
- Tootsie roll.
- A piece of bread, a beef ravioli,
a mayonnaise, and a Mountain Dew.
- And in a pinch, in a pinch rope.
- Yeah, we can eat that like spaghetti.
And then if we look at their,
how does this stack up against theirs?
Canned fruits.
- Okay.
Grape jelly, that counts, that counts, that counts.
- Canned veggies.
- Grape, grape jelly.
- It could be grape, canned beans, that's beef.
- That's beef, beans, beef.
- Soups and chili.
Chili has beef in it.
- Beans, beef, and bread.
- Dried beans, we don't have those.
Rice, we don't have those.
Flour, we don't have those.
(laughing)
Wait, no, this--
- And fellas, and fellas,
just take a look at this awesome bread.
- Oh my God, I'm getting hungry already.
- Oh my God.
Hold that up to the GoPro.
- Get it really close.
- Take a look at that bread.
- Oh man, that shit is loud.
I can smell that.
- Yeah, that is one of the best--
- Well, Pat.
- That is one of the best smelling things.
- Hey, you're gonna have to take a bite
with the grape jelly, buddy.
- Yeah, and listen, before we get to that--
- Oh wow, this looks--
This looks so edible.
Take a bite of that.
Come on, put that on there.
And you might-- hey, Pat, you might want a little of this,
too.
Come on.
That looks amazing.
Take a look at this jelly.
It's completely brown, just like a grape.
And Pat, if that's too bland for you,
I have some seasoning for you right here
that you can use, some iodized salt, which
we can use as flour, too.
(laughing)
- He's putting more on.
- Look at this.
- He's so hungry.
- Look at, oh, I'm starving.
I've eaten nothing but--
- All right, get your spoon.
You want some mayo in there too?
Here, put some mayo on the other half, Pat.
- I'm good with the mayo.
- We'll save the mayo for later.
- I'll cut this up and then, oh my fucking God.
- How's that taste?
- Dude, we need an overhead shot here.
- It tastes good, right?
- And you know, you don't get many treats like this nowadays.
This is a delicacy for sure.
How's that?
- And like any good bread,
it's completely too soft.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's always good.
- It's soft in all the wrong ways.
And it's also very chalky.
- Okay.
Well, that is good bread these days,
'cause it is bread.
Let's see, we have pasta.
Oh, this MRE is steaming right now.
Is it doing its thing?
Yeah.
We have peanut butter, jams, jellies, preserves.
Pasta, pasta, bread.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And bread that we have.
Yep.
Mac and cheese and other box meals.
This is a box meal.
Mac and cheese.
Hey, how about Mac and Devon go to high school?
Put the--
Peanut-- it's a-- peanut's my personal addiction.
OK, come on.
Don't say everyone fucking needs it
because you're personally addicted to it.
Yeah, exactly.
Some people don't even like peanuts.
He's cracking open a Tootsie Roll.
Not even a word.
He's just opening it.
Okay, so basically the whole Emory is getting eaten by him.
I have an amazing idea.
Oh my god.
Hold that up.
Tilt that down a little bit.
Oh god, that just, if that doesn't make you hungry, I'm not sure what will.
Alright, take a big bite.
Jesus.
Oh.
And the cake roll is completely rock hard.
Be careful.
(laughing)
- Be careful, I think all the dentists died.
Oh, look at that, head shot right off.
This is so hot, bro.
Oh, I got jelly on myself.
- I can't eat this, this is hard because it's rock hard.
- You spit it out.
You're wasting precious calories.
- That does look good, though.
- That does, that is one of the best meals
I've had in a while.
- That is delicious, it beats an acorn or a pine cone.
freezer. Some think the freezer is a bad idea and granted, you know what we need to do with
that Tootsie Rolls? Freeze it.
You have to keep the MRE propped up. See, I just took the jelly, I think I just accidentally
sucked all the flavor out of it because it just tasted completely just like a...
It was probably really flavorful and then you sucked all the flavor out of it.
I think I sucked all the flavor out because it was more, it wasn't even, it didn't even
taste like food, it just tasted like a texture.
So let's go down to cleaning supplies.
We didn't bring any cleaning supplies.
This jelly will be here forever.
- This is a cleaning supply right here.
- Bleach, lots and lots of bleach,
bar soap, soft soap, dish soap, ammonia,
window cleaner, Mr. Clean or similar, laundry soap.
- This haircut got me looking like Mr. Clean.
- Yeah, nice fucking try.
No, come on.
No, you have a haircut.
I have no hair, so I'm the Mr. Clean.
- Yeah, you don't really look like Mr. Clean.
You have to stop opening this stuff.
You have to open this on camera.
doing an apocalypse mukbang here. You can't just open it without saying anything. Get
a close up on this. Get a close up on him dabbing. He's dabbing. Okay, thank you.
Wow. I forgot about that.
Yeah. No, I don't think I've seen a dab in years.
We don't have any medical or first aid equipment. I think we're probably going to start using
this.
Oh, rope!
This is multi-purpose.
And Patrick has a bunch of extra skin on his back. We could kind of maybe take that off
and use that as-
Yeah, we can grab that and tie it onto one of us with rope.
he's also luckily he's oh this isn't this is a medical a medical tool to scalpel
yeah I've been an MRE is steaming well let's eat it then come on
wait but I don't know how long it doesn't have instructions on it it does
but I think you have to take it out of the because it's hot
it's hot at the bottom I'll give you that much let's see it says I work that you
just didn't even read the instruction she doesn't broke it I know what I'm doing
yeah I'm in the army yeah that's obvious yeah ten to fifteen minutes depending on
air temperature you're all supposed to shake it which you didn't do so it's
only hot at the bottom so Patrick can eat this
I don't want anything to do with this anymore.
You've wasted one of our two food items.
Well, he spit out the other one.
He wasted another one too.
This is your dinner tomorrow night.
There's still some bread for you.
Okay. Hold up. Wait, wait, wait.
And there's some for you too.
See, he's going to enjoy this.
I have a gluten intolerance that I developed.
I developed a gluten intolerance.
Lucky for you, there is no gluten in this at all.
No, it's full of gluten.
I don't think you're making heart death.
Oh, look at that.
Look, it's practically a saltine.
It's practically a pizza.
Basically a personal pizza that you're eating.
I'm going to eat it.
Oh, that's good.
Is it good?
Yeah, it tastes like the last pretzel.
Oh, man.
You guys have to try this stuff.
This is good.
Yeah.
Iodized salt?
I don't know what they put in this.
- I have to eat it?
- Just take a bite.
- Is it good?
- Just put some, here, here.
I'll...
- Yeah, wait, wait, put the three of this on there.
- Oh, it's not.
- Okay, I get it.
- Yeah, we can use it, no, here, here, here.
Open it up with this.
- Oh, no, no, I'm full.
I'm full.
My, my...
- No, just poke in the top with that.
- My stomach is shrank to the size,
Jesus Christ.
My stomach is shrank to the size of a pine cone
Oh my god, the aftertaste is good too!
I love the way it-
The aftertaste is one of the best parts!
This is actually perfect because it's the kind of food that stays in your mouth for a long time.
So you keep getting the taste, and that's great because we're in the apocalypse and we don't have that much food.
And look at how cute that is!
Look at how cute that little mayo drop is.
Put that open wide, come on.
Wait, wait.
Ewwww!
(laughing)
- And that mayo's been room temperature for a long time.
- Oh my god.
- You're being a baby.
- Honestly, the mayo makes it taste like dog food.
(laughing)
- So good.
- I wish I had some dog food right now.
- Oh man.
- Wow.
And the best part is I have no water or coffee to--
Wait, here, here.
No.
At least I have some Mountain Dew.
That is good.
That hits the spot.
I don't know who drank the first half of this.
That's how I found it.
But that is really, really good.
Yeah.
Wow.
This is one of the best days we've had in a long time.
I know.
This is a feast.
My god.
I don't think we should keep the M. Oh wait the M. Oh wow
It's leaking and it's too hot to touch
Loads and destroys
Higher bunker yeah, that'll be good. Oh, it should it should it has to be propped up like this
Okay, okay, all right luckily this place is very durable. Yeah
About this set is that set this
Is durable yeah?
Your hands smells like a burning plastic. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you need to go you got something bad on you
Yeah, as you did this so wrong. That's fine that you're gonna. Okay. Yeah touch your eye. Yeah, touch your eye with a different hand
No, you won't know it was that's a different. That's a different hand touch your hands together
I'll say it guys. I don't like mayonnaise that much anymore. I used to really really enjoy mayonnaise, but I guess something about
You know this this looking at looking at this right now
Have a tootsie roll that hold this up to the camera real quick looking at this right now is really making me hungry for Patrick's
butt and I don't know why
Toilet paper reserves
went up in flames
I forgot about the toilet paper fire. The toilet paper reserves, they had tons of toilet paper
like Fort Knox, the giant reserve, the US Army. Ever since freaking COVID, remember the toilet
paper stockpiling? Three ply.
That's been the worst part of this whole thing. The damn shelves at the fucking grocery store,
right?
And the worst part is COVID got even worse.
Yeah, I have it.
Yeah, me too.
We all have it.
Yeah, yeah. All right, is that kind of... I mean, I feel like that's it for today, right?
I mean, we had a feast.
I mean, hey, I just want to say I'm excited, you guys, to go into the rest of the future
with you guys, just goofing off and having fun. I think we can maybe do this for a thousand
years. Okay. All right. I'm down. I mean, as long as
I keep eating like that, right? Yeah, we'll bring in some more food.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We'll figure out how to get some.
Yeah, and basically, I mean, we're going to unlimited your billions of dollars. We basically
have unlimited resources to do whatever we want down here.
Patrick, you could maybe, you could wrap this up. You could box that up.
Yeah, yeah. Take that home.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, we don't really have it.
Yeah, your your hovel outside. Yeah. Yeah my hovel. It's called a hovel because it's what they paid that what now that I work for getter
Uh-huh. It's a it's a three. It's a box that hovers above the ground. Oh shit and
By the way, we need to invest in a pasty. I think to cover my leg. Yeah, that might be nice
Well, I'll get you guys some reconstructed
And can we have money I don't think that that's gonna work out for whatever reason that's fine
Whatever reason there is I don't think it's gonna happen. Well, thank you guys for thank you for listening. Thank you
I mean, I don't know who's gonna listen to this probably somebody in some other planet
Back I hope you're listening you do end up watching
on YouTube
Go to the YouTube channel podcast about list
Uh-huh, and I hope that you go to the patreon too because it's the only way we can
It's the only way Cameron can get richer. That's right. It all is gonna cam now. Yep
We'd like to expand this aquarium also, yeah, there's a lot of stuff we want to do and we how we need your help
We'd like to get maybe it we'd like to get a new skin for Jubio. You know, maybe we make them
Yeah, not look like that anymore. Yeah, so just keep us in your thoughts in your ears. It's gonna be like this forever
Bye. Bye
Bang, bang, bang, bang.