Check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check,
check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check,
I don't know what what Pierce is doing.
Well I realize that we can't close this.
Oh, Pierce, careful. Come on.
I am being careful, Cameron. Shut up.
He's not gonna break those doors. I'm worried about the doors breaking him.
That's what I thought happened earlier.
Check, check, check, check, check, check.
Checking.
Checking it out.
Alright.
Okay, I think we're all good. We're all ready.
Alright, let's do it.
Everyone's ready? Yeah.
Are they recording?
Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
Crap monster.
There it is.
What's up Matt?
What's up fellas?
How you doing?
I'm doing well.
Yeah?
New studio is looking good.
Thank you.
Yeah, this is great.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's incredible.
Tell me, why do you need three keyboards?
I don't need...
Oh, you just...
I don't need three keyboards.
Because they look cool.
They do look cool, yeah.
You were playing at the same time one song?
I heard that.
Please tell me you heard that.
Yeah, we're hearing popping.
I did not hear the popping because I have headphones on,
but what I will tell you is that there was some interference just there in the audio
that everybody will be able to hear.
It went "did it" right when you guys pointed.
I'm completely serious.
I'll let you say this is y'all's show.
I'm just a kid.
No, no, no.
You're the expert.
I was just gonna say, as to what this show is about to begin with, right?
Yeah, I mean, we're here in North Carolina with Matthew DeVita,
paranormal investigator, he also is all things audiovisual.
A master.
A master of all things audiovisual.
I would say master.
Expert.
IT, information technology degree holder.
Support specialist.
But anyway, we're at his studio and stuff's been getting weird.
We had a door fall on, Pierce's head.
Yeah, Pierce is here too.
I'm here in spirit.
Well, you're here in real it.
You were almost only here in spirit.
You were almost just in spirit.
Yeah, because you almost murdered me.
That's one big door.
See, and that's what a ghost does, it tears people apart.
He was, I watched it, he was far away from the door.
And the door came right back.
door so precariously like a time bomb like a like a like a Bugs Bunny villain I
would have felt horribly forever I mean not only would I've gone to jail but I
would have literally felt I'm not sure you would have gone to jail we would
have covered it I would have not told them that it was your fault I would have
said it was a good we would have dealt with it in one way or another yeah I
guess most murders that have happened while people were in the middle of
talking about ghosts go completely unsolved.
Yeah, because it's like, well, also like you deserved it.
Like, yeah, you were inviting something.
Yeah.
What?
Kind of like, did you hear another crazy thing?
No, I was just laying down the law.
He's just making a face at people, I guess.
I don't know what's going on.
We're recording it on video now, so I figure.
That's true.
Yeah.
That is true.
This is the first time, my instinct when Patrick does something like this is to be like, what
are you doing?
Nobody can see you.
there's a possibility that people can see him. Can I add to the listeners? Yeah. Feel free to
review this video or audio podcast and see if they hear anything that's not
part of this podcast. Yeah you guys should find a way to to dump all of the
metadata into the podcast. Have you ever opened up some audio and put it in
one of those spectrogram or whatever things and you see a big six-pointed
star devil horn. Yeah or a 666 embedded into the waveform. Or an open mouth with a tongue.
No but we've got some pretty horrible audio from investigations. Really? Just like horrible.
Audio that plays without even being pressed. I mean like voice, you know, voices caught
on audio that says like "get out" and things like that. Yeah. And what's more horrible
than that? Not a whole lot. Not much. What's the longest sentence that you've ever caught?
So when we did an investigation in downtown Wilmington, I caught an EVP.
So EVP, for those of you who don't know, electronic voice phenomenon, it's when we get audio but
we can't hear it with our own ears.
If we hear it with our own ears, it's known as a disembodied spirit.
So just clarify that before we go any further.
But the sentence was, "Hey man, how about stepping away from me?"
Whoa.
Wow.
That guy's kind of got a cool thing.
Yeah.
- This is some straight, legit, that was--
- Some kind of punk.
- I'm quoting, "Hey man, how about stepping away from me?"
- Wow.
- That was the E.P. we call it.
- Could not have been a Civil War guy.
- No, definitely not.
- That was the '70s.
- Yeah.
- It could have been, yes, I would say more modern.
- Little more modern.
- But don't you think that maybe a ghost would,
I mean, a ghost would be walking around, floating around,
seeing, you know, they're watching Girls and shit.
They know. On HBO? Yeah, they're like, yeah, that's what I mean. They're watching
shows. Yeah. Yeah, you caught on. And so they're hip to the new lingo and
stuff, right? I believe it depends on the entity. We talked about this early. So
there could be like a dorky entity. If it's an intelligent entity, then who
knows what's possible. But if it's more like a residual entity that's caught in
a loop per se. I could also see like, for example, maybe the ghost of a 50s
businessman. It might be likely for this businessman to pick up on the lingo and
perhaps say that a person's brain or blood was bussin bussin when he's
haunting them, but maybe a ghost of a caveman or a homo neanderthalus or
something with kind of a lessened brain capacity would not be able to say
anything besides "ooka booka." Because they never learned to talk in the first place.
Exactly. So you're not gonna be able to say a single vowel.
But now, there's debatables on that as well over, you know, can entities learn?
That's something else to consider.
You know, depending on how long the entity lingers after life, can it become more intelligent or is it going to stay the same intelligent as it was when it was born?
Sure.
I kind of like your idea.
So do you think a caveman could be Einstein level if it was around long enough?
I do like your idea of a caveman spirit. I've never even heard of that.
I think about it a lot.
about it a lot. I think you just want to hear a Oonga Boonga EVP. That would be pretty incredible.
I mean who wouldn't want to hear a Oonga Boonga EVP? I would love to. I'm, you know, I'm...
Because there's odds are... Me catch mammoth. How about you step away from me? Hey bud,
how about you step away? My wife, stop looking. You know? Any of those would be great. I guess
you're I mean uh so often it's people are afraid of Native American burial grounds
but almost everywhere is probably a caveman's yeah grave well do you think
the Ice Age kind of depleted all that well they could be called different
things in different parts of the world not necessarily just cavemen so true
they could be any they could be called anything yeah was it Neanderthal one two
and then yeah yeah yeah Neanderthal I don't think it turns out that there's
really not that many caves. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. People can't always find a cave.
Yeah, sometimes a caveman is born outside of a cave. I'm here because I have not
found a good cave. Exactly. You're a houseman. Well, yeah, but because I haven't found a
good cave. Yeah. I stand by that. You would, this would, this, you could do a cave
thing. I think a cave setup would be pretty strong. I think a stalagmite or stalactite there.
yeah maybe a stalagmite there. If a stalagmite or a stalactite was up there I don't care which one.
I forget which one is the one. It's a mite comes up and a tite comes down.
Did I tell you guys my uncle like deceived me so like he gave a very cogent
explanation of what they were and he was like yeah stalagmite because tigers
roam on the jungle floor in stalagmite because mountains grow and I was like
well I can't monkeys it was monkeys he said monkeys swing from the trees above
and Tigers roam on the floor below the complete opposite monkeys don't roam on
the floor and Tigers don't swing from trees but the right and the tight are
opposite. That's pretty obvious what I meant there. The best one of those is
is dessert and desert you know because a desert is super... a desert is not. It's very sparse.
There's not enough. Yeah go for it. But a dessert is super sweet. So what do you
get? Super sweet. A desert is one... For me... A snake. A desert has a snake. What I've
always thought, what I've always thought is a desert... But sparsely and snakes. A desert there's not as
much stuff there so there's only one S and a dessert it's like there's like
so much there's so much it's bountiful a desert is not sparse which has two s's
when it comes to sand which has one s. I'm so lost. We're kind of like...
So what do you get if you were to cross an elephant with a rhinoceros?
Since we're talking animals. Elefano. That's good. That only kind of works if you have a British
accent I guess. It would work better for sure. Here bump the mic after that joke.
Elif I know. Elif I know. Elif I know. Elif I know. That would be a Elif I know. Elif I
know. I think it would be a Elif I know. Excuse me, could I mustache you a question? Oh that's
Yeah, I must ask you a question.
Could I'm...
I think you'd have to drop the "could I".
Excuse me sir, would it be so wrong if I must ask you a...
Oh no, that does work.
Would it be so wrong if I must ask you a question?
Yeah, that one works fine.
That one works too well.
So what's new with you? Anything going on?
It's been probably close to a year, right?
I think it's probably last year.
Almost exactly a year.
I'm in so Cape Fear Soul Seekers has been disbanded. I'm sorry to hear that. No, no, it's we're all good. We I
Have rejoined another group called Erie Expeditions Paranormal
and
It's all good. And we're all still friends. We just don't do I'll still do some investigations, but it's just not gonna be under
Cape Fear Soul Seekers. Yeah, I'm involved in
Three productions
currently underway which none of them like to talk about. So are you bringing them up?
I will, you just want to know what's going on. Alright I'll guess. Kind of give you an
idea what's going on. We should guess. The Queen. No. Iron Man 5. They're all, one of
them is paranormal, two of them are paranormal related, one of them is gaming related. Oh
Right, you were telling us about this yesterday.
Halo. The Halo TV show. Peter Jackson.
What? Halo?
Peter Jackson didn't direct that, he was just gonna.
No, it's gonna be Magic the Gathering related.
Oh, okay.
It doesn't take anything to get you to talk about the things that you say you can't talk about.
Well, I can't give like specific names of the shows.
Oh, okay.
Based on...
That's what your NDA says?
Yes. Stranger Things.
No. What do you think of Stranger Things?
right how much are they getting wrong?
So much I could talk about. Yeah, let's talk about it. That's why you're here.
Well, but they're not doing a... well, they're doing more like dimensional
mm-hmm rather than paranormal. Do you have any interest in dimensional
television? No, no, I saw like the first couple of seasons of Stranger Things.
I thought it got, this is just my humble opinion, so I just thought it got too
chick-flicky. I agree, too much kissing. There's a girly stuff in the recent
seasons. The first two seasons, great. Yeah, they really jumped the shark in the third.
The most recent season, I heard that, well I saw some of it because my girlfriend was
watching it, girl show, but I mean a lot of these episodes are an
hour and a half long and more than half of the episode is like romantic.
And look, people are gonna hate on me for those, for my opinion, but I'm just, that's
just the way I feel.
Yeah, I mean I think-
You better buckle up, because people are gonna be fucking mad about that.
Yeah, they are. Look, they are on Facebook, good lord. People are like, "You can't say
that about, that's great, it's the best show ever." I'm like, "I mean, it's great, I'm
glad you like it, I just didn't like it after the second season."
Yeah, I didn't, I think it's, I think what they're doing now is wrong. I think it's a
bad show.
I mean, who sings, who sings-
exactly because i don't know about the dying
it was a never-ending ending story last episode i saw a a that was not good
it just was not it that was not for me so i'm what's like that what's the piece of
media that you've watched where when you like it has to do the paranormal and
you've watched it you're like wow that's exactly my experience what's the closest
to like all that is my experience with the time of mom
uh... fictional fictional like a ghost of the not a good production that you've
made a tax folks
or close to the real deal. I respect the Ghost Hunter people.
Not in a documentary, but in like...
Like something like The Conjuring or The Exorcist.
Um...
Closest to your experience.
Shining was...
You know, that hotel is really, legitimately haunted.
Right, but it does not necessarily actually flood blood.
You know, but he had experiences there when the writer...
Who wrote that?
Stephen King.
had and other people tons of people have had experiences there I would love to
investigate that place. God that would be awesome. That would be incredible. It would be insane. Maybe next time.
Yeah. Is that the Overlook Hotel is it? That's the fictional. It's Stanley's. The old Stanley Hotel.
Oh okay. And that place it's beautiful but it's it's it's what's the Overlook Hotel?
Overlook Hotel is the name of the hotel in the story but there's a real hotel.
But something like the Shining to some extent I've had you know maybe something
I don't like the show.
I assume you're talking about the ghost stuff in there, but is the psychic stuff too?
Maybe a little bit of both, yeah.
But more of the ghost.
Do you think that there's anything specifically paranormal, psychic about people being twins?
Never really thought of it.
But here's something else to think about, though.
We hadn't even talked about, and I'm sorry for changing.
Oh, no, it's fine.
We'll come back to twins.
So there are conductors that enhance possible paranormal activity.
Water, limestone is a big conductor.
Limestone?
Limestone.
So I should have mentioned this earlier when we were talking about things just when we
were hanging out.
But those can actually also be debunkers as well.
If that is in the area.
When you're seeing these shows and you know, if you see people are having, you know, sightings
and this that and the other, but they don't know for sure, you know, then you do your
research on what's around it.
So with the Stanley Hotel, you know, how much research have they done to see if it's definitely
haunted or if there's other factors that might be causing particular sightings.
So I don't know, I'm just saying.
- Sure.
- I just wanted to, I know that's got a little sidetracked
a little bit, but I just wanted to throw that out there
'cause I think it's worth, you know.
- Limestone's interesting because is it just,
does that lead to more, there are more kind of haunted
places that have large limestone deposits nearby?
- From my knowledge, possibly, yes.
- Okay.
- Like a haunted bathroom?
- Well that's, I mean, bathrooms at Bloody Mary.
Yeah, Bloody Mary, there's a lot of limestone buildup.
Moaning Myrtle.
Yeah, stuff like that.
Moaning Myrtle, where was that from?
Harry Potter.
Yeah.
Hogwarts.
I heard Hogwarts is actually built on a limestone deposit.
You should investigate Hogwarts.
That'd be great.
I am a huge fan of that movie.
It's one of my, or the whole series.
Harry Potter.
Harry Potter, yeah.
I thought the third one was the best.
The movie at least.
I don't know.
That's a toss up.
I mean, they're all good, in my opinion.
The first one's good.
Christmas.
was great. Christmas happens in pretty much every single one. Yeah, but it's more of a
Christmas movie. It's one of the big wizarding things. I like Goblet of Fire, I thought that
was good. Yeah, the Triwizard Tournament. That is a really good one. Speaking of Christmas,
we learned about something recently, the Anti-Christmas. Never heard of it. I mean go ahead. Anti-Claus.
You want to bring it up and then look at me and Caleb? I forgot a lot of it. Why did you
it up then. I thought we were going to talk about this. Why did we talk about it? When
did we talk about talking about this? I don't know. Is this a ghost thing? You said it.
You did say it. I didn't say let's bring it up on the podcast. I said well we'll show
him that. He doesn't even know what we're talking about. I have no clue. We discovered
the short story which we'll send this over to you I'm sure. We can maybe talk about it
at length at some point but we found a website of this person who purports to be a paranormal
investigator who has traveled to the North Pole many times and met Santa Claus and also
I think I have heard of that.
I didn't know it was called "Anti-Claus" though, but I think I've heard...
His organization is Mystic Investigations and his name is Xavier Remington.
I've heard... that's what I've heard of.
Really? You've heard of Xavier Remington?
I think so.
Wow. Because we stumbled across it and we were like so intrigued.
We were trying to figure out Santa Claus' birthday.
Can you pull that up?
I don't have Wi-Fi right now.
Also, just based on something we were talking about earlier, did you say that you have a
SoundCloud of you being possessed by a spirit?
No, I have a SoundCloud clip.
So my SoundCloud is Davida Studios, I think.
Or Matt Davida.
Either one.
It is a, we have caught a disembodied spirit at a cement plant that we investigated years
ago.
I thought you had maybe audio of you in the throes of inviting...
No, I got taken over at that plant.
But you don't have a recording of that?
No, but we have a recording...
I'll send you this, Matt. This is mysticinvestigations.com
We have a recording of who we believe took me over, which was a female spirit.
And you can hear it on my SoundCloud page of her.
We asked, "Am I the only person talking to you?"
And there was five of us in this particular section, and she said yes.
So you got a disembodied voice.
Women be saying that though, "Am I the only one you're talking to?"
They say yes.
Yeah, I do.
You never know.
Yeah, that is true.
Yeah.
Well, she answered appropriately then.
You didn't see her though?
No, no. We just, but we definitely heard her. Like, we heard her.
Did she have a hot voice? Kind of breathy? Like,
yes
very close to that
close to that
maybe it was him playing a trick on you
it was more of like a
yes
wow
oh crap
it doesn't matter
that could be a mystic
wait this wasn't a mystic
that took over you was it
no what's the difference between a mystic
I saw a mystic
when we investigated Lake Shawnee with EEP about a month and a half ago. Now I love
you've been a part of how many different organizations have you been a part of
through the year? A few. A few. I remember you had you had ASS which was still one of the
best names ever. Assessing Supernatural Spirits. Acknowledging Supernatural Spirits.
Assessing could have been even another organization too. It could have been. And now you have EEP
which is like that's not me okay oh yeah which is kind of like maybe yeah
yeah maybe so it's a genius Robby Spencer is the founder of that group is good guy
he's aware of the fact that it's it is a oh yeah oh absolutely I think so yeah I
tried to come up with one paranormal encounter nocturnal investigation squad
And what would that be?
Penis.
Oh, Lord.
I love it.
Isn't that a little...
You love that?
Isn't that maybe a little too crass?
Maybe people stop taking you so professionally?
Maybe even ghosts might not...
Maybe ghosts would be homophobic.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, exactly.
Here's the thing.
'Cause if you hate a penis, if you...
You're gay if you're gay and you think penis.
I had the group called Ass, and people still invited me into their homes.
So, you know, it just depends on the person.
Of course some people are not going to want us to come in there with that name.
Everyone has an ass, a penis.
Your reputation is what's most important.
That's true.
If people are like, "Okay, there's this group called Ass.
They're very respectful.
They've done tons of successful investigations.
We should probably invite them over."
Versus somebody who's like, "I've heard of this group Ass.
They're nasty."
Exactly.
They run around and they grab the ghosts and they do nasty things.
Maybe we don't want to.
This was 10 or 15 years ago.
We didn't really have Google reviews and all this stuff, you know, when I had ass.
Yeah, exactly.
So acknowledging supernatural spirits, that sort of implies the existence of a natural
spirit, right?
Yes.
So what is the difference between a supernatural spirit and a regular spirit?
Or are all spirits supernatural?
No, I think it all has to do with the level of intelligence.
That's just my personal opinion, you know.
Okay, so like a dog spirit.
- It's gonna be other peoples with other opinions, you know?
- Oh, but is it, yeah, I guess every,
I mean, you could just say every spirit is supernatural.
- I mean, I feel like maybe if this is my thinking,
maybe right now we have natural spirits inside us,
and once they're out earthbound walking around,
that's kind of a supernatural phenomenon.
- Right, so all spirits, a natural spirit usually needs,
or I guess 100% of the time needs a body to inhabit,
but a supernatural spirit can live outside of a body.
- It's not natural for a spirit to live outside of a body.
- Maybe a supernatural spirit might have more abilities
to travel in and out of realms.
- Spider-rooms.
- Yeah, realms.
Okay, so I have a question.
Is there any kind of wall that a spirit cannot pass through?
- Well, I think there are,
again, this goes into supernatural versus not.
So we've talked about this before,
whether how strong your will was when you were alive
might have factor into how strong your capabilities are
when you're in your next life.
- When you say how strong your will is,
do you mean like your--
- Your will to live.
- Okay, so you're-- - Your will to drive.
- People who have high vital energy.
- That are driven and-- - Yeah.
Versus someone who like say--
- Likes to sleep on the couch all day and not do anything.
- Yeah, or maybe someone who-- - Lazy people,
when they die they just, they're gone.
I'm just, this is a possibility.
Or like someone who just gave up on life and slipped away.
And just gave up, they said,
I don't want to live anymore, and they just slipped away.
So people without the will to live.
And they, yeah.
It could possibly not have quite the capabilities
that someone who's driven and strong will.
I guess if somebody--
Possibly, this is just a theory.
Yeah, with that theory, so people who commit suicide,
that represents to me very little will to live.
So are these people, they're just basically nothing.
Now, you say that, they may have different capabilities
because of their anger.
- True.
- So, if someone gets really angry enough to kill themselves,
they might be-- - They might have
different types of capabilities in their afterlife.
- It could, it takes a pretty strong will
to kill yourself too, maybe it's a different kind of will,
the will to die.
- But it's an angry will.
So you might only have one set of capabilities
in your afterlife, which would be anger related.
- Yeah, Hulk style.
I guess I'm trying to arrive at, we know what kind of people do become spirits and
little girls who have big wills to live often become spirits
but if you, I guess I'm curious what kind of person is just, they die and there's
just, they're just... Yeah let's talk about the kind of person who there's just
nothing. They're just dust, they don't exist anymore. No spirit, no ghost. Their spirit if it does exist is
basically stuck in time like a like a particle from a sneeze and you just walk right through it.
You're probably walking through billions of them every day.
Just losers.
So those could be possibly your residual type haunts.
Hobo.
Instead of an intelligent haunt.
A hobo is good.
The difference between a residual haunt and an intelligent haunt is an intelligent haunt
will have the capabilities to respond to you if you call out to them.
A residual haunt might be, say you had a routine and every morning you went downstairs, you
made a cup of coffee and you got your paper and you read your paper. That
might be your loop for the rest of the life. A paranormal team might
see this or witness this but that's all that they're gonna get. Right, so what
about, yeah I guess what about like a homeless, a hobo, punk rocker, a junkie, a pothead.
These people are just gonna kind of just a doper dissipate into just...
They, well I feel like some of them have pretty strong wills.
Again it depends on the will.
Yeah.
Like a punk rocker would have the will to dismantle the system.
So like break glass and, well glass, like break glass of establishments, like windows
and targets.
To somebody that had those lives, you can think of it this way, they might have a whole
different perspective in the afterlife and they might want to try to communicate with
you in any way, shape or form.
Yeah.
pops. We've talked about the pops. Although it's been probably 20 minutes since we heard
one. Also did the air conditioning turn on? It did. That's okay. It's fine. It doesn't
pick up too much. Not too worried about it. I was just worried. I heard the AC starting
up. I thought maybe it was the spirit. Those ways to communicate could vary depending on
how you were or in this light. Like the ghost of a hipster might be like "Latte please!"
I would be because I'm more Don Pardo. Well that could be if Don Pardo was a hipster.
Well if Don Pardo died. Well he did. If you said a lot, if you said latte, since I'm kind
of like you know a dad joke guy, I'd be like a little a. Yeah. A little a. I'm glad you
saved that. I know I found it in there. Bump that mic. That's right. Yeah. Okay so that's
That's interesting.
Or the ghost of a woman might be like, "Ooooh!"
A hot woman.
"Ooooh!"
A ghost of a lunch lady might be like, "Ooooh!"
This sounds more like their ghost of the studio audience.
"Here's your lunch!
Here's your lunch!
I'm hungry!
Lunch!
Ugly lunch!"
You know what would be interesting to me would be to collectively save, you know, all of these,
if we could get everybody to communicate and work together, save and share their findings
to see if those match up what we're talking about.
Why are people so resistant to doing that?
Oh, who knows.
Why is there not an open database
where we can post detail--
I believe there is.
--and find the overlap?
You could probably go to certain sites
to be able to find certain EVPs that you might want to hear.
But some groups are super secretive about what they do.
I still get the point in that.
You're keeping all this great information for yourself.
Declassify it.
There's some, there's some, it was a ghost.
There's some things I've done, we also operate on a confidentiality, like a doctor, you know,
we operate.
Oh, so it's kind of like a medical record.
Yeah, for some.
You ask permission.
If they say we don't care what you do with it, then we'll put it out there for anybody
who wants to hear it.
We used to have it on our websites and stuff, which are no longer up, but because I'm not
really, I'm with a different group now.
So if we were allowed to post, we would share away, but not all groups think the same.
Well, what about like a resource kind of for other investigators, like a database?
I would love to see that.
I don't know that there is one, but I think that's a great idea.
I think that's something we could move toward in the future.
Yeah, that'd be great.
I had a question, just this popped into my head.
When, do you think that,
can different spirits, do they interact with each other?
Or do they really just see us?
I think, if it was me, based on my experience,
and now granted, you guys know,
now the audience doesn't necessarily know,
I've been doing this for over 17 years now.
So I've experienced a lot, you know?
And a lot of my opinions I'm giving on this podcast
are based on my experiences, right?
So with that being said, yes,
I believe in both of what you said.
- Gotcha.
So they can interact with each other, they can.
- I don't believe all, but I believe some.
- They can get in fights and stuff.
- I don't know about fights.
But I mean, who knows?
- Yeah, they're on the same team.
- Look, maybe it's like prison.
Maybe you get there and they're like,
did you yeah who's the toughest guy maybe you gotta go hang out with these but our
angels and demons fighting so I mean if they are then I like the prophecy yeah
so then why can't any other spirits fight amongst themselves yeah yeah that's I
guess what I'm saying yeah you know maybe you do if you do something if you
have such a shit life or you have so little will maybe yeah if you're just
like I'd be you beat up or human human dirt or shut down maybe they show you
- Yeah, where you can't communicate if you wanted to.
- Yeah. - Yes, that's true.
- Someone they keep talking over you, trying to go,
hello, I'm here, I wanna communicate with you,
and another ghost is going,
(imitates ghost)
over you. - That'd be the Karen ghost.
- Yeah, exactly.
(laughing)
- Do you, so when you talk about strong-willed people,
I'm thinking about, just personally,
like, The Rock is gonna have a serious,
we should be afraid when he dies, probably.
- We absolutely should.
- He's like, that guy's got so much will.
- Yeah, 'cause we're at the place he's gonna hunt.
- Oh my God. - Hey, you know what,
I really hope he doesn't die in his Scorpion King costume.
You know what happens when you grab the rock's ass, right?
What?
You hit rock bottom.
Oh man, that is true.
What happens when you grab his cock?
You...
Oh no.
Come.
You come.
Oh god.
Cock bottom?
Is that cock bottom?
Cock rock 'em.
I think it's rock cock.
I want to change the subject here.
Please.
Okay, and a few more.
Actually, you know what, now that I think...
We were kind of doing something awesome there for a little bit.
I was going to give you a clip on YouTube, but okay.
But I do like the idea of, you know, being scared of the rock spirits.
Yeah, because he's somebody who, he wakes up, he sleeps two hours a night.
And his side partner, Kevin.
Kevin Hart.
Absolutely. Can you imagine him as a spirit?
Yeah.
well but he would small in spirit but not small in
stature maybe he would
he would get bigger and persona and everything else you know but that'd be
i mean as far as ghosts that haunt your house and your life kevin hart's gotta be up
there because of the comedy yeah i think and i will say that he's large in spirit
i would not mind he's a big little man
i would not mind him at all he's hilarious i would not mind him at all he doesn't like kevin hart
i would be really scared of the rock as a ghost especially if i had grabbed his
cock before he died. I think he might have a bone to pick with me. Well before you died
if you grabbed his butt you really have hit rock bottom. That spear's gonna latch onto
you. That's right. I'm gonna latch onto him. Watch out The Rock I'm coming for you. Oh
God. Why'd you demonstrate on Patrick? You said I look like The Rock. You look exactly
like The Rock to me. Wow. But I am really curious if what you think. Oh it's Dwayne's Johnson.
it's dwines johnson it's dwines rock hard on that because he did it we have to go
we're gonna have a lot of that i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't
know we do we need is rock hard johnson we do we need is johnson
that you are going to be the rock of all of the time
that's good
uh... really good
uh... what do you think do you think uh... what's going on with witchcraft
uh...
Is that real and if it is?
Are you a good witch?
I'm not a... I don't claim to do any...
What's wrong with you?
Well he is sort of...
Oh no, I believe in it. I don't want anything to do with it.
Sure.
It's just out of my...
Do you believe that there's such thing as a...
as he said so rudely like a good witch?
Do you think that's even real?
I believe there's a good witch and a bad witch.
Uh-huh.
Just one of each?
No, I mean I believe in good and bad witches.
Oh, gotcha.
I believe they exist.
And it's still going on?
Witches are still doing their thing?
The practice of that, absolutely. I have friends that are claimed to be...
Oh, okay.
I guess what we've always learned from media is you can tell the difference physically.
Right? So a good witch is blonde, and a bad witch is usually...
No, I haven't heard that. I know you can tell them in their demeanor.
Yeah, but they obviously...
Right, an evil witch is usually like...
Well, you say that, but not necessarily.
nice to you.
True, like Hansel and Gretel.
Yeah.
And then build a voodoo doll of you.
Oh man.
Oh yeah, just a ploy to get your hair.
That's something we haven't talked about.
We talked a lot last time.
Yeah.
We had a lot of things, but voodoo was not ever...
We talked about cryptids last time.
Yeah, we did a lot of cryptid stuff.
I want to cover new ground too.
What is your feeling on voodoo?
So we were talking about the Ouija board too.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't think we talked about Ouija boards last time.
Let's talk Ouija first.
So here's my take on the Ouija.
This is my opinion, this is for anybody listening, and I stand by this opinion.
The Ouija board, I don't practice, I've used it once on an investigation and I'll never
use it again.
What you're doing is real.
I don't care what people say in the comments.
This is my opinion on this and I stand by it.
If you use this thing as a tool, you better know how to use it, and you better know, I
would strongly advise to use it for a specific, if you're trying to reach someone's name,
reach that, try to, because if you're just calling out to anything and anybody, you're
opening Pandora's box. You really are. Especially if you're in a home where you think it's
haunted and you've already had experiences of it being haunted. That's
just a that's the same thing as us paranormal investigators doing an EVP
session. Same thing. Mm-hmm. Okay so yes it's a game by the sense of it being a
game. It comes in a box. Yeah but what you're doing... Hasbro does make it. Yeah.
Yeah but what you're doing is real. Yeah. So that's that's my take on the Ouija.
So if you if you do use a Ouija board in a place where you think it's haunted you
should know the spirits name first? I would know everything about anything
you're doing, every bit of research. That's an experts only. Yeah, research
everything first before you use it, and know how to close it. Yeah, you know. I used a Ouija
board in high school at my girlfriend's house.
It was me, her, and her friend, and we were
doing it and we got we only got to the name of the spirit and it was gub g-u-b
now does that now gub is that that strike you as cuz that we would that's one why
we stopped so that's not even almost a human what you do is Google it and see
what all comes up yeah I haven't done that
gub paranormal okay ghost were you using it in the mirror and it was you're
talking to a bug yeah maybe so here's why when I used when we used it so I've
just googled "gub ghost" and what comes up is "privately made firearm" and it's a
bunch of pictures of 3d printed guns. So here's what I...
Well I asked for the name and it said "gub ghost". I'm sorry I cut you go ahead.
I cut you off. Well I'm just saying that you know it could be a clue it's
intentionally leading you down a rabbit hole. It could be. So here's why I
say that so when we used it and I used it with someone who knew how to open it
and close it. A lot of these people using these things don't close it. When you say
open it and close it it folds like a like a settler's of the tan board huh doesn't
it just fold? You have to like close out the game I don't know how to do that but
I don't know I don't remember this was 15 years ago I don't remember last week so
that's hilarious I saw that. That's what came up when I googled "gub paranormal"
So when we used it all mine did was come up with we did the thing and I was
like nothing's going on it's just a bunch of numbers right I wrote those
numbers down in sequence right and I googled them when I got home and there
are all kinds of religious and satanic meanings to those numbers I never used
the Ouija board. While we're on the on the subject of the Ouija boards we
went a couple weeks ago we were in Portland Oregon we went to a goth night
club called the coffin club. I want to go. It was good it was fun.
The dance floor was a Ouija board.
As long as you don't have the planchette, is that fine?
I think that's fine.
But that's just my, again, I would love to have a Ouija board, like those carpets you
can get.
Those are kind of just, that's not a real...
They're really cool.
As long as you don't have multiple people's hands.
It can't contact...
It's the planchette is where the magic is, right?
Right, just, well I won't say that.
But yes, yes, you have to, to my knowledge of it, you have to initiate it.
Or someone's wearing like clear shoes.
Like planchette type shoes.
Yeah.
I mean as long as they're not, if they're sitting there walking on it and talking, you know,
trying to call something out, they just walk across it, you know.
And again, it could be in a totally different context because it's just been painted on
there.
It may not be the true...
Yeah, I guess that's right.
It's like a replica of it.
You say that everybody has some element of spirit in them.
That's what you believe, right?
I believe.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think that's a pretty common belief.
So...
not necessarily religions, just spirits. Yeah, of course. People oftentimes have a hard time
getting in touch with themselves. Do you think it is a worthwhile exercise to sit
there, just one man, sitting at a Ouija board asking yourself some
questions? I don't even think you need the Ouija board to do that. Really? You know, you can
meditate. That's what meditation is. Absolutely, meditation. So you would consider that a form of, it could be a
a meditation. You could be a meditator. Now, now we can take this on a different, you
know, if you're trying to get in touch with your your inner self, meditation, but
if you think something is attached to you or something of that nature, you still
don't need the Ouija board. Put up some audio devices, you know, I don't
recommend doing any of that stuff alone, you know. If you do, if one of our
listeners does find themselves the vehicle on which a spirit decides to
attach themselves what is the best way to get that spirit off of your person?
First and foremost sage is good. Sage. And what are they not like about sage
specifically? The smell. Just you know. Just stinks to them. It's just kind of the
opposite of sulfur. So spirits hate Thanksgiving. That's probably one of the
most interesting statements I've heard so far this year. I think most spirits
are probably Halloween lovers. Yeah. Oh is that why Thanksgiving... Who doesn't want to hear an oonga boonga from an EVP?
Thank you. Is that why Thanksgiving is after Halloween? Because you're cleansing.
You're cleansing. What is Thanksgiving but a giant Native American burial ground?
Oh my god. So some cultures may love, some cultural spirits may love
Thanksgiving. Some might not. Some might hate it. Maybe a pilgrim. I feel like a pilgrim
spirit will like Thanksgiving a lot more than a Native American. Yeah. Or a
hungry spirit. Yeah. But going back to get rid of things,
There's, you can, depending on your religion,
there's demonologists in every,
they're called different things in every religion.
You know, you can have people come bless your home.
You can have people, you can,
there's things you could do
that I don't necessarily recommend.
Like, I know, I've heard of, you know,
beating pots and pans, you know,
randomly at different hours of the night.
But I don't know if that's a good or a bad thing,
because depending on the spirit,
it might just make 'em more mad.
- And you might get a neighbor attached to you.
Or the cops.
You might get handcuffs attached to you.
If you're in an apartment building, I wouldn't know if I would recommend that.
But sage for sure, crystals, there's different types of crystals.
Which crystals are the best?
I can't not remember.
You'd have to go to a crystalologist?
Well you could just Google crystal protection.
Okay.
If a spirit is attached to you, is there somewhere that you can go that the spirit could not follow you?
Like a spirit car wash?
Well if you were like, if you were, yeah, well so better ideas than what you guys both said
is maybe like the bottom of the ocean or outer space. Do you think a spirit could follow
you to either of those places?
I would say yes.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think there's any, any, again, if the spirit can attach, if the spirit can attach
itself to you, it's gotta be an intelligent enough spirit. See I also feel that, again,
This is based on my experience, okay?
So I also feel that some spirits are locked and can't go anywhere.
They are like in a house and that's where they're going to be.
I don't know why.
I have no idea why.
But I feel and I know that other spirits have freedom to go wherever just because of all
the EVP we've gotten all over the place in my time.
So with that, yes, I feel like they could, you know, now they may be stronger in to be
able to communicate in different places. Uh-huh. Just because of the elements
around them. Yeah. You know, the conduits around them. Uh-huh. I, because I have maybe
an idea that if we can, if we, if people are being attached on by demonic or
scary spirits, I mean, maybe we can send these people to the moon, de-attach, use
sage up there, bring the people back down, and maybe we can just send all the evil
spirits out to another planet or the moon. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's kind of what I was thinking.
Yeah, do you just get a Ghostbuster trap that might be easier?
You do you know what that is though it goes no idea if I was to guess
It's I'm sure some it would be some sort of energy based
Yeah, you need DARPA for all that matter. It's like energy, you know
vacuum into a hard drive essentially but with it on a ghost level right using
using dark matter yeah yeah technology this is a question I've always had
which I don't know if that even exists dark matter technology do you I called
voodoo oh wait let's say we didn't we left food I want to talk about voodoo
again do you have you ever had a voodoo so if somebody look if somebody
offense but I'd be a pretty easy voodoo well sure you know but if somebody was
to make a voodoo doll of me, I would love for them to fix my back.
I have the same problem, yeah.
If you're gonna stab me in the back, could you do it with acupuncture ways and actually
hit the right spot?
Both of you, I guess because of your family, might be good candidates for a head shrinker.
What if there's a look-alike of some-- right?
[laughter]
He thinks I have a big head.
Caleb's face right then was priceless.
You guys are like Crash Test Dunks, all of you guys maybe.
I think I'm a normal person.
You are, no.
You look like a bug.
You are an ant.
You look exactly like a bug.
Yeah, that's why a voodoo person would not want to shrink my head because-
Because there's nothing, you already have the worst physical situation.
They would use your head to shrink-
Are we talking Beetlejuice head shrinkers?
Yeah, yeah.
They would use your head to teach people how to shrink heads.
your head is the anamorphic it's the the second to last stage in the anamorphic
book about shrinking heads yeah and bug okay yeah both so anamorphic but not
about it's an animal of a shrunken head turning into a bug. Are head shrinkers real?
I've never heard of them. I think I've seen there's photos of shrunken heads.
I mean I've never heard of them other than they would take they would take
heads and they'll... so that was a real reference then in Beetlejuice.
Oh yeah.
Can I pose a scenario here, a voodoo scenario?
So somebody really hates, let's say Pitbull, okay?
Somebody really hates the singer/rapper Mr. Worldwide Pitbull.
They make a voodoo doll of Pitbull, they're sticking pins in his chest and his heart, okay?
And somewhere...
Someone is going to hear this and do this.
I hope nobody does this.
Don't try this at home.
Don't do that to Pitbull.
And then somewhere in New York City, a Pipple impersonator dies.
Do you think this is possible?
Do you think maybe that someone who looks a lot like the Voodoo Doll...
You know, especially if they didn't really know what they were doing.
I would think that you would need to know a social security number.
Yeah, or an email address.
Or for Voodoo Dolls, don't you need like a strand of hair?
Well, Pipple has no hair.
Right, that's why Cameron expertly picked him as an example.
Maybe up there.
You don't know what he's got down there.
Yeah, but what if he doesn't?
That's true, he could have had it all laser removed.
Here's my theory, is the more...
No, he's got a little beard, he's got a little chin thing.
Yeah, that's a tattoo.
My thought is the more...
They call me Mr. Cleaner at work.
[laughter]
Because you're a janitor?
No, because I clean cars all day.
Oh, okay, I was close. I didn't know what you did for a living.
That's alright, but they call me Mr. Cleaner because Mr. Clean is already taken.
Right.
- That makes sense.
Oh, cleaner than clean.
- Yes, yes.
- Right, okay, so check this out.
The more DNA that you can get from a person,
the more accurate the voodoo doll is.
So basically, if you take their eyes, their nose,
their mouth, their legs, their arms,
eventually you will have-- - They might die.
- Perfectly, well then you,
but you replace all their organs perfectly.
- And then that voodoo doll will be able, yeah, exactly.
- And they immediately, they feel it.
yeah yeah that's a good point. But their original form is so like
is so injured that it might as well not even exist.
Or it just becomes a clone then at that point.
A clone where the original is intact. Oh my god, let's talk about clones.
Well what about a clone voodoo?
Yeah. Like you're doing voodoo on one.
If you did voodoo on a clone, would the clone and the original person get hurt?
just blew my mind. Also, has anyone ever done something really nice to a voodoo doll?
Like I said, like fix my back. Yeah, that's what he's begging for. Yeah, please.
Do you know any info on clones? Are they doing human cloning? I believe
they... because they clone to sheep. So without getting too much into politics,
there are people that think that Biden is not Biden. Oh, I'm one of those people.
I think he's branded.
But they believe that the Biden versus the Biden that was before the presidency
It's obvious.
Biden is not an imposter.
Especially recently. He was 600 years old six months ago and now he's doing backflips.
Yeah.
Makes no sense.
I'm just saying. I don't know.
What do you think of the theory that...
But I believe cloning is possible in humans. I absolutely believe that.
It's definitely possible. I just think that some people think that no one would ever cross that ethical line.
I think we've already crossed it.
What do you think of the theory that, speaking of people in power, that some
photos came out some weeks ago that were photorealistic, hyper-realistic masks of
world leaders Trump, Biden, Jill Stein, and they were basically saying these people
are not actually even real people. Different actors are playing these people.
That's why they act different. I don't think they're actors. I think they're alien
shapeshifters. Yeah, so that's more... you're more in that school of
thought than a lot of things. Look, you know, people couldn't... I don't... and some things I
joke around a lot about, some things I'm not, you know. I mean, it would not...
let's put it this way, if it comes out and that the truth and that's happened, I
would not be shocked. The truth was really revealed. I wouldn't be shocked. Not one bit. You'd probably be
shocked if it turned out that there were no alien shapeshifters. Oh absolutely.
Which how do you even prove that? Exactly. I guess you would have to have like a very trustworthy person say it.
Jollibee is an alien shapeshifter. Oh yeah, let's hear this theory.
So we talked, are you sure we got a minute? Yeah tell us. So I saw that video and
and my theory on Jollibee is that Jollibee is an alien shapeshifter. The
reason that all their food tastes so good at that restaurant versus anywhere else
that food at that restaurant was banned from his home planet. Why was it
banned from his home planet? I don't know. Because it's human food.
They banned it but all the UFO sightings we're seeing, you know,
they're transports. They have been opening up a lot of new locations,
they've been franchising out a lot more. There you go.
spreading like a virus and hey you know what good I'm not complaining yeah it's
just you know one next to my house the first thing that popped in my head when I
saw y'all's videos like that guy's an alien I mean you know come on now who
else is gonna come up with that but an alien I mean yeah Filipino where are
based out of? The Philippines. I was like, well that makes sense now. Why would you randomly
say that? He has some ideas about race. I'm a big respecter of the Philippines. There
you go. They're going to say I'm a big respecter of race. That too. What else? Here's one.
Do you think robots could be real?
They are.
They are real.
Like I mean like.
But now.
Oh my.
You're so pitbull.
Like that kind of robot.
But our, what do they call them?
Cyborgs.
No, Robotronics.
Robotronics.
Are Robotronics real?
That's an alien race.
Really?
Okay.
Oh yeah, we were talking about that earlier.
What makes them Robotronics?
I don't know that much about Robotronics.
You just know their name.
And I'm not even sure I'm saying that right.
a name for AI race of alien species you could probably google that. What do you say to the
person who thinks... supposedly out there anyway... who like that ghosts and spirits and demons and
aliens and AI is all within the purview of of human consciousness and that and that there's
nothing outside of this presence which is the human spirit. I'm talking to a friend of mine
who's in the film industry and we're talking about doing a show...
To your point.
...would be a fifth production about how all of this is interconnected.
Mm-hmm. But what do you say to the person who says, "Easy answer for why all that's interconnected is because it's all within our minds."
well as in there's no actual phenomena happening outside of our perception.
Outside of the inexplicable nature of human consciousness. That's
something I'd have to give a little more thought on. Yeah I think you could also
ask that question it doesn't have to be about aliens and werewolves or whatever
you could probably say the same thing about hamburgers and hot dogs. Or just
life in general. I think yeah I think that's kind of a... No one is wondering where those things come from.
i am
so wait where do i think i'll have to wait he he really wants to know where's
the beef
that's right
you never know what you sell hamburgers yeah you look like a burger king guy
do you think that if he died he would make a ghost or is he like too weak
willed and kind of just like a dust speck in the universe?
let me tell you something, i work close to nothing. I work close to nothing.
let me tell you i've seen little guys
beat the crap out of big huge bouncers in my days so...
Not this little guy.
Are you talking about in another realm?
No, I'm talking about right here.
Like when I used to own bet by my bar I have seen...
I have seen people that you would not think were able to do things.
Have you ever seen those videos where people like lift up a car?
Yeah.
Have you ever seen a guy like me have sex with a woman like Doja Cat?
Pornhub.
(laughter)
There's everything on porno, man.
You saw him fucking Doja Cat on porno?
I mean, it might as well have been him, you know.
(laughter)
Fucking Doja Cat, that's...
Oh my god.
(laughter)
Matt, have you ever seen...
Is that kind of thing possible in another realm?
Hey, look, they say that we all have an identical twin in this world.
I have many doppelgangers.
All of my doppelgangers are on Pornhub.
Yeah.
(laughter)
That's probably the worst place to find your doppelganger.
I mean, look, I'm just your average bald guy.
So there's a million of those on Pornhub.
I'm always searching just your average bald guy.
Me too.
You know, I'm not. I just happen to kind of scroll.
They should make a program where you, like NBA2K,
you just scan your face in and it finds the closest porn star. I'm trying to scroll through all of them.
But you're not allowed to scan your crush's face in. Or your crotch.
I have to scroll through all of them to find what I want to watch, you know, so they just happen to be, you know.
Is it mostly you're searching for stuff about ghosts and aliens or is it mostly normal stuff?
There's nothing normal on Pornhub. Sex is not normal. No, absolutely not.
Have you ever seen somebody die?
Um, yes. I've had, you know, I was a firefighter for 15 years.
Yeah. So, yeah.
Did you ever, do you feel like when you saw that happen, that maybe you felt like, when you've been around death-
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to get all serious all of a sudden.
No, you just answered Caleb's serious question.
Yeah, Caleb was the serious one.
I would have been offended if you had seen someone die and you said yes, but-
No, no, no, just straight up.
Is it?
Yes, on Pornhub.
(laughing)
- Touche, I see what you did there.
The circle is now complete.
- Bringing it back to seeing someone die.
- Yeah, so when you saw somebody die,
did you feel the sense that a spirit
was leaving or created or something?
Do you feel that when you're around death?
- No, at the time I'm just more concerned with--
- I wasn't able to save them.
- Gotcha.
- Than, you know, 'cause I didn't do my job.
- Yeah.
- You know, so.
- 'Cause you wonder about,
earlier that that one ounce or whatever that is in everybody that when you die
at thing I can't really exactly whatever the measure yeah that kind of that weight
I was wondering if if you're when you're around somebody who dies I guess we just
we can only speculate is it do you do you feel that weight leave the room or stay
in the room you know what I mean is that like the the pressure almost changes the
The times that it's happened to me, I've had, I think, one, two, two die in my arms.
I didn't think about that.
I'm thinking about a million other things.
Obviously, because a million other things were happening around us when we were on those.
So one of them died in my arm.
a few feet we were trying to save a lady that this is a period at my old studios
oh really somebody ran a stop sign killed this lady in her car. Oh that's awful.
I was the only firefighter and this guy that worked at the Good
Shepherd house that was behind the place he was a medic too we heard the noise
ran out tried to save her brought her back did CPR she came back for a few
seconds and then she just went. Wow. And we were still waiting on EMS at the
time. I had my, I had pulled my truck up to block the road because I had lights on my
truck and everything and and to keep it from anybody else you know coming to
interrupt the scene. So that was the second time. The first time it was that I
was actually on a call and we responded to a to a car accident at the Bradley
Creek Bridge. Wow. And it was she was she was basically DOA and we're pulling her
out of the car. There was nothing we could do. So you were a fire you were a
firefighter for many years right? About 14 or 15 years. 15 years and did you ever
have any paranormal experiences? Were you investigating when you were also a
firefighter? No, it all happened after. Okay yeah. And do you have but do you have it
did you have any experiences I mean I feel like firehouses are usually there's
some spirits around there. So we've investigated a firehouse. Really? Yeah.
Was it ever one that you we did not find anything in this particular fire?
Oh, no, did you ask them like has it they asked us to come passed away or anything?
They asked us to come investigate because really I was actually fired hearing an alarm or something
Well, they they thought they just didn't want to stay there overnight
There's people there so they asked the chief knew me through the fire department and asked and knew I was an investigator and
asked us to come in and investigate the place and
We didn't find anything. Nothing. Nothing. So what is that like that feeling of we just spent all this time money
Resources on an investigation. It's partly find anything. Is that is that ever disappointing or just we'll know again next time. No, so
This is what I don't like about the shows, you know
These shows have to deal with ratings and this that and the other so everything has to be exciting all the time
And it's just not the case
Folks it's not this is not how it
Yes, we have come across places that were haunted as shit, right?
But it's not like it's it doesn't happen every single it just doesn't happen. Yeah, you know, I'm sorry, but I'm I don't mean to spoil
You know
Most of the times we disprove and debunk things. Yeah, you know, we really do and
But you know, you know why and then people go why do you do it? Well
Because you know, it's a passion. We help the community. We give people peace of mind
We get to meet really interesting people we get to do things that a lot of people don't get to do
we get to go places a lot of people don't get to go and
All of that in my opinion is a part of it, you know, and we were talking about this earlier and
And I feel strongly about this as well. You know if you're wanting to be
Involved in the paranormal and to just go out and get scared and watch the little meters light up
You're missing the big picture.
Yeah.
And what I just said is all part of the big picture in my opinion.
It's better to come at it with like almost the scientific research minded.
Yeah.
Just everything.
You get to hear stories that aren't on the history books.
You know, you get to hear all kinds of cool hand-me-down stories.
And it's just, you know, it's just a great field to be in.
If you do it in a respectful manner, you will continue to get work
and you will eventually have an experience.
I think that that's a beautiful sentiment to maybe to wind down here.
I have a few final questions.
Have you ever investigated a place and been like, "Oh, thank God that place was not haunted."
Absolutely.
Yeah, it seemed like it was going to be very scary.
Let me tell you, just because a house is old doesn't mean it's going to be haunted.
That's a movie thing.
Nine times out of ten, usually it's land-related more than it is home-related.
There's a history with something that was there
before the house was even built.
Speaking of land, sea, kind of the opposite,
pirates seem to have a lot of stories about...
So you know what I'm talking about.
- Pirates are ghosts.
- They have a lot of stories about ghosts and stuff.
- I see what you did there.
- Do you, are pirates, is there certain professions,
I guess, that are just a little more prone to ghost,
becoming a ghost?
- To be a coroner.
- Probably a paranormal investigator.
- Do you, yeah, do you think you'll be a ghost
when you die?
- I hope so.
- Yeah, you seem to have a strong will.
- I mean, I'm--
- Do you think that maybe that's what all this is about,
is you're trying to accumulate data for when--
- The will to be a ghost later?
I mean, it very well could be,
because man, I'm gonna prank like all kinds of people
when I'm--
- If you prank me, and no offense,
I really hope you die before I do.
- No offense taken.
- And if you prank me, I would feel kind of flattered.
I guess if I ever get pranked by a ghost,
I'll probably assume it's you if you're--
- Honestly, there's all kinds of spirits out there.
They're not all angry or all sad,
like some people think there are.
There are playful spirits.
We've had people go to people's houses
where they just like to move objects, you know,
like pick up your car keys and set them somewhere else.
To me, that's a playful spirit.
That's not somebody out to try to get you, you know,
or whatever.
- Sure.
- How much dexterity does that take though
for a spirit to move a pair of keys?
- A lot.
- Yeah, I mean, it must take like centuries of discipline.
- Yeah, that's caveman Joseph being that.
- Did you ever see the movie "Ghost"
when it's with Patrick Swayze?
- Yes.
- Like magnify that times like a thousand, you know,
when he was learning how to ride on the,
you know, to move and pick up an object and move, yeah.
- Yeah, that's crazy. - Yeah, absolutely.
- I guess I, I mean, unless anyone, I have one--
- I have one more, you can end, I have one more.
Do you think there's any truth to the myths
of the Greek and Roman gods, Mount Olympus?
- I mean, there's, what was the volcano that,
you know, Pompeii, was that?
- Pompeii.
- I mean, that's, I think there's all,
I think there's connections there.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I guess it's a, there's so many stories, you know, Cyclopses.
I think there's some truth. You know, stories get twisted over time.
You know, you've seen, you know, you've heard jokes about the grapevine where it says
something at the beginning of the grapevine, by the time it gets to the end, it's, you know,
it's completely, you know, skewed, you know, so, but there's still some truth to it.
So I think there's some truth to it.
Yeah, to any of those myths.
I agree, I think there's some kind of...
Yeah, I guess every myth has its similar kind of grooves to it.
Definitely.
But yeah, I guess my last question that I have is, what do you think would happen if
an Autobot vs. a Decepticon?
I mean, Octopus Prime would just kill everybody.
Octopus Prime?
Optimus.
Yeah.
Well, I guess...
I think that wraps it up.
Yeah, I mean, Matt, you go ahead and plug your shit.
So, oh gosh, I don't even know where to start.
Go check out EEP.
Robbie Spencer is the founder of that group.
Where can you find EEP?
Facebook.
I think they have a website, but definitely on...
Remind us what that stands for.
Erie Expeditions Paranormal.
Okay, cool.
They're based out of Fuquay, but we go pretty much any...
We're going a lot of places.
We were at Lake Shawnee Abandoned Music Park about a month and a half ago.
And is that...
You have public footage of that yet, or is that coming out somewhere?
We're working on it.
Cool.
I am not in a, I don't run a group.
I am, that is his group.
He's the founder.
I am an investigator in that group.
A good group, good people, a diverse group.
Just it's, it's just a great bunch.
Um, if we do another one, I might have more info on the four
productions that I'm working on.
I'll say three of them are paranormal related and one of them is gaming related.
And as soon as I have information on those to where you can go check out trailers.
Then we'll do another episode.
Yeah, absolutely.
Keep an eye out.
Keep an eye to the sky.
Right, right.
And I guess I'm doing some music for y'all.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll figure something out.
So look out for that.
DaVita Studios.
Do you have a hub?
Do you have a website?
I'm working on it.
But I do have a Facebook page, DaVita Studios on Facebook.
And I have a YouTube page, DaVita Studios.
I've only got one song on it.
But I do have a page.
It's alright.
Yeah, we'll put it in the description.
Definitely. A little plug for us.
And as we get more, there's getting ready to be a, I'm working on all of those pages now.
I'm working on an IMDB page for myself as well.
I do all my music through BMI, for Matt DeVita and DeVita Studios.
Let's see, what else? That's enough though, right?
Yeah, that's great.
And then I guess a dual plug here in a little bit,
with Matt we're gonna go investigate a haunted museum we're gonna and we're
gonna make a video out of that and if you have to see the exclusive premiere of
this video you should buy a ticket to our live show in Brooklyn on Halloween
night. Do we want to say where it is yet? It's at the Bell House.
Do we want to keep that a secret? Maybe let's keep it under wraps. Yeah we're gonna keep that under wraps.
Look forward to it and if you want to see that you better come to the live show.
Halloween check that out Halloween night there's a swag.com slash shows tickets
are up yep there yeah see you there all right thanks Matt thank you appreciate
us fun again once again thanks for tolerating the stupid question no no I
mean the flow was all it was good
We've got an investigation coming up at the Museum of the Bazaar and I could really use
you guys' help.
This is the Museum of the Bazaar.
By day, a $3 admission Museum of the Bazaar.
Apparently there was some tragedy.
We should be concerned.
There's been 12 confirmed deaths.
I wouldn't go in there if you paid me.
What happened to your old team?
I'd rather show you.
Guys, I'm really scared.
They weren't brave like you.
Are you real?
Oh my god.
The first time we heard it, I was like, okay, roof creaking maybe.
I felt that was following us.
Why were you murdered?
Why did you die?
Did you hear that?
I heard a fucking voice.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]