Wow. He doesn't want to tell the story.
Yeah, why don't you just tell it. Tell the story.
You've told the most inconsequential stories of all time.
I've heard you tell stories about candy that you bought like a week ago.
Yeah, but that's like good.
That shit does taste good.
Yeah. Tell the story though.
Okay, so I was out buying my new gloves.
Looking good.
They look good. I'm liking them.
I was out buying my new gloves. I was in a store and a guy was following me around
The whole time I was in there
Because he I don't know he thought I was gonna steal or something. He kept blocking my way
Like I would like go I'd walk around I was like should I buy makeup? No
No, I think I have some at the office. You're saying this to yourself out loud in my head
Yeah, out loud in your head out loud in my head
Uh-huh
and then the guy keeps blocking my path and stuff and then I was like, oh, yeah
I just need to get by real quick and he went white people.
- It's true.
I would say, anything you did in that outfit,
I would say that.
I wasn't, you were in this outfit.
- And I'd love-- - It's not an outfit,
this is just my clothes.
- And I'd love to hear what you said back to this guy,
'cause I'm sure it was very interesting.
But it looks like the open mic is starting actually.
- Oh shit, oh my God, it's starting.
- You made me tell the fucking story.
- Yeah, oh there it is.
- Bud's Anything Goes open mic starting.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, all right, let's go.
- All right, Cameron, I think you're up first.
- All right, shit, okay, here you go.
Here you go, come on.
Cameron, everybody!
Woo! Go Cameron!
Alright.
- Yeah!
- Okay.
Okay, hey, good evening everybody.
- Woo!
- How's it going tonight?
Wow, big audience we got here.
How you doing, buddy?
- Hey, how's it going?
Where are you from?
- You turned your mic off.
- Hey, where are you from, pal?
Hey, where are you from?
Where'd you fly in from?
- Round here.
- Round here?
Oh, that's nice.
How was your Thanksgiving, by the way?
Good. You have a big, good, strong plate. Hardy, lots of vegetables.
Did you have a weak ass plate?
Okay, hey, hey, fuck this guy. All right, this, this audience, man. What are you gonna, I mean,
guy sitting here with a weak ass plate, back row of the audience. All right, let's get
to show on the road though, alright?
So,
I bring my wife coffee in bed.
Is she grateful?
No.
- Woo!
- She tells me she likes it in a cup.
- Ah!
(clapping)
- You know you're in a stoner's house
when there's Pringles in the bathroom.
- Oh shit!
- Anybody know?
- Anybody know that feeling?
- 'Cause they poop in the can.
So, I read about this CVS cashier who wrote some racist on a receipt and gave it to a customer.
Shocking.
Someone found a working cashier at CVS?
Damn!
It's mostly electronic.
Wait, I got, hold on, can I say something?
What, what's up?
Um, damn, someone actually read that CVS receipt?
Those things are mad long.
It's like a scroll.
It's like a fucking scroll.
You could add that to your material.
It's like a goddamn motherfucking scroll.
Um, you know you could say if you're gonna do that you could also be like and the cashiers are like wizards
The cat and the cashiers are like wizards. Yeah, they wrote something racist. What are they a wizard of the cook?
Yeah, you guys know about the I don't know anything about these from these are I wrote them
Okay, all I wrote every last one of these god bless you not even Bruce's as bossy as my girlfriend
Said not even Bruce's as bossy as my girl. Yeah. No, I heard who's Bruce Bruce
The fuck's going on not even Bruce's as bossy as my girlfriend. Hey, buddy. You're drinking some soda
Okay
You can drink soda
Soda if you're in the crowd just found out you can infuse weed with cotton candy
The county fairs around my home are gonna get real interesting
Excerpts from my mind. I will buy all the laffy taffy
Listen Becky, I don't care how much it costs. I'm bringing that tilt-a-whirl home and
Have you ever seen two Buffy's bunny so fluffies? Can we feed him some of this here cotton candy?
Did you say weed infused with cotton candy? Yep, that's what they're doing now that I just found out
So I just found out you can infuse weed with cotton candy
And those were excerpts from my mind, okay kind of leaning into Doug Benson territory a little stoner stuff
I'm a little bit of a stoner fan.
Okay, alright, alright, let's do something a little different.
Something a little different.
Something a little more intellectual.
Go ahead.
I often question whether or not God exists.
And just when I decide no, the singer of Nickelback gets a cyst on his throat and they cancel
their world tour.
Holy crap.
Touché, God.
Touché.
Wow.
That's, yeah, I mean, that's true.
It's not even funny.
It's more like a true kind of fact.
That's just kind of sad.
Yeah.
Because it could be a tumor or cancerous is
insists have cancer all right quiet and back okay, I
Remember when I used to keep a glamour shot of my girlfriend in my wallet now. I have 213 pictures of naked girls
I know on my phone
I
Remember when I used to keep a glamour shot of my girlfriend in my wallet now
I have 213 pictures of naked girls. I know on my phone. Yeah, that's
- Yeah, that'd be a different--
- This generation, man.
- Yeah.
Sony's releasing the PlayStation 5 next week.
If they really wanted to make a splash,
it should include a game called Recount.
You win by becoming president while still losing
the popular and electoral votes.
- Damn!
- Wait, why would they do that?
I missed it.
- If they wanted to make a splash.
- Oh.
(laughing)
All right, man, yeah.
- The other day, my wife asked me to bring her
a glass of water and said--
- Fuck her!
says she said make sure the glass is as clean as a whistle.
- Cut!
- She should have asked for a whistle.
- So, before I poured the drink,
you better believe I made sure there was nothing in that cup
but a ton of spit and a little bit of pee.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, serves her right.
- That's right.
- Wait, they get their glasses clean as a whistle?
- How are you doing, buddy?
- Good.
- Hungry?
Eat anything before this?
Combo over rice.
Alright, well fuck you man.
If I can't get something for nothing, can I at least enjoy my nothing before you tell me I need something I don't have?
How I feel about ads.
Damn, that's true.
Advertisements.
That was fucking true.
That's so true.
If life was like a video game, I'm pretty sure I'd be stuck in single player.
It's not that I haven't heard great things about the multiplayer experience.
Still, I find it overrated and outdated, what with all that extra tacked on, priceless DLC shit.
Yeah.
That's by dating, Danny.
That's the one I didn't write.
In the class I tutor, the teacher asked the students what they thought the most dangerous
game was about. I'm glad she didn't ask me, because all I could think about was tweezing my eyebrows.
Damn, that must be Greek as hell.
Tweezing my eyebrows.
I'm living in South Korea right now and it's a pretty interesting culture.
For example, there is no stigma surrounding cross-dressing, so it's not uncommon to see a man with a blouse or a lady with a penis.
(laughing)
- Is that right?
- That's the punchline.
- Oh my God, wow, that's--
- That's crazy.
- My game is like Monopoi, you ain't gonna finish.
- What's Monopoi?
- Monopoi.
My game is like Monopoi.
- But what is it?
- You ain't gonna finish.
- All right, move on.
- That would be funny if a lady named Wendy McDonald
opened a Burger King.
(laughing)
That one I like. I like that one.
That one's funny.
I do like that one a lot.
That one is honestly pretty funny.
That one is really...
Alright, let's keep it moving, folks.
My girlfriend says she doesn't like jewelry.
She's a keeper.
Fucking hate jewelry.
Yeah, keeper in the fucking...
Fucking jewelry.
Fucking hate jewelry, dude.
Keeper in the bathroom.
Thanks to Dr. Oz, everybody you talk to is a food expert.
They're more like food parrots.
Brrrap! Kale, kale!
Brrrap! Carbs, carbs!
Brrrap! Put down the fork, fatty!
food parrots.
(laughter)
Okay.
My girlfriend and I just broke up.
Aww.
An entire ounce of weed by hand and rolled it into one giant joint that represents our love.
(laughter)
We're very happy.
And hungry.
And sleepy.
Some people call a guitar an axe.
But it doesn't mean the same thing when you say I'm killing with my guitar
I'm killing with my guitar. Oh, yeah, okay
Yeah, I guess I want to eventually merge with computers and become a computer-human hybrid
So for me switching to eating organic food would be a step in the wrong direction I
I will smile for photos when you offer me actual cheese.
Until then, I will continue the long family tradition of looking miserable in photos.
Also, I will appear in black and white and wear a hair bun.
What?
In photos I'll be black and white in a hair bun.
Unless I have cheese.
[Laughter]
Who wrote that one?
DHL, zero.
Okay. Is there a picture of him?
It's black and white.
Oh, man.
Okay. Does he have a hair bun?
No, he has very little hair.
Oh, okay.
Ladies, you think a man should have to go back to having flip phones?
A good morning, beautiful how are you would take him hitting the key 64 times instead of 30.
That's double the effort.
Don't you think if he doubles the effort, you should double the fun?
I'm talking threesomes, ladies.
Heard that.
I'm talking threesomes.
I heard that.
Threesomes I had a I had a threesome with my girlfriend last night me and my dad really showed her
Wait, I had a threesome with my girlfriend last night me and my dad really showed her showed her we showed her
Dad really showed my girlfriend last
Threesome is like yeah, I'll teach you to fucking fuck one guy instead of two we showed her or two guys
We showed her what's what I ever have a threesome, buddy
Alright. Hey, fuck you pal. Okay, great. Killin' the energy. That's a chassis, yes. I just got
a part-time job, which allows for my full-time job as well. But, being a part-time ice cream
scooper actually really meshes well with my full-time position as a stoner. Damn. You
don't look like a stoner. I'm a stoner. You look like Scatman John. Or like Weedman Pot.
Let's try a little bit of scatting up there.
(scatting)
That's terrible.
That sounds nothing like scatting.
Yeah, more of a dorm.
It doesn't sound like scatman John at all.
Man, I like this stage presence you got with your dorm up there.
You look fucking badass.
You look like Andy Kaufman.
My girlfriend is one of those no sex
before marriage girls,
which is an odd thought.
That means she hasn't had sex ever.
Tell you what.
She sounds like an odd thought if you ask me.
And if she dies before she gets married, well I guess she has to have sex with Osama Bin Laden.
No idea what the... what are you talking about?
Cam, you look like Perry can't eat Jell-O.
Cause of stomach problems.
Stomach problems?
Cause he has stomach problems.
Perry, okay, I get...
Hey buddy, the only stomach problem I have is I'm like, "Oh, I need a slice of pizza, man!"
Cause I'm a fucking stoner as shit.
is shit. That one was, I made that one up. Damn. Damn. You can do improv too. Man up on
the spot. Alright. Okay. Okay guys. Okay. Let's bring it down a notch here. I used to
sit around at school and suck on sunflower seeds. Weird. So I was pretty disappointed
when somebody else got voted most likely to suck seed. Oh that's good. Okay. To suck seed.
Yeah no I got that part. Yeah the school slut probably got voted most likely to suck seed.
And what was her name?
Sluttington.
Slut-et.
Her name was Slud.
Nothing better than scrolling through your Facebook news feed judging people from high
school.
Heard that.
Yep.
Is there another part of the joke?
No, that's the joke.
That's by I Love Chunk.
Alright, I got one more for you guys.
Alright, alright.
I got one more for you guys.
So I killed a kitten one time.
Oh, fuck you.
I was walking to my car in the parking lot right after my high school let out
and there were these two girls searching for a kitten that had run up under their car.
So me and a few more people came over to help look because the two girls were hot.
And we looked and looked under the car for ten, fifteen minutes and we couldn't find the cat.
So I, in my infinite wisdom, said, "Ah, he probably ran off while we weren't looking."
And everyone agreed with me. So the girls got back in the car and all the people that were looking left.
And since I was parked right next to them,
I was the only one around to watch that little black and gray kitten fall from where it had tucked
itself in above the tire right in front of the back wheel.
I still remember the crunch as the tire crushed its little ribs and I still remember the look
of raw fear in its face and in its pale blue eyes as it tried to get up and run for just
a second before it collapsed with a shudder and lay still.
What?
Oh, that's my time everybody.
Thank you so much for having me at this open mic.
It's been fun.
Cameron Fetter.
Wow.
(applause)
- Keep going for Cam, everybody.
Wow.
That really was something.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that was a, so wait, you said that you wrote
all those jokes.
- Yep.
- Those are all jokes that we wrote.
- I wrote every last one of them.
- All right, here, you can have the cans back.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
- I know that's the thing you like to do a lot,
is listen to the show.
- Yeah.
What was it, so I didn't realize you were such a big stoner.
kind of came out of left field. I didn't know he was a big pothead, I guess.
Yeah, I'm... Look at his hair.
Yeah, well, that's a good point.
I'm kind of, yeah, I... Something...
Something changed.
Okay, probably smoked weed.
Probably, yeah, it was mostly, basically, I think that
once I smoked weed I realized that it makes you high as fuck.
Really? And I let that kind of influence my comedy, which usually...
I try to do more girlfriend, wife, ex-girlfriend, dead kitten material,
but I found that adding a little bit of spice
with weed in video games actually helps round out your set.
And even people in the audience who are more concerned
with soda or things like that
can really find common ground with you.
- I think that the people in the crowd,
if they don't laugh, I think there should be a penalty.
- I think they should--
- Or if they don't pay attention,
I think we should have a taser.
Yeah, if you don't laugh or interact in a crowd--
I agree. Speaking of, I think it's my turn to go up.
Oh, let's go. Yeah. Hey, Caleb Pitts, everybody.
Woo!
Thank you.
Oh, you just turned the mic off again.
Thank you. Thank you, everybody.
Woo!
First time up here, I'm a little bit nervous.
Pardon me.
It's all good, man. Just relax up there.
OK.
You're going to be a natural.
I'm kind of freaking out a little bit.
Just relax.
All right, I'm going to calm down just a little bit.
So I tried my hand at writing a script for an open mic event, so I want to know your guys'
thoughts on this, okay?
All right.
Hi everybody.
Oof.
Well, that's great.
I spent two weeks preparing for this and as soon as I get on stage, my mind just goes
blank.
Like my anxiety wasn't bad enough.
It's okay though.
I got a strong rope at home.
What?
I'm gonna kill myself, sir.
I'm gonna fucking kill myself.
This isn't my first time on stage.
I did a couple open mics in my hometown of Syracuse.
You're from Syracuse?
Yes, sir.
But of course they flopped. Naturally.
This is me we're talking about.
But I was also in a really weird place and I did a bit on how I was starting a cult.
It's a long story.
Plus the FBI doesn't like me talking about it.
Fuck it. I'm going to elaborate.
Don't.
That would help me appear less insane.
You're gonna get in trouble with the FBI.
I just come off as a crackhead to some people because I'm schizoaffective and autistic.
That's kinda like your car having a flat tire while your engine's on fire.
Even if you fix one, the damn thing still ain't going nowhere.
That's what my brain is, just one big lemon.
A lemon?
Got a lemon for a fucking brain.
Like a bad car.
That's how schizoaffective I am.
You should say jalopy.
Anyways, I was once in a cult.
It was fun, in a weird masochistic way.
I was virtually a slave,
and not the kinky kind that I prefer.
Prefer a sex slave.
No, I got pushed so hard that I became psychotic.
I thought that the birds were mocking me.
They would say things like, "Caw, caw,"
and "Cock-a-doodle-doo,"
but I mean, but I knew what they really meant.
I have never met such mean avians,
And I've crossed paths with quite a few geese in my day.
You're like a silly goose up there.
Yeah.
Making me laugh.
But I eventually escaped the cult.
That's how I got this scar.
Can we see the scar?
It's invisible.
It's directly on my face.
That should have meant that things improved for me, right?
Pro tip.
This one's for you, sir.
Here's a pro tip for you.
Do not take four tabs of acid in the wake of being horrifically traumatized by a cult.
Not only did it turn me into a woman, but I got it in my head that aliens wanted me to be the messiah.
That's a pro tip for you.
Thus, I spent three years homeless trying to start the most insane cult imaginable.
Truth be told, I actually thought I was going to get famous for being the craziest motherfucker in
existence. So I deliberately said the most deranged shit I could come up with for an
example of one of the milder things I did. One time I started going up to people on the
streets and asked them, "What's your opinion of ethical incest?" Some people got a kick
out of it, but eventually three cop cars whooped up on me and put a stop to it. They were not
happy with me, I'll tell you what, as you can probably imagine.
Yeah, man.
Damn coppers. I've literally been run out of Eugene, Oregon for stunts like that.
(laughter)
- But that's still not what got the FBI involved.
See, in my infinite wisdom,
I began trolling in character on Reddit.
I started getting maybe one or 200 messages every day
just saying some variant of, "WTF did I just read?"
But there were people who enjoyed my content,
thought it was funny, so, you know, really stand up people.
One guy was into scalping people,
and he was one of the tamer ones.
So I'm joking about starting
most messed up cult imaginable and a real cult starts forming. Go me. There was talk
about pooling our resources, buying land, moving everybody in, and taking over a
local government. It was that serious. I started getting cold feet but
fortunately I was saved by the wonderful men and women and other gendered agents
in the FBI who vanned me while I was riding in the park and brought me to the
hospital where I stayed a month. They shut down the cult too which I guess is
a good thing. So that's the sort of how I got on a list of two. Well, a part of it
anyways. I was only given a few minutes to regale you with my tale, but I'm
writing a book to tell my whole life story. The aliens tell me it will make me
famous. Or maybe not. I've been wrong before, but at least things won't be
boring. Have a good night everyone, and may you never ever follow my example.
Whoa. Wow. So that's it for me. By the way guys, another thing that this guy said is
he's writing a 65,000 page book about his life.
I found another post.
But that's it, I've been Caleb Pitts.
- Wow, thank you so much, guys.
- Keep it going for Caleb Pitts, everybody.
- I'll be back up here in a little bit.
- Let's have the audience cheering and clapping here.
- Why don't you do fucking something, man?
Do something. - Cheer, yo.
(cheering)
- This guy's all right.
- Okay, I'm liking that guy.
- Okay, he's good now. - Wow.
What a set.
That was, honestly--
- God, it feels good to crush, man.
- Yeah, it was honestly, what I liked about it
is it was somewhere between funny and memoiric.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Memoirical. - It's this kind of
identity comedy that is doing so well nowadays
that people just love.
- Like I said, that guy is, I did find another post
where he said he's writing a 65,000 page book
about his awesome life.
So I'm looking forward to it. - I would love to read it.
- I would read it. - 65,000.
- I'd read that.
- There's something about the phrase infinite wisdom
that these type of people really like.
- Oh yeah.
Yeah.
All right, well, I think-- who's up next?
Yeah, wait.
Who's up next on the list?
Who's up next on the open mic?
Who drew their name out of the hat?
I'm up next.
Oh, my god.
Oh, for real?
Yeah.
And so the past--
Do your stand up.
Well, I believe that this was a poetry open mic.
It's literally called FUDZ, Anything Goes Open Mic.
Oh, OK.
OK, you're right.
Oh, so anything goes?
Yeah, go do your thing.
Then, hey, why don't I just go?
Don't feel self-conscious.
Just get up there.
Just go, yeah.
All right, woo!
Woo!
Patrick Aradorin!
- Go get 'em!
- So this is a poem about my love.
Well, on February 28th, you asked me to type a poem about you.
Your eyes are as beautiful as a gray, cloudy sky.
Every time I look at you, I can't help but to smile.
I messed up one time.
That fucked up everything.
I'm sorry.
That fucked up everything with us.
I thought that I was forgiven.
I knew it wasn't true.
Now we have to be a hidden couple.
Your parents can't know. I can't hide it.
I am with the most beautiful woman in Midland, Texas.
And I want the whole city to know.
I am in love. I am not gonna hide it.
Your friends don't like me.
Well, tough luck.
We are together and there is nothing they can do about it.
I know I don't tell you it enough, but you are so gorgeous
I haven't even went on about your kisses
Do it!
They are sweet!
I would choose a kiss any day over a candy apple
Your lips are so luscious, I can't get enough
This will probably sound cheesy, but I just hope you to have my children
I hope that we are together forever
forever. I wish for the respect oif everybody, but I think since we will be at the same school,
we now have the chance to prove to everybody that we are the sweethearts darts for the classes of
2008 and 2009. I don't know about you, but I want people to know who we are, the couple that turns
heads. I am ready for this year. Speaking of a year, it is only two months away. I love you Lacey
Ann Horton. This is an honor. This is an honor of my fiancee, Lacey Ann Horton, who
accepted my proposal on the 26th of September 2005. She has been with me for
10 months and it's all I can ask for for anything more.
Pretty quick engagement, but I like that. That is lovely. That is so, I mean, better a
quick engagement than languishing around for six years, having casual premarital
sex, and doing God knows what type of drugs, those type of things. I have another
poem too. Oh my god, a treat. Talk that talk. I hate this. I hate it that you act different.
I hate it that we aren't us. I hate it that I can't be your one to run to. You hate me.
I hate me. What can I do? You are still with me but only so we can still be friends. I
hate that. I wish you would act like I'm important still. I wish that you could talk to me, not
some other guy. I wish we could be us from three weeks ago. I hate it that we aren't.
I hate it that you are so darn beautiful. I hate it that you blame me for everything that
goes wrong. I hate it that your friends hate because of rumors. I just want me and you
to be how we used to be. I could care less about friends.
Holy.
Just be normal with me. I used to make you happy. You saw the ring today. That's why
I'm working so hard. You told me you would never blame your hatred for me because of
work. What happened? Who are you in love with now? Why can't I be the one? Just a few questions
on my mind. Baby or Lacey? Which one? And there's some comments here.
Is that also about Lacey Horton?
You wrote that one about Lacey Horton too?
And there's some comments here and this is from Dark Rose and they say you have never
had love.
(sighing)
- God damn. - Holy shit.
- Do you believe that about yourself?
You and Lacey, you never had love?
- Well, I replied and said,
"Um, okay, maybe I shouldn't have asked for advice.
"That is how I feel about my love,
"and I really don't care that anybody else thinks about that."
- Damn, that is a good-ass comeback, dude.
That is great.
- And then I got a critical review from Espelina
that says, "There was no flow to this poem
"in any way at all, and it needs more than a little tweaking
"to make it sound nice.
"It just sounds whiny and childish."
I don't agree with that at all.
I think that's a mature poem.
- And you know what?
I'm gonna prove Espelina wrong.
- That's right.
- This next poem that I wrote.
- Oh my God.
- What did I do?
Well, I ain't sure of how this will turn out,
but hey, I still love this one.
She loved me for so long, almost a year.
But the last two weeks she was acting weird
and now I know why.
She was trying to get us to split up.
Well, out of anger, I did it.
I said we were over, almost a perfect couple.
Now I sit here in tears thinking, what did I do?
Had it all planned out, I had the ring.
August 27th would have been our year.
I was gonna take her out to Olive Garden,
the finest restaurant in Midland.
- Holy fuck.
- Then take her over to the ice skating rink in Odessa.
- Yup.
- Fall in the middle of the ring and then ask,
will you marry me?
Well, now I can't.
My mouth ruined my life, sitting here in shock.
She hung up on me.
For the first time, I am scared that I will never
hear from her again.
Man, I hate her, but I love her.
I love her because she just played this big game
of love and won.
I love her because at times, I believed that she loved me,
but for now, it was all a past dream.
I am ill.
I don't want to go on.
What did I do?
Well, I opened my mouth.
She tries to tell me that I ain't a bad person,
when deep down in her heart I fear that she doesn't care.
What do I do?
Scared to drive to see her 'cause I wanna kill myself.
Scared to go to sleep 'cause what if I don't wake up?
Scared to talk about it.
Thank God for all poetry.
I am just in too much shock.
What have I done?
Nothing right is my answer,
but I guess it is time for her to find someone.
I thought I was her special someone,
but man, love what you have, even if you hate it.
what what i do just to hear her say i love you jimmy
jimmy
jimmy is israelis is by the way that you
that's my stage name
uh... jimmy i think that's the case my stage name is jimmy
that was honestly raw
yeah the rise for us okay i have one and i have another poem you keep saying you
have one more
i have
What?
Is he just gone?
He's just gone, I guess.
Went in the bathroom?
I have a few more poems.
What a fucking asshole.
I know.
And I guess the bathroom's on stage.
Fucking worst comedy club ever, dude.
Who did that?
That's fucked.
This one is called "Too Much Pain."
Too much pain?
But there's already been so much pain in your words.
Yeah, how could there be more pain?
How could there possibly be something more painful than just walking?
The farther I walk into the frightful woods, the darker and closer it gets.
Each step that I take, I make another mistake.
As I go to sit down on a broken leg, something catches my eye.
As I look up into the starry night sky, I realize it was only an airplane.
As I retrieve from the broken log, I find the best spot to lay down.
I look up at the amazing night sky again. I begin to let my freezing tears drown my face.
Dude, take it slow. You're freaking me out.
I passed I start to remember the pain and I hate when I had a family that loved and cared when I had a
What I considered a home. I don't even know what I have anymore
All I know now is my lost and broken soul. That was the past the thing I cherish the most
I had to run away from all that pain. No way I have left with no one
Myself the purse I paid for running away was harsh
The fact that I don't have a family is too much pain that I will not take you have no family
This is my final goodbye.
Are you gonna kill yourself?
You're an orphan who's gonna kill himself?
You're...
Yeah, can you just sit down?
Yeah, just go ahead and sit down.
Maybe lay off the soda, then you won't have to pee.
If you're peeing that much, man,
something's wrong with you, health-wise.
Okay, I have...
I think...
You wanna, I mean, I don't know how many you prepared,
but I think we're, I think the, I don't know, I mean...
Yeah, how about you let somebody else have a turn,
you fucking asshole?
All right, names on the list.
- You'd kill yourself, you bitch.
- Okay.
- I don't know if you wanna do all of your poems at once,
is all I'm saying. - I won't do all my poems
at once, right. - You're blowing your load.
You keep saying one more, and then you do another.
- Okay, you know what?
I'll just, I'll sit down, all right?
- All right, sit down. - Okay, go ahead, sit down.
- All right, Patrick, or Jimmy, everybody.
- Jimmy! - Jimmy!
- I thought that-- - Let's hear it for Jimmy.
- All right. - All right.
- I'm gonna be honest.
(Jimmy singing)
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I thought that I was supposed to do all of 'em right now.
- Because you weren't paying attention
when the open mic rules were being read.
We all know that you were doing skateboarding games.
- Okay, but that means I'm gonna have to start
making stuff up on the spot.
- That's fine.
- That's fine, but it's--
- Yeah, that's fine.
- That's fine, and it's also your--
- Improv is something that you can do--
- It's anything, it's FUDZ Anything Goes Open Mic.
- You can go up there and you can do a hotkey.
- Anything goes.
- I'm getting that it's anything goes.
- It's literally, but get off the stage.
- Okay.
- Get off the stage.
- Anything goes for roughly eight minutes
and then you can fuck off, maybe.
So there we go.
Patrick Rowan, everybody.
Jimmy!
Or Jimmy.
Jimmy.
Good shit, Jimmy.
Great, great, great job, Jimmy.
That actually, I mean, I have to say, Jimmy, what you have just done, it actually brought
something into my memory that I had written that I had completely forgotten about.
Really?
Yeah, and I'm seeing that my name is next up on the list.
Oh shit, it is.
Yeah, which I forgot that I even signed up that many times.
But this is good, because now I have something prepared.
See I signed up as Jimmy because I thought that if I went up as Patrick then I wouldn't be allowed to go up twice
But now I know now you'll go up as Patrick on the second one. I guess okay
All right, I think I'll I guess I'll still be Jimmy. All right, that's fine. Okay. Well, it's my turn
Wow and here comes Cameron approaching the stage
Oh man.
I've just buttoned my jacket.
Be improper not to.
Hey, long time no see, pal. What's up?
Hey.
I'm not doing comedy this time.
Yeah, poets don't really do crowd work.
You don't have to worry about me roasting you or anything like that.
Uh, 'cause I'm more, this is more...
You know what? Fuck it. Roast him!
Just fucking roast him!
Uh, so...
What's up with, um...
Your facial expression are you confused?
Yeah, what's that your friend probably what are you eight eight months old yeah
Get him asshole. I heard you in the bathroom. You're going like this
He was going like I heard that - he's kidding. Yeah, I think he was coming in there. Oh wait. Hey, hey guys
He wasn't even coming in there
he was peeing and making that noise.
- Wait, ask him about the threesome again
and ask him who the two guys were.
- Hey, who were the two guys were?
What?
Nobody can hear you, you don't have a microphone.
- Yeah, how about you leave the comedy
to the professionals, okay?
And go back to-- - Even though he's a poet
right now. - Drinking soda.
- I wish he'd go back in the bathroom and stay there.
- Yeah, I wish he'd go back into his coffin.
And fucking die.
- Okay, now we got the laughs out.
- There's gonna be no more laughs after this, right?
This is more of a--
Because there's pain in my heart.
This is less about pain, and this is more about love,
which is what you inspired me to do.
OK.
Do something about.
So this is a poem that I wrote in 2010, and it's entitled--
And how old were you in 2010?
I wasn't born yet.
Oh.
This is entitled "Soul of Blue," and it's a love story
for my love.
I like love.
I used to have love, but then it betrayed me.
Take me with you, oh soul, I ask.
Will you free me with your peaceful mind?
One can only hope, solemnly pray.
Is the tree of souls my only destiny in this life?
Will the blue sky of your eyes consume me?
Ewa, I ask for clarification, for but a balance
upon this life.
Will we one day be planet-Earth friendly, I ask?
As long as monetary value be alive, we be set to slavery.
Is the world of truth real?
Is it viable?
Is cash our unobtainium?
There may be no reason to believe, but I wish to.
Tot skin, energy unmatchable, legs as long as the heavens,
with matching butts from a lust-worthy world of old.
A world of true freedom.
Where do I find such beauty?
Ideas loose me, elude me, entrap me, encase and transfix me.
Why does cash mean so much?
Possessions are but the seed of deception.
The wind of Western socialism/democracy
will eat away at the last of our freedoms.
Facts.
The swing of our blueness within can set us free,
but only if we believe.
And to my sweet blue princess of pan, I say,
I would blend with your ideology, complete unity within seconds and without a second thought.
Your bittersweet arrow could pierce my heart in anger, but your destined path is what is
sought by this soul, and I shall receive it within my personal internal grasp.
If only you, my sweet, could find the heart to see I'm far from a swaggering player.
Please.
Could have fooled me with that outfit.
Yes, sir.
For humanity's insight, see me, roll with me, unite with me.
I would rather your heart sealed with a loving kiss, my dear love, Neytiri, until the setting
sun disappears.
If but forever, a day, and a day still, you take my bitterness and make it whole with tender
berries of sparkling blue.
To me, there is nothing more than the love for our planet, for our species, and especially
our people.
And that's a poem I wrote about Neytiri from Avatar.
Wow.
That's amazing.
My love.
That is so beautiful.
That was beautiful.
beautiful. Thank you. Thank you so much, guys. Oh, thank you.
Now, that's too much. That's, I mean, what do you guys say? You
want to hear another poem? Yes. I mean, yeah. Is it about
Neytiri? I don't have, I wrote one about Neytiri. Just one.
Here, I'll read. Let's see here. I have, I have one short one
and then, here we go. Alright, I got, I have two, two short ones
that I'm gonna, I'm gonna finish up here on. Okay. I think,
judging by the people in the crowd, I think you guys might
like these. Okay. So let's get it poppin'. Is this a white person? It's for white people?
It's for people who appreciate poetry. Oh, okay. All right, here's my first, my
first of my two. This one is entitled "Thingy." And I wrote this in 2008. Okay.
"Thingy." From the tiniest prick to the world's biggest dick, penises are great.
14 inch meat to the 2 inch baby. I want you now
All right
Wait, that's thingy. You can't just go up here. I mean anything goes I wouldn't say going up there saying I want a baby dick
Is a you want a 2 inch baby?
2008 okay, so you were also a baby, okay?
Well that makes it a little bit better, but you're also performing it in
You're an adult you're up there saying oh as poetry is not about your you're asking gold
Boundaries you're talking about a baby
Baby limits and your ass must enter your little space, and I don't want to do that
I don't know what that means the hell. Are you know what that means?
What are you talking about? We've done a bunch of episodes about diaper lovers, and you guys don't remember
What do you mean a little I don't know what kind of pedophilic bullshit you're talking about, but it's not welcome
I'm at this on me. He said he wants a two-inch, baby
Okay, and he just reversed my brain again back to your ass. You're fucking gonna get smoked by okay, okay, okay fine
I shoot you right up there you bastard
Yeah, hands up. You're gonna be that poem was in poor taste. Okay, okay? I can admit it, but art is about being messy
Like your diaper. I don't wear a diaper. I wear a suit and you wear
Fucking bullshit, and this is what I think about your generation, okay?
This is a poem I wrote in order bring it on old bitch. This is a poem
I wrote in 2017 called of a generation. That's what I think of you motherfucker. Okay
Of a generation
Squandered youth
Squandered youth this generation listens to mumble rap and dabs to Migos and Justin Bieber
Then composing poetry or going outside to reflect shifting yellow black bumblebees or whiffing flowers in a metropolitan park
They'd prefer to dress slutty in a rancid dim lighting nightclub with crimson red flesh
They swiped red right on tinder then valuing masses that gave them liberation
Yep, the blue earth's weary
It impedes me from changing a globe
Yep, I demand a change and
That's what I think of you wait no fuck you old man
biters
Ankle biter. I'm not that short
You're the one who's talking about sucking on a baby's prick you fucking asshole. You want a two-inch babies brick?
Yeah, but it shut up. I'd never said that get off the stage. Okay, I'm gonna get off the stage motherfucker. All right
Well, thank you. That's my time everybody
Keep it going for our wonderful host Jubio
He's up there he's still on the computer there's nothing we could do about that yeah, I thought the Juby would well
You guys have inspired me. I think
yeah, but
Not so much to do all that kind of let's be honest kind of gay poetry stuff not that gay
Yeah, it's not really my kind of idea of a good time
I'm gonna stick to comedy, but maybe stand-up just isn't my thing so I'm gonna go do my new set okay
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoo
Kayla pits everybody one of the funniest guys. I know he's coming to the stage right now Kayla pits
Oh, oh, yeah, I have a multi talented multi hyphenated kind of talent list, okay, and I'll be right
I'm gonna change a couple of things all right up here for just a second here you change that we'll talk over here, okay?
I'm really excited for this set me too. I have to say I wonder I wonder what kind of crazy
Yes, his last set kind of challenged the form and I'm wondering if you can challenge the form more this time around
Cuz I just hey from what I I mean, I don't want to just
Reveal anything too quick, but what I'm hearing over there. There's a lot of my guys. Whoa. Oh my god. Look at this goodness
This is unbelievable
I
Can't believe what I'm seeing right now
He has changed everything
All right, all right Wow keep it going everybody
So you guys kind of woke me up in a way because I realized that comedy doesn't just have to be about
Just pure kind of like oh, this is funny as hell. This is about my life, right?
It doesn't have to be so personal it can also be about
the news
Whoa are you guys familiar with maybe Colbert poor daily show Sam Jay that kind of fancy be?
Sam Sam a Sam a Sam Sam Cedar the nerdest nerdest
like all this kind of crap is like a combo of
Funny comedy, but also maybe talking about real crap that actually John Oliver John Oliver forgot him
Chevy Chase show so I have just a bunch of these kind of day so daily Joe's that
gala guess
So here's my my December 11th
2000 here Griffin
And I got to do this can't you know I got to do this
Cheers America, here's my my December 11th 2020 daily joke monologue, okay?
42 year old Vince Carter made history last night by becoming only the fifth NBA player to appear in five
in
1,500 games
After the game he was asked by reporters what keeps him going he replied tons of Viagra damn Wow
Whoa?
Did that really happen? Yeah in 2011? Yeah?
Artist Jason Derulo had an Instagram post removed after he posted a photo of himself in Bali showing his bulge
Derulo
Responded by saying I have underwear on I can't help my size hashtag bring back anaconda
moments later it
Moments later it was reported that Jason will be starring in the sequel to snakes on a plane no fucking way
Snakes in a pants the curtains open behind her by the way
You're giving away. What's that gonna be snakes in an underwear?
Though it's more like snakes in his trousers snakes on a probably snakes in a Jane while he's having sex with
Jane Fonda now listen up guys
Scientists have created a once a month birth control pill that works on pigs good news for Patrick and
And are now wanting to test it on humans.
Upon hearing the news, talk show host Wendy Williams
volunteered to be tested on.
The group of scientists responded to her act of bravery
by saying, "Yeah, we've already tested on pigs."
- Whoa. - You fat bitch.
Wait, this is in 2011?
No, this is two years ago.
- Okay. - The Wendy Williams stuff.
- Yeah, that-- - Which I don't think she was really fat.
She-- no, but she, uh, she had to cancel the show
'cause she got really sick.
What?
Yeah, Wendy Williams doesn't have a show anymore because she got really sick.
Oh, Wendy Williams, that's another person with a show.
Yeah.
I just thought of that.
Oh, and Wendy Williams.
Style comedy.
And she says the killer.
The killer.
Yeah.
Speaking of pigs, singer Lizzo was spotted twerking in a thong at a Lakers game in Staples Center.
As soon as she got up to dance, fans sitting behind her were blown away by their first solar eclipse.
Lizzo completely eclipsed the sun.
Were the fans like two years old?
The fans were two inches tall.
So they got, they were very small.
Oh, a two inch baby?
That's for you.
Scientists--
You can fuck 'em.
I have more news, guys.
Guys, great news.
Scientists are working on a 1,000 year space mission
to save the human race by relocating it
to a hospitable planet.
In other words, a planet where Pitbull's music doesn't exist.
(laughing)
You gotta laugh, you gotta laugh from the audience!
Wow, we don't even have a cue card.
I've had my fair amount of critiques, besides the Emmys, besides the Golden Globes for my
late night Emmy Awards.
DesertSunrise84 said, "Didn't like any of them and I'm wondering why the ones involving women
rely solely on making fun of their appearance."
Which, you know, fair question.
Agree.
And I would say in particular, making fun of Lizzo for being fat, at least the way it's
done here, is not only pretty lazy.
Sorry, that's not me.
I say thank you.
That's how I responded.
But that's not all for me.
I got plenty more shit to talk about.
I'm looking for feedback here on news jokes in the style of a late night monologue or
SNL's weekend update.
And for some reason there's a Pokemon as the picture for this.
Which one?
The one with four arms.
Machamp.
- You're my champ.
- So basically, the past couple weeks I've been--
- So guys, listen up audience.
- You're my champ, buddy.
- Thank you very much.
- Go champ, go my champ, go.
- Okay, yeah, I'm the champ.
- Look at champ shining up there.
- Oh, look at his shiny head.
Look at how shiny his head is under that light.
- It's not that shiny.
- It's pretty shiny.
- Okay, so maybe I moisturized really, really well today.
- Bro's got a third eye.
You just turned the mic off again.
- Man, shut your bitch ass up.
- Okay, okay, okay. - You're like David Letterman
and Paul Sheehy. - Hey, okay.
- The past couple weeks, I've been writing news jokes
for fun/practice in the style of late night monologues
or SNL's weekend update.
But without an audience, it's hard for me to tell
whether any of these are actually funny
or merely amusing or neither.
If you have a minute, please let me know
to which degree you found them funny or not.
If there were any, if there were any you particularly liked
or disliked or any suggestions you have for me, thanks.
Here are the ones I've written so far, from most recent to least recent.
Okay.
Walt Disney World is building...
Okay guys, ready?
Yeah.
I also want to ask the audience member to behave, he's being distracting.
Don't...
Stop.
Say stop.
Yeah.
Walt Disney World is building an immersive hotel for Star Wars fans that will let them
travel through space in a galactic cruiser.
Woo!
Yeah.
Yeah, good news.
the hotel will make them a shipload of money.
Do you want feedback for each one? Yeah. That one was good. Okay. That's fire.
That one was good. In Sweden, a seagull flew off with a man's bag of weed just before it
could be used as evidence to arrest him. Police says this is not their first
encounter with the seagull mafia.
That'd be good. This one. Like one. Yeah, this needs some
this needs some work. That's a two. It's you need to iterate
on that a little. Yeah. Alright. Cuz the actually that's a
four because the premise. It's a little too. It's a little too
true. The seagull bloods or the crips. That would be funnier.
Okay, I'll remember that. In a class action lawsuit, some
Canadians have sued Red Bull for misleading them to believe
that it would actually give them wings.
The same people also want to sue Budweiser
on the basis that Bud Light doesn't weigh any less.
- Okay, I like that one.
It's a thinker, but it's good.
- It's more of a clever kind of movie.
- Yeah, it takes you, that's the one where you hear
a moment of silence before the laughs start to roll.
- Guys, here's a good one.
A fourth Matrix movie is under development.
- Okay. - Get excited,
with stars Keanu Reeves and Carrie Ann Moss set to return.
the movie is tentatively titled neo in trinity's excellent adventure
i like that one but they're to meet them
yet they made better came out of the head
now i don't have faced the music
uh...
uh... it's uh...
a florida woman
you've with all of us and i think that and out of ten not even get a read that
mother fucker
i don't even have to because you know that it's already funny as shit
No, I'll do it. I gotta make this guy happy.
A Florida woman was shocked when her dog came back from the groomer with pink ears and green eyebrows.
To see what her dog looks like, buy a ticket to Cirque du Soleil.
That's right. Fuck the Cirque du Soleil weird motherfuckers with green and pink makeup.
Put some real makeup on. What are you doing?
Surprisingly the phrase "Taco Tuesday" is trademarked by fast food chain Taco John's
who routinely mails letters ordering other restaurants to stop using it.
The company likes to send those letters out on cease and desist Sunday.
That's alright.
Oh wait yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
A five-year-old was granted his birthday wish when he got to be a Target employee for a
day.
That's a feel-good story. He says for his next birthday he wants to have a midlife crisis.
This old ass kid is acting all old.
Oh, I want to have a job on my birthday.
This kid's an old fuck.
He's an old soul.
John Huntsman, the U.S. ambassador to Russia, has resigned, citing historically difficult relations.
He has also broken up with his girlfriend, citing historically difficult relations.
Former Major League pitcher Kurt Schilling, let's give it up for the Boston Red Sox real quick. World Series champ.
Who doesn't love the Boston Red Sox?
Kurt Schilling got the bloody sock. The bloody sock. That bastard, they couldn't get him off the mound.
Uh-huh. He completely bankrupt to the state of Rhode Island. That's right. To make the best video game ever.
Mm-hmm.
Former Major League pitcher Kurt Schilling has announced that he is considering running for Congress.
Analysts question whether he can make it the full term without a reliever. So that's not a very funny one
That one doesn't make sense. He was a relief pitch pretty disrespectful in a tweet Donald Trump claimed that he doesn't have a racist bone
In his body. Oh, yeah, Donald Trump, then why have all why are all your bones white?
Whites are white ass white all white people aren't racist and if you want to see more in the future
I post these on my twitter account twitter.com slash Alan does the news. I
I didn't know you had that Twitter account.
That's cool.
That's me.
I'm definitely going to be checking that out.
Yeah, I just have a couple more daily jokes.
Oh, just a couple more?
Yeah, just five daily jokes more.
OK, let's count them down.
All right.
These are some more stepdad life jokes,
because u/goatofthrones asked for them, but not really.
Goat of throats.
Yep.
The goat, the throat goat?
Wait, actually, maybe I want to do a different one.
Hold on.
So Caleb asked this question.
Caleb is the throat goat.
I get my humor from my dad.
Do you remember that crazy ice bucket challenge thing
from a few years ago? Well, my dad, he died of ALS. Dad is, my fucking father died. My
father died of ALS, Lou Gehrig Syndrome disease. Is there any more in that joke? That's the
punchline? That's the topic of the day. Took a lifeguard class. They said sometimes a person
who is drowning, terrified, moments from death, will fight you, even though you're trying
save them that's what being a stepdad is like except no one's coming to save me
I'm drowning out here with my fucking you're drowning in kids I'm drowning
with my stepkids you're drowning your stepkids I'm drowning in them they're so
busy okay they're busy the boy the boy got caught being at school I'm guessing
that's one of my two stepkids come on man come on man think of your health
people can actually die of that of embarrassment oh shit I've learned a lot
from my wife for instance I've learned I'm a revolting mud man whose dirt-clad
eyes are incapable of perceiving filth that for my wife I can't live without my
wife and she can't live without a clean house if y'all track dirt in here she
knows about it. End of the studio. End of here. My wife used to wake me up early. Come on,
get up, we gotta clean the house. I can't really afford it, but I need my sleep, so
I got us a house cleaner. My wife still woke me up early. Come on, get up, we gotta clean
up before the cleaners get here. Stupid bitch! I'm hiring somebody to clean the house, you
fucking bitch what are you doing? Why are you waking me up? I'm having dreams about new
technology. And then one more joke guys. Alright. I'll end it on this one. This one and I'll
submit it. Pretty racist. This is called, this one's called, this one's as good as, as simple
as a title can come. Chinese Spanish. There's a half Chinese, half Spanish restaurant near
Yeah, I don't know what they serve, but I'm pretty sure it has rice
And that's all for me you guys thank you for coming out
That was incredible that was so good
Yeah, we'll tell world we'll break it down
Sure. Yeah, so
For me, I'm a huge fan of late-night comedy. I think bringing that to an open mic is
a
Beautiful. Yeah, a bit you would think me being an emo like I am I would not like late-night
But I think when I grow up
Yeah
People like like James Corden are bringing emo into late-night
They're bringing music and the emotions of youth are being brought into
the late-night scene and that
is good. I mean I feel like I was honestly reinventing and reformulating the genre in
many ways. Yeah. And I'm proud of myself and I'm proud of everybody who helped me. Including
you guys for giving the feedback on this. I mean you were great. I'm glad I could be
a part of it. You're ready for prime time. Really? Late night I mean. Alright. I'm ready.
Oh my god you could do the first prime time. The first prime time late night show. Okay.
Okay, yeah, I think that'd be great. Early night. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I'm checking the list here.
Who's going up? I'm seeing, I'm seeing, I can't, it's kind of smudged and I can't tell whether it
says Jimmy or Patrick Doran. It kind of, yeah. It seems like it could say either. My signature.
And it seems like it could say either. Well, you guys are in luck. Are we? Because I have,
while all that was happening, I wrote five more poems. I can't even believe that's possible.
Five more? I'm a very prolific writer.
Alright, well God bless you. Go do your damn thing.
Go for it, pal. Are you Jimmy or Patrick?
Jimmy! Jimmy, everybody! Jimmy!
Jimmy! Go Jimmy! Go Jimmy!
I'm back with more poems about my life.
And this one is called "D.A.M.N."
D.A.M.N.?
Damn, oh damn.
I didn't know exactly how much I loved her.
Here I find myself thinking,
you are at a dance without me.
Are you dancing with another guy?
Are you thinking of me?
I didn't know I loved her so much
until she started to be wondrous.
I didn't know I loved her so m much
until I couldn't be with her every last possible moment.
But now I can tell you that I know how much I love her.
My love for her only gets stronger.
People try hard to split us up but never succeed.
People said this wouldn't last
and tell us to get rid of each other.
After nine months, we couldn't love each other
any more than we do now.
Sure, we argue, but what normal couple doesn't?
We are not normal.
We would do everything to see each other.
I'm trying to see you so often,
but your mom doesn't like me.
I didn't know how much I loved her
until her mom said we couldn't be together.
until we had a near breakup.
I can't believe how stupid I was
to question your love for me.
I know you love me and I wouldn't do anything to hurt me.
You wouldn't do anything to hurt us.
we are both thankful for what God has given us, each other.
I ask for a kiss, but you give it to me like it is a prize.
Baby, your kisses are worth more
than any prize I have ever won.
I just wish I could get more of my prize more often.
I call and I call in hopes to hear your voice,
but still no answer.
I worry when I can't hear from you.
I didn't know how much I loved her
until I thought I was being ignored.
until we weren't holding hands.
I didn't know how much she loved me
until she told me that we couldn't break up.
I didn't know how much she loved me until she kissed me seriously.
Seriously?
I didn't know how much,
I didn't know she loved it at all until I hear those three little but big words.
I love you. They mean only something.
They mean only something to a person once in their life.
So Lacey Ann Horton, I love you.
Wow. That was great.
And now I got another one for y'all.
- Sure.
Does anyone care?
- I do.
- Yeah, I do.
- Yeah, raising my hand up in the sky.
- Look over here.
- That's the title of it.
- Yes, I care.
- Look over here.
- Does anyone care?
- Yeah, I already fucking said I care.
- I sit here on this thing I call a couch.
(laughing)
But usually I sit.
This time things are different.
School has been so freaking awesome today, but once I get in the car is when the life hits the fans.
I try to pretend to be everything is okay, but only if you truly knew me deep down.
I am a sad and miserable man.
Nobody asked or do they care?
I tried to be a good boyfriend, but no, everything I say always comes out wrong.
I walk you upstairs.
I find out you are mad at me.
What am I to do?
I'm just a helpless young man.
You think I would cheat again?
No one in this world trusts me.
Why? What did I do wrong?
I came home as soon as I walk in the door before I can even set my stuff down.
I am getting yelled at. My life is officially going to end in one month.
A marriage can ruin a family. Will it kill mine?
I only have two months until I'm 16.
I only have two years and two months until I'm out of this miserable house. Wow.
Only two years. Well, I guess I am done. No one wants to care.
No one cares to hear about my miserable life.
Oh, you're only 16 or no, you're 15. You're 15. You're married.
You have a family?
I proposed to Lacey Ann Horton, I guess.
The most beautiful woman in all of Texas.
The most beautiful woman in Midland, Texas.
Midland, Texas.
I'm pretty sure...
And how old is she?
I think she's also 16.
I think they were both 16.
Proposing to a 16 year old.
Got it on cam.
Okay, Jimmy.
Okay, well, here's another...
Okay, let's get it.
Here's another poem.
It's not Patrick, that's Jimmy.
That's Jimmy.
Yeah, that's Jimmy talking.
Jimmy can be a creep pervert.
Yeah, well, he's also 16.
Jimmy probably idolizes Pete Aubert.
bear. Damn! I just saw a picture of that for the first time. Really? Yep. What did
you think of the design? I thought the design was actually mad original. Yeah, it
is. Here's another poem I got here. "I can't stand." I just wish that
people would tell me the truth. I hate it when you tell me that you love me but
could be careless to treat me like it. I can't stand it when you tell me that you
You are not talking to a certain someone, but you shut off your phone and I check your messages
only to hear, "Hey look, I'm sorry for what happened earlier.
I'm so sorry, but please quit ignoring me.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it anymore.
No more lies.
I have done what you have asked for and you have lied to me since May.
I swear that I don't talk to him, Jimmy.
He just leaves messages.
Trust?
Trust, when you just proved my point?
I check your messages and hear his voice yet again.
And here he is apologizing for what happened earlier.
What exactly happened earlier?
It just helps prove that while I'm at work,
you were lying to me and messing around on me.
I can't stand to be lied to anymore.
I can't talk to anyone anymore.
If I try, I have nothing but problems to talk about.
And I am emo?
Just hug.
I am seriously on the edge of just kissing my life goodbye.
No, I know.
Don't do that.
Reason I had to live, but the pain I'm sitting here crying.
Is that what you want?
It is to make me cry once a night over you.
Well, you let me be my, well, let me be your Janani in a bottle.
I can't stand it for it's VIs.
That's Roman numeral four, right?
- Yeah, that's six. - That's six.
- Six, six!
I try really hard in life and never get a good job
or any kind of compliments,
but I bet you didn't know that I am sick to my stomach,
did you?
No, you didn't never ask me what's wrong.
Do you care?
Honestly, do you care?
Well, the only thing I'm saying is I love you!
- Damn. - Lacey Ann Horton.
- God. - Holy shit.
- Fucking damn, dude.
What I wouldn't kill to be laced.
Who I wouldn't kill.
Here's an editor's note from the comments.
Hey, I was at the movies with two managers.
We were supposed to talk about me getting a raise,
but instead they went off and told me that they were going to the concession stand
and I get a text saying that they would talk to me later.
They had found out some of their friends to go party with,
so I sat in my car as it was overheated and laid in my trunk watching cars and soccer or something like that.
But you were on my mind the whole time.
I love you, sweetie, and I thought that you promised me no more cutting.
Well, are you okay? What happened at the hospital, baby?
Please tell me that you are okay
I have to work a double shift tomorrow
But I will stop by on my time off if my car doesn't overheat it overheated on the way home
From them damn movies - I've been stranded since 130. It is 330
I am so tired, but if you can text me to tell me if it is okay to come over
I love you so much. And of course we are still together. I love you
I wish you could have been there in my trunk with me. I was so scared
it is dark and it is outside. I have never been more scared in my life. Well, baby, I'm
so sorry for putting you through so much stress, but I will make it up somehow. I promise this
to you. I love you. I'm going to go to bed. Mwah!
Hey, speaking of cutting, how about you cut a rug up there? Show us your dance moves.
That's nice.
Damn. All right.
Is that sound getting picked up?
Yeah, it's great. It sounds great.
Okay, I have two more poems here.
Two more. All right. Okay.
I'm buckling in.
This one's pretty short.
- Hit it.
I think you're pretty and short.
- Okay.
- Take it off.
- What?
- Take off your clothes.
- I'm not taking off the clothes.
- Take off your clothes, you stripper.
- These are my poetry outfit.
- Strip, strip, strip.
- All right, I'm gonna start this poem right now.
- This guy wants you to strip to show it off.
- I'm not doing it.
- I want all the ladies and the boys to see you.
- Let me start my poem, goddammit.
- Go ahead and strip it off.
And this is a poem about really just the pain in my heart.
(imitates guitar)
Okay?
It's about the pain in my heart.
African's Goliath Frog.
Goliath Frog throws his tummy around.
Rainforest is where he is often found.
Snapping up shellfish blue,
consuming littler frogs too.
Slurping up insects with nary a sound.
- Wow.
- Metaphorical.
- Okay, now make like a frog
and told off all your clothes.
- Yeah, hop out of those.
- Jump out of that.
- Hop out of those lily pads.
- Maybe this final poem,
maybe this final poem will give you exactly what you want.
- Your armpits.
- Take off your croaks.
- Let me fuck her like the island boys.
Talking about beating up that cooter.
Fuck her so aggressively,
she's gonna need a riding scooter.
I'm gonna screw her like the pear,
but I'm going in single,
talking about that luscious pinkness.
We all need a little chat and mingle.
She can't handle this sex,
talking about making her legs go stanky,
smelling like the goodest of goods
and the dankest of danky.
That smell, you know what I mean,
not the kind that reeks of fish.
I may be from the island, but this is my one true wish.
Signals straight to Johnson & Johnson,
pheromones that make your blood boil.
This spring is cocked and loaded,
talking about re-ready to uncoil.
She beats on my hourglass,
trying to remove the sand from inside,
talking about that island boy sex.
I'm gonna come as hard as the tide.
I'll stooge on her head like tats cover my face,
talking about connect the dots
and get the fuck out of my place.
Damn.
- That it?
- Oh my God.
- Goddamn, Jimmy, everybody.
- Jimmy!
- All right, keep it going for Jimmy.
That was incredible.
It's some incredible poetry.
Great, well.
- I mean, that's pretty much it for the open mic, right?
If you guys would have me, I would love to close it out.
- Oh, headliner?
- With a, just, it's fuds, anything goes open, Mike.
Anything truly goes. - Yeah, go do your thing!
- And I've prepared.
- I would love to see this.
- I won't even tell you what I've prepared.
- Okay.
- But I'm just gonna go and do it.
- Just go do it!
- Here's this.
- And I'm on the ones and twos.
- Oh yeah.
- Cameron Fetter, everybody!
(clapping)
Look at this tall motherfucker. He's looking like that Mike Stand.
Yeah, he looks like his name is Mike Stand. That's how he got so tall, from standing.
Hey, you enjoyed the show down there buddy? How you feeling? Good? Ready for it to be
over? What so you can go home and eat another weak ass Thanksgiving plate?
Oh shit! I mean seriously bro, all I saw on your plate
was ham and sweet potatoes and two rolls.
And that's it.
- That's all he had on that plate.
- That's all, okay, all right.
But this is not why I came up here.
This is not what I came up to do.
- I thought that that was gonna be the whole finale.
- Can you imagine?
- Yeah, I could definitely.
- If that was the whole finale, honestly,
I wouldn't be able to handle it
'cause my sides would be split.
- I would have him writing Jimmy poems
about taking his life.
- Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
- He'd be cutting his shit wide open.
he had i will sit here on the thirty minutes
to him
but he doesn't have that lacy and or no all hello he's got a different type of
girl
he's getting up beautiful
honest and smart
he's really got uh... steve lacy
and horton his two boyfriends yet
now i think that you
yet yet i got an elephant boyfriend
Just keep cooking his ass!
Alright, okay, here we go. Here we go guys. You ready?
Okay.
I walk a lonely road, only road that I have ever known.
Oh my god.
Don't know where it goes, but it's home to me and I walk alone.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I'm walking down the line that divides me somewhere in my mind
'til the borderline, borderline of me and I walk alone
ah
My shadow's only one that walks beside me
My shallow
Parts the only thing
Sometimes I wish someone would come and find me
*laughing*
Keep going!
*singing*
Oh my f*cking god, wow. Wow.
Thank you everybody for coming to FUDS. Anything goes Open Mic.
Get on up here, get on up here.
Everybody, you know what they do at the end of an Open Mic.
Everyone who was on the list comes up on stage.
Wow, what a great...
I don't think I've ever cried from singing before.
And that was one of the most beautiful fucking things I've ever that was more beautiful than any of my poems
I failed up on strudel
[MUSIC PLAYING]