Hi it's me Patrick from Podcasts About List. I'm sure at this point you're
already aware that every single one of these video episodes is started with a
little cold open to get you excited for the episode you're about to watch. So
this week I was tasked with creating the cold open and I just wanted to say that
I'm very proud of it and I hope that you like it just as much as I liked making
it. We have a great episode for you today and thank you for watching and then
start the video.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
(electronic music)
(man howls)
- Okay, and start over.
Okay, now sing into the microphone and start over.
- Okay, so I have to sing?
- Okay, just do what you did, but start over.
Okay, am I positioned correctly?
Do I look like I'm in some kind of red racist clan?
No, wait.
No.
Now you do.
No, you look like an AT.
Okay, so I'm never wearing anything ever again.
Really?
Asshole.
Our plan worked.
Fuck.
I'm never wearing anything ever again.
You're not going to get me to be naked all the time just by making fun of my clothes.
We're going to do a red hot chili peppers episode.
Dude, I have to say, we only wear a sock on our penis.
It was huge for guys like me who think aliens are sexy as fuck.
Not only does ET get to be naked at the beginning, then he dresses like a girl.
That is a serious score.
Hot as fuck yeah the first movie you get to watch with your family and Jack
I'll get to see a naked alien you see a naked alien and then a girl dressed in one
Yeah, and it's the same alien, but naked alien. Yeah. Yeah, he does go completely sheet white
He looks like a there's a scene in ET. I always forget that that scene existed where he like like he turns white et
Turn he say um nice to meet you. I'm et
Let's go yeah, he says gosh golly yeah
Yeah white ass alien uh-huh they fuck you et we write him - at the end he's already queers fuck
That's right cuz he's under five feet tall
Yeah the but the scene where et turns like sheet white I forgot about and then I kept seeing like
Like that picture posted of like et
Turning like they just eat dead et on the ground half dead eat in the river half dead. He's half dead
Okay, you have to continue half dead alien have dead white alien
All right, that's how you find it
When you want to cool if you want to Google search it you look up half dead white alien and that comes up et
In a river pops up
What were you saying though? I just forgot that existed you forgot I forgot that scene existed
And I thought that it was a nightmare that I had when I was a kid okay that I understand
I've definitely had nightmares before and then like I've had a lot of nightmares where et
Had nightmares before but where I'm like man. What a weird nightmare, and then like two years later. It's like some weird holiday
I'm at home the cables on small soldiers comes on and I'm like oh fucking shit. You wasn't even it was just a memory
I have yeah, I think specifically the et river scene. I think that's one that everybody thinks they just experienced
Yeah, I thought that I was sure
I've never heard you guys talk about this before I think might be right. I was convinced that that was filmed in the Charles River
As I love doing that when you're a kid is B is just be like oh
It's actually the office building in my town.
Which is a little different growing up in Boston
than growing up in Wilmington, North Carolina.
(laughing)
The only movie--
Not even, there's some movies filmed in Wilmington.
Growing up in Leland, like an hour outside,
I was like, I'm pretty sure that's actually
the back of the Best Buy.
(laughing)
I remember when, in the office, when Jim and Pam have,
they like, when they finally have a kiss or whatever,
get married or some shit like that,
you see like the back of a it's like the back of a warehouse or something oh yeah
and i was like
they had to use it so i think that's the best by in wilmington north carolina
all this by the exact as a
but it also was a bit you know it could have been filmed at best the police
station in my town was in a movie one time and it was slow that's keep
okay cameron dot redhead
haha
but you're not supposed to see you're not supposed to actually run i don't
remember what it was a little while i remember it was fine time to use it the
fucking Sarnay as they made you shit
famous.
Oh dude that wasn't that was water
town.
You only have one town over.
It's one over but the only the only
movie I remember the same police
station.
Yeah you're right.
Growing up like
I never pieced it together that it
was filmed in New Hampshire was a
Jumanji.
Really.
I thought that's a lot of the
Jumanji.
Wait I thought they filmed it.
I thought they filmed that inside
of a board game.
What the fuck are you talking
about.
Now a key in New Hampshire.
That's where that's where all of
that was like shot. They filmed Zathura in space. Yeah. For real?
For real. I love Zathura. I mean, technically, you know,
with the Earth spinning. Is there a scene in that movie where the
guy, the kid is like, "Oh, fuck, there's something at the door,"
and he goes and he opens the door and it's just space out there?
I think so. Yeah. That's so awesome. And then, who's that? That movie's so sick, dude.
It's Kristen Stewart. Kristen Stewart, yeah. And then it's like the reveal?
And then there's the lizards. What are the lizard aliens called, Jubio?
- In Zathura?
- Search Zathura, Lizard Alien.
- But there's this scene where like,
it's Dax Shepard in that movie.
And Kristen Stewart's character's like,
that's the hottest guy I've ever seen.
And then it's revealed that it's just the little kid
at the end.
- Oh yeah.
- It's been grown up.
- Wait, this is the alien from Zathura?
- No, Search Lizard Alien's Zathura.
- No, this is definitely him.
- Search Lizard Alien.
- This is him, show this.
- Put this up on screen.
- Yeah, you gotta put it up.
- That's him.
(laughing)
- I just wanna know what they're called.
I remember thinking the name of them was really cool.
- They're called character alien lizard with gun 3D rigged.
(laughing)
- That looks like a--
- Please just look it up, I wanna know.
- Turtle boy from Toy Machine.
- They should make a new one.
- I guess I'll look it up on my phone, you're useless.
- If they made a third, so they went back to Jumanji.
But if they made a third, if they went,
Jumanji is Africa, which is the past,
and then they do Zathura, which is space,
which is the future.
- I don't think Jumanji takes place in Africa,
I think it takes place in a fictional world of Jumanji.
No, it's Africa.
I don't remember that movie that well.
No, maybe it is.
You're not going to believe what the lizard aliens are
called in Zagora.
They're called Zorgons.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
Bet you're glad I looked that up.
I am glad.
Zorgons.
Did you see that one of the new Jumanji movies,
one of the plot point--
like the entire movie, I guess.
I didn't see the movie, but I read about this.
I think part of it is like, there's a mix-up
when they go into the game, it's like a video game,
and it's like Kevin Hart in Jack Black's body,
and Jack Black is just doing Kevin Hart the entire movie.
- Jack Black does Black Jack,
like we've talked about many times.
He does Black Jack.
He finally gets his opportunity to go Black Jack.
- How many of those did they make?
I feel like they made like two or three.
- They made three that Kevin Hart was.
- Heavy, heavy fart.
- Yeah. - That's Jack Black.
- Heavy Bart.
- Mm-hmm, yep.
Keep going.
- Kevin Hart's heaven fart.
He dies in the movie.
- Hey, as a heaven fart?
We're just playing heaven cart.
- Spoiler alert.
- Up there.
- That'd be pretty good.
That'd be a good video game
while your grandparents are in the Mario Kart situation.
It's not a bad idea.
- That's pretty good.
- Well, check this out.
- Pull this photo up, Jubio.
- Your dad's gonna get demonetized.
Don't do that.
Don't fucking do that.
But yeah, if they make a third Jumanji style Jumanji,
- Okay, I'll admit, Jumanji isn't in Africa.
- It's in a board game. - For now.
- Look, I'll, yeah, for now.
(laughing)
You're gonna go to Africa to meet Jumanji.
- I will, I'm charting an expedition
to see maybe if there's a town called Jumanji in Africa.
But Zathura, that's in space.
- You don't need to chart an expedition
just to look at Google Maps.
- Here's my pitch, I mean, it needs to be a trilogy, right?
They already, they have Jumanji, that's in the jungle.
that's in space. So then I think maybe that they could have like a third one that's just
called like...
In the water?
Okay, no.
No.
Just let him do his thing.
That's really fucking stupid.
Yeah, right.
That's basically the same as the jungle.
That's basically...
You're right. I forgot there's a fish in Jumanji.
And you wouldn't be able to hear the lines.
Yeah.
Asshole.
And I'm sorry. And Cameron, put her there.
Thank you.
Okay, continue your third Jumanji.
Okay, Coolsville. And it's a town.
Holy shit. It's a normal town. Oh, that's where Scooby-Doo lives. That's a good point.
Is it you they could make the third one a Scooby-Doo movie. Yep.
That's a really good point.
Well, you could get it could be like one of those themed like you know
that
they'll have like a Scooby-Doo version of Monopoly. Yeah. What if you get sucked into that?
Wait, what if the third one is just random stuff? They just go in there and it's just all stuff everywhere.
Yeah, there's just dice and chess.
It's just an actual board game.
They get sucked into it, and now they're on a tiny version of life.
Oh my god.
That's genius.
That's the thing about Zothro.
And there's just shit everywhere.
There's just tons of bullshit.
Yeah, there's just fucking bullshit.
There's just fucking shit everywhere.
Yeah, just garbage and all that.
Just leftover shit everywhere.
Leftover food and all the kinds of stuff.
Diapers and nasty shit like that.
There's shit and junk everywhere.
There's life and payday I played a lot of.
It's the same thing to me.
They're pretty much the same game.
Life was one of those games I never played, but I always looked at it and I was like, "Whoa."
One day when I get older, I'm gonna play this every day.
Did you guys, if you could get sucked into one board game, what you going with?
Not Mouse Trap.
Guess who?
You would be so good at Guess Who.
You look just like a Guess Who guy.
Wait, do you have a punch in on the hat?
Take your hat off.
No, a hat can be part.
Imagine this on a...
Guess who got it?
Wait, do you have a punch in on the hat?
Is...
Take your hat off.
No, a hat can be part...
[Laughter]
He looks just like Guess Who.
Yeah, when I have, when I have like long hair...
Does your guy look surprised?
[Laughter]
When I have longer hair, I look just like a Guess Who character.
You already look just like him, dude.
Oh my fucking god, dude.
This isn't showing up.
Oh, there it is.
Yeah, wait.
(laughing)
God damn, guess who?
That is crazy.
If you got sucked into guess who, though,
are you just gonna--
(laughing)
That does look like me.
If you got sucked into guess who,
are you just gonna sit there all day?
Like, I feel like that one's a pretty boring one.
You know, you don't really have to do much in guess who.
You gotta hold that face 'til you get stuck.
You're trapped for eternity.
- I'll try it right now.
- That is good.
- That is a good guess who face.
So what would you say if you were guessing who?
So you and me are playing guess who and we're both on this guy.
- We're both on this guy?
Okay, I'd be like, is your guy a girl?
- Yes.
- Okay, and I'm putting down a bunch of pieces.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, my guy's moving!
Caleb, my guy's moving!
My guy's talking to me!
- Well, which one of you has me?
We both can't do so you both have one guy. We don't know.
Okay. It's a new version of guess who where there's just one tile
and we both and we don't know that we have the same. Yeah.
We open up the thing. It's one. It's just a picture of him.
It's not a cartoon at all. Yeah. I go. It's a gift. It's
just me like yeah. Is your guy? I mean, yeah. Is your guy did
he just put a hat on? No. Oh my god. I know now you look like
guess who looking so sly and coy. Is your guy sly? Is your guy coy? Is your guy kind of...
I'm being really specific. Is your guy clever? Does your guy have a wry smile? What's your
guys favorite food? I think pizza. Oh okay. Put down a bunch of them. These guys don't
like pizza. These people couldn't like pizza. Their skin's too good. Pizza's good though.
- He just voted as a motherfucking liar.
- No fucking lie.
- True.
- Yeah, I'd probably go into Scattergories though.
- Yeah.
- That's not a good one.
- That Scattergories guy, the logo.
- Man, I'd probably go into Scattergories or Sudoku.
- The Scattergories logo go hard.
- Yeah.
- No, you need, man, shut up.
- There's two logos that go hard as fuck
and it's Sherlyn Williams and it's Gattagories.
- Who's Gattagories?
That's what I, when I play, Gattagories.
- I actually feel like, I go into Hot Wheels.
Huh hot wheels hot ones hot wheels. Oh my god wait a hot one
Do your game would be we should do hot wheels where we make celebrities eat toy cars
See if they need 10 toy cars sitting there with Halle Berry, she's too deep
You learn it yesterday cat got it why you just dropping
It in is that what that means yeah, okay, I didn't know that I'd love I thought it was like a
catch from weird
What don't say that what what
Okay, yeah, I'm a pervert yeah, I want to give her gastroenteritis no I give her gastroenteritis
That's not what I sound like guys. It's not very funny to do that. I want to put my finger in her butt
No, I didn't sound anything like that. Yeah
No, no, no
Make her a puppet with my finger. I didn't say anything like that. I said it I said something on accident. I
Wish I'd talked like that. Yeah, dude. It's so cool that like you'd be a laughingstock
Like like Patrick Warburton, I feel like has that voice because he's so tall but it's so cool when somebody is like
like six foot eight and they have the voice of a mouse.
- Who'da.
I met a guy the other day where he was like
really, really good looking, like model good looks
and like dressed really cool and I was like,
man this guy's cool as shit.
And then I met him and he's like,
hey it's very nice to meet you.
I was like.
- You met a gay guy?
- No, he was straight!
That's the worst part!
- The worst part.
- He was straight, I couldn't even suck his cock, dude.
It was awful.
Yeah, but it scared me. I was like you really do it. It always is all just a fucking create a character randomized sometimes
Yeah, you know yeah, that's all what let's hey. You know what that's why life is one big game of guess who mm-hmm
Mm-hmm bringing it back to that it is a bit of guess who but it's guess it you're trying to guess
Who's the correct religion?
Yeah, yeah, yes
Guess who should be in every like you know and every sci-fi and like Star Wars that they play like like
They're fucked up future chess and yeah, I think every Saipan movie where they're playing fucked up future chess
They shouldn't it chess will not survive. It's gonna be guess who yeah, it's gonna be that'll be so cool
Imagine imagine future guess who dude and you're like is your guy's ab rack 22x. Yeah
Well, there's only one Zabrak. Yeah everything but one. Yeah. Oh my god 22 xx
Fucking people it's categories. Yeah, some big-ass like yeah, okay. What's yeah piercer? What's every what's a?
Zorgonian that begins with Z everyone's like oh so blows
Zorbo's
Blurs yeah, I think I've only played scat again way too easy, but I played with I there's so many words by that point
It's categories is what that's where you come up with things. It's like it's like categories, and then you have yeah
It's like you roll it'll die. I played categories one time and it was but it was I played it
Basically the two teams were essentially one of the teams
Did not speak English very well. Yeah, and they really made the game a lot funnier
Yeah, they're just throwing out Spanish stuff and we were like, oh, I don't even know if that's okay. We don't know if that
Like fucking the scoreboard is just yeah, we didn't you guys are just getting them demolished
They were putting the numbers in Spanish - I had no idea what was going on
Yeah, yeah, there's I don't think there's numbers really
Letters game there is no sleep. It's numbers. We're the numbers under the sea. Oh
Doesn't quite it's a good answer because you get because you get points by the letter when I play it
We should be playing we should have a game night
Yeah, we had one the other night, which was pretty fun when we had a game night at the pub
Did we yeah you guys don't remember?
No, okay
What oh we played connect for no we play was a while ago meme or something oh, right?
Yeah, I do remember that I mean I didn't even remember that as being a game because it was so damn far
No, we played what was it? It's called like crazy. It was too fun for me to remember
We played some some game some it was called. Yeah, it was called. It was if you laugh you drink
Yeah, you drink and it was there was and almost everything
I don't want to spoil too much because I want to play that it was pretty fun on
Today it is funny. It is it is funny that they do have just like
board games at bars
I've never really like like just go there and hang out. Yeah, it's funny. They have drinks at bars. No. What are you doing?
What board games it?
Was trying to be Bill Maher with your eyes the board games of bars thing is a newer kind of thing yeah
Yeah, it's like why they have access to our fricking bar BS culture that I've never done the axe throwing thing yet. Yeah
Yeah, I bet first try I do that bullseye
probably
Didn't we try to in Philly and they were all booked up. Yeah. Yeah, we're what an evil city
Middle of the day yeah noon completely the axe-throwing bar is completely booked
The guys you want to go to make
What a cesspool fucked up dude city of fucking brotherly fuck you
Think about that yeah true. That's crazy. That's cuz they took away all the guns in that liberal Democrat cities all these kids
You got to go out there and instead of having Draco's in their pockets. They got axes that they're throwing. Yeah
Yeah, just like London. I got to throw with you what video games are doing nowadays people playing God of War
Yep, stuff like this. They think it's okay to carry an axe around and yeah other people
They go they go it's okay if I if I kill 10,000 people with this axe cuz they respawn
Yeah, no you learn that from people kids nowadays think that people respond when you kill them. Yeah, it's not you think so
But they don't do that. They should have a video game that when you die you die the game shuts off
They have that and there's one I know one guy who responds games, and he's way more important than any video game
Who yep Jesus Christ although he's not so yeah, I was saying about picking religion
I think I'm leaning heavily towards Islam again
Yeah, I think I'm getting back into Islam because of all the World Cup stuff seems pretty cool to me
Where you have a entire country called guitar and you can not you can't have any beers there
Yeah, they call it guitar right and you think hard rock. Yeah, you're thinking. Oh shit. Yeah
You got that you got your beer can sitting on either side of your head you're like I'm ready to play I'm ready to rock
I'm ready to
They're saying football football you're going oh my god
Guitar with a hundred thousand people watching football you get there your beers get confiscated
They cut your head off and they start using it to play soccer
And then you get there thinking it's gonna be all hard rock and then look who's there maroon
Yep, god damn it
What's going on guitar
Country
Music what the hell is this? Hell? No, where's
Boy music maroon 5 is not boy music
Sentiment you've changed my mind that's not a boy line having your body say yes to something your brain saying no
That's seriously some look for the guy with the fastest car
Yeah, they change all their lyrics up when they go yeah, they have to yeah, yeah, that's like when you go to horror is
In awesome called guitar it actually guitar. It's called guitar pretty much. Yeah, okay pretty much pretty much
There's a country called the rhythm
There's a big debate. It's like Sunni and Kufi or what's-her-name Sunni and Shiite. Yeah, it's like
Sunni and Shiites
Shit
Sunni Sunni, I will sue I will
sue me I
Will go to guitar Sunni and take
Yeah football yeah, I'll put my foot in my own balls are what's next a country called the bass
Yeah, and then drums and vocals and vocals and keyboards and keyboards and not so much
In saying more cowbells, right, where's the cowbell country
You know, they should
The original version of that sketch he comes in and he says more guitar
He says, "I want there to be more guitar."
And they were like, "This is already really funny.
You know what would make it even funnier?"
If it's an instrument that everybody likes.
Well, he improvised it. He did it live.
That's why they broke Jimmy Fallon.
Yeah.
Yeah, they buck broke him.
Look at that poor bastard on TV.
Broke him over their knee.
I think he's being held hostage. I really do.
I think Jimmy Fallon did something.
Nobody has ever had more fun than he has had.
Yeah, dude, every day he gets to wake up and fall down fucking 50 flights of stairs. He's so drunk.
So awesome, dude.
I think he's living in like...
He's actually my best friend and he's being held hostage.
I think he has some kind of like vision thing. I think he just sees Candyland around him.
Yeah.
I think he has like pyro vision from TF2.
They inject him with something every morning that makes him see everybody as a puppet.
That's why he laughs so much during his own questions and stuff,
because he'll be talking and he'll see like a unicorn fly by or something.
A gumdrop man.
Yeah.
He's talking to like fucking like Drake who's just made entirely out of gumdrops.
So people say you're so sweet.
What?
What are you talking about?
So what flavor are you?
He's just so fucking crazy.
So your mom was a wax bottle and your dad was wax lips.
And you grew up in Candyland.
Jimmy, the cameras are off.
His life took me like Joker.
They filmed all his parts separately.
Yeah, he's green screened in.
Yeah.
Yeah. But in his case, he has to be rainbow screened in because his world is
so...
Because he's LGBT.
Yep, that too.
Yeah.
Yeah, we should maybe have a triple host of the next tonight show. Maybe us three could do it. Yeah, I think if you're listening buddy
We can I would I would consider you a mentor. I'm kind of I've been consider us Minto's cuz you're so
No, I'm kidding I I have been kind of tired lately
So I would prefer if we could maybe have it changed to the this evening show
Yeah, oh, that's a good point cuz I just a little earlier not not so much. I've never stayed up so late
I'm a very early riser in the reverse sense.
Have you, uh...
[laughter]
I've got a better...
Yeah.
Have you... no, you guys, you guys have... well, you went to Universal, right?
Oh, yeah.
Did you go on the...
And I did it big.
Did you go on the Jimmy Fallon ride?
I didn't go to Univ... I've never been to Universal. I was busy at the Universal team.
Wow.
Studying.
Actually, everyone's in the Universal.
Yeah.
Damn.
Drop that mic.
Holy fuck shit.
That's why.
I rode the VelociCoaster, though.
Really? I did too. Yeah, no you didn't. He's lying. Did it blow your shit back? Yeah. I read the
VelociCoaster. You're lying. He's lying. He hasn't been there when the VelociCoaster
was built. A kid got killed on it. I read that. That's not true. Three kids got killed at the same
time because it was so scary. That makes it cooler first of all. I read the VelociRaptor. Oh, the meme?
Yeah. So that actually changed my perspective on quite a few subjects. Yeah. Including math and science. Yeah. Yeah, when I
I rode the VelociCoaster, Shaquille O'Neal was on it.
He's a liar.
They wouldn't let him on it.
He's too tall.
His head would get chopped off.
His head wouldn't get chopped off.
Wait, did his head get chopped off?
Wait, that's actually the most awesome story I've ever heard.
Wait, you've never been on that?
I've been on it three times.
And I almost bought a hat on it.
Oh, and Shaquille O'Neal's wife was on the ride with him.
And I hear she's only one inch tall.
And it's like, how did that work?
His wife is Tinkerbell.
It is a little bit weird that like every woman that Shaquille O'Neal has publicly dated has
been not just normal size but like really small.
Yeah, I mean it's almost women are 5'2".
Normal size is gonna be really small.
Nobody, but he's only dated women who are like...
I know, but what I'm saying is I don't think there's much difference.
There's a difference probably with his penis.
You think he's ever picked his girlfriend up by her head?
Like this?
Like, just palmed her like that.
Oh, definitely.
Like, "Hey, I need to grab something on top of the fridge."
Like a claw in a factory?
Just like, moving her along?
He's picking his girlfriend up by her head so she can get like,
or like, "Oh yeah, we put the paper towels up high this week."
"Alright, go grab 'em."
Yeah.
Like, did you ever see the video of like that like spine training thing for a baby
where it like holds the top of the baby's head and it like swings?
Yeah.
Yeah, he just does that.
That's how...
I forgot about that one.
That's how he entertains his girlfriend.
Yeah.
She's like, dude, let's get him questions.
She's like, who are you texting?
And he's just like...
If I was that tall...
I forget what I was talking about.
If I was that tall and I had a hand that big,
I'd be holding a...
Shit, I'd play basketball.
I'd be the greatest baller of all time.
Dude, I'd be so good at rock, paper, scissors
I would use my powers to just get every cat out of a tree.
No you wouldn't.
Leave that to the firefighters.
I've never seen a cat in a tree.
I have.
Okay, I don't care.
I've seen a bird in a tree.
Me too.
And I called the fire department because I got confused.
I saw a partridge in a pear tree.
Really?
At Christmas.
Anything else?
Yeah.
Two turtle doves.
Anything else?
A French hen.
One?
Yeah.
It was just at the store.
What store has all that?
Birds-R-Us.
That song should be like, and 100 ornaments in a tree.
Yeah.
In a pine tree.
We'll probably get into it closer to Christmas, but let me tell you what,
there would be some serious, if I was in charge of writing that song for the next year,
there would be some serious revisions.
I'm talking Nintendo Switch,
I'm talking fucking a couple of cans of soda pop.
Spirit of Christmas.
Eggs.
Most of my groceries.
They do need to add the Spirit of Christmas to that song.
On the first day of Christmas, I got my groceries.
Yeah, all of them.
On the second day of Christmas--
You still have to get groceries during Christmas time.
Twice as many groceries.
I got more groceries, because guess what?
I'm having people over.
Yep, who you having over?
Third day of Christmas, I'm having people over.
Yeah.
Fourth day of Christmas, the people are going home.
They slept over.
Oh, all of them?
We all had too much to drink.
Wait, did you guys have like a sex--
--group sex thing?
Fifth day of Christmas, I'm getting tested.
You have groups-- you had group sex.
For what?
It group sex on Christmas.
doing a whole screening.
- Well it's not on Christmas yet,
this is during the days of Christmas.
- Wait, you did a screening of your orgasm?
- We're doing screenings after
to make sure that none of us got--
- Screenings, like you're all sitting there doing--
- Screenings, watching the video.
- Doing like film review, like a high school football team.
- Nope, you're all sitting in like,
you're all sitting like this,
with a notebook, you're sitting back in the theater chairs.
- Sitting on--
- There's a flicker of the projector.
- Benches of the locker room,
with you with a projector here.
- And you see that, what's that?
That's a wart.
- Yeah, fifth day of Christmas.
Like Al Pacino in and get that work burned off in
Once upon a time in Hollywood. Yeah, that just that he's in there with you and he's just talking about the movie
What a picture Wow
It's a picture of my penis
What a picture oh my what a picture and so if you can zoom in right there wow, that's just beautiful
Look at that scroat fold
That's nasty that's nasty crap that's from some nasty crap. Yeah, I'm burping so you know it is that ghost energy
You know what it is. It's Black Friday. Yeah, yeah, so everybody knows
What happens the first?
Friday or I guess the first what happens the first Wednesday that is a
Wednesday is when you get prepared for Black Friday, right so that's not what I'm saying
So maybe you let me finish my little segue introduction here, or maybe you want to do it. Okay. I'll do it. You know what?
Okay, so Black Friday was invented by and I can't say it
It was invented by and I'm gonna say it. It was invented invented by turkeys
Why did they invent turkeys?
Who and you know what turkey in a minute black bread? You're you know what your job is so hard
Doing segues into the list is so hard.
Everybody knows what happens.
The Wednesday that's four days after Stinksgiving,
it's Black Friday. It's Black Friday today, guys.
Wait, we actually know who invented Black Friday.
Oh.
It's Jay Gould.
And that was a famous turkey.
So we're going to talk Black Friday today.
Alright.
So let's pull up this list here.
Now I just want to give you a little background on this website
website before we get into what so this is this is ranker we've been on ranker
I know we've been on ranker but I'm just I'm just showing off the website a
little bit first okay show off okay so we have ranker I mean we can see the
type of stuff that they're showing on ranker yeah we do have ranker for the
Republicans we do yeah say nay more why nay more has so much beef with Black
Panther and Wakanda say nay more oh I get that yeah and he has beef with Black
Is he the bad guy from the new movie?
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Did you see it?
No, I did not see it.
I was going to ask you for spoilers.
That's one.
You could look at this article maybe to find some spoilers because it says he's YA's beef.
He's pretty timid about spoiling the bloody pictures.
Okay, wait, you have to click on the thing.
Okay, yeah.
So here's some other stuff that we have on Ranker.
Actors who played roles written for someone completely different and nailed it.
The most epic moments in World Cup history.
underrated movies based on real life crimes, all the known rings from the Lord
of the Rings and what they do. So you're getting the general idea of what kind of
thing we'll see on this website.
Yeah, and for the first one there, actors who played roles written for someone
else and nailed it. I heard that Optimus Prime was not supposed to be in
Transformers. I heard that that was supposed to be...
It was supposed to be Kevin Costner.
Yeah, Kevin Costner.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Kevin Costner was supposed to play that, but he got sick. He got really,
really sick. He got sick. It's called the Cybertron curse. Yeah. It was supposed to just be
Kevin Costner walking around and doing all that. And he's supposed to be doing the same exact voice from JFK.
Yeah, yeah. He's supposed to be going, "Optimus, we gotta..." There's another character.
Well, he's talking to the mirror. "Optimus, you gotta get your damn self together. We gotta stop the..."
"Optimus, you're so beautiful." He was very sweet. "Optimus, you're the most beautiful..." Yeah, and he was going like, "Back and to
the all spark back and to the all spark. So yeah, you get the
general idea of what's going on on this on this website. They
have a science section that I was looking at here. Probably where I would probably
spend most of my time on. Right. Wait, hold on. So you're looking, we're
looking at the science section here. We got science, Ross Geller is
the number two best fictional paleontologist. Ah. Number,
chicken is number one best kind of bird to eat. That's true. Penguin,
number two coolest animal that lives in the in the tundra. I mean,
So that's the science section.
What's a pangicula?
I don't know, that's why I didn't read that one.
Oh shit, okay.
It's a meat-eating plant.
So we're on the science section today, and you're thinking, "What science?
Why are we here?"
And I found this list on Ranker, on the science section.
What happens to your body when you die in a human stampede?
By Laura Allen.
And you can see this is categorized under the "weirdly interesting" section of the science.
Weirdly interesting.
I'm finding myself weirdly interested by this.
- That is, I mean I guess this is clear
the tide of Black Friday.
- Yeah.
- Right, which is in Black Friday you get--
- There's somebody that died in this game.
- In the service of trying to get something very cool,
you know, maybe a TV, maybe they re-released
another version of the PlayStation
that's thin or something, right?
And you're running and you're fucking jumping
on people's heads like Goombas trying to get that Nintendo.
- It could be worth it to you to die for this.
I would give my fucking life for a Sony Ericsson.
Dude, for a new salad spinner?
Ugh!
Oh my god.
A sous vide?
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
I wanna die right now!
You wanna cook all your food in a water bag?
Yes.
I would rather fucking die
than not have a sous vide in my house.
So either way I'm winning.
I bought my dad a sous vide for Christmas two years ago
and I haven't seen him use it.
Really?
Yeah.
How expensive were they?
It was like 150 bucks.
Oh, I thought they were like $1,000.
No.
Oh man, I might have to get one.
I had my siblings chip in.
What the hell do you use it for?
You cook a steak really good.
But you can cook a steak really good with a damn cast iron pan.
Yeah, but you boil it first.
In a water bag.
Oh, a boiled steak?
That sounds damn good.
Sounds so good.
Yeah, so I kind of just took selections from this list.
It was kind of long, but we can just start off here.
Every year we hear about some poor soul
dying in the massive shoppers on Black Friday.
Death by human stampede isn't the most common way to go,
but it definitely is one of the most horrifying.
But what causes human stampedes,
and why do you die in a stampede
rather than being helped or picked up by others?
The answers will rock your faith
in human goodness to the core.
- That's okay.
Yeah, I'm ready to be rocked.
It's the perfect time of the year
to have your faith in humanity completely rocked to the core.
- I love that this list is on Ranker.
It was making me laugh so much
that Ranker put this out for Black Friday.
(both laughing)
- And it's weirdly interesting.
- It is weirdly interesting.
So first of all, you won't be able to move.
When trying to avoid being killed by a crowd, you should be sure you're able to move.
I will say, I've definitely been at things before where I was like,
"There's too many people up in this bitch, I'm out of here."
Yeah, I do think about that sometimes.
If you can't move in a room,
just don't be in it. But I also have been at shows before where
you're on the floor level thing and there's a million people around you,
And I do convince myself that I have superhuman strength and that I can hold back everybody
doing this.
But then somebody crushes you to death.
Yeah, you die and there's a bigger guy.
So the mistake you're making here is you should make sure that you're able to move.
I have definitely.
I remember, I think next time I go to a big crowded concert, maybe a stadium show or something,
I'm on the floor, there's a crush, I'm scared, I'll just kind of pull out my exosuit.
That's smart.
I think the button on your chest yeah
the worst crowd crush I've been in was was a
One of the what the hell boy
I just clicked a button on this by accident nice damn the worst one I ever was in I think was when the
Patriots won the Super Bowl
Living in Boston I lived on the corner on or I didn't live I worked on the corner on Boylston
and I had to go like a quarter of a block to get out of that.
- I had the exact same situation.
- And it took me an hour to get like 40 feet.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It took me a fucking hour.
And I was literally, and I was like,
an hour being the biggest piece of shit of my life.
Like I'm fucking throwing elbows in granny's faces
and like pushing people over.
- Well that's, yeah, you're--
- Get out of my fucking way!
- You're doing that in Boston anyway,
so it's like everyone there is used to it.
- Exactly, nobody gave, really cared.
I also had like a giant backpack on.
- Yeah, I had, you had like,
you had kind of like arm blades.
- Yeah, yeah, so I'm doing this and stuff.
- Confusing. - Slicing and dicing.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And your legs are replaced with blades.
- I'll admit it, I'm the guy who threw the beer at Gronk.
- For real? - Yep.
I hit him right in the head.
I was drinking beer at work and I got so fucking mad.
- You gave him more CTE than he already had.
- Yes, sir.
I mean, he keeps, his name's Gronk.
- Yeah, you knocked him back to normal
for like half a second.
- Yeah, he had a British accent.
- Ew, what in the world was that?
- Another beer can comes up and hits him.
I've been playing American football for so long.
Did somebody thought pie twice in my face?
Yeah, he's talking to British accent and he gets hit again and that's immediately when he had the idea to make his energy drink.
Yeah. Dude, the Gronk monster was actually really good.
Yeah, I'd like to see Gronk's monster.
His penis. I'd like to see his penis suck on it.
I'm gonna slurp that shit up like spaghettis.
Alright, next up here we have...
You're going to get very, very hot.
Initially, the only warning you might have
that something is wrong will be the fact
that you're getting hot, like really, really hot.
This is going to be problematic for you
from the very beginning.
- Well, thank you for saying that.
- Hey, I think you accidentally switched
into what happens when your body falls into a volcano.
- No, so that's actually what's surprising is no.
- Yeah, this is weirdly interesting.
- It's weirdly interesting,
that's why it's so weirdly interesting.
- But you have to admit,
it would work for that list as well.
You're going to get very, very hot in a volcano.
I think that you might have a different warning that something is wrong.
Yeah.
No.
Because you're going to fall in, and you're going to be like, hmm.
I feel like the first thing is that--
Something is off.
You're going to be in a volcano.
I feel like that's the first warning.
You can be convinced of that's anything.
Yeah, or maybe that you're falling.
I'm in a black and red room.
Off the rim of a volcano into the lava.
I'm jumping on a red trampoline.
You know what?
You know what you could have said?
What?
That this is supposed to be on the list of if the floor actually was lava.
Yo!
Oh, shit.
We should write that list.
That's a good idea.
That's a very good point.
can choose from this list. You're going to get very, very hot. And then I think it'll
work out. I love the language in this list. This is going to be problematic for you from
the very beginning. It kind of makes you imagine somebody who thinks they're about to die in
a human stampede because they're getting crushed and they're searching desperately for how
to survive and they get this. This is exactly, yeah. They're reading this on their phone.
- The lens I want you to look at this through
is somebody who currently is dying in a human stampede
and they look up what is happening to me.
(laughing)
- On their phone?
- They're on their phone and they're like,
what happens when I die in a human stampede?
- You're gonna get very, very hot.
- This isn't how to survive a human stampede,
this is how to get out of one.
This is what happens when you die in one.
- I think there probably is no way to survive
if you're already in a human stampede.
- Well, there is some advice they put at the end,
I don't remember if I put it in the slideshow or not,
but it literally is just like, try and walk away.
Try and go out of there.
- Okay, as tempted as I am to jump into that human stampede,
I'm going to resist.
- Okay, next up we have,
the group will basically become a liquid.
So this works for the volcano one too, actually.
- See, I'm telling you, this would work perfectly.
- Think of it this way.
If you took an hourglass and poured sand through it,
you'd see that all the grains flow through
with the ones on top moving to follow the ones on the bottom.
Now imagine you're just a single grain of sand
somewhere in the middle.
and now imagine that the greatest and has a lot of those are repeat a heart and
needs to breathe
it's easy to see what's the problem they should make uh... they should make our
glasses all that
yes screening mission except with parts of the world yet
j_l_ living standard hurts
it feels painless
yeah i think i was so he stepped on the beach the other shipment of sand man so
you know i'm i'm in i'm in the human sympathy to be crushed i can't breathe
i'm scrolling on my phone three d but i'm like all
it's problematic i've figured out that
- This group is almost becoming a liquid.
I'm almost a piece of sand in this group.
- What do they mean by the group will basically become a--
- It's like when you see a physics simulation
of water or something, and there's all those little beads,
and they're just being thrown to and fro.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- I would say you end up becoming one of those beads.
- It's also if you're at a demonstration
of the liquefier ray.
- Yes.
- That's also, I think that might be specifically--
- It says the group will become a liquid,
and then their example is sand.
- Sand is a liquid.
- The goop, maybe they meant to say the goop
will basically become a liquid.
- Yeah.
- That's kind of as close as it gets.
- That makes way more sense.
- I'd be so scared in there, my pee would become a liquid.
- My poop would become a liquid
'cause I'd be shooting poopy diarrhea everywhere.
- Maybe that's how you survive.
- The asshole next to you.
- That's how you survive.
Nobody wants, even in a human stampede,
I mean if people are stampeding,
it's gonna be a full stop if they smell shit.
- Yeah.
- Oh, oh, who did that?
- Oh my God, my.
Who did that?
Yeah, their legs were going like, "Wadawadawada."
And then they completely stopped because they're like,
it actually smells like fucking baby shit.
Everyone's gonna go home.
Yeah, someone's shining a flashlight in the air
and the poop cleanup squad comes through.
It's pushing everyone aside.
Dressed up like Monsters, Inc.
Carrying the guy who put his pants out on a stretcher.
Code 2319.
Oh yeah, that shit's scary.
Blowing up all those hats and shit.
Just donate them to a fucking shelter, man.
I'd wear 'em.
Yeah, fuck, I'll wear those fucking little boy socks.
Whatever, I don't give a fuck.
Not a problem to me.
Send them to me.
I want them.
Why are you blowing them up?
It's not even that I would wear them, I want to wear them.
They look dope. Send them to me.
Those look comfy.
And my feet, give them to me.
Now.
You damn monk.
Next up is, someone in front of you will probably fall.
probably fall and I don't believe that they put this picture look at this
picture someone falling stampede is definitely going on there well that's
the first that's the the first that's the first victim of the it looks like a
damn music video yes it does so like tattoo all the things she said music
video yeah it's from that yeah other people are going to fall on you holy
fuck see I do I want to be that guy I want to be the guy at the yeah yeah the
I'm not going in there.
No thank you.
I'm going to be the guy in the top right corner there.
I would like to live.
I would just like to live in every situation.
I would like the outcome to be me living.
I've been thinking a lot about dying, just getting hit by stray bullets all the time.
I'm always like, yeah, I see too many videos of people, you know those videos where it's
like, "Just another day in wherever," and then it's just like, you hear like 5,000 gunshots.
I'm like, one of those bullets is going to fly all the way from Detroit into my apartment
Building hit me right here in the middle of my head. Yeah, that's why I would never go to war. Yeah
War would suck due to that the possibility of getting shot. Yeah, it's not that for me
I think it's just like I just like my stuff here. Yeah, that's true. I like mine, too
I also camo looks like fucking shit honestly on me. Yeah
Goofy makes me look I also Billy all those utility belts and shit. Oh you have to carry
I do look kind of chubby and that's yeah, I don't want helmet makes my head look so round my I had a teacher in
And I hate that it says born to kill on it.
Yeah.
I had a teacher in middle school who told me that if I was like, I was asking him about
the draft and I was like, he was saying like, "Yo, yeah, if you're on medication, they won't
draft you."
And I was like, "Wait, so I take Adderall, will I not go to war?"
He's like, "Yeah, you probably won't."
No, dude, you'll be sought after.
Adults who take Adderall, you're going to be like the fucking, you're going to be like
the precogs from Minority Report.
they're gonna have you in a fucking tank and you're lying,
they drop like 10 Adderall pills down your throat
and you're just with your mind
controlling like 100 drones at once.
And they're all flying around,
they're all flying over like a wedding,
they're supposed to drop bombs,
they're like going down and touching all the curtains
and like eating, taking little bites of all the food
and flying around and getting distracted and leaving.
- They played a good song at the wedding.
I wanted it. It's like 10 drones. They just make a human shape.
It's just like they played the electric slide.
Yeah. **** Yeah. Um next up. Oh, this is so here. This is
actually part of of other people are going to fall on
you. Uh so you've fallen down in a crowd. No big deal. Just
get up again quickly and you'll be fine right. Nope.
Eventually, people are caught in a crushing effect from which
there is no escape. Oh **** Yeah. There's no escape. I can't
imagine what it's like to be crushed live and pose the question. Yeah, I met a
guy who liked it. That's so that's so rude. If I was if I was dying in a human
step and I'm looking at this, I'm like, oh, there's you'll be fine, right? Yeah,
I'll be fine. Nope. No, people are caught in a crushing effect. I tell you guys
about that guy. I met what guy Kevin carpet. What's this dude who wraps
himself up in a carpet in New York and then just like lays down places. Did you
crush him? I stood on him. Yeah. Did you try to like really get him? It's a
It's a sexual fetish, right?
I would try to hurt him.
It's gotta be.
I think I enabled a sex guy.
Well, it's not that you enabled it, it's that you had sex with him, basically.
Yeah, in his way.
In his alien world.
Well, he puts himself, I saw a video where he wrapped himself up in a carpet and just
put himself on a crosswalk.
What an easy way to satisfy your sexual fetish is by being like, "Oh no, I'm like a funny
thing that happens at bars," or whatever.
Yeah.
And Pat sees him and is like, "I'll have sex with that guy.
I'll do it right now."
you know what? Was he fine? I didn't see him. I only saw a carpet. You didn't see him at all? You only knew him as a
carpet? Yeah. So he could have been empty. Yeah. It could have just been a carpet. You just
stood on a carpet and said, "That's Kevin." Somebody said, "Oh, do you see like he's
in front of the bar?" And someone's like, "Yeah, that's Kevin. He's in a... there's a man
in that carpet right now." You wouldn't say... I mean, nobody would be like... the
The bartender wasn't like, "Hey, get this fucking carpet out of here."
No, the bartender was like, "Yeah, that's Kevin."
The hell is going on in this damn city?
We live in Sodom and Gomorrah.
I know.
That is a current...
Cleansing.
Yeah.
This place needs to be fucking nuclear annihilated.
I guess he's been doing it since the '80s.
Since the '80s.
Then it's been that bad that long.
The carpet probably smells bad.
Yeah.
That long.
He probably got a new carpet.
What, are you washing in a giant washing machine?
Yeah.
That thing's huge.
How do you wash that?
How does he wash himself in there?
- How does he, he's a guy, he sits on the floor,
he's a carpet!
- He's a man, not a carpet.
- It just doesn't make sense.
- It makes no sense!
- Oh yeah, I mean it makes no sense!
(laughing)
- You will not be able to escape
even though your brain will tell you to.
- Yeah.
- I think that's true of most ways that you die.
- 'Cause your brain's like, don't do it bud!
- Yeah, just get out of here!
- Come on!
- Try escaping!
- Knock it off! - Get the hell outta here!
- You need to not do this.
- Yeah, just don't do that.
You're going to experience some horrifying things.
This could be, I mean, okay, but riddle me this, you fucker.
- Sure.
- Playboy Mansion, Human Stampede,
you're dying by-- - Oh my God.
- There's breasts and fucking stinky wet pussy
getting all over you. - Dude, with my luck,
I'd be between the guys that were there.
- Exactly, be realistic. - I'd be there.
- A little wall of guys, there's like a thousand women
who are all getting crushed to death over here,
and I'm in this, I'm pinned in a corner
by five sweaty fat guys. - Yeah, of the waiters.
- You're dying with Andy Dick on top of you.
(laughing)
- And all the girls are over there dying, going, "Ahh!"
- And Andy Dick is in your face, like, "Hey!"
- "Hey!"
(laughing)
- Just biting you.
- Yeah.
- Let's die together.
- I actually like this stuff.
- Yeah, you're right, with your luck, that would happen.
- I hate my fucking luck.
- With my luck, all the fucking animals
that live in the playbook.
- Oh, I just dropped the clicker.
That's my fucking luck.
- Your luck sucks, dude.
- Dude, I can't believe that.
- And even worse, I took it away from you.
- Oh my god.
- That's how bad your luck is.
- Let me get a good look at Cameron.
Oh, well no, you have my arm just fucking broke. I think you're having a stroke normal luck though. I aren't just broke
No, you sound luck thing you're having a stroke
You're pretty good stroked out face. Yeah, yeah
You imagine if one of us had a massive stroke on it's gonna be incredible can we promise to release it?
Yeah, oh if you have us like dying during an episode or have a stroke or yeah
I want to make a pact right now.
Yeah, let's do it.
Anything that happens.
I didn't.
Any meta, anywhere.
So, this would work.
This is actually more of an
achievement than anything we've
ever done.
Terrifying.
Meta, like, if we get a close up
of this, if we if we explode
into blood suddenly on air,
then it's getting it's live.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's important.
That would be like that'll be
called the Red Mists episode.
That is the that's like what I
think everything is kind of maybe
working towards.
One or all of us dying on air.
Yeah, I'm gonna start working towards that.
We're gonna do some GGL and hang out with you and stuff.
I'm gonna start eating really unhealthy food to try and die.
Yeah, cause I wanna die.
That'd be so funny if you just end up looking like me.
(laughter)
We all just start eating like shit and turn into bad.
We wanna eventually die on air, so we're all eating junk food.
(laughter)
You guys die?
I'm trying to bloodwire myself by just eating chips everyday.
(laughter)
I don't know, this guy's a death wish.
- Fuck.
Like what horrifying things are you gonna experience
in a human stampede?
- Oops, you gotta click back on that.
- Oh my god, Jubio.
- Okay, if you're in front of the crowd,
you could be the first to die.
Makes sense to me.
- In front of the crowd, but is there anyone in front of you?
'Cause I'd just run my white ass away.
- I'd run backwards.
- I would just say, I would go like this.
- Stampede is about to start, right?
Everyone's coming towards me.
I turn around, see there's a stampede.
I start doing this so that everyone thinks that something weird is happening.
Okay. That's smart.
And then you cause a stampede the other direction and the P the P other people on
the other side, they're in the front there first to die. Not me.
I'm down like bowling pins, right? It's easier.
Like we're all going down backwards. You can breathe up. Yeah.
You can breathe up. You can breathe up.
You know what I would bring silly straw, like killer clowns from outer space.
Big long one. So it doesn't matter how many fucking 50 fucking, uh,
lifeless children's bodies deep I am. I'm underneath that whole thing. I got a
giant thing like a reed in a pond. Yeah, like a snorkel. Yeah, and I'm just...
You're like a ninja. Mm-hmm. Yeah. You're gonna go deep in a 50 dead children's maze, is that what you said?
No.
No, I'm at the bottom of a pile of kids. If you're in front of the crowd, that means you're safe.
adults
Here at the Wiggles concert, I'm not
That's funny to you
Wait, that's fun. That's way more tragic. Oh, yo the fucking pit during fruit salad was insane
She went stupid if you're in front of the crowd that means you're safe right they're all going to crush you
That's bloody mental. They keep they keep asking you there keep going like you're fine, right?
No, you're actually gonna have the biggest disaster of all
fucking die
Asshole no one will be able to help you God
God might be hopefully maybe a pregnant mom who gets that strength they get yeah, that could be here
Oh my god. I'm yo if I'm at a concert, and I'm in the pit throwing elbows
That's why I stay next to a pregnant mom yep
And you know yeah, if I want to jump into the pit I turn to that mom and I say I'm your baby
You need to always convince if you need a pregnant mom to do something really well
You got to convince it she that her baby's about to die. Yeah, yeah, yeah
- Yeah.
- Oh my god, these dishes are so dirty.
They're gonna make your baby die.
(laughing)
- They're done instantly, dude.
Superpowers.
- Uh huh.
- It's true that security personnel,
and maybe a few helpful bystanders,
could try to help you,
but they're not going to do much good.
You may crawl over bodies,
you may push people,
you may claw at them, fight them,
even bite people in rare instances.
Expect to be pushed, bruised, scraped, hit,
and screamed at while you struggle to live.
- Okay.
I expect that's how I will die anyway.
Yeah.
Is getting screamed at.
Pushed.
Screamed at.
Pushed, screamed at, and screamed at.
Yeah.
Well, I die slowly on my deathbed.
Old age.
I'm dying--
Don't die!
--of getting screamed at.
Yeah.
Dying by getting screamed at because--
That is how you're going to die.
Yeah, that is how you're going to die.
Don't eat that!
[LAUGHTER]
Don't!
Don't you dare!
And you're not-- you don't even eat it.
You just die from being-- you get startled by the scream
and die.
You're eating like a radioactive rod of uranium.
Don't you dare!
Don't you dare eat that!
Then we got-- you won't be able-- here's a three,
lightning round.
You won't be able to breathe.
Your ribs may crack.
You may die of a heart attack.
That's like Dr. Seuss.
You won't be able to breathe.
Your ribs may crack.
You may die of a heart attack.
Oh, The Ways You'll Die.
That's what the freaking book this is from.
I wouldn't want to read that book.
I'm not sure anybody would.
You have to make that parody book.
I know.
I would read that as like an adult who's into twisted parodies.
Like, I don't know, one of my favorite types of shirts,
I don't know if you guys have seen these shirts,
and it's like a picture of kids playing with a board game,
and it says, "Let's summon Satan."
- That shit is fucking awesome.
- That's the type of shit I think is funny.
- Cameron's favorite shirt is a picture of kids.
- Other people, well, they're summoning Satan.
It's not really, it's kind of a stretch.
- You know what I like?
I like ones where maybe it's like--
- He likes to stretch the kids over his body.
- It's like an old milk ad, right?
And it's like the milk has been poured in a cereal bowl,
but then it says at the top, it says, "That's jizz."
Or something.
- Yeah, that's good. - Got jizz.
- No, not got jizz.
Well, that's too much of,
yeah, I guess that's a better priority.
- That's a gut milk shirt, but it says got jizz.
- See, he actually thinks that's funny.
- He likes shirts that go hard.
- Yeah, I do.
- Yeah, he really does.
- I do.
- Yeah, I like shirts that go hard like this.
- Yeah. - Yeah, and I, my shirt--
- It's sweatshirt day, y'all.
- Sweatshirt day.
- Every day's pretty much been a sweatshirt day.
You didn't even get excited for sweatshirt day.
Sweatshirt day, fuck yeah, motherfucker.
Oh yeah, motherfucker, sweatshirt day, motherfucker, let's fucking go!
Then we have,
"You will not be trampled to death, probably."
These guys are getting crushed by some kind of
communist block. Yeah, look at this
picture. This makes sense
why people die in human stampedes, and I'm looking at this.
Yeah.
Why is that thing at the concert?
That's the stage, dude.
Yeah, it's a new guard prop.
For this next song, "I want you to go
go fucking crazy. They just they just start dropping his giant hydraulic.
Oh, yeah, it's not really a stampede at that point. Yeah, but it says you won't
be trampled. There's a hydraulic press. Well, yeah, you'll be crushed to death by
a giant press. Yeah, it's something like death.
That's awesome, dude. So if you're in a crowd and you feel like it's getting too
dense, don't panic. Go with the flow of the crowd and try to move in a diagonal
direction towards the side. Don't try to stop. Keep your hands to your chest to
defend your breathing space and don't fall because the next moments after that
could be your last.
So that's how you avoid a human stampede.
That's the instructions they give you.
- You go diagonally. - So you scroll through
15 list items that, I cut those down a ton.
Those are all really long.
You read, it's probably a 10 minute read.
You get to the bottom and they say,
"Just go with the flow."
- I feel like you should lead with how to survive.
- Yeah, well that's a different list.
This is what happens when you die.
- I'm calling 911.
- Yeah, that's a good call.
- I'm stuck inside at the Brockhampton concert.
I'm getting completely crushed to death. I'm calling 911. I'm being crushed by 4,000 4-foot-11
guys. Dude, that's actually genius. I'm getting stomped out by a golf lift fluorosneaker. That's
why I carry around a strobe light with me, okay? Because I'm getting crushed from all sides at the
snail mail show and I'm holding up my strobe light, okay, it's flashing out
people who are saying, "Oh my god, that guy's excited."
Yes sir.
Yeah.
They're like, "Oh, Levi, that guy's having fun."
What's another concert that you would be crushed at, you think?
Obviously.
Girl pool.
Hame.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
You'd be crushed at the Hame concert?
Dude, I got fucking, I got like basically flattened to two dimensions at the Iron and
wine show yeah I know we're joking about this but my friend did die getting
trampled at the Frankie Cosmo show yeah a friend of mine got turned into fucking
mush at a perfume genius show it's actually true it was really really bad
yeah completely turned into a bloody pulp he was just like a bunch of meat
with two eyeballs sitting there by the end yeah it's actually cruelly kind of a
cruel irony but my friend actually got turned to dust at a duster show no yeah
Oh my fucking god really scary shit. I brother died in a bird crash
He started doing the machine and people
Immediately mass panic dude people just fucking dying everywhere. We need that dude. We need to be the first
Comedy show where somebody dies by trampling people get fucking human stampeded
We'll book, we book like a five capacity video.
(laughing)
We try to fit like 150 people in it.
- We book the bathroom of a theater.
- Yeah, we just try to shove people into there.
And then we turn the lights off, we seal it,
and then people just die of asphyxiation.
- Yeah.
- It's not a bad idea.
- And just to remind you what website we're on here,
here's some, here's the recommended stuff at the end.
11 details about what it's like to be skinned alive,
creepy things you didn't know about falling to your death,
plot twists that happen right in the middle of the movie
and change everything, and underrated sci-fi movies
that flopped at the box office.
- Oh my God, did you look at all at the falling
to your death one?
- No I didn't.
- Oh man.
- That'll be a list for another day.
- Yeah, we're just gonna do death lists on Reaker now.
- I would love to fall to my death.
- I love creepy things you didn't know.
- Yeah.
- You will turn into a ghost.
- Did you ever hear that--
- Your bones will come out of your body.
- It's not true, but they say you die before--
- They say you can't breathe.
- Yeah.
- I can breathe.
- They said, I remember that's a fact.
I remember learning that fact when I was a kid,
which I don't know if it's true,
but they're like, if you fell off the Empire State Building,
you wouldn't be able to breathe
'cause you're falling so fast,
'cause the air is going through so fast.
- I feel like you learning that as a kid
changed a lot of things in your life.
- I feel like you learned stuff that changed me.
(laughing)
- Okay, all right, it's fair.
- It was, yeah, it was more my experiences.
Yeah, mostly my experiences changed my life.
- Yeah, it was mostly the things I did and had done to me.
- Nice.
What's funny?
I'd love to see you work for Ranker.
(laughs)
Dude, I could do a good job.
Ranking all the things that it happens to everybody.
Dude, I have the best resume ever for Ranker.
I've talked 500 hours talking about lists.
That's a good point.
I've written more lists than the people who work at Ranker.
Once we retire from all this, we definitely could.
Which, God, I can't wait.
Yeah, just started the video stuff, we're ready to go.
Yeah.
Yeah, we put all this money into the set, we're done.
Yeah, it was a good run.
Five or six more episodes.
Yeah, that's about all you guys are getting.
gives a crap. But if you want more episodes, go over there to the Patreon.
Patreon.com/podcastaboutlifts. We just did an episode where we ate food out of a
diaper, or multiple diapers. It was Diaper Talk 4, Thanksgiving. I'm sure you guys
have heard of Diaper Talk. Who hasn't? And today I messed up the camera angles.
Alright, now go to the other camera. So that's not that, you're kind of stealing my
thing now. I can't even get it I can't even get my own thing. Go on go on go on patreon and
subscribe. Can you cut to my camera real quick? Okay hold on okay wait one second
okay now switch to this camera and go on patreon and go on patreon and YouTube and
and
I'm going to take my pants off.
Bye!
[BLANK_AUDIO]