Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Podcast about Lists.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
- Okay, and welcome back to Podcast about Lists.
- Give me the date.
What date is it?
- It's October 4th.
- October 4th.
- Today, 2022.
- I got a Balls Guarana soda.
- Sorry, what's the episode?
- Instead of getting a Diet Coke.
- Do you know the episode number?
- Oh, not off the top of my head.
Let me double check really quick.
I just feel like I need the heading on this.
- Let's see here.
It would be, that would be episode 211, I believe.
- 211.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- Yep.
211.
All right, we can just continue.
I'm just gonna be taking some notes today.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Any, all right.
- Just some notes.
- Just notes? - Just for me, yeah.
- About?
- Don't mean about everything.
About every part of the show, yeah.
- Okay. - It doesn't matter.
- Did you write down that I had like a strong opening?
- It's not about you guys, it's just, you know, for my own.
- Right, but did you write that down?
I don't see anything on the page yet.
I mean I can write, I'll write.
Can we pause so I can go buy a Diet Coke?
I mean that's going in the notes if we do.
Is that worth it to you?
Would that be worth it?
Why are you looking at me?
It's your decision.
You're one of the three.
I know, I can't look at him though because he's in control of the notepad.
So why do I have to decide?
I mean you can do whatever you want.
You're also in charge.
I'm the only one who isn't.
The one thing I should be in charge of right now is Diet Coke.
It's not like the report card, but you can go.
Yeah, you can go if you want to. I won't reflect.
And it won't be... Alright, pause it.
God.
So you... What happened to the score?
Okay, that's definitely going in the notes.
Yeah, that's going in. He fucking faked me out.
The notes were really... Honestly, they weren't going to be a report card for either of you guys.
It was just so that I could keep my little ideas written down, so I wouldn't interrupt you guys.
Right, so like... Start talking. Say something.
Sure. So, um, over the weekend...
Fat.
There could be a fat guy.
Huh?
In what?
You're calling Cameron...
Cameron started speaking...
What are you talking about?
And then you immediately said fat.
But could...
Are you calling Cameron fat?
See, that's what I mean.
I'm trying to streamline.
I'm trying to improve my own performance, okay?
He's trying to give us body dysmorphia.
No, I'm not, you skinny mini.
No, I'm not, you skinny mini waif.
Damn it. I didn't want to be a waif.
Can I tell you guys a joke I came up with?
Yes, Fat.
Okay, never mind.
See, that's what I mean. I need the notepad so I can put the stuff in here.
You haven't written a single thing on this notepad.
What are you talking about?
He wrote the date.
He did write the date.
Okay, my bad. He wrote the date and he wrote the episode number.
Went over right there at the top of the dash.
He wrote F A plus.
That's a lowercase t.
What letters does he mean with the plus?
It's a lowercase t.
F A plus more letters.
No, I'm not saying F-A+ one letter or more. I'm not saying that.
That's what he wrote there.
F-A-T. And that's just one of the notes that I'm writing, so I don't just blurt it out loud and ruin the fucking episode.
Uh-huh.
Okay, well let's keep it on the notepad then.
Okay, I got a piece of wood in my eye earlier and nobody cared. And I didn't even tell anybody.
You did say, "Oh, I got wood in my eye."
And nobody said--
And then you got up and you were covered, so I could hear more about you being covered.
- No offers to walk me to the ER
or to carry me all the way to the hospital.
You didn't care.
I would need, I need to go to the hospital.
- 'Cause I know that you know what to do.
- Yeah.
- I trust that you can find your own.
- But not even an attempt of,
- No. - Hey, here's some water
for your eye.
- Some water. - Nothing.
- You wanted water? - I don't know if that helps.
- I don't know what to do with eye stuff.
I've never had my eyes hurt.
- My cat's eyes. - Never had your eyes hurt?
- Speaking of. - Yeah.
- Gotta take him to the vet.
Nice, how was that?
I haven't taken him yet.
Oh.
I have to take him to the vet.
Oh, so it's not a story yet.
Yeah, that's not a story yet.
He's saying something that is in the future.
But knowing him, he's a little crazy.
It's gonna be a story.
I'm gonna go home for Christmas in December.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
I think we all might go home for Christmas.
Yeah.
So that's pretty interesting.
You see what I mean?
Like that, if you had a notebook like me,
you could've just written down,
God, I gotta go to the vet.
No, 'cause he has a, I mean, you've seen Mo,
you've seen his eye. Yeah. What's that stand for you know?
Because I've wondered... Moreover. It doesn't stand for moreover? Because I've
always been wondering what does the Mo stand for? His eye is a little... a little
bit of a cloudy eye. I got to do something about that. I think I'm
developing a cloudy eye. Not from the outside, but my interior is cloudy.
Yeah, my left eye... I think I'm gonna need to get... You have cataracts. I think I have some kind of
glaucoma or something. Yeah. Betty Wop style. I think I might lose this eye. I'm worried.
See I am worried because I'm like his eye is a little bit
swollen and red
Caleb I know Moe's I do get worried sometimes about losing like I think that if you're
I think that if we're they're gonna take out his eye. I think that honestly comedians are at a higher
There's it's scarier to have to lose a leg or a finger because that's all they're material
Yeah, then you have to become the guy with no with no finger. No, then you're blowing up
That's true.
You're going to have Instagram Reels.
I'm going to love them.
Comedian with no fingers.
Kills.
Yeah.
Comedian with no fingers slays
packed crowd.
So yeah, I have no fingers.
And you have a perfect
opener every time.
Do you think Steve Hofstetter...
Steve Offfingers.
That's what you would be if you lost your fingers.
But do you think Steve Hofstetter maybe...
He already had balls.
As soon as he started going, like the heckler thing,
like as soon as he started doing like,
"Yeah, I'm gonna just destroy hecklers for the rest of my life."
Do you think at some point he was like,
"What if I just get rid of a leg or something too?"
Yeah, elevate it just one more level.
Yeah, I mean he really did.
I've been working on a series of videos,
"Comedian Destroys Hecklers in Wheelchairs."
That's a good...
in a wheelchair. Yeah. What are they heckling? Usually they say normal heckling stuff. You're
not. Oh okay. Shut up. They don't have a specific wheelchair. No. But you have wheelchair retorts.
Yeah. I went to the fucking wheelchair and dick sucking factory. No, I don't actually
talk about the wheelchairs at all. It just happened. For some reason all of my hecklers
just happen to be in wheelchairs or on crutches or have bandages around their heads. But you don't
say any jokes about the wheelchair because let's face it, that won't be PC. Yeah, exactly. I don't
don't say like hey I'm up here doing stand-up comedy you're down there doing
sit-down uncomedy because it's not funny for a second.
Yeah so you're doing like...
I'm just specific people I guess.
There's something about my vibe.
Because you have a very able-bodied vibe.
Yeah and I think it just makes people in wheelchairs jealous.
[Laughter]
Yeah it's truly just a jealousy thing.
Yeah, when I walked down the street pretty much people in wheelchairs look at me, and they're all jealous
Yeah, you should yeah, yeah let them know
Yeah, I'm gonna make a note of that that was so funny, I'm gonna steal that
Doing is this what the notepad is you you take gonna
We'll do callbacks.
You say jokes that we say on the podcast and then you're gonna go do them in stand-up.
Not in stand-up, I'm writing a movie.
So you're doing like a David Mamet style, like you're just recording your conversations and then using that for dialogue?
No, it's gonna be a new scary movie. Like in the scary movie, like Wayne's Brothers.
Speaking of movies, I went to...
Speaking of movies!
Speaking of movies, I saw Avatar and IMAX on the big IMAX screen over the weekend.
the weekend. Yeah I bet the 3D was really good. There was no 3D. What? You knew that. I wasn't
even gonna bring that up because it made me so heartbroken. You didn't have to, hey, come
on. The projector was broken and they didn't do it in 3D. But I still think even without
3D it gave me Pandora Syndrome. Yeah? Yeah, I mean I'm watching this movie. What is Pandora
Syndrome? You know when people are like, they watch the movie and they're like, I'm so depressed
because I can never live in Pandora, the planet from Avatar. It's like the opposite of Paris
Syndrome. But I feel like I watch that movie and I can never look at a human woman if she's
Affectionately again. I
Need her to be eight feet tall and blue. Yeah, and not wearing clothes. Yeah
Got her ass her asshole pussy and boobs are out the entire movie what her nipples? Yeah, there's all blue
But yeah, but she doesn't even fuck with those. She just fucks with her hair. Yeah, but she they still hug and kiss though
I got a
Trust me they hug and which is basically three brother fucking hugging kids all over
Some of those women are giant and blue and beautiful there was an avatar porn parody that came out in
2008 and
It came with a blue Navi fleshlight. I do remember seeing pictures
Yeah, that's in the movie. Oh wow yeah
They straight up do they have them out the entire time hmm
It was a shot in you were the necklace in front of him
It was it was a it was shot in 3d and then it was in a there's a
tabloid story that says woman claims
Watching 3d porn got her pregnant and it was the avatar one dude. Oh my god
I would love to get a Navi. I can't believe that she got pregnant by a Navi. Yeah, that's what I was 3d porno, dude
That's the dream. Yeah
That's my dream. We were talking last night about
Picking specific mates so that you could have a fucking awesome dope big son. Yeah avatar ultimate
Yeah, God, I think you want like to fuck like LeBron James or something. No you want a fucking avatar
Yeah, right cuz it'll split the difference cuz blue mixed with whatever a normal skin tone is it's gonna look pretty fine
It's clear well, so even yeah, cuz I might look a little bit colloidal silver Lee
That's okay. That's that's also gonna be nine feet tall. Yeah
How tall are the avatars?
They're huge.
They're like 10 feet tall.
So I'm 4 and a half feet or so.
But I'm 7 feet tall, so mine's going to be 9 feet tall.
My son's going to be like 6'8", 6'9", you know?
That's a good, that's like a center in the NBA.
Yeah, yeah, you know.
I mean probably more like a power forward.
Alright.
I don't really know that much.
Not pushing that.
The extent of my knowledge of the NBA all comes from winning time.
Really?
Mostly.
That song?
It's time to shoot the basketball, there's hoops and a dribbler is here.
Shooting time, there's popcorn in the stands, and they have ice cream and they have beer.
I want to win it's home. I know who I want to win it's home. There's Drake.
It's still winning time. Why do you say shooting time?
Because they change the... Shooting time is what Patrick thinks that a lot of the
NBA players should be subjected to. Whoa!
the sports photography while i've been credible you on the sidelines
you look like you for the just walking off the court
uh... in front of the that canada running down the road and the court petitions
does have that that was super bright flashes it's a good thing for trying to
answer
uh...
dot or and that
at the cool
obscured they should have to wear still play
to late griffin uh... yeah
What team is he on?
He, I don't remember.
I think that we need to fix the WNBA.
Fix it how?
Like, Joana Mann fix it?
Like, the ringer fix it?
No, what?
Not fix it like, let's fuckin' win.
Yeah, fix it like we win.
Fix it like spay them.
I think it's as simple as we spay them, first of all,
and then we just put 'em in something
a little more feminine.
When I was a kid, I thought that--
Skirts.
When I was a kid, I thought that the NBA players
and the WNBA players dated.
No, they do not like each other.
Or at least the WNBA players don't want to fuck any of the NBA players for some reason.
It's like, "Well, it's a match made in heaven."
But they end up fucking each other straight or just in black style.
Who is it? Lisa Leslie?
Lisa Lampanelzi? Yeah, she's funny.
Yeah.
Who are the other WNBA players I know?
Brittany Griner.
She got locked up in the...
Oh my God, yeah, she got arrested for... rightfully, she got arrested for smoking weed in Russia.
She's in a gulag now.
Yeah.
Yeah, which is smart.
you know she's in the penile colony she gets stretched out. Yeah it's the case for every
one of these degenerate pot smokers. I agree. They should be thrown into a... and you know
she's in a six by six cell. And that's width by six. Or six by... or she... yeah. It's like
she's in Bender's apartment. Yeah. Right. Oh my god. The reveal of Bender's apartment's
true size yep that actually was touching it was but it was all on a hot dog oh my
god or whatever happened yeah the dog I remember the dog when his brother turned
into a hot dog brother was a was turned out to have been part existed when his
brother when he turned out to his head other turned out in the middle of
prison yeah that was fucking disgusting why are we seeing his whole why is fries
brother or is it benders brother it's Frye Friar's brother and it doesn't have
a brother are you know fenders a guitar yeah it's a brother
benders a bot benders brother benders bot brother is not under bender is a bot
but no dog's way to a brat yeah dog is my OC character fender benders brother
and he's kind.
How about Slender?
Man.
I'm actually scared of Slenderman.
I bet Leela's little pet would eat Slenderman.
Oh yeah, Kith.
No, not Kith.
He's talking about Wogler or whatever his fucking name is.
What's his name?
Nibbler, I think.
Nibbler.
What the hell did you just say?
It's the name of the character, Patrick.
Yeah.
It won't work, it's the actual name of the character.
Yeah, this guy reads Tom Sawyer, he'd be saying the name of the characters too, I'll tell
too, I'll tell you that much. Yeah, old Cameron. What's wrong with saying Tom Sawyer?
Wait, no, it's Huck Finn. Huck Finn, Tom Sawyer. Huck Finn has a friendly gen. You know what, I wouldn't read any of it
anyway. Yeah. Yeah. I'd read a graphic novel. Your eyes, when you just looked up at
your hat, your eyes were completely crossed. Yeah, I had some of your sawdust on my hat.
My sawdust? I'm not wood! You're wood. In what world am I wood? Yeah, and also there's no sawdust in here
because we aren't building anything.
- Yeah, that's true.
I see what you're doing.
- Yeah. - And I like it.
- Yeah, so it's October, it's pretty scary.
- Yeah. (screams)
That actually scared me.
- Yeah, that was frightening. - And you can't do stuff,
you can't do shit like that.
This is now a professional work environment,
as of recently, and we've upgraded a lot of the--
- That's true, yeah. - Mentalities about our
workspace, so you need to stop doing it.
- Yeah. - You do need to.
- And Regina, if you're listening,
it's part of the show, there's gonna be jump scares
this whole month.
- Oh yeah. - Yeah.
Oh you want to, well how's it, you spoiled it.
Yeah.
You spoiled it.
Well okay, it's not really spoiling, it's just setting the ground rules for the month.
But if you have rules about, oh you're going to get scared now.
They had rules in Scream.
Scream was funny though.
I don't give a fuck about Scream.
What happens in Bodies, Bodies, Bodies?
They all get nude.
Are you fucking serious?
They slap it, then they clap it.
Slap it?
Wait do they slap it in Bodies, Bodies, Bodies?
I don't know.
I hear there's a movie actually show bodies and bodies and bodies they get in
there like rec room for a dream really they go ass - yeah Wow I think I watched a
different dude they get the kid they get the camera in there so deep it looks
like 2001 a space odyssey beyond Jupiter I'm like a light on one there movies
like buddies buddies buddies mm-hmm three bodies and one baby yeah buddies
buddies buddies was a great movie the good buddy's killing the pal on the
Buddy. That's right. I remember that. That one was good. Yeah. Sunday Buddy's Sunday.
Remember that one guy? That was mentioned in the game. Yeah. Remember Buddy Kruger? Yeah. He was a good hang.
Buddy Kruger, he hit Bob Fingers. He'd come into your dreams. A nice man on Elm Street.
He'd come into your dreams and just hang out. Yeah. Bring you soda. Come on. Sit down a while.
And he had those fire fits too. Dude, Buddy Kruger, he would, in your dream, if you were like,
"Oh, I've always wanted to try this."
- Not Friendly Kruger, Friendy Buddy Kruger.
- What were you saying he would do?
Stop eating your finger.
- I'm trying to, I didn't have time to throw a nail.
- He's like, he became a cannibal for October.
That's terrifying.
- Yeah, Buddy Kruger, if you had like,
if you're like, "Oh, there's a flavor of Pepsi
"that's, they only have it in Canada."
Buddy Kruger would bring it to you in your dream.
- That's right. - Damn.
bring the all-dress chips right and he'd be like no it's fine no you don't have to
Venmo me for these yeah imagine well here's a problem with Venmo and Buddy
Krueger he can't touch his phone because he got those I think they're only only
has it only has it on one hand acrylic nails his other hands he has acrylic
nails that he scratches your back yeah yeah good friend he's such a good friend
he's a perfect combination of a man and a woman and he's got one man hand and
one girl hand. If and if you need it. One boob. One part of the vagina. One ball. He has a
big acrylic nails and he's the kind of friend where if you need it he'll scratch your back
while you fuck him too. If you need it. And he won't be weird about it after. Because
he only has half of a vagina it's really small and tight. Yeah. You just shouldn't touch
the other half. Don't touch the other half. It's a sliced half. It's a bisected penis.
looks like a like a one of those guys that are in your it looks like a hot dog
that exploded in the microwave oh said that that wasn't right in when a buddy
versus Jason buddy oh yeah Jason bro he's yeah friend that Jason bro he's just
went to an awesome camp yeah yeah go to an awesome he went he went to the fat
camp from the Ben Stiller movie Ben and Stiller movie yeah I didn't say Ben and
Stiller no I well if I think it's two separate guys I don't think that there's
been an I don't think they're in a comedy Caleb hit his head partway
through a Ben Stiller movie and thought it was a different guy in the second
I have recently been stealing my eyes have been moving further apart and becoming two people and separating like an amoeba. Yeah
My mitosis mitosis mitosis. Yeah, my toes is fucking separate. I'm just separating is - yeah
Yeah, but the Ben and Stiller movies are really fucking funny because dodgeball weights heavyweights
That's a
Another level. Yep. Okay. He's that costume
Cartoon his name is white. I white his name is whitey or white Goodman white Whitler
His name is whitey or is it whitey Goodman or white good good white men. I don't remember
That's the movie you writing. It's white devil. I remember I told my friend my friend growing up about that movie
Where he says something about his name being whitey
And then my friend told me to quiet down because whitey bulger could be around and he could
He could whitey bulger would think that we're making fun of him
Then he explained who whitey bulger was to me and he was it. I remember whitey bulger
He was a serial killer who killed annoying little kids. Yeah. Yeah. Mm-hmm. I remember learning about whitey bulger, too
I did too and I did my I did a duck boat tour of Boston and we drove by the
The courthouse and they were like whitey bulger was in there and I was like who the fuck's whitey bulger
Nobody knows your also everybody knows whitey bulger in Boston. Yeah, insanely funny name. Yeah, it's great
Whitey Bulger. Whitey Bulger. Yeah. Johnny Depp. I think he would uh oh yeah that's right.
Johnny Depp, Black Mass. Johnny and Depp. Black Mass. I forgot about Black Mass. Whitey Bulger.
Bulger. Black Mass. That's his brother. Yeah. Controversial Bulger. Yeah his brother Black Mass.
Johnny Depp played a controversial character in the sequel. Yeah, he made an interesting choice.
but like Buddy Kruger he was very kind. Whitey Bulger, bad mean guy. Blacky Bulger,
very nice dude. No there actually is and we didn't just come up with that idea and say it from our own brains. That's a thing that already existed.
you're right I'm making it out if you're from Somerville you know if you're if
you lived on Winter Hill you know that Blackie Bolger would would go around he
would go around the fucking just try go what did he do just try you go to
Victor's Deli okay and do what he would water the subs he'd get subs there and
Somerville okay all right that's a guy from Somerville that's his character I've
been working on oh that's a pretty bad character really yeah it's really bad
it's bad yeah that's better this is on my veil there we go I've never even heard
of that anyone from some real sound like that could be some real England yeah
it's actually it's a disgrace that I haven't done it justice I'm actually uh
fuck some real from some her ville cuz yes I'm gonna just shut off my microphone
and I think I'll just be quiet for the rest of the episode I'm gonna make a
note of that you guys know my friend Gugler yeah he doesn't exist yeah yeah
Oh, you're talking about him really. Yeah, he has never a little bit. I do. Yeah, it's just never even been any remember the real guy
That we used to hang out with whose name was um micro. I do not know. I don't remember micro
Yeah, yeah from dirty jobs. No. Oh
Micro, yeah, Mike row no micro
Wait, Mike row. No, it's very same as micro
Can you attest to this Patrick?
Yeah, his first name was micro his last name was nothing. Okay, he was green
Micro, no, he was from outer space. Yeah, but he existed
No, his last name was nothing his name was micro nothing I do it, you know, I found out the energy from my green space
I found out the other day if I moved to Korea
My name would be pits Caleb. Yeah
Right. I actually I actually
would also my name would be Fetter Cameron if I moved to the mirror world.
Well is that kind of what Korea is then I guess? I mean that's at least some evidence for that.
I think they share some traits. I mean think about it. They literally they have a mirror in the middle.
Well that's South Korea. Yeah, it's perfectly mirrored. So maybe North Korea is just the same as America.
Uh-huh. And then South Korea is just... You don't know because there's a big gate around it.
Is that a gator? Is that a gated community? A gate around North Korea. Oh I thought you said there's a big gator
around it. No there's, well trust me. That would be scary if there's a moat. Oh my god.
They should change it to a moat. The Great Wall of China should be turned into one of those.
Do you know why every other micronation has failed so far and has been fucking destroyed?
It's because none of them had moats with gators.
Exactly.
That's a good point.
Or sharks.
That's why I keep asking you.
Was Waco a micronation?
No, it was just a cult.
Oh, okay. Well, were they trying to start a micronation?
I don't think so. I think they just were a cult.
Who was trying to start the micronation?
You dirty job, micro.
Was it, was it?
I already said that.
Huh?
I'm just talking to myself.
Oh, microstation.
- Micro station. - So try running.
(laughing)
I'm just talking to myself 'cause I turned crazy.
- Whereas it wasn't Ruby Ridge, was it?
That was-- - It might be.
- That's a porn star.
- No. - No?
- You're thinking of Ruby Tuesday.
- That's a restaurant.
- No, that's a Rolling Stones song.
- Oh shit. - Yeah.
- Okay, so I'll make a note of that.
I'll just Google what was the micro nation.
- I watched your note, all you did was draw a dash
and then you put the pencil down.
- 'Cause I couldn't remember how to spell.
we'll be putting a picture of these notes up on twitter so far has been sat it
says report but it really looks like it says something else yeah because of my
handwriting
this one i'd forgot what i was gonna say some of this going to do a smiley face
and i did the eyes off center so now just looks like one big scooping
looks like a jay well you're a high-level a
operation atlantis and early nineteen seven oh i'm your base libertarian group
built a concrete hold ship called freedom
which they sailed to the caribbean intending to permanently anchor it as
their territory. The ship sank in a hurricane and the project was abandoned.
Yeah. Isn't there one that's still like that? That's my impression of them.
Yeah, let's make the ship out of concrete. Yeah, this one's like, let's make it out of
concrete. They were concrete men. Yeah. There's like an island that Google owns.
Yeah, Jeffrey Epstein, Little St. James. When you think about that. So that's
basically, Big Tech is some kind of fucked up. Hold on, yeah, let me explain
though big tech is like some kind of fucked up right wing rightist thing so
now let's bump mics now. Hutt River. Yeah I'm a butt giver. You want some? Pound
that out. That's where the Hutts live. Yeah. Okay let's hear let's hear some more
micronations here. Most of them are really not interesting. All right well
what about local country of world peace a country without borders for peace loving
people everywhere. What's that one micronation? It's like an island.
Is it? There's the... Sealand? No, it's the fucking... the guy... there's like... it's just
like a landing strip for a plane and then like a... it's got like that plaza...
Delfino Plaza or something and there's like a big statue with a star thing. Yeah,
I know what you're talking about. There's a little blue bugger keeps running around going...
Yeah. Right? He's sliding around. Yeah, that's Sealand. That's the principality of Sealand.
There's fucking graffiti everywhere. There's a fucking talking robot. I know what you're
talking about that's the principality of seal and there's a dinosaur that eats
vegetable it was a world war two era anti-aircraft platform built in the
North Sea oh wow I didn't do that yeah that's what that was oh shit
well asked and answered I'm gonna write that one down that was a yes yes all you
wrote down was yes no you're I was the beginning of it the sentence man well
yeah okay well I ate a battery today you did not a battery line why are you
looking at me like that leave me alone this wall say that to Patrick Pat guess
what guess what I had for lunch the Reuben we both had a battery we both had
a pastrami sandwich I swallowed it no I swallowed it like a cartoon cat with a
goldfish yeah I kind of do want to diet coke really bad actually ate some
raindrops last night you have raindrops yeah those are you should get look at I
I straight up think that we should get a Costco membership for like one month, buy a mini
fridge and then just filled up with awesome sodas.
This is an idea that I've had for a while.
I think a Costco membership is like 8 bucks.
We probably could get a business card.
At Costco?
Yeah.
Oh damn.
Oh my god.
Dude, we could share it and actually buy fucking groceries.
You're the only one with a car though.
I'll take you too.
Okay.
I'll take you to Costco. There's a funky town
Got stabbed whoa
That's do we that makes a lot of yeah, that's do we yeah stoolie
Stewie Griffin Stewie Stewie Griffin Stewie Griffin go get a diet coke
I'm your cause been
Yeah, you fully cause because you have a coke in one minute. I needed he's fully caught doesn't need a diet coke
Yeah, I don't think yeah
I don't think you do keep that bad stuff out your damn body drink yourself some fucking I drink a drink a soda called the balls
Ain't even gonna say anything yeah, I'm even gonna touch those balls. Yeah wait
My name is okay, so I I brought a list
I'm about to sing the Cleveland Show theme song.
Yeah, I know you were. That's exactly why I started saying that it's time for the list.
White boy speaks Cleveland in perfect...
White boy speaks perfect Cleveland to Loretta.
(Laughter)
Ow.
No, to Donna.
Donna's his new wife.
Yeah, Loretta leaves him.
That's why he's speaking to Loretta.
Yeah.
White boy speaks perfect Cleveland to Donna.
has words
with has a little bit of words for the little red white boy i believe that that
has words in perfectly split
for loretta and donna
the and white white white boy has a a talking to and i'm a writer
and probably for a while
kyle or
or skyler abby
and robbie
robbie's robbie their bear in that show
what the hell's going on in songbird
and even a bear
and even a bear remembered okay all right it's true love we share so this is uh
this is that website we've been doing this is the last one I don't on this
website ghost Street um which we did the ones about the breasts this is an
important handsome because this is at the end of a trilogy this is the third
this theory this is gonna go down in hillogy mm-hmm as a trillid as a
trister II it's the end of the trilogy it's also the end of ghost street with
the start of jump scare month. Jump Street month. Do we call it Jump Street or what
are we calling because I know that every episode... What are we calling? We call it
like 21 Jump Street but we call it like 8 jump scares. 21 jump scares and there's 21
jump scares throughout the month. How many episodes do we do? Well it doesn't matter
we just put in 21. Yeah yeah. 21 total by the end of the month. I think that we should
have a lot more jump scares.
- Than 21?
- 21 is--
- That's way--
(screams)
- We already used up two.
- Yeah, exactly.
- So we have at least--
- We have to have 21.
- Yeah, so we get two each at 16 total.
- Yeah, 21 is the perfect number.
- So we got, now we have a couple,
we'll add some extra ones for some of the extra ones.
- Yeah, but I feel like that jump scare you just did
is just--
(screams)
- You were the one complaining we were doing,
that we burned through two and you got three.
- Now you've done two in like a minute.
- And it was so close, too.
21 jump scares. We have 18 left. I think it should be the 31 days of Halloween. There's
one day of Halloween. We're starting this on the 4th day of October. We're only releasing
episodes on 8 of the days. You can't divide 8 by 21. That's why it's scary because it's
random. We don't want it to be per exact. Maybe this one has zero. Maybe next episode
there's none of them but then there are a bunch of them in a row yeah and we'll
save the lap but we'll save the last one for the end uh-huh cuz there's gonna be
a lot of jump scares yeah on the Monday but anyway this is Halloween this is
under the category Miranda ghost and this is a special October list called top 10
most creepy ghost in the world holy fuck I wish I'd saved the gut a gump scare
for that okay I'm scared yeah a gum what's that a reason Vietnam and his
fucking there's more yeah yeah what's a gum scare is when they go to the you go
to the doctor and they scan your brain you're worried they come out they look
very they look very concerned it's they say you might have AIDS and you go
that's got to be a gum scare it's gotta be a gum scare another gum scare is
maybe like a feather flies in your face or you write you wait you wake up you're
running huh did he run while he was he sleep while he ran no is it not stop is
Is that the insinuation of the movie?
Yeah, you slept all you ran.
What the hell's wrong with this guy?
I know.
He's got a mental deficiency.
Okay.
What the hell is wrong with Forrest Gump?
Oh, you know what the real Gump scare is, is when you go to Bubba Gump and you find
a toenail in your coconut shrimp.
Did I already talk on the podcast about-
In October I would love to find a toadstool.
Did I already say on the podcast about what my uncle Tim said when he watched Nathan For
You?
No.
He was- We were watching Nathan For You with my cousin at his house.
He walked in, watched it for two minutes,
he's like, "Jesus Christ, is this guy retarded or something?"
He just didn't, he was like, "This guy is stupid."
And he wouldn't stop talking about it.
Then he was like, "Oh, so he's a YouTuber."
(laughing)
And we were like, "Yeah."
- Like Nathan Fielder?
- Yeah, we were like, "Yep."
- We thought Nathan Fielder was a YouTuber.
- He was like, "Oh, I get it, he's a YouTuber."
My Uncle Tim's a beast.
- Yeah. - Sounds cool.
- Where does he have that accent?
- 'Cause he's from Midwest somewhere.
- Okay.
- I don't know, he married him.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
of real. What did this have to do with Forrest Gump? Just made me think of, you know. Top
10 most creepy ghosts in the world. Everyone will be afraid of ghosts, but some brave.
Because the creepy figure it makes us afraid of ghosts, any place or a country must have
the myth of each of hauntings. But here are a few countries that have the most scary and
creepy ghost in the world. Okay? Wait, a few countries? That's what it says here. But it's
the most 10 most creepy ghost in the world. It's worldwide goes down by
country. I mean, we'll see. Some of them are, you know, specific to
countries. Here's my guess. Samurai from Ghost of Tsushima. From that.
Uh-huh. So from Tsushima. The blue electricity guy from Scooby-Doo from
Cyberworld. That's gonna be definitely on there. Yeah. Bigfoot's gotta be on there.
Bigfoots a fucking dinner. Yeah the Jersey Devil. Ghost of my grandmother. Yeah at my
house. Yeah America. America. Okay well what's this ghost? Texas ghost.
Cowboy, Texas ghost. Number 10, incubus slash succubus. And
let's look at this, check this picture out. Oh my god, suck you this. Hey incubus,
I'd rather just see them in concert, not in my room.
Yeah.
At the end of my bed.
Get out of my room.
Yeah.
This ghost is a ghost that is very scary.
What does not, he will prey on the girls who was falling asleep at night.
After getting his prey, he would fuck the girl that aims to make the girl pregnant with
his child.
More made more daunting, this ghost faced creepy have the horns and wings on his shoulders.
I like that all of these are kind of written, like I don't know why I think this when it's
read on this website but I think that it's always written like like like
medically you know yeah just to say the word fuck in there yeah to use the word
fuck as like a like like oh like he would uh you'd like penetrate the woman as
she sleeps yeah it is a very I don't know I don't know where I was going with
there you know a lot of these could be read off like a teleprompter on the
- Yeah. - Or something.
- That's what I, yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
- This ghost is a ghost that is very scary.
He would fuck the girl that aims to make the girl pregnant.
That kind of thing. - With his child.
- With his child.
- This ghost faced creepy. - This ghost faced creepy.
- Had the horns and wings on his shoulders.
- It's horns. - It's horns.
- It's horns.
- It's cone. - It's horns.
- Can you scroll down to stop?
- Huh?
- Can you scroll down to stop talking about cone?
- It's horns.
- No. - He loves that cone kid.
The Cone Kid's funny as fuck. That kid's gonna be so cool when he grows up.
Dude, if that kid writes a fucking book,
I'm the first customer in line to buy that shit.
You're gonna read the Cone Kid's book? It's gonna be misspelled. It's gonna be so fucking funny or good.
No. No.
It's so funny how burnt out he already is. If that Cone Kid becomes a cartoonist,
count me number one fan of whatever he draws or animates.
have you seen the clip of the cut the corn kid on the red carpet and he's just
like uh...
but they're like
is their cornered the movie he's just gone
i've seen that
but that kind of makes me pissed off it's like this play along say it's called
yes but i'd be fucking funny yet just say you're it's a year cold thing
nobody cares what your sad clown act okay robin williams
well you exactly what you're going up and i'll go now if you have a a a a
yet on the fuck up here
uh... cover-up like robin williams uh...
it a cone cobb pipe
probably played by a pie
did you have a corn cobb pipe in a button those into a state of the course
that's not mine
as papa
uh... shit
and it's a lot of by the sailor was a very
he said
where man
and it is a strong are there any answer on the internet to do
he ran
he went to fight the protesters
he wanted to bring peace
and then they ended up invading
the whole middle east
papai the sailor
he expanaged so fast
that he went to the middle east and he made a blast
and the u_s_a_ will win
that's a u
as a is
the best i did not know where
with the red and blue and white bear to do it's the greatest one we have
the white hair and child
as a sign of childhood about pop i got the white little in my brain like i like
i thought i was not going to shock of a very little look at a red and blue
- I just felt it in my brain.
The white there too.
- And the white there too.
Blue at the white there too.
It's the best flag that we have.
- Oh, Bloody Mary is number nine.
- Bloody Mary.
- Legend of Bloody Mary is very popular
in the Western world.
This ghost will come out when called
in front of the mirror three times.
Bloody Mary.
- That's two, mother fuckers.
- No, we read the title and then he said it.
- I'm not in front of a mirror.
- The black mirror of your last life.
The screen is on, it's not a black mirror right now.
You're in front of that, that's also on.
Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary.
Guys, I actually am scared and I wish
I could take back my words.
This is gonna affect every episode of this month.
Let me at least finish reading this here
because this is the most important part.
Bloody Mary said that the story
could be called upon to kill people.
Bloody Mary said that?
Yeah, see aren't you guys glad that I wrote that?
You guys are getting real comfortable
with saying her name three times.
And it's pissing me off.
that's a good point i will stop at request your what's kind of drink and you
think of that estimate of use in it
bloody mary well you know it was i will say it three times about that there is no
problem order in three bloody marys on a fucking tuesday morning tell you that
much
what i would like the ones i would have had a very rich history chicken in them
i didn't hear you said what was it
actually i uh... caesar
it's called the caesar what's it what's another to the to our friends north of
the board we call it though
i can't remember
uh... states called the b_m_ or bloody mary's
okay
and when they really like the and what is the instant for uh... lights and already
so i didn't hear it
well b_m_ is with a stand for no one is what is a stand for a candidate called a
season one of the night here display bloody mary kill
who's uh...
uh... okay well i would bloody mary
and mary mary why would bloody weight was six afraid of seven
bloody mary he said it for the third time
haha and i why did that were you gonna die
jesus your white ass your cracker and what is it to get killed by bloody
fucking bloody mary in a poll of my wife is getting killed by bloody mary bloody
mary as a chopper when
she's in the she's gonna slide on you yeah bloody mary slide on my back
the she split in the back the premier
yeah she came back around basically bloody mary i'm one of her ultimate ops
Number eight, when to go. Look at this picture. I know when to go. When
bloody Mary's in my fucking mirror. That's right. Or when the bell rings.
That's where I'll go in my pants. Yeah. I know when to go. When the cops show up at the party.
At the function. Yeah. Ghost stories, this one coming from the United States.
Initially this creature came from outer space and a high intangible large
animals and fanged and clawed like a wolf. The ghost continues to eat human
flesh to stay alive. This ghost is hiding in the forest and going out at night to
search for victims as food, which is more frightening. Supposedly humans can also
be turned into a Wendigo when doing certain ritua. I've never heard of a
Wendigo. Really? I've never heard of a Rituala. It's a Native American monster. It
looks like a circle. Yeah, they've circled nothing in this picture. Have you ever played Until Dawn? Yeah, love that.
That's about Wendigos. What? Yeah. Really? A Wendigo is like a skinwalker. He's clearly never read the journal.
It's the same type of thing.
I don't like when the ghost is on the movie.
I'm going to look up a picture of a windigo.
I actually searched windify.
It looks like it has antlers, I think.
Oh, okay, a windigo.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
So apparently, according to this, it came from outer space.
Like from a ritual.
Which I didn't know about.
That's actually a Jotun.
But it kind of looks like it.
Which is actually a Norse god.
It's a Jotun.
It's an ancient Norse name for John.
how about you move your ton of ass yeah how about you put your ton back in your
damn pants and how much you don't drop that ton ton ton ton ton ton that was
honestly like the earlier thing where you beam ton ton into my head okay what's
next number seven is Banshee. You got somewhere to go you keep looking at the clock yeah
sure. I have to take my cat to the vet. Is he about to die? I don't know he's got a weird eye
thing he's had that for the entire time it hasn't been read it's a little swollen
right maybe he's becoming evil like Kotor yeah maybe it's showing up in his
appearance he's grown horns you have veiny skin that's true maybe he's
turning into an incubus whenever I see some guy at the gym with like way too
many veins I'm like you do realize I mean do you fucking evil right yeah I
feel like if you have a lot of veins you're weaker cuz you can just get them
Mm-hmm. I get just pull them out of someone if I see them. What is this a banshee?
Yeah
Banshee is a ghost. I'm just gonna hold on a minute. You know what a banshee is
The banshee is a ghost yeah
I
Thought a banshee was a purple plane that you ride
Even then it's a taxi ghosts that is shaped naked woman with a very creepy face with disheveled hair
This ghost is a sign of death that when there is a voice crying Banshee backyard
Then there will be people that are going to die at home. Yeah, I hate when the moon. I'm outside in here
Me too, and then I go out in the backyard and I get killed by a Banshee
Yeah, I tell you what though that looks less like a Banshee more like some kind of clansmen if Klu Klux Klan
Yeah, that's true. If if you were in your house, and you heard someone outside
Like in a ghostly voice say backyard. Would you go in your backyard?
yard? If you heard somebody say in a ghostly voice you're next in line for
the death for death and it was from like maybe the end of a dark hallway and you
saw like teeth and like eyes and stuff and it was saying yeah you're next in
line for death would you walk towards that or would you probably just stay in
your home? You saw the killer. There's a hallway outside of my home? Alright
hypothetical if there's a killer on the loose and you've seen this on the news
right but then you open up your closet and there's a sign that says the killers
near and it's written in your own blood right but then you look down your
fingers are all pricked you realize you're crazy are you gonna go kill
yourself are you killing other people others okay hmm others yeah so if you
walk in make you the killer if you see a clown super statue right uh-huh give it
a kiss super statue well it's bigger it's huge yeah if you see some leveled
up from yeah you say where's the you tell the where's the beef you say where
you took all the parents you say was up say where's the beef yeah and then they
tell you exactly where all that is. Are you gonna go eat the beef or what?
I don't... I think I might. Okay. That's pretty cool.
Number six is doppelganger. I don't think that's a ghost. I think that's
some kind of genetic... Well let's find out.
Let's just find out if it's a ghost.
Why don't you read right here and see what it says about it being a ghost.
What if you see yourself in front of your own? Yes.
Doppelganger is a figure where it resembles a ghost yourself, not just physically, but also the behavior and dress exactly the same as you.
Supposedly, if you look at the doppelganger, it means death will soon pick you.
So that's pretty much exactly what you just said about the hallway, too. Okay, so you look into the hallway. It's a complete
ganger of you. Yeah. And you are saying, "Wait,
I don't have a mirror in my hallway."
right? And then the doppelganger starts moving towards you, his hands turn into
claws, his mouth turns into a knife. Are you running away or are you running towards it
trying to bang the mirror? If I run away it will chase me because it's the
same as me. What would you do if you saw your funniest cousin? I'd probably bang him.
What if you looked into magic glass and you saw something that looked exactly
like you? I'd probably bang that too. Yeah, yeah. I'd probably bang it till it died.
The funniest cousin who's a doppelganger of you? I'd bang him till he smelled bad.
would he smell better with the room smell I'd smell him badly I think you wouldn't
smell him you would stink him I'd stink him up with by banging him to death
thinking I'd be stinking yeah you guys see the Jeffrey Dahmer movies the Jeremy
Renner one the bomb one where's Jeffrey Dahmer in the Middle East he's diffusing
bombs in the yeah yeah so getting a tattoo hmm why is this guy why are we
vilifying this hero I don't understand yeah yeah but there's any sense Jeffrey
Dahmer movie he apparently I didn't know this he's trying to make he's trying to
make robotic zombies that's what he was doing in real life yeah I know I didn't
know yeah it's crazy he's in he's crazy dude he's the guy was nuts oh he was
there's that serial killers go is such a yeah he is crazy he was making zombie
slaves pretty cool yeah sex slaves he would drill into people's heads and like
pour acid into their brains. He also made everybody watch The Exorcist 3.
The third one. The one with the "BURP!" Yeah, yeah, yeah. It took me a second, yeah, but yes.
Yeah, that one. Yeah, that's a good movie. With Brad Dourif and Dorsey Scott. Yeah. Good, good movie.
It is such a good movie. Jeffrey Dahmer, if you will, his taste in movies and men.
That's what I was saying, dude. I feel like if I could sit down with
Jeffrey Dahmer, I could just like hash it out. I feel like I could have a
breakthrough. I feel like me and him could connect on some level about movies.
I think he'd break through the fucking front. I think you know you could know
I was I was saying this to Patrick Jeffrey Dahmer would not kill me because I would give it up for him and my and I
Would it would change him you think that I would give him I would give him but so good you think you would see you
Would stop you think he'd give a magic, but yeah, I think it's the one I think that I
Think if I could if I save it up, and I get fucked in the same it up one time
If I'm like
Like if I never get if I never get butted my whole life
My whole life you watch it Virginia. I'm like, you know, I'm in I'm
Early 30s. Okay at this point cuz still young enough to for Jeffrey Dahmer to wanna see it, but me but the buddy
But I've been here as you get older. No, dude, I've been doing stuff. Yeah. Yeah, I've been I've been a lot ease and stuff
of yeah all sorts of I mean basically everything under the sun and then
where the thing that thing yeah the sun dry exactly now like a race yeah.
I think I think I'm getting down on the bed. I think I'm putting my butt up in
the air and I think I'm jack hammering him like I have control of the situation
of course, like he he he doesn't even want
(laughter)
And I think he's never killing anyone ever again after that.
So you're showing up to jail.
You're going into the...
You're doing a...
I don't think... I think in this scenario...
This is pre-jail.
This is pre-first jail.
He hasn't been caught yet.
This is like 22 years old.
This is the inglorious bastards of Jeffrey Cameron.
Cameron has a time machine.
Yeah, yeah, he's going back before his first kill.
So you force him into your crazy tight butt.
Which we've established is magically delicious.
It's full of mana.
It's never been used and it's ready to be used.
Okay, yeah.
It's like a pear.
You know when the pear is the perfect ripeness?
Yeah, it's folded.
It takes like 30 years for a butt to get that ripe.
It's perfectly crispy like a white Hanes t-shirt out of a bag.
clean and it's really clean it's going never never not vacuumed it never only
things ever came out of the car one yeah I went to the car wash and I use like a
three a three gallon fleet yeah your but you dropped a gallon of fabuloso down
there yeah there's I mean it's fabulous everything everything that you could put
in there to make it better I did that okay and then you blow his mind yeah
right and he says wow I never want to make a fucking zombie sex slave in my
Yeah, exactly. There's one thing I know I never want to do is kidnap a 16 year
old boy and turn him into a sex. Right? Yeah, it's like that could never be as
good as this leg and then maybe in front of him. I get back into my time machine.
I'm like you want to get this again. You got to see you got to survive till till
2022. You got to stay out of jail be a good clean boy Christian boy. Maybe I'll
give you this again. Then I'll play kind of toss my butt like do a little like
yeah
doesn't know your shoulder like it
up of my uh... kind of my hand on my head and and swing to a little swing
if you ever want to see this again
and then you are not going to have a lot of other people
what's the fact that this appear
uh... and i think that you
and when he gets if he'd makes it all of them for me again
back in the future
yeah well but you also had like tell him like what i don't be bad
you got a tell me you have a memorized so that i was so bad i think i think
killing people again. Well it's just immediately after the last one because you just time travel.
You also have to think if you do that and you go back to the future what if the idea
of him not having that makes him go crazy. That's not my fault. Oh and then it's even
worse because he's trying to make the holes in people, he's trying to turn them into SpongeBob.
Yeah he's trying to either turn them into SpongeBob or doing surgery on their butts. I mean honestly
If that happens, it's not my problem because I did more than anyone else did to try and stop him.
That's true. Almost nobody did anything to stop Jeffrey Dahmer based on the movie.
Yeah.
Yeah, cops kept coming up.
What do these people try to do? Run away?
Yeah, guess not.
Tell people about him?
No, dude. Throw it back on him.
Yeah, ruin his life.
That's right.
Yeah.
He's trying to take your life. You need to ruin his life, girl.
He has no bed frame.
No way.
So that's why nobody ever gave him an X-Level, but because he's a slob.
He was a total slob.
Right?
He opened up the fridge, there's fucking tongues and teeth and brains and eye sockets and shit,
and you're like, "Jesus Christ, clean it up.
At least do some meal prep.
You know, get your shit together.
Overnight oats."
I would have gone back.
See, I would have taken a different thing.
I would have tried to become his gym buddy.
Try to get him on a new program.
Would have been, "Hey, creatine.
It's good for your brain.
We're gonna get you on..."
That's actually a great idea, is to make him really, really strong.
That would actually really help out in that situation, if he was extremely strong and powerful.
take out that stress in the jaw. Powerful. And maybe he might even kill a
professional bodybuilder, right? But if he only kills one bodybuilder, that's
enough meat to last you a lifetime. So why is it? That's the problem, he's going to
these gay clubs with these little skinny guys and he's eating one of them being
like, "Oh, I'm still fucking hungry," right? It's like when you buy a rotisserie chicken.
I'll eat two rotisserie chickens if they're not from Costco. Exactly. If they're too
small, I'll go, I'll eat one, I'll go, "Fuck, I'm still hungry." Go back, eat another. But
But if I got one of those Costco big ass roto chicks, I'm fucking good for days.
I don't like a chicken salad with leftovers.
My strategy is entirely different from both of yours.
I go back in time and then I bring him even farther back in time.
I go into the time machine, I take Jeffrey Dahmer, I grab him, bring him into the portal,
it's a portal based one.
I go all the way back.
I show him Rick and Morty.
Okay, well, you didn't have to come in with a better idea.
I'm sorry, okay, continue.
You already had yours.
You go all the way back.
Well, no, because now it's like, if I showed him Rick and Morty, he would understand that
like depression is actually like something that you can get help for.
It would kind of cure him of his kind of like solipsism.
That's true.
Yeah.
He would have a really, he'd be like, okay, other people don't matter.
You know what another good solution is, is maybe cut off his head.
See, that's what I was going to do.
It's too hard and bloody.
him back in time to like the 1700s. Well then what he's doing would be okay.
If he was in the 1700s there wouldn't be a problem.
He's our king. I'd bring him back to the year 33.
Okay and I think I do know where you're going with this. I'd show him the miracles of
Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ multiplying the bread. Jesus Christ
baptizing John the Baptist. Jesus Christ rising again after he's been
crucified, right? He's turning water to wine, all this stuff. He's walking on
water at the end, right, with the disciples. I would show him all that and I
say, "With all of that in mind, with the glory of Jesus Christ in your brain,
you know, all the Old Testament myths are true, do you still want to go make a
zombie sex slave five-year-old?" And if you do, then... If you are, I just want you
to know, you will be... like, first of all, all your victims are gonna be fucking in
heaven, and fucking each other in heaven, and all of you, you're gonna be in a
lake of fire yeah right you're gonna be fucking burning alive forever right
eventually there's gonna be a full-on tribulation if that happens in your
lifestyle in your lifetime and your lifestyle yeah right and you're gonna
suffer facts yeah did us I'd go back in time and kill him yeah yeah that also
would work to kill him with like a kindness okay ah swan that number five
Aswang. Look at this picture. That is old Greg. That is Patrick on any holiday.
Pat, go ahead, take this one. Ghosts that this one is very well known in his home
country, namely the Philippines. That's the sound it makes.
Aswang is a traditional ghost in the Philippines shaped like a cross between
stories are powerful terrible and sometimes can turn into a giant black
bear it is said during the day I swung bridge a little try that again
Baru no just Baruja Dukhan a man like he did that to a man yeah Baruja
gotten done well not just a man keep going with a quiet personality even
while in the next will turn into a ghost and act cruel and creepy even a man with
a quiet personality can turn into a ghost and act cruel and creepy true man with
quiet personality Jeffrey Dahmer every time I think I got a quiet personality
number four is changeling okay and this is changed into a wheelchair this is
this picture this is a crop of the movie poster for the movie the changeling I
wish I could not change my late Scott that is not I wish I could change my
I wish I could change my make it fucking to make it wider. Cangeling is one
creepy ghost next change. Changeling appearing as a substitute. If a child
stolen by supernatural beings as a meal
still
as a meal
physical shape is identical to the stolen children, but has a slightly
different behavior be Baral a time later. Changeling would be catastrophic
and continues to do so would cost the lives of the people who are around him.
So a changeling is a clone, or a shapeshifter.
- Yeah, a clone of a, it's like when fairies steal a--
- Keep throwing peopleistic things it could be.
- When fairies steal a baby and then they leave
a one that's a clone in its place that's evil.
- Really? - Yeah.
- I didn't know that. - Yeah.
- Oh wow.
- It's old, like, I wanna say it's Irish.
- Does that still happen or is it like cured,
like smallpox?
- I don't know.
- Oh, okay.
- I feel like it's probably one of those things
that happens rarely, but we have a vaccine against it now.
Like the black plague.
Number three is Yuri.
- Yuri.
- Behind the beauty of the Japanese state
turned out to save the mythical story very creepy.
One of them is a ghost named Yuri.
Yuri is a ghost who is described as the woman
who has pale skin and long hair and unkempt
and runs smack float surrounded by fireballs blazing.
It is said that Yuri is the incarnation
of the women who avenge his death.
- Wow, she runs smack float surrounded by fireballs blazing?
- Listen, I know women who run,
I know women who smack, right?
but we float surrounded by fireballs blazing.
I mean, that's reserved for kind of a dark phoenix.
- Yeah.
- Sounds like a Pokemon.
- Or a video game enemy of some type.
- Number two--
- Pokemon are the enemy in the game.
- Oh, that's true.
That's a good point.
- But it's made a different enemy.
- You know what they should give you?
You should be able to go into the Pokemon games
with a riding lawnmower, John Deere.
Just fucking obliterate him.
- Yeah.
- Tear that--
- I mean, yeah, you're tearing down the grass.
- Just get that grass.
I don't want that grass boy.
Uh huh.
Right?
And you should also have a fucking, you should be able to fill, like the office, you should
be able to fill the caves with jelly.
I should have one of those, the McDonald's machines they use on the male chickens, or
on the chicks or whatever, and I have that and I'm catching every Pokemon in the area,
and on the route, I'm walking around, I'm catching every Pokemon, they're all watching
me catch every Pokemon.
I have a giant bag full of Pokeballs.
I'm walking back to my house, I have a big plate glass window that they can see, I'm
bloated, just dropping all the Pokeballs in that machine.
- Of course. - They're like,
"You have to stop, we wanna catch some Pokemon too."
And I'm like, "You gotta be faster."
- That's right. - Yeah.
- I caught 'em all. - I can do, they're mine,
I can do what I want with them.
- I got a shiny Absol.
- I wanna find the Mr. Mime, speaking of nests,
I wanna find the Mr. Mime nest or the Mr. Mime hill
and I wanna pour molten lava down there.
- Yeah. - And create a statue.
- I would love-- - With burning bodies.
- I would love to pull the legs off a Mr. Mime.
- Me too, imagine the Roto Chicks
in the Pokemon universe, right?
- Oh my God.
what a Mr. Mime tastes like probably like cotton candy. It's so fucking good. Yeah, gotta be good. So good.
Yeah. Those hairs. The hair on the head would taste so good.
Number two, Rougarou. Rougarou alone is as an ordinary man who led a normal
life like most people until adulthood then signed normal nya nya up here. The
The signs that he will continue to feel hungry and then eat.
This is written in complete normal English Patrick is just having trouble reading it.
Whatever Ackman until the Sat-nya.
He will feed on humans as well.
Sometimes he would be camouflaged as an ordinary human being as a way to trap prey and ultimately
will make food as a remedy against hunger.
Food is a remedy for hunger.
That is true.
I never thought of that.
I didn't think about that either.
Hunger is an affliction.
Yeah.
Like food is the remedy.
Yeah, exactly.
- That makes sense to me too.
- Food has gotta be hunger's remedy.
- Alright, any guesses on what number one is?
I just scrolled down and saw it.
- Plants.
What is this list again?
- Top 10 most creepy ghost in world.
- That's gotta be fucking the devil.
- It's zombie.
- Oh, I said the zombie's enemy.
- It's like the same dude.
Alright, zombie's not a ghost, alright?
- Alright, zombies are very famous in western countries.
Figure undead rising from the grave is certainly very scary.
No wonder if the devil, this one,
being one of the most frightening demon world.
Zombie is also widely used as inspiration
for the film "Overseas."
Terrible shape and Degan blood stains
that exist throughout the body
makes it more scary zombie.
Though walking with a slow, zombies are very dangerous.
This is because the zombies constantly hungry
and will salulu try to eat any creature they encountered.
- Did you, have you guys seen those videos
of these fucking deer that have this crazy disease
that makes them just spin in circles like zombies?
- That sounds crazy. - No, I didn't see that.
like get some some it's like some brain-eating disease and eventually it
gets to the point where they just like start running in circles till they die.
That's nuts. I love stuff like that. That is cool. And then the thing the fungus that takes
over the bugs or whatever. Cordyceps. Yeah the cordyceps those are cool. Yeah.
That's the fungus that grows in ants brains and it makes them climb up to high
places and then it explodes their heads to shoot the spores out. I cannot wait
until something like that evolves into humans. It's COVID. I actually
think it's COVID. I actually think it's COVID. There's one comment on this list
under posting commentar if anyone wants to read it here from Valky Padro.
A casino will not allow players to gamble or play slots. Dr. CMD, if you enjoy
playing online Chinese slots with a friend... That's not Chinese. That's Korean.
Well, I'm not wearing my glasses.
I was just going to let it happen.
There is Korean, always Korean, something you can do when you, Korean, stay at your hotel.
In our opinion, and then I think there's more.
Ballas.
No.
That's not more?
That's not, the ballas doesn't mean more?
No, it just says ballas and you click on it, it scrolls to the bottom of the page.
Oh, okay.
Well, there's posting llama there.
What is posting llama?
What?
Top five richest singer in the world.
Wait, top 10 unique staircase in the world. What is this?
Top 10 unique staircase ideas for you.
What do you say in the world? Staircase hanging? Such stair design suitable for minimalist home? That's beautiful.
Staircase shaped tree bring natural feel unique and interesting.
Flower petal staircase the steps were like flower petals when seen from above.
Stairs once library space under the stairs turn into a bookshelf.
Staircase tilted this ladder is dangerous for children and the elderly.
Why is it making the top 10 then?
Yeah, I guess it's interesting.
It is interesting.
The staircase from another world. Unique.
Flues as it appears from another world. Penetrating the
surface of the floor while the stairs look very clear.
People should just come check out this website.
There's tons of good shit on here.
But that's the end of our trilogy.
Yep, that's the end of the trilogy and this is all
leading up to a big announcement.
What?
That we have a show at the end of the month.
And we haven't announced that yet.
Halloween night, you gotta go buy tickets,
it's gonna be incredible,
Bell House, the Hell House I should say,
Halloween night. - Welcome to my night, man.
- We got Sarah Squirm on it, we got Pierce Campion,
we have the actual devil, we have more to be announced.
It's gonna be incredible.
- The guy who invented the cronut.
- We're premiering a video
that you're gonna wanna be there for.
- And you honestly will,
the video is gonna be pretty fucking awesome.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And there's gonna be a serious--
- And if you bring a pillowcase, we'll give you candy.
and you do everybody should be 100% true dress up in costume bring a pillowcase
we are gonna be handing out candy if not only if you're in a costume you're in a
costume you will get a bag with candy in it but you will be it is gonna be a
full trunk or treat we're talking about maybe doing a cake walk
maybe doing an apple bob okay so just you know the video I think is the most
important thing because it's ever made the most important video ever made