You will listen to the whole episode. You will watch the episode on YouTube.
You will laugh at the funny parts. You will cry at the sad parts.
You will put $15,000 in my pocket for a $13,360 T-shirt in Oregon, Texas.
I'm a genius, I got this!
(upbeat music)
- Yo, what are you doing?
- I'm looking through all my bits.
- Your mic is completely off.
- Turn your microphone on.
Oh my God, there's a bit right there.
- Is it?
- Yeah, now it's on.
- Okay.
- There's something right there.
Kalo's microphone.
- Oh, we can do the turned off microphone here.
- Okay, wait, all right.
- Okay, I'm doing it too.
(audio cuts out)
And then--
And then this and then--
- I don't think that's gonna sell that well.
Now that I think about it, I don't think that'll sell
very well on the audio part of the podcast.
- Or on the video either.
- Maybe the video would be the least too.
- I had my mic shut off that whole time,
but I couldn't think of anything to say.
- Right, yeah, there's some ideas I have,
but I don't think, yeah, I probably won't end up
doing that one, that one might be a little too involved.
involved? What is it? I was thinking maybe I could get like a... Well don't say it
because then when we do it later... But I don't think we'll use this one. I think
it's probably a little... You think we don't use it even at all? There's no
chance? Once you hear it you'll probably say, "Yeah we probably shouldn't use that
one." Okay. I was thinking maybe I'd go... Well this is a perfect time to
actually cut your mic. I'd pretend I get... Well I was pretending I was maybe
thinking I could pretend I got like a hair transplant, right? And then come in
and I was wear like a bag over my head for a while
and then I'd reveal my hair transplant
and I just got like maybe a Hitler mustache.
- That was your transplant?
- Yeah, you see like the fucked up ant legs,
but only here and maybe a little up there.
- It's really red and blowy.
- Yeah, it's like a--
- Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Something like that might be kind of funny.
Hitler hair.
- Nobody, that's the thing, why is it just the mustache?
Why not his hair?
- It's the hair.
Everyone has that style.
It's the hair too.
Everybody knows the hair.
I see that hair everywhere.
You know who has that hairstyle a lot of the time?
Who? Pipsy Zero got me burping.
Holy shit.
That's the hardest burp I've ever...
That was a weak burp.
You know when they're spiking?
You couldn't think of something in time.
I was going to say, emos have Hitler hair.
No they don't.
Are you kidding me?
Emos have Hitler the hair. Yeah the swoop like that. It's different
Okay
He has one purple highlight
Actually, yeah, I think I'm your thing of Hitler I'm thinking you are
Hitler's
Emo that emo Hitler picture his emo guy from the Peter Jackson documentary
Peter Jackson documentary.
Meet the Feebles.
I didn't watch it.
You know Peter Jackson took all that World War 1 footage of people
getting their legs blown off in trenches and stuff
and was like, I'm gonna make it HD and 16 hours long.
Can I put it in full K?
Is that what he sounds like?
You know he like ruined New Zealand?
Yeah.
Pretty funny.
He put a big chess board there.
Did he?
A big upside down house.
a couple of fun things about the set that we are the bunker that we didn't know
you move over for a second watch this can you cut to the plasma ball cam watch this
guys well this is honestly ah ah ah ah ah so go wide now so if you say bah it
turns yeah and watch this cut back to the plasma ball cam so it does this it
does do that when it's touched and what I did say it was synced up to camera
episode. Baaa! What the hell is going on? This is the craziest shit ever. I think there's something magic on Cameron.
There's something fucked up about this plasma ball. Baaa! I didn't really realize
plasma was so anti-mortal. And watch, now watch what happens to Caleb, cut to the
Caleb camera, when I do this. It's pretty, it's, I think it's really similar to what
happens in the plasma ball. It's showing up. Yes, I don't know if it's showing up on camera. And now watch this.
"Bah!" So it got a little scary. It honestly did scare me a little bit. But it doesn't
happen to Patrick. No. "Bah!" Nothing. Try it again. "Bah!" Try it again on me. "Bah!"
But you guys know... Wait, you just transferred your "bah" to me. Whoa. "Bah!" "Bah!" Wow!
Are you seeing this, Caleb? This is crazy. "Bah!" Okay, now you do it to me. Okay. "Bah!"
there's no Bob from him but what hey why do I get a short but wait come here
bah okay that he's got a we try it on me now nothing yeah you didn't get a thing
hey hey why don't I work ah eggs milk see I do my grocery list but that was
(laughter)
- I was in the middle of talking.
- Oh whatever.
- Yeah, okay wait what about this one?
E.T.
- Okay.
- Goes home.
- I like E.T.
- See I'm just trying to do a movie.
- I like that E.T.
- If you stick to movie references I can do that.
Stop flying over my tongue.
- I like that E.T. looked like a toad.
- You liked that?
- A toad skin.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause he could've just been a toad.
- I think I would've made this.
- Enormous toad.
- Oh, that's an E.T. set. - Oh, E.T.
- Enormous, I get it. - Oh, yeah, okay.
- I think if you had to make any food out of E.T.,
I would really love to eat E.T. calamari.
- Like his asshole?
- No, his fingertips.
- His fingertips and neck.
- Like cut it, just cut, dissect him,
and just eat him like that?
Deep fried.
- Well, yeah, but not just like that.
Prepare it, of course. - Have you seen these?
- You've seen these?
- There's like a five-star chef.
- Yeah, yeah.
- There's these, this animator made a bunch of these videos
where it's him, not him, but it's somebody,
He animated like a chef cooking the starter Pokemon.
- That's funny.
- And it, honestly, the pulling off like Squirtle's shell
made me a little sad.
- Well, you've talked about this before,
how in Pokemon, they don't eat meat in Pokemon.
- Yeah, they're all vegetarians.
- That's the whole thing.
And I've never, anybody would eat any Pokemon.
- Right.
- They would all be pretty good, I think.
- Yeah, but have we talked about it?
Have we talked about which one would taste the best?
Definitely, I can tell you that we have
'cause there was a good month or two of my life
when I asked everybody that question every day.
- But the only one, there's a couple
that would not be good though.
- Yeah. - Any of the ones
that are made out of rocks, I don't want to eat a rock.
- I think it could be good, have you ever had rock candy?
- But sweet. - Yeah.
- Do these rocks have, does the rock have--
- Salt is rocks.
- Have you ever seen those, you know, like the,
you can cook a piece of chicken on like hot stones.
- Do you know a Pokemon I wouldn't--
- You could cook a Charmander with a Geodude.
You could burn the Geodude.
- Oh! - Okay, yeah, yeah.
- That's like, maybe there's a Pokemon
that's like a cast iron pan.
- Because no other food, really, you can cook it.
So you use a Charmander, you use its flaming tail
to cook, let's say, a Squirtle, okay?
You eat the Squirtle, and then you can eat the Charmander.
There's not another food that you can make something with it
and then eat the thing that made the food.
- That's a damn good point.
- You can't eat your oven or stove.
Here's an idea for, where do you buy pots and pans?
- The store.
- Crate and barrel.
- Here's an idea for crate and barrel,
how about you start making the pots and pans
out of stuff that you can fucking eat?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, like a salt lamp.
- Like a bread bowl.
- Or like a tostada.
- A bread bowl that you can heat up and then eat at the end.
- Yeah, you should be able to cook in a bread bowl.
- A bread bowl you can buy at home.
- Is that so much to ask?
- Look, this is why people listen to this show,
is our amazing ideas like this.
- Well, oh my god, listen, this is,
okay, this is gonna be trippy as fuck,
So anybody who's smoked weed recently,
don't listen to this part.
But imagine you have a bread bowl,
you're making your food in your bread bowl, okay, right?
- I'm already giving you money for this idea.
- Yeah, you're making food in your bread bowl,
and then it's like, well how did they make the bread bowl?
They made it in a bigger bread bowl.
And how'd they make that bread bowl?
- Oh my fuck.
- Because everything you make,
you should be able to eat the thing you made it in.
- Speaking of bread bowl, it rhymes with Red Bull.
Have you tried this new Red Bull flavor?
- What Red Bull flavor?
- Fig Apple.
- I can't go buy you one right now.
- We live in the Fig Apple.
- Ow.
- Okay.
- It's not so funny now, is it now?
- Hey, Caleb.
- It really hurts when you're paper cut.
- Hey, Caleb, you know what?
- Bah.
- Okay, now don't.
- We're going back to bah.
- Don't paper cut.
- And you're gonna get,
I'm gonna slice the shit out of you.
- You're not gonna do that ever.
- Ow!
Stop!
Do you think I could,
I could maybe give you a paper cut with this.
- No, it's too thin.
- Do you know which Pokemon I wouldn't eat?
- Crap-Dar.
- I probably wouldn't eat Crap-Dar.
I probably wouldn't eat the ice cream cone one.
Too spicy.
- True.
- For you, I bet.
You did just have a Chippy Chip for lunch.
- Yeah, I'm too full.
- Get a close up on the Chippy Chip.
- This used to be full.
- What a great name for a chocolate chip cookie.
- Dolly Madison Chippy Chip.
- Dolly Madison?
Vanilla flavored ice cream between
Two chocolate chip cookies rolled in chocolate chips.
You've never been to the Dixie Stampede.
You guys have any idea what that is?
No.
Dolly Parton's Dixie Stampede.
I know what it is.
I don't.
Where you go and they start--
it's basically Confederate medieval times.
And you get to eat--
they roast the pig and all that stuff.
And they have a lady who they pretend
is Dolly Parton, who's like--
The lady with big tits.
Yeah, I think she's wearing--
She has like a pillow from her bed in her chest.
- Do you remember that time we,
it was before a show we were doing
back in like 2018 or something like that,
like summer 2018.
There was that dude selling all those books outside.
It was in Boston.
Dude on the corner selling these books.
And then he had this one box of just adult books.
And there was that big book that he had.
It was like a German book.
Yes.
The whole thing was like, it was a 1970s, like, just women with just boobs that were too big.
Like heart hurting ones.
Yeah.
Like, like prosthetic.
I remember that.
I completely forgot about this.
Prosthetic boobs.
I don't remember.
You might not have been there.
I don't think you were around then.
I don't think you were around.
No.
I wasn't born.
Yeah.
You weren't around then.
You, you, once you.
around back then. Yeah, definitely not. I don't think I... That was so funny. I honestly don't think I
came onto the scene until around 2019. Yeah. I don't think I was really around. I think it was 2019,
because it definitely wasn't 2018. I didn't know you guys that well then. You're not that old. I'm
not that old, but I've been on the in the scene since then. Oh, that makes sense. Yeah. Yeah,
I do. I feel like anytime you go to an antique store, there is always that bin of like... Old
porno old porn but it's always like mostly playboy and then one of them is
like a 70s thing about who like bush yeah who can grow the biggest bush yeah
they're doing Chia they're doing the Chia thing on their bush they like to be
silly with them yeah the bush thing I'm listen I'll say it I'm glad that's out of
style hope it never comes back in a style giant bush I don't want that giant
bush yeah unless it's my own stuff and yeah I definitely don't want to have to
shave all the time. Me too. Yeah and also deodorant? No. Yeah. No no no no. Yeah. No.
Thank you. I want to grow my armpit hair out so long that it looks like a
predator's hair. Yeah well all you have to do is stop shaving it. I mean you keep
shaving it. Yeah. Well I shave it because of how much I swim. Yeah. Armpit hair has a
has a limit right? It can't get longer than like. No. That must be a friction thing.
Anybody with short armpit hair they shave it. How come your head hair can
grow forever but your armpit hair... I guess it's because it has to be because of this.
Your head hair cannot grow forever.
Ow! That hurt my feelings. So maybe take it back.
Okay. Thank you. Moving on.
Well that hair can grow forever. Yeah, that hair is gonna grow forever.
Somebody told me, somebody very rudely yesterday asked, he was like,
he's like, "Do you, oh, Caleb, I love your mustache. So like, every day do you
shave right in between the two parts of the mustache? I was like, "No." He was like,
"Oh, it just grows like that?" Then he laughed at me. He laughed at you? Yeah.
It doesn't even go up. It doesn't go... I don't have any... I mean, I can't even see it on camera.
It doesn't even like... Oh, I guess never mind, because it does... I was like gonna say, it
doesn't even like connect. It doesn't connect anywhere. Yeah. It looks like
eyelashes. Yeah, honestly. You should get a John Waters thing going.
That's what I'm going for. You should dye it jet black. You look like if they
combine John Waters and Divine. What? What the hell? I honestly don't know what
you're talking about. You have no idea? Okay, so... I don't know what you're talking about.
Not so artistic. Somebody doesn't care so much about transgressive art.
Isn't that movie about she eats diarrhea and fucks a dog?
She doesn't eat diarrhea, she eats a dog poop at the end of the movie.
It's dog poop. It's hard and solid dog poop.
That movie is one of the best movies I've ever seen.
What?
They make a butthole saying bird is the word.
That sounds like pretty funny honestly.
Yeah, it's so good.
Is it nasty though? It's nasty as hell.
Oh, I hate nasty shit.
I'm not too big a fan of the nasty stuff myself.
I think I don't like, I think I'm getting to the age where I'm a little too aware of,
I'm starting to get scared of blood again and I don't like blood in movies anymore.
Really?
Yeah, I've been watching some scary movies. I watched some clip from Terrifier 2 where
something horrible happens. I don't even want to repeat it because it's so great.
I didn't know the Terrifier was a film series. I didn't know Terrifier was a, I thought you made that up.
They made Terrifier 1 in 2016.
I thought I made it up too. Yeah, but apparently.
- Nobody named Terrifier in it,
they just called the movie that.
- Oh, what's the guy's name?
- Art the Clown.
- I bet that has some kind of double meaning.
- Well thank God, I'll say this much about that.
Thank God that they stopped making
the scary movie franchise,
because that has gotta be the most easily lampoonable name
in horror movie history.
- Yeah, Bart the Clown.
- Yeah, and he could look like Bart Simpson.
- That's actually, that's yeah, that's even smarter.
- Bart the Clown.
- And he gets choked by Homer the Clown.
- Homer the Clown. - He's a weed cart.
- Yeah, okay, let's keep going.
- And Marlon Wayans character. - Dart the Clown.
- I was thinking it would be-- - Dart?
- I was-- - And he's a cigarette.
- Yeah, I was thinking it was gonna be
maybe a kind of commentary on consumerism,
Walmart the Clown. - Ah.
- And he'd, I guess he'd be Walmart colors.
- Does Walmart have-- - Maybe like Lart the Clown.
- Walmart used to have a mascot.
- This is a crazy nonsense. - It's a nonsense, yeah.
- Does she ever have a mascot? - What does her name even mean?
- Yeah, well, Lart the Clown, asshole.
- You guys remember that Walmart used to have,
it was the smiley guy. He used to have guns too. Yeah. Thanks.
Thanks Trump for getting rid of the guns in Walmart.
That asshole hated guns. Yeah. The smiley was a smiley guy.
He just had a smiley face. That was Walmart's logo.
The mascot. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then they got rid of it.
They don't have that anymore? They don't have, I don't think Walmart has a...
This is Walmart's logo now.
Walmart's logo is, or mascot rather, is the greeter.
Oh, it's a it's a 120 year old lady.
Yeah, that yeah.
Yeah, a woman who's there was there was originally it was it
was the the greedy greeter and you would grab all the items
from Walmart.
He became friends with the smile.
Yeah.
Yeah, I honestly can't tell sometimes if the person at the
front of Walmart is a greeter or a homeless person at like
you're asking me for something.
They stop you.
Really told.
They're asking you to say hello to them.
It's really funny that they stop you at the greeting thing
to like do loss prevention and it's like they're they're two
jobs are to say like hi yeah and then their other job is like you fucking I
know you fucking stole something and if that is a shit I'll say this if the last
line of defense for Walmart for like stealing is a 100 year old woman who
always has a band-aid on her finger I want to playstation 5 I'm coming in 20
minutes early I'm kidnapping her easiest kidnapping
yeah your life honestly she the shoulders walk with you you just carry a
thing of Werther's originals around just give her a coupon she'll be fucking
I'm walking around looking for a grandson in two minutes. It's a
coupon. It's a coupon that says grandson's kiss. Yeah. Yeah.
They made it. I mean COVID made it really easy to to kidnap
service workers because now every single store has a thing
where it's like would you like us to bring this out to your
car? Yeah and you can be like I'm going to go to I'm going to
call Best Buy. I'm going to say I need I need your cheapest USB
cable. I need whatever costs less than $1 and I but I can't
go in because I'm afraid of disease. so I need you to come
put it in the trunk of my van.
- You pull up, you drive up--
- I need a female employee.
- With a big grabber in the trunk.
- Can you come plug it in the console?
I'm completely paralyzed and I can't move at all.
And then they crawl in and then click.
- Before that was never possible.
You'd go into Best Buy and be like,
I'm having trouble carrying this,
can you bring it to my car?
And they'd say yes, but only if it was a TV,
it was thousands of dollars.
- Yeah, exactly.
- I'm not spending thousands of dollars
to kidnap Kevin with long hair.
He looks like a girl, that's why I want him.
- Kevin with the long hair?
- Yeah.
- He's skinny.
Yeah, he's skinny.
Little skinny string bean Kevin.
Arm acne.
Arm acne, but shoulder acne.
That's what you got on Kevin.
Yeah.
Right, but if you blur your eyes.
Kevin.
But if I get him on a regimen once he's in my house, I could clear that shit up.
That's the main reason I want him.
I think he could be a contender.
Gonna be putting retinol on him.
Yeah, cover his body in retinol.
He blows up.
He looks like he got stung by a bee all over his body.
And if he misbehaves, that covers his body in ethanol.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's the shit right there.
Cut right and then all of a sudden you're sending him into the hood to do videos
Full of keratin debris yeah, yeah, you want I also want to say you want to be getting guys from Best Buy
Dog-human mutant hybrid runs wild. I
Just watched the fly to recently speaking of dog-human hybrid is there a dog-human hybrid in the fly - oh, yeah
You haven't seen it. No. Why don't they call it's on it's on HBO max. You should you'd really like it
It's made by the the special effects
Supervisor of the fly. Mm-hmm. So the director of the fly - that's it
Movie it's it's good. Oh, yeah, I don't like HBO max. What the hell is wrong with
Are you the guys been laying off all these people from HBO Max? I don't like HBO max. I don't like Discovery Plus. I don't like
You know I only like the parent you like peacock. You know what the paramount one is fire
I'm about to say to you. I was about to say you can bite my shiny metal ass that weird guess what that's a paramount property
Dude, I always thought Paramount Plus, I always thought that was the joke one.
I always was like, that's stupid.
That is the most fire one.
You know what they got on there?
Everything.
They have all of Star Trek on there.
Strangers with Candy.
They have Strangers with Candy.
They have every movie.
They got Fixer Upper.
They got Mission Impossible.
They have Jackasses.
The Wild Jackasses.
My favorite movie series.
And you can connect it to your Amazon Prime.
And that's what today's episode is about.
- We're gonna do a tutorial on how to connect Paramount Plus
to Amazon Prime.
- So what you wanna do is go into Amazon Prime,
go to subscriptions, and what you will do is
where you can add a subscription,
add a subscription to Paramount Plus,
and that will authorize a monthly charge on your account,
9.99 for Paramount Plus, and that's ad free.
Because Paramount Plus has 9.99 subscription,
which is ad free, but they also have a lower subscription,
which I believe is 5, 6, 8 dollars, I can't remember,
but that's not available on Amazon Prime.
You'll only be able to get the ad-free plan
as an Amazon subscription channel.
- If that's expensive. - If you have an existing
Paramount Plus account. - It may seem expensive,
but when you see the catalog,
you're gonna change your tune.
- Is it worth canceling my loop rate?
- And if you want to change your tune
from Spotify or Apple Music,
Amazon Music is a good alternative.
- And Amazon, that thing sucks.
- Amazon Music, Amazon Music.
- Don't you wanna get your music from the same place
you get your Paramount Plus and your packaging?
- You know what they should offer on Amazon Music?
If you buy a movie on Amazon Prime Video,
you should get the soundtrack for free in Amazon Music.
- That's actually a really good idea.
- If I buy Moulin Rouge, I should get the soundtrack
for free.
- You really want the Moulin Rouge soundtrack?
if I buy, I just, I'm thinking musicals.
- Well, it's just if you want the movie.
- Or you know what?
Full audio track of the movie in my library immediately.
- Why not both?
- I buy Joker on Amazon Prime Video.
The whole Joker.
- You just listen to it?
- Just listen to it.
- Yeah, probably be better that way.
- Audiobook style.
- Audible.
- Damn.
- I think--
- This boy hates Todd Phillips.
- We should do, what are you doing?
What are you looking at?
- Look at--
- Dollar bill?
Show the camera.
There he is, Benjamin Franklin.
Right there.
I mean, if you don't know that face, then you're not American.
Yeah, if you're an American and you don't know Benjamin Franklin, honestly I think that
you've gone to a charter school or something.
He looks so good in this picture.
Yeah, and there's, I mean, that's the, there it is right there.
I mean, it's like...
Right on the back here.
He looks great.
He looks incredible.
Flip that over, flip that over.
put that over here. You have a better, you have a better, right there, Statue of Liberty.
There it is. It's like the, just, just, what everyone loves about America. And they got
a little, they got a little excerpt from the Declaration of Independence here. This note
is not legal. It is to be used for motion pictures. Yeah. And this is actually, it's, it's actually
Hoffarth. Who's Hoffarth? That's Hoffarth. Type in, will you Google this name? No, you won't be able to see it. Yeah, that's...
that's it says Hawthorne. I want to learn who this Hawthorne. Yeah, can we look up Hawthorne
really quick? H-O-F-F-A-R-T-H Hawthorne. One of the little known founding fathers. Hawthorne
look up Hawthorne $100 bill. Yeah, why was he on the one? What did Hawthorne do that
was so great. Hoffarth.
100... it doesn't say much about Hoffarth.
Images of Hoffarth $100.
Maybe it's the owner of the...
Is it... could it be Joseph Hoffarth right there?
There it is.
Oh, there's... there's Hoffarth.
These are rare. These are like $2 bills.
Yeah.
You know, you got to go...
Get the Hoffarth $100.
Yeah. It's a special edition. It's like a McDonald's BTS meal.
Yeah.
And the treasurer is Linda.
Linda?
Linda what? I can't read that. Linda Hoffarth?
Mike, Mike, see Mike Lee. I love having props.
Yeah. I'd love to have so many props in my life. Oh wait there's a, it says it right here.
Oh, Secretary Pablo Banana.
Hey, I didn't vote for him. Yeah. Okay. Oh that's Linda there, okay. Yeah.
Doesn't that look like that says Pablo Banana? I did vote for Hoffarth.
I did not vote for Pablo Banana. Zoom into lower right there, Pablo Banana.
The treasurer? The secretary right there?
Yeah, right where your mouse is.
We need to see... I need everyone to see this signature here and help me verify that it says Pablo Banana.
Okay, we're having a little bit of a technical difficulty.
Some kind of technicality.
You're just zooming in on Hoffarth.
Alright.
Yeah, right there.
There it is.
Alright, well...
[laughter]
Yeah, who do you think is the next person that gets put...
'Cause due to inflation, we know about inflation.
Yeah.
Inflation is gonna, eventually we're gonna need
a thousand dollar bill.
A $10,000 bill.
There used to be a thousand dollar bill.
I know, I know, you dickhead.
And you know who was on it?
Shut the fuck up!
Hoffarth.
Hoffarth wasn't on it.
I know.
He's on the hundred.
I was doing a callback.
Who was on it?
U.S.E.'s S. Grant, I think.
I think it was Mr. 1000.
(laughing)
Really?
Yeah, don't you remember that?
He had the sunglasses.
(laughing)
- Sunglasses is a 1000. - Misto one foul wow.
- I don't think it's Ulysses S. Grant.
- Why are you saying Ulysses like that?
Ulesses. - Ulesses.
- Ulysses. - Ulysses.
- Ule-pee.
- The-- - Ule-pee.
- Ule-pee. - Ule-pee.
- Ule-pee somebody. - Ule-pee somebody.
- I won't.
- When I freeze it and I put it in a snow cone maker.
- I think it was actually Bill though.
- Who's Bill?
- $1,000 Bill.
(laughing)
Okay. Plasma ball right now. Plasma ball right now.
Bah!
Bah.
There you go. That's just a mental reset I need. I see that every once in a while.
But with inflation, we're gonna have a $5,000 bill. We're gonna have a $10,000 bill.
There's gonna be, eventually, $100,000, million-dollar bill.
Who should we put on it?
I think I have an idea.
Oh, who?
Bill.
$1,000 bill.
Why would you put $1,000 bill on the $10,000 bill?
Okay.
I was thinking maybe it would be somebody like Lady Gaga or Lizzo.
Do you think they'd ever do a bill that had three people on it at the same time?
I mean, what do you look at?
I always Grover Cleveland.
You know we have a guy who looks things up for us.
Yeah, but I didn't want to make him do that.
That's very nice of you.
people on one bill, kind of a $3,000 bill, and it's like, "Oh my god, what if the $3,000
bill is three $1,000 bills together and it's like this big?"
Holy shit.
They just never cut them apart.
Yeah, it's a square and it has three different faces.
And I don't know who the three faces could be.
I actually have no idea what three guys...
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of hard to find three guys who work perfectly together and have
kind of the exact same look that you need for a bill like that.
And maybe their heads are really close together in the thing too.
What does it say under on the crest though?
Does it say three guys?
Does it say everyone's name?
Three guys.
Three guys who don't give a fuck.
I have the perfect idea for the $4,000 bill.
Three identical strangers.
That's what it says.
It could be completely digital and on the computer.
Let's only have three guys on it.
Let's tell them we have three guys on it.
Yeah, you know, these NFTs basically eventually
there'll be pretty much everything.
You'll be using NFTs to wipe your ass with eventually
because they'll be actually physical.
Non-flushable toilet paper.
Yeah, well that's what that would be.
That's what the baby wipes are.
NFTs, I say no fucking the way I'm using those.
No fucking the way.
No fucking the way I'm using those.
No fucking thought.
fucking thought.
Because I have a lift.
I have a lift and a speech impediment.
An NFT what else could that?
Why are you making light of speech impediments?
What?
Cease?
I'm maybe of a personal best interest.
Why are you making light of speech impediments cease?
Cease what I mean?
I will cease my speech impediment joke.
Remember Max Keeble's principal would say that shit.
Did you ever know anybody who couldn't say their R's well into adulthood?
No.
I think I did.
Kind of.
I knew one person who did not well.
I knew only homeschooled kids, so pretty much that was the only other person I knew.
That was the only people you knew.
I knew a lot of people who were 16 years old, like, "I just got my Dwyva's license."
I'd be like, "Oh, cool, man.
That's awesome."
I knew one kid, I swear to God, name was Ethan, looked exactly like a fucking bird.
Yeah.
had a look like a pigeon had a this kind of thing going on and couldn't say as
ours. Hope he's doing all right. Yeah me too. Yeah I was doing good. We have a list
today. Yeah. Cameron found. Yeah Cameron. You intro this one. Sure. Yeah wait I am
curious how'd you stumble upon this? Stumble upon I was looking up lists. Yeah.
Just a normal just looking up. Just doing my Google rounds. Checking my different
different web groups for what's funny or what's like funny on the web.
This seems like so hyper specific. It doesn't seem like it has that many views even.
How did you end up finding this?
I was just finding lists, googling around, personal.
I'm in business. It seems like you're saying the same thing
so that we stop asking you, but you're not answering anything.
Stop asking me what? I'm saying where'd you find this list?
It's on, it was on, I was Googling around and you were looking at different groups. You
already said all that.
Yeah, web groups.
Subscription, like email.
Listen, everybody's a part of web groups, okay? I think we all are pretty familiar with
how those work.
Yeah.
Web groups.
Web rings.
Exactly.
Web 3.0.
No.
Google Plus.
Do you remember that?
I think no fucking the way I'm on there.
I mean, not to get sidetracked, but do you remember that one time we were hanging out
at this bar one time, we were talking about photography, and somebody walked up to us
and said, do you remember?
You were here.
Yeah, I was there.
Somebody walked up to us and said, "Were you talking about digital photography and Web
3.0 spaces?"
This honestly, this city should be just bulldozed completely.
Well, okay, but it was somebody who was like clear just clearly very like like fucked up
Yeah, and they still were like no and she's like fuck you. Yes. She said she said she literally was just like okay
Fine fuck you then and then she's my ears stole Patrick's drink all my beer and drank it and then walked away
And then her boyfriend walked back with the beer and was like I'm so sorry you got owned dude. I
funny.
It's fucking owned.
Yeah.
And then Patrick went like this.
I don't even want that.
Wait, I was there.
I think I came back.
You came back.
You were there after.
You didn't see it.
You didn't see it, but that was.
It was pretty funny.
That was a crazy interaction.
I'm basically not there breathing these days.
I've been thinking about that.
Anytime I hear the word Web 3.0 now, all I think is that person stealing my beer, and
guess what?
I'm not getting on board with that shit.
Oh no.
I hear all I'm saying is I hope I hope a spider doesn't make a new web 3.0
Cuz the spider webs that we have these days are already enough. Yeah, there are enough with the webs like there's one right there. Yeah
This is scared of it. Sorry. You said it's he said he said it was scary. He didn't even get scared
Enter the list yeah sissy factory yeah
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Sissy hypnosis and behavior modification.
- I went to the sissy factory on a tour in high school.
- I went to your sissy factory, nobody knew you.
- Pound that out.
- Yeah, that's what I saw at the sissy factory
was some sissies getting pounded out.
(laughing)
I went to the sissy factory on a tour
and they let me put, they let me go in the tube.
- There's a tube at the sissy factory?
- You got Willy Wonka'd at the sissy factory?
- I fell into the chocolate river.
(laughter)
- Bro got glooped.
- There is definitely a sissy named Augustus Gloop.
- Yeah.
- So this is a sissy website.
And it's a sissy factory for sissies.
- I'm just imagining just like a,
and let's say it's like,
(humming)
just like a conveyor belt of all these like.
- Just tough guys getting pumped
in the sissy factory. - Getting justified.
- And just getting, getting.
What's that thing, the thing from like Attack of the Clones
where it like squishes like C-3PO's arm
and then they come out--
And then they just turn into like a sissy.
Beautiful sissies.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's basically what this website is.
Yeah.
And oh, you got, so okay, so yeah, you have to,
this clicker thing, yeah, it has to be focused over there.
Okay, all right, so this is the Sissy Factory.
And it says, okay, so let's be clear here.
The goal of this blog is to fill your mind
with new concepts and ideas
and turning you into a well-trained sissy,
to corrupt you, to play with your insecurities
and manipulate you little by little
until you realize it's too late.
I know you're way too afraid to really embrace your destiny.
It's all right.
Here, you can take all the time you need.
I know that you will come back again and again
unable to resist your urge, to your urge,
unable to resist to your true self.
Because no matter what happens, you keep coming back,
you keep looking for more, you keep surfing for sissy porn,
you keep fantasize about being a girl,
you keep having thoughts about submission.
It's probably not the first time you read this page.
Accept it.
I feel like you're reading this to us to maybe hypnotize us.
It's also, I'll say you didn't really stumble much.
It's almost like you had this thing memorized.
Yeah, I was reading it off the screen.
Yeah, but you just like, you hit every B,
you had all the right inflection.
Are you, you're--
Have you read this before?
You're not trying to corrupt us.
I had to go through it to make sure
it's suitable for the show.
You went through Sisyphication.
Well, no, I had to go through, no, okay,
I didn't go through, I had to go through the factory.
I had to like inspect it.
I'm like the health inspector.
Okay, but the health inspector usually
eats the food I think. Sure, but the health inspector doesn't usually turn into food.
That's a really good point. Not usually, unless it's a very bad restaurant. Yeah, so here's
some comments on this main page here. Okay. Shia1girl says, "I have been comming 10 times
a day on your blog since more than a year and can't stop. I really can't." It seems like
that might hurt your body to comm that much times. And two anonymous's say, "Just found
this place and we'll be back all the time and someone else says can't wait for
updates a new girly tasks. There's tasks on this website. Yeah. So it's kind of like
geocaching. Well I mean we'll get into what the tasks are I don't want you guys.
But I want to. I need you guys to kind of go through the process organically. Okay.
Alright. So are you, it really does seem like you're trying to sissy-fy at me. Yeah.
And hey I don't need to sissy-fy you guys at all. Okay. So a lot of these
commenters really like this website as you can see, but there are some who feel a little
differently which I think is the next one I put on here.
Yeah, fuck you, piss of shit, playing with our mind.
We straight, love girls.
So not everybody's on board so much with the process.
Fuck you, piss of shit.
I guess that's the other thing is like, this guy, how does he end up on this website in
the first place, right?
Because somebody who's not all that interested in becoming a sissy.
Imagine you stumble on this website by accident like a sorry imagine somebody yes
Stumbles on a website like this by accident random guy could any random young man
Yeah, of course stumbles on something like this on the internet
Maybe looking about googling funny top 10 list mm-hmm
And they end up on something like this and they find themselves
Sissified because the process that they went through was not under their control. That's a good point imagine
How much rage you must feel you probably bubbling with just just bubbling to the brim. Yeah, absolutely
To the right to the fill a little it just completely ready
We're only like a pot of noodles like a vat of lye. Oh, that's so fucking up like shakshuka. Yeah, just
Bubbling yeah your eggs inside it with those eggs inside of you as a sissy boy now. No you're not a sissy
No, you're mad that they're trying to make you yeah, yeah, I thought that you turned into it
No, you can I understand how any random guy could be oh I tried to Google thirsty
I tried to Google thirsty or I tried to I tried to I was okay
I was I yeah, I was good 60 year old looks like I googled anal play yeah
But and I found something I found a I found a list of ways to you know well. Yeah
Gory details I tried to Google sissy spasic movies and what came up was sissy gaping movies
What the hell happened here basically the internet is a dangerous place, and that's why yeah
- Yeah, if someone is trying to sissify you at every turn,
you don't know when stuff like this could happen
or where it could happen.
I mean, it can happen.
One second you're watching,
I can eat spicy food hypnosis.
Your YouTube auto plays,
I'm a girl.
- I'm a sissy dude hypnosis.
- I'm a girl.
- Yeah, yeah, no, it's scary.
- But I can eat spicy food though.
- That's true, which might be--
- Taco Bell, here I come.
- Is there a--
- Finally, I have enough spice tolerance.
I may be a complete sissy,
But I finally have enough spice tolerance to go to Taco Bell.
I can finally get a Mexican pizza.
I'm wondering if there's a--
Goddamn that auto play.
I had Taco Bell the other night.
I pooped more than I ever pooped in my life the next day.
Really?
Yeah, I just felt terrible after that.
I felt great.
I pooped literally more than I've ever pooped in my life.
OK, I'd like to say this really quickly.
That's the third story that you guys have told that is you two
and I wasn't there.
Well, you don't stay out late enough.
You guys go to Taco Bell--
Oh, yeah.
We have some weird-ish, dude.
Yeah, like this fucking damn list.
I was wondering, is there, do you think, I guess, no, because there can't be macho hypnosis,
right?
There can't be.
There's hypnosis for everything.
I guarantee it.
There is, okay, because there's, I mean, this seems to be a very big sub-sect, this seems
to be a very big community, but I'm wondering if there is the reverse community, which is
like people trying to, men or women trying to become...
Macho guys. The exact opposite which is like women trying to become
macho guys. I like 1000% guarantee that that is just fully an actual thing
in the way that you described it. There's so if you, I think it was...
Every action has an opposite reaction. Well no, there's just people, there are hypnosis videos for
literally everything. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah but you don't hear, you hear more about
about sissy hypnosis. You hear more about them but I guarantee it exists. You never in the
sissy hypnosis community you don't hear about the macho hypno community. Do you think there's
YouTube videos that can help me grow a horn? Yeah. I've been thinking about that. Grow horn
hypnosis. I've been really thinking about that. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. I think that that is
something. Do you think it would work? I think I'd need to drink like a crazy amount of milk
for that to happen for me. Yeah. I don't remember what's next here. Let's see here. Oh yeah
Post more slush.
Oh, that was posted the day before my birthday.
This person is, this is almost, they're trying to sissify the sissies.
Yeah, the factory.
The factory, the factory, yeah.
Who owns, is it a sissy that owns a factory?
I don't think so.
Again, it's not usually.
I think it's a master.
If you're at the Doritos factory, a Dorito doesn't run the damn thing.
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
The first sissy small business owner.
[laughter]
I can't wait for the first sissy president.
Yeah.
That's gonna be huge.
Oh, well, no, because that was Herbert Hoover, right?
The FBI guy.
- Hoffarth, you don't think he might have been?
(laughing)
- You don't think he might have been his,
more like putting the sissy president on a dollar bill
and doing like a kissy face?
- Hoffarth.
- What's the Herbert Hoover, is that a conspiracy
that he would wear like ladies underwear?
- No.
- So he did?
- We don't talk about conspiracies or support things
like that on this show.
- Yeah, no thanks.
- It's not okay to talk about presidents in that way.
- Herbert Hoover was the president of the FBI though.
- He's a president of anything.
- Yeah.
- It's not okay to demean them.
- How about you check your democratic politics
over at the door there, buddy.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause we're trying to get sissified right now.
Okay, so we got--
- I think you're trying to get sissified.
- Here's the actual list we're doing.
- I'm not trying to get sissified.
- Here's the actual list we're doing, okay?
10 things not really manly you should do.
- Okay.
- Hello, sweetie.
- Hi.
- Today you're going to, so all right,
already working on Pat.
- What?
- Didn't even do anything.
- Did I say something? - Yeah, voice, yeah.
- Today you're going to learn how to appear more girly.
If you want to be a better sissy, you must think as a female.
In fact, you must be overly feminine.
You must be a stereotype of the woman.
- Okay, so what are even some women's stereotypes?
I'm not even-- - Shopping.
- Shopping is big, probably. - Shoplifting.
- Okay, true shoplifting is--
- Well, let's take a look here.
Let's see what the first thing is on this list.
- Being too tired.
- Oh wait, this is not, okay, so, but how?
I mean, this is here, we're gonna get some information here.
But how?
Well, it's very simple, princess.
- No, thank you for calling me that.
Thank you for calling me that.
- Thank you for calling you that.
You just have to add some girly behavior
to your everyday life.
Everything you do must be overly feminine.
At first, it will ask some efforts,
but very soon your mind will change.
Your brain will make new connections.
You can change the way you think
by constant repetition of this girly behavior.
You could even not notice it at first
because we are talking about the long term,
but it will affect your psyche, your mind, and personality.
Here's a list of 10 things to add in your attitude.
- Okay, so I-- - Ready?
- I'd just like to say, even before this goes any further,
this is not working on me.
This is like the last thing I'm interested in, I think.
- Right, and so it says it's long-term,
so you wouldn't actually notice a change yet.
- But I mean like, first-- - So it was working on you.
- So far, first item and shit, it's like, pfft, don't care.
- You don't even care?
- I mean, that is-- - This isn't the first--
- It's not working on me either.
- This also isn't the first--
This is not the first item.
- It's just, but-- - This is,
we haven't even gotten to the first item yet.
first item here. But I barely feel anything. You barely feel anything? Barely nothing.
So go ahead, test me. Test you? Okay. Yeah. Alright, well let's look at what the first
thing is here. One, tears come really easy. And all these are by the way are gifts. Okay.
But I couldn't, I didn't want you to, we can't go to this actual website because the amount
of pornography and buttholes that are winking and flexing at the screen is unsuitable.
You always see that in porn and you're like, "How do they do that?"
Yeah.
Easy.
You can flex your butthole?
Yeah.
What?
What kind of ass kegel do you have to-- what exercise to flex your butthole?
Mine just opens up like a--
Shit, shit in a lot.
Yeah.
Mine opens up like a garbage disposal and then just closes.
It's really bad.
Yeah.
Mine beatboxes.
If I'm farting.
True.
Come on.
You would think that the sissy website wouldn't have so much god damn pornography on it.
You'd think it would have more good advice.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, this list has no pornography in it at all, but I just didn't want to be on this
website because there really is something around every corner.
There is a thing going in a thing or a thing coming out of a thing.
It's really...
Really tip toe.
It's really, yeah, it's dangerous.
Try to be overly sensitive and show your emotions.
For too long, you've learned to hide your feelings.
From now on, you will show where you're sad, happy, or excited.
Crying at the end of a romance movie is something you should be proud of.
Okay.
Yeah, it's not really for me.
I have more cry at the end of like sports and dad movies.
But you do cry?
In like my own kind of stoic way.
Dad movies like what?
Like the daddies gets hurt.
The daddies?
Or have you been watching a movie called The Daddies?
I know like the dad, the fathers, sorry.
So like the daddies or fathers get--
Oh, the founding, oh Lincoln.
Lincoln makes me--
Hoffarth.
Hoffarth, Lincoln.
(laughing)
Hoffarth biopic.
You know who would have been great, rest in peace,
Philip Seymour Hoffarth.
Oh my god, yeah, look at how--
He would have been incredible.
He would have been a perfect Hoffarth.
For Hoffarth.
So that's pretty sad.
But I don't even really wanna think about that.
Yeah.
I'm fucking Hoffarth.
(laughing)
Fuck man.
I'm gonna be on the fucking $100 bill.
I need to go across the fucking Delaware somewhere.
We're gonna fu-
No, that's not what Hoffarth did.
Hoffarth didn't do that.
What did Hoffarth do?
All he did was take a picture, a painting of himself.
Yeah.
To be on the $100 bill.
He took a picture.
He died the next day.
He took a picture and he-
He was the guy, he was, he was, Benjamin Franklin was, was sick that day and he, they were like,
"We need to paint this today so it can go, we can send it to the press."
And he was just, he was just off to the side and he was like, "Oh fuck, man, I guess you
Yeah, he invented he also invented gravy
We're gonna fucking add flour to fucking bacon fat oh
Yeah, this is all a fucking yeah that way he was he was I mean one of the he's a founding father for a reason
Yeah, yeah, I'll say that much
What's next on here to have a diary? Okay, so I don't have a diary. I have a notebook. You know, it's a diary. No
It's not really a diary, I put ideas in it.
It's a diary.
I guess the difference between a diary and a notebook is a diary I guess doesn't have that, it has less ideas, more of a recounting.
Yeah.
I've never thought about that.
The notebook is nice, but I will say I fucking hate when my little brother breaks into it.
Yeah.
It pisses me off.
Oh, because the...
The lock on it.
Yeah.
The heart-shaped lock.
It's like, okay, I get that you're mischievous and shit,
but that's literally my personal ideas are in my notebook,
so please leave those alone.
- Yeah, exactly.
Theories, diagrams.
- I'm putting, there's math in there and stuff.
- That type of thing.
- There's a lot of numbers and measurements.
- Yeah.
- In the past, many people regularly kept a personal diary.
It's a great way to record your thoughts and feelings,
like why you've cried at the end of this particular movie.
Try to write few lines a day about girly things you've done
and use as much color as you can.
It seems like crying at the end of a movie is a big thing into sissy hypnosis.
What was the last movie y'all cried at?
Probably it would have to be...
Oh, let me think about this.
Hold on, let me think for a second.
Think about it.
Probably...
Well, hold on, let me think.
You have all the time you need.
You don't have to keep asking.
Yeah, let me think.
Yeah, I never cried at a movie.
I just went through all the movies I ever watched.
- Oh really?
- That's why it took me so long, yeah.
- I think when I was a kid I cried at Click
and I cried at Shrek.
And I think I also cried at The Boy in the Striped Pajamas.
Those were probably the big three.
- I cried at Bridge to Terabithia.
- Yeah, I thought that, I remember my friend Joma
cried at that and I accused him of having a crush
on the girl.
- No way.
- Right?
- I cannot tell you, my little nerdy kid asked,
I can't tell you how mad I was.
'Cause I had read the book of Bridge to Terabithia
before the movie, of course.
And they make up a fantasy world,
and they're playing, how fucking mad I was
that there was no dragons or giants in that movie.
- And also-- - That they play in a treehouse.
- Show the girl dying.
- Yeah, make her hit her head on the rock.
- Yeah, blood.
- Do a Mortal Kombat x-ray attack.
- Yeah, exactly.
Get a close up of a blue bone breaking in half.
- And a health bar going down.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I don't think I've ever really cried in a movie.
- I already said that, so.
- No, I don't think I've ever been able
to suspend my disbelief enough in a movie.
Shut up.
That's got to be one of the lamest things you've ever said.
Yeah, I can't believe that you said that.
I've never been able to suspend my disbelief enough.
Aww.
I'm just in pure disbelief. I can't even cry.
My disbelief is too active.
I'm not crying because this didn't really happen.
Yeah, it's too just nothing's actually happening.
When I see Tom Hanks on screen in a movie,
I'm not crying.
I'm never thinking, "That's Sully Sullenberger."
I'm thinking that's Tom Hanks playing Sully Sullenberg.
And that's and what makes you cry is to really believe that something is currently happening.
Yeah.
It's not to have a sad emotion or anything like that.
You might be like a sociopath.
Yeah, that's kind of scary.
No, I cried at a video of a dog once.
But that's real, right?
Dog getting...
But the fact that...
You don't cry at anything that has a...
Have you ever cried at a sad song?
No.
Yeah.
What song?
Um, "Pop Goes the Weasel."
That is sad.
Because you realize they're not playing the song live.
Yeah.
It's an mp3 file.
Well, that's what's sad about it.
Or a flack.
- Is that their, oh, I wish I could've heard them play
Pop Goes the Weasel live.
- I wish this was a flack.
- Oh.
- It's too compressed.
- Okay, and let's see here.
Three love gossips.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- I do love gossiping.
- You have to show a special interest to gossip.
You must know every detail about the new girl or guy
everyone is speaking about.
You have to speak about Caleb, too.
- Okay, that's not.
- Did you know that Angelina and Brat
were living in a new house?
(laughter)
- You have to speak about futile details
and be jealous of course.
- This was clearly written by somebody
who's midway through their sissification journey.
They're not getting the details correct.
- Well no, no, Brett is Brad Pitt's name
after he got sissified.
- But there's no--
- True sissy fans know that.
- Or somebody's halfway between the macho and the sissy,
they're saying Angelina and Brat.
They're thinking about sausages still.
- Oh, they're thinking about the sausage
that's gonna go in their butt.
- Oh, that could be sissy.
Back to sissy mode.
It's a good point.
- Yeah, let's see what's next here.
For drink girly alcohol only.
And I want you to read this quote for us.
- Everything that has been listed so far
has been something that I do.
- That you do?
You already said you don't cry at movies.
You don't keep a diary.
- Yeah, you don't do any of this stuff.
- It's the last, you gossip and drink.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I guess you know what?
I guess it's the last two.
- Yeah.
- Pink wine. - His brain's already resetting.
Pink wine makes me slutty.
Yeah, do it in maybe her voice.
I don't remember what she sounds like.
Pink wine makes me slutty.
That's what Jordan Peterson.
Oh, it makes me bloody slutty.
Pink wine turns me into a complete slut.
I turn into a complete, sissy slut.
They're being sissified by bloody pink wine,
it makes me a slut?
No, I don't remember who that is.
When you introduce pink wine, it turns me to a total slut.
- Total slut.
(laughing)
- He was in slut rehab for a while, I heard.
He was acting like too much of a slut.
- Jordan Peterson was addicted,
his daughter got him addicted to pink wine.
- Yeah, and addicted to lipstick.
- Yeah.
- And then I started to put on lipstick,
and it turned me into a total and complete slut.
(laughing)
- What do they mean by girly alcohol?
- Fruity drinks are the only alcoholic beverages for you,
with a glass of wine, of course.
The way you drink is also important. Try to be as classy as possible when you're drinking
your second Cosmo. By the way, have you read the last issue?
Okay, so they're saying you can't order... See, this is an important...
So you can get a Cosmo, but you also have to get a glass of wine. So when you're drinking,
you have a martini glass in one hand, and then the other hand you're holding wine. So
it's like rose and then a fruity girl... like an espresso martini or something. So basically,
You just have to be an alcoholic too.
You just gotta get fucked up.
Yeah.
You gotta also be a light.
You have to be one of these girls who drinks one beer and is like, "Ahh."
But not beer.
We're not talking about beer.
Unless it's a mixed beer.
Mixed beer.
Yeah.
Ooh.
A mixed beer.
I'm kind of interested in that.
Candy and beer.
It's Bud Light and it's Coors Light and it's a splash of Miller Light.
I will say, I think I'm approaching this.
(laughing)
- That's a good idea.
- Dropping a Jolly Rancher into this beer thing
like it's a fucking, like it's lean.
- Dude, what'd you just put in my drink?
No, it was a Jolly Rancher.
(laughing)
No, I just put a, no, I'm serious.
It was literally a Jolly Rancher.
- It was actually just a Jolly Rancher.
(laughing)
- Five, spend time with girls.
- No thank you.
- The more time you spend with girls,
the more you will get used to the things they do,
the way they talk or think will become normal for you
in no time.
You will learn what they like and their hobbies.
Of course, you should spend some time
with the most feminine girls you know.
- I'm spending time with them right now.
- You and me.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And they're in my head.
(laughing)
- It's Tinkerbell.
- Tinkerbell was bad.
- She was feminine as fuck.
- She was bad, bro.
She was bad.
- She was feminine as fuck, dude.
- She actually was.
Tinkerbell was yeah fucking bad. I do bet she liked girly drinks
Definitely kept a diary
Do not use a harsh language or curse words. What are you talking about?
That's what it says like hose always say that yeah, we're not talking about hose you're right sissy's mother not talking about
Distinction you're right. Let's get one thing fucking straight. I'm sorry. Hey, you know sometimes I you know this new world
Hey, let's get one thing straight, and let's get one guy on straight. It's not working on me
I'm not becoming a sissified girl.
Thank you very much.
- That's very simple.
No curse word, it's not elegant.
And you want to be an elegant princess, don't you?
- I'm gonna do male-- - A sissy would be too
scared to wield the sword of fuck.
- I'm gonna do masculine affirmations for myself.
- Dude, the sword of fuck is one of my favorite weapons
in one of those irreverent, earthbound inspired
comedy RPGs. - Sunset Overdrive.
- This is just making me want to do even more manly stuff
like drink a, or have a hot dog.
Like play with your hands.
A hot dog? It makes you want to have a hot dog?
Yeah, just fucking gulp a hot dog down.
What's more manly than that?
Okay, so we're talking about-
At a football game!
I just want to go and watch a football game and have a hot dog and gulp it down.
Yeah, he'll be at the girls football game.
Yeah, to jack off!
Yeah, the flag football game.
Yeah, I'll be at the girls football game to fucking jack off in the audience, asshole.
Yeah, he will be a cheerleader.
Yeah, he's gonna be at the flag football game and guess what?
He's gonna have all the snacks cut up.
- Not true.
- I'm gonna be a--
- I don't need a guy to cut my snacks up for me.
- Hey guys, just a heads up,
I'm gonna be a cheerleader this year.
A leader of cheer at Christmas cheer.
I'm gonna be one of the cheeriest Christmas celebrators
of the entire world.
- You know, I could actually believe something like that.
- Yeah.
- Okay, the next one is seven smile often.
- Not my thing.
- Smiling is a way to show your feeling
and also not to appear as an alpha man.
You must smile more and more to look offensive.
If someone pushes you, just smile and...
What's... I'm hanging on the edge of my seat.
It was probably like a gif of somebody...
Oh, sucking a cotch.
No, there was nothing.
There was nothing?
Yeah, there was nothing.
It just said, "Smile and..."?
Yeah.
I got me hanging on the edge of my...
I mean, not hanging... I don't care.
This is a sissy trick.
I'm not tricking you.
Sissies don't trick.
Sissies get tricked.
You just said, "I'm not tricking you.
Sissies don't trick," which means that you're a sissy.
I didn't say that.
(laughing)
- Swipset doesn't, that word, swipset doesn't work.
(mumbling)
(laughing)
I don't know what you're talking about.
- All right, I'm gonna get you one day.
You can be a sissy, I'll hold you down.
- Always say sorry.
- Oh, that's the next one. - That's what the and is.
- Always say sorry, I'm sorry.
That's what it says.
- I'm getting you.
- You're getting me what?
- Getting me a bag of smart food?
- No, I'm not gonna get you.
If I do, I'd have to cut it up and maybe chew it,
feed you like a baby bird.
By the end of this, dude, you're gonna be fully sissy'd.
- I'm, check this out.
- Damn, he actually, yeah, we got it like that.
- Yeah.
- We got a 28-pack of chips.
Not that big of a deal. - I don't even care.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - I'd throw shit like that.
- Doesn't fucking matter. - That might break
some of the corns. - Hey, cut to the wide shot.
- Fuck. - I don't even give a fuck.
You see that throw, too?
Manly throw. - That was--
- Not like a girl at all.
- It's perfect form.
- Always say sorry, I'm sorry.
Even if it's not your fault,
even if you have no reason to apologize,
saying sorry must be one of your gimmicks.
You should always sound like you're begging.
- Ugh.
- Okay. - Oh.
- No.
- I might have to try that.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Ah.
- Let's begin.
- Okay, Ash.
- Okay.
- How would you, I mean, always sound like you're begging?
Like in every situation?
- Yeah.
- That's hard.
- Yeah, I guess.
Like, how do you say like, hello in bed?
- Hello. - Can I say hi to you?
- Please, can I say hi?
- That's exactly, yeah, that's, that's.
- Girls don't do that. - You nailed it.
You nailed it instantly with one try.
- No, I don't act, I don't have a natural.
- Yeah, what would that even sound like?
(laughing)
- No, it didn't work out.
No, I don't know what the, no.
- Okay, be too obsessive about cleaning.
That's not me, my fucking clothes are dirty all the time.
Not only you hate dust, but you should look overly disturbed
when something is messy.
Clean a bit, even if you're at a restaurant
or at a friend's place.
If someone asks you why you're doing this,
just say, "Sorry, I can't help it."
Yeah, I'm afraid of dust.
No, I hate cleaning fucking dust.
I hate dust because the mites are too big.
Yeah, it's not my thing.
I don't like mites.
See, I don't care that this fucking, this table's filthy.
There's cables everywhere, it doesn't bother me at all.
I don't care at all about any of that.
Not a big deal to me.
- I was gonna put something on the table,
but then I don't really have much to grab over.
- Yeah, there's not too much to put on the table.
- Yeah.
- Oh, nevermind.
I thought I saw something.
It was nothing.
Number 10, don't be afraid of being dumb or silly.
Okay.
- Okay.
- I'm pretty sure most of you are pretty smart,
so it's not going to be easy,
but there is some way to achieve this.
You can stop having an answer to everything.
Relax and speak spontaneously.
Acting silly is fun.
Don't be afraid to look silly.
You can even pretend if you want.
The key is to ease your mind
and stop trying to solve any problems.
- Kind of a zen.
- Yeah.
- Of a zen situation.
- Yeah, no it is.
- Honestly, that one, pretty good advice.
- Not bad advice, it's not bad life advice in general.
I think even non-sissies like us
could probably find something.
- Yeah, non-sissies like us.
- Yeah, yeah, could probably find something to gain from.
- Everything on this list, now that I think about it,
maybe all 10.
- Yeah, you know, most of them has a little, you know,
it's like, yeah, you know, a couple of things.
It's like, you know, what they say about
every religious text has little nuggets of truth in it.
- Right. - So like,
Bible, the golden rule, Islam,
it's like Muhammad was the number one guy, you know.
Like, you can learn a little bit from the sissy thing.
Not, you don't have to take everything so seriously,
you know, but-- - The sissy king.
- The sissy thing, they got something.
- The sissy thing of ours.
- All right, well, that's pretty much it, right?
Is there anything else?
- Yeah, there's a few things here.
- Okay, show me. - You should go through.
You know what you have to do now, sissy.
See you soon.
- Okay.
- Okay, look what Patrick just did.
- What? - So he's saying so,
I'm again-- - Completely, completely.
I'm just gonna try this slide again.
- It's working on anyone?
- So I'm just gonna throw this slide up again.
- Okay.
- All right, don't wait. - Okay, that's interesting.
- I'm not gonna say don't.
- I mean, you need to just--
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Let me just try one more time here,
'cause, okay, so three times, that's kind of--
- Three times what?
Okay, never mind.
So we're just gonna move on here.
There's a few comments I wanted to read.
I practically do she all these things now.
Well, what they're saying is I do she things.
Yeah, she all.
She all, all she all.
Everything I do is a she thing now.
Everything is a she thing.
Shell.
Or shell things, yeah.
Thank you, training accomplished.
Well, that guy, you should get,
do you think you get like a diploma when you're sissified?
That would be huge.
Yeah.
I would not like to have that.
Well, that would be very small.
That would be, is good about it.
That's what the sissy thing is.
- They like small stuff?
- Yeah, it's like a little cute little dollhouse thing.
You know?
- I'm Janine Spades and I've completed the training.
- That's a good name.
- You should have--
- I still did anonymous for the username.
- Are they accredited?
- Janine Spades.
- An accredited sissy.
- Do you think my credits would transfer
to the sissy factory?
- I've been in a macho factory for a little bit.
- Yeah, but I kinda wanna transfer.
Probably not a lot of things.
- Yeah, and here's, I think this is,
Yeah, this is the last one.
Hello, I just wanted to let,
I wanted to just let you know,
you've inspired me to write.
I really like the way you write and train us sissies.
Thank you for the content.
- Wow.
- That's so funny to me to go through this entire website.
It's like how to become an anal submissive slave.
And you're like, I should be a writer.
(laughing)
This makes me want to be an author.
- You know that novel I've been thinking of.
- Just a completely different type of hypnosis.
- Yeah, writer's hypnosis.
- Yeah.
- Speaking of hypnosis,
I feel like the plasma ball is kind of hypnotizing me.
Can you cut to the plasma ball really quick?
And I have something to say while the plasma ball is on.
- Go back this way?
- Yeah.
You will subscribe to the podcast about list Patreon.
You will give money to the podcast about list Patreon
where video episodes are being uploaded every week.
That's right, the video episodes are not just on the YouTube
they're actually also, they are on the Patreon
which has plenty of video episodes for you to look at.
It's only one so far, but soon there will be millions.
And you will want to subscribe there
because big things will be happening.
And at some point, maybe even behind the scenes things
of other things may be on the Patreon,
or even footage of things you couldn't even imagine
will be on there.
And on the Patreon, it's not uploaded to YouTube,
so we're able to look at porn live on episodes.
We can look at pornographic websites
and show a butt with a plug or a pussy with a finger.
- And you know what?
And I'm gonna say this right now.
If you subscribe to our $3,000, I think it's still called--
- It's Filipino Mr. Bean, I believe.
- You get to come to the studio and touch the plasma ball.
- Yes, look how fun the plasma ball is to touch.
- If you give us $3,000 a month,
you will be allowed to come in here,
touch this plasma ball as much as you want.
You can do this trick with it.
Wait, wait, hold on.
- Okay, do that, yeah.
Okay, now just make it look really hypnotic right now, okay?
You will give us money.
You will watch us YouTube.
You will listen to us audio.
You will look at our RSS feed.
You will like us all.
Okay, well, I think that about covers--
- That'll do it.
- Everything, right?
Yeah, so, whoa.
- What?
- All right, see you next week.
Did you turn into a-- - Bye!