Hey there guys, Caleb here. Basically, Jubio's making me record this. You need to go over
to, you need to go right now and pretty much you need to subscribe to the YouTube channel,
youtube.com/podcastaboutlist because we're going to be doing a lot more video kind of
stuff. There's going to be more videos on there and more some fun stuff on there pretty
soon and also Jubio, including Jubio, is going to be doing some singing videos. He's trying
to get on American Mexican Idol and Mexico's Got Talent and Mexican the
Mexican Shore so go check that out okay bye
had a chicken Caesar rap just now saying it I mean the all makes it sound like it
was maybe a bad move. No, I had a chicken Caesar wrap and guess what I had with it? I love
chicken Caesar wraps. Would you? I had Dr. Pepper. Wow. Look it, it's over there. I do,
I believe you. I can see it from here. I only see a white table. Let me go grab it real
quick. No, I think it's really. I think you should sit down. No, I think it's fine. No,
I really think it's. You want to grab it? Okay, he's going to grab it. He's grabbing
it. Oh, he got it. It's in his hands. Wow, he actually grabbed it. Wow, and he's grabbing
No, no, you can't bring if you bring that recorder over here. I will fucking ruin your life
He put it back down
He took it back down. You don't want me to play the recorder on there really don't I really really least favorite thing in this
Office right now, which is there's there's a few things
I feel like that that's in competition with for worst thing in the office
What are the ways that this I would I can give you at least a top to give me a top to top to our things
We own the recorder and that grabber. Oh
Oh, the grabber. Do we still have the grabber?
The grabber's somewhere in here.
I feel like maybe we hid the grabber.
I didn't do that.
I think you hid the grabber.
I did not touch the grabber.
I guarantee it's somewhere in here just under
all this stuff that doesn't matter.
Yeah.
All this random ass crap.
All the junk.
We just own a lot of junk, man.
I guess we probably shouldn't have started
letting our neighbors put their trash in here
Yeah. For a dollar a day.
We're not, that's not even that much money.
That's a tiny amount of money.
I thought, see, I thought that if we started letting the neighbors bring in the trash, then
we, you know.
We'd be able to maybe convince them to have sex with us.
No, I thought it would be our treasure.
Right.
Oh, because it's someone else's treasure.
One man.
Maybe this will be treasure.
Turns out it's a lot of banana peels.
Yeah.
It's mostly trash.
I don't think I've seen one piece of treasure.
There was one treasure.
What?
A golden coin.
Oh yeah, but that turned out to be chocolate.
Yeah.
And it also had banana peel juice all over it.
It was vintage though, and the foil was worth a lot of money.
Really?
Yeah, I actually went and sold the foil behind your guys' back.
Well that was your treasure.
I haven't found a single piece of fucking treasure.
All I'm getting is boxes.
Well here's the treasure for me.
What I'm saying is under all this trash somewhere there might be a piece of treasure that is
a grabber.
This is the only treasure I need.
Diet Dr. P.
What is your policy on if you-
I got two beverages right now.
I got a ghost energy and a diet Dr. P.
We're done with beverages.
I want to ask about, this is I think going to be probably something we, honestly, we could
talk about this for two hours. I'm not sure that we're going to, but we could. What is
the policy on food or beverage that you find on the street?
We've talked about this a million times before.
If it's candy and it's in the wrapper, if it's like a full...
We shouldn't even touch it.
Oh yeah, I just had one question because the other night we were out and there was a full
slice of pizza.
Okay, that's different.
What is that? Can you eat that?
Is it in the box?
It was in the box.
and you look at the cheese, is the cheese still warm?
- From look, I don't have heat vision.
- No, no, no, you know like when cheese pizza,
when cheese pizza starts getting cold
and the cheese goes back to it,
like it doesn't look like a liquid anymore.
- But I kinda like cold pizza, I'll fucking say it.
- Don't eat pizza, pizza's out of the question.
- It really, you know what, it depends on how hungry I am.
- You haven't eaten in days.
- Okay then, yeah, okay.
But if I need in days, I might eat a deer on the side of the road.
Good luck catching a deer.
You asshole.
On the side of the road.
You just disrespected hunters everywhere.
It's really easy to catch a deer.
Here's something.
Ready?
No.
Yeah, it's really easy.
Here's a double standard I've just realized, right?
You find a candy, Hershey bar in the wrapper on the ground, right?
Society says, don't eat that.
You find a Hershey bar in the wrapper on the ground at the
parade.
Society says run and grab that before someone else gets it.
Yeah, go grab that right now.
That's actually a very fair point.
Yeah, but if you think about it,
the variable is that a clown threw it.
So it leaves a clown plus candy.
If a normal guy drops a candy on the ground,
you shouldn't touch that.
A clown throws, a clown arcs it.
That's the other thing.
If a guy's walking a parade
and he just drops candy straight on the ground,
I don't think you're supposed to go get that.
If you take, what about a toss?
If you see it be tossed onto the ground,
I think you can get it. What about a pill that you find on the ground?
A pill, you take it.
Yeah, I think you can take it.
But what if it falls out of...
As long as it's still in the wrapper.
Yeah.
What if it falls out, what if it's a parade, what if it's a Super Bowl parade, it falls
out of Gronk's pocket?
Do you take that?
That means, yeah, you take that.
Or do you return it?
That's gonna be good.
Why don't you return it, though?
I think that pill might kill you.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Have you seen that video? It's like the older, it's like a woman driving like a Porsche Cayenne
or something and she's driving on three tires and like the fucking this the
bumper is scraped up her she's driving on the fucking like was it the bearing I
don't know car parts that's a skateboard part she's driving on the fucking thing
axle the axle she's driving on the axle and somebody that's also a skateboard
part I was so close you're a pro but she's driving on it and then somebody
pulls her over and is like, "You have to stop driving." You just bumped
into this guy and she looks at him and is just like, "I..." Somebody was helping me out
back there. No. She starts like making like lizard faces at him. I've never heard of this.
While she's leaving the car, they zoom in on her seat and you see like two
big-ass like Xanax or something. Like she laid them? No, they
- She fell out of her purse.
- Oh, okay.
- But she was like-- - They zoomed in on her seat,
she laid to it, that's what I think.
- The guy looks at her and is like,
like, "You're on painkillers or something,
"you can't be driving."
She goes, "No, I'm not."
(laughing)
- For those who didn't, who can't see, he went, "Bam."
- Yeah, I did a blim, blim, blim.
- He did a Yoshi, blim.
- Blim, blim, blim.
- It's a good video.
- Yeah.
I need to, I haven't been seeing all that many crazy people
as of late.
I really just, I don't see him on the tour.
- I just talked to a crazy guy at the store.
- Really?
- Yeah, I asked him where are the paper towels
and he said, "No English."
I was like, "What the fuck are you saying?"
- What are you, a fucking lunatic?
- That's not an answer to that question.
- Yeah.
- This guy's fucking, he can't understand.
- Crazy, yeah.
- He's out of his mind.
- He's in his own little world.
- Yeah, I know.
- He's making up crap.
- I see these people all the time listening to this music.
It doesn't make a goddamn lick of sense.
They're in their own little world.
They made their own music where they just go like,
It would be awesome to have, like to drive around and blast music that is in just a made-up
language.
Just have music that you made for yourself.
That's funny.
That's just in a language that you created and just translate every song you like into
an imaginary language.
Or just go around listening to the Simlish versions of...
Katy Perry last Friday night Simlish.
Cooler Than Me Simlish.
- Oh yeah.
- ♪ A sabba doo woppy, kaboowa boo wow ♪
- And you have mixtapes, you have a bunch of, you know.
- Yeah, have you heard this?
And then you put it in.
- Yeah.
- That's what you would say before you put it in.
- Right.
- Have you heard this?
♪ Rabby robite ♪
And then just put it in.
- Yeah.
- I always thought Seagor Roast was somebody
fucking up the pronunciation of Sugar Ray.
- I think we also talked about this.
- Oh fuck.
- Yeah, I think we--
- I think it's time to end the show.
- No.
- We, this is two episodes in a row,
I think that we've had a complete conversation.
- Yeah.
- That we've already had.
- It's been way more episodes than that.
I'm trying to be more vigilant about it.
That's the only, we do it constantly.
I'm trying to finally say,
we talked about this, don't talk about that.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
- What if we just--
- I think we need to break new ground.
- But isn't there--
- I think we need to do something
that changes the medium forever.
- Let's talk about a brand new topic.
- That's what I'm saying.
All right, how about something we never,
what about homework?
- Okay.
- I think we've talked about it.
- Okay, wait, what about the Grinch?
- I swear to God, we've also realized this
and have done this.
But we need to actually--
We have done this where we try to--
And it worked for a long time.
We didn't have to do this.
But we're back at it.
We have to find the next thing.
So we did poop, too.
Yeah, we did poop.
Man, that was the worst show ever.
What are we talking about?
Poop?
Candy?
Candy made of poop?
Yeah, but we have talked about candy.
We never talked about candy before.
It is a complete Groundhog Day situation.
Oh, it is a Groundhog Day.
Have you guys ever thought about what you
would do in that situation?
We haven't talked about this.
Have we? Maybe.
If you were in a Groundhog Day situation, you realize...
I'd probably kill 100 people and then myself.
Yeah, am I Bill Murray?
Yeah, you're the Bill Murray.
Then I'm committing every crime I can fucking think of.
Have we talked about this?
No, we haven't.
You're just... now you're just...
See, you know what you did to him?
You see what you fucking did to him, Cameron?
He thinks that... look at him.
I've never seen his eyes this big.
He's freaking out.
He'll get used to it.
He'll get used to the new paradigm.
Alright, we haven't talked about this.
Let's just keep talking about it.
Did he die?
Did Bill Murray die?
Yeah, he was executed by military tribunal. Yeah, exactly. Did we talk about this? Maybe
in 2019, it's been a couple years at this point. We've been doing this for four years now.
Groundhog Day though, I guess it's the "which crimes are you like, even if I could do that,
I wouldn't do it." Probably raping, I wouldn't do that. He was baiting you into saying that.
- Yeah, this guy admitted.
- Now there's a sound bite of you saying that word.
- Yep, admitting he would never do it.
(laughing)
- Oh, we got you so good.
- He doesn't understand how audio editing works nowadays.
They can remove words from sentences and change contexts.
- Okay, yeah, wait, wait.
I need to set that up.
- Which crime would you wanna do first?
- And then we can cut to that.
That'll be really easy.
- Yep, perfect.
- Yeah, I guess that one's a big one I probably wouldn't do.
- Probably, or wouldn't do.
- Probably not.
(laughing)
- Probably wouldn't do.
I wouldn't do that one.
I wouldn't do that one. I don't think I would kill anybody.
I don't think I would eliminate the world.
I think I would kill like...
The thing is also...
I think I would kill like a bunch of small animals, right?
I'd kill a bunch of little animals.
Yeah.
And then I would start wetting my bed a lot.
Mm-hmm.
Because it's, you know, I'm gonna wake up with clean sheets tomorrow.
That's a really good... You can shit your... You never have to wipe again.
Exactly. I'm gonna wake up...
Bill Murray's not waiting that long.
Is it worth waiting 24 hours though?
He's not wasting his time every day.
I can either wipe my butt now or wait 10 hours and not have to.
Also does he have to... I don't remember the rules of the movie. Does he have to go to sleep?
He has to go to sleep or get killed and then he wakes up in that hotel room.
I've never seen the movie.
But the way he solves it is he helps somebody find true love or something or realizes true love.
That doesn't make any sense.
I thought he kills the groundhog, not chicken.
chicken he kills himself a bunch of time is he the groundhog I never understood
this movie he's uh he's there what he's not name he's not a news reporter
groundhog okay he's there to be a news but is his name like hog like David hog
or something no his name is Bill hog bill hog bill hog Murray begins bill hog
Murray Gaines I don't he's a and he's a dwarf I don't think I would I don't
think I would kill anybody I don't think I would either I would kill myself I
I don't want to hurt my, I don't want to hurt.
- So what would you do?
- I honestly would just probably just look at my phone.
(laughing)
Pretty much every day.
- I'd go somewhere probably.
- Or I'd take that, you know what I'd do?
I would know, even if I found out,
oh I gotta give this bitch a kiss to win.
I would still probably do a like,
Duolingo lesson a day for like five years.
Learn everything I possibly could.
- Every morning you spend.
- You remember the next day.
- Yeah, I'm learning Japanese.
- First of all, you gather all human knowledge.
That's a gimme.
Also, every day, you spend all of your money in the morning
on like the best food ever, or a day trip.
And you can--
- Your bank account's gonna reset.
- Exactly, you can spend all the money you have every day
to do something that will not go away,
that's like going to a roller coaster.
- He'll remember the next, he remembers everything.
- I'd get a MasterClass subscription.
- Yeah.
- Judd Apatow MasterClass.
I'd learn how to write the funniest fucking movie ever.
- I would do that.
- Yeah, I'd do the Steve Martin one,
learn how to do stand-up too. Yeah. Have you seen that the news report that came out? No.
The news report? Why am I saying it like that? It was a fucking Rhett and Link
interview with Seth Green. That news report that came out? Yeah, from the news.
A Rhett and Link interview. It's a Rhett and Link interview with Seth Green where Seth
Green is like, "When I was a kid, I wouldn't give Bill Murray my seat, so he picked me up
by my ankles and shook me over the trash and said, 'This trash goes in the trash!'"
That's funny.
That is one of the funniest things.
That's a joke you can do with kids.
Yeah, was he pretending it was traumatizing?
Picking a kid up by the- Yeah.
Oh, what a bitch.
I mean, maybe if Bill Murray did it, I wouldn't like it.
I'd also-
I'd be like, "That's dope."
I definitely feel like maybe I brought- There was a substitute gym teacher in my school who
used to do that. He used to pick kids up by the ankle and shake them around. That was like his thing.
That shouldn't be allowed. It definitely shouldn't. I would rather...
I know, but that's what I'm saying. I didn't like that and I didn't want that to happen to me. Wait, it happened to you?
No. Oh. You dodged it? I stayed away from him. Do you know anybody
who got shook? Yeah, like everybody. Everybody but you got shook?
He was like, he was, you know... He was a tall kid. I mean, look at him.
I think even a scary freak like that who shakes kids upside
down knows that there's one kid that if you do it, that kid will like,
we'll bring the whole operation down.
I feel like I would have cried and I probably would have like,
none where I was. I don't know, but I was a shy kid. You know what I mean?
I was a shy, quiet kid. And I feel like you either,
you pick the shy quiet kid up by the like, and it's,
you're either getting killed in 15 years or, uh,
you're going to jail for molesting children. Yeah.
I had a PE teacher made me do a pull up. I never forgave that bitch.
Amanda fucking would love to put a bullet in her head.
- The worst thing you can be as a teacher,
like if you're a gym, the worst--
- The worst thing you can be is a teacher.
- That's it, I'll say that much.
- But like the worst attribute you can have,
like if you're a creepy teacher,
the worst one you can be is gym, like a gym teacher.
- Yeah. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- But like a creepy math teacher, it's just like, yeah.
- That's a math nerd. - He likes math.
- Yeah. - Yeah, he's obviously--
- A gym teacher likes children's fitness.
- See, I wanted to-- - Exactly.
- I had the wrong kind of gym teachers all,
I never had I wanted like all my becoming a gym teacher because like oh my God, I
fucking love wiffle ball.
Yeah, what job can I get where I can play with my favorite watch people play
with a ball and you just giving way too in-depth notes on the football technique
and all of my gym.
Oh my my PE teachers in school were fat or like really short or lesbian.
Yeah, yeah, I had a lot of hot lesbian and I was like dude this sucks.
I want like a Rob Riggle.
I know.
(laughing)
I want Rob Riggle with a whistle
and his shorts are too small.
I had an Australian gym teacher.
I had a heavy Boston accent lesbian gym teacher.
I had another, there was like two gym teachers I remember.
Like the only one who wasn't,
the two who weren't fat were the Australian guy.
You met an Aussie that young?
Yeah. Holy.
Mr. Levis.
Mr. Levis?
Levis, Mr. Levis and he said, "Cow cow puffs like me."
(laughing)
- He was also a health teacher.
- He said, "Do not eat cocoa puffs."
- Do not eat cocoa puffs.
- Do not eat, whatever you do, do not eat cocoa puffs.
- Cocoa puffs.
- The other one was--
- That's just what they call it over there.
He lost the accent, but that's just the name of it.
- Cow-er-puff.
- The other gym teacher was in first grade
and it called him Tiny Tony.
- Tiny Tony.
(laughing)
He's like a regular at my mom's restaurant.
I shouldn't talk about it.
No.
[LAUGHTER]
Talk about-- do they still call him Tiny Tony?
No, but I think we called him Tiny Tony behind his back.
How tiny was Tony?
He was probably like 5'7".
It's not that short.
It's not short.
It's just--
Tiny Tony.
It's just when you're a kid, you--
You have to take any opportunity you can
to call someone Tiny Tony.
Yeah.
If someone's name is Tony, and they're even a little bit short,
they have to be Tiny Tony.
Yeah, you're one letter off, bud.
You're going to be Tiny Tony.
Yeah, I mean, that's like-- but tiny, really, I'm thinking like 4'11".
He's a nice guy.
I don't even know why I call him that.
Tiny Tony because he's small.
He was just my gym teacher and I was just like,
I don't want to go to gym.
Tiny ass Tony.
Tiny Tony.
Good guy.
They're all good guys.
I disagree.
Teachers?
I did have a fat gym teacher in second grade
who taught us scarf juggling.
And I've definitely talked about it.
Probably taught you how to scarf down food, too, a fat guy.
Yeah.
He was legally blind and he rode to school on a bike.
and he also had like a carriage that he like dragged his kids.
- There were these three blind kids who went to my school.
And we always saw how they ran, yeah.
- Did they stick together?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- You're getting quiet 'cause it's true.
- They were little mice.
- No.
- I was doing three blind mice.
- No, it's true.
It's true.
You said you had three blind kids at your school, didn't you?
- Yeah, and we always saw how they ran.
Really? Yeah. And how they run. And we saw how they ran. And they stuck together?
Did the farmer catch it? Yes. With the carving knife? Yeah.
I didn't ever, you know, I was, it was devastating. I'll say it. It was fucking devastating.
When the farmer caught you with the carving knife?
No. When I found out that blind people don't just see black, that devastated me, bro.
I usually, that makes you, I feel like that makes you go, whoa, like a high guy.
That just, I was devastated. I always assumed. Blind people see like shapes.
I mooned so many blind people.
Well not you.
Some blind people can't see at all though, right?
Very few.
But legally blind doesn't mean you're actually blind.
Yeah, but I thought just any time I met a blind person,
anyone whose eyes went the wrong way,
I was like,
"Okay, I'm going to be showing this guy a fucking picture of my balls."
Yeah.
And telling him it's the weather.
I had a friend who was legally deaf.
Yeah?
Like a rapper.
I think we all knew her. I just won't talk about it.
Okay, okay. Rather odd. I actually had a friend who couldn't taste or touch or smell or see or hear.
I had a friend who was completely made up in my head.
I had a buddy, my friend was made up and also he was a rock.
I had a friend who was a nose, just a nose.
Really? Yeah, he fell off my other friend.
Wow.
He was surgically removed from my other friend.
- Yeah, but he was chill.
- Yeah.
- He didn't do much.
- Could he see or hear?
- He couldn't do anything.
- Could he smell?
- No, his name was Nose too.
His name was Devin's Nose.
- He couldn't smell?
- He couldn't smell 'cause he have to,
something has to be, he could smell for somebody else.
- Do you remember that video?
- Yeah.
- The blind guy on the French Voice
and he sings "Lose Yourself"?
- Yeah.
- Oh, speaking of French, I also was devastated
when I met my first French person.
It was the first person from another country I'd ever met
and he stayed with me.
he's like some missionary guy. I'd be devastated too. He was a missionary and I was like dude,
you did missionary with me? He's sitting there, he's sitting there. Yeah, he's a little older
than me. I had to give up my... He eats a snail in your house? You had to give it up to him
and he did missionary with you? Alright, let me... Yes, yes, he fucked me and I was like
devastated. As I said, I was devastated when I met my first Frenchman. No, I had never
met him before, I've never met a person from another country before. I mean, except for
like I guess like Peru but then I he was like the first European I know I know
you might have that's just a funny thing to say I guess Peru but I so he was a
missionary or some shit or his parents were and he had to stay at my in my room
for like a week and so I had to sleep on the couch and I thought that I was gonna
have like a new French best friend and he fucking he went he spent four minutes
with me decided I sucked so much ass that he made his mom driving to GameStop he
bought 2k and then came back just played it on my Xbox a whole week never talked
to me bastard wait why was he there he's when parents were in town doing something
for some church and they're staying with us well he came to and he's from France
he's from France and he just played 2k and I would come in I'd be like do you
wanna do you want to look at my book right and he'd go no no no no I want to
I find the play, I find the play, I flip on James.
And then he was always dunking.
And then he made me, he made himself in 2K,
he made me in 2K.
And he hacked the game or something,
made himself fuck my character in the game to death.
To death. To death.
There was some little French-Canadian kid,
one of my mom's co-worker. Some low-class
French-Canadian kid.
My mom's co-worker, it was like her kid,
and we had to hang out with him one time.
and he was the most annoying person I've ever met.
- Francophile?
- What?
- He's a francophile.
- It's getting near.
- No, he's French Canadian.
- It's getting near Halloween.
- No, not, what do they call that?
Francophone.
- Francophone.
- Francophone, right?
- Yeah.
- Francophile is you like the disaster artist or whatever.
- Francophile.
- Francophile's monster is completely different.
- Francophile is what he was doing
with his damn students at NYU.
Those 17 year old kids who were in his acting class.
- He was speaking French to them?
- He was being a francophile?
Franco is being a file. Oh, he was being a file over there. Yeah. Yeah, he's being a complete file. Uh-huh - 24 year olds
I thought it was NYU high that's still not right though. Yeah, I agree. Yeah, it's still not right to 24
It's still not right to be James Franco. Yeah, it's not like him
I think a lot of these men don't understand about this Leonardo DiCaprio thing. Yeah
a child do you guys ever watch the the
the
Planet of the Apes reboot trilogy. Yeah
the one with
Walbert is the one from 2001 there's the trilogy. Oh the new one. Yeah, I've seen the first one
So how like the first one is like James Franco like raises
Caesar Caesar the chimp yeah, and then Caesar like it's like a knowledge virus or whatever
He becomes super smart and he eventually like goes to war with the humans and the other movies, and it's so funny
It's like all it is all James Franco's fault. He's destroyed
I really like this chimp and then just like years later just the chimps are
declaring war on humankind and exterminating the planet. I love the original like five
those movies are so good. The reboot trilogy was really good too. I gotta see the reboot trilogy but the
original I did I got I got the originals on blu-ray yeah come over nice I've um
what's it that the third one it's like planet of the apes and then beneath the
planet of the apes then the third one which is like is that escape I think it's
escape, escape it's like they somehow go back in time to the 70s or whatever and
then they're like treated as like the biggest celebrities in the world.
The monkeys are? Yeah, they're like hey in the future, we're gonna take over.
The second one is so sick with the mutant, the underground mutants, you know
like the crucified apes and stuff. I do often think like if I gave Phil like a
a gun and the ability to think better and I put it at my head I wonder if he'd
pull the trigger cuz they'd be like well I don't need this guy yeah or if he
loves me you know right do you think you'd eat you if you died he would eat
me I've come to terms with the fact that and not all dogs will do this if I
pretend to be asleep for too long he'll eat me he will start eating yeah yeah
he will start trying to rip my flesh off.
- Yeah, that's okay. - I think,
maybe try to be stinkier.
- Yeah. - I've been trying my hardest.
- No, what are you talking about?
Dogs love it when stuff is stinky.
- He tried to lick the poop off my ass the other day.
I was sitting on-- - I was worried
that my cable would go and--
- I was wiping my ass.
What are you doing?
I was wiping my ass and he resumed into the bathroom
and tried to eat the poop off of,
like I was like, you know, I hiked my right ass cheek up
so I could put my hand under.
- Yeah. - And he like tried
to shove his mouth in there and lick the poop off me.
- I guess dogs really do learn from their owners.
- Dogs, no.
(laughing)
- Who, how would I do that?
- See, that's one of those things where it's like,
you know, it's funny,
dogs always seem to look like their owners
and it's Phil eating poop and Kaleb just has a big
brown ring around his mouth.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I don't eat, I don't actually eat poop though.
- I think, you know, it would just be a funny scenario
for a joke or for a real photo that was taken recently.
- If Moe ever gained like,
- Sentience?
I think that I would at least be able to reason with him to stop trying to eat my hand.
He's going crazy.
I am kind of worried that if I leave the house for too long, my chocobo is going to run wild and rip up the couch.
And it's true. Your chocobo sucks.
Yeah, he kind of has a bad temperament.
It's not cool for you to say that. I can kind of say it, I guess.
I don't want you to kind of bad mouth my chocobo because I do love him.
I he talks shit about my animal every pet that I've ever owned you just don't like my chocobo cuz I named him Patrick
Yeah, I don't I don't like that either
All right, what's wrong with it? I think it's a cute name for a chocobo. It's not a cute name for a chocobo
It's great. It's a fucking green one. That's normal. It's not a good one. It's not green cuz it's sick
It's just green on it's sick. You feed it chocolate. You're thinking of my Yoshi whose name is Caleb
Okay
It's from Final Fantasy, it's the bird that you ride
And this is a Pokemon. No, this final fantasy Chocobo. It looks like stupid. Are you completely daft?
I'm a don't you ever bloody say that to me again?
You knots don't you? What are the what are the pets called in Club Penguin?
Penguins, what are the pets the little ones?
I think they're penguins a lot of shit the little the hairy hair balls turds. I never what are they called?
I never played like Club Penguin. I never played it either. I never played
Like middle school or runescape. Yeah, what are those called puffles? I want one of those yeah, yeah until I never did
It's into your in your food
I'll just hit it
(laughing)
- Just like any other pet.
Just smack it if it does the wrong thing.
- Smack it on the nose.
(laughing)
- Imagine what kind of sick freak in the Club Penguin,
like, in the Club Penguin universe
would put peanut butter on his penis
and let a puffle lick it off.
- I don't think puffles--
- A dog maybe, okay, a dog I get it.
- A dog I understand. - It's got four legs.
- Yeah, that's enough.
- But a puffle, that thing is small.
- A puffle is just a--
- A puffle is inhuman.
- It's a goddamn ball, it's barely human at all.
- Do you guys, you get like, you see like the,
like people being like nostalgic about like Club Penguin
or something that you didn't like do
as a child specifically.
- That's every day with you guys.
- Yeah, well it's like a universal experience.
And then you just get so annoyed by it
because you were like, yeah, but when I was a kid,
that was like baby shit.
- That's how I feel about Pop Tropica and Homestar Runner.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I never knew nothing about those.
- And then people are like insanely nostalgic about it
and you're just like, I don't, shut up about this.
- And I go, buddy, I was on the computer,
I was looking at pornography.
I'm actually, I handle it with grace and I don't even care.
It doesn't bother me when people talk about stuff I didn't do.
But what if somebody...
Make it a conversation about something I know about.
Do you care if people brag though?
I like when people brag.
Oh, I have millions.
Like, does that bother you?
You have a million?
No, because I have more.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
You might be a special case then.
I have millions at least.
Maybe if someone said they had trillions, I'm not going to say I have more than that.
If somebody says...
But I do have billions.
I mean, I shouldn't say that.
is
you're saying something that's about Myra Hindley? It's a Myra Hindley joke?
I don't know who Myra Hindley is.
Okay, first of all, I don't know what a
Hindley is and I don't know where you got yours but I don't have one either.
There's a Smith song about it. Oh okay, yeah, wrong crowd.
And there's a Brass Eye episode. What about me and this guy?
Brass Eye!
Brass I rightly is it this door and she's buying ropes to tie up a child
Brass I don't brass eyes in God. What's making a hobbits to brass eyes?
Yeah, the big eye on the tower
I never understood why his eye is up there and where's the rest of his body they explain that in the new Amazon show
And they're gonna say yeah, that's what I like actually Patrick is fucking explanations
That's they said on instead of fucking mysteries of God's universe. I like the new they're gonna reveal who Sauron is in
Season two and he's gonna be exactly evil like Walter White and Tony Soprano you sour on you soured on my balls
You put your sour you you soured on this ghost energy warheads
Which is a can of flavor drink real guys look speaking of ghosts speaking of candy notes stop
I have a whole of it, and I just let me let me do let me handle a segue here, okay?
You hit my chin and my mic and I want to have a higher place just to
See I chipped his tooth look no your tooth got shit. He chipped my teeth
Okay, so now I'm completely thrown off and the episode's over.
Ghost Candy.
Speaking of ghosts, you know, it's Halloween month.
It's October.
Alright?
We've done, we did ghosts.
We did a scary story.
We did jump scares!
Oh, fuck you man.
We did, we did.
We're supposed to have 21.
What episode is this?
I think we did soda.
That's kind of a Halloween thing maybe.
You drink soda with your candy.
There's one huge Halloween thing that we've been missing out on that I've found an important
database to handle here, and that's candy.
So today I found this blog called Candy Fest Gummyville,
and they have an article here called
Top 50 Candies Everyone Needs to Try,
and this is under the category Candy World.
And I want you guys to take a look at the picture
of the person who runs Candy Fest Gummyville,
and I just wanna read you here.
(laughing)
Can you scroll up a little bit there so I can read?
White Keegan Michael Key.
But he's in a gummy candy sweatshirt and he says,
I'm obsessed with candy.
You don't have to look far to see my love fest with a sugary
treat of started to engulf my life.
Once I gave up candy for a month and I almost cried when I
found a gummy bear on the floor.
I accidentally dropped days before behind the kitchen table.
It was as hard as rock but tempted me with his tiny gummy
face his super tasty tiny pineapple gummy face.
So here I am starting a candy block.
I wanted to kick it off with a Cleveland Indians logo made out of Skittles to showcase their
2016 championship, but obviously I had to switch my plans.
Thanks Cubs.
Rolls Eyes.
Let's go Cubs.
But I couldn't decide on just one topic.
So you get 50.
Here's my list of 50 candies I think everyone needs to try, in no particular order.
And who knows, maybe it'll inspire you to turn into a gummy-loving, sweet-obsessed,
candy-gushing maniac too.
#High5.
I remember that World Series.
It was extra endings because of, there was extra endings.
And like a two hour rain delay.
It was a great World Series.
It was a great night.
Yeah, I was in community college and this kid was running around in like the
dorms that we stayed in, this kid was running around in his underwear and then
I went and hung out with him in his room and he was so drunk he told his
friend to punch him in the kidney as hard as he could and I got a video of it.
Really? Did he piss blood? He punched him in the kidney so hard and then he
passed out on the floor. Go Cubs! That's sick. Yeah I also I don't want to go into
what if we pause right now and go buy all of this candy? Okay we just did that.
All right we're back. That's just a good idea. So we'll just taste test each of
these as we get on the list. I don't eat candy man come on I'm not gonna eat
fucking 50 candies. It's fucking October. I'm not gonna eat 50 candies. It's fucking candytober. You eat
candy you do I hate you do my dentist tells me this knock it off but Andy's
good AF I don't care whether you eat candy in general or not we're doing a
candy episode today and you're gonna try candy I'm don't you all right so you
don't have to eat them you can just try them and spit them out to a bucket okay
and then he'll have a he'll eat all the chewed up stuff I'll put it in a blender
yeah number one is M&Ms mm-hmm which the other day I found out you can if you're
somebody is sharing your location with you, you can notify them whenever you go
to like a specific location, it'll like give like a notification. Set it up so
that my dad gets a notification whenever I go to the M&M store. So he can get like
send you an order basically? Yeah. Yeah. It's like if I'm ever on 1600 Broadway
it's like you're you're you will get a notification. Dude I will say last time I went to the M&M
store I got a fuck ton of M&M's and they were I was getting the key lime pie I was
like getting the other flavors what did they just say earlier they're pretty
good man what I don't it was like a year and a half ago probably the only time I
ate candy that's the only time yeah last time I guess that's probably the only
time you ever ate candy yeah but let's see there's a bunch here
skittles okay so kind of starting kind of kind of like he's a yeah he just was
thinking about hard shells. Taste the rainbow and tropical orchard spooky
lurking lemon anyone? And more flavors. I remember lurking lemon. I don't remember
lurking lemon. I don't either. I remember Liz lemon. He knows that he knows a
secret Skittles flavor. You're lying that you know exactly what it is. Did you
know there was a huge backlash when they switched from lime Skittles to sour
apple Skittles? Apparently the lime and lemon were too similar to some. I was in
favor for the switch. Sour apple for life with a Y instead of an I. I uh yeah I
I didn't even know that they switched the flavors
until there was all those commercials
where he's just talking about that bullshit.
- Right, so for this right here,
before we get to this one,
I do wanna take a little sidebar here.
Juli, if you go to the next tab,
I just wanna show you a little of this guy's background,
just so you understand, all the pictures on this list.
I wanna read you this guy's Instagram bio,
Candy Fest Gummyville.
Life is better in color.
All photos I snap.
Candy and gummy lover.
So he's a candy photographer.
- And Lancaster PA.
- Yeah, I wasn't gonna say where he lives,
so it's all good.
- Well, if anyone can find his Instagram, it's right there.
- So he just takes pictures of candy?
- Right, but it's kind of like you'd rather
to say it directly to a bunch of people.
He's a candy photographer.
- This guy is awesome.
- He does a pretty fucking damn good job.
- Candy lover, it's incredible.
Candy lover and gummy addict and sugar king.
Born and raised in PA, sharing photos of my fave treats.
- Oh my god.
- He's a, look at this.
- Oh wow.
- He does professional candy photography.
So I'm pretty sure all of the pictures
on this list that we're reading, he took.
- These pictures look fucking incredible.
- I thought these were all stock photos.
- They look like stock photos of--
- They're so good. - Damn.
- A lover of all things candy,
especially gummies and sour treats.
- He's so talented.
- He's extremely talented. - Candy has gummy though.
- But the reason I bring that up now
is because this next one, the picture.
- Oh, that's him with a peach ring.
- That's him holding up a peach ring.
And he looks terrifying like Gollum.
- Yeah, it does look like Gollum holding the one ring.
- He does not, he's not a person
who should ever be out of focus.
- Yeah, I agree. - He looks like
the insidious demon when he's out of focus.
- He looks a little bit like Epic Meal Time.
but it was the smallest candy meal of all time.
- He's the spin-off, Epic Treats Time.
- Having one single piece.
- I don't know, I like this guy now.
- This guy's cool, I like him too.
- I called him White Key, Michael Key.
I think he's actually--
- You think that's an insult, okay.
Yeah, you're white.
- Yeah.
- You think that's an insult, okay.
- If he had said he looks like Keegan-Michael Key,
you'd be like, yes he does, that's awesome.
- Yeah.
- But if you say white, it's like, ugh.
- What's wrong with being white?
- There's a lot of things wrong with being white.
There's a lot of stuff wrong with being white.
you say that? Yeah, why would you say what's wrong with being white? What do you mean?
Patrick, why'd you say that? Juvio, get off the white pride Wikipedia entry. You're
gonna start saying some weird crap if you read that. Number four, gummy bears. The
classic gummy delicacy, seriously, Haribo is the top-notch kind. Even come in super
tiny form, bottom right pick, but Albanese from Indiana, USA are also amazing.
- Albanese are, Albanese gummy bears are so good.
- Yeah.
- Those are, I used to be, I used to be a big Haribo ho,
but now I've been Albanese freak.
- I don't know if I've ever had them.
- All right, I'm an Albanese pleaser.
Albanese pleaser.
- Now we say Albanese pleaser.
- Albanese or Scrooge is my name.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Albanese or Scrooge.
I've never even heard of Albanese gummy bears.
- Albanese gummy, if you can find them,
I usually see them at like, they're like the TJ Maxx snacks.
I usually see them at nonsense stores.
You know like the TJ Maxx snacks that you can find
that are like, it's like--
Yeah, stuff that you can get when you check out?
These are like a dark chocolate pretzel.
Oh, yeah.
Like MILF snacks.
I do know that.
Yeah, they're like Trader Joe's type thing.
Trader Joe's candy.
Trader Joe's is like one rung below--
MILF chow, that's what you're talking about.
Yeah, one rung below MILF chow.
Yeah, MILF chow.
Which are all of the snacks at TJ Maxx
that are like truffle potato chips.
- It's dark chocolate stuff for milfs to chow on.
- Yeah, like a dove.
- Yeah. - What are you signing?
- Go back to the list, Julio.
- Yeah, what are you doing?
- You have to stay on that. - Don't buy it.
- You have to stay on the-- - Chicken feet.
- They taste like heaven blended with cherry lemonade.
Seriously, so good.
- I agree, those look great. - Look at these.
- Yeah, those look--
- I don't like them against the green background.
- No, but those do look tasty.
- I've never heard of those before.
- God damn it, dude.
But there must try I'm straight up I've got a sweet tooth like this guy and this list is making my mouth water
Some of these candies I really want
All right, let me put my finger in your mouth to check it's watering
Number six is airheads, but what actually is the mystery flavor? That's a good question. I thought it was just random
No, the mystery flavor of that's the lollipops. That's what yeah, yeah like dum-dums. Yeah, dum-dums. I'm looking at you right now
Yeah, I'm looking at I'm between two dum-dums right now. Yeah, I'm between two dum-dums, too
What do you you're there's you are the right dum-dum? I'm between two dum-dums, buddy, okay?
We're look actually you guys are stupid because you don't realize the earth goes all the way around
I've really I really so actually right now Patrick is behind me. No. He's not yeah
He is if you go all the way that way he's straight up behind me. That is true. That's kind of scary
Yeah, oh my god. He's blue you blew my mind. He is behind you technically if he looks that way
He's looking at your back because of the round don't look at my back. What do you say stop?
He's looking at my dog and trying to lick on it get it's way too far away to look in that direction
You know how big his tongue is what have you measured it gay? Yep? I measured it
Hershey's kiss and yeah, you know what the cherry quartz the ones are to die for I haven't had those in so long read this
this paragraph here. Also, one time my friend dressed up as a Hershey's Kiss at
Hershey's Park. Oh, summer job memories in high school and was rolled down a hill by a Kiss.
I think about it each time I eat one. Always hilarious. I also love that this guy worked at
Hershey Park in high school. He's been on, he's been, Candy has been his life, his entire life.
Look, I used to think the Candyman was a horror character. Now I think that the Candyman
is an awesome, is an awesome guy. I love this guy. This guy's awesome.
Yeah.
Um, number eight is Wilbur Buds.
These sound crazy.
Wilbur Buds.
Hershey gets all the love in PA, but Wilbur Buds are arguably even better.
Try these ASAP.
Plus, if you ever visit Lilitz, PA, a super cool-
Lititz.
Come on, man.
Super cool town.
They have a new store.
Rage comics vibe.
Yeah.
My girlfriend showing me Lititz.
Kit Kats.
What is a Wilbur Bud?
That seems like a euphemism for something on a pig.
That's uh, this is what...
Wilbur?
Oh, never mind.
I was gonna say this is what Wilfred Brimley ate that gave him diabetes, but then I remembered
his name is Wilford and not Wilbur.
Wilfred Bud.
Wilfred, yeah.
If it was a Wilfred Bud, hey, I would have had to...
You're thinking of Wilfred's...
I would have had a whole lot of a joke.
You're thinking of Wilfred's Bane.
Ah, yeah.
Wilfred's Bane, which is still sugar.
Number nine is Kit Kats.
There's something special about this candy.
Side note, it was my favorite candy bar to impersonate at Hershey Park.
Again, summer job at its finest.
Kit Kats in America.
This guy also is so into candy that when he dresses up as candy, it's not dressing up
as it, it's impersonating it.
He's like doing a Michael Jackson tribute show.
Almost.
God damn, he doesn't just look like a Kit Kat, he fucking moves like one.
Look at that, he's got everything right down to his...
Look, he just gave that guy a break.
Oh my God, he's snapping off left and right.
This guy goes up to people dressed as candy and does Stolen Valor stuff too.
(laughter)
- What flavor are you?
What factory were you made in?
- Number 10 is nerds, and I'm between two nerds.
- I'm between two nerds too.
- We are--
- Hey look, if--
- I actually am between a nerd,
this guy has a theory about the earth.
- If you're around me, nerds are in the vicinity.
Classic.
- I don't get it.
- That Nick Cannon video.
- Oh yeah.
- I consider myself to be a member of the Wonka family.
And when you think about the meaning of the word nerds,
That's a perfect video.
It's a really good video.
Remember when you get those little boxes with two flavors
and you just dump them in your mouth,
but then your spit would make the box all wonky?
And you'd be all, it's falling apart
and nerds are falling into the cracks.
Hashtag candy props.
I know exactly what he's talking about.
You get your spit all over the nerds box?
What the fuck are you talking about?
You put the fucking nerds box like this
and you're trying to like shake it in.
And your spit shoots up like a fountain into the box.
What the hell are you two talking about?
No, I don't understand.
No, these two.
The computer and him.
Look, if you were a real candy fan, you'd know.
You just pour them, you didn't pour them into your hands?
You were pouring them directly into your mouth?
Like a fucking...
Pouring them directly into the mouth because I got the two...
You're feeding yourself like a fucking fish?
Yeah.
Put it in your, just put it in your hand.
Hey, hey.
The thing about being a candy fan is sometimes you get to pretend that you're a different
animal and you're eating the candy like it's like fish food.
I don't think I would ever pour the nerds directly into my mouth.
This is how to eat them.
This is a video on how to eat nerds.
See, this is what I do.
This is what you would do. You'd chug it like a Gatorade.
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
Pour it in your hand.
Shake it like a rich guy and like pop it.
Yes. That's how you're supposed to eat it.
Next is Reese's.
I do like Reese's.
Reese's Pieces, Reese's Cups.
Nut-rageous. Get in my belly.
Did you see these new Reese's Pieces?
Did you see these new Reese's Pieces
stuff comes yet? Also, it's Reese's Pieces, not PCs.
Well, he wrote it as, "It's Reese's PCs, not PCs."
Oh yeah, and honestly, Reese's Sticks are probably the most underrated Reese's products.
They're amazing.
Oh yeah, Reese's Sticks existed.
I've never heard of a Reese's Stick.
Those are so good.
You really are a candy guy.
Yeah.
This is fucking crazy. You know all these candies, man.
Number 12 is Ring Pops.
The only one I did know was Wilbur Buds.
Yeah.
And I will be trying them.
them. Ring pop says candy bling check. Number 13 is a whirly pop this is I don't know
this one oh yeah I do what am I talking about I know this one. He took a photo again he
decided to insert himself. He looks so he's where he looks like he's wearing
the Robert Pattinson Batman makeup. I think he's allowed to insert himself
with the candy. Oh 100% so I just wish he would he would not make that face. This
is the one that's just a face of excitement. This is one of those big
spiral lollipops. That's the face of a podling being drained of energy in the dark crystal.
That's so mean. This is one of those lollipops that gets stolen from babies. But I don't know
why anyone would ever want to eat one of these. No, they're pretty gross. They're the worst candy.
Yeah, they're really bad. But you do have to try it. These are the ones you must try. These are
not as favorites, these are must tries. And I will say, even though these suck, you should have one
once in your life. Hey, I sucked on one and I hated it. I feel like these always get stolen out of
of your hands. This is also this is the one that you learn instantly as a kid.
You see, I think you see it in the candy store and you go, Oh my God, I want that.
Yeah, you get it once you lick it. You're like, this is disgusting and you're
gonna never get it again in the cartoons. Yeah, yeah, the TV doesn't. Yeah,
tastes like I'm gonna be like, Hey, I'm gonna feel exactly like a kid. Kids. A
kid can jump off the roof 10 times and not and get hurt every time and still do
it. But you get one one whirly pop and you will never get it again. Yeah,
that's true yeah number 14 is Smarties the white ones are so good and I have no
idea why I want all of the white ones hook me up Smarties you know in Canada
Smarties are chocolate he's actually right the white the don't wait for
anything he's back Juvia's back on the white pride with it off that page it's a
different that's a different it has nothing to do with Smarties yeah and I'll
say those guys yeah yeah I'll say those white pride not dumb dumb they're
definitely no Smarties in that bunch are quite a bit of dummies
Jolly Ranchers. This guy is right though, the white Smarties are the only good ones. I love
Smarties. I think Smarties are at top tier candy. Nah, just only the white ones. I don't
really care what you have to say about candy. I don't know if they're top tier candy. I
really, really like Smarties. Yeah, you don't care what he has to say, but trust me, you
come to me with that shit. And what? I'm gonna tell you, I'm gonna put you in your place.
Put me in what place? I'm the candy man. Alright, I'm gonna see a debate on Smarties. I think
they're really tasty and I like their texture. You like their texture? Hey buddy
how about you go eat a piece of sidewalk chalk? Because it doesn't taste like
Smarties. Okay he counterpointed now you need to... What if they made sidewalk
chalk taste like Smarties? Probably eat it. I've been bested.
I've been bested in the field of intellectual debate. That's fucking incredible. I cannot
believe you guys squashed that. Number 15 Jolly Ranchers. I love a rancher.
Yeah, I haven't met church. I just fucking pop them in I pop for at a time watermelon Jolly Rancher
Did you know that these are the most popular candies out there always a top-seller and for good reason number 16 zero zero
I
Fucking hate
Rolls when I live in when I lived in Boston I
Lived like four blocks away from a Tootsie Roll factory so every day. I would what yeah
So I was in Cambridge as a Tootsie Roll factory. You never told me that
Why would it matter to you? Patrick, I live four blocks away from the Tootsie Roll factory just so you know
They before you come over
You can't they don't do tours and actually they have like 16 armed guards
They don't do tours or anything
But if you if you save all the Tootsie Rub if you find the Native American with the star
If you save all of those and you give them to them
I think they give you like a t-shirt, and I had a bunch of them
What the fuck are you talking about Native American with a star on the tootsie roll wrapper?
I know what he's talking about. I've never heard of this pop rapper. Yeah, I know that I tootsie pop
I didn't know he's talking about and if you save up and I always wanted this shirt if you saved up
20 dum-dum wrappers, and you like sent them in
You got a t-shirt with the dum-dum logo on it, and it's a little it's a little pop guy listen. I
Didn't do that because I didn't know that you were so weird at the time that you would want to go just sit outside
You didn't know me that well back. I'll throw rappers at a factory and say give me give me a t-shirt
Give me a t-shirt that would I would love I think I would love a tootsie roll
I think you would've been shot on sight
But anyway, I would every day that I would like I would be so hungover and I'd be waking up at 6 in the morning
to go work at
folding towels at the gym job that I had and
And I would have to walk in proximity to this Tootsie Roll factory,
and the smell was so fucking disgusting that it just drove me crazy.
Yeah.
And I just can't, I'll never have one again.
They were never good in the first place. Those are always terrible.
Number 17 is Gobstoppers. Don't bite them right away. Just don't do it.
But they taste so good. So many layers.
Wonka is definitely the best maker of candy.
I'm actually with you. I think fictional Wonka is really good, but not
real life. Oh my god. This guy forgot what the fucking entry was. Yeah. Number 18, whatchamacallit.
You've had a whatchamacallit? No. Yeah. Oh my god. They're so good. Every time I went to the
pool growing up I would get one of these at the snack bar. They were from the
freezer. Definitely freeze these. Do a frozen whatchamacallit. Oh my god, wait. I have to read this
next one. I'm sorry. I just saw something here. Number 19, Jelly Belly Beans. My grandpa, one of
the best people in the world, just FYI, and I get a 40 flavor box and transform
into mixing beans recipe extraordinaires. I was also part of the Jelly Belly Taste
Bud Club when I was little. Yes, that was a thing. I'd get sneak preview flavor packs in
the mail and everything. Also, Dr. Pepper Jelly Belly Beans. Nuff said. And he has a photo
of Dr. Pepper Jelly Belly Beans.
That photo is great.
Second of all, the Dr. Pepper Jelly Belly Beans and the Snapple ones are so fucking good.
This fucking guy has been in the game so long.
This guy is the candy king.
And he's a mixing beans recipe extraordinaire.
Oh my god! He transformed into a mixing beans recipe extraordinaire with his grandpa.
He was one of the best people in the world.
Number 20 is grapefruit gummies. His grandpa Joe. I do like these.
Oh my gosh. These are probably my favorite ones.
The Haribo fruit salad. Any kind of fruit flavored gummy with a sour thing on it.
Those are good. Haribo fruit salad is a slept on bodega snack.
I'm gonna sleep on you. You're gonna be my... You better not. You will be my bed in four hours.
I will be duct taping you to the ground and sleeping on you. Number 21, pop rocks. You know,
not my favorite. What was the... Pop rocks are... It's a fun... It's a novelty. Yeah.
He's... Always fun. These are never not fun. I'm 28 and they're still so fun. True.
The myth... What do you mean they're still so... Are you like picking up a pack of these on the
way home with like... It's been a long day at work. That's what I do when I have pop rocks.
I gotta throw back a pop rocks. There's a myth in the 70s that a kid drank a coke
with pop rocks in his mouth and he died. And his head exploded. Yeah, his stomach exploded.
That's what I heard. There's a bunch of different versions I think. And then
that then it was crazy that that turned out to be true about Mentos and Coke.
Yeah, that it kills you. I don't think it kills you. It doesn't kill you, but it kills you.
It makes an alien come out of you. Oh wow. Well I'm just saying like, like it was
like oh yeah pop rocks and coke is just a myth and then like finding out like from
YouTube that like oh yeah they'd stuff actually it makes a candy with coke it
well there yeah one candy but they were just off yeah I don't think it'll make
your head explode it will make your head explode with soda in it so it will come
out your ears Oh so you poured soda and Mentos in your brain that might know you
pour it into your mouth if you have holes in your mouth that go up to your
brain it might go on your brain yeah yeah that makes complete sense I don't
I don't think Coke's gonna come out of your ears.
I think it'll come out of your mouth.
The throat and ears are connected.
But I don't think, I think it's gonna come out of your mouth.
The throat and ears are connected though.
You're useless.
If your mouth is closed, it might come out of your ears.
Number 22 is flavored candy canes.
I do like these.
These are always, oh, speaking of.
These are always in the light.
The Sour Patch Kids candy canes.
He mentions them right there.
Those are the best.
All right, so candy canes are a staple of the holidays.
minty, cool, Christmas-y, but flavored candy canes
are literally the best version of this holiday tradition.
Sweet Tart candy canes, Sour Patch Kid candy canes,
you name it, sign me up.
- The red one?
- And right now they're hitting stores.
Also just saw Trolley has a version.
What?
- Damn.
- What?
- A gummy candy cane sounds good.
- You wanna--
- Trolley has been--
- I was in a laundromat and the--
- I wish it was a candy store.
- I wish this was a candy store right now.
I was doing my laundry and the Chinese guy who runs the laundromat,
he's watching a video on his phone in Chinese. Um, and it had that,
you know, the like YouTube video editing where it just cuts to short clip,
like reaction clips of like clips from movies and stuff.
He's watching something that was completely in Chinese,
but literally every like three to five seconds, it just played the Lil Jon.
What? Like really loud.
Oh wait. I think I know that's they do. There's a foodie,
foodie China 88 on Instagram.
Is it in Chinese?
I mean, it's not the one I watched, but it's like,
was it like a cooking video?
I was only heard the eye.
I wasn't up over his shoulder watching his video.
Every couple of seconds, he'll do like,
like he says, like, give the food a Thai massage,
mix it with water from the Mississippi River,
mix in evil chicken bouillon, and they'll go, what?
Maybe that was it.
Yeah, I think I've seen this video.
(laughing)
Number 23, peppermint patties.
Love peppermint patties. Not for me.
I love peppermint patties.
No, thank you.
Peppermint patties are so good.
Well, he's patty and you're definitely a peppermint in your attitude.
Number 24, Buckeyes candy.
Uh-huh.
Never had these.
O-H, even Michigan fans have to admit these chocolate peanut butter candies are way better
than anything a Wolverine candy could be.
#Amiright.
You did a little Ohio State photo shoot there.
In dirt pudding or a road trip snack, sour or sweet.
So many options, but you have to go with Trolli Worms.
has been doing some crazy things with gummy worms lately. I don't know if you guys remember
the neon bursters? Oh, the bursting crawlers? And the crunchy ones? The crunchy worms were
pretty good. The crunchy worms, I have had a bite of those. Oh, Paige not found. Who
was that beautiful woman? That beautiful character. Number 26 is Dum Dums, classic lolly, tons
of flavors. Yeah, I'm between a couple of Dum Dums right now. Come on. I'm also between
some Dum Dums. I'm between a Mike and an Ike right now. Yeah. Number 27 is Mike and Ike's.
Mike and Ike's mega mix.
You can kind of tell he's--
The sour one.
That song.
The blue pack.
That shit was good.
I'm snacking on that blue pack.
Snacking on that blue pack.
You can tell he's kind of running out of energy
with this list, 'cause he used to be writing a paragraph
about each one, and now they all just are just one sentence
of what the candy is.
Well, if you know--
He needs to candy up.
If you got a sugar rush--
Yeah, if you got a sugar rush,
eventually you're gonna crash.
He's crashing right now.
Yeah, 'cause then we got Starburst,
and he just says, "Let's be honest,
"these are the coolest candies.
"Also, did you see the gummy versions?
get them now. The gummy versions were disgusting. I had terrible. No, those are
the one of the recent gummy drops. Those are the new, those are the air ones. Oh,
those are terrible. Yeah, those are different. Those are bad. Okay. I'm
realizing every candy I've had in the last three years has been something that
you've handed me. For the most part, me too. I have not had any candy that I've bought for like years. It's only been him coming in and being like, try this and put something in my mouth.
I think the only candy I bought is probably those Starburst gummies.
I'm just an adult man who eats candy.
You really are.
Oh, I had some Sour Patch Kids recently.
When was the last time you had steak?
Oh, I couldn't tell you.
Probably never.
You eat candy.
No, I've had carne asada, if that counts.
I think the last time I...
I mean like a meat and potatoes meal.
Like I cooked myself a steak.
With no candy.
Last time I cooked myself a steak.
Sure.
November 2021. So not that long ago. Yeah. A year ago. But when was the last time you ate candy?
Like yesterday. What'd you have? What'd you have? I had a Reese's cup.
And what, so what makes you... I bought a two pack. What makes you, when you're at the store,
what compels you to buy the candy? I'd say to myself, I haven't had candy in a little while.
I've been good about it because I saw a dentist and they were like, "Yeah, you're like, you
have the only reason..." They told me the only reason I have cavities is because I grind
my teeth.
And not the candy that you buy all the time.
I didn't tell them about the candy.
When they ask how often you eat candy. So they must think that you're in there just fucking...
I think they usually don't ask that to adults. I don't think that's a question that they ask
a guy who comes in.
How often do your parents let you eat candy?
Dressed in real tree.
True.
They're probably going to ask you how many times a week you
eat candy, even though it's probably three.
Yeah.
I think I do.
I think I will say maybe three times a week I will get a candy.
Yeah.
And I'm obsessed with gummies.
If it's a small serving, I think it's fine.
I think you do you.
I think it's OK to do whatever you want.
You know, I have a--
I'm realizing my candy is that I do--
I'll get one of those Oikos Greek yogurts every once in a while.
That's my candy.
And then every once in a while I'll have one piece of a dark chocolate bar before
I go to bed and it keeps me up all night.
The worst thing, I like ice cream. That's my candy.
The worst kind of thing I,
the worst thing that I ever picked up at the store and I realized that I needed
to stop eating so much candy was I bought a Ruby
chocolate bar, like a, it's like a red chocolate.
And it had, it was like with guava filling.
- Yeah, those are bad. - Or passion fruit.
- The red chocolate is bad.
- Red chocolate with passion fruit in the middle.
- I've never even heard of red chocolate.
- Ruby chocolate.
- I was like, oh man, this is not good, one.
And two, I'm a candy freak.
- You're a male candy addict.
- I'm an adult candy addict.
- You're skipping ahead a little bit.
31 is Hershey's bar, one word, classic.
- I just love a normal Hershey's bar.
- Now I wanna read 32 is Turkish Delight.
- I love Turkish Delight.
- I haven't had this.
- Just tasted this candy this year.
Now I know why Edmund was so tempted to destroy his family to get an unlimited supply of this.
If you don't get that reference, I'm disappointed.
Dude, I was such a fucking CS Lewis superfan that for four years in a row I asked for Turkish
Delight for Christmas.
I had the box set.
It does come in a box.
It's really good.
Dude, take five is the perfect candy bar.
Take five and Baby Ruth.
Those are two very underrated ones, yeah.
Sweetest first, that's gotta be the worst candy ever made.
I like Swedish fish. It's terrible.
They see said they're going on.
He said I never had a candy that tasted so
unique. So this is a
candy expert. He says it's at least unique.
Cadbury eggs. This is a
Halloween episode. We don't care about Cadbury eggs.
Easter food. Warheads.
I like Warheads. I drank a Warheads
thing. I like Warheads. Red
cherry slices. It's a picture of him with his
grandpa. It says my grandpa and I would sit
and eat these while watching baseball
in Ohio. That's so sweet.
Alright, well leave your fucking...
Peachy Penguins!
How about you, B? Try being a little bit, just like, I don't know,
why is he bringing all his personal shit into this?
Stop going so fucking fast, Juvia!
Stop! Yeah.
What's wrong with you?
I'm scrolling.
Go back to Peachy Penguins!
I said Peachy Penguins!
I want to learn about these!
Patrick, read about Peachy Penguins for us.
Love these! You don't understand.
They are peach-flavored.
I know they're black and white, that makes no sense.
They are peach-flavored and they're absolutely delicious.
Try them ASAP.
I don't think I will do either.
I don't think I will either.
I want that candy so bad.
Orange Tic Tacs.
Orange Tic Tacs, I can't handle them.
One time I got in trouble at a summer job
because I ate all the orange Tic Tacs.
They were supposed to be used as breath mints
for all employees.
I ate the whole thing in the first hour of my shift.
Also, I used to get these in my stocking at Christmas
and it was the best.
Yeah, these are not breath mints.
I completely relate to that.
Yeah, I forgot how much I love those.
They are really good.
Tic Tacs are good.
Fun Dip.
Lindor White Chocolate, come on now.
Yeah, shut up dude.
Actually, you know what?
I don't hate white chocolate as much
as much as everybody else says.
I can enjoy a white chocolate and macadamia is pretty good.
I really don't like white chocolate.
I might eat some candy today.
I think white chocolate, it can be like a tiny chip in a cookie I guess, but anything that's
made out of white chocolate I think is disgusting.
But like if you ate a whole brick of white chocolate that's...
I actually might like that, yeah, now that I think about that.
I've never tried a brick.
Remember the Cookies and Cream Hershey's bar?
No.
You haven't?
Go try that.
Those were bad, I didn't like those.
Those were terrible.
Yeah, those were terrible.
I'm gonna say my knowledge of candy, probably anything that came out past 2009, I don't
know about.
Yeah.
The Cookies and Cream Hershey's bars, I ate too many of them as a kid, and now when I
think about that flavor, I want to puke.
Why?
You don't like candy.
I think the Cookies and Cream Hershey's thing also made me want to puke as a kid.
Yeah.
It's too sweet.
It's specifically a puke-making flavor.
Is it just really sweet?
Yeah, you can go get them at the bodega, whatever.
All right, let's split one, man.
Oh, you know what they do have now?
It's making me crave candy so much.
A blueberry muffin Kit Kat.
Is it good?
It's so good.
Hubba Bubba gum, I got that in my hair when I was five,
and my mom had to cut all my hair off.
What?
I ate a whole thing of Hubba Bubba,
and then I was trying to get it.
You know the bubble tape?
I do love Pez.
I love Pez.
Number 47, Pixie Stix.
"My mom wouldn't let me have these until at least 15, I swear.
"Some family choking problem.
"Not that that would ever happen to me or anything.
"#almostdiedwheniwas22 #oncherrygummies #onherbirthday #babyshewasright"
- Wait, he almost died from a cherry gummy and he lists cherry gummies as, like, 47?
What the f-- wait, wait, did we--
And he didn't mention this in the cherry gummies thing?
He just said, "I ate these with my grandpa when we watched baseball in Ohio!"
- Maybe he skipped over it.
Hold on, scroll back. - No, no, no, no, that's all he said.
Do not tell Juby to scroll anywhere.
- All right.
- Dude, I wanna hear that story.
He ruined his mom's birthday by choking on candy?
- Dots, dude.
- Dots are terrible.
- Dots are so good, what are you talking about?
- Spree is good.
- Spree is really good.
- That's a really great candy.
- I'm glad we can agree on that.
I'm glad we saw Spree's after.
- At the end of the list, what did you think?
Is this all the best candy ever?
What did I miss?
Hope you enjoy my candy ramblings.
Seriously though, go get these delicious treats.
- You know what I will say?
and total world candy domination.
- I will say what he missed,
and going back on the I like white chocolate sometimes,
if it's done right. - Yeah, I mean,
you two with this guy,
I think you two could together create an amazing list,
'cause you're both kind of candy monsters.
- Candy men. - Candyaholics.
- Yeah.
- But a zero bar, white chocolate nougat,
some kind of like fudge on the inside.
- You know the ingredients to the candy bars?
- Yeah. - Yeah, that's dangerous.
- Yeah, it says it on the label.
- So if you want one of each of these candies,
you can come to the Halloween live show
where we'll be giving out one of each of the candies
we just said. - Oh my God, it's time to be real.
- I know it is, but I'm trying to do the thing here.
But yeah, go buy tickets to the Halloween show,
swagpoop.com/shows.
And yeah, I think that's basically it, right?
Anything else?
- You can come to my house if you need somewhere to be.
- Oh, go to the candy store.
Yeah, the candy store is open.
Bye.
All right.