Tonight, war, traditional family values, animal rights, free market capitalism, privacy rights,
global climate change, lunchtime, Christmas, will all be debated on Real Life Debates.
(dramatic music)
(alarm blaring)
(upbeat music)
- Welcome.
- Welcome to the show.
- Ah, fuck.
And greetings to you as well.
- What?
- Just trying to be kind of respectable.
- Oh yeah.
- Do my respectable thing.
- Okay, being a fucking weirdo.
- Weird shit.
No, I'm trying to be respectable. I've been trying to bring manners more into my life a little bit.
You know, make eye contact with women on the street and stuff. Just look right at them, kind of.
The thing that you're supposed to do, and I read this I think on, what's it, Jezebel.
Not familiar.
You look a woman straight in the eyes on the street and you point your hands, you make a fist like this.
Okay.
and you say, "Energy! Energy!"
No, you're supposed to do this.
And then you siphon their life force.
You think you're supposed to do a Wakanda forever?
Yeah.
I don't think you're supposed to do that.
Women-kanda.
I don't think you're supposed to do that at all.
Women-kanda are not as good as men-
Yeah, they're better.
-kanda. No, that's not what I meant.
Yeah, they're not as good. They're as great.
Okay, so we have our first debate topic.
Basically, today we're doing a bit of a debate-style show
Because I mean we've been sharing
These mics here for going on three years and to say that we almost yeah
Well to say we but wow wow okay?
Wow very soon. Yeah, very soon, but no way for four years for
Geez and there's been so many at three
There's there's been so many things that have changed on this well
But also to say over the years to say that we've butted heads about certain
Social and political issues I would say would be an understatement. Oh absolutely because we occupy as we know three different
Parts of the political quadrants the triads yeah
Well, it's part of a triangle. It's the try a political triangle. I've never this is a concept
This is a concept that Cameron came up with is the political triangle. Yeah, I mean I you guys know
I did a stint as a political scientist. Yeah
Really, yeah from the ages of five to seven and I came up with the triangle that was pretty smart. Yeah, yeah
I actually came up with it in music class.
You took the spectrum and you just kind of bent that part.
I wonder what your inspiration was.
It's three points, three political points.
And I mean I can't reveal what they are because I mean we're going to kind of introduce them
in a minute.
Yeah, we're going to get into that.
So today we're doing, we're going to have a debate.
Am I supposed to introduce it now?
No we can go, so like I said.
Debate's too formal.
Debate is too formal.
Although I am into rules and respectability because of where I am on the political triangle.
I like anarchy when it comes to arguing my point.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
And I'm directly in the middle.
So we can go ahead.
We have some political cards we can describe.
Let's start with maybe Cameron.
Yeah, I'll introduce myself first.
Let's go ahead here.
Hi there, everybody.
My name is Cameron Fetter, and I'm a comedic leftist.
Some facts, political facts about me.
I wrote in Shrek in the 2020 election.
That's who I voted for.
is a complete absurd yeah it's absurd it's a bit ironic to where's the I think
you don't grasp maybe the idea of irony it's kind of a kind of that's part of it
you know to act like a fucking stupid head like I mean like I think a lot of
conservatives are now days now are stupid cool now we're Democrats do not
think about it but I also support vicious ad hominem insults on
conservatives their families their children I think that anything should be
completely fair game I think that it's okay to insult an eight-year-old girl if
her dad is a politician, I think that it's okay to say things about her appearance.
That much is clear. That's part of my political beliefs. Yeah, I can tell. I believe that colored hair should be
legal. I think there should be no legal restrictions against having colored hair.
I agree for no reason. I think I might vomit. And also I really I want more
episodes of Tuca and Bertie and I've been saying this for a while but seize
the means of Netflix and let's get some more cartoon shows. Now what does that mean?
there. I'm I'm the means that basically means to get more of
something you want. Okay, so I'm I figured you for an O and a fan
or away not only I'm the
you know, I kind of just like anything with a comedic bent
interesting and also with a leftist bent. Ah, and then we
have a thing you like. I like bents. Yeah, I like things with
Okay, I'll keep that in mind. I'll give you something to bend.
I think now we should introduce Caleb's political views here.
So I'm just a normal Republican, okay? I'm into respectability in politics, right?
I want sensible debate. I want what you do in your own home, that's your own business, okay?
I have no part of that. I really just want everybody in America to have the tools to support themselves.
And then this last one, I don't think I wrote that. Yeah, I don't think I need to go over that one.
that one yeah yeah it must have been a glitch that was that's a kind of glitch
has nothing to do it must have been something about the graphic design the
color scheme oh yeah white text only that's what I meant when I when I put
that on my card I was like can you make sure it's white text oh yeah right
there's other colors of designer designer he must have been yeah I mean
by the way you're racist fucking shitbag for putting shit like that on your
mother fucking card. Oh, this must be the ad hominems you're talking about.
Yeah, well that's what I would expect from a... Oh yeah, nice one stupid head.
That's what I would expect... Okay, wow, that is fucking... Okay, are you calling me the
stupid head or him? Because... Both of you fuckwads are ass clowns to me.
Alright, well I guess it's good... I guess I should introduce my political
beliefs here. Yeah. I'm a complete moderate. That's why you're in the middle. Yeah. With a yellow
microphone. Uh-huh, and I have never really... Wait, I have a blue microphone and he has a red microphone.
Do we have to switch them out? Yeah.
I have never fully affiliated with a party for long enough to really understand anything.
I was a liberal from 2011 to 2012.
From 2012 to 2013 I became conservative after reading a couple articles.
And then after watching my favorite show, I became a South Park conservative.
conservative which I don't know if you can you can see here scoot to your right
to my right yeah okay I see that little patch yeah there I think that's the logo
of the political party oh nice and can you tell us what that entails being a
South Park conservative um it means that I agree with all of the ideas of Cartman
Okay, which I mean I'm not familiar with it's a little well. Well. I did because I was only a South Park conservative from
2013 to
2016 okay, and then at that point I I I mean it's a
Pretty similar already I became libertarian did a little lateral move there. Yeah, but then I became a South Park conservative again
And currently I'm a member of a political party that I made up
Called the birthday party and we do all sorts of vermin supreme type shit, but I'm a supreme big fan
Yeah, I also don't know when the elections are happening and it's it's mostly about throwing a good birth
So you actually like so let me just get this let's go ahead and jump into this this guy actually thinks it's something like
Vermin supreme is making a mockery out of the political
You actually enjoy crap like that well, yeah, I think I'm I funny costume you have a funny costume on
That's your hair. What do you mean your costume?
You haven't always had that?
No. See, I'm plum bald under this wig.
Who would call that plum bald?
I'm completely bald.
What kind of plums do you eat where they have black hair an inch thick all over them?
Yeah, I don't think I'm eating the right plums.
No, you must not be.
Get that hair back on your head.
Must not be.
Yeah.
Get that hat, or that hair back on your head.
Yeah, I have to.
I mean, it's part of the birthday party.
To bring it back to the debate about Vermin Supreme, I mean, as a kind of comedic, ironic,
I'll say it, dirtbag leftist, I think that funny and ironic costumes are actually great.
Like as you'll notice, if you saw somebody like me, a comedic leftist who votes for Shrek,
Garfield, Death Grips, this type of thing, you'll see a guy like me dressed like this
walking down the street, you think,
"You know what I'd do? I'd punch you in the fucking face, you bastard!"
No, you wouldn't, because you'd see what I'm wearing right now,
you'd think, "This guy's a USA Republican conservative,
he's wearing a shirt that says 'God Bless America'
and a hat that has an army gun that says something on it."
And what you would think is,
"This is a Republican wearing Republican clothing."
Little do you know, it's like Halloween for me.
I'm creating a comedic costume like dressing up for Austin Powers.
Interesting. I actually wouldn't think,
in no way would I think that you were a conservative,
because you do have colored hair,
and it would be very, very obvious to me that you were basically a liberal woman type person.
You have cutted hair.
I have. I have what's called a crew cut, okay, and it's very popular in the Republican Senate.
Yeah, it looks like a fuzzy nut.
As a moderate right now.
Can you maybe tone down the comedic part of your leftist attitude?
Yeah, and your children are ugly.
And I don't even have children for the first...
Good.
Okay, so actually what you're doing is actually it's actually called ad hominem, and it's completely
Yeah, he said that he said he believes in okay. Well. You're you have a you are a complete turd this guy doesn't even
Know that
You can't even engage with a woman. That's not true. I make a child
I'm gonna stay directly in the middle still until one of you okay well in that case. Let's talk about let's maybe cool
Let's talk about policy. Okay. Can we talk about policy? How about the war on drugs? Okay?
I bet you fucking like smoking dope. Yeah, wait dope pot and more. Oh my god. He actually liked a little done
You can't be serious, and I think the war on drugs should be Thor on drugs
They should make a movie that has psychedelic imagery with Thor in it. I don't
I don't side with that anymore
Directed by taiko a TT. Yeah, I'm not I don't fuck with that crap. I don't really care taiko a t for kit taiko psycho
psycho
Crazy TT. I don't like him very much
I'm on his side now because I think that his voice strikes me as a bit gay whatever accent that is
Kind of gay to me. I think gay people rule the world in a good way
Well, I think they definitely rule the world you were very close there
You said you in a good way got you to move over to the left
Yeah, well, I think that it's a bad thing I
I'm not really budging on this one.
Oh my god. Okay, well what's next on policy?
Well, I personally, I mean, I'm curious to hear what you think about this.
Yeah, I'm curious.
It's actually...
Is that, were you saying that in a good way?
Is it a good way or a bad way?
I'm saying that in a bad way.
Okay, then I'm gonna stay over here.
Okay.
I'm actually a staunch supporter of hipsterism.
You're a, uh...
And I think it should be enshrined in the code of law.
I bet you...
I'm in the middle. I'm back in the middle.
In fact, I don't even think we should have laws now that I think about it.
Hipsterism should be codified in the Declaration of Independence.
You think that should be in the Constitution?
I think that should be the only thing.
The only amendment should be what? And how would you phrase that?
Hipsterism.
And let me guess, you'd probably think it'd be funny to make it the 420th amendment.
Yeah. Either that or the 69th or...
Um...
Uh...
420-69...
4...
4... 42,000...
42-0s...
Here's what I think.
He touched my hat.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
I'm back over here.
Here's what I think.
I'm back on his side because he believes.
I don't steal.
He believes.
He's lying.
Hey, we can agree on that, pal.
Watch this.
Hey, Cameron.
That's my.
Hey, you want this for free?
It's welfare.
Yeah.
I love welfare.
And you're staying over there, you sick son of a bitch?
I love welfare, too.
Oh my God.
I really.
Sorry, I like working for my money.
I really don't know anything.
Here, can I purchase that hat?
Yeah.
I will do anything for that hat, and I mean anything.
- Okay.
- So what do you want me to do?
- How about you put on this wig?
- I'll put that wig on, yeah.
Well, maybe you two could talk about a policy
while I get dressed.
- I have no knowledge on policy at all.
- Do you have any concerns that maybe would affect
which side you would end up on?
(laughing)
- So it seems to me--
- Why do I look like such a pretty girl?
- You're a fucking Final Fantasy character.
- You've become what I like to call
a Lois Griffin conservative.
- You put on the fucking long white wig,
you become Sephiroth, and now you're fucking Sora
from Kingdom Hearts.
(laughing)
You're just an anime guy.
Any type of hair you put on--
- That looks scary.
Ah.
Okay, I like this, and I'm gonna keep it on my head.
Okay, colored hair SJW.
No, I'm not a-
That was a trick.
Ad hominem.
That was a trick that I played on you.
No, I'm not-
And I'm actually going back to my own middle party here.
Okay, so maybe you should pitch us on your party.
Yeah, so tell us a little bit about the birthday party.
You don't have to care about anything.
What does that mean?
It's all- both sides are actually fucking bad.
Wait, is that- that's the policy of your party?
Well, I can agree with you on half of that.
You can't scoot into that way.
Why not?
Because that doesn't make any sense.
I hate fucking both sides of this political bullshit though.
Wait, then you're the same guys.
I love the right side because of my right wing.
Oh, I guess I actually love the left side, I just realized.
Oh, okay.
Now that I think about it. But you know what I hate?
What?
You know who's sitting right here?
Barack Obama. Hillary Clinton. Joe Biden.
Adolf Hitler.
Kamala Harris. Adolf Hitler actually is sitting right there.
there now that's it all we have a very i another day
as kids are always for now not just kids are ugly hitlers
i don't think he had any children
exactly at all i couldn't even get you can have a chance to read that's
actually proof that he was a liberal democrat
is that he had dogs which are if you if i mean if somebody's childless but has a
dog that's i would say liberal democrat thing
okay fuck stick if you know if you think i feel obligated to defend a liberal
democrat you know the first mother here's a thing about my it's my shit so
So here come the insults.
Fuckface Von Clownstick.
Shit like that, right?
Daily Show type ad hominem arguments.
Okay, Dr. Kofefe.
Oh my god, and his hair is orange like Trump's skin.
I think I have to go on this side.
And this is a clear divide.
So these two represent kind of Hollywood elites, soccer coaches, that kind of person.
Soccer coaches.
Right?
Over here, this is an all-American football coach.
Yeah, you look like you had too many Hollywood delights, candies and foods.
Yeah, you look like a...
As fat as a balloon in a hot air balloon.
You look like Drop Dead Fred.
Who's Drop Dead Fred?
It was a movie.
What?
With Rick Mayall.
I haven't seen that movie.
Okay, well you look like him with that wig.
Okay, I'm moving further over to my side because of how much...
You're moving further to the right?
No, I'm being completely... I'm being pushed even further right wing by you two, okay?
I'm getting... And this... I don't want to tell you what this is, right?
Right when I get off camera, shit's gonna get bad.
You're gonna wanna cut my microphone, okay?
If I get any further right than this,
you better tread lightly.
And don't tread on me.
- I see, I see.
- I see, something about don't tread on me
is I motherfucking hate that message,
but the design is so cool.
- I'm seeing the rage and the passion that you have
in your speech just now.
- Thank you.
- I think I'm kind of.
- Okay, hey Patrick.
- Thank you.
- Hey Patrick. - I like it.
And now I have a buddy over here.
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do you can't do a mic drop on that. Hey, can you switch the camera to me?
No
SpongeBob memes all right don't don't drop the mic that's so loud and really bad listen to this
So what other policy things you want to get into let's get it about people listen to this
I don't even care okay that I okay
So it's one thing to be a fucking liberal Democrat, but to be a nihilist and not I do think they should all get free
medicine that costs a hundred thousand dollars and other people should
have to work for it. You think that my ginger ass should be out there slaving
day and night, which by the way we were the original slaves, I think everyone
can agree with that, ginger people like me. You think that we should have to work
our hard asses sitting in the pill factory, right, at a pill press. I
sit at that pill press all day. I'm pressing Xanax, I'm pressing Welbutrin,
Life-saving medication. That's right. You think that that should be free?
Yeah, because I think a guy in a flannel needs to be able to eat ice cream without pooping his pants. Okay
Say asshat. Yeah, usually because I don't like sarcasm and irony
So I mean it literally like you have you could have an and you know, he looks like he looks like gritty
So I actually like him. I'm not well, you're with gritty. You are missing out what I'm missing out pull up gritty
What the hell's gritty pull up gritty? Well, this looks like a delightful
sports iconography piece
This looks okay, right. What's so wrong about being a hockey mascot. We like gritty
Wait, okay, so I like gritty - then he seems pretty awesome. Yeah
Can you pull up a gritty me? I'm sure he would yeah
I'll pull up gritty memes search gritty memes here and pull these up. I'm not so sure what that means memes
You're gonna like memes. That's so this is that's the nice means of production you got there be a shame if someone seized it, okay
So that's basically the opposite of your whole so so even though I am a right-wing Republican even I can admit that's just funny. Yeah
Really
Is that Wow person of the year it's a Muppet of the year yeah, it's a mascot of okay
Okay, now pull up big chungus all right. Oh my goodness pull up big chungus leftist meme big chungus and gritty
Okay, pull up leftism. Yeah, big chungus left. Okay, so pull this up. Okay, so this is all right is is
Not true, so that's missus fucking propaganda. That's dr. Prager Prager is a very is a good friend of mine. He's a very good man
He knows that if you're not this is sized you might as well be in a dumpster
It says the left wants to take away big chungus, and I just want to say that's not fucking true
Okay, and also this type of propaganda is evil
And they should could take a page out of North Korea's book if they're trying to create something
That's nice and helps people I'd take a page out of North Korea's book
And I'd crumple it up, and I'd play paper bin basketball with it at the office
Yeah, I miss every shot cuz you're a fucking clown if I if I go toe-to-toe in a presidential fitness test
I'll fuck you up kiddo
If I
If I picked up North Korea's book, I don't think I'd understand a goddamn thing that's written in it
I bet you I bet you can agree on that
I bet you were the kid who faked asthma to get out of the presidential fitness. No actually I actually I did not fake it
okay, and
Is sometimes when you have asthma?
You can't do things like your homework or running or being nice to your mom this leftoid once a presidential Johnny test
That's what's a cartoon president.
Yeah, and I'm proud of it.
President of Johnny Test?
Yeah.
What is that?
What's Johnny?
Johnny Test.
Oh, Johnny Test.
Like Johnny Test.
Because he is president.
OK.
Or their president.
I bet you're a their.
Yeah, who what when--
He's over there.
Who what when in their, asshole?
What the hell does that even mean?
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, that's right.
That's what I'm saying.
Nitty gritty political discourse.
OK, keep bringing on the attacks.
I don't even care. I got a thick skin unlike you your skin is thin and white
I hate I hate all these whites in politics ruining this politics right here
No way you're moving over cuz cuz of the white thing all right. I don't want to get in okay
Hey, shut up. It's pale. I don't pale ass. I don't want to get a whitey
whoa
She's the W or hit me what the hell's going on saying hey whitey over here
All right, you shut your trap first of all you don't know my you don't know my results snow roach
You don't know my 23 and me results snow roach says fucking that almost feels normal races
That's out of out of the podcast that might be
That's a kpop people made that up snow road yeah to call white people urban dictionary snow roach a white
a white person.
(laughter)
So that was how much we were about the funniest thing ever.
Alright, well then I'm glad you're being mad about it, asshole.
(laughter)
Whatever happened to the old...
And I support K-pop.
You're staying on...
After he used a vicious slur,
like snow roach.
That shit made me laugh.
Okay, well you're both a couple of...
That's what it's about though, it's about laughing.
It's about laughing and holding hands with others and helping the world get...
I also fucking leave the birthday party fucking murdering some motherfucking CEOs. Okay, let's get this started. Okay, by the way
I start fucking murdering so here's here's a clear example by the way of how leftist distort reality
He just said mother motherfucking
So first of all you missed like four fucking words their ass hat and you made it into a hip
Now you're saying I actually came up with a comedic leftist song recently. Oh, yeah, it's a parody of a different song
And it's kind of similar to, it's a little bit about killing CEOs. I can't sing it.
Yeah, okay, Weird Al Gender Switch.
But I can hum the tune.
Come on. Weird Al, Weird Al, get that again. Let me get a clean take of that.
Okay, Weird Al Gender Switch.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty good. So I came up with this comedic leftist song that goes like...
(humming)
(laughing)
- I think that this, that song,
I mean I'll write down the lyrics and send them to you later,
but I think it really communicates comedic leftism.
And it really like--
- Might even have been the peak of comedic leftism.
Might have been maybe the greatest ever doing.
- It might have all been ended at that point,
all comedic leftism.
But then it also could be a young--
- There also could be a Mario edition on YouTube.
(laughing)
- True.
- Which I would really love to see.
- Close this up.
No, we don't need to see that.
(laughing)
All right, well this is getting--
- They done turned that boy to Mario.
- This is getting out of hand, I would say.
This is getting completely out of hand.
(laughing)
This is some kind of...
We have a lot of new listeners coming,
they're gonna have no idea what the hell we're talking about.
It's gonna send them down a bad rabbit hole.
All these little 10 year olds who watch The Yard
are gonna come here and be like,
what the fuck's going on with these psychos?
They're all gonna be so confused.
Yeah.
Oh man.
I saw another comedic leftist video about Starbucks.
Yeah.
Okay, so...
But what I like to...
If you take it at its word,
It's kind of like your end of the political spectrum.
But if you look at it through an ironic lens.
And you know what I just remembered you from
is a video shot in a car.
Now that was me.
That one was me.
Yeah, that one was actually me.
Yeah, no.
And I stand by that one, by the way.
That one, I had a little bit of flip-flopping kind of era
where I was going, oh, a left-oid kind of video.
Yeah, comedic, yeah.
Yeah, right-winger kind of video.
Now I'm solidly just a normal right-wing Republican type.
I will say I find a lot of stuff pretty disrespectful that Trump and Governor DeSandwich are doing
that's not very good.
Governor DeSandwich.
Or whatever his name is.
I don't think that any of that is very, very good for America in the political discourse.
I'm more in the Ayn Rand kind of version of Republican where it's like we need to be respectful,
we need to do eugenics, we need to not make...
I think you should check out South Park Conservatism.
Yeah, I think Link from motherfucking Legend of Zelda should chop your head off.
Okay, that don't make no sense.
You know what?
First of all, Legend of Zelda...
I could handle almost every single ad hominem attack that you've done today, but that one
was too far.
I don't care.
I don't give a shit.
Listen, I don't give a shit who I alienate when I'm doing my transgressive and some would
say ironic comedy.
I don't even care.
To me, it's all about making myself laugh and making my friends laugh.
And guess what?
It doesn't matter what we say because we all know we support healthcare.
So you're saying, "So what, we get drunk?
So what, we smoke weed?"
Yeah, exactly.
Is that by your band Blink 182 Genders?
Because I blinked in 2014 and woke up 182 genders.
Yeah, and that's from your band, Blink 18 2-year-olds.
Maybe 2 18-year-olds.
Maybe 2 18-year-olds from a Hardee's commercial who are both eating hamburgers with me and
roasted onions on me
yeah i think you know you've also heard that her into my own my penis that's
from your bed and i was remembered uh... brand the offspring
uh... the offspring offspring that i think yes actually
not what it was our by and and i'll be like you know the offspring the uh...
the offspring that looks of was fuckin there's no way in that's why you
probably want to abort them now
yes abortionist
that's usually why i like i support abortion is going looking at these
fucking republicans children
and i'm like these children are so ugly and we're going to have a look at what
you call them chugs
yeah i don't know what i would call them
judge in years
has a lot of them they're growing up and these these uh... they're gonna turn
into fat shards
and i i that's right by support body shaming
uh... well i think well actually have actually read you all wrong wait that's
not i'm listen i'm a as i'm borderline i think it's okay to body shape people if
they're bad fucking people
okay i'm borderline obese
and i'm borderline a nazi and i don't even like that yeah and i have borderline
personality disorder i'm proud of it and i'm a man
holy crap well i think it's good for men to have that you just admitted you're a man
yep there goes your leftist cred
yep you're done for well what you see what you have me all wrong i'm not a
normal leftist i'm a comedic leftist it's actually better to be a man as a comedic
leftist oh i didn't realize that yeah actually because women can't meme
Damn. Okay, so again, I'm not really into the misogyny stuff, okay?
That is not so much my bag
as you would leftistly put it. Yeah, I'd like to see you in a bag
banged around the back of a truck. So there goes the violent part and that's where I can smell the
Che Guevara on you.
Is that you're like, "Oh, we'll kill the dissidents." And you see me as a dissident, you're doing
Robocop vision, perfect alpha male detected and then you want to kill me.
And meanwhile you look like a fucking ugly piece of shit.
How do I look pretty in my new wig?
He does look pretty in his new wig looks pretty nice. I will say as a moderate
I think we can so maybe you can scoot on over to the beautiful side
Maybe leave this dirty you you're like pigpin from the peanuts. You're just I see flies
No, no, no that's based in true reality I saw a roach under your arm when you raised it up
No, you didn't I did what you did roach
Might have been that yeah probably come from all that smoking. He's doing yeah, and so let's get into mass
Yeah, I love I love being on this side in the middle here because I can look I think that he sucks
I think that he sucks so when I see when I see a mass shooting in the news
Yeah, my first thought is great more fodder for my jokes to my friends. Yeah, I bet you do
I'm doing run hide fight. You're sitting there. You're thinking. I'm gonna laugh laugh laugh jack off laugh and and fucking die
Yeah, or just laugh laughing. I'm gonna be a target. Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna be the next target you're in the school
Mm-hmm no cuz I'm in the middle in the school. Why are you doing in the school?
There's not a mass shootings don't just happen at schools. We were talking about school one
Yeah, I thought you're talking about the one that happened at my school. You'd be at a garlic festival. Yeah, okay
I think you and me can reach across the aisle and agree
That's a weird spin way to spend your time as a grown man. What going to the garlic festival. Yeah for me
it's like more music festivals. For you it's probably more butt festivals.
And for me it's like...
Butt festivals for you.
No, not butt. No, no. Maybe book fairs.
I like book fairs.
Scholastic book fairs.
With that haircut you look like you're going to be going to a Ren Fair.
Okay, well, there I go scooting ever so more rightward.
And here I am just barely on camera at this point.
If you go to the wide, my left arm is...
Oh man, this left arm is reaching into kind of Mussolini territory at this point.
But now that you're this far away,
- Mm-hmm.
- We can't appreciate this.
- I actually hate wildlife aquariums.
- Holy crap.
- So let me guess, wait,
- I think it's, I actually--
- Wait, so you think that we evolved from that?
- Yes.
I think I evolved from this specifically.
- I actually also hate wildlife aquariums.
- Really?
- I think wildlife should be free.
- Yeah, free to buy and eat.
- Yeah.
- Oh!
- Yeah, I said it.
- He suggested that?
- He wants to eat a turtle.
- He wants to eat a turtle?
- And we're gonna sit there and just let that happen.
So hard it's show as you break your teeth you know I go out fucking fuck me and my uncle go out there on those deep
Fish sea boater the boat fish the deep fish deep sea boat deep sea fishing boat deep sea fishing
And we get a couple of six-packs right we down them
Then we put the rings on the end of a fucking line cast that bad boy out of the ocean
Beluga whale catch him right there reel them in we make barbecue salad out of that barbecue salad
It's a new thing that we created out of whale meat.
That wig just started to have like a second wave on me when you were talking.
This is the last thing, this face is the last thing most endangered animals ever see before
they're gone off this earth forever.
Their only hope is that they find them in amber somewhere.
Right?
Stop laughing at my face.
(laughing)
- You really do, you really do look like a Japanese person
to a white person.
- Really?
I feel like I'm a compliment.
(laughing)
- You look like, you look like anime Ron Weasley.
- You look like Ollie London.
(laughing)
- That is not me at all.
No, look up, look up, who's like a strong--
- You look like, you look like,
you look like when Klasky Kuspo made
Ronald McDonald animated.
- Look up Kaworu from Evangelion.
- See, I don't even know what the hell you're talking about.
What are these, sushi rolls?
Come on.
- From Evangelion, type in Evangelion.
Which I love as a leftist, I should bring up.
- I bet you do.
(laughing)
I like evangelism it's crazy how much hair changes my entire I've been a major
way I don't remember what it was like that I'd you know I said pretty much
It's just the exact same thing.
(laughter)
I barely remember it at this point.
Alright, you know what?
Is it time to
kind of settle this debate
once and for all? Do we have a final topic
that you'd like to tackle? You were the only one
I think who came prepared with
facts. Me? Yeah.
I think that's pretty apparent.
Emotions, facts.
I think I've realized that
you and I,
Republican and me as kind of a comedic ironic
Shrek ism leftist. Yes
We maybe have more in common than I thought and it's maybe that I think what that I agree with your stuff
I think it's funny to do it's if I think it would be funny if I was a Republican
I think maybe I could be it would be funny for me to be a Republican. Really? Yeah
Well, if that's the and I think that it's funny to to do that and I've been lying
I've been on his side the whole time. You've always been a Republican. Yes, sir. I'd like I mean
I need to actually.
I would say this podcast is fully a Republican podcast.
I mean, we're not--
I don't really want to break kayfabe here,
but I mean, if anyone-- it's a fake debate, obviously.
We're breaking kayfabe.
Obviously, Cameron was a parody.
A straw man parody that we just hurled insults at.
And me, I was just up here being myself.
Exactly.
I really don't think of that about--
I want to make this really clear,
because I know it's like my face saying it on video,
and so that's maybe bad.
I really think, I think that all Republican children are beautiful.
Yes, he does.
I don't think they're fat.
No.
If anything...
And I think they should be cherished.
Yeah, they should not be rolled down a hill.
No, or rolled in breadcrumbs or rolled...
Or put in a big cauldron and with stock and celery.
Right, and cutting carrots directly into the cauldron.
And a witch is circling and whistling.
And that's what they're doing at over 3,000 Planned Parenthoods here in America.
Exactly.
put that they've the child is completely born they put him into a soup
uh... they make stock out of the child and i i really i really think it's wrong
what leftists are doing i i don't think i've heard this through executing
republican children you know how they're doing this what they've been locking them
in sky zone for twenty four hours wild
that's awful with your beast
mister bs that's an upstanding republican yes i hope that he becomes a
president one day
so this is a way i think that we can all uh... we can tackle one of our favorite
websites today. Yeah. Right? Which is conservopedia.com. Okay? So this is... I
mean, this is... we already... no introduction is needed. We go here every day.
It's my home page. We've already... we discovered this or discussed it on the Patreon episode.
So here's the splash page. Conservopedia, the trustworthy
encyclopedia. It's clear that some Patriots saw... Wikipedia saw that any old
leftist left-winger Democrat could add whatever they wanted to it. Not only
a true conservative patriot but a member of the
Schlafly family. What's that? His mom was a very like staunch anti-feminist
speaker. I've never seen anybody wear on their face how hard they're thinking as
much as you do. You like blinked like four times. I was trying to remember what I read about it.
That was me remembering how to type. She was a patriotic, anti-feminist woman. She was a patriotic, one of the
most, one of the most, actually and you know what, for a woman, even though she
was a woman, I actually did like hearing her talk. Oh wow. Okay. So this is the
Conservapedia, the trustworthy encyclopedia. Here's some popular articles
at Conservapedia. The Equal Rights Amendment, I bet that one's good.
Conservapedia, Proven Right, Benjamin Franklin, Mystery, Does God Have a Sense of Humor?
which I checked in on it and I didn't didn't make a slide for it but one of the
things is one of the evidences for that was that there's duck-billed platypi and
it said it how funny is that which is true. Scientism, which I don't know what
that is really. Augusto Pinochet. What else on here? Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Oh, underrated sports stars. Yeah. And then Pete Rose is in there.
Algar Hiss, I'm guessing that is a snake. Yeah. So you missed
overcoming homosexuality. Yeah. I could take a look at that. I have no interest in
that page, personally. But this is what one I really like on here, which is
Hollywood values. Hollywood values also known today as Hollywoke or Hollyweird
quote-unquote values are characterized by spreading sexually transmitted diseases,
public obscenities, decadence, narcissism, hypocrisy, rampant drug abuse, abortion,
adultery, lawlessness, and the promotion of the homosexual agenda and cultural
Marxist. I do like that both Hollywoke and Hollyweird were so good
that they had to... They couldn't give them up. Yeah it's just Hollywoke has a... it
It doesn't sound bad.
- Right.
- Hollywoke doesn't sound like fucking bullshit.
- Sounds bad to me.
- Woke stuff.
- In 2014, even in the context of the fashion industry
dress stars of the Academy Awards
and celebrations of St. Valentine's Day,
61% of Americans agreed Hollywood has too much influence
on American politics and social values.
- This is nice 'cause I fucking hate
that people are trying to take the saint
out of St. Valentine's Day.
- Yeah.
Did you pull up anything for St. Valentine's Day?
No, it wasn't all that interesting.
I just wanted to know what a...
We can always freestyle at the end of the day.
I think we all know what St. Valentine's Day is.
It's when a man gives a woman chocolates.
Yes.
And a woman gives a man...
A back rub.
A hand in marriage.
Yes.
Okay.
Hand in marriage job.
And service.
Forever.
In perpetuity.
Yes.
Is what I like to say.
To my wife.
I feel like I'm so sick of these Hollywood values
and just getting into American culture, right?
It's always, you know, you can't drive two feet
on the BQE here in New York City.
That's, you know, giant shootout,
people doing back flips on top of semi trucks,
cars exploding right in front of you.
- And they're all driving hybrid cars.
- Yeah, they're all--
- And even the buses are hybrid now.
- Even the buses have back flips.
- I also, these Hollywood values leaking in,
I mean, you're speaking, you're speaking about hybrid.
I saw a hybrid called a Predalien.
Wow.
That I think was influenced by Hollywood.
Yeah, it was disgusting. It was gooey and slimy, and it had a predator's mouth and an alien's mouth combined.
They have made, even in New York City, liberal New York,
they have made the buses hybrid.
Yeah.
I, back in my day, every bus rolled coal.
Every single bus.
Uh-huh.
You would stand at the bus stop, you'd come onto the bus covered in soot.
Yep.
Sometimes a bus would break down, they'd have to call their supervisor, come out and say,
"God damn it, there it is, the catalytic converter's still in this goddamn thing." Rip it out with his
teeth, right? Spin it on the ground. And you know, sometimes it would break down and that wasn't the
issue, they couldn't figure out how to fix it. You know what? Everybody on the bus would get off
and push it. They'd work hard. Everybody. And now there's this whole movement, by the way,
speaking of catalytic converters, young American patriots going around, helping out,
being good Samaritans, helping out working families by taking the catalytic
converters out of Subarus and Fords.
Right? And those are good people. Those are good American cars.
Yeah, because you get in there... A Subaru? That's an American car. Yeah, I think it's from Detroit.
You get in that car... Can you imagine? Christmas Day, right?
You get in your car, maybe... And there's a bow on top of that car. There's a bow on top of the car,
the catalytic converter is
gone, right? It's already been shipped off to a communist country like South Korea.
They turn that bad boy on, just coal blows right in your dog's face.
You gotta go, "It's a Christmas miracle."
Yeah. Beautiful.
Yeah.
You know what they should do?
What?
These patriots who are taking off the catalytic converters,
they should also add those whistles.
I agree.
Into the exhaust.
Yeah. Let's do it.
And you know what? Put a couple of crushed Pepsi cans behind the wheels.
And the nuts and put the truck nuts on and maybe those truck nuts on those cars and that's I love looking at those nuts
When they're on trucks, let's add a kappa sticker. Let's just go for it salt life on the whole back window
Next oh, so here's some of the contents here Hollywood is a tool of anti-social pedagogy
conflict over values description death sexually transmitted diseases crime falsehoods disrespective marriage
Offensive behavior slash moral depravity and then Hollywood actor Dan Aykroyd on bestiality. Oh wow
Yes, I'd like to touch on that really
Yeah, this is Hollywood actor liberal Dan Aykroyd on bestiality
I draw the line at bestiality because it's unfair to the dog or the cat if the dog or the cat had consciousness
Then that'd be okay with me
Bastard Wow I see I for some reason I believed that
The comments or his comments would only be about getting blown by a ghost
Yeah, I was gonna ask what his thoughts were on on sex with ghosts. Yeah, well
I don't like that's pretty apparent
Is that a ghost a beast? A ghost is a beast. A ghost is absolutely a Halloween beast. Yeah, okay
Well, I think conservapedia might beg to differ
Pull up ghost. I don't think I have ghost there might be a ghost thing. My clicker is broken
Am I maybe?
So here's some more Hollywood weirdos director John Waters claims that his biggest influence for his quote-unquote
Films are pornographic movies in addition. He is openly homosexual and thinks he's okay
He you know what okay his tiny little mustache. Yeah, it's people who have tiny mustaches must be gay
And you know what John Waters made a movie called serial mom
Right no serial mom. Oh, he wants to
completely make a buffoonery over the nuclear family. Exactly, give me bacon, egg
and cheese in the morning, mom. You know what another movie he made was called?
Huh. And you guys... What is it? Just say it. Because you're gonna be grossed out.
Okay. Say it. He made a movie called Pecker. Oh, god damn. He made a movie called... Wait, so it's about a
bird? No. Oh. It's about a boy who takes pictures of... Don't even... Okay. Okay.
So I just I searched ghost on conservapedia really quick. They do have a
page for ghosts but it's for Ghost the Band.
Alright, whatever. Agnostic and left-leaning Cenk Ugar and his view on
the legalization of bestiality in some circumstances. Cenk Ugar, the
creator and host of the left-leaning The Young Turks web news show
said, "I'm a young turd." Yeah, that's what I like to call him. "I'm agnostic now. I was
born Muslim. My whole family is Muslim." Maybe, Juby, if you could add some spooky
music behind that. In 2013, Cenk Uygur said that if he had the power to do so, he would
legalize bestiality in cases where the person is pleasuring the animal and the animal appears
not to mind. Do we have a close down clip of this? I don't think we do. I would love
to hear him saying this. But I mean, I believe it, right? It's right there on Kitsubopedia.
It's interesting that he's saying specifically that he would legalize it if he had the power
to do so. Not that necessarily he thinks it should be legalized, but if I had the power
I would legalize that. I'm not going to petition for it.
No, he's not too active in the world.
But if I found myself in a position where that came across my desk, I would probably
stamp it.
He wins a President for the Day contest. Somehow the piece of paper slides across his desk
and just says the dog fucking bill.
I'll tell you what, I'd hate to see Cenk Uygur as the President of the United States.
agnostic president first of all.
- And you know what I'd hate to see even more?
Him fucking a dog.
- Yeah, well, you know why he's partin' in that turkey,
that's the problem there.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Oh yeah.
- So he can, hey, it'll be doin' a different
kind of gobbling.
- That's right, he's fillin' his asshole with--
- On his giblets.
- Fillin' his asshole with bird seed.
Disgusting.
- Stuffing.
- Disgusting.
- He's puttin' peanut butter on his butt.
- Stuffing and gravy.
- No, okay.
- Well, he'll be making gravy.
- Here's another Hollywood elite, Adolf Hitler.
- Okay.
What does he look like?
Hitler and his youth, so here's the truth about Adolf Hitler. Hitler and his youth was a financially irresponsible bohemian.
A German word of the time roughly the same as the English term "hippie".
Ugh! Yuck!
So there, it's settled! Hitler was a hippie.
Hey, there's one hippie that I respect. I'll tell you who it is.
Who's that?
Charles Manson. Okay, you know why?
Why's that?
Because he made the entire world hate hippies.
That's right.
Rightfully.
Thank you, Mr. Manson. We salute you.
He knew what was up.
Tip of the hat to you, sir.
Hitler may have been an atheist.
Is that so?
Adolf Hitler is theorized to be an atheist.
He reportedly loathed Christianity, the bastard, and his father considered having faith a scam.
How fucking dare him?
Yeah, I mean this guy is completely disgusting in every single way.
And other beliefs, Hitler supported animal rights.
Oh, probably animal wrongs.
That's probably what they mean by putting the quotes there.
This guy was a vegetarian hippie.
So just think that when somebody supports animal rights or thinks that maybe we shouldn't
be throwing those baby chicks into that massive meat grinder.
Uh-huh.
I mean that's a Hitler-rite kind of deal.
Definitely.
You know what, hey, I support animal rights.
Yeah?
Animal rights to be eaten in a delicious dinner.
Animal rights, the right to be smothered and covered.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And peppered and chipped.
That's right.
Yeah.
Over there at Waffle House.
Yes, sir.
And that's moderate Patrick Doren.
Yep.
Profanity.
(laughing)
So, you know, we were doing this whole, again, kayfabe
about when we were using profanity back then,
a couple minutes ago.
- And we're not gonna use that.
- But we keep it clean for the most part.
- And dare I say it, I'm not gonna,
I'm gonna say it just so I can drive the point home.
- Okay.
- We're not using that crap anymore.
- Yeah. - No, yeah.
- Profanity. - And I think you guys
can probably tell by how awkward I sound
when I was saying some of those swear words.
Mother.
- Yeah, you definitely did sound awkward.
- Stuff like that.
- It didn't sound natural coming off your tongue.
- People who are maybe more constant swearers
might listen to that and be like,
this guy doesn't know what he's doing,
but I think I put on a pretty good show.
- You did.
- I did believe that you swear like a sailor.
- You did sound like a bit of a sailor.
- When I said A-S-S, clown, did that come across?
- That was pretty good.
- Okay, cool, cool.
- I've never said A-S-S in my life.
- So, profanity, also known as bad language,
swearing, cursing, or cussing, or vulgarity,
is the usage of words, if you can even call them words,
that are considered to be offensive or abusive.
Its use is taboo in polite or formal environments
and more commonly accepted in informal contexts.
In 2008, it was found that liberals are more than 12 times
likely to use profanity on the internet
when compared to conservatives.
Tell me that's shocking,
'cause it doesn't really shock me at all.
- You know, that honestly, it shocks me that it's so low.
- Yeah, I would think it'd maybe be 13 or 14 times more.
- Yeah. - And here's on the right,
this is one of the greatest cussers of all time,
Penn Jillette this guy this guy somehow he he saw magic acts, and he's yeah
You know what that needs a bunch of f-words and you know I actually I prefer his his his
Compatriot who does not cuss at all he keeps it completely clean
I think he's just I think he's afraid to speak up profane words tend to involve certain near-universal subjects filth particularly
Human waste forbidden sexual practices and blasphemous treatment of the sacred oh
- Oh gosh.
- That's a swear already.
- Among profane words, there exist at least two levels
of offensiveness.
There are also, in many languages, including English,
euphemisms.
Now I traffic in these euphemisms every so often.
Such as darn, drat, gosh, frap, and so on.
- Frap, nice.
- I cannot get enough of these words.
I frap and love these.
- Yeah, I love these as well.
- It is such a good way for me to release
what I'm feeling inside without stooping to the level
of a junkie liberal.
- The 20th century saw a shift to sexual terms
as the most offensive.
Recently, racial terms have grown in their offensiveness.
The N-word was commonplace and acceptable
until the mid-19th century.
It is now too offensive for use even in male-only settings
due to political correctness.
(laughing)
Yep, yep, even in male-only settings, you can't do it.
Wow, that has gotta be political correctness gone awry.
Profanity in religion.
According to some interpretations,
profanity is prohibited by God in the Ten Commandments.
My interpretation.
This can be extrapolated from Commandment Three.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord thy God in vain,
for the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain,
since much profanity is in the form of swearing or cursing.
Satan manifests in Hollywood through its insidious profanity
such as seen on HBO.
Wow. Oh, yeah.
HBO. I hate HBO. Yeah. I hate bullcrap on TV. Yeah. Homosexuals, bisexuals, and over sexuals.
And overtly sexual. Overtly sexual. Having sex on my TV. Yeah. How about off? That's what I,
when I turn it up, somebody says, I'm gonna turn HBO on, I say, how about off? Yeah. Yeah,
maybe press the off button on those. Hate bile and ovaries. I mean, I barely get past the first
I barely get past the first five seconds of most of their programs, but even the very beginning
of their shows are pornographic.
You hear it's a voice going, "Ahhhhhhhhh."
That's true.
You're right.
I just turn it off right immediately when I hear that.
You know what they have on there now?
What?
One of the most demonic programs I've ever seen.
What's that?
Sesame Street.
Oh, God.
This show that teaches your children that numbers can speak to you.
Yeah, let's learn from a talking bird.
Let's go ahead and learn from a talking elephant.
And you know what?
This guy Grover is teaching children that it's okay to be bad at service jobs.
And blue!
With a big pink nose.
By the way kids, a lot of young kids now because of Grover and the like are going into these liberal arts schools getting stuntman degrees.
But enjoy being a coffee shop barista at Starbucks.
Just like Grover.
So here's some, they go through some of the media in America
and they tell you why or why not it might be
for or against conservatism,
for or against good traditional family values.
So this first one is American Dad.
Don't let the patriotic sounding title fool you.
Like all Seth MacFarlane animated productions,
it's stand behind liberalism while bashing conservatism,
which is personified by protagonist Stan Smith,
a Republican CIA agent.
And one series regular
is a sexually ambiguous extraterrestrial.
In a case of truth in advertising,
Stan's teenage daughter, Hailey Smith,
is a far left hippie who is truish,
hateful, and sometimes violent.
- Truish?
- Yeah, while stridently standing by her liberal views,
and like Brian Griffin on Family Guy,
is used as Seth MacFarlane's sounding board
for his viewpoints on the show.
Hey, Seth MacFarlane, how about you leave the tunes alone,
go back to Broadway, shaking your ass, you stripper?
- That's right.
Seth MacFarlane, I just wanna say,
says a lot to me that Seth MacFarlane,
when he's peddling his kind of far left disgusting views,
you know what kind of people he has to choose
to say those views?
A dog and a woman.
- Yep.
- Yeah, big surprise there, asshat.
- Yeah, it's like if I were making a show like this,
I would probably put--
- Oh sorry, I said the A word.
- Frapp hat.
- Frapp hat, I meant to say?
Sorry, I got so caught up in the whole--
- If I was making a show like this--
- You dreading frapper.
- I'd probably have Superman say my views.
- See, frapp, we can still say frapp
in a male only setting.
They haven't taken that from us yet.
- No, frapp is probably one of the most common words.
- It's gonna go soon though, thanks to liberals.
- Probably they're gonna say,
"Oh, you can't say frap anymore."
- You can't say frap or drap.
- Yeah, you know what they'd say?
"It's offensive to milkshake Americans."
- They probably would say that.
Yeah, which most of these people are.
Caillou, "The title character
of this Canadian animated series
lacks effective communication skills
and throws whiny tantrums."
Who's that sound like?
Democrat?
- Oh, Democrat.
- "Teaching young audiences that behavior of that nature
can get them what they want.
It was eventually canceled on 2021 with parents rejoicing."
Remember that parents flood in the streets yeah
That was Patriots
Was one thing I liked about that show a kid high-t kid very high-t kid bald bald it bald it
You know what?
Caillou's father mm-hmm should have smacked him more beat the shit out of that little kid
He's bald head red swing around by the ankles
Crunch pull him yes, I love egg. I love that movie Matilda mm-hmm. I fucking love I
Wanted I will say one of the saddest endings. I've ever seen in a movie and sobbing my eyes out got independent. Yeah, no. Thank you
mega babies
1999 to 2000 so this has got a kind of an interesting slant to it aside from copying Rin and Stimpy because of the humor
Rugrats because of the premise and the powerpuff girls because of the trio of heroes trend seen throughout works of fiction
This Canadian animated series, please add info so they just kind of got him on ripping other ripping other
Other car you know what and you know what being a copycat big is a liberal crime. Yeah, that's right
Next is real time with Bill Maher don't even get me started
This political talk show typically fit features a liberally slanted panel that routinely insults conservatives and religion
Mar is a well-known militant atheist, he kills people for that, who denies that
Jesus Christ ever walked to the earth in a manner similar to Holocaust denial.
Because I would say Jesus Christ walking the earth is probably on the same level
as the Holocaust, right? Yeah. Ignoring historical accounts, spiritual evidence,
and even archaeological evidence of his existence. How do you ignore spiritual
evidence? It's right in front of you. And archaeological. Plus he smears
conservative women in a vulgar and sexist manner but receives no
controversy whatsoever for it. Let's change that folks. He has even been known to the
dreaded n-word to refer to black conservatives and never came under fire
by the rest of the liberal media who claims to be against racism so this guy's
using the dreaded n-word on TV. I think they meant to say he has even been known
by the dreaded n-word. Oh I don't think oh yeah true he did call himself that one
time yeah oh yeah so they also have they so it's not just TV shows it's not just
TV shows they also dip into some some some music right and they say here in
addition these songs are cons are these songs a conservative has to be careful
to avoid as they pretend to have their values at heart but are deceitfully
liberal ah okay so these are deceitfully liberal songs starships by Nicki Minaj a
A song going to the beach and wasting money on drugs, smoking and alcohol.
Basically just getting high and partying.
Nothing more liberal than wasting money.
That's right.
Born in the USA by Bruce Springsteen.
This is an example of subliminal propaganda.
The song seems patriotic but is in fact anti-American,
tricking anybody unfortunate enough to hear the song.
Even Ronald Reagan, may he rest in peace,
was notoriously tricked by Springsteen into playing the song.
Contains a racial slur towards Asians.
What the hell?
So even Ronald Reagan Bruce Springsteen took advantage of poor Ronald Reagan whose mind was turning into complete oatmeal
Yeah, and he and he made him like this song
By the end of his life only knew how to eat jelly beans, yeah
I do love jelly beans, but that's another topic for another debate
We're gonna have a tribute debate very sexy. So they like these are some songs that they like - so this is tribute by Tenacious
Comedy single, but it's also a very popular song about overcoming Satan and alludes to many other Christian themes such as heaven and hell
I hate Satan. Yeah, I'll say it right now. So yeah Jables and KG
Frap that dratting bastard. Yeah, which bastard is okay, cuz that one's in the bottom. Yeah
What else is over here room room by Charlie XCX
Now this is written by a true American patriot straight as an arrow
Yeah, an ode to American car culture and the American dream under capitalism anyone who works hard enough can eventually buy a lavender Lamborghini or a bubblegum
pink
And charlie xdx as many people know in American of an American born American patriot
Uh-huh, she's a true American patriot. Yeah, she sings this song. I don't care. I love it
Yep, she sees the Declaration of Independence or the Dead Sea Scrolls. She says you know
Exactly. She said look just like that
Here's some of the worst liberal movies.
Oh, this is an essay. So this is a...
These are all individual essays.
...something somebody made for class.
Alright. Note.
We at Conservapedia do not care if a movie is considered a classic or that it is a famous movie that many have nostalgia for.
If it has liberal elements and/or the creators of a certain movie had some liberal agenda in mind when crafting the story's narrative, we call it out.
it out. Just because people love movies does not mean that Hollywood isn't trying to push
a liberal agenda with them. While a good amount of great conservative films are produced every
year, Hollywood continues to produce films that attempt to normalize and aggrandize amoral
lifestyles and liberal bias. Below is a list of some of the more outrageous examples. So
here's some liberal movies for you.
Alright, let's check these out.
Alright, number one. Milk. Sean Penn portrays openly homosexual politician Harvey Milk in
this biography.
That's what the movie's about?
Well, that's all it says under the description.
Okay.
The next is Billy Elliot.
This British film, now this is a crime.
This British film stars a boy who represents the homosexual agenda
by wanting to be a ballet dancer rather than play sports.
Wow.
There are very poor family values as the family is constantly cursing at one another.
Disgusting.
So this kid is so gay that he'd rather do ballet
than play football.
And sit out there and lead with his head in a peewee football.
Wow.
Right? What's wrong with you?
Maybe he's trying to infiltrate ballet from the inside and take it down once and for all.
So that might be maybe a...
That could be a good spy thriller.
I actually think we should produce that.
Take down male ballet.
Or just all ballet.
All ballet.
Yeah, all ballet.
Things pretty leftoidly.
Philadelphia, homosexual agenda setting trauma.
Really glorifies the homosexual lifestyle.
It glorifies the homosexual lifestyle while also being named after one of the first cities
in the country.
You know what they did?
The reason why they did that is so that when you Google, it's like one of those posts on Reddit,
they were like, "Make this named Philadelphia so when you Google Philadelphia you see this sickly AIDS patient instead of the Liberty Bell."
You see this gay stuff?
I just saw this leftist news report on TV and this is disgusting. It's homosexual and Philadelphia related.
But apparently the homosexual community, they have started a petition.
they want to replace the Liberty Bell with the Tickly Balls.
No.
Interesting.
I thought it was the puberty smell.
No.
Which they love.
Which they love the smell of puberty.
They do like it.
They love the smell of Axe chocolate, which by the way, do not put that on.
No, don't put it on.
A true patriot does not put on that.
No sir.
A true patriot puts on Old Spice Fiji.
Yeah, and Electric Shave.
Yeah.
Or just classic Old Spice.
Hey, you know what?
Water.
Yeah, you don't really need I mean you can God have you a smell I have to wear I have to wear deodorant
And why some because of some gland problems?
Mmm, I don't have any glands yeah because gland problems because I was trying to go away and probably eating preservatives
And you know that are bad for you
We are all on an army does I'm on a complete carnivore diet at this like I've been making a lot of these videos
Of what I eat in a day one meal a day
For pizza Friday and yeah, I love pizza Friday. Yeah, pizza. Here's a you don't need to wear
Any kind of deodorant no, and you don't need to eat vegetables no
Okay, so here's what there's one last one on this slide. I believe which is
Jackass the movie essentially a montage of ridiculous stunts and pranks with no coherent story
That's if it had a if it had a plot line. Maybe they'd be yeah
- Is it so hard to add a straight romance
in the middle of that?
- I have never watched Jack Frapp,
but I can tell just from the clips I've seen
on Conservatube, which is a website that I'm subscribed to.
- Go check out Conservatube.
- $25 a week.
- Yes, sir.
- Great, great videos.
They have some actually really great stuff debunking
some of the stuff they do
and why that wouldn't be possible.
- Wow.
- I wish we were in my debunker.
Well, we are right now.
We're in debunker right now.
- We are in debunker.
- So here's Bad Santa and Bad Santa 2.
This insult to the sacred holiday of Christmas
features gratuitous coarse language, sexual escapades, drunkenness, and the main plot
involving a con man posing as a mall Santa so he and his dwarf accomplice can rob the
mall safe.
It was bad enough that critics panned Disney for allowing the trashing of a cultural icon
like Santa Claus, as well as even then Disney CEO Michael Eisner, to be disgusted with the
resulting film, acting as one of the main reasons for Miramax being cut loose from Disney
alongside Kill Bill.
This sequel follows the already revolting Bad Santa.
Miramax, which distributed this movie as well as its predecessor, was acquired in 2016 by
Belm Media Group, which is owned by Islamic propaganda channel Al Jazeera.
What?
Oh my god.
And that's what, you see that movie, you can tell.
You're smelling the Islamicism all over it.
Yeah, because Miramax was an incredible company.
Yes.
Miramax was so great, and you know what, you can tell that they're smearing all this Islamic
propaganda and bad Santa.
They named the character Herman Merman to make fun of white people's names.
That's right, disgusting.
literally named the movie after Santa being bad yeah yeah bad Santa is yes I
bet Santa is bad when you're in the Middle East you're eating if you say
food and you say you know what say it fast think about think about the Muslim
agenda here bad Santa's tomb that's in it - my god that's in his tomb they want
to see bat they want to see Santa entombed yeah that is all and you know I
don't want to say that you know I don't I don't listen to I don't listen to rap
and hip-hop you know thank you but I will say yes Santa's bad bad meaning good
like damn oh okay all right yeah yeah yeah yeah like darn I was basically enough of
a different song Godzilla liberal and homosexual director Roland Emmerich turns
Godzilla into a girl and enforces the idea military does more damage than
Godzilla see and I hate when that idea is enforced yeah that the military does
more damage than God's not right it's not true
It's not true.
Godzilla's bad, but the military's way worse, right?
Yeah.
No, the military's better.
Godzilla literally has knocked over a building before?
He's stepped on people.
It's disgusting.
And Godzilla's not a human.
Anyway, basically--
This movie also contains--
I don't know if you guys know a certain actor
by the name of Broderick.
And he has portrayed a character who
thinks it's cool to skip school.
And he killed two people with his car.
And acts like a total frat head and gallivant around town
and disrupt the affairs of working people.
- Yeah, in terms of skipping school.
- In terms of people with this car, in real life.
- In terms of skipping school, I'll skip the public school,
go straight to the home school for me.
- Yeah. - Thank you.
- Paul. - Yeah, trust me,
if Ferris Bueller was at a charter school,
he would not be skipping a damn day.
- No, sir, he'd get hit by a cattle prod.
Paul, 2011, this extraterrestrial rescue mission
could have been a harmless comedic tribute
to the science fiction film genre.
Yeah, if it didn't portray Christians in the military
as close-minded idiots while depicting atheists
played by godless writers and co-stars Simon Pegg and Nick Frost,
who support extramarital sex, homosexuality, and mind-altering drug use
as the only sensible people,
Pegg and Frost have explicitly stated that one of the movie's main messages is
that there is no God, and anyone who believes in him is an ignorant boob.
Oh my goodness. Can you say a different word there? An ignorant frap,
they're saying. And to compare, and to call
somebody a mammary as an insult.
It's disgusting, because first of all, if I'm not married to you, I don't want to see those
things, you know what I mean?
And you're not even calling me...
And if I am married to you, one night a year, and only for our annual baby.
Yep, annual baby, and when I'm done, I'm saying, "Booyah!" Just like that. Just like God says
to do.
I say cha-ching.
My well is dry.
Oh, nice. Lucky you. You don't have to do all that.
No, I just sit at home, I twiddle my thumbs.
And here's one of the most disgusting communist leftist movies ever made.
Barnyard the original party animals.
First of all, what the hell's wrong with god damn Hollywood?
You're telling me that the animals on the farms are partying.
I guess so.
Having unprotected premarital sex.
So let's see what's a pig and a cow.
Set on a barnyard where animals speak and behave like humans in the absence of real humans.
This Lion King clone stars a bull who witnesses his father die after being wounded by coyotes.
Yeah, 'cause that's normal to have a dead dad.
Then gradually accepts the responsibilities that come with being the leader of his animal community.
Nevertheless, Barnyard accepts disorderly conduct because the animals still party recklessly,
even with a serious, dedicated bull in charge.
Plus, it portrays humans as either ignorant or stupid and persecutes coyotes for being carnivores.
The neurotic ferret Freddy goes to liberal lengths to avoid temptation to eat his rooster friend by becoming a vegetarian.
Disgusting.
Not only that, but the bulls lack horns and have female udders, and there are brief scenes referencing alcohol and gambling.
The boy cows have udders.
Okay, first of all, at least show what comes out of those.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not—listen, I'm a conservative first, but I'm also, like, interested in anatomy, right?
I want to understand how it works.
Make those cows human.
Come out of that this this movie should have had an entirely Hugh cow cast yeah
And I think that's the worst part here is it says if they portray humans as either ignorant or stupid
We've got to be the most leftist thing
This is also I mean this this needs this it uses CGI which is literally a tool of deception
Which is essentially makeup yeah, which no, thank you. It's computer deception makeup made by these these literal computer geeks who sit all day
They type like this
Bill Gates Bill Gates Steve Jobs Steve Jobs, you know
While I'm over here Mitt Romney Mitt Romney, you know, it's writing with a quill what conservative getting it? Okay
Well, that's not what they're doing though, you know, that's what I know cuz that's that's CGI for me
Oh, we know for you. Okay. So these computer nerds are sitting there drinking yerba mate
Right or or coffee urine urine mate. Yeah the urine of their mate
Yeah, they have a male mate who makes a cup every morning, and they drink it like hot coffee
And you know and you know that your Bermuda is actually filled with phytoestrogens that I know that and boobs yeah
And I'm fighting off estrogen every day of my life living in this goddamn girl country
Yeah, what's next the secret world of Arrietty Japanese anime film is about a tiny tiny homeless family that steals from regular people
So I'm tired of these
These little homeless people so this whole the whole movie basically saying hey if you're small enough and homeless enough
You can take whatever you want from a guy's working family. Yeah, how's wrong with them? It's not right. No. Thank you
Get that frap out of my face. This wig is getting pretty itchy
I might look a little bit like a reidy's cousin at the yeah, I think I'm gonna be real with you
I'd say that's why I took it off
You as a trick what else is here that might have been the end. I don't know is it the end
Yeah, that's it. I mean that's it for conservapedia for me.
Wow. I mean that's enlightening.
I mean it's enlightening in that I liked it, but it's not enlightening in that I already
knew all and believed all of that.
I'd like to send Enlightening Bolt into the United States Congress to destroy every Democrat
who works there.
There's an album cover you might like.
Okay, let's check it out. Go see the Patreon. We're going to upload 3D printing schematics
for an assault rifle.
Yeah, hey and all I want to say about the Patreon, I guess want people to Google what holiday
it is on Saturday.
Oh yeah.
What world holiday.
Oh yeah, we got some videos coming up on Saturday.
I mean maybe you can even Google it right now and just show people what holiday it's
coming up in.
There will be a special episode.
And also from this episode on.
November 19th.
From this episode on we might be engaging in the kayfabe again.
Right, yeah.
We might be going back into the kayfabe.
Okay, so that's not the one I meant.
But this one is actually, you know what?
That's even better.
We're gonna celebrate that too.
Yes sir. See you then.
There's Jubio.