Podcast about list. This ain't your grandma's podcast.
Hey douchebag, suck my twat.
And, I said, "Hey douchebag, quit being a f*cking twat."
Welcome to Douche FM. You're listening to three biggest twats in the civic brain.
Uh, you know what? I think I'm a douche.
Who thinks there's a douchebag present?
Do you guys think twat is better or dash?
Ow, I hit my douchebag.
I was douching for about an hour and it didn't even come out clear.
And your mom's a douchebag, douchebag.
Yeah, and I said, "Your mom's a douchebag, douchebag."
My twat was too small to have sex.
Should we just make it a rule that we start every episode by one of us going
"Woo!" or "Uh-huh!"
That's how you go.
We used to start, I used to just sing.
I've been practicing my singing a lot lately.
Well, you can't say something like that and not prove yourself.
You have your song, your famous song.
So go ahead, sing your song. What do you got?
Twinkle, twinkle little star
terrible. You are an awful singer. That is- I'd like to see you do better then. Yeah.
Twinkle twinkle little star. No. What I wonder what you are. You didn't even get the words right.
When you're up there in the sky you make me feel so right all summer long.
Twinkle twinkle little star. You are getting worse every time dude. I'm doing
well the thing I am a... I don't know what happened but I'm legit crying. He's crying.
Okay first of all I made him cry with my music. Second of all I'm a chameleon. I
sing whatever style I want. That was... Twinkle twinkle little star. Oh my god
and he's a rapping star. Twinkle twinkle little star. That's like kind of a kid
rock style. Exactly. Any style. Yeah. Give me a style. Classical.
Fuck you! That ain't cl-- this is classical if you're doing a classical version.
That's a conductor. That's not music. That's a type of hand singing.
The conductor is the musician. No, he's got a lady at the concerts now that's doing the fucking
hand singing. Oh, yes. You mean an interpreter for sign language? I don't know what the hell
you're talking about. Interpreting. That's the hand singing. It's hand singing. No it's not.
Then okay. She's singing with her hands. What the fuck are they doing? They're doing that.
Here's the thing man. Why, how many deaf people go into concerts and they're like,
yeah. You know what I'm saying? Probably enough. Yeah. You think a lot? I think a good amount.
There must be some if they're spending money on a hand singer. I guess you're right but like
what how, I just, I guess I'm just curious at what point. Well they're just like you and me.
They just can't hear a fuck. Oh, I guess they're not like you. But what we can hear is the that's I think the hand singers
For people who come with your plugs. Yeah, that's true
I don't want to damage my hearing but I want to understand what I'm saying
Yeah, I fucking love like I was at a I was at a show on Sunday
There was like there's a car like deer doing a comedy show, but they need those guys at stand-up shows. Yeah. Yeah
We need somebody we need a sign language
Like the whenever they sell like earplugs at the bar. It's like a music venue. That's yeah comedy
Yeah, so it's my favorite thing to do is just go up to the bartender and ask for the earplugs. Yeah favorite thing
It's so funny. Oh
Yes, I just connected the two things yours at first
I thought you're just for saying you like to bite your plugs
Yeah, it's funnier than anything they would say on stage yeah, I wear I'd probably wear them when you're up there no you bombing
Go up there. I'm that much anymore you go up there, and you just eat shit. I said that much anymore
it's being humble being honest okay pretty often but not that much anymore
there we go I like that that's yeah you know type of honesty you get on this
fucking show I've had a real bad bomb and I'm and I'm trying to think the last
time I ate total shit one time I was in a show of like five people that's not
even a bomb you know a bomb the bombs the real bad ones are when you're it's
it's like a packed fucking house and everybody's like,
this show's great, and you're like, yeah it is.
You go up and you just, oh, it's bad.
I opened for Ali Makovsky at Hideout, dude,
and oh, it was bad, bro.
It was so, so bad.
- She's the lady who goes on like Rogan and shit?
- Yeah, no, she's a great comic.
Dude, oh my God, it was bad.
- I think I remember this.
Yeah, Hideout, the one at, what was it now,
White Ball, right?
- Yeah, the one at White Ball, yeah.
Oh my God, it was so bad.
It was like one of those ones where I got off and Sam Mike was immediately like,
"You need a drink."
And I was like, "Yeah, yeah, I do."
I bummed really bad. I was opening for the count.
- Which one? - I kind of fucked it up.
You never told us this.
Well, because I went up there and I was doing...
I mean, I kind of didn't...
This was back in my days when I didn't really know how I was supposed to do shit.
- Yeah. - I was doing numbers before the count.
- You dumbass. - You buried him.
- You stole his material. - And everybody in the crowd was like,
we'd are not here for you doing it and you are not familiar with his act
not that's a thing to i was so did i i i i don't even know how i got in that
situation beyond as up there now is like
five ten twelve
nearly
that's not even the right fucking or he does it is i know i was trying to mix it
up you know i was i was into all he was doing his own he's doing all county
albright county that go up and i was like after you it's like you know like
all this is why he fucking crushes yeah exactly and in the snow and he came up
up and he came up he honestly he came up the first thing he said that fucking guy
room erupted. Oh my he didn't even have to make a joke. He just said that fucking
guy and then one yeah three. God I came close to killing myself with the last of
his own material. He does yeah it's kind of endearing you know it's super
endearing. It's the worst part about it. Was he like was he cool backstage or
anything or is he like he was really nice beforehand really yeah and then I did
I did not see him after because I left.
- Oh, you were too embarrassed.
- I was so embarrassed, dude.
- It's raining out, you go to an Irish restaurant
to get a shepherd's pie, you eat it by yourself.
- That's exactly what I did.
How did you know?
- I've done that a few times.
- That's how you, if you bomb real bad,
you go eat a full shepherd's pie.
- This is if anything bad happens.
- I eat a full shepherd's pie, six glasses of Guinness.
And then I throw it all up. - Well, that's like
a two glass of it all up.
- 'Cause I have bulimia.
- How do, people pretend that,
people pretend that Guinness is like a tough guy beer.
like 60 calories. It's cuz it's so dark. Yeah it is dark. It's a beer that has like
actual flavor in it so that's why people are like yeah you know. Irish. It's actually the
flavor beer. I'm sipping, I'm drinking a beer slowly because I'm actually in
control, the alcohol doesn't control me. It comes out of the same fucking thing that the
nitro cold brew at Starbucks comes out of. There's nothing like cool about it.
I don't think I like, you know what, I don't like Guinness that much. Really? Yeah.
crucified yeah I like it with a like a dinner you know I don't care for it's too
dark yeah what do I want to do I want to look down and think I'm drinking oil
speaking yeah if I can't taste it this week a novelty over a glass again I wait
so if I want so I want to be aware if I have it in a big oil drum I think it's
oil I don't think so I don't want that especially when the drum is closed I
really are as like this weekend that tasted like coffee when after I told you
guys about this. Me and Noah were looking for like apartments and I accidentally
broke into someone's house. Did you just think that they were showing the apartment?
I heard you say you and Noah both said like yeah we
walked into somebody's house but what happened? Yeah, tell the story.
We're on the house hunt and I looked at this
website it said like open house this like Sunday the 8th 8 a.m. to 8 p.m. mm-hmm
and I was like oh okay so that must just be like like you can just go in you know
whatever there's gonna be a realtor there whatever you get the the spiral
sandwich exactly yeah so I we like open the we just buzz the place and we're
just like oh all right we'll just like that probably makes sense the realtor's
probably just like sitting in there waiting fucking people to show up yeah
Probably be like six people in here.
Just talking, walking around asking like, "Oh, what kind of,
does it get optimum or does it get five?"
And then, so we go in, go up like three stairs.
We're like, "Oh yeah, this moving in here will be a bitch.
It's like a three, four walk."
They went up three stairs.
Yeah, I know.
Literally, I was like, "I'm not going to say it."
Really?
Okay.
That's too stupid.
I'm not going to interrupt for that.
Jesus Christ.
The hallway was narrow.
I meant like, I meant that the hallway is narrow, whatever.
and then uh getting the fuck you remember like i almost like trying to move into my
current place like we almost got my neck split by the fucking next couch you were did not almost
ask joe like me and joe almost died six or whatever the laser was cutting down and it went like that
on my neck and it's a 20 000 pound couch yeah yeah bad purchase um so we need a new couch we opened
the door to the place and there's like a guy on his phone with his friend just like cooking like a big
sundae dinner and like the kitchen is like right at the door so I like poked my head and I was like
hello he's like what what's going on I was like is this the open house he said no boss that's not
here and then just shut the door on me and I was like oh shit oh wait no it's 3L oh my god 3L so
So then I open up 3L. It also unlocked, but it...
What the fuck is this apartment building? Everybody's got an unlocked door?
It's also unlocked, but it has like...
There... It's still fully, like...
I love when my door unlocks.
There's underwear on the person's table and shit.
Like, it was like, there is not an open house here.
I don't know, 'cause it's the right address. I went into the correct place.
But who fucking buzzed me in?
How did I get into this building? It's one of those ones that has like the...
I think most people, if somebody buzzes your number, they just click the yes thing.
Well you shouldn't do that.
Yeah.
Cause that's how you get traffic.
That's how you get a guy like Patrick in the house.
And I wanted to eat that guy's Sunday dinner so bad.
You should have just pretended, were you wearing this?
You should have pretended you were like a mechanic or something.
Yeah, I'm here to fix your dinner.
And then you unlock their window.
I'm a personal guy, I'm here to fix your plate.
There's been a leak reported in your dinner and I need to seal it up.
I'm the poison checker. I came here to check your food for poison.
I heard you're making a big Sunday dinner.
I'm from the city. Do you have a license to cook something that fucking delicious?
Can I see your Sunday gravy license, please?
I need to test your ragu. Was the guy not happy that you broke into his apartment and looked right at him?
No. And said, "Your house is open."
Well, why is his door unlocked? It was open. It was open. It is technically an open house, man.
Yeah. Yeah.
I could have
uh... claimed prima nocte
is that the one no manifest destiny not the whole guys fucking wife
i think it that that's a shit set
and i'm here to do pretty much
uh... is the prima nocte time
so you you not you don't want to do it
uh... so what he has been showing that there is a fucking got that mixed up
I'm gonna go freshen up in the bathroom while you finish your supper.
It's also so funny to be like a not like, this is a prima nocte, the thing is like the
king can do that, right?
Or whatever.
Yeah.
Like just like a random guy, because it's like, yeah, I'm too prima nocte.
I basically just read about prima nocte.
You don't know this, but I'm the king of this building.
I was just elected your king.
You got to let me in.
You should have voted.
Yeah.
You should have voted, man.
Homeowners association, we meet like three times a week.
And I mean, and also, I mean, while I'm here, I would love that you're tithe.
Yeah.
- You have to tie it, and give me your 10%.
I'll take 10% of that meal.
- 10% of that meal and all your furniture.
- If you don't mind me asking,
what's the deal on your dowry?
- Yeah, I would walk in, yeah, I'd walk in
and I would just take books and stuff off their shelves.
I'd be like, oh, and I want this painting.
I'm not gonna take your money.
I'm not that kind of king.
- I'm just gonna take your wife.
- I'm not gonna take your wife
and a few tasteful pieces of decor.
- Hey, shut up, I'm just doing prima nocte.
- I'm gonna look through your DVDs and see what's good.
Yeah, you don't want me to put sanctions on you, do you?
Because I'm not opposed to it.
Do you have DVDs or do you have Blu-rays?
I have both.
I don't have any physical media.
I was asking this guy.
Oh, you're still talking to this guy.
Okay, well, I was gonna tell him the guy.
I have both.
Oh, yeah, that works.
Yeah.
Yeah, I am not looking forward
to trying to find a new apartment here.
'Cause the one thing I do love
about looking for apartments here,
you're not, it's not x-ray.
How many times do we have to go over this?
You can't, you will not--
- Let me try though.
- No matter how many times you put--
- We know this way, Caleb.
- I have a green shirt on and it's green screened out.
No matter how many times you put your hand behind my--
- Oh, my hand is disappearing behind it.
Wait, go back to the other camera.
- You will not see your hand behind my body.
- Go back to the other camera.
- You are so stupid.
- No, the other one.
The third one.
- Wait, no, the other one.
Yeah, this one.
- My hand is disappearing behind him.
No, not this one.
No, okay, go back to the other one.
No, the other one.
- This is not good radio.
horrible because you won't switch to the one I want. You're giving up. I love when
you're looking... I've been looking at some apartments just casually, you know. I think
I'm a month to month, so I can move whenever. But I love when the real estate company comes
in to take the nice real estate photos and whoever lives there is clearly a piece of shit drug addict
and didn't clean anything. So it's like this beautiful big panoramic picture, but there's
a box of doughnuts and shit open, there's pizza everywhere.
Yeah, there's a pink couch there.
They're all running around.
I hate that, dude.
When it's a photo of the living room couch
for a new apartment.
And Bart's there.
It starts off as a single cell organism
that goes through all of evolution and then all of a sudden
they're sitting on the couch.
If I were a realtor, I would take the pictures
I would photoshop Bart in.
That'd be funny.
That would be the funny realtor.
This could be an apartment for a Bart.
Mm-hmm.
You could say, or Bart for scale.
Yeah.
You know?
Make him this big?
(laughing)
Yeah, he's a big--
This place is huge!
He's a centimeter tall.
Bart for scale.
'Cause nobody knows how big Bart is.
Yeah, exactly.
So if a place is really small,
you put Bart, pretend he's like five something, right?
And you like, or you put him like that kind of scale,
even though it's a six foot ceiling.
Yeah.
And then all of a sudden,
you're selling it.
Bart is 6'2". No he's not. He's 6'2" on the show. They're all giants on the show.
They're fucking not. Speaking of ceilings, my landlord has not fixed, there's three
holes in my ceiling from water damage. Bullet holes! He's ignoring my calls.
So Rupert, if you're listening, something very bad is gonna happen to you.
Allegedly. Allegedly? You're gonna hurt your landlord? Allegedly I will.
because my best friend Alex is upstairs right now he's got water in his room
from all the holes in his ceiling and he's not answering the call so you're
I'm gonna harm you allegedly and we why do you have holes in the
doing a character saying this yeah we're gonna be one of the most nothing things
you've ever said is that you're gonna hurt your landlord no I'm not gonna do
that oh okay all right you know I watched a bunch this weekend man I had a
my battery because I watch it. I I got really laughing at
it's a normal thing to say to your friend if they ask what they're what you
if you want to know what he
roasting
you're roasting the way he says on peanut butter baby. It's baby butter
baby says ah you said butter baby baby butter baby baby butter baby butter
baby. I watch a bunch of
now i think it's funny uh... i watch a bunch of videos this weekend the first
time of people uh...
shooting at each other
yet yeah i found a bunch of videos of people should each other
as a couple
something so interested in what i have to say i hate you leaning over like this
no stop it's not a good sound
you sound like a whole some kind of bovine now you're roasting
i said you sound like one of the uh... old no i'd love some roasted bovine
right now. Oh my god! Roasted bovine is good. I've been watching these videos of
people, there's all these videos where people like security camera footage of
people getting in gunfights and stuff. I was having the time of my life dude. Yeah.
Because it's videos where guys sit there at gas stations like 90% of them. They're
guys who are sitting there pumping gas and then they see, it's always in the
south, and they see like a guy they don't like and they pull out the biggest most
illegal gun you've ever seen in your fucking life. They shoot 500 bullets and
and they hit nothing, and then that's the end of the video.
But then I saw one where the people actually get hit
and they die.
- Yeah, that's not fun.
- That's not nearly as funny.
- Yeah. - You see the one--
- Why do people like those videos?
And then I told Noah about it,
and Noah's like, "You gotta watch this one."
And he sent me one of a guy
just getting his fucking head blown off,
and he's like, "Isn't that cool?"
Like, no! - Goddammit.
- Why do people like those videos?
- I'm gonna move in with him,
he's gonna be playing that on the fucking living room TV.
- Dude, he sent me one, it was like a guy,
like two it's like neighbors these two neighbors and they're getting in an
argument the guy's like fuck you neighbor man you fucking suck and they
guy what he's like fuck you and his wife's Aaron she's like fuck you too and
then the guy's like oh fuck me and then he kills both of them instantly whoa I
don't know if it's it's a snowy yeah old that they are on yeah yeah I saw one
anything girl he like executes the lady and I was like why then he goes back in
his house and he shot himself. So you've seen it? Yeah. And why are you not
like scarred? I am. It's scary. He's damaged. Do you know how damaged my ass is? Can you
imagine how terrifying it is to fucking die? Yeah. It's probably peaceful. Did you see the one
the one that everyone uh what's his name that guy Matt Walsh posted it and was
like there needs to be uh there needs to be like they need to be more lenient
when good guys kill bad guys and it's like a video of a dude just like unloading
a full clip onto it like a dude's just like waving a gun around in a restaurant and then
he like shoots it after the guy like he kicks his gun away and then like shoots him like
six more times it's just like oh this guy is like yeah that's like every good guy with
a gun is just a guy waiting to like kill somebody. I have such a good idea for a conservative
comedy sketch. What's that? Luke Skywalker. Holy crap I'm already in. Luke Skywalker he's
in a he's getting shot at by a stormtrooper he deflects the bullets runs up cuts off the
stormtroopers head liberal cops show up handcuffs oh my god right we need to get a
conservative daily wire sketch what if that's a great fucking idea
where I was going with that good I think I just got upset watching that here's
another one that you could do is they come out with a new Star Wars movie yeah
yeah and it's a guy you know it is a guy he sits on his knees and he prays a God
right? He's a real religious guy. He's a religious nerd. He prays to God
and he says, "Please let them make a new Star Wars movie." He goes to the movie and
they got Mark Hamill in a fucking wig, right? And he's got fake breasts and all
of a sudden he's some Luke... what's a girl version of Luke?
Luciana Sky... not a guy washer. Sky shopper. Yeah, Sky shopper.
that's good and he's a girl shopper and then so and yeah basically disney's
gone. Oh here's another one. Okay,
yoda oh shit. Yoda is teaching a class a college class. Oh fuck me. He's like
the force works this way, but it says it written reverse. This way the force
works. Yeah, I couldn't think of that that or he could say like and then okay
and then a young yoda girl. Oh God, college age yoda girl, smooth with a
nose piercing nose piercing.
And she says she says
don't think force works that way, but in reverse. Oh fuck me. Or maybe not
don't think that force works that forward.
That's a good point.
But yeah, well, maybe she's okay.
Maybe she's actually like me for force works that way.
it actually doesn't. Oh, that's good. And then Yoda's like, "Oh, me know lots about
force." That's how Yoda talks. And then, and then, handcuffs. Yeah. Oh, I was gonna
say. They say, "You tried to Yoda-splain." I thought this is gonna be a different,
well, first of all, imagine that video, "Good Guy with the Gun" video, where it's
the guy who's waving the gun around the restaurant, and then he comes up with a
lightsaber and just does that, right? Uh-huh. That's the, that, that video. That's good.
this one yeah Yoda is teaching its atheist professor Yoda oh fuck me oh no
and he's teaching his class he says real God is not I was yeah - yeah one brave
marine normal just why you are he stands up and he says real God is yeah and then
now that yeah yeah yeah he has head pops off and coins go everywhere exactly yeah
yeah maybe there could be one where all the liberals move to Tatooine and it
gets expensive to live there. See we do need that. They have
I want blue milk in my latte. And they open a coffee shop called Jawa Java. Oh my god.
They want blue milk. I can't have blue milk I can only have oat milk.
Droid milk. They would like droid milk. They probably think I'm a droid.
Yeah, oh my god, don't even tell me that my son would say that to me man. That would make
Yeah, well that's another just that's him also being a complete SJW you call me mom
My son is an SJW
But yeah, we would do so good at a conservative Star Wars
We need a conservative SNL dude. Yep. That's what we need. We need oh my god. Wait, wait, wait
This is it's the whole United States or genders. No, he's saying no. No, no, no, where is a conservative here?
He's in more
Fun of it. I have a really I have a really good one. I have a really good one
So the Mandalorian, okay, it's the Mandalorian. It's the scene where he takes his helmet off
Yeah, he's like dying and he takes his helmet off and then this this blue-haired lady with a piercing with piercings all over
tattoos up the neck gang tattoos shit gang tattoos yeah and she said and she
the second his helmet comes up she says put that helmet back on haven't you
heard about Darth Kovid oh my fucking god fuck oh my god is incredible that's the
thing about a lot of these people who wear masks you know who else wore masks
and then she's like this and she kills a line of babies yep here's here's what I
Yeah, we could do a whole we could do a whole thing. It's a it's a
Bakery a conservative normal conservative bakery that fucking won't make a gay wedding cake
Yeah, and then people are coming in and they're asking for gay wedding cakes and they all have masks on but they have like Jason
Voorhees masks or like
Mask like Jim Carrey mask on right? Yeah, what's that one? Maybe?
Yeah, man Halloween every other year take your mask off inside the store Halloween this year keep the mask on or you're going to jail
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- What the hell's going on there, man?
- It's like some kind of-- - And we're recording--
- It's like we went into an opposite world.
- This is 2020 right now,
and we're recording it in 2020.
- I think that Star Wars in 2020,
or was a long time ago, 2020 BC.
- Yeah, 2020 BC. - We could do--
- Yeah. - Way, a long time ago.
- We could do all sorts of conservative SNL stuff, I think.
- But mostly Star Wars. - I think that'd be really good.
We could do straight Stefan.
- I think it's just gonna be Star Wars.
- We could do an entirely straight Stefan,
where he talks about-- - I think Stefan
would not change in conservative--
No.
He might be right.
No, no, we would do straight Stefan and he'd be talking about different Dick's sporting
goods he went to.
He'd be like, "They had footballs and they had basketballs and they had basketballs,
footballs, and they had a golf ball and a golf club and they had swimming trunks that
were really long.
They went past your knees over there."
And I ate lunch and I ate dinner.
I didn't eat breakfast.
And then I ate lunch.
"I don't eat breakfast.
I'm doing intermittent fasting and I'm on the carnivore diet and I only eat honey, dairy,
meat and we go God that's some funny fucking conservative that's funny it's
true yeah can I do another Star Wars one a really short one yeah so it's Darth
Maul okay and he has his double lightsaber but he's like he has the two
but he's like rubbing them together and he's going like oh okay gay I didn't
know what I didn't know where this was going until you said he was gay and then
I thought it was fucking hilarious we did but I feel like that there yes still
one's the face tattoos too. Yeah. Cause those gay guys have facial gay gang tattoos.
All gay guys have face tattoos. Gay facial gang tattoos like nowadays people have.
We can do conservative good neighbor too. We'd be kind of a bad neighbor. I guess
it's just the opposite. Bad neighbor. And we'd do... Better neighbor. Better neighbor.
Yeah. Oh good homeowner. That's yeah. That is good. Good homeowner. Because you know
when they're saying good neighbor they're talking about an apartment building. Yep.
in some left away country.
- For sure, for sure.
- But we would be good homeowner
and there would be, what's a good neighbor sketch?
- Could do like Kyle interviews where he's talking normal.
- One of those ones where he smokes weed
but he's just smoking cigarettes and normal tobacco.
- Well that's just Chris.
- Yeah, he might be right.
- I think they covered all the bases there.
- Damn.
- God damn it, wait maybe they're already conservative.
- They are conservative.
- Crypto-conservatives.
God bless you good neighbor.
- Boys after a couple of good old boys.
- Yep, weekend update we could do.
Oh, that would be a really easy to put a conservative spin on.
Work week update.
Yeah.
Right?
And they'd be doing, what kind of stuff they'd be doing?
This week, liberals are taking an extra lunch break.
Yep.
During the day.
Blow that smoke off your mic, that was heat.
Oh my god.
Meanwhile, conservatives work the whole day through, nine to seven.
Yep.
Five days a week.
It all has to be about work weeks.
Oh yeah, fuck.
I fucked all my jokes up so the Dow
Actually makes a bunch of money. It makes everyone extremely happy. You know what I would love
The liberals are more concerned with the cow as they are Hindu. I guess this is just kind of Dennis Miller kind of stuff, huh?
Yeah, but it's about work weeks. Oh, you're right
You know what I would love to do what I would love to get on there at some point is having
Maybe a liberal could say something stupid and then the conservative could say you are the weakest link
think no, he could be like say brainless. That's good. Yeah, I really like that
term right yeah is being like say brainless. You really think that there's
a fucking sixty thousand genders yeah. I have a good joke a good one. That's all
about work weeks. All right conservatives are often seen working a nine to five
job. I'd like to see a liberal live to ninety five. That's all the drugs and
smoking and drink it and well drinking is okay. All the drugs and smoking is okay
Oh the drugs. Yeah. Speaking of drinking, I have something I promised I was gonna do.
Wait I have a joke. Okay do your joke, I'll pull it out. So this week I worked 40 hours
because I'm a conservative Republican. Meanwhile a Democrat family walked into
a liquor store and said that's that 40s hours. Yes. Of malt liquor and then they
sat around with no job. Yeah and my job, I'm a mall clicker. Yep. A mall clicker? I'm a
full-time, I'm a mall clicker. Get a real job like working Amazon Mturk on your
netbook like I do. Yeah. As a conservative. Or being a mall clicker. Or being a
clicker at a mall, whatever that could possibly mean. Is that like a clicker of
like you like how many people go into the mall? It's a mall clicker.
it's obvious. All right, what do you have here? I have, I found this on the on the way over here.
New energy drink called Blue Magic. It looks like an old energy drink. Can I hold it up to the camera?
Yeah, hold it up. Yeah, let me actually check, speaking of that, let me check the expiration
date on this. You're drinking it regardless. Yeah, it expired in 2022. You're gonna drink that no
matter what. All the way in 2022? That was almost a few days ago. Yeah, just October 2022. That's
That's not too bad.
- That's really not that long ago.
- And this is a whiskey flavored,
non-alcoholic energy drink.
- Uh-huh.
- So.
- It's called Blue Magic.
- Blue Magic, and look at this logo.
- The L-U.
- Of two dragons fucking.
- I don't think it's, I think it's a double-headed dragon,
like dragon tails, two heads are better than one.
- I think they could be fucking.
- They are having sex.
- What's wrong with you two?
You think every brother and sister--
- Look at the expression of the one on the top.
- The one has its tongue out.
- He's going like this.
- Yeah, and the other one has its tongue out.
I think that you two are reading into this a little much.
I think we'll all take a look and we'll all take a sip.
It says best served chilled.
I'm going to let you take a sip first and depending on your facial reaction, I may or
may not take a sip.
It certainly smells like whiskey.
Does it have legs?
Does it actually smell like whiskey?
Yeah, we need like a...
I don't know what that means.
Legs is when you put it in the glass and then it like, when it trickles down.
Does it have legs?
I don't have a glass to put it in.
that have what's one of those what's one of those little things you put
definitely smells it definitely smells like whiskey and by that I mean some
kind of gasoline I don't think it smells like whiskey gasoline and by that I mean
some kind of gasoline what are you eight years old smells like it smells like an
energy drink for the most I definitely can I can I detect a hint yeah of maybe
the smallest whiskey smell but I think it mostly smells like an energy drink
that matters the most here is the taste yeah which I would say with most things
that you taste yeah does it taste like
whiskey because it could be whiskey
flavor but also not have like can you
stop fucking running your mouth all
there goes yeah it does taste like
whiskey really yeah that tastes like if
you've got like a whiskey red bull at a
bar read the ingredients before I do
this yeah whiskey and third one is
carbon dioxide what I was I was reading
some of your ingredients either water
water sugar carbon dioxide, so yeah, gas it fucking like to make it bubbles in
no sit all to make it bubbles.
I just a little ingredient sidebar something funny. I saw on an ingredients.
I was I read the ingredients of a sour patch kids bag and the first ingredient
is sugar as you can guess. Oh, you know what the second ingredient was bloody
tell me it was inverted sugar. Oh, I've seen I've heard of that reverse sugar.
Yeah, is that the sugar that's on the outside?
It's simple syrup.
All right, here I go.
It's my turn to try this weird drink.
Okay, go ahead.
It doesn't taste like whiskey.
It tastes a little bit like a whiskey ginger.
It tastes like some kind of berry.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not bad.
I kind of like it.
It's all right.
Now you have to try.
Yeah, I will.
I'm just looking at it.
Best serve chill.
I serve and I chill.
Yo, you do.
You do serve.
I serve.
Look at my green shirt. I see Joe McHale right through me. God I wish I was like him.
Yeah this is just an energy drink. Well it's whiskey flavor. I don't think it really has a flavor.
Yeah it's not it's whiskey flavor and it's distributed in the Bronx. It was
made in Vietnam. Mm-hmm. Alright I'm gonna have one more sip and then I'm seriously
done with this bullshit. Yeah. So something got in my tooth from that. Huh?
Some kind of there's debris in that I'm not getting more of that. There's debris all right
I'm not gonna. That was my back wash. I don't let a dirt in my mouth
Why well we could also we could also drive up to their their address here drive after having a sip of that bullshit
That's true drunk as hell right now. I'm fucking going crazy. You look honestly
I'm so boy is shit with your awesome hair up. I fucking hate him put it up put it up right now
What do you mean? Oh?
Yeah, like oh my god. Oh my god. You're so you're gonna make me cry this
I'm here cuz you put your hair up, and it looks flames
bro
Don't tear I hate them. I fucking hate that you know what will make you not cry. You're not tearing up
You're tearing it up. Look at how you know to make you not cry right now
What's that is we did a tour of food at a tours of our house?
This is yo, motherfucker. Welcome to MTV Cribs
We're your three hosts Cameron Caleb and Patrick and today. We're about to show you our crib. Yeah
Do we have we don't have an intro cute or anything? No?
The Cribs intro I've never seen
Prince it's like blueprints, and it just says MTV Cribs, so maybe like Jubio could like found the piece of debris
This is plastic that was in that look at this just this came out of that just look up MTV Cribs
- Crib's intro. - That's a hair.
- This, this little piece of plastic sand.
It's right there.
- Well, that's where the flavor is.
- Maybe.
- Yeah, we can just splice that crib intro in.
- Yeah, this is basically a crib.
It looks a lot like my house, I'm gonna be real.
- Yeah.
- It looks beautiful.
Who wants to go first with their crib?
Patrick, you wanna show your crib off?
- I'll show off my crib first.
- All right, and I guess we're in VR
looking at each other's cribs.
- Yeah, so this is my crib right here.
- Whoa!
I live in an apartment in Bushwick. One of these new ones.
Oh my God, this thing's sick.
One of these new big glass buildings.
I like the style of it.
Yeah. These style of buildings are actually some of the most affordable and
actually most goaded.
And what's the address of it?
The address is, um, I think it's 12 something
DeKalb. That's what this is in Bushwick. It's off of DeKalb.
This looks dope, man.
This actually is fucking fire cause there's so many amenities and rooftop party
time amenities I love that you can't tell if it's a hospital a school an apartment
complex or some kind of office that's like an ideal oh yeah that's the type of
building you should live in now let me see let me show you what this let me show
you what my apartment looks like in here right so I need to scroll the next thing
here is my living room okay so what and Caleb seems to be blocking a piece of
art that I bought with his head because you can see on the on the hold on go
back to that camera right here that these by my pixelated art pieces right there
and that's just another piece of my pixelated art right there
Pat what's going on outside right now what Oh nothing nothing's happening
outside nothing yeah this is just a normal ass day in Bushwick outside okay
as long as Eric Adams is the mayor and he won't fucking fund the NYPD that's
true yeah but because the NYPD got defunded I got this awesome art piece
right here yeah wait which one this one right here what you're not pointing
anything oh that one okay did you think you were me for a second you pointed
behind no I thought you'd be would have had the sense to go back no he's not so
smart mm-hmm all right now let's go on to the next yeah I want to see the
room was that this is my living room this is my bedroom oh what happens what
do you mean magic yeah what is that real relations with my girlfriend here fuck I
i'd be fuckin and suck it in here
what the hell are you talking about? my girlfriend and my hoes
you have hoes and a gia? i got hoes too and i got spinners on my bed
i almost thought that was a jaws movie poster
nope that is left shark describe your room
these are some art pieces i made
these are all... you made them? yeah i made them in adobe illustrator
this one says dance like left shark
This is a Jaws poster that instead of Jaws it says Left Shark.
Yes.
Left Shark is my spirit animal.
And #LeftSharkSwag.
Now that's fun.
This is a character I invented.
Left Shark?
Is that your OC?
My OC.
That's original content just by you?
Yep. Uh-huh.
See I'm wearing my blue Left Shark jacket.
Whoa, you are.
This is the jacket I made to look, see?
Yeah, it looks...
You do kind of look like Left Shark.
Do I look like Left Shark right now?
right now yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so as you do you fucking paint put
up all your artwork in your own room so you're in here on that show on my hose
always in the bed right now look at Wow you I show my hose my art and I say I
made this so you bring girls back you bring hose back you bang them you bang
sluts and that's the magic and they look up and they see that and they say oh my
That must be original content. Yep Wow and that's where the that's what the magic is on creatures love that
Oh, she's in hose seeing my fucking Lucy in my room. They love when you have OC. Yeah, all right
Let's go to the let's go to the kitchen now, and this is another
Original artwork
You made that artwork
So it looks like it's some kind of
Metal like plate metal and it says get oh my god. Wait. There's a fire in my kitchen. It says ghetto gaggers
Yeah, that's not important right now. There's a fucking fire
Well, we know
Yeah, I don't remember that from something. I don't know what that is either. This is a piece of art that I bought
It's made out of rebar and gold. It's kind of beautiful. Yeah, pretty. It's a bit blingy for my taste
Yeah, well, you know, it's crib. So I had to do it up blingy style. Yeah, I'm more classy than that
And then I want to show you this last room in my house here, so this is my secret door
Oh, I love a secret door. Yeah, nice Cara Delevingne's
Architectural digest video nope she has a vagina door that is messed. Oh, yeah, and I'm
Do you have to rub it to go into it? Yeah?
Yeah, you probably smell it to fucking get it to open yep, so we're gonna. We're gonna take
Before you go through it yeah, you probably have to walk around fucking fine trying to
I want to go through this door, but it's too dry. Yeah. Yeah, that's right, but I'll go in anyway
Which is not a problem
Yeah, no, no. All right. Let's take a let's take a step right into this door real quick, bro
I I do say I do have to say like a seeing if I see a dry
Pussy in like a porn video. I stopped fapping. Yeah, that keeps me from fapping pretty fast
And I've been into fapping lately.
Really?
This is supposed to be an auto play.
I've been over...
I mean, not to ruin the bit.
What is this?
Harry Potter, Gryffindor ambiance?
This is in my secret room.
Wow, it's kind of sick.
It is cool.
Yeah.
So y'all, fapping or sexy times?
It's going to be fucking fapping for me.
I've been into fapping lately.
I really like fapping a lot more.
Yeah.
What do you guys like to...
Fapping to a naughty video.
Do you guys like to fap to...
You guys like to fap to NSFW stuff or more people going wild?
I do like NSFW.
I like NSFW OC.
Oh yeah, that's good.
It's not made by some fucking trillion dollar studio like MCU style.
Yeah, for sure.
MCU style naughty videos.
I hate naughty videos.
Naughty photos on the other hand.
Naughty gifs I quite like.
I do like.
I love a naughty gif.
to a naughty gif. That's right. Here's another part of my room. Here's the thing, I hate
when you're watching a porn, the gifs are the best because there's no sound. Sometimes
you're watching a naughty video and the girl's like "a naughty video" and you're saying,
you're talking to the video, "oh behave video" and then the girl sounds like fucking Gilbert
Gottfried or some shit, kills my boner. "PUT YOUR PENIS IN MY ASS!" Yeah, and I'm going
- And then, "Sound off, please," and a gif.
- I want you to fuck my butt!
- I'm watching a gif, and I see the girl mouthing.
- Yes.
- Those upstairs are gonna hear that.
- Yeah, they're gonna be like,
"Gilbert Gottfried's downstairs getting fucked."
- He's alive!
He's alive!
- Fucking fucked, holy shit.
- He's punching the ass so bad.
- I see the girl mouthing, and I'm doing my own voice.
I'm going like, "Oh yeah, put it in my ass."
- Wait, why?
- So it sounds sexy.
- You sit on the, you're telling me,
you sit on the toilet seat.
- Yeah, or on the--
and you walk or on the my pillow on the floor on the my pillow on my pillow on
the floor. What's your favorite place in your house to fap? I really closet. I
like to fap with my back against the front door so no one could come home.
Yeah, I get it. See me. That is good. I was talking to somebody about this
share under the doorknob and I sit in the chair and I fap really hard and it
makes the chair go "Eek! Eek! Eek!" Everyone in the lobby of my building can hear it.
Everyone can hear it just going "Oh, oh no."
And when the chair breaks, they just hear the sound of like a Jenga tower falling down every day.
I keep breaking chairs by leaving the door.
And then I just hear like a clattering noise of me going "Oh!"
"What the hell's going on up there?" "I'm a stuntman and I'm practicing."
I'm practicing on my fucking clothes. I'm not fapping. I was talking to somebody about this the other day.
Somebody told me that they were at their parents' house and they were fapping,
and they were like, but their door doesn't have a lock on it over Christmas.
They were fapping. Getting caught as a grown man.
And they were just saying like, "Yeah, it sucks. I'm worried about getting caught by your mom or your grandma or whatever."
And I was saying about, do you think it's worse to get caught masturbating completely,
just like in the middle, masturbating, you had no idea they were coming?
or is it worse to like hide it or something but for whatever reason you
can't hide that you have like a huge boner and so your mom walks in it just
looks like you're sitting there watching TV with a boner hmm probably jacking it
but like when you as a mom you hope that you your brother or your son faps you
hope that he faps don't put your mic down like I'm crazy I guess I'd rather
my mom not genuinely for us you got so lost in describing what this is no I
didn't I did you else you were getting so like but your mom walks in she's in a
nightdress and you're fucking and you have the biggest boner my god yeah right
and she's just like why is my son sitting there with a boner for no you
you're like no no that's a bug yes fly swatter and you're like mom I have to
tell you something she gets the bug assault gun out I was I was fapping mmm
10 naughty videos it is better to do the girls voice I think when you're that
good at it will you come to the girl voice on my videos that I watch my naughty
video naughty video all right show us a house pet this is it that was it yeah
that was it you have a small hey man I have an apartment in Bushwick half of
your fucking house is a secret room yep well there's different there's different
angles of the secret room there's tons oh my god yeah you have a bloody amazing
secret room huh it's bloody brilliant all right well it looks so small on the
outside but then you get into the secret room and it's like oh my god it's like a
whole other apartment. Well gee that was MTV Cribs. Oh fucking wait we still got
two more houses to go to. No they put three people in every episode of Cribs. Let's check out, now we're ready to check out my
fucking house. Sounds good to me. Caleb's house. Is this a room? Or is this not your room?
This is the title for my house. Go next. Is this the outside? So welcome to my hood. You
remember that song? Yeah. Welcome to my hood. Everybody's fucking cool. Gangsters
and the gangsters Bloods and Crips are all here. Welcome to my hood. Welcome to my
hood. Go next. Here, if you come to my hood and oh yeah I live in I live in
Fart. It's like right next to Saldogi and Syud. You can't really see Syud but it's
over there. I live in Fart. Have you heard of Saldogi? No. Yeah, Saldogi and my penis.
- You're so good at annoying me.
- I was gonna do that.
- Yeah, true, do you know Dogi?
- Yeah, have you seen Fart?
- I mean, Bofa.
- No, go next.
This is my house.
You can't miss it, it's got giant impact font
that floats above it that says,
"The perfect house doesn't exist, dot, dot, dot."
As you can see, it's about 50% house, 50% garage.
- Yeah, we're about in the way to see that garage, Pat.
- I am a bit of a car guy, okay?
I know you guys know that about me.
don't kiss each other please cuz I that's not allowed in my apartment house
uh... it's dangerous to do a fart maybe
which way do I go to show this garage?
don't worry about it it's a garage go next
uh... so let's open up the door into my house hey you're in the way get out of the way of the door
just have the camera on me it's my fucking house open the door and let's
see what's inside my house
looks like we interrupted
interrupted Jim Norton
he's just sitting right there at the entrance
heads was a gem
and and all my name are a
don't mind you know or and he hangs out sometimes
at my house and welcome to my house that's cool right let's go next what's
up uh... so here's my kitchen and my pantry
this is where i do all sorts of stuff on watching adam regis you know i'm
I'm watching Kenji, I'm watching Joshua Weissman on a loop, on mute.
This was the big feature when I talked to the architect.
I said, "Here's what I want.
I want a one-to-one recreation of the guys' grocery game set directly in my kitchen, and
I want competitors running around doing their thing.
Let's check on one of those competitors.
Press next for me."
Oh my God, it's Jim Norton again.
What's he making?
He's making scrambled eggs.
I can't wait to have those.
Oh my god, I'm hungry for some scrambled eggs.
- You can't really see very well,
but they look really good right here.
- They look delicious.
- Look at how good those eggs look.
- They're still in the shell.
That's a--
- They're probably scrambled inside though.
- He likes them rare.
Here's my bathroom.
- Oh, this is fire.
- This is a fire-ass bathroom, is it not?
- Good bathroom.
- So here's what I like.
I have only a urinal.
I put my turds in it too.
I just thought, I was like, you know how I always wanted it?
It was a fucking urinal.
Everything's mechanic themed.
got the old mechanic newspapers on the wall we have that that soap that Patrick
got for the office for some reason that washes off the oil which by the way I
would like to why the hell did you get a fucking five gallon thing of that of
mechanic soap okay at the time it didn't make sense but then we started building
a set in here and you're getting paint on your hands all the time don't slap
this like that was a great point it was a good I didn't ask did it work out I
I asked why did you get it in the first place?
- Because when I lived in the dorms in community college,
my roommate had it, because my roommates were--
- He was an oil man.
- They were both mechanics.
- Oh, okay.
- And they were like, "I like this."
- And I liked, yeah, it made my hands real.
If you don't do a day's work and you use that shit,
that pumice stone makes your hands soft.
- Hmm, I don't like it 'cause it smells like nothing.
So we're in the bathroom.
Go ahead and click next.
Oh my God, wait, Jim! - Jim!
jim's in here some so sorry jim we interrupted you you're standing there
in your underwear you get ready for showers something
that's my bad buddy
so let's go over to the living room all you know i got to know don't know that
it is a little bit here it got a lot like your i'm and i got my office and
if patrick a move i got my office over there to the left
uh... that's where i do a lot of my that's right you all my work
uh... have my my framed uh... pictures of bridges
those are some bridges. Get his cock out of your mouth right now. I didn't have
anything in my mouth. You're so gullible. Again, I like to keep that whole...
I like to keep that whole kind of car theme moving throughout the whole house, right?
Yeah. Cars are cool. They're fucking badass, no? I love all sorts of cars.
Cars is dope. Mitsubishi Eclipse.
That thing is badass. Toyota, Honda, Ford, Volkswagen.
I was about to say Toyota.
Toyota, Honda, that's true. They can be...
They make that.
That's a real car.
They make that for rich guys. Autobots, Decepticons, Predacons.
Yeah, me and Cameron saw a Decepticon or Autobot on the way over here.
For real?
Did you know that Autobots are in like 2002 Ford Fusions now?
Really?
It's fucking crazy.
It was a Jetta.
Or a Jetta, that's what it was.
And it was so dirty.
It was covered in dirt.
It was the dirtiest car I've ever seen.
Probably from fighting a Decepticon.
Yeah, probably.
That was a Beets Pill or something.
It was probably from the Beast Wars.
Yeah, it had to have been.
Yeah.
So let's keep going. As you can see, I have some awesome ass art that I hung up in my place.
This one says "Heavy Metals" and we got "Feh, Peh, Beh, and Zin."
Oh, that's our initials. You got a friendship painting?
Yeah.
My initial is "Zain."
Fetter, Patrick Bourne, and...
Zain.
That'd be a cool new name for me.
Yeah, it would be good.
Zain Caleb.
Zain.
That'd be my alternative ego.
That could be good.
Zain.
I got more art though.
This is a beautiful portrait of a beautiful mind.
This is Dr. Jordan B. Peterson.
This is him thinking about,
thinking about just hot dogs and hamburgers
and all that kind of stuff he likes.
With no mustard, by the way.
- I love his frog throat.
- Yeah, I think he looks really good here.
And if I were him, I would also sell this in my store.
Is this.
So go next.
And then I have this one that says Adolf Rissler.
I just thought that was a dope-ass fucking piece of art and hey if you want one too
go ahead and click next if you want one too you can go to Redbubble and get the
Riz design for people with the highest Riz ever poster and I did this I paid in
for interest-free payments of 430 with afterpay a doll for Rizzler. Wow and you
got the semi-gloss finish too. Damn and they used a picture of your house for the
fucking fucking well yeah of course what are you doing stop okay and how to get
in the semi-gloss one time for the one time so go next and here's where the
magic happens here is where the magic happens race car better okay when Patrick
said magic he meant sexual relations you know I'm learning that tricks I have okay
wait hold on watch this okay it may just look like an ordinary pencil right watch
this who do do do it's completely rubberized oh wow there's a rubber right
at the end of the pencil that's the kind of thing that I've been learning how to
do in my racecar bed and I have a bunch of dope-ass books everywhere I have
Jay Leno's garage that was actually a heavy inspiration yeah yeah yeah I had
Jay come out and do some consulting work oh is that why his face got all burnt
yeah the B I would say the number one thing here though is my safe if you can
if you'll move just a little bit.
- I have, there's no--
- Just switch the camera and all those cameras.
- Switch cameras.
- I can move better than Patrick can.
- Oh man, nobody can see my--
- And even then, no, it's totally in black.
Maybe move the page around, yeah.
- Oh, well it's not.
Oh my God, you left my safe over there.
There's my safe, so that's why.
Wait, what a second, wait a, what a second, wait a second.
My safe is fucking open.
- What?
- Wait, what the hell happened?
Go next.
Who, oh my God, it's Chip Chipperson.
and he, Chip Chipperson, the bastard, broke into my fucking safe and started
stealing my, looks like, $24 out of my safe, 'cause he's such a thug
gangsta. God damn it, Chip Chipperson, he keeps sneaking into my house.
It's been a serious problem. Luckily, press next. Luckily, my security guard's
on it. He's gonna come in and he's gonna take this bastard out of
here. Oh, he's in your teacher's lounge. Yeah, he's in the teacher's lounge.
I have one in there. That's what I lock up. That's the number one, yeah.
When I become a millionaire, dude, I'm putting a teacher's lounge.
I was never allowed in there in school.
Yeah, a teacher's lounge where teachers aren't allowed.
Yeah, exactly.
The teacher's not allowed.
Oh my god, a nightclub that's called the teacher's lounge.
That would be fucking badass.
But basically, yo, that's my crib.
So I'm going to have my security guard kick your ass out.
Peace.
Damn.
You didn't finish yours like that.
That's how they're always supposed to finish it.
They finish with peace.
They say, I'm kicking your ass out.
Can I, um, can I redo my ending real quick? Play that one more time?
Um
I'm gonna cast a spell to make your ass leave
Peace. Peace out. And then you close the door right on him. Yeah. All right. That's good. Yeah. Yeah
All right. So griffindor who do you think had the cooler house so far?
I think you did because you had chip chipperson in there
No, yeah, you I don't want chip. Hey, if you want that bastard vagrant chip chipperson in your house, you can fucking have him
All right. I don't want him anywhere near my mtv crib. All right guys
- Guys, simmer down.
- All right.
- It's time for the master, the house master.
- All right, is that you?
- I guess.
- You're some kind of house master?
- I'm the house master.
Okay, pull it up.
Pull up my crib.
All right, so this is my crib.
- Cameron, this looks like a fucking laboratory.
- Looks like an outhouse, man.
- Well, this is just the outside of my house.
- Okay.
- And I think you're gonna be surprised
when you step inside.
Let's go to the next slide here.
Because, and let's move into my foyer.
- You have a foyer?
Let's move into my foyer, please. There it is.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
So...
It's so spacious in here.
Umbrella Corporation vibe.
It's actually really, really spacious, and there's a lot of
doors that go into different dimensions.
Yeah, so it's a long, long...
It's like a nightmare before Christmas.
That's scary. There's a long, long hallway with tons of gray
doors everywhere, fluorescent lights. It's kind of a, I would
say, neo-brutalist style.
Yeah, so I'm really into architecture and style.
Neo, I think I learned from Neo-Nazis or the Matrix, and then
list I think that's a Skyrim thing. How did you learn that from
Neo-Nazis? What do you mean? The word Neo? You were hanging out with them? No. He was
just doing research. No. The name. The name. Okay that's what you meant. But the next
room I want to show you guys is my living room. Okay. So let's see my living
room here. Please. Alright. Oh who's this? Your roommate? Oh yeah that's one of my
roommates what's his name that's Tad oh shit he's yeah he's a tad he's just
relaxing he's a tad too front and center in this photo if you ask me I mean it's his
house too he you know he can yeah I would say MTV Cribs very rarely does one let's
not focus too much on the room I mean you're supposed to be showing a life of
excess and luxury this guy look at this look at the okay look at this liver I
got I have a plant on wheels probably don't see that in a lot of houses do you
I've seen that's that's motherfucking
Wealthy you want to talk about my house. You don't think I have a plant that's okay
Person with a bad house y'all's are the person with a good house
You know how wealthy Cameron is huh? He's got watermarks all over his living room. Holy shit. I love paint job designer
Designer
But let's move on to the kitchen. I guess you guys don't like the living room so by Ted
I taste it's a bit. Oh, that's Marcus. Okay. Hey Marcus.
Is Marcus who?
It's we are.
It's one of my roommates watermarks, dude.
Yeah, I dream.
You had it like that dreams time and the spiral had it like this,
but that's just Marcus, you know, he he likes to talk on the phone.
He's got use a conversationalist.
Hey, yo, my grades get your feet off that damn oven.
You're gonna get your pig don't tell Marcus what to do.
That's nasty.
Also, I didn't realize that you had fucking I think this guy might be squatting.
Look at his ripped jeans.
Yeah, dude.
He's he's a hippie.
- Do you live with a homeless?
- No, he literally lives in the house,
how could he be homeless?
That's just Marcus, bro.
You guys are focusing way too much on the people.
- No, I'm focused on these watermarks.
- Look at the white tile.
I do like subway tile.
- The white tile, and look at my jars.
- Oh, I love mason jars.
- I have jars up there.
- Do you have pickles in them?
- It looks like I have yellow and white in the jars.
- Damn!
- Another thing of art that I have up in my house
is actually a mason jar is a cup.
That's what's in my house on the wall.
Okay, well, I don't really care about that because your house is over.
What's the next room we're going to?
We're going to head to the dining room.
This is where you take the food from the kitchen.
Who's this?
Oh, that's Brick.
He's fucking huge!
Yeah!
Well, he's just one of my roommates, don't worry about him.
Brick, what the hell are you eating?
He's a hunger guy, he likes strawberries, he likes bread.
Looks like he's eating half a cantaloupe.
Yeah, he likes cantaloupe too.
I love that Henley.
Yeah, and look at his collar.
I mean, wow.
Oh my god.
That's just Brick, don't mind him.
I mean watermarks around the fucking house dude. You got a dole be stock you are
We go like that you were so money, and you don't even fucking know it now
So I do want if brick if you could just move out of the way which it seems like he's kind of he's kind of
Just staring us down. I do might be a little he's might be a little confused that you guys are in here
So I'm not drinking from this French press straight
It's a little blurry because it looks like maybe the cameras focusing on brick
But you can see all my utensils in the back in the background. It's a French press a mocha pot
Oh, fuck um and you can see my shelf. Oh, well, you can't see my shelf, but there's a lot of utensils. Yeah
I know this background. I'll say I'll say your diner or your kitchen looks lit. Yeah. What is my dining room?
I'm Johnny room looks lit. Well, you said kitchen for yeah, I know well I get confused sometimes
I get all my house get off of bricks breast
Get off of his breast right now Patrick stop licking brick. This is his house
You're walking into his house being so fucking disrespectful actually nasty to him. All right, you'll want to see where I sleep
Oh, for shizzle.
Bedroom's up next.
Damn, who's this?
Who are these for?
That's the family.
The Smith family.
Is this where the magic happens for them?
No, that's where they sleep.
Oh my god, wait, are you fucking this whole family?
No!
They make magic two times, look at that.
They sleep during the day and I sleep at night.
What do they do during night?
They get up.
And roam?
And go around.
They go to work.
Even the kids, they go to night school?
Yeah.
Oh god.
There's a vampire family or some shit?
But, you know, I guess it's kind of annoying that they're sleeping here right now because
I wanted to show you guys some other parts of the bedroom.
I mean, I want to see there.
There's not even a single.
I guess this must be the Smith's room because there's not a damn watermark.
What are you talking about?
Dream's time, right?
Well, you're covering it up, pal.
Oh, shit.
I got it like that on the comforters.
No less than on the on the kid.
I like it because these are a watermark on the kid to the family's
kind of enjoying a dream's time right now.
They are out snoozing on your seat over here.
I got I got some flowers down on the corner.
I see that.
I do really wish that the Smith family would kind of move out of this shot
because I want to show off my bed. Let's not bother them. They're asleep.
I'm just screaming in here.
Alright, well let's go to the closet.
Oh shit! Sarah Michelle Geller!
That's not Sarah Michelle Geller.
But her name is Sarah.
Damn!
Coincidence.
She just stays in the closet.
I don't really know what her deal is.
No watermarks in the closet though.
Does she help you see my clothes?
No, she just isn't there.
That's a good move not to put the watermark in your closet.
really do much. Do you ever
accidentally reach for a coat and
you actually grab her, you wear
her all day? I have done that
once or twice. That's gotta be
bloody embarrassing. I shouldn't
admit that, but you see my
shirts, I got stripes, I got
checks, I got solid colors, I
got no pants to shirts. Whole
closet, Joseph A. Bank. Whole
closet, only shirts and one
woman. Kinda Winnie the Pooh
style. Yeah. Closet, I like it.
I'm walking around. That's
fire. No bottoms. That's fire. I
don't wear bottoms at home,
dude. Definitely, you don't have
to, it's your house. No, fuck
no. You know what I'm saying? I
don't remember what the next
for communist Asia. So the next room is my bathroom. Oh snap wait. I hate to
alarm you. There's two lovers in your bath. That's Billy and Willa. Oh snap.
They just take baths in there. They're dirty people. They're dirty like in a
sexual manner. Are they making a naughty video? She's drinking his piss look.
Yeah, she's got a piss cup up there. But no, they're just, they just, they like,
they usually roam around during the day. So they usually take a lot of baths and
they're, they like to be, we like to be water efficient in my household. So I let
to take two baths at once. Okay, it seems like they like taking two baths at once.
Yeah, they're friends. They're just friends. Yeah, they're telling me with
each other. See, this is the problem. Hey pal, I don't ask too many questions
about my roommates. I'm trying to stay on good terms straight up. If I was
what's his name, Billy, if I was Billy, I'd be getting fucking I'd be in a
woody. Okay, well, we haven't even met woody yet, so I don't know why you're
bringing him up. Well, you'd be calling me woody because I'd be sitting in his
bathtub with a fucking boner that could put out the sun, but I am kind of
annoyed at this that they're taking up the frame here because I really can't
show off much of my bathroom. I mean you can see my my my bath faucet my tub
faucet that's a good one. That's quite nice. Candy cane style yeah as they call it. Yeah it's got
the hook to it yeah looks like a metal candy cane. I do I do wish. You know I've been
talking to all these realtors as of late every fucking apartment I go into and
they've been saying yep the faucets all candy cane style. Stainless steel appliances
candy cane style faucets. I wish that Billy and Will would get out of the damn tub
because it's I've got a beautiful bottom of the tub. Oh yeah does it have a gumdrop
stopper? Mm-hmm. Oh gumdrop stopper M&M pebbles. Like a fishbowl. I bet that shit feels so
good on your back when you rub up and down on it. Yeah I do rub up and down on
it but I'm not in the bathtub that often because they are in the bathtub 23 hours
a day. They're in the bathtub often. And the other hour they are in the dirt. So please
Please tell me you have a shower in the bathroom as well.
Well, no, it's just the bath.
Oh, damn.
That's nasty.
You nasty, bro.
That's that type of shit you get in Bushwick.
Well, I get to take a bath a day because there is one hour they're not in there.
That's true.
But, you know, you guys thought maybe I only have one bedroom.
No shot.
We got a guest bedroom.
Anytime you guys want to come over, you can come to the guest bedroom.
Isn't it a bit weird that we've never been to each other's houses?
Here, let's show it off.
So that's Woody.
Whoa!
That's Woody.
That's Woody!
Woody, what are you doing?
What are you doing? He looks like he's a tired tired guy today. He's all tuckered out
I don't think he's trying to sleep. He looks like he's looking to the door for help
He's a construction worker and he works hard during the day. So he comes back and he just zonks out
He has a condition where he sleeps with his eyes open and with his arms and legs
Why is he tied as it looks like he's tied almost no, those are his cuffs. He wears
He has to climb these kind of like electrical towers and all sorts of buildings
So he uses those for it to balance himself. He's strapped in like Mike Berbiglia
So that he doesn't jump out a window in the middle of the night. He's not strapped in at all guys
He was really less or a few wears. Those are bracelets. Oh, he's like Chris Cole. He wears fucking sweaty
Weas those are bracelets those he hooks them into the construction site so he doesn't fall down
Oh, the bracelets is one of those seasickness bracelets cuz he rides a lot of boats for a bracelet
I'm sorry that I so insensitively accused him of being sexual. He's cosplaying as Macho from Pokemon
And the bottoms - yeah, okay, I like it. Yeah, but let's see what my what my next room here is
I want to show you all my man cave. Oh, hell yeah
I hope they're not in there right? I hope the boys aren't in there right now, but well, that's what you want in the man
Okay
What the hell looks like the boys are busy watching sports, I don't think so it looks like maybe they're going on some kind of
You've been watching too much avatar. He started acting like James James Cameron doing some deep
- James, 'cause that is James there with the gas mask on.
- Really?
- I don't know if he can hear us.
He probably doesn't even know we're in here.
- Gas mask, is this a smoker's lounge down here?
- And that's Tyler's foot up there.
- Where is the rest of them?
- You can tell Tyler got the shiny feet.
That's how you can tell.
- Who's this guy with his back to us?
- Oh, don't worry about that guy.
He doesn't live here.
- Yeah? - Oh, okay.
- We're gonna move forward to my study though.
- Oh, okay.
- This is where I get a lot of my research done.
- Yeah, I'd love to see your study.
- Hey, you could almost call that your man cave study.
There's so many studs in there.
Those are my study.
Really?
Wow.
Yeah, and these are some more of my roommates.
All these little families?
Yeah, well, none of them are related to each other.
Oh, that's cool.
That's cool.
So it's like a co-op you live in.
No, it's just a house.
Oh, it's just a house.
Yeah.
But this is where I get a lot of my research done.
Yeah, I don't know why you're moving the mouse around
down there.
That's just one of my roommates.
That's a baby with a weird-- he's got a fucked up head.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's the most fucked up head I've ever seen.
That's Darryl.
How old is he?
you're twenty seven. He's small. Look at how small it's just the angle of the
camera. I really wish that all these people weren't getting their study done
right now, because I really wanted to show you guys my book collection, but
it's just so so far away and we can't really get past my room mates here.
Yeah, we have to jump over all those people. Look, look, I'm crushing their
head. No, don't do that. Okay, that's not very nice to do. That's actually
violent. Yeah, that's very violent. Well, I have one more thing to show you
guys in my house, and it's actually outside. This is my backyard. Oh my God,
this is your backyard. Whoa, some of my room mates are having a picnic right
now. Holy cow! That doesn't look like a picnic. It looks like nearly a million
people. It's actually a thousand. Wow! That's way more than a thousand people.
It's actually thousands. Oh, to the point where it's a million. Maybe not. That's
the thing, when people say... A thousand to your tenth power. But it's my backyard
anyway. A million could also be thousands. And you can see, so that up right here,
that's Clint. Oh, hey Clint. What? And over... My girlfriend got mad I couldn't find
Clint. Over here, right over there, that's Gabriela. Oh, she's lovely. Yeah, she's
lovely and so far away that I can barely tell. This guy right here that's actually the
gardener I don't know his name. Oh and that's Alfonso. I know Alfonso from school. Yeah he lives here.
But that's my crib so you know usually I would say get the fuck out but if you
guys want to join the picnic. Alright yeah I'm not opposed. I can fucking eat.
That's fun. I'm ready to do I'm ready to I'm ready to have a picnic.
Jibio can't though he's on the other side of the world. Jibio what's your crib
looking like? He's gonna look up a teepee. He lives in this. He lives in the blue pen.
They haven't made your house yet. Oh okay. You live in a McDonald's? Wow. Wow.
That's where he lives. He lives it nowadays. Alright well listen up, if you
like these cribs then watch all the other episodes of Cribs. Now get the fuck out!
mm-hmm and subscribe to podcast about cribs on the patreon and also watch us
on the twitch and also Jubio will be doing a blood drive terrible it's in get
the fuck get the fuck out of now fuck out
I'm a fat
[BLANK_AUDIO]