Here's everything I do in a day as an author.
My alarm went off at 11.55am so you know what time it was.
Coffee!
Then I sat down and started writing.
At 12pm I wrote a book called The Dander, a science fiction book about intelligent cat
and dog dander.
Then at 1pm I wrote a historical fiction novel called Hip Hip Hooray about the power of celebration.
At 2pm I wrote a young adult action novel called The Adventures of Computertron.
I think my nephew's gonna love this one.
I took a quick break for lunch, but while I was eating, inspiration struck.
So I went back to my computer, and at 3pm I wrote a recipe book called "Peanut Butter
Upon Toast."
At 4pm I kept working hard and wrote a book called "The Lawsuit" which was set in the
Harry Potter universe.
To lighten things up, at 5pm I wrote a children's book called "The Happy Smiler."
And then at 6pm I wrote a book that was NOT for children called "The Wet Bedroom."
And then at 8pm I wrote a memoir called "The 8pm Blues."
At 9pm I wrote a horror book for dogs called "Owl Owl Owl".
Then it was time for a quick bathroom break, and while I was in there I found myself inspired,
and at 10pm I wrote a short story collection called "Tales from the Bathroom".
At 11pm I finished up a script for a podcast I've been writing for, and that was all the
work I did that day.
Around midnight I sat down on the couch and watched my favorite TV show "The Real Housewives
of Durban" until 6am.
Then I went to bed, and the cycle starts again.
that's what it's like to be an author. Bye y'all.
[Music]
Grogless January.
Grogless January round two.
Doing grogless January again.
Man, 30 days no grog.
Well I started two weeks in.
Yeah. This time.
We're going Chinese calendar.
Okay, that's a good point.
Chinese New Year just happened.
The last time I did Grog was January.
I was sober for six months.
So, let's see what happens.
That's just January.
That's true.
I had six months of January.
Six months of January.
Yeah, my year didn't start until June.
I'm trying to cut down on swill for the most part.
Too much swill?
Too much swill.
I'm trying to cut down on twill.
I got too many clothes in my apartment.
I had a little too much grog over the weekend.
Oh.
Doing piano bar.
Wow.
the dueling piano bar. How, yeah, talk about how was Rosemont.
They played that? And they said GD. Yeah. And first of all,
I was groggless enough that I, or I was grogged up enough that I sang
along with the GD. Okay, now here's a joke that I would say if I
was roasting you right now. Okay. I would be like, the dueling piano bar,
Caleb looks more like he would be at home in the dueling banjo scene
in Deliverance, but I wouldn't say that if we were in a roast situation.
And I wouldn't high five you. Compared to the rest of... They don't high
I have enough at roasts.
Yeah, that's true.
Compared to the...
Hey, somebody gets a good roast in, nobody walks over and just goes...
They need to, man.
They do, yeah.
Compared to the rest of the duels in that movie, though, not as good as the rest of
the duels, I would say.
No.
The violence-wise.
No, yeah.
They're really not as violent as the other duels.
Well, I mean, I guess a duel is one-on-one, mano-y-mano.
Yeah, I would say the others are kind of sneak attacks.
Yeah, I get you.
There's a lot of...
There's some ambushes and some flanking
that goes on in that movie.
- Oh yeah.
Who's in that?
It's John Voight, Burt Reynolds.
- Fucked up little baby boy.
- Yeah.
(imitates baby)
- He's ugly, man.
- Yeah.
- What else did that actor do?
- Gummo.
- I think that guy was also in Toy Story.
- Yeah.
- He was Mr. Potato Head.
- No, he played that spider.
- He was the baby spider.
- Mr. Potato Head when he loses one.
- He played that spider with the eye.
- Yeah.
- That's gonna be so awesome.
- Oh, he was Mad-Eye Moody.
When he grew up in Harry Potter.
- That has to be so awesome being an ugly actor
who's looking for that kind of thing.
- There's that like,
the thing that like boomers like to share on Facebook
where it's just a picture of Steve Buscemi smiling
and it's like in black and white and it says,
Steve Buscemi didn't know he was ugly
until people started saying it.
- I don't think Steve Buscemi's ugly.
- Steve Buscemi's not ugly at all.
Dude, have you seen young Steve Buscemi?
- I'm fuckin'. - Yeah, I knew him.
- Yeah? - I knew him
in middle high school. - For real?
- Yeah, middle and high school.
- Yeah, we went to a combination both.
- Wow. - Middle high.
Is it Buscemi?
It's called Middle High.
Because it's one C. Or is it Buscemi?
Are you trying to re...
Is it Buscemi?
Your name is Steve Buscemi.
What if it's like a thing where it's like Rihanna, where Rihanna pronounces it Rihanna?
She's Jamaican though.
She's not Jamaican.
She's Jamaican.
She's Asian.
She's Jamaican, but she moves those hips.
No, she's from Barbados.
Rihanna from Barbados.
Barbados, Jamaica.
That's a whole bit in detail.
I thought she was from Prescribia.
I want her Aidos.
- Her A, her A-dose.
(laughing)
Yeah.
- All right.
- I wish, oh she's from Haiti?
Really?
- I think so.
- She's gonna be hating my pants.
- I did hear that she was from Disturbia though.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- It's a fire ass movie, it's just a rear window rip off.
- I wanna be disturbing her.
- Is it a remake? - Re-window.
- Is it a remake of Rear Window?
- Rear make?
- I wanna look into her rear window.
Her butthole.
- Rear.
(laughing)
I'm gonna look into it, call somebody on the phone
"My God"
"You need to see this!"
"Something has happened in Rihanna's butt!"
"I'm looking to the rear window right now"
Why is it, why are we doing that?
My all red hitchcock
My hitchcock's going bloody insane looking into the rear window
It's giving me vertigo!
This bird is giving me vertigo!
My bed's looking in a rear window, making my bed get better go.
Looking in that rear window, oh.
And it's my hour.
Oh, I'm turning into a complete psycho path.
Or a psycho, a normal psycho.
Psycho, just a psycho actually.
Just a psycho.
Not a path, but I'm looking up.
What other movies did he make?
Dial M for Murder.
I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna dial M for murder still.
- Notorious.
- I'm gonna be notoriously on the run
from looking at her butthole.
- It's making my north go north.
Bye north.
- To catch a thief, I'm gonna catch a queef.
(laughing)
- Man.
- Yeah, that's what Albert Hitchcock would say
if he was alive.
- Hitchcock.
- Yeah, Albert Hitchcock.
- And then we could make his video
where we're looking at her butthole
and it would be a perfect Kuleshov effect.
- Alfred Crombie and Fitchcock.
- We could look at her butthole and go,
Alfred Crombie and Fitchcock do that for--
- Shut up.
- No.
- Do that.
- And it's a shirt.
- No, no, no.
- We could look at her butt and in one video,
we could be like, and in one video we could be like.
- Oh yeah, so they're actually making the same face.
- That would determine whether or not--
- Yeah.
- Her butthole's making the same face.
- Well, so the thing is--
- Coola Shavafeh, that is a cool name.
Coola Pull, man.
- Coola Shavafeh?
- Yeah.
- Everyone knows that, man.
- They're putting our degrees to work.
- If you've seen a YouTube video, you know that shit.
You see a movie, right, and it's a woman and she's wearing a dress and you're like,
"Okay, that's nothing." But suspense is when you put the camera under the dress.
You show what's under there. Everyone knows what's under there. People go, "Ahh!"
Yeah. Oh my God. Then it gets tense.
It's your bloody rear window.
Yeah.
And my bloody rear window.
That's just too fun. It's too fun to do, man. I love doing--
Rope.
I've gotten to the point--
Shooting a rope.
What's rope?
Rope.
Hitchcock movie?
Did he make a movie called Rope?
Rope.
Why'd you not get you I just thought of it chest row I did I said oh say it like that
There we go
Shooting a rope white rope
Row he didn't make a movie called white rope
No, I'm gonna make a white rope in the
Diana's rear window mm-hmm. That's what that's the through line here Alfred Hitchcock probably is the best names for sex
Yeah, or sex names for movies. What's that?
Huh the train goes into this it's supposed to the train goes into the hole oh come on
Oh, that's um fucking is that sex movie God. What movie is that sex fucker is it that's that?
Yeah, that's North by Northwest. Yeah, yeah speaking of
Things like that
I watched uh, no, I just watched that Bloodhound Gang music video for Foxtrot
I showed my girlfriend this week. I've never seen that one. Foxtrot uniform Charlie Kilo where Bam is in a banana car
I've never seen that one. Oh, yeah, Bam is in a banana car
He drives around Westchester PA and he keeps seeing hot women construction workers
But at the end of the music video he gives his banana to a gay man at the end of the tunnel
And it's fun.
- Were they a purely funny album or song maker?
- Yeah. - Artist?
- They were like if a family guy was rap.
- Yeah, put your hands in my pants
and I bet you'll feel nuts.
- Yeah, they have, I defend them all the time.
They have bars.
- I thought that was euphemistic.
- Mighty tighty whitey and I'm smuggling plums.
- Some are nuts.
- That's a lyric from the Mope.
- Mighty tighty whitey and I'm smuggling plums.
I don't get that at all.
- It's fun to say.
- So it's more of a MF Doom kind of like nonsense.
- They say that. - It's about food.
- If you say that enough times,
the Pac-Man will show up and smoke crack with you.
- Are you, what is wrong with you?
- That's from the, that's the music video.
It would make a lot of sense if you saw the music video.
- What are the Pac-Men?
- Pac-Man shows up and smokes crack with them.
- Oh, I thought you said the Pac-Man, right?
Am I crazy?
You said the Pac-Man show up.
- I processed Pac-Man.
- Oh, I heard the Pac-Man.
I was like, what's that?
- The Bloodhound Gang mope music video.
This is why I think their family guy was a rap.
out of nowhere, Pac-Man shows up and smokes crack with them.
- That is funny.
- They had that music video where it was like
the Why You Know guy and the Forever Alone guy
and the-- - They did that?
- And the Trollolol guy.
- They did a Weezer. - It was called the meme medley.
- You're thinking of Weezer.
- No, I'm thinking of the Porthouse Gang.
- They also did that song,
♪ What are the locks, baby ♪
- Yeah, they did that.
♪ Chackie, chackie, chackie, my old one ♪
- My house at my-- - My roommate loves that band.
- I was visiting my aunt and uncle
and they have a little cousin who's like three years old,
three or four. And he got his grandmother, got him a little
tricycle, a little toy tricycle. And it has a speaker in it that
whenever you ride the tricycle, it plays What Does the Fox Say?
And he got it like this year.
I would fucking, if my mom came and did that, oh my god, she'd be going home.
She would not be coming to Christmas ever again.
He kept getting on it and started pedaling. It was just like, it was to the point where,
So long I didn't even wreck. I just heard the music of it. I was like what is that?
It's like what why do I know this and then I'd be shooting the tires off that thing crazy
I'd be setting IEDs all around my house. They have a funny toy to exist off. You'll this had that song, Massachusetts
My roommate loves to used to love to show us that video all the time. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, it's on he likes Yilvas. I like that song that song's funny you like funny music
Have you heard of have you heard of these guys Pete and Baz they're like old UK drill rappers, that's not funny music
That's not that funny, but that video where it's not them
It's the other guys where the it's the bald guy the other guys has is a funny movie Norman Payne
movies and music yeah, Norman Payne has that song where he says like
What does he fucking say?
I gotta take a piss in a shit and a wank in a tree?
That's not funny as hell.
The bald guy?
I think you're confusing though, like that's not
I mean like you sit around listening to the Lonely Island.
No. Yes you do.
You love the Lonely Island.
Not this weekend, it was Bloodhound Gang this weekend.
Incredibad was last weekend.
Next week, Rucka Rucka Rooka.
Throw it on the ground.
That's my ringtone.
I throw it on the ground.
- That's a good cut.
That's an old school one,
one of those old school ones
where the concept was not very strong.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's clear that they just like can't--
- It's clear that they made them do a song a week
for a fucking year.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- They probably wrote that at four in the morning.
- Yeah, I remember--
- They were like, this is gonna be so funny.
- I feel like I never listened to the full songs
of any of those, and I would just hear a hundred people
at my middle school or whatever just go,
"Jizz in my pants."
And I'd be like, "Whoa, that sounds funny."
(laughing)
You know what it was?
- Jizz in my Pants had a grip on the culture.
- Yeah, for real. - Dude.
- Like a boss. - Like a boss.
- It was Jizz in my Pants like a boss
and threw it on the ground.
Those were the big three I feel like
where I just heard the,
for me I heard those three.
- Lazy Sunday.
- I'm on a boat. - No, because those are.
- I'm on a boat. - I'm on a boat,
that's true. - I'm on a boat
is bigger than threw it on the ground.
- No, Lazy Sunday was probably
of those, the smallest in that.
- But in terms of-- - What are you talking about?
That was the biggest YouTube video ever.
- In terms of people just saying the one line.
Not like the song being popular, but just of somebody like, "I threw it on the ground!"
You know what I really love to do is look up parodies of Lonely Island songs that people make.
Those are good. We were looking at that for a while.
Yeah.
The "I'm on a Boat" ones where it's like...
The "I'm on a Boat" with the guys... It's like the guys doing... It's like an office and they're
having their Christmas party or their... Some kind of party and they made a whole thing called
"I Gotta Moe" and it's for Movember.
- It's almost always either an office thing
or like a guy's getting married and his buddy's like,
"You know what we need to make, dude?"
- Yeah, we're gonna walk out to this.
- "I threw it on the cake."
- Yeah, no, no, you remember the one--
- "I threw it on her finger."
- There's the one--
- "We are a part of the system."
- "I'm on a boat" parody.
There's the "I'm on a boat" parody
that was for a wedding reception.
- "We are a part of the system."
"I threw it on her finger."
I have a new brother and sister.
In-law.
There's a there's an I'm on a boat parody that was made for a wedding reception.
We are missus and mister.
The chorus of the song is instead of I'm on a boat, it's we're so in love.
I heard that one too.
Yeah. We're so in love.
We're so in love. Everybody look at us because we are so in love.
Yeah, that is a good fucking song.
I love that song.
I love I just love parodies of parodies because it's like
It's already like, the song's already funny.
What are you gonna do?
How are you gonna tweak it to make it better?
Well, because you gotta personalize it,
'cause I've definitely heard songs where I was like,
"This is some funny shit. I wish my name was in it."
Yeah.
You know? Tribute.
"This is just for Caleb."
That could be Tribute by Shane Shazam.
"You gotta believe me, and he don't have no hair."
"A long-ass fucking time ago in a town called Caleb's house."
"Lived there a guy named Caleb, he was quiet as a mouse."
That could be another lyric.
That would be a lie though.
And though he...
It could be about how you got loud as fuck.
Yep, that's when I learned to access my voice.
You are loud as fuck.
Yep, that's true.
Can't take you to the movies.
I get that though. I think I did a lot of stuff like that.
We used to just one for one recreate digital shorts.
Yeah.
We used to take a flip video thing and we did the one where he punches him in the face.
That was on my YouTube for a very long time.
long time. I wish... It still is I think. I think there's still a video of me
punching my brother called "Punched into Face" on YouTube on his... I wish I still
had mine. His Pivot YouTube channel. Jimbo the office worker. It's gone.
It's been scrubbed completely from the internet. Pivot was awesome dude. Pivot was so sick.
The sketch that I wrote with my cousin. No we can't find it. There might be
some compromising personal information in that video. Yeah. Yeah might have
I have a picture or video of my little tiny--
I can't even find Jimbo the office.
My doodle.
Your doodle?
Your doodle was not on YouTube.
I think I put my doodle on YouTube.
You doodled on YouTube.
On YouTube, yeah.
You did not doodle on YouTube.
I put my doodle on YouTube.
You didn't, bro.
Yeah, I did.
I know that you didn't.
Well, he's already found you.
Jubio's already found you here.
Oh, you're right.
I live in Irvine, California.
Yeah, it's got your middle name right there, Caleb Undefined--
Caleb Undefined Pits.
Caleb X Pits.
29, 20--
That's such a cool nickname or middle name there, Undefined.
That is fucking awesome.
That's kind of what a nerd would name their kid, though.
That's true.
Undefined.
Did you guys make sketch comedy when you were children?
Oh, yeah.
I was just talking about it.
When I was 10 years old, I wrote a sketch with my cousin.
What was it?
Where a guy is at an office, and he
keeps getting asked the same question,
and then he shoots his boss.
But then he finds--
he keeps getting asked where the TPS reports are.
Really?
And then he finds-- and then he goes, oh, they're right here.
And then the credits roll, and I think it's like Kevin Rudolph
or something.
That's sick.
I wish I had that fucking video.
We definitely made a bunch of stupid YouTube sketches.
The one that I remember that's completely lost the time that I wish I could watch again
was like when I was too young to understand.
It was probably like elementary school, maybe like third grade.
My friend made Animal Wars.
Whoa.
That is sick.
What's Animal Wars?
It's about stuffed animals.
I made some stuffed animal shit.
You remember the ugly dolls?
We made a video.
I've talked about this with Pierce at least, maybe not on the podcast.
we used to make, we made a web series called Retardamon.
- Yeah, I remember it.
- Yeah.
- You've talked about this a bunch of times.
- I've got Retardamon, sorry, yeah.
But I don't think I mentioned that it was ugly dolls
were the Pokemon.
- Yeah.
- I can say it if I want to.
- My little brother got really into Lego stop motion.
- Uh-huh, oh, that was fun too.
- But he didn't like, I mean, he wasn't good at it.
- That's too hard, man.
- But he would like--
- The people who do that are fun.
- Yeah, no, no, he never--
- Those people are all rich now.
The kids who were doing that shit.
- Yeah, he didn't fucking stick with it.
- Like with it. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - I don't know what he done.
- Animal Wars was very,
Animal Wars was very,
had a kind of a geopolitical focus.
- Tell us. - You know what I did though?
- There was stuff,
but there was, they had,
all the animals were from different countries.
- Was kind of cool. - Some of them were.
- Wait. - Sorry, I'm on my own
train of thought.
- Yeah, I can-- - I'm thinking out loud,
I'm sorry.
- Would you get the animals
and have them fight on camera?
Were you the one who uploaded all the videos?
It was like,
Mongoose versus Cobra. - They were,
that's the thing,
they literally weren't even,
we never even uploaded them anywhere.
we didn't even know how to get the video from the video camera to the computer.
So we would watch it on the video camera and be like, "Look, this is Animal Wars,"
and watch it on the little display thing on the side.
I made a full hour-long movie when I was a kid.
Really?
Yeah, it was a horror movie called Revenge of the Tiki,
and it had a 15-minute scene that was basically just what I thought was a one-to-one recreation
of the Dumb and Dumber toilet chocolate scene.
You just, yeah, I forgot, I also,
I made, me and my friends made a movie at the media center
called The Disappearing Boy.
No!
What happened to him?
He disappeared.
Fucked me, really?
That is bloody terrifying.
And then he met the inventor.
The inventor of what?
The inventor, he said, I'm the inventor.
Holy crap, was it like God?
And you could tell he was the inventor
'cause he had, he had a piece of bark on his arm
that we said was like an invention.
- Wow. - And the invention was a piece of wood
on his arm? - He walked around like this
with a piece of parka. (laughing)
- Kids are so stupid, man.
- We're genius.
- The one cool thing that my brother did do
with his Lego thing, I helped him out with it,
but he took his Indiana Jones that he had
and then we painted the face to look like Rorschach
from Watchmen. - Whoa.
- Rorschach Jones. - Uh-huh.
It looked cool. - Indiana Shack.
- Damn. - He replaced the hands
with like, we like made like a little Rorschach Lego.
'Cause we were like, I was 11, so he was probably nine.
And then we saw Watchmen and we were like,
his mask is cool, nothing else about him.
I don't know anything else.
I don't know anything else about him.
I just think he looks cool.
- The mask was cool, dude.
- The mask was so cool.
- I remember the first, I remember when somebody
brought in Watchmen, this kid, Paul Winder,
he brought in Watchmen and he was like,
Caleb, you wanna see a penis?
And I was like, hell no!
- Patrick Wilson's dong, right?
- And I went, shit.
I might be gay.
I've said it before.
You know how Watchmen made me know I was gay?
As I read Watchmen, in my takeaway, I was like, "Damn, Rorschach's mask, it represents black
and white morality."
Holy fucking shit.
That's crazy.
Damn, you were a different kind of gay.
I was looking at the cock.
I was a child.
I've talked about it up and down.
It's its uncompromising worldview.
And I was saying, "It's his uncut cock."
Look at that thing.
That thing is uncut.
There needs to be more blue wieners in that movie.
I what do you think?
They did it.
I didn't even see it.
I never saw the movie.
Oh, you never saw it?
No, he didn't bring the movie into it
and show me the DVD and say, look at the cock on the DVD.
You scan it with your eye.
Oh, yeah, I can tell that there's cocks in this movie.
There's a big blue wiener in that movie.
I was watching the fucking--
I think he shows his--
I was looking at the comic book.
I think he shows his penis in the TV show.
Oh, you're talking about the comic book.
I was talking about the movie.
The TV show.
The sequel TV show.
Yeah, that guy apparently has a big one.
Yeah, I've seen the show.
He's got a big one.
He shows it in the show. It's the only reason I really watched Watchmen was
Me for their cocks, would you get man? Would you guys show your balls and your dick in a movie?
Yeah, I think about that. I'm getting paid enough
I don't think but last night I think it depends on I don't care if I get Terrence depends on the context
Yeah
So last night I was watching hateful 8 and there's a part in the movie
Where there's a character in his entire part of the movie is he walks around in the cold with his dong all shriveled up and
his balls hanging and then he sucks Michael Jackson's cock.
He sucks Samuel Jackson's cock and then he dies.
That scene is so sick.
It's a great scene.
I don't remember that movie at all.
I remember seeing that in theaters and being like, "Oh my fucking God."
I saw that in theaters.
I remember I had a flashback to when I saw it in theaters and thinking then, "I wouldn't
do that."
I was like, "You couldn't pay me enough to be that fucking guy in this movie."
I saw that in the theaters but that was back in the days when I was smoking weed and I fell
asleep through that the whole movie long movie yeah I fell asleep and I woke up
and it was like the end of the movie what's the extended version last night
didn't need to extend that movie yeah enough there was like parts of the movie
where nothing fucking happens for 20 minutes right it's just like footage of
them riding in the fucking caravan I don't think I ever saw the extended
version was it a but would you do that would you do that
yeah wait what's up no not suck his thing no see I'm interrupting you cuz
you're saying nothing right now.
- Kurt Russell broke an antique guitar on the set by accident.
- Yep.
(laughing)
- That's what I was trying to remember.
- He breaks a guitar.
- Go on.
- Why'd you remember that out loud to yourself
looking at the ground?
- I don't know.
- You're like, "Kurt Russell breaks a guitar."
- It was a fun piece of trivia.
It's a fun piece of trivia.
- Antique guitar.
- It's a guitar from the 1800s that he broke.
- Who gives a motherfucking shit?
- The Martin Guitar Company.
- Remember seeing that movie in theaters
and you come back after the intermission,
you hear the narrator's voice,
you turn to your friend, you're like,
I know who that is.
(laughing)
I don't know if you know who's talking right now,
I know who that is.
- Who's talking?
- It's Quentin Tarantino.
- Oh my God.
- That's his voice?
- That's his voice.
- I don't think in the extended version.
- And so they're in the cabin now.
- They definitely used a different person
for the extended version.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's like a whole different voice.
- Bruce Byrne?
- No, it's just in the movie.
- And their domergue has a little bit of a secret.
It's like a weird, like, audible voice.
Anyway, it's probably his voice. Would you show your balls? Yeah. If in cock,
if they were like, it's going to be 10 degrees,
it's going to be 10 degrees and the whole world's are going to know forever.
The side of your car. I'd rather keep it a secret dude. Straight female.
You can also get like a, uh, uh,
you could get a VFX artist to make your, I would say yes.
On camera. That's the only way to win is you tell them I'll only do it.
If you give me a prosthetic tiny cock, because then it's like,
Hollywood rumor, they had to use a prosthetic, his cock was too big.
They had to make it look like a pinto bean.
I would say yes, I would take the money, I would get to the shoot, I would start the
scene, I would start peeing.
And they would do, "Okay, can we take it again?
Don't pee this time."
I'd pee again.
I'd do it every time until we ran out of daylight.
To cover you up.
Yeah.
I was like, "I'm sorry, I'm just so nervous."
- Until they draw you naked on the back of your body
and add a little cock at the bottom.
- And then I poop.
- Yeah, you're backwards and you have like rubber underwear
that has a dick.
- Yeah.
- And a mask of your face.
- It's right on your butt.
- Yeah, and you're wearing a diaper, yeah.
- If you work in VFX, you need to make this right now.
We're creating a crazy character for you.
Now that I think--
- I wanna see this by next week.
- Now that I think about this, if I was offered this
and some famous director was making a movie
and was like, okay, I want you--
I want you so brother I want you either Russo brothers are like we want you in
our movie but there's gonna be a scene where you're walking through the snow
completely naked and then you have to suck Samuel L Jackson's cock I would be
like didn't hateful a tardy do that you're right I don't think you need that
in your movie right I guess that's a bad hypothetical that's bad yeah yeah but
would you do one where would you do a movie where the entire movie is not even
the scene just the entire movie is like a bunch of hot girls pointing at your tiny
cock going you got a small cock you got your dick is small. Would you guys do that movie?
Yeah how much am I getting paid? $40? Yeah. Make it 60. Okay then you do it? Make it 60
and I'm in. That's okay that's okay. Is this the guy whose cock was in the movie?
I think it is him I remember Craig Stark? Whoa. Must be related to Tony Stark. Yeah.
short yeah I'll say play Henry short played long-haired freak and licorice
pizza hey that's everyone in the goddamn movie see but I think this is what you
end up doing if you just show your cock in a movie you turn you also play
robber and robber and Emily the criminal he got robbed of his fucking manhood in
that movie I'll tell you that much by Samuel L Jackson did so he's a honey boy
this Shia LaBeouf mmm Shia LaBeouf Shia LaBeouf me used to be the funny boy when
he was on Transformers.
Transformers, he was pretty funny.
He was so funny in Transformers.
I would say Bumblebee is the comedic relief of that movie, though.
No, it's actually Skids.
Yeah, Skids and then Jazz and Bebop.
That's in the second one, though.
Yeah, I think one of them is named Mudflap.
Jazz and Mudflap.
Bebop is Ninja Turtles.
I mean, are you thinking of the very racist twin?
Yeah, I think one of them's name is Mudflap.
Yeah.
I can't remember what the other one is.
jazz and or bebop it's be about my rocks and that's a pig and a rhino yeah what
I know it's a it's a it's a it's a boar and a rhino yeah like a yeah it's got
Optimus Primal, he's got the Predacons, he's got G-Tor,
Beetle Borgs, you know what I wish they would make a movie for?
They stopped making that because they ran out of footage in Japan.
I want them to make a movie about Zoids.
Yes dude, fucking Zoids!
Zoids is the perfect knockoff, like Transformers, like Gundam type thing.
thing because like it's only it's other all dogs yeah all the robots are just
giant dogs there's no they're not oh yeah now I remember these they all look
exactly the same. Zoids was a Toonami like that was the number one Toonami. I had Zoids
Gameboy Advance game. I had a game called Zoids Legacy. No I'm thinking of
Spectrobes. Look how few types of Zoids they are they all look literally exactly the same.
Spectrobes, Spectrobes was like Disney's RPG for the DS that like was
essentially all of it looked like this right? You know what they should
bring back? What? Pokemon. Yeah. Whatever happened to Pokemon? Buddy, hey I've got
big news. What's the news? Scarlet and Violet takes place in España. I'd like
to see Scarlett Johansson capture her in a pokeball. And Violet. Yeah. And get Violet with her.
her. Attack her. Don't attack her. Rip her arms and her legs off. Put her in a pokeball,
rip her head off. AHHHHH! Kill you, Scar Jo. Don't do that to Scar Jo. I'm just kidding.
Scar Jost. She's gonna be soon. Yeah. When she's wed to Jost. I'm happy for them. Jost
wedding. Yeah. Yeah, imagine the roast Jost at that wedding. My god, imagine the toast
The Joest wedding. The Joest jokes.
The Joest jokes. The Roast jokes.
The Roast jokes. Imagine Scar Joes jokes.
Scar Joes Joes jokes. They're gonna be badly scarred from those Joest jokes.
Those Joes jokes.
The Roast jokes when Joests elopes with Scar Joes.
Meanwhile they're doing a weeding update.
Yep. Yep. With Michael Cheba.
What the fuck is wrong with us man? We have actually some kind of fucking virus.
I found out today that people get carbon monoxide poisoning and they don't even die.
They just get really fucking stupid.
What do you think happened to us?
I don't know, but I think it that. I think it that.
I saw... I think it that. I don't know, but I think it that.
While I was doing the research for today's episode, we'll get to that later,
but while I was doing the research, I found this thing that was like...
Somebody went on Reddit and was like,
"I think that somebody's sneaking into my house and...
like breaking into my house and writing post-it notes to me about things that I have to do
for the day and like I think I have to go to the police, like this is getting really, really
scary.
Oh, I saw this.
Yeah, and then somebody was like, "I think you might have carbon monoxide poisoning,"
and they went and they had like a hundred parts per million of carbon monoxide.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That shit was crazy.
But I thought that carbon monoxide just killed you.
I didn't realize that it could just make you crazy.
Well, it depends on how bad it is because it's how weird Al's parents passed away.
They passed.
They passed away.
Oh, they passed.
I'm trying to be respectful.
I'm trying to be respectful to the weirdo.
That's how they passed on.
That's how we lost them.
I hate when people say pass away.
Yeah, I definitely have,
'cause hanging out at your house when you had the gas leak,
I, maybe it's just getting older and realizing,
yes, I am very stupid,
but I've totally gotten stupider from that.
I don't think it was that.
I think your house was Jupiter.
You would only come to my house--
And I'm going to get more stupid.
Every once in a while, first of all.
Also, natural gas leaks are not,
it's not neurotoxic.
It just makes less oxygen in the air, basically.
- Well.
- But it's definitely not good for you.
- To each his own.
- Yes, if something happened to you, I'm not gonna.
- Yeah.
- No, you've always been pretty stupid.
- I don't know.
I don't know if I've been this stupid.
- You used to be stupider, actually.
- I think you used to be stupider, yeah.
- Because you were fat.
(laughing)
So you had like, you were making poorer choices, too.
- I don't know, I feel like--
- I don't think I was stupid, I think I was just--
- You were definitely dumb.
- I think I was just very sad.
I think you used to be stupider.
I think about it, you definitely used to be really stupid.
I think you used to say some stuff where I was like...
You used to be way stupider.
Never mind, you're still so stupid.
Yeah, I'm still pretty fucking dumb.
Yeah.
I got a new couch.
Is it comfy?
It's comfy.
Moving on.
Very comfy.
Next.
I'd like to move on to the couch.
I'm jealous.
Can I come spend the night?
You can.
Just sleep on the couch.
It's so fucking comfy.
And I slept on the couch.
You slept on my couch.
- He slept over my house one time.
- I did.
- 'Cause there wasn't any--
- I slept over.
- All my wife's family was in town.
- Yeah, yeah, I remember.
- So he slept over.
- I remember that.
- I, yeah, convinced all my roommates that I got,
that we were getting, that we were gonna break up.
And so I came in--
- Did I tell you that?
- Yeah, yeah, and so I came in and I was like.
(laughing)
And Neil was like, "Hey, buddy, hey."
Like, everybody's being so nice to me.
Neil and Alex were like, "Oh, oh, Caleb, oh."
- Oh, that's funny!
- You wanna play X-Box?
(laughing)
- Everyone is saying, the first thing that everyone said
when they saw you was, "Hey, buddy."
(laughing)
- They talked to me like I was a dog.
- It's awesome.
- You were like a make a wish kid.
- Yeah, "Hey, buddy."
- And then your last wish was coming over to my house
and playing Mario Kart.
- Yeah.
- That'd be my last wish.
- Everybody's letting me win Mario Kart shit.
Like, damn, dude.
They have blue shells, they're not throwing 'em.
It was awesome.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- It was a really good time.
- That sounds like a good experience.
your house. You guys have sat on my old couch and it's uncomfortable.
You remember how uncomfortable it was? It was an uncomfortable couch.
It's nice of you that you never said it. I mean I knew it all along.
I didn't want to embarrass you. But this new one, it's bigger, fit more people, it's
more comfortable, it's longer, it is uncut, it hasn't been cut apart at all.
- Oh, that's good. - It's completely,
and it retains, the sensation is completely intact.
- So when we do succession nights,
when that comes back on-- - Yes, and it has arms.
- It's gonna be at your house.
- It has arms.
- You remember my old couch, the fainting couch?
- Yes, I do remember the fainting couch.
- The which couch? - Is it like that?
- The which couch?
- The fainting couch that I had.
- What does that mean?
Remember he had that shitty weird couch?
- That was not that shitty.
- Mine is not shitty, so that--
- No, it's not like that at all, it's like a nice couch.
- That couch was actually comfortable as hell.
- I slept on it a couple times, too short.
- Yeah, it was just too short.
- Yeah, this new one, three cushion couch.
- Holy fuck.
- Remember how I was in my apartment for a fucking year?
- Yeah, I do.
- I had two couches at my apartment for so long.
- Which you're thinking, wait,
every guy's biggest fucking dream is his couch.
- But no.
- My dad has two couches right now.
- There was a couch behind the couch.
You can see it in the prank ass video.
There's another couch in my apartment
because it was my old roommate Joe's old couch
and he did not want to move it and I don't blame him
because getting that into the apartment
almost killed the boat. You shouldn't have to move a couch. I agree. No, that's what
people are for. You should get to cut it up and shred it. Definitely. And still get the
money from selling it. Yeah. You know what I hate to move? A piano. Ohhhh. Look at that
one over there. We've never even... why don't we plug that in right now? Start playing.
Because we gotta start the rest of the show. You're talking babbling nonsense like a baby.
Babylon nonsense. Okay. Well what's the breast of the show? The breast of the show? That's
you I didn't say breast but you are the breast you are the base of the bread I
slur my words and I'm the tummy I'm the tummy you're the tummy so what do we got
what do we have next you're the brain all right well I'm the breast cuz everyone
likes to look at me sure I like to suck on you you're full of milk because I
like to say I'll take your jiggle your chock full I'll take it you're chock
full of milk and you should be bigger.
- So we brought in something exciting today.
- What was the prize of that?
- It is a magic book.
- Holy fuck.
- Oh, that was way too loud.
- What?
- That was way too loud in my fucking,
in the, or sorry, there's a Bible on the thing,
in my effin' normal ears.
- It's not a Bible, it's just a magic book.
- A Bible. - No, it's a Bible.
- And it's what we call a magic book,
because this book, let me tell you,
Quite literally, quite literally,
this book has every story ever told.
- Wow, it tells. - Or every story
that ever needs to be told.
- Every story you ever need.
A lot of people say, oh, I like my favorite author's
John Green and shit.
They're fucking faulting our stars
based on a series out of this book.
- If we're reading out of this book,
why don't we play the piano? - Israel hath sinned.
That's what I'm seeing here.
- Where?
- Joshua 7, 11.
- Oh, they let a seven-year-old read that?
- Israel hath sinned.
- Holy shit. - Who's Israel?
Therefore the children of Israel could not stand before their enemies, but turn their
backs before their enemies.
That's in the Bible?
That's the top thing in the Bible?
The top thing is top right.
Well you heard it here first.
So go ahead and tell the people what we're doing today then Cameron.
It's story time.
It's story time, straight out of the Bible man.
Straight from the word of the Lord himself.
And I actually have to grab my reading glasses.
Call me motherfucking Bible man.
If somebody wants to read a story first, I have to you have reading glasses
I won't grab my reading glasses go ahead. I have a story I could maybe read
You know what are the odds that I flip to the exact right page pretty high it seems
Pretty high pretty good all right go ahead tell us I need I might need somebody to hold my microphone. I got you
This is a passage from the Bible called what desire will make foolish fanboys do oh
Oh, I remember this verse from when I was going to church.
"Bam always waits for Villa in his dressing room
after a show."
Shit, I'm just doing this.
"Well, it's not just Villa's dressing room,
technically speaking.
It's the whole band's.
But the other guys, they're not jackasses.
No, that's him.
They know what goes on here after the show,
and they have the decency to stay the hell away.
Bam's running late."
Sorry, really quickly, what book of the Bible is this?
This is in the book of Jazia.
Jazia.
OK, continue.
Bam's running late.
He got caught up recording some promo for some DVD
that he doesn't even remember agreeing to.
He tried his hardest to move things along
so he could at least catch some of the set.
And as unabashed as he is, even he's
not sure if he could look at an MTV producer in the face
and say that he's late for his Finnish rock star
dick sucking appointment.
So late it is.
I just wanna note also, my glasses broke this weekend.
- So you could be getting some of the details wrong.
- Yeah, but the words could be, some of the words could be.
- So late it is.
When he does arrive to the venue, he wastes no time
and hightails it right to him's designated backstage area,
following the directions that a flabbergasted
and starstruck security officer gives him.
The room he arrives to is pretty bare bones and small,
paling in comparison to the fanfare the band typically gets
when they play shows in Europe.
But for the purpose that they need it for, it'll work fine.
Throwing himself on the couch, Bam reaches for the pack
of cigarettes on the coffee table and lights one.
He doesn't normally smoke cigarettes, but he swears
he's somehow getting secondhand nicotine addiction
from Villa.
Or it could be the taste of cigarettes on Villa's lips
that he's addicted to.
He takes a drag and taps his foot along to the sound
the last few seconds of the kiss of dawn hoping to god there are no plans for an
encore song tonight patience unsurprisingly never was BAM strong
suit was that was that really so beautiful he's holy ghostin yeah luckily
another song doesn't follow just the usual thank you we love you now get
ready for my chemical romance and then the enthusiastic screams from the crowd
Bam sits upright and glares at the closed door waiting.
It's about 15 minutes before the door opens and Villa steps into the room with a frustrated huff.
Bam exhales. You would have thought he'd been waiting for hours.
"About fucking time you got here!" Bam complains, pouting.
"I haul ass through LA traffic! I still get here before your set ends and it took a really long time for you to walk your ass down the hall!"
Villa chuckles and smirks. "My sincerest apologies, darling," he says, sarcasm evident in his tone.
Edna Mode? Got caught in a conversation with the singer from Mike Hem,
Gerald I think his name is? He shakes his head, no no, Gerard that's it. He was
telling me about how much he liked our set. It was sweet of him to watch it all
but to say it too? How cute! Kind of slipping into Cosby a little bit.
No, no. What do you mean? He did a little Cosby. He's not a Bill Cosby. Keep going.
Bam Scott says he takes another drag from his cigarette. Yeah well you like
him so much why don't you go and fuck him then well he's performing right now so I
can't exactly do that Villa says as if on cue the sound of another singer
screaming San Bernardo he can be heard as the band begins their set but you know
so another time perhaps he is very pretty yeah right the assholes are
walking Hot Topic discount bin BAM grumbles stubbornly through he though he
still immediately scoots towards Villa when he comes to join him on the couch
You can't seriously say you'd rather fuck him over me Villa raises a brow now. I never said that I did did I
Be careful jealousy isn't very becoming on you
Jello
Jealousy
Villa plucks the cigarette out of BAM's hand and takes a drag besides he exhales the smoke only moves closer his lips
His lips hovering over BAM as he speaks
There's only one fanboy. I'll
True there's no way this is five pages on I can stop right now if you want no get a bag get to the good
Okay, man come on
Well, we were just about to get go. Okay, then go. I'm not I'm not a fanboy BAM mumbles like he doesn't have countless tattoos
Over and he doesn't drop everything to come anywhere in the world just to fuck him and his body isn't trembling begging for Villa
right now. It's the worst lie in the world and it's not fooling anyone.
Certainly Villa who gives a dubious look before that smug smirk resurfaces as his
hips his hands slip under Bam's shirt. "Would you prefer groupie instead? I'd
prefer whatever gets your dick in my ass right now." It's not very often that Bam
asks to be fucked especially not so outwardly but what little patience he
has is gone. Villa spent another the whole time talking about how amazingly
Stupid the my chemical romance guy is and BAM's not sure how much more he can fucking handle. It's
Exasperating gripping BAM's chin delicately Villa tips his head upwards and smiles now that certainly can be arranged
He crashes his lips against BAM and kisses him deeply. I don't need to read the rest of this
He fucks BAM R. Jarrah that's in the Bible and that's in the Bible. Thank you for sparing us the every gory detail
Wait, I'll skip to the I'll skip to the end
Let's get dick in yeah need to know if they fucking repent at the end or so
Let me see here
This great village shit-eating grin morphs into a warm smile. I don't like that. I feel like maybe we
That makes that a little too literal yeah
That's right. He is villas number one fan. It's a title
He will wear with pride something no one can ever take with him especially not some my fucking chemical romance ass clown
there if you want to see me single-handedly coerce people into
thinking that VAM thinking about VAM again in 2020 feel free to check out my
okay and then it's but I think there's a printer error this must be new
international version yeah I don't know this yeah Bible this might be this might
be one of those Bible has hyperlinks this might be one of those teen graphic
novels yeah that might be a real story oh yeah here's a Margera and Bill Cosby
Here's a page we opened to, Leviticus 27.
What? What?
The very thought of the Bible is so hilarious to you, you fucking atheist agnostic.
Which one is...
What are you talking about?
What is going on?
Leviticus here, this is the one. This is the book, this is the anti-gay book.
They're all anti-gay, man. That's why we...
- Hey man, that's why we're--
- Yeah, this is the one that says
man should not land with the, the man with the thing.
- You're thinking of Invictus, the movie.
- Oh, I'm thinking of Incubus.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- The band. - Yeah, you are.
Well, that was a wonderful Bible story, my friend.
My good fellow.
Perhaps it's my turn to read one, no?
- Sure, yeah, you can read the story time.
- Here, I'll read a couple.
They're all from the same book.
Yeah, the motherfucking Bible.
- Yeah.
- Let's see, which one do I wanna start with first?
Real quick, what's y'all's favorite book
- The entire Bible.
- My favorite book of the Bible is Leviticus.
(laughing)
- I like the Adventures of Hercules.
- Oh, that's a good one.
- Adventures of Hercules are fire.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- And I'm also a big fan of Index.
- Oh, I like the Book of Shur.
- Yeah.
- I like the book--
- I like the Book of Shur.
- I like the story of Michael and Toby.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm a big fan of the book of Women Fart Stories.
(laughing)
- My favorite, hold on, let me flip her open real quick.
All right, this is a story called Dream GF
from the book of Women Fart Stories in the Bible.
Women Fart Stories 2121.
I love running with my girlfriend.
She and I usually run outside often.
She always runs ahead because she knows
I like her ass in leggings.
"Hello, we cannot stop," she said.
"Sure," I said.
Then she and I went into the woods
and she pushed me down near a tree and tied me to the tree.
- Taste this, you're cock bastard.
- Okay, I can tell the kind of antiquated mindsets
that went into this and kind of,
this is one of those things where you know,
the books about like owning slaves and stuff like that.
These are, we just want to say these are viewpoints
that people don't hold anymore.
- It's not, and we can't judge the Bible
'cause of what it's in it from a different time.
- It's not like you're gonna stop riding Splash Mountain.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, so let's, we know you keep going.
- So back to the story, she said,
taste this, you're cock bastard.
And then she fez on my face so the whole face vibrated
and you could feel the smell that was so frantically smelling
but still good.
Oh damn, it smells bad.
Best hell you smell it, she said.
I usually pretend I do not like her farts,
but I have always done so.
I think if she knew I did, she would stop.
I sometimes have to put my hands over my crotch
because otherwise she would see my hard cock,
but now she had tied my arms around a tree
and I could not protect my hard penis.
Hmm, that's what I think it is, she said,
looking at my hard cock.
Do you know what? I have always seen your cock get hard by my farts, and I actually understand you.
I myself can also be ignited by my own farts.
This is beautiful.
It's really like, this is Song of Psalms level, like, beautiful poem.
It's like spousal understanding.
In that case, I actually have a little surprise for you, then.
She pulled down her pints, but only so that her ass was visible,
and then she opened up my fly and out flew my cock hard as cement.
Hey, the last time there was a fly on pints.
Oh, shit.
True.
Oh!
She took my cock and slowly began to touch it on the glands.
Then she takes a firm grip and starts jerking it really hard.
Are you ready for another fart?
I know you like them.
Sounded like it came a fart, and then I came after it.
Note, I Google translated this text from my language
to English, so that's why some parts sound really,
really weird.
I don't-- I mean, it's in English.
I don't know.
Originally, you have to imagine it was Hebrew or something,
right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
That's probably what they meant.
- At the end of all the Bible verses.
I wrote this in my language and translated it,
so please excuse any English errors.
- And here's a little, just a little comment.
This is in the notes.
- Yeah, the annotations.
- This is also in the Women Fart Stories chapter.
Does anyone know any stories where the protagonist's
farts are very stinky?
For example, that the farts are so stinky
that they are capable of withering flowers,
or that the smell disgusts her.
- I actually have an answer.
- You do?
- Larva Island.
- Oh, Larva Island. - Oh, Larva Island.
- I do remember Larva Island. - I don't know that.
Explain what it is. - You're gonna watch it
and have some fun later tonight.
- Here's another-- - I'll tell you.
- Okay, so this is from the next chapter over.
This is from Girl Fart Stories, another one.
This is no longer Women Fart Stories.
This is Girl Fart Stories, one chapter over.
My mom and sis is farting on me, is it normal?
I'm a boy of 17 years.
My mom and elder sister is making my life hell.
They wants to sit on my nose every day.
My mom says if I don't obey them, they're gonna tie me up
and we'll do their stuffs forever.
I have no other way to sniff their butts.
(laughing)
Sometimes,
sometimes,
sometimes my elder sister farts on me.
The horrible thing is that they both make sure
that my nose is touching the bear hole.
Is it normal? - Oh no.
No.
- So that's like God, like, you know,
you think like, "Counselor Nicaea,
"why'd you put that in the Bible?
"It seems like it should be like maybe apocryphal."
but I can see how that would help some young men. For sure. Especially at that time, again,
you have to take all of this as the time when it happened. Yes, yes, absolutely. And also,
that's what I was going to say, you have to look at it, it is not meant to be taken literally.
For example, the nose can represent a temple. A temple. And the bare hole could be the mouth of
God releasing the word of God or a cloud of faith. It could be that. A swimming pool or a bathtub
just bubbling with faith, Jacuzzi style. This next book also is from Girl Fart Stories. It's from
the book of Appropriate Bike 4337, which is the gospel of Appropriate Bike 4337. I'm familiar.
This is Step Sister Help Me Out. So yesterday was the best day of my life. It started on my birthday.
my stepsister was angry with me for adding milk to her tea
because she was lactose.
- Ah. - Oh.
- So she, which I didn't know they even had it back then.
- Yeah. - So she was in her room
dealing with it, I excited my partly to check on her
and her her gas fetish.
I got there and she was in her room holding her stomach.
When she saw me, she got angry, grabbed and said,
"Since you're the one to do this to me,
"you're going to help me out of it."
Then she grabbed my face, letting out a 20 fart.
(laughing)
(laughter)
- I didn't know they got to that level back then.
- Yeah, I guess they could get to a point.
- I thought they only had ones or twos.
- They're eating, you know, hummus and stuff.
That'll make you fart.
- Yeah, it's true.
- Aw, that felt so good.
How'd it smell?
I smelled it all and pretend to be grossed out
and she didn't notice.
Aw, did it stink.
Next time, think twice before missing with me.
I let her do smelling all of it.
Why can't I smell anything, she said.
Then she noticed my boner.
Oh, that's why you did it on purpose, didn't you?
"I tried defending myself, but don't worry, I'll let you.
"I shyly asked if I can taste them.
"She said yes and took off her short and panties.
"Then she fed them to me.
"Okay, her come a big one."
- Oh, that's where communion comes from.
- Oh, that is, yeah.
You take it off and you let them eat it.
"Then she fed them to me.
"Okay, her come a big one.
"Then she let out a big shart.
"Be both blushed, I'm embarrassed me,
"because I want to it her shit."
(laughing)
- Because she started, "I'm my mouth, sorry I'm,
"I'll be right back."
She tried to get up, but I would let her.
She got the hint and smiled.
"Okay, fine, if you wouldn't move, I'll just use you."
She used me and we agreed we would be doing this more often.
- Wow.
- I love, oh my god, I love that the bike--
- It's appropriate bike.
The Gospel of Appropriate Book of Luke.
The author of this...
We don't know who it is.
It's unknown.
Put it by the pseudonym.
Went into so much loving detail about
"I'm my mouth, I'm my farts"
this kind of thing.
We really see the importance that they place on this.
And then she uses him.
It's like Jesus wept.
It's one of the most expressive single sentences.
She said, "I'm going to use you"
and she used me.
you and she used me. Because you know what she's using him for. Yeah. But he doesn't
have to get explicit. He's already saying I want to it her shit. So you don't need
him to say she used me like a human toilet. It's so it's a used me. You can
imply it. And it's one of those. Jesus crapped. It's one of those things where
yeah if you take that story literally you know like like every story in the
Bible if you take it literally you're gonna you're gonna go insane and that's
why it's about sharing. And that's why I find Gnosticism to be such a powerful
refuge. Nauseousism is what we're reading. This is nasty-sism. So I, listen, I just have one
last Bible story. Okay. A biblical tale to weave for you two. Sure. That comes from
the next book. Uh-huh. Which is the book of shit fart hobby. This book, this book,
this story is, and we all remember this, VeggieTales did one of these. Yeah.
Chinese girl let out a Chinese takeout smelly fart in the bank.
It's my lucky day.
The most common phrase in the Bible.
The bank queue, they're talking about a river bank.
Yes, in Egypt.
What faith is it, Baha'i, where they say, "Lucky day to you."
I don't know, but this is...
Lucky day, lucky day to you.
You guys are all having a very lucky day in the Bible.
It's my lucky day.
- It was my lucky day.
The young Chinese woman ahead of me in the queue in the bank
let out a loud fart sounding like a prawn cracker.
(laughing)
And for the next few minutes,
there was a smell of Chinese takeaway.
- I know that what he meant by a sound of a prawn cracker,
but I would love to imagine a fart that sounds like
prawn cracker.
- I'm sorry, excuse.
She turned to me and said quietly with a shy smile,
I'm sorry, excuse me.
And I said, "It's okay, it's no big deal."
And she said, "We have good big deals at our takeaway,
and I will give you complimentary prawn crackers
with your next order because of my accidental fart
I just let out."
(laughing)
- What a coincidence.
- I know, it's amazing.
I said, "That's so very kind of you."
And I asked the name of her takeaway,
and she said, "It's the noodle bowl."
And I said, "Maybe toilet bowl would be a better name
after that beautiful fart you just shared."
(laughing)
Imagine being the woman in that story though.
- That beautiful fart you just shared with me.
- Yeah, imagine--
- After that beautiful fart you just shared with me,
you should call the toilet bowl.
- Imagine being the woman in that story
and then she's like, "Oh man, I'm so embarrassed,
"I just farted in front of this guy."
- And the guy is on the ground on all fours
like a bloodhound.
- This one is like the screw tape letters,
there's a little bit of a dialogue.
Dangerous Bloke says, "Then what did she say?"
And then our esteemed author says,
she said, "I farted deliberately,"
'cause that's what turns me on.
Farting in queues when there's a man behind me.
I fart in front of men whenever I can.
I asked her to fart again and she laughed
and let out a massive one, lasting around 10 seconds.
I suddenly started to feel intoxicated
and the next thing you know,
I was sitting in an ambulance being asked what I ingested.
How could I say?
Which would be in an awkward situation,
is trying to explain.
I smelled a takeaway fart from a Chinese woman in a non-cracker.
- I'm liking the situation of smelling a fart
and becoming intoxicated by it and getting drunk off of a fart.
- Yes, oh my god, I can't drive.
(humming)
- Oh wait, no, that's Crazy in Love, goddammit.
What's Drunk in Love?
Drunk in Love's the other Beyonce song.
♪ Drunk in love ♪
- Drunk on farts.
♪ In the honor of a crazy ♪
- Drunk on farts, we were talking about parodies earlier.
- Yeah, man, I haven't eaten anything all day,
so your fart is really, it's taking me out.
(laughing)
Might have to stay home.
- There's definitely farts.
- I need some bread.
- We were pre-gaming and you farted and I had to go to bed.
I do have to say this, if you're doing fasting,
like intermittent fasting, I've definitely had farts
where I'm like, that just broke my fast
'cause I smelled that.
There was too much particulate in that.
- Yeah. - You know?
'Cause you know you have-- - That was solid matter.
- You're allowed to have black coffee,
but you're not allowed to have coffee with milk.
Some of those got some milk in 'em, man.
- Yeah, for sure. - All right, there you go.
This is all you.
- That's a hanging cloud. - Yes, definitely.
- Yeah, all right, well.
- I love the Bible. - You guys have been reading.
I do really like the Bible. - The Bible is actually lit.
- You guys have been reading some,
I mean, let's be real.
You guys have been reading some deep cuts.
- Yes.
- A lot of people, they might not have heard
these Bible stories before, but for me,
I don't know if you can see this beautiful title page,
I wanna take it just right back to the beginning.
I'm like, DJ, run that shit.
- Hold that picture up.
- He saw the picture.
- Show the folks at home how beautiful that is.
- It is a fucking lovely picture.
- It's gorgeous, but I'm like, DJ, run that shit back.
We're taking it back to where it all began.
- The beginning of the Bible.
- Genesis one.
- We're starting Genesis 1. - Damn, damn.
- I'm just gonna go ahead and do it,
'cause people, you know, they hear these deep cuts,
they might fall astray.
- Yeah. - They don't remember
how it started.
Well, folks, this is how it started, okay?
- Wow. - Talk that.
- Genesis 1.
Oh, hi.
In te beginnin, Sealing Cat mated Teskai's and de Earth's,
but he did not eated dem.
De Earth's had no shapes and had a dark face,
And Ceiling Cat rode invisible bike over to waters.
At start, no has light.
- Oh God.
- And Ceiling Cat says, "I can has light?"
And light was.
And Ceiling Cat sawed to light to sees stuffs.
And splitted to light from dark,
but tat was okay 'cause kittays can see into dark.
And not trips over nethin'.
And Ceiling Cat said, "Light day and dark no day."
"It were first!" "One!" Exclamation points and one.
Wow.
And Ceiling Cat said, "I'm in your waters making a ceiling."
But he no yet make a 'er.
And he made it a hole into ceiling,
and Ceiling Cat dood to skies with waters down
and waters up. It happen.
Oh my God.
And Ceiling Cat said, "I can has to firmament."
(laughing)
- So it was Tatooth Day.
- Holy shit.
- It was Tatooth Day.
- That was the Tooth Day.
- Oh my God, I know that's why we celebrate Tooth Day.
- Yeah.
- And C-Link, God did all Tatooaters in your base.
- Shit.
For real?
- For real.
Yeah, and you know, I just wanted to kind of run it back
and do, you know, just back to Genesis.
- I like it, yeah.
That's like, you did also like, that's like clearly hip-hop inspired.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's been, it's, I think that this was, this was
written back when hip-hop was burgeoning.
Yes.
Kind of first appearing on the scene.
But yeah, so that's Genesis and then I have some stuff to share that's a
little more, you could call this apocrypha, I guess.
Okay.
But these are some things that...
I call a lot of stuff apocrypha.
Yeah, I do too. But people might not know this stuff is in the Bible.
Because it's not, it's not just words.
Believe it or not, it's not just words.
And I wanna pull up a kind of a visual aid here
'cause I want people to be able to see here
what's going on in the Bible.
And I just realized I forgot to put on my reading glasses,
but I'm gonna have to squint at the screen here.
So I'm gonna put on my reading glasses real quick.
- Put your reading glasses on.
- Can I get those on?
- What the bloody hell are you on about?
Put those on.
- Cam's Bible thing, okay.
- There you go.
Cam's Bible focals, now you can see.
- Wow, you look like John Lennon right now.
- Who?
- John Lennon.
- Is that a Bible character?
I don't think so. - It's a Beatles character.
- So let's talk about Bible stuff.
My Bible thing, I didn't write that on this slide.
That's kind of a little, I think it's a little reductive
and disrespectful of the Bible.
- Yeah, it's a little sad.
- I think our producer put this slide on there.
- Yeah, some agnostic producer,
some Bible thing, it's called a fucking verse, asshole.
- Yeah, well this is--
- Why don't you change that right now?
- Let me show you one of these things.
One of these things.
- Yeah, show me that. - Now you got me doing it.
- Great, great.
- The virus is spreading, great.
- But for those who don't like to read,
those who like pictures, there's actually some options.
Actually, some options in the Bible.
Okay.
So, here's this first thing.
This is called Spirit Man, and this is a superhero comic that
is in the Bible, the book of Spirit Man.
Oh, they have a podcast.
I'm familiar with...
And they have a podcast called Not About Us.
I know...
You said Not About Us?
Not About Us.
Kind of sounds like Potabat List.
It does kind of sound like that, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Not About Us?
Not About Us.
That's... we should send a DMCA.
Well, I think we should join their fan club.
But... so this one is kind of an option.
Now, this is a more advanced...
there's multiple comics in the Bible as most people know. Yeah. This is one of the
more advanced ones and this is kind of a... it's for the teens, okay? This is not for
the youngins. This is for the teens. Okay. And this was created, this was written.
We actually... this is actually one part of the Bible we know who made it. We know
the author? We know the author and it's Scott Alan Snyder and Everett Paul Burris.
Oh, wow. Are there any relation to Hannibal? Yes, actually. It's actually Hannibal's
great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-grandfather.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, 'cause this was, I mean, it's in the Bible.
It was written back in the, you know, you know,
back in the day.
So these are who create Spirit Man,
and we'll look at some examples of why.
I actually am not a huge fan of Spirit Man.
- Why?
- As Bible Comics go on, I'll show you why.
- Oh, okay.
- 'Cause I think it promotes some bad ideals.
- Okay. - Oh.
- For example, punching.
- Come on.
- Punching is present in Spirit Man.
- That is not good to do.
- And if we look at the art,
some scholars have even kind of proposed that perhaps these are pictures of
mentally challenged people being punched. Really? Based on the art, based on the art.
I would have to actually agree with you. Some Bible studiers. Except maybe the bald guy on
the right. There's no way he is mentally challenged. Yeah. He just doesn't look like that at all.
And it's also, it's promoting, it's promoting sound effects like wump and pow
which are a little too violent. What? Pow I've heard. Wump? Were you guys allowed to
say pal growing up I wasn't I definitely was no no because of what would it's
come along with you know language punch won't pal swamp but even beyond
violence lap which sometimes there's violence in the Bible we all know that
church yeah I wasn't allowed to say that I was I wasn't allowed to do ka-ching
either yeah yeah rang was a separate greed we were in a no-crying household
cuz we had a lot of like excess there was actually yeah I had to make do with
yeah I could get away with the third yeah but flump flump for now yeah no no
thwomps. Yowch. Nope. But anyway, it's not just punching, because there's
violence in the Bible. We can get over that. But you know what else isn't in
the Bible? What? Well, it is in the Bible, and I don't like that it's in the Bible.
Okay, what's that? It's these types of outfits. Oh my god. What's that? See, I don't...
There's something about the guy on the left. I like him. The guy on the left,
that's a girl. Oh. Well, that's also promoting androgyny. Yeah, promoting
androgyny a shirt that says gamer and a hat with a biohazard symbol on it no
thanks no thank you and then we have wait oh actually I like that the hat with the
biohazard that indicates this brain is atheist yeah that's true stay away put
in this brain by Rachel Maddow stay there yeah yeah good idea actually and but
then we have moody mopers I hate in the middle here and depressed this guy on
the far right here kind of looks like a long-haired mogul somebody look looks
like somebody maybe three weeks ago that guy definitely looks like he has a
a fucked up gut microbiome.
- It's not right to have hair that looks like that.
- I'm gonna have to agree with you.
- It's unchristian.
- Unkempt.
- And in addition to the outfits,
we also in Spirit Man have people in high school
with tattoos.
- Jesus Christ.
- Oh my God.
- And HS.
- These are high school students in Spirit Man.
- Really?
- They're completely covered.
- Wow.
- You can see they're standing next to lockers.
- They better be temporary.
- Yeah, those better just be shirt sleeves.
- Also, there's rubbing up on that girl.
- They're grabbing the girl.
- And that guy's rubbing up on that guy.
the girl has tattoos on her area.
- Oh, God no.
- Every student at this school is covered in tattoos.
- Are you sure this isn't a college?
- This is, no, it's a complete high school.
I read Spirit Man and I can confirm this is a high school.
- Oh my God, they have undercuts and side cuts.
- Yeah, it's just not right.
This shouldn't be in the Bible.
So if you're looking for a good alternative,
I like Captain Absolutely, Battle Against Dr. Relative.
- Dr. Relative?
- Dr. Relative is Captain Absolutely's villain.
- Oh, because it's Relatives and Absolutes.
- Let's see some stuff about Captain Absolutely here.
- Defending truth, justice, and lots more truth.
So Captain Absolutely here, here's Captain Absolutely,
here's his bio, which that's a thing
that I always thought the Bible should have more of,
is bio boxes, info bio boxes.
Mild-mannered librarian Josiah King
had never heard of the Bible.
(laughing)
Until a massive explosion revealed a chamber
full of banned books.
That night, Josiah read God's truth for the first time
and it, along with mysterious radioactive fumes,
changed his life forever.
- Wow.
- World view.
The Bible contains absolute truth,
timeless God-given wisdom on how to live.
Superpowers, strength, flight, height, six feet, one inch,
eyes, pale blue, favorite sport, wrestling.
- I would too if I had super strength.
- Biggest problem, paper cuts.
He reads a lot of books.
You will know the truth and the truth will set you free.
Three.
- The truth will set you free?
- Three.
- Wow.
John 8, 32.
And that's Captain Absolutely, but there are other characters.
Oh, there's also Hannah.
- Oh, hello, Hannah. - We all remember Hannah.
Seeing Cap's heroics inspired Hannah Lynn
to put her faith into action.
Sometimes this teenage inventor's zeal for God
leads her to take shortcuts,
like the time she stole Bibles from the library.
Naughty, naughty.
However, Hannah's courage and intellect--
- Wait, I thought there weren't any Bibles
from the library, it was banned.
Maybe after-- - Or she stole them.
That's why it was banned,
'cause people were stealing too much.
Yeah, you're not allowed to read a stolen book.
However, Hannah's courage, intellect, and heart
make her a terrific sidekick.
World view of the Bible changes lives.
We need to share its truth with as many people as possible.
Inventions, rocket boots, fire suit.
I've invented some of these things too.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Fire suit, that sounds kind of hellish.
Five feet four, so she's green eyes, petite, slim thick.
Favorite school subject, science,
and biggest problem, fear chemist.
I have no idea what that means.
As in my research, I could not find
if there's a character named fear chemist
if the Bible just I don't sometimes the Bible it's confusing. Yeah, it can be
weird and then there's a quote. Yeah, we don't have to read that but then we get
to dr. Relative God Darren tell his evilness Darren Gray was a computer
programmer Lord and Josiah's friend after the explosion Darren discovered
relative truth the idea that everyone makes their own rules since then he's
trying to take over metropolitan ville and then I draw a little metropolis
No, that's ancient. It's in Babylon.
Yeah, so it's pronounced different from how you would expect it,
because it was from another language.
And destroy God's truth once and for all.
I hate when radioactive fumes allow my friend to discover relative truth.
And just try to destroy God's truth.
It's so relevant to today. That's the thing about the Bible.
It really, it's part of your life.
Do you mean relative to today?
No, it's not relative today.
It's relevant.
Okay, continue.
Worldview. Right and wrong can change, depending on what's best for me at the moment.
at the moment. Weapons, neutralizer, laser, shackles of selfishness, and Lyris 1-6. I don't
know what Lyris means. Height, size is just a number. So he's small. Yeah. Eyes green,
favorite snack, sunflower seeds, and biggest problem, instruction manuals. Nobody tells
Dr. Relative what to do. Not a lot of brown-eyed people in this book. No, it's mostly green
and blue. I fucking hate you. Yeah. Alright, what else? Here's some pages from which it's
It's hard to see here, so I'll just describe it.
But basically, whereas in Spirit Man,
Spirit Man punches and uses punching,
and a sword actually,
Captain Absolutely actually uses humane weapons
like pillow fighting.
- Good. - And he actually
pillow fights the villains, as you can see happening
in almost five panels on this two-page spread.
- You know, we weren't allowed to say thwomp and thwack,
but we used to hit each other's pillows
into a bloody pulp. - See, this is perfect.
Thwomp and poof.
- Yeah, that's good. - And whoop, thwomp.
- That's not-- - Pidge?
- Yeah, I was allowed to say one.
- And God sees you is another side effect
that we're seeing at the bottom of the page there.
- And a rainbow.
- But that's Captain Absolutely.
I just have one thing that's in the Bible to close out with.
- Yeah, go ahead. - Okay.
- That I want everybody to be aware
that you can always flip to the back of the Bible.
It's still on this, what are you doing?
It's still on this.
Stop doing that.
Okay. - You are fail.
- I was talking to God.
- Don't give him that ego.
- And this is something that you can always look at
in the Bible if you're feeling like you need a little pick me up.
Okay, let's see.
And this is Christian Sonic art.
Whoa! Oh, I love this stuff.
From the book of Bible Bubba 20.
And so go ahead and click this link here.
This is, it's hosted online,
but it's also in the Bible over on one of these pages.
Wow.
So just scroll through this
and just show off what's going on here.
And you can always check this out in the Bible
if you need to.
It's a collection by Bible Bubba 20.
Oh my God.
It's Christ in white Sonic?
Wow.
Just keep going.
just keep just scroll through it. White Sonic reminds me of the Cherry. I love you God and Jesus, you know.
Here's uh this is Sonic at the crucifixion. Oh my God! He was there and he did nothing? I need, I need a
print of that. Here this one's really good. Um I really like the art in this one. It's a prayer.
So this is at the back of the book. This one is amazing too. I need a print of this too. I want
these in my home. Yep and we can just, okay and then that's also in the bible. There's some ads
and the Bible for diabetes.
Well, that was incredible.
And here's some more.
But we don't need to look at all of it.
Just know it's there.
Just know, go out and grab a Bible.
Flip to the index by yourself.
All right.
Well--
Well, that's the Bible.
Yeah.
I think that's it.
What else?
Our shareholder meeting--
Oh, yes.
--for this month is this Friday on the 27th at 5 PM Eastern.
We're going to need everyone to RSVP to that.
So go ahead and subscribe to the Executive Producer.
Tier if you haven't yet, you're gonna wanna do that.
- It's gonna be pretty big.
- It's gonna be a good meeting.
- It's gonna be a good time, man.
I'm also in Pittsburgh with old Adam Friedland,
February 3rd and the 4th, so come out to that.
And I maybe will tell some Bible stories on stage.
- Yeah, that's exciting.
- I am gonna be not in Pittsburgh,
I'm gonna be in Brooklyn.
- You're gonna be eating your own shit in Brooklyn, New York.
I'm gonna be in Brooklyn playing with my toys.
Tonight I'll be in the tub.
And signing off.
Scene.
Bye.
Amen.
Oh, I got a pee pee.
[BLANK_AUDIO]