(upbeat music)
- Ooh, here we go.
- My life be like.
- That's what you got?
- Yep.
- My life be like.
- Mm-hmm.
What do you mean, that's what you got?
- Not headphone headphones.
- Here's what you have, that's what you got.
- I'm doing an awesome new face.
- Okay, that's gonna be great on the audio.
- Yeah.
- Fist bump me, Patrick, and we fist bumped.
- See, that's how you do visual bits.
- Then I will also make a new voice up.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Wow.
- That's not new.
- Not really new.
That's new Sullivan voice.
- Oh, here, ah.
Fuck, how many voices are there that I can do even?
- You're not even the man of 101 voices.
Cameron's getting a call.
- Great, now you're wasting everybody's time.
- Who's wasting, Patrick's the one who said it.
I silenced the call and put it in my pocket.
What the fuck are you doing?
- This is a bit-- - Chill the fuck out.
- You're right, you're right.
There's a lot of stuff flying around my brain today.
I am too--
- I'm sure I can see it on the surface of your head.
- You can see it, I don't have my hat on because I--
- You don't even have headphones on.
- I know, I also am feeling-- - We got this new splitter.
- Which, by the way, once we understand my racial history,
I think that this might not age so well,
that you guys denied me headphones.
- We did not, he forgot his headphones.
- And you didn't even ask me to bring you headphones
like I usually, you usually ask me to do and I usually do.
- So you're saying because of my race that I'm stupid.
- We don't even know it yet.
We don't even know what you are.
The racializer has even--
- It seems like you're saying that about your own race,
which is kind of weird.
- We don't know who mine is yet, who I am.
Who am I?
We don't know.
- It's true.
- We don't fucking know.
- We have a big, big thing we're doing today.
- In the second half, so stay tuned.
- But in this first half, man, what did you guys eat for?
- We're just gonna shoot the crap.
- What did you guys eat for breakfast?
- I didn't eat breakfast yet.
- I had a McGriddle.
I was really hungry when I got here,
but I woke up at like 11, so you know how it is.
- Yeah.
- Had to get to work.
- Had to get to work, too.
- I was already late for work.
- Had to clock in.
We should get you a punch-in card.
Wouldn't that be fun?
- Yeah.
- That would be a great idea.
- We could put it up somewhere on here,
and then every episode we begin with me punching it in.
- That looks so much fun in movies.
- Yeah.
- You punch in and prove that you worked there.
- And then they changed it to just like a fucking iPad
in the back of the restaurant.
- I know, man.
- It's so fucked up.
Did you guys see this this it's a lot harder to do time theft that's for sure way harder
Oh, yeah, this amazing news story know about the twitch streamer who murdered somebody and he made a fake live stream while he went and
Killed this bitch no bitch. It wasn't a bitch
Okay killed this lady
He went and murdered this woman. She's not beautiful went and murdered this girlfriend his girlfriend this girlfriend
- He made, so he just like played a video through OBS.
- Yeah, he literally played a video on Twitch
and in the video he's like,
"By the way guys, my computer is so messed up
"that I can't interact with the chat today."
And people were just like, "Okay."
But yeah. - That's so crazy.
- He almost got away with it,
but there was about 40 CCTV cameras that recorded him
going over to the lady's house at the same time.
- Wow. - So yeah, that's pretty hard.
- Oh, those could have been pre-recorded too.
- That is exactly what I would argue in court.
I would say, see this, no video evidence can be submitted in court. It's all fucking useless bullshit.
See? That's actually really smart.
What is information? Information doesn't even...
Well if I could fool 120, 150 people with a fake video, who's to say you couldn't fool one person?
Exactly. And that's why I killed her, to prove that point.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
And then I would bow.
Yeah.
Most things that people do are to prove a point.
Like this.
We did this just to prove a point to somebody.
We started this whole podcast.
That's true.
Prove a point to that--
They said it couldn't be done.
--piece of crap that was doubting us.
Yeah, that's right.
And you know who you are, and we won't say your name, but--
why'd you cut to Cameron?
There we go.
That's a high camera.
You-- there's a lot of headroom on that shot.
I could sit up a little more.
- Yeah, there you go.
- This is how it's supposed to be.
- See, this is what, we're putting the camera like this
to train your posture.
- Yeah.
- I need to get a new chair that I can sit in.
I wanna get a lazy boy.
I think I'm at the time in my life
where I need to get a lazy boy
that I can sit and watch golf in.
- I think I need to be put into basically a saw trap
to fix my posture.
- Yeah.
- You know the one where it goes on their face
and it opens their mouth really wide?
- What?
- Have you not seen Saw?
- I think he would be too afraid of it.
- All of them?
- He's too afraid of it.
- I think the iconic saw, the one where it's the reverse bear trap.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I don't remember that. I've only seen the TV version.
- I think that's literally in all of them.
- I've only seen the TV version.
- He's afraid of saw.
- I guess they take out all the traps in the TV version.
- Yeah.
- It's just like, "How do we get out of this bathroom?"
And Jigsaw comes on and he's like, "There's one thing you need to do."
And then it cuts to them.
- It cuts to the end of the movie.
- I need to be put into this to fix my back, I think.
- A reverse bear trap?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I wanna get an inversion table.
- Yeah. - What's that?
- Yeah, it's a table where it goes upside down
and it hangs you.
It's like you ever done-- - Oh, I've seen those.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Yeah.
- And it pulls all the blood in your head.
- Does it do anything? - Until you die.
It kills you if you stay on for hours.
- Yeah. - You can die
if you fall asleep on it.
But that's true of everything I said.
- Then why do bats fall asleep upside down?
- Because their heads, or their brains,
are in their bottoms. - Oh.
- They're reverse people. - Okay.
there were a lot of it we had a good answer and i think that's not how i
had a yeah i know the results later one of you could be a reverse person uh...
that usually test for that and also be a little bit of a little further result
it would be a positive view of course person listen
reserve we can't get into the
back we're just we're literally how do you know how do you know you're not a
reserve of reversing
i might be but i was a it's impossible for caleb to be
because a reverse person person is you remember whatever person is read all
talked about it before. Not on the podcast. We've had a long conversation. That's why I
say we can't get into this. Oh, we have talked about reverse persons. Yeah, a reverse person
is somebody who they are their hair and their body is their hair. Now I remember. And they're
upside down. So Marge Simpson. We brought it up because Marge Simpson is blue. She's actually the
blue part and the yellow stuff is her hair. And that's the yellow hair that's on the bottom of
her. That's a reverse person. By the way, that's why it's not possible for Caleb to be a reverse
That, by the way, is the kind of conversation that we have that we aren't doing for the podcast.
When we sit around...
That's what we do when we turn the microphones off.
That's right.
I just assumed that we did that on the show.
No, we haven't.
We've never talked about that.
I've probably clocked, like if I had steam time, like steam play time on talking about reverse people,
it would probably be two and a half hours.
Yeah.
We talked about reverse people for like the entirety of Texas.
It wasn't even that no we were this was no reverse people was when we dropped Patrick off at the skate park
I'm that bridge the cool one. Yeah, oh
Here's just walked it around a lake a beautiful
Reverse person homie. I'm the blue stuff up top. Yeah, and my hair is yellow
I remember I was like skating FDR that was like a
Childhood dream of mine, and then you guys come over
Yeah, you say you come up to me and say Patrick. We got it go there's
is an amazing idea that we just had.
Yeah.
And the best part about that is that you would think like--
you'd be like, oh, well, that's kind of like, you know,
you're sitting in a bus for days and days.
It was day one.
Day one.
We were like four hours into the trip.
Yeah.
And we just got to Philadelphia, and we were like,
I'm a reverse person, homie.
Just making no sense, dude.
Man.
Yeah.
You got to get back on the road.
I know.
It really does amazing things to your brain.
- I feel like Jeremy Renner at the end of "Hurt Locker."
- Yeah.
- When he's like, "There's 16 more people dead
in Afghanistan," and then it just cuts to him on the road.
- Oh, we should make a movie with you called
"The Fart Locker."
- Yeah, "The Squirt Plurker."
- Doesn't make any sense.
- That's not, that's not.
- Yep, and it's a random movie, starring cheese.
(laughing)
Directed by sport.
actually like this now. What would happen in the random movie? What was it called? The Sporklerker?
The Sporkliker. Oh, Sporkliker. But it's like Loiker. You know you should put in that Miranda
Sings. Put her in there. I thought you were going to say Miranda Cosgrove. Both of them.
Both of them. Bofa. Bofa. Put both of them in. And that's the main character's name is
Bofa. And there's a lot of hilarious situations that he gets into because of his name. That
That would be a funny movie to have a character named Bofa, and it could be called "Bofa
Deez Adventures" and he has two adventures during the movie.
I met a guy...
It's a documentary about the only guy ever to have two adventures in one day.
Right when you think the movie's over, he's got to start his second adventure.
I met a guy this weekend named Draven.
Draven?
Like from League of Legends?
I don't know, man.
I got scared.
Two Dravens I can think of, there's a Draven in League of Legends and Draven is the name
is Brandon Lee's name in the Crow I think.
Oh and Draven Cosgrove.
And Draven Cosgrove.
And also this guy Draven that I met in League of Legends.
Miranda Cosgrove.
So that's a third Draven.
Miranda Cosgrove's husband.
It was really, you know when somebody tells you, you know when you're like hey nice to
meet you what's your name and someone just takes you so just off guard with their name.
I had that and he was like, I'm Caleb and he was like I'm Draven and I went oh.
that and I was like oh that's rude yeah shouldn't when somebody tells you the
name you shouldn't go like oh what okay hell is your name
Draven I've had a few of those yeah people doing that where's no no what's
your what's the worst name you've ever seen somebody have not the worst my
worst my worst reaction my worst reaction was when and this I think we
met this guy on tour so if you're listening shut out beating a guy named
Jafar. Oh my God. Yeah. I bet we met at Jafar. Was that in Seattle? My worst reaction was
that I made him show me his ID. Yeah. That was in Seattle, right? Which is probably not
a good thing to do. No. Yeah. No, but I had to. There was like two months. Jafar. Two
months during COVID where we were just obsessed with Jafar. Yeah. Jafar's a funny character.
Dude, Jafar is good looking. He would be, if he was in New York City, he'd be walking
for Balenciaga.
Oh, he would.
Absolutely.
Yeah, he's skinny.
I mean, and perfect too, because they're satanic as fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of Satan, I got really into this morning, I really got into the Jesus Twins.
They were this really bad musical act that just walked into Howard Stern one day, and
they were like, "You got to let us on the air, Howard."
And he was like, "Okay, whatever."
And they just started talking about how they were going to be famous musicians and shit,
and he was like, "Okay, we'll play a song."
And they played like the worst song ever.
And then they kept coming on Howard Stern
until eventually, it had been like a couple years
since they'd come on.
And then one of them just like walked in just alone
and he had like a shaved head.
And they were like, "Hey, you're one of the Jesus Twins."
He was like, "No, I'm not the Jesus Twins, I'm Satan."
And he like sat.
- Dude, that's the opposite of Clipse.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He went from no malice to malice.
That is incredible. It was a reverse clips. They did a reverse clip and he like
walks and he sits down in on the Howard Stern show and they're all like so Jesus
twin like it's so crazy I haven't seen you in years and he's like uh-huh uh-huh
and they're like so where'd you come from like what brought you here and he's
like I was in a mental hospital in Long Island and I just ran out of it yesterday
and he just escaped a mental hospital and then a couple years ago he got shot and killed by the police.
Pretty amazing story.
That is incredible.
The Jesus Twins.
That needs to be a movie.
What happened to the other twin?
He is alone. He doesn't have his brother anymore.
Okay.
Yeah, it's pretty sad.
That is sad.
And he's an atheist now.
He's agnostic.
I think I would be agnostic about that.
Oh, actually there was an appearance between the one where he was crazy and when he killed himself,
or when he died with a cop's gun,
where they both came back in and they were like,
yeah, we're back to being the Jesus twins
and I'm not Satan anymore.
(laughing)
- Wow. - It's pretty awesome.
Yeah, and then they got banned for saying
something anti-Semitic to Howard Stern.
- Ah, yeah. - Damn.
- Which is Jesus twins, Jesus was a Jew.
- Yeah. - That's actually true.
- Yeah, so I don't get how you could call yourself
a Jesus twin.
- What did they say to Howard Stern?
- They said something that I can't, well,
I'm, you know what, let me find out what my DNA results are
and then I'll decide whether or not
I tell you what they say to Howard Stern.
- Okay. - Okay?
- So I'll remember that. - It would suck to be
the Jesus twin that didn't become Satan,
especially if you're brother, if he was flip-flopping.
- Yeah. - If he was like,
and I'd have to, I'd call him up and I'd be like,
"Hey buddy, are you Satan today?"
- Yeah. - "You wanna hang out?"
But before I come over, tell me the truth,
level with me. - You gotta tell me.
- Are you Satan today? - Be real in the day.
- You know what would suck though is you're
somebody who believes that you are now like Satan or you're possessed by like or
you are you've become some biblical entity but it's just like one of the
fucking side characters you know yeah like yeah I don't Job I'm Job or I'm like
what world is this place is Job a side character who's okay interesting I don't
know too much about the Bible I can tell I think Jesus is the main guy he's the
guy that most people think they're the second coming he's only in half of it
the guy the guy that everyone thinks that they're the second coming of and
- And he's in the bad part of it.
- But who, like, in the, like,
oh yeah, I'm the second coming of Peter.
- Peter is a massively important character in the Bible.
- Okay, then who's the least important character
in the Bible?
- Probably one of the fucking girls, I don't know.
- Yeah, okay, then saying that, like, you know,
I've been--
- Bathsheba.
- Yeah, Bathsheba, okay.
- Bathsheba, fuck her, she's a hoe.
- Yeah, I'm the second coming of Bathsheba.
- Get this about Bathsheba, man,
she took a shower outside.
- Oh, and that's where the word bath comes from?
- I don't think so.
- No.
- But Bathsheba also is represented,
there's an episode of Veggie Tales where,
and the whole thing with Bathsheba
is that she tempted a guy into fucking her,
and yeah, and cheating on her husband,
and it goes really bad.
But in the Veggie Tales version,
they were like, man, we have to tell that story.
There's so many stories in the Bible,
but we have to tell that one
about this guy fucking this girl.
So instead of sex, instead of this girl's,
or this guy's wife that this guy wants to have sex with,
will make it a rubber ducky that he's taking a bath with.
And so that's what the--
- Oh yeah, don't covet.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, don't covet that ducky.
- Yeah. - Yeah, but Larry.
Larry covets the duck.
- I'm really glad that VeggieTales was covering coveting.
- Do you guys know the one, the really good Bible verse
about the bald-headed guy and the bears?
- Where he kills a bear?
- That's him on Fire Island.
- No, but VeggieTales should adapt this one.
Here, Jubio, search.
Search, if you guys haven't read this Bible,
this is like the best Bible, search Bible verse.
I think it's Elijah, search Elijah Bear.
- Does he, wait, does the bear kill a bunch of kids
or something? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here, click this, here, I'll read this.
Then he went up from there to Bethel,
and as he was going up, by the way,
young lads came out from the city and mocked him
and said to him, "Go up, you bald head,
"go up, you bald head."
- Come on. - When he looked behind him
and saw them, he cursed them in the name of the Lord.
Then two female bears came out of the woods
and tore up 42 lads of their number.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- And he went from there to Mount Carmel
and from there he returned to Samaria.
- That is the most amazing thing ever.
You kill 40 kids and you go to Mount Carmel?
(laughing)
- Yeah, Candy Mountain.
- Two female bears came out of the woods
and tore up 42 lads.
- Yeah, two female bears.
Yeah, fucking Burt Kreischer and Tom Segura.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
We need to move to Los Angeles
and have a video podcast of us in Los Angeles
where we have on just random fucking guys.
- The LA, the LA creme de la creme.
- We need to link up with Bobby Lee Wright.
- Oh yeah. - Oh man.
- Yeah, that would be good.
- I would do anything to link up with Bobby Lee
and have him tell me some story.
- Yeah. - About Jordan Peele.
- Damn. - Yeah.
- Yeah, now I'm just thinking about the possibilities
if we lived in LA.
- Oh my God.
- We could maybe even become famous actors or musicians
in Beverly Hills. - We could go to Los Feliz.
- Holy shit, man, we could surf.
- Yeah. - We could be surfers.
- We could go to-- - Oh my god.
- We could go to a coffee shop and go like this.
- We could wake, guys, we could wake up every day.
- Type in the coffee shop.
- We need to move to Los Angeles, it's perfect.
- We could go to Silver Lake.
- We could wake up in Silver Lake or Echo Park
and we could walk down to our coffee shop.
- Wake up to Silver Lake. - We could get a oat milk
soy latte. - Go to Hollywood.
- Then go to Beverly Hills. - Yes.
- We could go to Inglewood. - Pasadena.
- Mm-hmm.
- The Palisades. - Then we gotta go to Inglewood,
- We gotta give the hood some love.
- We gotta go to Compton.
- There we go to Ladera Heights.
- And then we could go up to Seattle.
- That's too far, man.
- That's on a train, though.
- But we could go up there.
- We could take another-- - 'Cause we're on the
same coast, so we could go up there.
- You could take a four-hour train ride to Oakland.
- And then we'll take another train ride from there
to Seattle. - Go to Emeryville.
Emeryville, a beautiful city.
- And then we'll go down to--
- Pixar in Emeryville.
- Why are you talking like this right now?
- Emeryville's in Pixar.
- Why are you talking about Pixar?
- Emeryville and Oakland.
- Why are you doing that?
- We're talking about Los Angeles stuff.
- But why are you not--
- I'm doing an LA accent.
- You're not saying anything.
This is just, you're talking weird today.
- I'm not talking weird today.
- Yeah, you are.
You keep being like, also you're doing this.
You're punctuating everything by tapping.
- I do that all the time.
I don't know why. - I know, that's new.
That's been a new thing with you.
- I don't know why I do that.
- You've changed so much since I've known you.
You've gone through so many different phases
of the way that you act.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and now you're in this one.
- And now, listen.
- It's 'cause of the video.
After we've seen you change, today is the day you're gonna see us change.
Mm-hmm.
Into a different color.
We're gonna completely...
You know what?
My life is gonna change today.
Speaking of, I don't know if anyone wants this.
Your Discover card?
Nope.
Here, show that.
I have a Clipper card with 775 on it.
So if you need to ride the bus in Emeryville...
What's a Clipper card?
It's how you get on the bus.
It's not a haircut?
See, you did it again!
You hit the table again to finish your sentence.
I think it's because I'm in the corner.
It's how you get on the bus.
What is that? I don't know why, but it helps me speak.
You know what happened?
We were talking about clips earlier.
He's trying to do grinding.
Oh true, let me get you a pencil.
I used to do that, but I had the worst rhythm ever.
(laughter)
(rhythmic beat)
Yo Caleb, play the grinding beat.
Yeah, I got you guys.
(rhythmic beat)
It was pretty awesome, and basically
Basically everybody thought that I was gangsta.
Yeah I would do it and I would just go like, "Ow!"
(Laughter)
"Ahh! Fuck off!"
I played it too hard dude.
"Ow! My finger!"
I don't think I can do the grind 'em beat anymore guys.
They need to make more songs that you can use a desk to create.
I'll say it man.
There's still pen tapper guys.
There's still guys who are really into...
Do you guys remember...
Do they still do when they do the harder, better, faster, stronger on your fingers?
No, but they need...
They need a fucking song to do that again.
Oh yeah, you're right.
What was that called?
What was that video?
Finger banging.
Finger bangers.
But they did it with like,
there was like other songs
where they would do it with multiple people too.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm saying, that needs to come back.
Yeah, this is what it was.
Work it.
Do it.
Work it's easy, that's work it.
You know, yeah.
I could do that.
It's gotta be Daft Punk songs, right?
'Cause that's what the--
Well you could do any song though
that has a lot of words in it.
I was gonna say,
I was gonna say you try to do that with--
Rap God.
superheroes by Daft Punk. No, you should do a rap god. There's three lyrics in that song.
Yeah. Barry Manilow's single. Rap god would be the best one, man.
Rap god would be... Here's what I would do. I'd go, right when he starts rapping, I'd
turn around and the entire... I'd be on my back.
That's a great idea. That's pretty funny. And then just the front just says, "I'm
beginning to feel like a rap god, rap god." Yeah. And then you'd cover up rap god.
And then on this side it says Eminem on this arm. He doesn't ever go Eminem.
I don't know, Eminem, Rap God, featuring...
Who's it featuring?
The other guy.
You know who needs to link up with Eminem, dude?
The most amazing combination in the world is Eminem and Sia.
My two favorite artists when they...
My mom and dad, for real.
They are my mom and my dad.
For real, for real, parent vibes.
Have you guys seen what Eminem looks like now?
He looks like he's in disguise all the time.
Yeah.
He always has, he looks like he's got...
He dyes his beard dark.
- He's got a completely black facial hair
and like a fucking camo army hat.
- Yeah.
- And he walks around and he says he's sorry to Haley.
And I don't know who the fuck Haley is.
- Haley is a barista he yelled at.
- Oh, okay, that makes a lot more sense.
- I thought it was Haley's Comet.
- Yeah.
- He should do a cover of that song.
- The Shine Down song?
♪ I just saw Haley's Comet ♪
- You know I saw them live?
- Yeah.
- As the lyric of that song, I just saw Haley's Comet.
♪ I just saw Haley's Comet ♪
I should do a bunch of thoughts that are just things they see. I went to go see
the- I just saw the- Walrus and Gromit. Walrus and Gromit. Walrus.
I was like, I saw the moon. I saw a constellation. I drove four hours to
Charlotte to go see a shine down with my cousin and Chad. You guys know Chad. I
brought Chad with me and we went, we got there and me and my cousin went in.
And that's the virgin. And Chad didn't, my buddy Chad didn't have a, he didn't
have a ticket, but he was like, I'll just buy one when we get there and he's
he was like 16 and we get there and the guy was scalping him he was like how
much for a ticket the guy said $250 and so Chad was like okay I'm just gonna sit
in the car while the concert and so we went we enjoyed the concert it was
completely incredible. Did he drive? No no so we went back and he was in the back of my dad's
Suburban he was completely naked asleep in the back. It was like the middle of
summer it's like a hundred and five degrees outside and I didn't leave the
keys with him so he just like sweat to death and had a heat stroke in the back of the car.
It was pretty incredible dude. Wow. He just drove home man. Yeah. Yeah. He had a great
time. He has to have. Yeah. Well. You wanna start racializing? I think it's time to start
race off. Oh my god. Ladies and gentlemen. We have the machine here. The racializer. Welcome
into the race off. This is the racializer. This is how we will be.
It scans DNA. It does scan DNA.
And we have two DNA samples. We have one sample that's been pre-scanned,
I believe, that we wanted to start with. Patrick has already had his.
Oh yeah. So the background here. Me and Caleb, we don't know our DNA statistics.
Patrick already knows his. So me and Caleb will be having a race off.
I didn't even get a DNA sample, I just know it based on feeling.
Uh-huh, and he has a vibe check, I guess.
What the hell is he on about?
He's gonna do his vibe.
My vibe.
First.
So, we're gonna...
And then we're gonna go through and we're gonna actually figure out...
It's basically gonna be a competition.
Scientifically, it will be a competition.
But Patrick is gonna serve as our control because we're pretty sure of what he's got going on.
Could you go over to Patrick's control DNA report?
Yeah, he is the control group.
All right. So this is my DNA report. I'm in control of the experiment. Yeah.
And the clicker does not work.
It's not on. Now it's on.
You know, 99 percent British and Irish.
Ninety nine point nine percent. Ninety nine point nine percent. Yeah. Wow. Yeah.
What does that feel like, man? What does that say? Yeah.
What is the 99.9? There's a new gray. There's a gray thing.
0.1% I cannot see what that says. What? 0.1% bullfrog? Bullfrog? When was that
updated? July 15th? Yeah I haven't looked at this in a while. Bullfrog? Click open the
like the drop-down. Ribbit ribbit ribbit ribbit ribbit ribbit croak ribbit ribbit
croak croak croak. And do you understand what that means? I don't know I don't speak a
a lick of bullfrog. A lick? I don't speak like one of these. Yeah, I guess. You bullfrog?
I guess this makes sense. This is a picture of my mom and dad. That, okay. And that came
up on 23andMe? Yeah. Okay, I would like to say that actually does look a lot like your
(laughter)
- That looks just like your fucking dad, dude.
That is what I imagine when I think of your dad.
Your mom looks like that with no mustache, pretty much.
- And then there's my grandpa.
- Okay, alright.
- Well, I thought you'd be able to see the slides better.
I thought we'd be able to look at all the places
that I've tested.
- Well, it's always the small.
- I guess it's really small, yeah.
- You need to make it big when you--
- Oh, here we go.
- We have a system for you, I'm making you bake for us.
- So all the people who are watching and listening
in the UK or whatever can say like,
oh yeah, he has a county--
- County mayo. - County mayo vibes.
- Bro, you're county mayo?
- Okay, no surprises there, right?
- Yeah, county cork, yeah,
'cause all the wine I've been drinking.
- County Kerry, kind of John Kerry, Jim Kerry vibes.
County limerick. - Can you move over
to the UK, the UK here?
- Who gives a fuck about the UK?
- Well, I wanna see what parts of the UK--
- I thought you hate the UK.
Well yeah, but like, I don't know, maybe it's very,
oh okay, looks like I've got some Scottish in me.
You got some Manch in you, some Manchester?
That is amazing.
Morrissey vibes.
Yeah, no doubt.
Wick.
You're from a place called Wick?
Oh, Newcastle-
It's Scandor Wick.
Newcastle-Upon-Tyne.
There, I got a lot of DMs from somebody
who kept asking me if I've tested
for Newcastle-Upon-Tyne for some reason.
What are you talking about?
Somebody kept asking me, I forget who they are,
but that's gonna be really exciting for them.
- I don't think that anybody's gonna care
all that much, if I'm being honest.
- One person, and they'll say it,
and they'll message me and say,
"Thank you for finally answering it."
- All right, well that's amazing.
So you're 99.9% human.
- And I'm a little bit bullfrog.
- And a little bit bullfrog.
Thank you so much for that.
- I guess that must be very recessive.
Your dad was a frog, and you're 0.1% frog.
- Yeah, you look way more like your mom.
You favor your mom in a major way.
So let's go ahead and put our samples in the racializer.
I got my blood sample right here.
I'm ready to put it in the racializer.
Cameron, you want to grab your sample?
Yeah, sure, hold up.
Cameron, you're supposed to bring blood.
That's my blood.
That's your blood?
This is blood?
This came out of you with a syringe?
Yeah, well, not with a syringe, but yeah.
It's stark off-white.
Well, it's old.
And there's not that much of it.
It was sun, it got sun bleached.
Got sun bleached?
Well, I knew what we were going to do
is I got the sample a few weeks ago.
I left it in my backyard.
and I was actually full when I...
- Yeah, it's blood.
That's pretty obvious, it's blood.
Yeah.
All right, so let's apply this.
- Yeah, let's hook these up to the...
- Oh, wow.
The cables here.
- Yeah, go ahead, Pat.
- Who's going first?
- Well, we need it, we should,
I guess, yeah, we can do Cameron's first, right?
- Okay. - We're gonna do mine first.
Do we?
Oh, wait, well, first, actually,
we have a surprise for you. Yeah, here, give me a second. We have a surprise for
you. So guys, here's the thing, this race off thing, the whole point of this, right,
is that it has to be a competition. Yeah. Right? We want to see who wins, okay? So we
thought, man, that's really hard to do if we don't have kind of an established
ranking. Okay. Okay? So obviously me and Cameron, we're gonna be a little bit
biased because we're trying to win. So Patrick, we made this for you. This is
Patrick's race ranking.
Hold on, let me move the ratio later really quickly. So this is your
race ranking. So this, you know, we've heard you talk about wanting to do
this before. So, Pat, we have to... Wait, wait, wait. So I have to do this before? This is how we
get... We have to figure out what the points are going to be. So here, there's some
numbers in here. So these all have point values, okay? So these are point values
that you have to associate with these. So these go all the way from 2 to negative
23. Yeah, so... You can put it down on the table. It'll be visible. You have positive 2 all the way down to
-23. -Okay.
Okay, so that's, if you give it a positive 2, that'll be plus 2 points.
-Yeah, I can -12. There's a lot of numbers in here.
-Yeah, there's 24. And you also have a free space here. -And you have a free space, which means that you can make up whatever you,
just pick anyone that isn't on the board and you can give them a, kind of a wild card.
-Oh yeah. -So here we have a rating. -An official -23?
-So let's just go across. -I get a 22, I think. -A 22, I think.
-My is the lowest one. -Yeah, this is the lowest one.
So French gets negative 22 points.
So let's hope we don't pop French.
That's going to be a bad, bad news.
Yeah, that's going to be rough.
That's going to be terrible for you.
We got-- here, can we just go in order from left to right?
Egyptian.
What are we giving Egyptian?
Um--
And remember, there's only--
Let's go plus 2.
Plus 2 for Egyptian.
All right, so Egyptian is the highest.
That's the highest.
That's the highest you can get.
So now Irish.
Irish, I mean, you know.
You're going to give me-- all right.
Just so you know, Patrick, there also
is Indigenous American, Spanish, Moroccan, Somali, Saudi
Arabian, Mexican, and Korean.
And you've just used two of your positive values.
You've got a long way to go, Pat.
So, okay, so free space is one.
So what are you filling in?
- Oh, that's just, I mean, that's just there.
- Okay, so that's just to get rid of it.
- Oh yeah.
- All right, so now every other value
is gonna be negative.
- Next is British.
- So it's only negative.
- Yeah, yeah.
So British, what are you giving British?
Negative 21, I like that.
- Okay, all right.
- I like that move.
- Yep, all right.
- Indigenous American.
(laughter)
- Negative one, interesting.
So you think the indigenous Americans are the negative.
- You should lose points to be a negative.
- At this point, honestly, there's no way I can win this.
(laughter)
Optically.
There's no way I can put anything on here
that'll make me look good or bad.
Everything that I do will be questioned.
So what is happening right now is a complete randomization.
I have no--
So you don't even think that there--
I don't care if you're black, white, purple, or yellow.
OK.
All right, Spanish is up next.
OK, let's go.
I just saw you reach for the negative 3
and then got the 16 because you remembered
that Spain is in Europe.
All right, then we gave French negative 22.
Now we have Finnish.
Finnish.
I want to finish this whole thing.
Yeah, you want to finish off the people of Finland.
So go ahead and give them--
negative 7, OK, I like it.
Interesting.
Portuguese.
All right, Portuguese.
Portuguese, yeah.
Negative 19.
OK, Algerian.
Yeah, what are we thinking about Algerian?
Negative 14.
Interesting.
Cypriot from Cyprus.
OK, don't know too much about them.
So I mean, my opinion is going to--
Negative 2, wow.
All right, Pole of Not--
from not knowing that much about them.
All right, negative 3.
OK, now Polish.
Polish.
And upside down negative 15.
That's 51.
I like it.
OK, Moroccan.
Again, don't know too much.
To North Africa.
Negative-- but they also speak French.
So is that making you rethink anything?
It's making me rethink a little bit.
We-- oh, you can switch it out if you want to.
Go ahead, switch it out.
We're good.
We're good now.
No, switch it out.
All right, that's fine.
Saudi Arabian.
Let's see Saudi Arabian.
Remember Jamal Khashoggi?
Oh my god, you have just swayed me.
Yeah, that's right.
Yep.
So you think it's negative 20 to be Saudi Arabian.
Negative 20 points for being Saudi Arabian.
Look, as a big Khashoggi head--
Yeah, he was a huge fan of his journalism.
Yeah.
No, honestly, the coolest thing that guy ever did
was get turned into shark food.
[LAUGHTER]
That's the only cool thing he ever did.
Next is Ghanaian, or--
Oh, like the pigs.
Yes.
From-- yeah.
Negative 5.
OK, Somali.
Somali.
What are we doing for Somali?
OK, I just want to point out, you got French on here twice.
Yeah, that's Juvia's fault.
Yeah, a Polish guy did this.
Oh, OK.
Somali.
OK, not a big Captain Phillips fan.
No.
All right, next is--
I watched that.
That's the first time I've watched a movie,
and I hope that bad guys win.
That's right.
Negative 2 for Somali.
They still give him a negative.
Interesting.
Mexican is up next.
And remember, there is a Mexican guy on the phone with us
right now.
It's the second lowest number I have left.
Negative 6, OK.
Negative 6.
French.
The second lowest number you have left.
French again.
I did 22.
We'll say this is the French people abroad,
so maybe like kind of Montreal.
French-Canadian.
Yeah, Francophones.
Well, when you say that--
Negative 9.
OK.
All right, Italian.
Minus-- oh, that's pretty high for Italian.
That is high, yeah.
Girlfriend's Italian.
Unassigned.
Next was unassigned.
I'm not sure what--
I got to put negative 8 just to keep things good at home.
Yeah, I get it.
Unassigned, I guess, would be every other race in the world.
These are all the 23 and me.
OK, so anything else is negative 17.
OK, Indonesian.
Oh, man.
So by the way, just--
Yeah, you're on the left.
--people at home, he has negative 11, 12, 10, and 13 left.
He goes negative 10 on Indonesia.
All right, so we have Korean.
And a negative 11 for Korean.
Now, Orc.
Orc negative 12.
So let's look at it.
Let's pause here.
Let's look at everything that's below Orc.
everything that he has higher than orc.
Okay, so higher than orc he has--
- British is lower than orc,
so what race is worse, Spanish, French,
British, Portuguese, Algerian?
- But better than orc, he says it's,
or yeah, sorry, so yeah.
- Look, I've already said, I've already said,
- It's worse to be Saudi Arabian
than to be an orc, says Patrick.
(laughing)
- Nothing I can do is gonna make myself look good.
- And the Korean people coming in just above orc,
- I'm just barely edging out Orcs.
- Okay, so there it is folks.
- Scandinavian at negative 13.
- This is Patrick's official race rankings.
Pat, go pop your head up up top
and give it a big thumbs up.
This is all you.
Me and Cameron have been planning this for about a month.
We got so excited when we had this idea.
And this is gonna be basically--
- This is how we will score our 23 and over.
- This is how we're gonna score everything,
which we're gonna start right now.
But first we're gonna need to put our blood DNA
into the Racialator.
- All right, Cameron, you do the honors.
This is you first.
- Okay.
- And we will revisit the board just to make sure.
We'll tally up points afterwards.
- Wait, no, you hook it up to the--
- I hook it up?
I don't spray it onto the front of it?
- You spray it on the table and then put--
- You tried to do a cum shot on the Racialator.
- It's not a cum shot, it's a blood shot.
- A blood shot, yeah.
- Excuse me, you.
- Put it on the table.
- Oh, put it on the table, okay.
- GPO, can you punch in on it?
- All right, here we go.
- Okay, just squirt it right there.
(laughing)
- And now those cables are connected to the sample.
- Oh my god, wait I hear it whirring.
- Whoa.
- Oh my god, oh my god, okay, alright.
So Cameron, welcome to your race report.
This is all you, dude.
- I have, yeah, also me and Caleb
have not looked at our results at all.
- No, we have not looked at our results.
- Jubio put all this stuff together.
- Jubio's the only person who knows our DNA ancestry.
And I honestly, I have chills in my body.
And I wanted so badly to get to this part.
Can I make a few predictions?
Yeah, okay. That's what I want to get into first.
I want to know, we'll do this before each of us,
what have you been told is your history?
The only thing that I,
so whenever I asked when I was a kid,
my parents would just say a bunch of random stuff
that I don't remember because I was a kid.
But the one I remember is,
I'm pretty sure I'm at least part Polish.
I think that that's going to be on there.
I would guess that based on how you act.
but by by vibes that I've been good but that I've been trying to I was
trying to cultivate and what I'm hoping for I'm hoping we could see on this
presentation I'm hoping for some Native American some Mexican yeah and some
African so Mexican that's how you said that I've been and I've been trying to
cultivate that in my you're trying to do what before I gave the DNA sample I was
thinking I was just thinking a lot of stuff you're doing the secret you're
trying to manifest exactly Native American Mexican and African let's get
right in. I'm getting, I'm getting, I'm squirming in my seat trying to see your race. Me too,
I'm excited. I honestly cannot wait to know everything about your racial history. Alright,
alright, we're ready? Yes. Alright, let's find this, let's find this out here. I'm 100% y'all.
At least you're whole. I'm 100% that bitch. I'm honestly so nervous. I'm really liking
the amount of, of, you have a lot of squints on your heart. Yeah, you have a lot of stuff
on this and I think this big blue thing I'm gonna guess right now probably some
British and Irish stuff. I'm gonna guess that you are a hundred percent amazing
friend. Oh my god. Okay I wish I thought of saying that. This is even more nerve-wracking because I didn't make this
PowerPoint so I know what's gonna happen when I swear. I'm terrified. Okay.
European 92% wait only 92% oh my god that's pretty crazy I've been saying for
weeks I think there's gonna be something you might have a fucking amazing
surprise in stores let's check out I'm guessing this will be the European stuff
right here 56% okay what's Northwestern Northwestern is gonna be like British
and Irish I think. No, no, no, it's like Polish. I'm sure it is actually, we'll find out. Alright,
what's in there? British and Irish 44%. 44% British and Irish, that's not what I was expecting
that much. Wow dude, almost half British. That's pretty crazy. 4% Scandinavian, .8% Finnish.
And then broadly Northwestern European is 6.9%. I did not think I was going to be that
much British and Irish. Hey, County Cork, me too. That's amazing, you guys might be
we're cousins related friend we probably are related that's a way to look it up.
Well so that's but that's only 50% of of this of this of even the European part yeah so what
else do you have let's see here.
Eastern Europe well I mean 9% when he numbers that's pretty excited to me that is I do like
that a lot.
A lot more than I thought all right here.
- Lesser Poland. - Voivodeship.
- Why would they say lesser Pol--
- Yeah, why are they calling it lesser Poland?
And one region?
Is that 29%?
Is that what that means?
- Oh, he's in the and one region.
- I don't know. - Oh yeah.
- You are a hooper 'cause you're tall.
I don't know, press next, it'll probably tell you.
- Whoa. - Oh my God.
- Oh, Southern European, Spanish, and Portuguese.
So you're 30% Polish.
- Wow. - That's a lot.
- Yeah, that's a-- - Is that more than you thought?
- I think that is more than I thought.
- That's a fucking lot of Polish, man.
- I thought I was gonna be, all together,
was gonna have 50% DNA maybe.
- Yeah. - So the fact that I'm already
at 80% is kind of blowing my mind.
- It's kind of surprising you.
Her Portuguese man of love.
- That's you. - That's me, yeah.
Oh, more Polish.
- Yeah. - But.
- Dude, I can't believe you're 30% Polish.
- That's pretty crazy, I'm pretty happy with that.
- That's, now you have like a,
30%, that's enough for it to be your identity.
- I live in a Polish area.
- That's your cultural identity is Polish.
- Oh my God, I probably gravitated there unconsciously.
- Holy fucking shit. - You definitely should.
Holy shit.
That was a Polish magnet.
All right.
All right, let's keep going.
Let's get into the good stuff.
The small percentages are the exciting ones.
OK, 92% European.
Yeah, OK.
All right, press next.
Let's see what's next.
Oh!
4.3% indigenous American, dude.
That's fucking right.
I knew it.
Wow.
That is amazing.
Oh my God.
- Wow. - He was prepared, dude.
- I manifested it, I knew it was gonna happen.
- Wow, dude, victory lap. - Oh my God, I'm so happy.
- That is incredible, I'm so happy for you, bro.
- 4.3%.
What's that? - That's huge.
- That's a 20th?
- Yeah, one 20th, dude. - Wow.
- You're card carrying-- - I'm gonna find out my tribe.
- You have to. - Yeah.
- Wait, does it tell you?
- I hope it tells me.
- It might tell you, who knows?
- Yeah, it's gotta tell you.
- Yeah, okay, it just says 4.3% indigenous American.
These could be your cousins.
- Those could be my cousins.
- You blend right in.
- Damn, that means your ancestors did something really--
- That's incredible. - This is why--
(laughing)
- That means your ancestors did something terrible.
- Well, my great grandpa--
- What, you think it's terrible to use
every part of the animal?
That's what you're saying, Patrick?
- My great grandpa did claim that he was Native American,
but it was unclear if he actually was.
- Oh, wow. - So this is answering
a lot of questions. - So there's something, so--
So the question has been answered.
So the question, so yeah, what, I mean, what,
great grandpa, that's what, what percent is that?
That is 16th and eighth, I don't know.
Yeah.
Grandpa percent, so that's--
That'd be an eighth.
An eighth?
Yeah.
Okay.
So it was like, so basically,
if one of his parents was 100% Native,
then you would be about,
you'd still be somewhere between that and--
So the point is he was completely not lying.
Yeah, that's pretty incredible.
And he was 100% Native American.
(laughing)
and he was not just a really dark-skinned white guy.
- That is so amazing to know that, man.
- That is really exciting, but I think there's probably still,
that doesn't add up to 100 yet, does it?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so that's, okay, so we have, I think, 4% left.
- We got some purple stuff.
- Wait, keep going, but I have to send,
I'm gonna send something to Jubio really quick,
but you can keep going.
- Okay.
- All right, I'm excited to see what this is.
Western, Asian, and North African 2.5%!
- No way!
No way dude. What? Oh my god dude it got even better. It got better bro. I'm the whitest
guy on the show. Dude you're African. Oh my god. Western Asian. I've been walking around
my apartment saying to my girlfriend I'm gonna get my test results it's gonna blow your mind
I'm gonna be African. You're gonna be African? Well where, where, cause you could be like
Like don't try to downplay this you fucking cracker. It says North African. That's the opposite of South African. I forgot.
We get to call him, you get to call him, I mean I don't know yet, but you get to call him Whitey.
That's right. I've already been called Whitey by him a million times. Okay, Whitey. Well now you know why I've been doing it.
Oh my god. That is the most exciting. North African 1.1%.
Anything good in there? Who knows?
Northern West Asian. Oh, that's why I don't know what, I mean.
- Like Cyprus. - Cyprus?
- I think it's near Greece, I think.
- Yeah. - Maybe, I don't know.
- I guess I don't actually know anything.
- I don't actually know anything.
- There's a lady from Cyprus, I guess.
- I'm gonna have to learn about it.
- You're gonna have to learn about your history.
- My 0.3% heritage.
- That is so amazing.
- That is really exciting to me.
- Very exciting stuff.
- I always knew I was a total melting pot.
- That's true. - And now you have actual--
- I always knew I was multicultural.
- Now I know you are a complete melting pot, yeah.
- All right, let's see what else we have here.
Oh!
- 0.2% Arab, Egyptian, and Levantine.
- Dude, this is like, I feel like all the stuff
that I thought that I was gonna be, you are.
- Yeah, I'm 0.2% Egyptian.
- I thought I was gonna be Egyptian.
When I saw that Jubia added that to their racial ranking,
I was like, that's all me, dude.
- No, dude, I think I might become a hotep now.
- You have to. - Yeah.
- Yeah, because I-- - Well, is that why,
I mean, we haven't looked at yours yet,
but is that why Orc is on there?
I didn't even think about that. I guess that's probably me then, right?
That probably does have...
Because you just kind of got all the awesome stuff right then.
Yeah, I'm kind of bummed I didn't get Mexican.
Maybe I'm about to get 0.1% Mexican. We'll see. Next slide, maybe.
True.
If that happens, if I get all three...
Let's see.
Trace Ancestry. Who knows?
Wait, let's see. Does it go into that?
Oh my god.
Wow.
Wow, dude.
Sub-Saharan African.
0.1% Somali.
Dude.
Wow.
Yes, bro.
This is amazing.
This is the greatest day of your life.
Well, here's the thing.
I remember when I did the 23andMe,
it did say that I was point Sub-Saharan, like 0.2.
He's going to ruin everything right now.
And then it got then they got rid of it. I don't really care because I'm Native American. Okay. Yeah, you're a hundred percent white Irish
Yeah, you're you know whitey
For you know what that means to be a hundred percent Irish your family used to be the the lowest I literally
in the worst country in the world I
Already won being 30% Polish. That was all you were every yeah, everything else is just amazing victory
- Brown and black icing on top of the cake.
- I don't think you should say brown and black icing.
- Why?
- All right.
- Yeah, but you wouldn't say that.
You're not allowed to say that.
- Is this the end of the slideshow here?
- Yeah, that's it.
- Oh my God, dude.
- Oh, and unassigned.
- 3% unassigned, so you did pop unassigned.
So wait, really quick.
So really quick, can we add up your--
- There's more stuff, there was more stuff.
- Let's see more stuff then, let's keep going.
- Timeline.
- So you were--
Most recently, I was British and Irish and Eastern European.
Okay, and it looks like everything else
is from the 1600s.
- That's not that long ago, honestly.
- No, that's basically like--
- No, from the 1700s.
- Where do you find this timeline thing?
'Cause I didn't see mine. - Oh yeah, I can't see it.
- So you were North African as recently as 1850.
- Wow. - Civil War vibes.
- 1850, that's Victorian times, right?
- Yeah, dude, yeah.
Wow, that is amazing.
- So I wasn't even in Victorian England.
- No, no, not at all, dude.
- That's incredible.
I'm gonna go home and change a lot of stuff. I mean everything is different for you. Everything is fucking different
All right, what's next? I think it seems like that might be the end. All right, so really quick
Can we can we add up the the points for you? No, all right, so
What do we got keep it keep it keep tracking your head? Okay, so you are to go back
I have to should I go back and this out of so they just add them all together
Someone take out their phone. I guess and just do calculator here. You do it me do it. Yeah, it's your come on
It's your point you be oh shit
Had this or or Juvio can do it on the computer. I got it. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do all right ready
All right. Yeah, so first up is British. Yeah, you are British, which is - 21
- 21 okay, okay, and and but you're indigenous American well Irish - is okay Irish is zero
Okay, and then Scandinavian is next
Is that on here negative negative 13?
Okay, and then finish negative seven negative seven
Okay, Polish, which is negative 51
Come on add it negative 51. Okay next Spanish and Portuguese
Spanish is negative 16 and Portuguese is negative 19 negative 19
Okay, and then what's next here indigenous American?
That is negative one. Negative one. Again, very interesting choice by Patrick.
And then, is African on here? Cypriot? Oh yeah, Cypriot is, what is it, where is that?
Oh, negative three. Negative three. Okay, and then Egyptian? Egyptian is, man I can't
find any of these. There's so many. I missed the first one. Plus two, wow!
- Wow. - That's huge.
You're such a melting pot, man.
- Okay, and then the Somali.
- Somali and Guinean.
So Somali is negative two and Guinean is negative five.
And then unassigned is negative 17.
- Negative 17 for unassigned.
- All right, so what's your total?
- My total racial score is negative 153.
- Negative 153.
- Yeah. - That's what you are.
All right, I don't know if I can beat that.
That's pretty good.
- Yeah, I think I got a pretty good score.
- All right, Patrick, if you would do the honors,
will you spray, or I'll spray this,
and will you connect--
- Don't mix them together, whatever you do.
- True, okay, wait, I'll...
- Oh, it's nice and red on the table.
- Yeah, nice and amazing red on the table.
All right. - All right, it's all hooked up.
- I hear it whirring.
It's calculating my race report right now.
- Wow, look at this. - Okay, dude.
- Putting that cherry limeade shit in the spray,
it is a crazy smell in the room right now.
- It is smelling so bad. - Your blood smells like
I actually attach a certain cultural importance to fragrance.
Guys, I need you both to shut up because I'm about to uncover the secret history of my
family directly live on air. So here's what I've been told about my family history. I
have been told that my great, or my granddad is Italian, okay? My mom's dad. And he looks,
if you guys have met him, he looks like a human basketball.
That is the color of him.
It's like an old leather vintage Spalding ball.
So I've always looked at him saying,
hmm, I'm not so sure.
And his mom looked even worse.
- Worse is not the word you should use.
- Every, well, who knows, maybe I can use it.
Everybody in my family is ugly and they're fat too.
So I'm trying to learn where all these people are from.
So give me three predictions.
So I'm predicting--
Are your three hopes?
The three hopes.
I hope that I'm some meaningful amount Italian,
because that has been the only kind of like cultural thing
that I've ever had.
Was that we'd be like, yeah, we're Italian.
We'll eat-- like at Christmas, we eat Italian food.
I'm hoping that I am Native American,
because my dad would say that we were Native American.
Yeah.
And it would be nice for us both to be Native American.
- And then we could be kind of, we could be brothers.
- We could do stuff together.
- Yeah, we could be amazing spirit brothers.
- You're gonna be so mad when it's like
a decent amount Irish.
- I don't think, to my knowledge,
I have no Irish in my blood.
Oh, and I think I have Spanish in my blood.
- What's your third hope?
- My third hope is that I am,
I'm from Africa.
I want to be, okay, I'll say this.
I want to be 100% African.
Okay.
So I'm ready.
I'm ready.
But I'll accept whatever is given to me.
I'm not going to protest.
I'm not going to send an email if I'm not happy with the results.
Okay.
All right.
Let's get into this, guys.
I'm so fucking nervous.
This is amazing.
Okay.
Caleb's report.
100% Caleb.
100% CP.
Oh my God.
I do not like this.
So already I'm looking at this?
- Yeah, the blueness of it.
- It is all looking very blue, first of all.
And second of all.
- Yeah, dude, that's European, dude.
- Dude, this is bad news.
And a huge chunk of it is one blue thing.
- You're completely European.
- Dude, this is not good.
All right, let's see.
99.8% European, dude.
- Wow.
That is a shot to the heart.
(laughing)
That is really sad, dude.
I honestly am just so fucking sad right now.
- God damn.
- 99.8, dude. - 99.8.
At least give me 100.
(laughing)
- 99.8.
- Oh, this is breaking my heart.
- That means 0.2% is not European.
- That's true.
Let's look on the bright side here.
- You're gonna have 0.2% of something.
- Oh my God. - Maybe it's unassigned,
but it's not European.
Definitely on a side who would have thought that you were the most racially diverse
Not me
Expecting that I was expecting it. I knew I had it all right. Let's get into this raced off
Not 81 point 5% Northwestern European yeah, and we remember what that is holy crap
Irish
I knew it. We're all Irish. Dude, I honestly had no fucking clue that I was even 1% Irish.
You're gonna start listening to Wolftones with me.
Dude, that is crazy. I'm Irish? That is the worst news I've ever gotten in my life.
You said all this stuff about how, "Oh, I've only been a peasant my whole life." Bitch,
you too. No, but I have at least one other thing in
here is it's only 68% so I'm more than half Irish that is so fucked up that is
so fucked up man that is really hurting my feelings okay let's see did I kiss
you before I spit into that thing I'm trying to fight it back or did I kiss
maybe like a fucked up ugly bitch fucking Irish that's yourself no you were a
are
Wow. When they clear out all these results, when they like finally tally it up and
figure it out, you might be a hundred percent Irish too because I remember it
said that I was like a hundred percent Scandinavian. Southern European, okay this
is where it gets good. Look at this picture too. All right yeah I'm a little
bit interested in this at least. This is some intrigue because this guy has a
mustache. All right. 17% Italian, okay Camparia. Okay.
- Nice. - All right.
- In five regions.
- Yeah, and then broadly Southern European.
Okay, so I'm about a fifth Italian, almost.
- Congratulations.
- All right, that's actually more than I thought.
I always thought that I was like 5% Italian.
So I'll take that.
I still, it is pretty upsetting
that I'm triple that amount Irish.
(laughing)
And I don't know a single--
- When Julio said to us last night,
he was like, "Oh, when we do this,
"we'll do Cam's results first
"and then we'll do Caleb's after."
and I was like, oh, this means Caleb is gonna be something,
Caleb's gonna be like Egyptian or something.
- It was reverse.
- And then it's actually that you're getting damned.
- I'm fucked, dude.
- You're being tortured.
- This is so fucked up.
I can't believe it, dude.
I'm not, wait, am I not even Spanish, bro?
My grandma's a liar?
My grandma told me that her grandma--
- Wait, go back, didn't it, I feel like--
- Where does it say Spanish?
- Oh no, it's French and German, yeah.
- Dude, that might--
- Yeah, you're not Spanish.
- I also thought that I was like 20% German.
- Well, there's still a lot of Europe to go.
- Am I fucking adopted?
Am I adopted?
My grandma claims that her mom, or her great grandma,
or her normal grandma, was 100% Spanish.
- We'll see, we'll see.
- Okay, Southern European, Italian,
broadly Southern European.
0.5% Eastern European, I could see that with that picture.
99.8% European, dude.
This is honestly gotta be one of the worst days
of my entire life.
- This is the highest high, the highest high for Cameron.
Ticked my lowest low.
(laughing)
This is unreal, dude.
- Finding out that you are Irish,
you don't look it at all.
You don't look a--
- I can't believe it.
- You look like you were made in a tube.
- But I look like a little Somali, right?
- You do, yes.
You look like a Somali pirate, yes you do.
You look just like them.
- All in all,
- Okay.
- There's .2% left.
- There's .2%, so guys.
- Hey, hey, hey, crackers.
Drum roll, give me a drum roll.
- Not three complete crackers, no.
- Yeah, no, he's not.
- Oh yeah, that's true.
- Listen, this guy's a--
- If you call me a complete cracker ever again--
- He's a Weetabix.
- I'm gonna fucking eat you.
- Okay, two crackers and a mutt.
- Don't call him a mutt.
First you do race rankings, now you're calling people mutts?
- What's wrong with you, man?
- Hey, I didn't wanna do the race rankings.
- You did not argue at all.
- We really thought, okay, we were going,
the plan was that we were gonna give you the thing
and we thought that you were gonna say,
oh no, there's no way we can do this.
So I was printing out, before you got here,
I was trying to print out a bunch of emojis
that you could use instead,
so when you said no to the numbers,
I could bring out the emojis.
- The emojis is a way better idea.
- But they were all like frowny faces and cameras.
(laughing)
- But you immediately were like, yeah, let's do it.
- No, 'cause I knew there was nothing I could do about it.
- You had been planning it for so long, dude.
Okay, all right, 0.2%.
- All right, blow on the dice, blow on the dice.
- Unassigned.
(laughing)
- You didn't blow on the dice, dude.
- Oh my god.
I'm not at all Native American.
- Well, let's look at the timeline.
- Oh yeah, let's look at the timeline.
- Let's see the timeline.
- All right, that actually is what I resemble the most of,
out of everything that you've showed.
All right, so originally I'm French and German
and Scandinavian, then I was Italian,
and then British and Irish, only in the last 100 years.
- So that's why you didn't know about it,
is 'cause it just happened.
- Yeah. - I don't, wait.
(laughing)
I'm trying to think.
- Well, no, but yeah.
- The thing is, my grandpa is from like the middle
of nowhere, and we were talking about how he has
like no real idea of his family history, I guess.
- Yeah. - But then my other grandpa,
yeah, they're, my grandma claims to be German.
My grandpa is Italian, I just found out for real.
And, wait, but wait, there's more.
No, that can't be true.
Wait, what's going on here?
- There's more?
(laughing)
- No way, no way.
- I have less than 2% Neanderthal DNA.
Did that mean that, that's low, right?
That's pretty low.
- I think that's high.
- You have one variant associated
with having a worse sense of direction.
You have two variants associated with being less likely
to have a fear of heights, okay.
You have one variant associated with being more likely
to have a fear of public speaking.
And you have four variants associated
with being a better sprinter than distance runner.
- Wow.
- I'm a high performance athlete.
- Yeah. - Oh my God.
- And you're afraid to talk.
- And I'm afraid to talk, but I can jump off of--
- Yeah, you can run.
- I would actually say all of these are completely opposite.
I'm so scared of heights, and I'm not a good runner at all.
Wait, wait, what is it?
Okay, I get it, I have--
- I feel like that's gotta be a lot of Neanderthal DNA,
though, right?
Or else they wouldn't, I don't remember what mine was,
but it said that I have 56% more Neanderthal DNA
than most users. - Wow.
- My, less than two, I really thought
that most, okay, so the people that I've seen
that have Neanderthal DNA, it said like,
like, oh, you have so much, you have .2%.
So the fact that it just says less than 2%
means that I could have one and a half or something?
- Yeah. - That's pretty scary.
- Yeah, I think that's a high number, I would think.
- You think I'm full Neanderthal almost?
- Probably. - Wait, less than 2%,
that's what the unassigned is then.
- Yeah. - I'm 2% fuckin'--
- You're Encino, man.
- Dude, I cannot believe this, man.
- That's cool.
- All right, let's add it up. - That's a win.
but the i guess i'll take a look at the other side of this this slide show
all right let's uh... let's add it up okay all right over all reviews outside
so
high-end if you're on the earth three things
i i may win but i lost to the i may win but i completely lost alright so british
and irish so british
is negative twenty one
right negative twenty one
irish is zero
then we have sold it
Here's my timeline.
- What's your timeline?
- My timeline is just British, one to two.
(laughing)
- Scandinavian is negative 13.
- Negative 13, okay.
- French is negative 22.
- Negative 22.
- German is not on here.
- That's fine.
- But we'll call that negative 50.
- Okay, I'll take negative 50.
- Yeah, I guess German is unassigned.
Italian is negative eight.
- Okay.
- And then Eastern European's not on here.
Unassigned is negative 17.
- All right.
- And we'll call Ork Neanderthal.
That's negative 12.
- Okay, so with that, that puts me at negative 143.
- Oh.
- With the random negative 50 that we threw in.
- If we take, I mean, okay, the negative 50
doesn't have to be there.
I think you won numbers-wise.
Okay, negative 93 then is my score,
according to Patrick's racial ranking.
Yeah, well, I guess that's not what we should say.
That's not an objective score.
That's just what Patrick thinks of us.
That's just one racist's idea of what our points are.
Or racialists, sorry.
Racialists, that's what I have to say.
Not racist, it's different.
So Patrick.
I think, honestly, I hate to say this,
I think that the ranking is,
Cameron has the coolest, you have the second coolest,
and I might have the worst lineage on the entire podcast.
- I think you're, 'cause Patrick's is cool
'cause it's so, it's just one thing.
I think that has a shock factor.
- Yeah, whoa, mine is like so shit, man.
- I have 51% more Neanderthal DNA
and I have the same amount as Caleb.
I will say, I do truly think
that I manifested this into existence.
I don't think I deserve what I got.
- I'm wishing all week that I had been doing voodoo
my house. I have what I literally every time I just kept thinking about it I
would say to whoever I was hanging out with I think I'm gonna be Native
American. Look me in the eyes did you go to a witch doctor? No. Are you planning on
becoming a witch doctor? Fuck me man. All right I mean that's it for the race.
And just so you guys know if they do end up correcting the score or whatever I'm
I'm not, I'm never checking it again.
I've never even looking at it.
- You're passing this on to your children.
- Exactly, this is, yeah.
- This is incredible news.
- We are doing our shareholder meeting for this month
on the 17th of February, which is a Friday.
And I assume at 5 p.m. Eastern again.
- Short month, we couldn't do it on another Friday.
- That's right.
- The month's too short.
- So check that out.
- I'm gonna be, so subscribe to the $15 tier
to get access to that.
- I'm gonna be in the beautiful city