(ominous music)
[Music]
(eerie music)
[MUSIC PLAYING]
So guys--
You said you wanted the first thing.
I have first thing today.
Go ahead.
First thing.
I have first thing.
Sorry.
I mean, get this off.
- Your first thing is, oh, I'm gonna get tangled up
in the cord. - First thing, first thing.
- Damn!
- Foot locker.
- Cameron's a sneakerhead now.
Foot locker, y'all. - What type of these?
Adidas.
Ow!
- Don't take 'em off the, dude.
- Why did you try to attack me?
- 'Cause you hurt me and I yelled ow and you kept going.
- Do you see what happens when you get
the first thing in the episode?
- No, he did second thing bad.
Second thing was bad, first thing was good.
- You did the first thing and you introduced a toy
that he could play with.
- That's not a toy, it's on my body.
- Your foot is my toy.
it's not a little bit like a little like told you that i don't know if you would
you start with you if there was a parrot or a parakeet sitting in a cage at
vicious lips which you stick your finger in that cage
i would ask what he did he's that
you stuck your finger in the cage
no he had a kiss finger you might have to know i think it was my foot you put
your fight directly him into my life that is the only i had to do it no no no
no no so i don't have a lot of the one who attacked him and that's what's
getting your retribution you don't attack the parakeet the parakeet attack
text you. You're completely reversal of everything. He's ruining this already. I'm not ruining
anything. I was going to start with mine. He's going to ruin this. With my new parody.
Go first thing. Okay, here's my parody. You guys are going to do the song. You guys are
going to do the song. You start over. You know that song, it's like pretty woman, walking.
Okay. It's not a boulder. Squidward, it's a rock. It's not a boulder. That is how you
do first thing. Squidward, it's a rock. It's not a boulder. That's the second part. Ready?
That pizza makes me smile, the pioneers rode these for miles.
Not once did he put his fingers near me.
Until that point.
I'm scared.
But that's pretty good.
If I genuinely did hurt you and you weren't doing a joke, I'm very sorry.
It hurt me, that's why I yelled ow.
I thought you were doing a joke.
I don't have flexible legs, I have very inflexible legs.
I actually have a problem with my legs.
I think you have maybe all of your bones fused together.
- It's my muscles that's the problem more than the bones.
My bones are probably strong.
- You don't even never ask me for a massage.
- You don't even never ask him for that.
- I don't even like massages because they injure me.
- I really am scared of getting a massage.
- What kind of crazy person are you?
- Nobody likes massages, okay.
- I like a massage from a big--
- I've had to be in full traction from a massage before.
- I would never have that hospital.
- I like a massage from the biggest woman ever.
- No you don't, no you don't.
- And she steps on my back and I go, "Oh!"
- I would never get a massage.
- It's an involuntary noise.
- Massage is a slippery slope.
I was talking to somebody about this the other day.
I would never get a massage for the same reason
I would never join the military.
- You'd never get a massage from like--
- Wait, okay, no, I need to hear what the same reason is.
- Okay, so I would never join the military
because I would be afraid that I would be
a perfect killing machine, and I would never join,
or I would never get a massage because I would be afraid
that I'd be too, just--
- You'd be too good at killing masseuses.
- No, I think I'd be too seductive.
I think whoever it was, they couldn't help themselves
and they'd end up molesting me.
- I don't think so.
- You know, okay, so--
It does suck when you get like the massage and they slip their thumb in your butthole
I've never had a massage. So I've been watching a lot of curb your enthusiasm. So I'm been kind of recently seeing etiquette through a different lens
and
I'm wondering what would happen in a scenario when you go to the masseuse and they say undress to your level of comfort and I'm
like this
Yeah
Well, that wouldn't be that would probably be the more like
They're like kind of low, but and then I take I take I take off everything I leave on undies and socks
Yeah, missus comes back at a wine on the table. Did you leave your socks on?
Man I hate that I'm gonna curb your enthusiasm real-life scenario
Stop I haven't seen
To somebody basically half of the scenarios are he's that's true. Yeah
It is I was gonna say I haven't seen I've seen maybe the first season that show I was gonna say I get into a lot
Of those scenarios in my real life probably because of my level of intelligence and your race race
We're your racial remarks that you make
They're not on purpose Brad Paisley wrote a song about me
Honky-tonk lady with big-ass jokes
You're not there's no part of that's what the song's called
Paisley is that type of country song? I'm hung William
(laughing)
- Yeah, William Hung.
- I didn't know that about you.
- I'm hung like a horse down there.
(laughing)
And that's the reason why I can't go to the masseuse.
Is that, you know what I would just hate, dude?
- I've seen, you are a liar.
I've seen your penis.
- I'm hung like a fucking horse.
- You're hung like a church mouse.
What you are.
- Why you looking at mice penis?
- I'm hung like a church bell.
- Gay pedophile.
A mice is a child.
- A mice is not a child.
- A mice is a...
- A mouse is a baby.
- Is a rat the, no.
- No, it's not like veal.
Like that what's a mouse's baby called a mouse's baby or well what a cub
Sensitive shitty says I can't say the c-word on YouTube man walking around saying the c-word yeah, we're 90 minutes in right 90
We should not have eaten that subway subway we got worms now
You claim that there was worms in all Subway food.
What's the kind of bread called that I got? Italian herbs and spices. That's what I thought. Herbs and cheese I mean.
Yeah, okay, because I always order I say that the one with herbs. Was yours crunchy at the end?
At the end? Like the part where the loaf starts.
The crunchy part of the bread. The part where the loaf starts because mine was crunchy. I think they over toasted it.
Oh.
You know, what's weird is subway leaves much to be desired. I don't know if anyone else has what the fuck
Hello
Hey
Jubio did you do that?
Fucking nightmare
You can all take a move
Why did you
Why did you tape our mouths shut if we're doing a podcast it doesn't make that much shot
I lost I lost two mustache hairs on this piece of tape man. I got a little mustache. I lost how did you lose more than me?
But now it looks like we're asking I need to I need to switch the levels can I put both tonight
Fine everyone just be nice to me. Don't move. Don't don't be crazy. Okay, okay
All right, I've been a crazy situation, but sometimes a crazy guy
I thought that's a normal guy has to do crazy things. Okay, you just listen you seem like a good guy. Okay, I
Think I check your microphone. I think your mic is
What's going
You seem like a very very nice guy you seem like a normal guy the microphones not working
Check oh my god. Is it working now? I fixed it for our captain
You're already on his yard. He's best friend
Okay, you have to put your hand up my hand is up
Oh, my hand everyone keep one hand up unless you're moving the levels. I got one hand up. I don't touch the level
That's his job listen. You seem like a nice guy. Okay. I didn't what I mean. We'll give you whatever you want alright
I just want to get out here with my life
You know what I want. What do you want? You know what I want. What do you want?
Episode again, why why don't you do the Mad Libs anymore? I don't know it was like a three
It was just a thing that we are doing
Outside nobody likes the
Did you
What why does this look like
Dragons episodes or having Felix
episode with Brian! Is that your name? That's... hi! Hi! Oh my god! Hey Brian! Nice to meet you Brian! Today's been a crazy day! Hi! It's nice to meet you!
That was a nice try but he's crazy. That was a nice try you son of a bitch! I didn't plan that with him, he actually did that on his own.
Brian I'd just like to make it pretty clear that I didn't try to get the gun or distract you. They told me to do that. I didn't tell you that!
They both whisper. They told me to do it in my headphones.
I didn't say shit.
I didn't say anything.
Sounds like you told him to do it.
Cause he did. He seems pretty sure.
He's pretty sure you did it.
I didn't do shit to him.
Well now it's time for you all to dance.
Bang, bang, dance with me.
Woah, woah.
I'm gonna shoot your feet.
You're pointing at your own feet.
Ow, ow, ow.
I was dancing too.
You need to calm down.
You need to calm down, Brian.
You're being a little bit crazy.
Jesus, it's been a crazy week for me. Let me tell you that.
I can imagine.
What's going on with you?
I was trying to get on comedy bang bang. I was trying to audition for comedy bang bang. I went to a room.
A guy who looked just like Reggie Watts, I swear. A guy who looked just like Paul Scheer.
You look like both. There was two different guys.
You look like two different guys.
Oh, okay.
You just don't try to point out any logical fallacies in what I say.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm just not in this real life. I'm not just messing around no more, okay?
Okay?
I can tell you're very serious.
Now, we're gonna do some mad lips.
Okay.
Okay?
*sigh*
Yeah, this is gonna be a good time.
You underhand slamming me?!
No editing tricks!
Don't-
Don't you shut off my audio!
Don't you try and make me look short!
Don't you try and make me look-
*stutters*
We're not gonna try and make you look short.
We're not doing anything.
How's this? How's this?
Yeah, we'll all get low.
Everyone get low!
Okay.
Alright.
I got a small torso!
I understand-
I got a one foot torso!
You understand me?
People can't see at home, but his legs go-
Long legs.
- My legs are cramped up underneath this table,
but that's neither here nor there.
- It's not here or there, guys.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Cameron, you're my favorite one so far.
That's two less caps in your ass.
- Okay, two less.
I don't know, are we getting to zero caps,
or is it just--
- Now it's time for the Mad Lib!
- Okay. - Okay.
- Mad Lib is called Brian's Birthday.
- Is it your birthday?
- That's neither here nor there!
Okay. Okay. That's also not here in North America. Alright. Alright. We'll do the Mad Lib.
Alright. We'll just do the Mad Lib. We don't have to have the gun in my face and the legs.
I'm not comfortable doing that yet! And stop playing footsie with me. I'm not comfortable stopping that either!
Alright. I'm very nervous. Okay. And it makes me feel comfortable. I'm stimming with your feet.
Okay. Alright. So don't mind if I, you know, play around a little. Okay, anyway!
Brian's birthday is the name of the ad-lib.
And I just found this one too.
I just found this one too, like you guys are saying.
OK.
You found this on the street?
I found this on the street, just like you guys are saying.
That's why there's dirt on it?
That's-- uh-huh.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
OK.
All right.
Uh-huh.
That's why there's--
And that's dirt.
That's why there's dirt on it.
We believe dirt.
And it's dirt.
I believe you.
We believe you.
I have no reason not to believe you.
That's why there's dirt on it, and the smell is dirt too.
I can smell-- it smells just like dirt.
It smells-- it smells--
oh, yeah.
All I smell is dirt.
It's dirt!
It smells like the garden section at Home Depot.
You at home?
You listening?
Hands up!
Don't shoot into the microphone now.
Don't shoot him.
Everybody listening at home, hands up right now!
You can shoot us, but don't shoot our listeners.
Don't point that gun into that microphone.
Don't you dare try to shoot our listeners.
Let's just go with the mad lip.
Let's do the lip.
Alright, alright.
This is a mad lip I found.
I didn't make.
This is a mad guy who's making us do this.
Jesus Christ.
I'm sorry.
He said that.
Our voices, it's pretty easy to confuse our voices.
We have a lot. Yeah. That's why we did video. I do have a hard
time telling white men's voices apart. Oh well. Thank you for
assuming I'm white but results coming in for these two. Oh
that's not true. Our twenty-three and me is in the
mail. So watch out. Okay. Yeah. So we'll we'll update you on
that later. We'll kind of see it for him. You know, I can
kind of see it. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe like a Hawaiian vibe.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Continue. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Brian's birthday! There was a big party at... here's our first blank... a guy named
Brian. Do we have any suggestions for a guy named Brian? Big party at a guy named
Brian's house. Brian. Brian. Oh yeah, Brian! That's pretty good.
That's kind of funny. Yeah. Okay. Okay. There was a big party at Brian's house.
Okay. Opposite of Nobody was invited. So Opposite of Nobody is our first...
One million people. Everybody. I like everybody a little more than one
million because... So, one... Fully graphite gun. Scratch, scratch, scratch. Everybody was invited.
There was a big party at Brian's house, everybody was invited. And they all
showed up except for the guys from podcast in the room with three members
can we think of a podcast in the room with three members I could think of a
podcast room with four members
everybody was showed up except for the guys from podcast about list even though
I know they saw my word for email do we have a word for email email email
straight to your phone doesn't it mine I have my notifications actually turned off
I use it on my computer most yeah it's easier to type that way yeah sometimes
you don't get emails if they come through my computer or we have like a
a spam filter yeah yeah and he looks at most of our emails and we goes through
him where is he where yeah where's he he must have he must have skedaddle okay
yes we're alone on this one yeah right I think that's a big problem
there right yeah so yeah yeah okay so name for a birthday boy went to go get
them so named for a birthday boy can we think of a name for a birthday boy I
hate to say it but Brian again Brian Brian give me the birthday boy yeah
Oh wow! That's a really good answer for the Matlip!
Is that funny? Is that good for the video?
It is! That's funny!
Brian...
So, Brian went to go get them.
So that they could come to the fun gathering with celebrities.
Can we think of a name for a fun gathering with celebrities?
Gala.
Gala! Yes!
- Yes! - Okay, gala.
- Gala. - Gala.
- Yes!
- We'll do gala. - Gala, yes!
- Gala's funny.
- Birthday gala. - Gala.
- Birthday, so-- - Brian's birthday gala.
- Brian went to get them so that they could come
to Brian's birthday gala.
(clicking)
First, he went to the store where you buy hardware.
Anyone know, can think of a store where you buy hardware?
- Ace Hardware Store. - Hardware store.
- Hardware store. - Ace Hardware Store.
I'll just combine them, Ace Hardware Store.
- Okay. - All right.
- This is coming along good,
I can't wait to hear the finish.
yeah product me funny and bought some things I could hit your what can I hit
your head with thing I could hit your head the pillows pillows something a
little harder hello filled with the brick oh I guess a hammer hammer
we don't want to do a paintbrush or I wish I'd come up with something else but
spray paint, sandpaper. And Brian said, "Oh, these will be great to use for..." What's a
word for hitting you on the head if you disobey? What's a word for hitting you on the head?
Great for hitting... Punish? No, we're not going to... Not punishment, right? Retribute?
We don't want that. Maybe a reward. Reward. Reward. I like punish. We'll go with punish
Punish you in the head if you disobey.
I think reward is maybe funnier.
And then they would say, and then they would say,
what's an exclamation ending in ouch?
Youch?
Couch.
Like, ouch.
When you're walking down the street,
you see a new--
Couch.
Used couch.
Yay.
Secondhand couch.
Or just out for a second.
Free couch.
That's kind of funny.
Green couch.
I like green couch, that's kind of funny.
I'm gonna go with green couch.
Okay.
Green couch.
be real funny. Yeah. It's done. Then, Brian waited at uh a
restaurant where you can have it your way. What is a
restaurant? You're going to have it your way. I mean, most
restaurants, I think you can kind of have it your way,
right? Yeah, I think that's true. I've been told no. I I
I very rarely. Sometimes, there's no substitutes. I
couldn't have a whopper in my way at most restaurants.
Something like that. Okay, well then, I guess if you're
saying, you're kind of leading us a little bit. I'm going to
be honest. It's not really how Mad Libs is supposed to work
and I, you feel like you're acting a little bit kind of
of like a loof when you really, you know, I'm going to say Burger King. Burger King.
Burger King, that is such a good, Caleb!
Yeah, yeah.
Patrick, I'm liking Cameron and Caleb so far, you are pissing me off.
Oh, Pat.
You're pissing me off a little bit.
You have a good answer.
I said Burger King.
Well, Pat, you take the next one, Pat. You think you have a good one for the next one.
Yeah, come on.
Alright, let's drop Burger King.
We'll give the next one to you.
Until it was time to, synonym for capture or abduct.
Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse.
Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse. Abuse.
I forgot that you told me you liked it.
- Well, thank you for getting the message out.
- I said, "Sign up for the Patreon right now
and watch the Patreon Mad Libs!"
And then I followed up and said, "Did you do it?"
And if they didn't, I said, "Why not?"
And if they stopped responding, then I'd go,
"Please, please don't ignore me."
And then if they continue to ignore me, I go,
"What, did I do something to piss you off?
I'm so sorry!"
And then if they kept ignoring me after that,
then we'd end up in a very similar situation to this,
where I kidnap them.
- Okay, well, thank you for all the fans at home.
You can maybe learn something.
This is super fun.
- What's a nicer word for victims?
- Friends.
- Nicer word for victims, friends.
- Hostage.
- Hostage is a little nicer than victim.
- Guest.
- You haven't heard of hostage yet.
- Guest, I like that.
Guest.
And then they all hung out together
and they had
thing you have when it's a good time
boner
boner?
you want to get a boner?
I like you guys but not like that
yeah that'd be gay
you're fitting right in
you fit in
oh no
is that a
okay i think we missed our chance
missed your chance
you had me down didn't ya
uh we were pretty close
you got me slipping and that was the last time
listen i'll admit it i have a 6 second reaction time
ok i've had it tested by the doctor
i kinda went like this a little bit
i was about to
that's why you can trust me
and uh
see it's just so late my reaction time
i was not so fast
you were lucky
Press the button again on accident. Yeah won't happen again though. I'm sure it won't
Definitely won't happen again. So is there anything else in this matter? Okay, and then Brian Patrick and Caleb did
Something that should have been a long done a long time ago the podcast
Why is it Ryan Patrick and Caleb it's something that was supposed to be done a long time ago wait
Wait something that's supposed to be done a long time ago, but you didn't include Cameron
Caleb went back to Brian's what's an awesome thing party the party that I was having earlier Brian's birthday gala
And recorded an episode called name of the greatest podcast episode ever I guess it would be the new
That's what you think the whole so the episode is called the new
Madlibs episode the first of the rest which is all Madlibs
That's the episode
Featuring
Okay, so why is camera
God my fucking react guys. I want to grab it, but I have to do the levels terrible
I really got this close.
I was scared.
You had me scared for a second.
You should see me at the NFL combine.
It was pretty bad.
It was really, really bad.
The word for ending and the end, I guess the finale, the finale, the finale, the finale,
the finale.
All right.
So let's go.
OK, so that was the Mad Libs, right?
So, oh, excuse me.
We got to read what we have.
- Wow.
- Excuse me, we gotta read what we have.
- What?
- Gotta read what we have.
- Okay, so what do we have?
- All right, there was a big party at Brian's house.
Everybody was invited and they all showed up
except for the guys from Pot About List
even though I know they saw my email.
So Brian, the birthday boy, went to go get them
so that they could come to the Brian's birthday gala.
First, he went to the hardware store and bought some hammers.
And Brian said, oh, these will be great to use
for hitting, punishing.
And then they would say, a green couch.
[LAUGHTER]
Couch!
Then Brian waited at Burger King until it
was time to kidnap his guests.
I remember that.
And then they all hung out together and they had fun.
And Brian, Patrick, and Caleb did a podcast.
Brian, Patrick, and Caleb went back to Brian's birthday gala
and recorded an episode called the AdLibs episode,
which is now the first one of the rest of all of them,
which they're now AdLibs.
The end.
- Wow, that's a very nice story.
- So that was pretty, that was good, right?
That's what you wanted for your birthday,
was a whole Mad Lib.
- Not so fast!
- Okay, that--
- Not so fast, wait a second!
That is a scary--
I don't want to hear that from you.
OK.
That's enough.
Jesus Christ.
That is an intimidating--
We rent this place.
You can't--
We don't own this table either.
This table is not ours.
We rent this table month to month.
You must have seen no Gats Aloud sign on the front door.
There's another Mad Lib.
What the hell is this?
No, I've got a list!
I've got a list!
Oh, good.
Oh, he's got a list.
I've got a list!
You find this one on the street too?
I found the list outside.
In the same place?
Were these in your back pocket?
Why do they look like this?
I found the list also outside and it's got dirt on it.
I found the list but it also just happened to be all the demands that I have.
Alright.
I found the list.
I found it!
Okay.
Alright.
I can tell that, yeah.
It's dirt.
It looks dirt.
And you take a smell.
What's that smell?
I already smelled it.
It's clearly dirt to me.
It's dirt.
That's a dirt smell.
That's a dirty dirt.
I actually don't think I need to smell the dirt.
I don't think you need to smell it.
You know what dirt smells like?
Yeah, I guess I was a little.
Hello!
Excuse me.
excuse me hello
it's just dirt
okay
excuse me i've got a new piece of paper to read out loud
okay what's this one
this is called
reasons why i have to replace
cameron from pod about list
from podcast about list on the podcast about list
that's the name of the list?
that's yes
Yes! That's the name of my list!
The name of my list is the reasons why I will replace Cameron as the new podcast host.
So this is why the Mad Lib ended with just me, you, and Patrick going.
That makes so much sense.
I was wondering what one of you guys were going to pick up on that.
I think he picked up on it, but I was ignoring it.
None of you noticed.
I didn't know. It was too clever for me. I didn't know that.
- It was a little too, you're a little, listen,
we do something called lowbrow humor,
if you wanna check our TV Tropes page, Brian.
- I know I'm a big fan, except for only the
Mad Libs episodes, I think everything else is mid!
- You think it's mid?
- I think everything else is mid, except for the Mad Libs!
- Okay, that's fair.
- And there's a big reason why, and I'll tell you what,
it's this big dork right next to me here.
So number one reason why I'm gonna replace Cameron.
- If he didn't have a gun, I would defend you.
- Thank you.
but he's got a gun.
- Reason number one!
- Okay, what's number one?
- It's my birthday.
- Oh.
The whole, remember in the Mad Lib when I was saying
it was Brian's birthday? - Oh, I thought
that was just a Mad Lib.
- Oh, me too.
- It's actually your birthday.
- It's actually my birthday.
It's my birthday today.
- Oh, that's nice.
- I wanna say I'm sorry.
- That's nice.
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, Brian.
- Oh, let's do it.
- It's your special day. - Happy birth.
- I thought we were, that's copyright.
Oh shit.
Happy birthday Brian, it's your special day.
Happy birthday Brian, hey hey hey.
And then go away.
And go away for your birthday.
And then go away on vacation.
On vacay.
Vacay.
That sounds nice.
But!
I don't know, because I have to work around the podcast schedule.
Because I'm going to be the new host!
I have a new host and we're gonna... maybe this guy goes on vacation forever.
Okay, number two! Reason why I should be the new host instead of Cameron...
'Cause I got... I have a lot of funny ideas! I have so many funny ideas!
Uh-huh. Like what?
Okay, here's... uh...
Ha! Okay, I have a funny idea.
For what if Lena Dunham
met Jake from State Farm?
I like this already. Which... Lena!
Oh, from Girls. Lena Dunham from Girls. The one and Jake from State Farm.
The old Jake or the new Jake? The new Jake from State Farm. The new and improved Jake from State Farm.
Okay. The buff one. Oh, he doesn't...
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I could definitely not put up the numbers.
I know I could put up a pair of numbers.
Wait, you were saying that what if they met?
So this is what if
Lena Dunham and Jake from State Farm
met. You're going to act this out first?
I'm going to act this out. This is something I
do instead of whatever Cameron does.
And here it goes. End scene.
And please don't interrupt me.
End scene. And please, please don't interrupt me.
Okay. Okay. End scene. And please don't interrupt me.
Oh god, fuck.
Okay.
Um, uh, oh, Jake from State Farm.
Oh, I, my pussy.
Oh, I, my, I hurt my pussy.
I felt, I fell down on my pussy, uh, the other day and I think I bru, I, I broke it.
I think I broke my pussy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Lena Dunham, relax.
You don't have to get that personal to get State Farm's personal policy price plan.
That's my funny idea.
I don't know if I would have--
That's actually pretty funny.
That sounds like something we could do on the show.
That's what I'm saying, right?
I mean, my methods are a little extreme, but you see--
I mean, Lena Dunham--
you had me at broke my pussy.
That's already pretty funny.
That's something she would probably blog about or something.
She'd probably show it, too.
And then Jake from the same farm--
Probably pull down her pants and show it to Jake.
I feel like that was implied in the scene is that she's kind of showing the phone.
She's like has a big red kind of mayor phone that she's aiming at her broken pussy.
And Jake's like, "Ahh."
It's broken.
Yeah.
Well, because she's probably also on her period.
She's so stupid that she thinks that it means her pussy broke out.
Oh my God.
Maybe I'm intellectualizing this too much.
No, no, I like it.
No, it's thematic.
Well, that's the kind of thing you're going to have to get used to if you're the new, if
you replace Cam.
I guess if you replace it listen
I
Agree, so if camera if you're gonna replace Cameron Cameron's kind of known as the kind of
The gentle giant first of all but also kind of the voice of reason you know
So I would need you to bring some element of that to the table
Because we already have like basically a crazy guy and a mentally disabled guy, and he's the voice of reason
So we need you to fill that you just have another funny guy. Just another crazy just three
crazy wild guy. I don't think you can do three crazy guys. I think you can do two crazy guys.
Reason number three that I will be number one on the host list. Also by the way I will
get first billing when I'm the new host. Okay. We don't really do billing. Well you got to
do it somehow. How do you order it now? Whose name goes first? Be honest. When what? I think
it's alphabetical. I think it's Caleb Cameron Patrick. Wow. Okay so it works alphabetically
- I'm gonna start, 'cause my name's Brian.
- So you-- - Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah, you'd be Brian or Brian.
- Brian, Caleb, Cameron.
- Well no, Cameron is already not.
- Maybe Brian, Caleb, Cameron.
Brian, Caleb, Brian, Patrick, Cameron,
Brian, Caleb, Cameron.
- I feel like it's one too many names.
- What if it was Caleb, Cameron, Patrick,
and then separately, Brian?
- Featuring Brian?
- Brian, and then another, a different podcast.
- Introducing Brian.
- Brian.
You say that to me and then I start seeing red.
You know what I mean?
- Okay, so scratch what I don't--
- I can foretell down the line--
- That could be your own sort of like,
you could do like a Bill Burr kind of Monday morning
podcast called like Brian Sees Red,
and you're in there and I bet you hate traffic
and bad weather, right?
So we could just get you, you could use the studio,
you could just click record.
- Hold on, let's do a test run right now.
Yeah, let's hear you talk about traffic.
- Okay, oh Jesus Christ.
Here it goes.
Hi, my, um, hello, welcome to the new episode of Pot About List
called Brian Sees Red, the new feature on Pot About List.
And I hate traffic.
Fuck. Fuck you, traffic.
Do you have a car?
I know.
I thought there was a solo thing, man.
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, that was the guy.
Come on, man. Kill me over.
That's my bad. I'm sorry.
Come on brother, alright now.
I like this "come on brother" that could be your catchphrase.
Kind of a southern...
Come on brother, come on.
Put your thumb like this way.
I'm just getting going here, about to drive in now.
See that's good man.
That is good.
It's way better than you being a new member of the podcast.
That's better.
You think that's good?
Yeah.
Well I'm not satisfied!
Okay.
Because nothing makes me feel as good.
When I was listening to the Mad Lids episode about Pod About List, I was in the best relationship
life. I had a six-figure job. I had a full head of hair. I was six foot two. I was cruising
down the boulevard every day. I went to clubs. I went to football games. And now look at me.
Sounds like the perfect life.
Yeah. Now look at me. I wake up at 5 p.m. every day. I got a job working for Uber Eats,
Testing out food, testing out the bad deliveries
that didn't work out.
You test the bad food.
Everyone has to test, when the delivery doesn't work,
somebody, it gets thrown into a little,
well basically every restaurant has a tube.
And I'm sitting there at the other end of the tube
with my mouth open.
They put the, forgot to put the ketchup on the burger
or whatever, classic.
Yeah.
I hate when they do that.
That happened to me before.
And it shoots directly to you like a grenade.
And I'm on the other end, I'm getting paid, you know, the more I swallow, the more I get paid, okay?
It's commission?
It's commission based! So I gotta be sitting at that tube 20, sometimes 18 hours a day. 18, sometimes 20!
Wow, I didn't know that was a job.
Yeah.
You know what, my question is, where do I sign up for this job?
Honestly, you're making it sound pretty awesome. 18 hours just sitting there eating burgers with no ketchup?
I hate ketchup!
Yeah.
Oh well. It doesn't compare to the life I once had. I ruined it. I ruined it all. I kept waiting
for the new Mad Libs episode to come out. But it never did. And slowly but surely I fell
to the perils of online gambling. No. Don't even talk to me about it. We're very familiar
with online gambling. We're very, you know, pro. I'm pro online. I like gambling. We're
you're very pro. We're very pro
or steak.com. Yeah. Use code
Brian. I owe every cent I'll
ever make for the rest of my
life to Draftkings.com. Don't
end up like me kids. Don't ever
online gamble on pot about
list. I was I was going to be
mad any day. Every day. They
had an option on that. Oh, they
got all the action on draft.
Well, technically, I didn't even
right now. Technically, don't
we have to sign off on it can we get that taken down and i can't believe you're betting on
whether or not we're gonna do another madlib. They got all sorts of bets on there.
What hats are you gonna wear? Wait is that why you made us do a madlib?
That's... I...
Oh, you know what? I didn't even think to fix it like that with the gun and all.
You're gonna go to jail for that. I already ran out of money so that would have been a good first move.
You didn't even make the money off that? I just did this out of desperation.
And I want to be on the show.
yeah what i thought i was a little is
everybody i got a new list for you
list isn't it yes it is
alright now everybody
shut up
number three i'm an expert audio engineer
i'm looking at cameron doing these levels
that might could be louder
my voice should be way louder right now
i'm whispering you want me to turn it up
he keeps turning me down and i'm like whispering
over here i'm like i don't think anyone can even hear me
turn it up
turn it up all the way
This is perfect, okay
Well when you become the host will do that
He's laughing already
I'm funny volume the fun is a really funny voice
Well
You're not gonna need a much longer
You can use them to do whatever you like you'll be out on the street
You'll never podcast in this town again asshole. Can I podcast in Boston?
You can go to Boston podcast with the small fishes if you want, but the big boys, but I'm not getting killed
I
Might not kill you if you if you seed your seat without too much of a fight, okay
We can maybe make this we could let's let them continue the little edge
We'll hear the rest of this far on the list is I?
It's my birthday
Today, but also my birthday's could come up next year, too
So that's I guess that's my birthday right now, but also later. It's gonna be remember my birthday, too
So then you have to be nice to
Okay, I mean, I don't really see how that's different. I guess you're gonna have that every year - yeah
By this day and then you'll have you'll have to be nice to me
And then you'll wish you had already done it by now just being pretty nice to you right now
I think we have been called the cops or yeah, there's not even a single. There's no button as we don't dial 911
That's right
But you still have to keep his hostage
I thought you do I want that I guess I want to host it with you. So don't please don't know that's fine
I'm fine. Okay. Oh, no, this isn't cool. I don't like this.
Keep it like that. That's fine. You can continue the Lord.
Just for safekeeping, I might hold on to this for a second.
Okay. Yeah. I don't know why you gave it to me in the first place.
Well. It's funny. It's funny.
He's crazy. I'm crazy, alright? Okay.
I lost everything I have. I lost my six-figure job.
Yeah. Alright? What was that job?
I was working in sales. I was working in, I was doing customer, I was a customer service rep.
For for for zales you seem like you would be really good at
Working in sales at zales as a customer service rep. Mm-hmm. Yeah, you sold like jewelry to rappers
Did rappers go to zales?
Stout Rolex at zales
I'm not you know me. I'm not a jewelry man. You can get a rolling face at zales
Can you get do people go to like it's like polo G going to like K jewelers
Every kiss begins with Claire's wife
Claire's ears pierced your yg or one of the jeans
You know hip-hop's not the same since since Mac Miller left the frame that's true, but anyway number four I
Number five Cameron cut his hair recently and let's be honest folks. Yeah, that's best look
I like it was a cooler rocker. I liked him when he was a rocker
I'm still a rocker
Look at that look at that right there. I will say that's pretty limp. That's pretty well
That's what rockers do like this right you look like you're gonna fit a fucking dick and balls
Yeah
You have to admit that
That's that's a gun that doesn't really prove. Yeah, I guess but but like this is like kind of like when you hurt
You know when you're a kid you know when you're a kid you start first I guess
I don't like this you know you do like the okay sign on your penis
That limp that looks like shit. What no you're so you're he's right your hair changed you the change the hair is
Yeah
I think I'm on his side on this one. Yeah, you guys are on his side get your old hair back
Although maybe you want to keep it short cuz you'll be doing job interviews
soon. Um alright, number seven, everyone's afraid of Cameron.
Cameron's a scary guy. Cameron's got a scary uh scary look in
his eye. I don't like to make uh close eye contact with him
cuz he cuz he I've never seen such a glare. We don't talk
about it that much but yeah, me and Pat, we are, yeah, we're
scared of Cameron. Yeah. You guys are, you're scared of me?
I mean, just like I, you are bigger than us and you kind of
have a temper on you. I don't have a and you have a history of
violence so I just feel yes I'm a little bit scared of you there you think I have
a temper Patrick there well I'm speaking to you I'm speaking to you there's a lot
of glass on the on the ground here I don't know why what what don't know why
there's a lot of glass.
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
His fluorescent tube parties.
Where he smashes the fluorescent tube.
I don't have fluorescent tube parties.
He smashes the fluorescent tube.
I don't do that.
I've never heard of that.
Yeah, because you're not the target of the tube.
Does he hit you with fluorescent tube?
You are not my tube target. I wish you were my tube target in a different sense.
He calls me.
He says I need you to come to the office and print something for me.
print something for me, my phone doesn't connect to the printer.
My phone doesn't connect to the printer.
His phone doesn't connect to the printer, so he...
And so I dropped six to ten times worth, days worth of fluorescent tubing.
Days of fluorescent tubing?
What happens six to ten times on six to ten different days.
Okay.
And maybe a day's worth is about ten tubes.
Sixty, ten?
Seventy.
Sixty to seventy.
He says that there's no ink in the printer, I lean over, I crouch,
and then he breaks a tube over my head.
That is...
Okay, that is...
That's not a temper thing though.
You said they were parties?
He calls it a party because he has snacks.
Ryan, you're... listen.
He's crazy and he even seems
taken aback by kind of how rude and...
A tube? Everybody in America
has tube parties.
That's like apple pie
or hot dogs on the 4th of July.
Not everybody has apple pie on 4th of July.
I said apple pie or hot dogs
on 4th of July. Some people have cake on 4th of July
because it's their birthday.
And on their birthday they think we're gonna tape four tubes together. I've never done a tube party on my birthday. That's - I wouldn't waste
Midnight you know you wouldn't do it
Would you do a two-party today? You wouldn't right?
We've been over the two-part, you know what I
I would rather hear the next reason that I have to die then keep talking about it
You know actually this is going into my this is my next point. Here is that Cameron is he's got he's got mass shooter in cell
vibes doesn't he? And I don't fuck with that.
I don't have mass shooter incel vibes.
You kind of do have.
My shirt has pets and animals on it.
But that's clearly ironic.
It's not ironic, it's cute.
You kind of do have a little bit of a mass shooter.
I'm not wearing it to cultivate a cute and affable thing so I can go up to anybody and
get into a building.
I don't think that's cute or affable. I think that it's really like your eyes.
It's not?
No, no, no, no.
I think it's your personality.
Yeah, and like kind of the way that you walk and move and look and talk.
and your beliefs as well.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some of the things I've heard you say too, yeah.
- Yeah, you say shit all the time like,
eat the rich, you know?
And it's like, what are you, a mass shooter inso?
- Okay, well, didn't want this to get political.
- But everything is political to you.
- You guys might wanna look up a little thing called Chapo.
- Okay.
- And you're gonna look it up and you're gonna think,
the Mexican?
No, brother, and you shouldn't say the Mexican.
You should say the Mexican guy.
You're giving honestly, not just incel, kind of SJW vibes as well.
I'm not an SJW mass shooter vibe.
You kind of seem like a combo between an SJW and an incel mass shooter.
Those things can't be combined.
Okay, so choose one.
Incel or mass SJW?
You gotta pick one.
I mean, you're the one who loves them both so much.
I don't have to pick one.
You just pick one.
Alright, are you an SJW or what are you?
I'm just me.
You are either an SJW or an incel.
Alright, he's, so that's another.
And what's the next one?
I know the answer, it's incel.
What's the next thing?
And, okay, listen, listen, alright, I'm not an SJW.
So what's the next thing?
- And, okay listen, listen, all right.
Now I said I used to be six foot two,
I'm six feet tall now.
- You lost two inches?
- I lost two inches. - That's horrible.
- It's just, it was--
- You know what can help that is good posture.
- And zinc. - Oh no.
- You gotta start taking zinc.
- Zinc and good posture, maybe get like a back aligner.
- The rack.
- I'm hunched over on this tube about 18 hours a day.
- Oh, so it's shrinking it around.
- I've got murder on my back.
Drinking me right not a lot of calcium in that food either
No and Cameron's too tall this is my point is a camera Cameron Cameron's too tall. I mean what is this guy?
He's like he's like a he's like
Dikembe Mutombo
That sounds like a mouse
Pretty small mouth okay wait. I'm not a mouse
I'm not a liar. I'm a jokester. I don't want to have to work with a liar. Are you really?
Though my methods may be mad, there's a madness to them. There's a method to them. And that's
what I'm saying is I'm opening your eyes now, I think.
A little bit.
Is that this guy is just dragging you guys down. I mean, where have you gone with this
podcast? It's gone nowhere.
I'm not a liar. I'm a jokester.
I don't want to have to work with a liar.
is that is that this guy is just dragging you guys down. I mean,
where have you gone with this podcast? It's going nowhere.
You know what I mean? Fast. Definitely. You know, so hitting
the brick wall. I mean, this guy, do you think it's his
fault? I think this guy is in control. He's he's like the
puppet master. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I am not a puppet. He's like
wait. I just shut up. I just imagined an SJW puppet master.
Yeah. Actually, it's giving me a free song. Oh my god. Well,
about it he's got a puppet fud. True. That's not a puppet that's a baby.
Baby puppet. He has a little puppet mascot. That's not my mascot it's our mascot.
It's just as much you guys as puppet mascot. So you are a puppet master. That wasn't in the Madlibs episode.
That wasn't in the Madlibs episode guys. Puppet master says what?
What? Puppet master confirmed. What did you say? Moving on. I couldn't hear you.
Moving on, my reason number 11 is that...
Is that I'm...
I'm cute as a button!
I'm so nice!
I'm sweet and cute!
- Oh, wow.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- You do look really cute.
- Don't I look so sweet and cute?
- You remind me of Harry Styles.
- Don't I look like Harry Styles right now?
- Yeah, or, wow.
- I'm so sweet and red.
- God, you're good looking.
- Don't you wanna just love me all day?
- I wanna pinch your little cheek.
I'm a nice looking man. I'm a tall drink of water.
You're a hot tall cup.
And also is that number 12 is that with the various things that I have said online and done in public as well as my criminal record,
I'm thinking podcasting is the only job that will be acceptable, is tenable for me really.
Well, I mean you know that we do background checks, right?
We let's do a check right now. Okay.
Well, do you have any criminal history?
I knew this was coming.
Yes.
Have you ever done any drugs?
Yeah, this is coming one and a half one and a half one and a
half one and a half drugs one and a half of what drugs I do
one and a half.
Zans I do one and a half Zans at the club the other day.
That was your first time and only every time doing drugs.
It was the other day, it was about two days ago, and I just said, "You know, I wanted
to do some Zans."
Yeah.
So you said, "I'm going to do one and a half Zans."
I said, "Well, I did one," and then I said, "This thing's not kicking in.
This Zan ain't shit," you know, like that meme.
And then, so I said, "Give me another one!
Give me another one!"
And I tried to wrestle it out of this motherfucker's hand and I only got half of it.
It split in half.
Like a wishbone.
A slow-mo probably.
very strong grip strength. What were the effects of the Zan? I was barred out
essentially. I actually was out like a light and slept through the flight.
Yeah I took a flight. You took a flight? Right after that? Yeah. You jumped out of a plane to nowhere?
I wanted to go to LA. Two days ago you went to LA? Yeah, just for like vibes right? I wanted to go
See if I could pitch some pilots
Have some meetings. Okay, and what happened at the meeting with these producers?
There wasn't a meeting. Let me tell you let me tell you that much right now. Is it similar to this?
It was similar to this except this is actually you guys are a lot chiller about it than yeah
I mean adults whim I would say keep
Don't change Rick and Morty you better not fucking change anything about Rick and Morty. Yeah, yeah
This was voices the same, but this was only two days ago. Just two days ago. Yes
Man, yeah, they didn't like our pitch either
We pitched a travel show where you go we would go and see all the famous spots where all the famous vines happened
So we'd go to like the Zendaya is Michi wall
Be cream the wall where dad backflip though, yeah
Do the the place where the guy hits the skateboard or whatever and they said they said that nobody would recognize it. That's a street
That's a wall. The Zendaya is Michi sign isn't even there anymore. Yeah, they change it to a different move
So they just basically have no taste in comedy. Yeah, they're falling they fell off
I mean, yeah, it's crazy. I mean you just gotta fucking
Pitch it to it's it's all on FX these days all the real shit. I mean for sure
Roku yeah
I heard to be as a little money
Samsung TV Samsung TV is on yeah, it's like all they want is animation anyway pretty much no travel shows
Hey, hands up you motherfuckers. You thought I was running low on energy because I came in so hot. No
I'm stuck out a couple more here. Okay? Um
So this is the only job that'll hire me, please
Please hire me and don't do a background check into my criminal history
We won't background check
Don't ask me don't ask any of my friends about the contents of my character for character references
Okay, yeah, I don't know any of your friends
Square
Number 13 is that I I can make I can make a whole nut
I can sexually bust down any any ho
Megan Fox Megan Fox Pamela Megan Fox
Fox I could I could Riz nut and
About 30 seconds, can you 30? Okay?
Can you teach me and Patrick how to have a Riz and make?
Woman cuz I hate we both need it zero
zero. We get zero.
Cameron's not taught us how to have any riz?
Cameron's never taught us anything.
I know that he eats pussy all day.
I tried to teach you guys some riz,
you guys were not receptive.
He comes in here and does this.
He asks us to smell his double finger.
And we say, "Why would you put two in there?"
And you know, I'm so riz-less and I'm a wimp,
I think, "He's doing the improv gun!"
No, no, no, no, no.
As I, what really happens, I tell you
to smell my finger and it smells like my penis
I jacked off into a girl from across the room into a girl. That's Riz. That's Riz
It's called all these dope-ass fucking kung-fu Riz moves, and he's not teaching us bullshit Brian
I wish I could take you guys to the Riz dojo, but you would not cut it the hojo
Yeah, so you'll teach us how to fucking finger fuck
How's about this? I'm gonna go to the bathroom really quick, and then cuz I
I ran here.
You've been sipping on that ginger ale.
I've been sipping on the zero sugar ginger ale.
Thank you to Schweppes.
You got that from Schweppes?
Yeah, I went to Schweppes.
This is the one,
my one friend who still talks to me,
he...
You went to Schweppes? You went to our university?
I, well, no.
I mean, there's a campus there, but it's for the
interns.
But I went to Schweppes. I went to Schweppes HQ.
My one friend who still talks to me is HRW Schweppes, and he has given me
He's given me a lifetime supply of zero sugar ginger ale.
That's very subtle.
My favorite.
I didn't know you knew Schweppes.
That's just another thing that you bring to the table is that you could probably give us...
Literally, literally. That's funny, right? Can I stay?
We'll talk about it while he's in the bathroom.
the battle. I've been sipping on the Schweppes awful. I gotta go peep and poop.
But I'll be right back. You guys do me a favor and just don't call the cops.
No, we're not gonna call the cops. There's no service in here.
Yeah, it's in a basement. Okay, okay. I really don't want to kill anyone.
I don't want to make you dance. We don't want to dance. You have no motive for this.
I'm not a bad guy. You're not a bad guy. I've done bad things.
I can tell you yeah you have a nice soul all right well I got be all beer all
right enjoy the be thank you have fun you got a jiggle a handle yeah of the
door and the toilet yeah might take a minute you're bringing the Schweppes in
the bathroom with you and I'm gonna take my ski mask just in case anyone
recognizes me on the way the bathroom okay okay
Usually my gun
We can't call the cops we lose our cred
No, we call 3-1-1
Or is that 411?
Wait, what's your idea?
Traveling?
I was going to call 411.
That does nothing for us.
Yeah.
Because, I mean, we've just had this back here for like a month or something.
Oh, yeah.
This gasoline?
Jerry can.
This gasoline.
One gallon gasoline.
Oh my god, and I have my lunch.
You brought your lunch?
Oh.
Big bowl of popcorn.
And he's a food tester.
Holy shit.
We could tell.
Oh my god, that is so sweet.
- Okay, you go ahead. - Look out, look out.
Okay.
- And gasoline is poison, right?
- I don't think you can eat it.
- I think it ruins popcorn.
- It definitely ruins popcorn.
- It's melting the popcorn.
- Yeah, I think it's corrosive.
- And the-- - Shh, Kyle, he's gonna hear it.
- Oh, I'm sorry, hold on, I'll keep my voice down.
- Okay, just pour all the gasoline.
- Yeah, just pour all the gasoline onto the popcorn.
- Shh, shh.
- Shut the fuck up. - Quiet.
- Sorry, I have an Irish whisper in my voice.
- That's probably enough.
Okay, that should be all the gasoline on the popcorn. I hope he comes and eats this and kills him.
Maybe in front of his seat. He's gonna smell it, man.
I just heard the toilet flush. It smells like fucking gasoline.
Oh, hey, Brian! Oh, Brian!
Hey, guys! We got you...
I'm gonna get my ski mask. Yeah, get your...
We got you this. You said...
So, we had an idea...
And it's your birthday.
And because it's your birthday, we didn't have a cake.
We had Caleb's lunch lying around.
Uh-huh. And since you're a food tester...
- Why don't you, um, taste--
- Eat the popcorn.
- The present.
- Popcorn, huh?
Well, hmm.
Hmm.
- Smells pretty good.
- It smells--
- It does smell great.
- It's heavily buttered.
It's got a lot of butter on it.
- It's an oily butter.
It's an oily--
- And you didn't eat anything before you came, right?
Oh, no, no, just a banana and toast this morning with some coffee, of course, with my French
press.
Okay.
You must be hungry then for, it's almost, what, almost three o'clock.
You know what?
I'm not hungry.
You're not hungry.
Actually, my appetite was spoiled.
But it's good.
really nasty crap in there and I just I don't want to I don't want to have to do
that don't you want to refill I don't want to have to take another
it's really good right lunch he eats every day popcorn and paper it's good
it's good but it's good it's birth I can't eat it cuz it's but oh it's if I
had eaten it this is what I would do it
yes oh wow and I like and I like it even though I'm not hungry
I'm not hungry. On second thought, you know what? I just really don't want to have a crap
again later, you know? I just, I don't. I know if I eat now, I'm going to crap later.
I just don't want to do it. I'll put this over here and when you do get hungry, you
can eat it. Yeah. Right? That's very thoughtful. But until then, you should, we definitely
should, let's not make any rash decisions on the future of the podcast and who's going
to live or pass away.
- We're not making any rash decisions.
I thought we were making rash decisions.
- Popcorn gives me a rash.
- That's what we were talking about.
- If I decided to eat it, I would get a rash.
- And an incision.
- Yeah.
- And you know when you bite the popcorn kernel,
it makes an incision in the roof of your mouth.
- The corn gets stuck in the, ah, yes of course.
My mistake, I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- I won't look at you that aggressively.
But I still gotta keep an eye on you.
- Okay, gotcha.
So, okay, so you've hung out with us?
- Let's look at the facts.
- Let's look at the facts, all right?
- Let's look at the facts, come on.
- We hung out, we had a good time.
- We had a great time, right?
- Yeah, we had a good time.
- So here's the thing, man.
- Yeah?
- We don't have to kill Cameron, or--
- No.
- Right?
- I kind of was thinking we were all on the same page
about this, we're all gonna kill him now.
I thought we--
- But--
- Come on.
- Well, okay, we're not all on the same page.
I mean--
- Well, three against one, you know what I mean?
versus one is still, I mean some cultures they don't,
a one beats the three.
- What culture would that be?
- Polish.
- Native American.
- So you're saying we go by Polish rules
where minority rules in a voting situation.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Well, this minority right here,
in terms of who has a gun,
I'm the, in that case I am the minority,
and i rule and i say
can we please kill him please
just we're not going to die i don't want to die just because it's your birthday
okay i'm not going to die
i don't want to die stop making me dance i danced so much last night i'm tired
my legs are sore i danced i hit the gritty he went to elsewhere
wow he hit the gritty at elsewhere i hit the gritty in my living room afterward too i did
two gritties
so it's your birthday by the way
brian brian
I mean, we gotta know, how old are you turning?
Me?
Yeah, you said it's your birthday, so how old are you turning?
How old am I turning?
You mean in terms of years?
Years, yeah, your year age.
I guess today, if I go by today and then count back, 365, 365, 365, 365, 365, 365, 365, 365,
if I go by today and then count back...
365...365...365...366...
Excellent sleep here...365...366...
I think I'm turning... gosh...
900 years old!
I'm turning 900 years old, actually.
900?
Yeah, 900 years old.
That makes not even a lick of sense.
Wait, Brian.
You can't live to 900 years old.
Nobody lives to be 900 years old.
That's impossible.
Except for Yoda, but he disappeared and he turned 900.
Wait.
But that can't be.
Wait, what's happening to you?
That can't be.
No!
I've been defeated!
Wow, that solves that problem, I guess.
It's not that big of a deal, right?
Yeah.
And now we've got a free gun.
That's cool.
Whoa!
Oh nice gun time gun time gun time gun time gun time gun time
Bye!
Stop!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
you