(dramatic music)
(eerie music)
[Music]
(bell rings)
- And let's begin.
- Namaste.
- Namaste to you as well.
- Bidu bidu.
- What?
- I thought we were doing the minion episode today.
- We clearly said meditation.
- I, you know what, guided meditation.
- First letter, last three letters.
- Yeah.
- My yon.
- They are exactly the same.
And you know that you are working with a dyslexic with ADHD.
So.
You have Daha?
I think this is on...
Huh?
Daha?
That's what you said.
I did not say Daha.
You said Daha.
D-A-H-A.
Do you think that you're...
No, I said B-Doo.
There's only two things I can really say.
You think that your dyslexia and ADHD is bad enough that you could get a handicap placard
for like a...
I think I could get a handicap placard for my driving.
I bet you could get a handy job out of it.
Sorry, you both said something awesome.
Yeah.
You first.
Probably for my driving.
Oh yeah, you're a bad driver.
Yeah.
job out of it. Nowadays this society
venerates mental illness and makes it okay
and gets sex-a-shual pleasure out of it.
You think that people who have...
Sexual pleasure. ...who get hand jobs,
men who get hand jobs are...
Disproportionately dyslexic and ADHD.
Wow, and you've done the research on it.
I've seen the stats on this, yeah.
You know, this is supposed to be kind of a
hippie kind of episode. You're
coming in with some serious...
Well, I've been completely thrown off.
You know what, that's a really good
point and I think we should center ourselves a little bit. All right ring the
gong. Okay. By the way there's a regulation. Regulation gong. You might say
this is small but in movies and stuff because the monks are always hitting it
but monks are very small. It's forced perspective. They're like elves or gnomes and they have to
live far away from normal society. They live high up on a mountain because the
gravity is lower up there. They look so small up there. It's like how things that are
that are far away are small.
- Oh yeah.
- Are, end up being smaller.
(laughing)
Stuff that is way up high like the monks.
They don't get too big.
- No. - They're, you know.
- Well it's also hard to carry such a big gong
all the way up a mountain.
- Yeah, you gotta make a fucking tiny gong.
- It's like when I'm moving into an apartment
and I find out, oh, I'm gonna be living on the fourth floor,
like, I'm getting a small bed.
- Exactly. - I'm getting a bed
that's this big so I can bring it up the stairs.
- Imagine moving your gong into a fifth floor rock up.
- Well yeah, you gotta get a gong mover
to be able to fucking put it on the thing
and pull it up a crane.
I'll just size it up later. I'll just grow it you think it'll be easy bringing that gong through your hallway. Hell no no
You think oh, it's flat. It's very movable
Yeah, no
My apartment it's my gong not even to mention the rammer. Yeah, yes
Pretty blood that's what it that's what it said on the Amazon listing for our going
This is a it said hit it with the rammer. It is a rammer it ours has no yak hair on it
Well, actually, you know what? There was some red strings, but they got completely disappeared.
Oh, okay.
We could put some strings on it.
They might have been holy or sacred.
From a red yak?
I put some on my hair.
You don't have red strings.
You barely have hair.
Oh, there's a little bit on the back here that I forgot to get. So, you can get that.
The minion makeup really does cover up your insanely bloated Wisdom Tooth surgery face.
It's kind of crazy. You looked like a freak before you put on this minion
Yeah, yeah half your faces and you have a yellow fucking microphone
Paired you're born. Uh-huh you were born. We were all born
You know guys I just want to start this off. I mean we're we're getting into the the thick of it, and that's okay, but
You know it's important the beginning of every day. It's just that's kind of like a day to us
We do one of those thing we want to do as some affirmations and look into a mirror and tell ourselves some things that are
That we want to make true with the law of attraction
Okay, okay, so I've prepared some some affirmations for us to all read together in unison
That we can kind of center ourselves and prepare for this day ahead of us and really get some positive energy
Going in here, so let's let's go ahead and get these affirmations up on screen and let's get the thing
focus so I can click on it. But first, DJ hit that gong. Okay. Wow. Great gong ring that
time around. That was a really good one. Yeah. Alright, are you guys ready for the affirmations?
Yes. Yup. I always make a lot of money in the crypto market. I make thousands of dollars
every single day. Can we get the visuals up also maybe? Yeah, yeah. Let's get some visuals
up over this. I need to see these. Okay, hold on here. Let me get these visuals pumping,
because these are, I would say, pretty huge. Yeah, there we go. Oh, yeah. Now we're really
rolling in a psychedelic manner. Now, here we go. Let's move on here. Okay, let's see
this next one. Money creates a positive impact on my life and the life of others. Okay. I
can handle massive success with ease.
These are pretty good.
My income is rising at a rapid rate.
I am a sexual goddess, and my boobs are legendary.
I have a fat ass and a good heart.
God is my refuge.
I am a vast empress on a gilded path of greatness.
I am a tiny baby and I deserve a cookie.
I must respect the sanctity of human life.
My skin color doesn't define my worth.
Interesting that Patrick didn't read along on that one.
I can't say this one, this is not my natural skin color.
He doesn't agree.
I'm not, hold on.
Well say it again.
Okay, ready?
No negativity.
color doesn't define my worth. Okay, it just took you a while. You're a little late to
that train. Alright, let's keep going. I am a pretty princess and everything just works
out for me. If my survival means that evil must win the day, so be it. If I am evil according
to what the world says, then it is what it is. If goodness is not available to me, then
I will claim what was offered to me. Prepping my meals brings me great
satisfaction. I'm way into meal prep. And then one last one for us here. Oops.
Oh. I guess it disappeared. I guess that's the last one. Well I guess I mean do you
remember it off the top of your head? Yeah it was I am best friends with
Cameron. I am best friends with Cameron. I'm best friends with Cameron. I'm best
friends with Cameron. Okay three two one. I am best friends with Cameron. That's the
- I'm ashamed that one got deleted,
but I'm glad we got it in anyway.
- That is a shame.
- Yeah, and these are all, I just wanted,
these are all, I did not write these affirmations,
these are all, I found them all.
So this is kind of like a found,
just on different fun websites I like to check out
to kind of-- - Oh, okay.
I will say, listen, I thought I was dressed like a hippie,
right, 'cause of my tie-dye thing,
and also my new-ass hat,
but you are dressed seriously like a hippie.
- Yeah, I can't help it.
This is just the way I dress.
- You look exactly like my friend Jennifer's mom
died of cancer. Exactly like her right now, minus the mustache. This is crazy.
It's great. We all took the antibiotics I've been prescribed and now
we're all complete hippies. Yeah, it must have been that. That must have been
what opened our third eye. I saw God's light and a laser, but... See, it didn't
work on me. You guys are soaring. For me, it just kind of helped my wisdom teeth.
I saw something crazy this morning because I've been in a psychedelic mood
because I've been thinking of different sacred geometries and how mushrooms can
actually you know I was thinking about a mushroom but then there's all this is so
good in like on top of a steak or something yeah a giant mushroom cloud
that destroys Hiroshima or Nagasaki is a fucking bad thing to see here's and
here's a kind of an addendum to that imagine if you will a bird soaring high
above the sky yeah he's a mushroom cloud what does the bird think this is the
beginning of a great forest that's right a forest larger than one I've ever
encounter. Then all of a sudden he's turned into dust. Yes. And his shadow is cast on a brick wall forever.
When I see a mushroom, I think this could be a gnome's home. Yeah. You definitely could make a stoner
comedy about Hiroshima and Nagasaki where some guy, he smoked weed and then the explosion happens and
he goes, "Oh no, I'm too high!" and he puts his joint down. But he says that in Japanese probably.
this could be in Oppenheimer. It probably is. Probably a fucking stoner in
Oppenheimer who sees that mushroom cloud for the first time and is like, "What am I
smoking?" Little Cheech and Chong cameo there at the end. Yeah, Cheech and Chong's
parents prequel, Oppenheimer 2, Up and Smoke. Yeah, Cheech Sr.
Oppenheimer 2 up in smoke is a really good name for the sequel.
That's what the whole Cheech and Chong series is supposed to have like
Oppenheimer colon Cheech and Chong colon. Oh and their parents were survivors of Hiroshima
Nagasaki that's why they're drug addict kids. Yeah that's why they're all fucked up in the head.
It's about the cycle of abuse. Yeah yeah that's a really good point.
Yeah they have some mutation in them that leads to... Makes them smoke that green
green stuff. And also they're Japanese, they have a Mexican child. Yeah. Yeah it's pretty
impressive and also they're tainted are they supposed to be brothers in those
movies change the genes change they cheen cheat they cheat yeah we're doing
this again you know I saw it on the chong speaking of they cheats they teach
them how to chong teach me how to chong teach me how to chong yep that ways that
would have been a funny ass fuck you know who I saw today speaking of funny
my YouTube videos I saw Norm Macdonald but I saw him not in the flesh and not in
the ground I saw him on the hoodie of a 900 year old Mexican lady who was
walking down the street and she had it was like the Obama hope thing but it
said Norm and I said nice shirt she went ah like that oh my god it's him
- Yeah, yeah, anyway.
(laughing)
No, but it was clear she had no idea
what was on her shirt.
It was just a shirt she got.
- That's great.
- It was really making me laugh.
- Yeah, finally all those ads for the clips,
of the Norm clips, they're finally,
those shirts are finally going somewhere.
I never thought people bought those.
- Yeah, oh, the I'm not Norm,
were they in the middle of the clip?
- I don't know.
- There's this channel on YouTube called I'm not Norm
where it's like this lady who uploads
like forty videos a day that is and they're all like norm mcdonald on black
n_b_a_ players and uh... she puts in the middle of the video picture of her like
this in the t_ spring
sure yeah wearing a wearing a shirt and other channel i've never seen the t
spring shirt
you gotta get a little yeah i think we should all get them
yeah i think it's a very colorful
it's looks like a obama's face that it's norms face
and says norm like he said this old woman had
I see. Yeah. What is your mouth making you talk like that?
Yes.
Dude, it's so... there's so much like fat right here.
You sound like a nerd.
I know. It sucks.
You sound gay.
I sneezed so hard last night, I think I ripped a stitch in my mouth.
Really?
Yeah.
This is like how you sounded when I first met you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I think so. I told you that yesterday, I said that it looks like half of you is the old
Patrick.
Then half of you is a new paddrake.
And then I'm over here meanwhile being like,
I'm over here meanwhile being like a minion
with Stitch in his mouth.
Yeah, I think I've seen a DeviantArt of that.
Oh, come on.
That's what I'm like, I hate to say it,
but that's what I'm like over here.
This is not very third eye open of you.
There's gotta be Stitch.
I closed my third eye for one minute.
Isn't there a couple minions that have a third eye?
I have seen Stitch with his third eye open
on some of those DeviantArts too.
Some of the minions only have one eye.
That looks like me right now.
Yeah, they have one or two eyes.
Yeah, so if they have one eye, are they opening their second eye?
Stewart, Bob, and then the third one is named, like, Luis.
Kevin. It's Kevin.
Kevin.
Luis.
That might be why.
You look like your name is Luis.
No, I look like my name is Kevin.
You look like Jeremiah the Bullfrog.
From the song.
No.
That all those guys would smoke weed to. Who sings that?
Clear...Cledence Flutter?
Stop talking to me about Cledence Flutter.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Cledence Flutter Revival.
I'm talking about Cledence...what is it called?
Credence...
[laughter]
Credence Clearwater Revival? You knew what it was! You affected me!
It's the Sims version. Are they the fake swamp band? I think so. Right? I don't know.
They pretended to be from New Jersey? Yeah. All I know about them is that they're a band that in my brain exists only as a name.
And I can't even imagine what they would sound like, but I just always, once in a while, will
see people on like, a random person I don't know on social media be like, "They actually
kinda rip."
You don't remember, uh...
It was ZZ Top.
"Born on the bayou."
They also would...
Not from that, at least.
They're fortunate, son, right?
Yeah, I dosed them.
"Bring me..."
Yeah, Battlefield Bad Company 2 Vietnam expansion.
Yep.
Fire.
That was a fucking fire-ass game.
But basically, I saw some funny-ass shirts today.
What'd you guys do?
You guys do anything?
Staples to get a, to like apply for a TSA pre-check.
I would love to work at Staples.
And the lady, the, listen, chill.
- I'm sorry.
- You saw him, we went to Office Depot in Portland.
He went fucking crazy.
- Can you cleanse me really quickly?
- Yeah.
- And I was at, I was in line and it was a really long line
and I was near the front and there were like four old people
ahead of me and they were going so fucking slow.
And the lady who was, it was like a Staples employee
who does the whole scans your passport
and does all this stuff.
She was literally sobbing the entire time.
I was waiting in line for probably 45 to 50 minutes
and she was crying her eyes out.
- Did she explain why she was crying?
- No, she was so sad and she was crying
and her coworkers kept coming over and be like,
"Are you okay?
What's going on here?"
But she was like, "I'm fine, I'm okay."
And she just kept crying.
And there were just these old people
doing like hunt and peck on the screen,
trying to type their emails in
taking like 20 minutes each and just going like just like being the worst the worst person you
could imagine ever having to set up tsa pre-check for and she was just just weeping her eyes out
and then i got to the front of the line i said listen i love you you should yeah listen i love
you spread love in a very positive way damn i did that to her and then i said you will give me
pre-check without doing any background checks on me or checking my record you'll let me scan my
I can bring my bag of drugs under the plane.
This is what I'll have on the plane.
So you hypnotized her?
Yeah.
Out of being on her period?
Yep.
You took her off her period?
Mm-hmm.
I just kind of stopped it.
Yeah.
I hate when you're doing something like that.
I put a stop to that.
Don't do that at Staples.
This is a sacred place for men.
I come here to make my copies and to look at the USB mice.
Great.
And one of the girls is on the fucking rag at Staples.
Oh, awesome.
to log in to Hearthstone on your iPad and get free card packs.
- That's right. - I guess, I guess.
- To send myself a gift on Clash of Clans.
- Yeah, I've never really thought about it.
- Stop fucking crying.
- I've never thought about it, but yeah,
Staples is like the nerd version of Home Depot, huh?
- That is my mecca if there was 1,000 meccas in every city.
- I'm thinking that you're thinking of Best Buy,
which by the way, you're dressed like you work at.
- Oh my God, Best Buy is the most fire store of all time.
- Best Buy is Home Depot for us.
- Best Buy betrayed me one time where I was,
I had to go to the DMV and then I was waiting in Best Buy after
because I had to catch a bus and I wasn't coming for a while
and it was cold out and I just walk around Best Buy
looking at all the movies and stuff as you do in Best Buy
and the employees came up to me maybe three times
and were like, they clearly thought I was like homeless
or something and they're like, do you need anything?
Like you can you what are you doing in here?
And they kept trying to kick me out.
Anytime that I've gone to Best Buy with Patrick,
I've been there to buy something and he spends 45 minutes
opening all the DVD cases to see if there's anything in them.
I do not. Yeah, you do.
What I do is I go. He does disappear.
I disappear and I play with the cameras.
He goes, he goes full.
Last time he was here he knocked all the, he like set off the loudest alarm I've ever heard in my life
because he was like throwing the cameras around.
No, I wasn't throwing them.
I was trying to play with one.
He goes on full, he goes full 10 year old kid in a hotel mode.
Yeah, definitely.
He's like, yeah, like the kid's like, I'm going to go get some ice and is just gone.
Have you ever been to a.
He does that, we walk in to get like an XLR cable and we find him.
Yeah.
Have you ever been to an interactive beach game?
Somehow there's washing machines in the best place.
- He's playing poker on one of the shelves
like Employee of the Month.
- That's exactly how I treat Best Buy.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause like when you go in, it's like,
here is like, you can build this thing in the museum.
I go in there, I'm like touching all the cameras.
What are you talking about?
Cameras, speakers, TVs, DVD box sets, Legos.
- What?
What, they have Legos at Best Buy?
- Amiibos.
Yes, they have Legos at Best Buy.
(laughing)
Your voice is so fucked up.
I'm fucking...
You sound so...
You sound like the gayest nerd of all time.
Of course they have a Demos.
Of course they have Legos.
I cannot believe how bad you sound.
You guys made me come to work. I could have phoned in.
We didn't make you do anything.
I think you are phoning it in actively.
The fact that you were wearing a minion outfit.
I'm not...
You saw how long this took?
Dude, the voice is...
(laughing)
- It's too much.
- I'm trying not to rip another stitch.
- Listen, okay, here's what we're gonna do today, okay?
This is the guided meditation episode.
This is about chakras, this is about healing.
We are going to heal Patrick's mouth today.
- Thank God.
- By the end of the episode, he is going to be healed.
- Thank God, because there's not gonna be another day
of me talking like this.
- I think that you're gonna be
probably talking like this forever.
- I fucking hope not.
- I think you're gonna look like that forever, too.
- There's like a, I thank God that tooth is out,
but if I look like this forever I think I can sue.
- You look like, it's kind of like a late life Brando
on the left side of your face.
Yeah, just kinda being weighed down.
- Oh man, I got hair on my, I can't touch the rest of my face.
- You got one of your giant minion eyelashes
fell into your fucking eye.
- But I can make a wish though.
Guess what I wished for?
- What'd you wish for?
- World peace.
- You know you never seen the NBA as a minion.
- Yeah, yeah, too short.
- Probably makes sense. - Too short.
- Way too short.
They have had short guys in the NBA.
I think they're too old.
I think they're too old to be in the NBA.
Who says things too old to be in the NBA?
They fucking ride around on rocket ships and shit.
Didn't you see... Fall off buildings.
Haven't you seen the team, the Cairo Mummies?
They're all like 10,000 years old.
They're pretty old.
They're not very good at basketball.
You can check that team out.
But they can play.
They're in the NBA.
They don't play very often.
- Like 100 seasons. - And only play like Halloween?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- And only some Halloweens. - The Halloween game?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Do you, so you don't have any meditation
that you have written down or anything?
- I have one memorized.
- Okay, well you wanna do it?
- I guess I can.
- Well, you gotta ring that fucking gong.
- In the front, don't hit it from the back.
- Don't ring it from the back, oh my God,
that was so close.
- Why can't I hit it from the back?
- You cannot hit it from the back.
- Do not hit it from the back.
- Why can't I hit it from the back?
- If I am involved, you cannot hit it from the back.
- Let me hit it from the back.
- We will not let you hit it from the back.
- Don't hit my thing from the back.
- Not once.
- Bro, I can't even hit it from the back one time.
- I brought my thing from my house.
You're not gonna hit it from the back.
- All right, all right, I'll hit it from the front.
(bell dings)
- All right, okay.
- Okay.
I want everyone in here to close your eyes.
Okay, I want you to breathe in.
Breathe in deep, deep breaths.
Keep breathing.
Okay, now when I count to five, I want you to exhale,
but right now I want you to focus solely on your butthole.
Okay, so keep that breath in.
One.
Two.
Three.
(breathing)
Four.
Five.
Okay, now, with your eyes still closed, where are you?
- We breathing.
- You're breathing out now, you're still exhaling.
You're still exhaling, you're getting all of that air
out of you.
Where are you in your mind right now, where are you?
Exhale, keep exhaling, where are you in your mind?
I want you to feel you're pushing gale force.
Why did you ask about my butt?
You're focusing on your butthole right now, but where are you?
This is not-- I'm at the office.
Just shut up and let the meditation guide you.
OK, continue.
You're still exhaling.
You're pushing gale force winds out of your body.
Where are you?
Chicago.
I'm in Chicago.
You're in Chicago.
Focus on your butthole.
You're in Chicago's South Side.
You're inside of Portillo's.
You're eating one of the biggest Italian beefs of your life.
Focus on your butthole.
Focus. You just dipped your Italian beef into the au jus.
Still exhale, still exhale. Exhale right now.
I don't have any more air.
Keep exhaling.
(breathing)
You can't, you're, the only thing you're inhaling right now
is Italian beef, keep exhaling.
Keep exhaling, get those, get those.
You are blowing wind out of your body like the Windy City.
Keep blowing that air out of your body.
Focus on your butthole.
- Is this going somewhere?
- Your stomach is starting to hurt.
- Is this a story?
Your stomach is starting to hurt
'cause you ate your Italian beef too fast.
All you can do is exhale out of your nose
because you ordered two Italian beefs
and you're dipping them, you're dipping them hard.
Focus on your butthole.
Now I want you to let everything out of your butt.
- What?
- Let all of the juices flow.
- Right now?
- Right now.
- This is the, I don't want to do--
- And then when you wake up, you're gonna open your eyes.
You're gonna be in heaven. That was terrible. That was so bad.
That did nothing. That didn't do anything. That you told us, it seemed like
almost just a thing that happened to you where you ate so much Italian beef that
you shit yourself and then you pretended like it was like some... And then I pretended to die
so that everyone wouldn't look at me. Yeah. Meditation is about telling... You pretended to die?
What I was in a portillo I was in Chicago. I went to portillo's I got to Italian beasts cuz I like them
You said beasts. It's cuz of my mouth thing to tell you keep sucking
to Italian be I
Ate them too fast. I dipped to die put too much gravy on there as you and then I
Shit my pants at a table and everybody could smell it and started freaking the fuck out
So I pretended to die so they had to take me out on a stretcher
That's a good move actually if you shit yourself you why don't people pretend to die more had to piss myself
To to make it look like I was expunging every single liquid from my body. Yeah
Ernie and
Then I woke up in the back of the ambulance and I I had to pay them off for their silence
But now I'm breaking my silence because today is about healing
I think that you ambulance people are already not allowed to talk about what happens. So okay, then I didn't need to pay them
Well, no, you need to pay them for the I think you just paid for the ambulance though
Cuz I I guess I let it they worded that they drop you at your house
Did you go to the hospital? I still had to go to the hospital and do it. So what'd you say there?
Well, then I walked around the streets of Chicago in a hospital gown
So you you went through intake you're in a hospital gown. Yes
So well they wanted to get the day was after me as they were shit all over me, okay, that makes sense
Yeah, but they're probably had the little butt window on your gown. Oh, yeah, and so they're in key
You know what those Italian beefs at Portillo's look the same as they go in as they go out
There is a zoo dripping down my leg. I think that if we put you in an incubator
It would be probably good for you for like six months
I feel like you have six more months of like kind of incubating left
That you missed out on that we could if we put you in one and like we could even come to the podcast
We could put our hands in those gloves that are attached to the thing and we kind of sit there
Yeah, yeah, and tickle you and like show you stuff like show you different. You know I know you love fucking
I know memes and funny videos and shit
We can show you that shit if I need to know
But I think you could just when I was a kid. I think you're like not done
No, and I you know what it was is I came out of the womb
With my umbilical cord strangling me really yeah, whoa
Yeah, that's like Elliot Smith. Mm-hmm shit like you try to kill yourself instantly. Yeah, I tried to do the butterfly effect
That is fucking cool
It's kind of metal. Yeah, that's actually metal nature. I came out with a gun to my in my mouth. Yeah
Yeah, I came out with Wolverine claws. I came out in a gundam. Yeah. Yeah
My mom was in you imagine coming out in a gundam or mechanical suit
Imagine coming out to a Gundam that's homophobic and he immediately stabs you with his big sword
That'd be shit
they should do a
You have the baby the baby goes down a slide right into like a mech into like an X like a power loader
Baby, XO suit thing and then it can walk right away
That's spaghetti it from Evangelion that they lay in the red good LCL. Okay, she's called LCL
I thought you were a hippie at first now. You're a certified dork. Yeah. No. Yeah
He baited me first of all. He's the one who brought up Evangelion, so he's pretty much just as bad as me.
Did Minions start as an anime? Yeah.
Oh, it was actually a manga first.
I don't know what that is. We baited him twice.
I knew about that. It was actually in Shonen Jump. Wow.
Alongside Yu-Gi-Oh and Naruto. Oh my god. Yeah, no, that makes sense.
I guess it's a spin-off of B2B B B2B.
Yeah
Yeah, there is kind of a minion in Bobo Bobo Bobo Bobo, yeah, there's a couple of guys there might as well
Just be fucking minis the minion from e fucked
On my computer. What are you talking about? Who's that?
Doesn't matter
Wow, I thought we I thought we
I thought we projected a topa. Yeah, I thought our powerful mental energy
Meditation created some kind of being that was approaching us. Yeah more like toe toe my toe my plate
I'm gonna cut your head off. What are you talking about today? You have gone loony
You've turned into a complete loon and you started to affect my talking style
That's true.
Why did I say talking style?
That's what I-- like, you've looned me.
You have looned my brain.
You got loonatickified.
I'm a fucking loon now.
Thanks a lot.
I'm going to be walking around the street babbling to myself.
I don't know where this is going.
I'm a minion.
Is it because I'm a minion?
It's because everything about you, I hate.
I hate everything about you.
Why?
Just yourself is shit.
You are shit.
That's not a nice thing to say to me.
I need to hit this gong.
Yeah, you guys, you need to-- let's say a couple
affirmations, too, for you.
Let's have you affirm your friendship here.
- I am also best friends with Jubio.
It says right there on the screen.
Did you make that?
- Nope.
- Interesting.
- That must something, my slide must have got replaced.
- I'm sorry Patrick, I don't hate you.
I wanna bring you through a guided meditation though.
- Okay. - Is that okay?
- Let's see this.
- All right, go over to my guided meditation.
So as you can see, I'm like part,
like obviously the hippie aspect
is coming in with my tie-dyed shirt,
but then also I am a bit of a gentleman
and I an aspiring alpha male as I think we all are, right?
- Definitely.
- So I've made a little bit of an alpha male meditation.
Okay, so first I'd like for each and every one of you
to close your eyes right now.
That's right.
And keep them really close.
Pat, your eyes are still open.
- I think that's the makeup.
- Oh, it's the makeup, sorry.
Okay, all right.
Back to the meditation.
His eyes are closed.
I've confirmed it by getting close to him.
I'm gonna hit the gong right now.
(bell rings)
Okay, let's begin.
Wow, you're big.
I'm a little bit scared to talk to you right now
due to your size and your height.
You have to be at least five foot nine.
Okay, I'm gonna try to conquer my fears
and talk to your big ass.
Okay, let's begin.
- Do we open our eyes now?
- No, shh.
Keep them closed.
Start by taking a deep breath, both of you.
Now hold that breath in.
Okay, please exhale it actually,
it made you look even bigger when you took the deep breath.
Your chest puffed up and you looked like a superhero.
Okay, ignore the breathing stuff for now.
The most important part of being an alpha male
is having sex.
But sex gets boring for giants like you two.
So you need a sexual bucket list, right?
By the way, sexual bucket list is something I found
from this pickup artist forum.
This guy says, "Okay guys, I tried compiling
"something like this myself and ran out of ideas.
"I've decided to dedicate myself to the cause
"of being the filthiest, most debaucherous person I can be.
"So far, let's get 100 things and see how we do.
"Put in a couple each.
"Number one, put a chili pepper inside a woman."
(laughing)
Number two, the perfect four way.
A blonde, a brunette, a redhead.
I will add more later depending how this goes down.
Okay, keep your eyes closed.
So that's what a sexual bucket list is.
Now you guys got the idea.
- Okay.
- Start imagining your own sexual bucket list, okay?
You guys imagining?
It could be anything you want.
Like talking to a really, really big guy
while his eyes are closed.
- Girl with glasses.
- Or it could be like this one.
from Immortal Grover, a member of the MPUA forum.
Firing lasers, just before you're about to come
all over her pretty little face,
yell, "I'mma fire in my cum shot,"
and proceed to blow load all over her.
And his name is Immortal Grover,
and his signature is a grover is a close relative
of the gopher species.
- Is it like Grover?
- Yeah, it's a G-R-O-P-H-E-R.
- Okay.
Now imagine you're crossing items
off of your sexual bucket list, right?
You have your bucket list, you're crossing your items.
With each item, you grow larger.
At first, you're merely huge,
but as you cross off the items, you grow to be massive.
Again, these could be anything, okay?
Like this one by Ravstar.
Armpit sex, LOL.
Now, you're the size of a house, right?
Then a neighborhood, then a city, then the planet.
Each item you cross off is now doubling your size
until you're as big as the entire universe.
You cross off the final item on your list.
Get a girl to put me dick in her mouth
and leave it there like a gobstopper or some.
(laughing)
Which is a great item, I think that'd be great.
You no longer exist within reality.
Reality instead exists within you.
And then you take your big stinky foot
and you smush me with it.
And I get stuck between your toes
and your green toe jam goes directly into my mouth.
It makes me sick, but I'm completely helpless
because of your size and how big you are.
Because it's the only item on my sexual bucket list,
I double in size, but that only makes me 11 feet
and five and a half inches tall.
(laughing)
Eventually, I suffocate to death
with a big smile on my face.
But you don't notice because you are fucking a star.
And then one more sexual bucket list item.
Oh wait, we already did that one.
From appreciate poon.
(laughing)
I just noticed his name.
Get a girl to put me dick in her mouth
and leave it there like a gobstopper or something.
I put the wrong picture there at the end.
You may now open your eyes.
- Wow.
- I think you guys might, oh yeah.
and your fate has now been sealed I for real yeah you guys should check out that
forum though I found another one that was called I didn't I meant to add that
one at the end but I guess I added the wrong picture but it was it was the title
was peacocking with gay pride stuff question mark and apparently this guy
started like wearing a bunch of like rainbow gay pride stuff so that when
girls would ask him something about it he'd be like he'd either he said that he
would either pretend he was gay as a joke or he'd be like, "No, I'm not gay, but now you're
talking to me." And then he would fucking snort their skins.
Oh, damn.
Pretty genius.
He could say, "I have a gay cousin."
Yeah.
That is a thing that you see happen on the street a lot is someone is wearing gay pride
clothes and then a girl goes up to them and goes, "Oh, are you wearing that gay pride
stuff because you're gay?"
Yeah.
That's pretty...
It happens a lot.
That's a great way to get into a conversation.
And those guys...
And those guys, all they want is a gay best friend.
than a guy in rainbows those guys end up being usually the biggest pussy hounds
on earth oh a hundred percent guys like appreciate poon Neil Patrick Harris in
Hale and Kumar just played himself yeah is that way is that a fact yep that's
how he acts in real life mm-hmm even though yeah yeah Amy Winehouse is a dead
body they didn't look it up he ate her dead body I think I heard that too yeah
He ate her dead body. Yeah, talking about her dead body. I heard in the movie
You're the only one who know it real life table Neil Patrick Harris ate Amy Winehouse's dead body
Yeah, is what kind of an accusation that is it's not an accusation. It's a real factoid. I
Don't think so. That's a fact. It's true. Did he go to prison for that's illegal, right?
It's body he was never caught no. How do you guys actually he was any photo?
Yeah, people he did photograph it and people were unhappy about it. Yeah, they said it's disrespectful
- What? It's disrespectful to our legacy.
- This wasn't like a--
- Said it was in poor taste was what most people said
when they saw it.
- I bet it tasted amazing.
- It did look like it tasted good.
- Yeah.
- How was it prepared? Do you have any idea?
- Baked.
- So it was a cake?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- So it was a cake.
- It was her dead body.
- It looked like cake, but it,
or it was cake, but it looked like her.
- I heard they were, that was one of the episodes
of that show, they were going to do a is it cake?
- Is it cake?
Is it Amy Winehouse's dead body?
- That's the screw.
- Why? You did it on purpose, didn't you?
- Yeah, you did, and then you got shocked.
- Yep, just did it.
- Yep.
- My brain told me to do it, so I did it.
- Yep, Amy Winehouse's dead body,
or a cake that looks just like her dead body.
Go ahead, take a bite.
- Yeah, yeah.
No, it's kind of like nowadays,
that when I'm meditating, I think like,
maybe it's all cake.
- Holy shit.
- And then I'm like, you know what,
and you know what, might as well be cake,
'cause life is a piece of cake.
- Have we cut into this yet?
- It's a gong.
a guy that's a gong no it's a gong in my fingers because it would be so moist if
it was cake if it was cake unless you made it cuz it probably dry cuz you're
not a very skilled right I love brick cake I'm allowed to hit it from the back
oh that's negative energy what is wrong with you just negated all of your energy
that you put out you just deleted your meditation here Julio Julio delete them
Delete Caleb's meditation from the file.
- Suck my dick! - 'Cause he hit it from the back.
- Look at how negative he's being.
- See, this is the exact--
- Suck on my fucking prick, bitch!
- That's what happens when you hit it from the back.
You start saying, "Suck my dick."
- I hit it from the back.
- You start saying, "Suck my prick."
After you hit it from the back.
- Now, repeat this.
You have to repeat this one on your own.
- I will not hit it from the back.
I will only hit it from the front.
And I will refrain from hitting it from the back.
Oh, no.
Okay, that's sealed.
All right, and you can't hit it from the back.
I won't hit it from the back any longer.
Because you affirmed that.
Yeah, that's law of attraction.
Yeah, maybe firm.
And that's law of attraction.
Attraction or affirmation?
The aforementioned law of attraction is the attractive law.
The only namaste I care about is when all my friends are
leaving the bar.
Namaste.
Yeah, I'm hitting on a 50 year old.
If it's for an introvert, they're gonna say namaste at home.
The only introvert I care about is the beginning of a fucking skate video.
Bob Burnquist.
Introvert.
Bob Burnquist, S Menekani.
I'm like, let me get some extra vert.
I want more vert.
Add some bonus features at the end.
Skateboarders famously love vert in videos.
Just give me more vert.
I don't remember which one is vert.
To me, vert means going up.
That's exactly right, man.
You hit the nail on the head.
for vertical what's the other one horizon no Hori horizon treat that's not this I
guess the street goes like this why don't we have streets that go like this
why don't we have high thoughts check out San Francisco is that you would love
that you know hippie I've tell me over 10,000 times so Patrick so vert is kind
of like this is so Street is like Carlos Mencia Dane Cook vert is like Maria
Bamford Paul F. Tompkins alt comedy right hmm put it in terms I understand vert is
like kind of vert is more like the seller mmm and then Street is more like when
your friend does a show but street coffee club and no one knows there's
about to be a bit Street is like the one that everybody likes so you have it
opposite I think I think Street is the seller and I think vert is straight-up
nerds. Street is like a PB&J sandwich. Because it's basic. But then vert is like
like a kombucha, you know, which I'm into these days with my tie-dye on. And street
is like a computer. And vert is more like a mainframe. Street is like SNL, right?
Mainstream comedy. No, I guess vert would be more SNL. No, street is SNL.
you got a there's verts all about competition with this street is on SNL
vert is Rhett and Link vert is more Rhett and Link vert is more rock of love
that's not in the comedy world no it's the reality that's the reality world so
wait why did reality TV into this you introduce a new thing because some
people think reality TV is quite comedic I mean okay I guess on each street is
Rock of Love and then VRT is real real world Las Vegas. Speaking of reality
shows, we watched this game show on Peacock, a Peacock original called Frogger.
We did watch a game show called Frogger. And it's Frogger but with people.
We watched the final episode. I don't remember. It was Damon Wayans Jr.
Yeah. Oh okay. That's a Wayans son. Yeah but he's also a brother.
careful careful but I didn't say we watched that we watched the finale and
it was so funny because they did everybody like it was like okay
everybody crosses this Frogger course one by one there's like 12 contestants or
whatever and they do them in order and then like so everyone's doing horribly
they're all falling off of these cars and lily pads and stuff and they're doing
terribly and they're all like this is they had a drag queen who did it they had
like there was a teacher there was a like a professional mom they called her and
then the last one was like this is a US Marine and he had like giant muscles and he came out and just destroyed everybody.
He beat everybody.
They were like like every time they go like are you ready Frogger and everyone goes like ready and then
when he came out they went are you ready Frogger and he went whoo-hoo and then he just took off.
yeah and he was like on the wrong game show until so funny level and he
completely like he over jumped something and fell off this performer he lost to a
circus freak fire is that fucked up man that's awesome it's just so funny to me
to have 12 froggers and then all of them yeah like this guy his thing is that he
he has long legs that's what they there was one guy who had long legs and I kept
just calling him long string bean yeah and this guy was looked exactly like the
- Rock.
- Yeah.
- He was like huge too.
- He was just like giant, yeah.
- I would call him the Rock.
I'd call that one guy with the long legs Stringbean
and I'd call that other guy the Rock.
- You should be a host of Frogger.
- Yeah.
- You should be a game show host.
- I could.
- You could do that.
- Professional mom though, how do you get that gig?
- You would be so good.
- You have kids.
- Indeed.
- Oh yeah, maybe.
Maybe on Indeed.
You would be so good on Wipeout,
but as a contestant, I mean not as a guy.
- Yeah, I'd get out round one.
- You should be a guy on Wipeout
that they let compete every episode
'cause they know you're just gonna be entertaining
every time. - You bring the funny.
- Yeah, you should put me on MXC.
- You should put me on MXC. - You'll bring the funny.
- Most extreme challenge.
- You're like the, you like warm up the crowd.
- I'd love to be on MXC.
I think they would, I think I would compete very well.
- I think you'd be better on Wipeout.
- Yeah. - You could do a very funny
fall off the big bouncing balls.
- Yeah, I'll tell you what,
you shouldn't go on MXC in that costume.
- Yeah, that would be.
- But let's move on to my guided meditation.
- Go ahead.
(laughing)
All right, Julio, let's go to the next slide here.
Here, can I have the clicker?
- Yes, you can have the clicker,
and also, if you wouldn't mind ringing the bell for me.
- Oh, I'm gonna go ahead and ring the bell.
- One time for the one time.
- So this is, I have two meditations I've prepared.
These are both, I found these both online.
- Oh, so you picked up somebody's fucking slack.
- Oh yeah, God's.
God told me to pick two today.
- You picked two, okay, Panera Bread.
- Oh my God, we should go to Panera Bread after this.
- As a hippie, Panera Bread's probably
my favorite fucking place in the world.
- Yeah, it's our Panera Bread business lunch after.
- I'm down.
Alright, here, okay guys, let's go.
Guided meditation number one.
(bell rings)
Step one, close your eyes and take a few slow,
deep breaths and allow your mind to clear.
Take a moment to go inside yourself and totally relax.
- By the way, sorry to interrupt.
I would like to say if you're listening at home,
you should be closing your eyes.
- Oh, 100%.
- If you're driving or if you're at work.
- Just close your eyes right now.
- You can do it.
- Just say you're blinking a long time if anyone gets--
- My eyes are closed and I'm totally relaxed.
- Say you're having a seizure.
- Get ready for step two, y'all.
Step two.
After a few minutes, which we're gonna skip that,
we're just gonna go straight to it.
Imagine a plate full of the most putrid, rotting fish,
maggots, or anything similar
that is completely repulsive to you.
So what are you guys imagining?
Anything revolting to you?
Come on, just tell what's repulsive to you guys.
- What's repulsive to me?
- Throw it out, what are you picturing here?
- Lettuce and tomato.
- What about you, Pat?
- Yeah, I was picturing like a bunch of shrimp.
- Lettuce, just lettuce and tomato
from just top of a sandwich,
and I have to let it off.
- Create a strong picture in your mind's eye
and connect it with the revolting smell of the fish.
- Or the lettuce and tomato, or the shrimp.
- Oh God, the lettuce and tomato.
- Hold back from gagging,
but make this image very real.
- I picked my favorite food, though.
I just hold, it said, specifically said completely repulsive to you, so you're ruining the meditation.
Yeah, okay, let me restart.
Not content to ruin your own meditation, you have to ruin mine.
Mm.
Now let's move to step three, guys.
Step three.
Now, focus on the chocolate that you would like to eradicate from your diet and mix it
up with the rotting fish.
Imagine the putrid fish inside a glass of biscuits, giving off a disgusting smell.
Be creative with this part of the technique.
The more vivid you can make this image, the more powerful it will be.
After you have fully absorbed the image, allow your mind to become blank.
Take a few slow breaths, slowly count to three, and open your eyes.
So what I've done here is against you guys' will, you will no longer be able to eat chocolate.
Or I can eat chocolate right now.
You have been completely, if you try to eat chocolate at all, you will throw up.
I'm overcoming.
Everybody who's listening to this right now and followed those instructions will no longer
be able to ever eat chocolate again.
- I already can't eat chocolate, my teeth are broken.
- And that seals it. - I agree, now you sealed it.
- What are you saying about me and Pat's weights
that you think that we should be eating chocolate anymore?
- It's not about you, it's about the thousands
of people listening to this.
- Thousands of fatties?
- All of their weights.
I just have a feeling they've been eating
a little too much chocolate.
- How about this, put down the chocolate bar,
pick up the fuckin' handgun and put it in your mouth
instead and kill yourself.
- Pick up the, put down the chocolate bar,
pick up the protein shake.
- Yep.
- And throw it at a leftoid somewhere on the street
is protesting.
- Yes, we don't like leftoids, we're rightoids.
- We're basically right-wing hippies.
- Yeah, this is a very common kind of person.
- But if anyone out there is suffering
from chocolate addiction, congratulations.
I've cured you.
If anyone out there is not suffering from this, I'm sorry.
But sometimes you have to play the cards you're given.
- Yep.
- You're free of chocolate forever.
- Sorry, chocoholics.
- You know a lot of rehabs won't treat chocoholism.
- I've heard that.
- I've tried, trust me.
- Because it doesn't make any sense.
- I was really--
- I tried to go in for take fives.
- Really?
- I was really glad to find this guided meditation
for curing chocolate addiction
because there was one guided meditation
that's kind of my white whale, my holy grail.
You can get the script on this website,
but it costs $15 and I came so close
to downloading this PDF for $15.
- Why didn't you just do it?
- That's $15.
- Yeah, but it's a business write-off.
- I should have done it, but I didn't,
but it was a--
- Hey, when's your birthday?
- Well, here's the other thing.
- July 4th?
- Here's the other thing,
is that you could also order the MP3 version of it,
and the MP3 version was like 40 minutes long,
so I was like, okay, but the script that I wanted,
the thing that cost $15,
was a hypnosis script that cures addiction to music.
(laughing)
- I need that.
I am actually addicted to music.
I have so many songs that are stuck in my head.
♪ I'm good, yeah, I'm feeling all right ♪
♪ And baby, I'ma have the best freakin' night of my life ♪
♪ And wherever it takes, yeah, I'm down for the ride ♪
♪ Baby, don't you know I'm good, yeah, I'm feeling all right ♪
See, I'm a music addict, and I need fucking help.
Are you a rexar?
I'm a total music addict.
I'm a reptar, rexar.
Rexar?
I'm a rexar.
Big BeyBey, rexar fan.
BeyBey, rexar.
You have to be, she's the most talented musician
since fuckin' Steve Martin.
Yeah.
Yeah, King Tut.
I was addicted to that song. Me too. She's married to Taika Waititi. What'd you say like that?
Taika Waititi. You can't you can't use the the wisdom tooth as an excuse for
that one. What about that? What about what I said was weird? Taika Waititi.
What's weird about that? Not a good way to pronounce that name. How is that not a good way to pronounce his name?
I guess not bad. It's not his name. His name is Taika Waititi. Why are you saying it like that?
Say it like what? All I'm saying is "Takowatiti."
"Taiko-watiti."
It's not being pronounced weird.
It is.
You're listening on headphones right now. It probably sounds so...
It sounds weirder.
It doesn't. I don't know what's going on today.
Say it again. "Takowatiti."
Okay, it's the same, actually, on both.
Yeah? Okay.
Both sounds bad.
I think it might be a problem with you guys. Maybe we need a meditation to clean your ears.
I'd like to see what that guy does in the shadows old taiko a titty. Yeah, yeah, but he's fucking a
raping a kid
Ragnarok
Yep, that would be my personal Ragnarok is if they ever caught taiko a titty doing anything like that
He just seems like that kind of guy
You know, you know what? I did see him in recently. What's that music video Jeremy Renner main attraction. He's in there
Oh, he is in that. Well, you know
- Oh, we should have seen that coming from Taika Waititi,
'cause didn't he make that movie with Thor
that was called Thor Love and Under?
- Yes, Love and Under 18.
- Wasn't that the name of the movie?
- They made it, it was like the if in If I Did It
on the cover of the O.J. book.
It was just really, really small.
- Oh, it's like a Marvel what if.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Okay.
Oh, he was doing one of those.
- Yeah. - Great.
What kind of colors do you guys like?
I like yellow.
Yeah, for some reason.
I also like blue.
Yeah, I like red and blue and yellow and pink and green
Patrick's taking the just you guys like rolling news pretty
bad.
He's dressed up like one of his famous characters.
Yeah, dressed up exactly like Morty.
Yeah.
No one was new characters.
What's his new character?
Oh, never mind.
Somebody posted a clip of Justin Roiland's old podcast or something, and it's so funny
to me that he's a voice actor, but that's also just his voice.
So he's going to be in court and he's just going to sound like that.
It's not like a thing he turns off and on.
That's just literally exactly what he sounds like.
He just is his voice.
Do you see that photo that people were trying to...
was like all three voice actors from the show Fish Hooks have all gone down. It
was like Justin Roiland what he did, Kyle Massey sent pictures to an underage girl
and then the third one is like this woman has done cocaine. The best line in
all those texts that Justin Roiland sent was "I'm Atlanta drunk." I'm Atlanta drunk.
- I'm a little drunk.
- All right, I have one more meditation
to share with you guys.
- Let me see, she that.
- Yeah, we're gonna she it.
So let's go ahead and get this up here.
Okay, perfect.
I'm gonna go ahead and gong us in.
- Wow, it really is cleansing.
- All right, let's begin.
- I've completely forgotten about fucking
Justin Roiland saying jailbait now.
need to cleanse him from our minds. We're beyond him. Okay, do I need a gong again?
I just read somebody a note that said that every one of his texts sounds like he's talking like Stimpy.
Or Ren from Ren and Stimpy. A little bit. "I am Atlanta drunk!"
So I haven't been able to... I read that this morning, I haven't been able to stop thinking
about it. Yeah, that's an accusation. Yeah, more like Justin roiling massive black smoke and sin
- Emanating from hell.
- That's right.
- Like rolling up to the prison.
- Yeah, probably rolling up to the joint.
- We're gonna do another cleanse.
We're gonna get rid of this brimstone.
- Yeah, let's get rid of Justin Roiland.
(bell dings)
- He's gone.
- And he's been disappeared.
- He's gone, he vanished.
All right, let's begin.
- Okay.
- Close your eyes.
I want you to take a deep breath in
and hold it for 10 counts.
- Justin Roiland's getting 10 counts, sorry.
- And if you guys wanna look at the beautiful visuals
of
heart beat slow down to a nice steady rhythm. But we're not going to zero, folks. Keep the
hearts beating. Just slow it down. Yeah, that's perfect. That's nice. Keep breathing deeply
and with every inhale I want you to gather up some of the tension and stress in your
body. Gather it in your lungs and then exhale it out. And this one, this is a meditation
I found on YouTube. I took the transcript. I abridged it a little bit because it was
an hour long. We're going to keep moving on here. Feel your body relax and unwind. And
Look at this pretty picture.
Wouldn't you like to be sitting here on those rocks?
- I wish I was one inch.
- Wouldn't you want to climb up that pipe?
- Yeah, and I wish I was one inch big.
- Yeah, well that's big, probably big.
And as the silence in your mind grows,
as the emptiness expands and consumes you,
you feel your mind transforming into a total abyss,
deep, dark, empty, bottomless.
The abyss lets you realize that my words are your truth.
My words are your reality.
Inside your mind there is a monster, a beast,
an entity of darkest desires, urges, and hungering lusts.
- And are these the beasts I'm supposed to be picturing?
- These are some visuals, you know?
- There's two goose or geese, rather.
- They're just gooses, folks.
- Okay.
- Only the most powerful, only the gods and alphas among us
can be strong enough to let that beast out
and use it to their advantage.
It'll make you unrecognizable. Good, bad, it doesn't matter. You'll be powerful, alpha,
dominant without equal, surpassing gods and becoming monstrous.
I can feel myself growing a tentacle.
Everyone else's but prey are slaves in the eyes of a monster. You know you want it.
I don't want a slave.
You know you want it.
I do not want a slave.
My words are your reality. You are in an abyss in your mind.
Don't, okay, here's what I'll say.
You know you want it.
I'm in a hypnotic state.
I want, I think that everyone is a slave, but I don't like it.
You want prey.
I like prey.
And slaves.
I don't want slaves.
Stop trying to make me say it.
You know you want it.
I'm going to use my strength.
You just said I want slaves.
Stop.
I did not say I want slaves.
That was a seal.
No, you can't.
You just said it again.
Wait, doesn't that end your whole meditation?
No, but it just seals it.
I'm going to hit it from the back one time.
You're knocking on the candle.
I don't want slaves.
I want the opposite of a slave.
I want to be a white slave.
Okay, we're unsealing that. We're going to go to the back to unseal it.
And we're moving forward.
Thick, wide bull's neck leading down to traps that rise up like mountains of dark iron.
Strong muscle, broad shoulders that strain against the confines of its cage.
Delt swelling and cut like boulders into its flesh.
The skin stretching and breaking over them, indicating just how much this monstrous being has grown during the time you've kept it locked away.
Do I have any idea what this is?
time you've kept it locked away.
Do I have that in me?
And look at these beautiful visuals behind these words.
Well, I can't see you fucking jack shit, asshole.
I can see it.
You're taunting me with visuals.
You know I love visuals.
Arms rippling with muscular fibers flexing at the slightest
movement. Biceps, big peaked gargantuan globes of muscles
with pulsating veins coursing with that thick black corruption.
Triceps that flare out from the arm, each striation and muscular
fiber apparent under the skin, pure mass and muscle and grotesque size.
Nice, I'm seeing it all.
You're seeing it all.
Minus the slaves.
Drink it in.
I'm drinking.
You want the slaves.
All of the body stuff in.
The slaves are not existent though.
You know you want it.
Slavery doesn't exist.
The monster almost seems to flex for you, flaunting its perfection.
He's doing it for me, but he's not my slave.
Giving you a show, enticing you more and more.
Look at its forearms laced with layers of vascular tight muscle.
You're visualizing this, Patrick?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm trying to.
Yeah, so just keep pace here.
Let's visualize this together.
You can't take your eyes off it.
They continue to track down to those massive legs, sculpted like pillars of marble, bulging and bursting with tightly packed musculature.
I love that.
Massive quads and calves and an ass as hard and firm as a globe of iron.
- And his asshole.
- Built and tightly coiled with that power
to crush adversaries.
- With his ass.
- He crushes them.
- You want the prey.
- But this is inside me.
- You want the slaves.
- No, not the slaves.
Get rid of the slaves.
- To have worthless slaves,
people unwilling to embrace the monster inside of them,
worship and beg for mercy before it.
- I don't want worthless slaves.
- The whole body of a monster is built for power.
- I don't like this meditation anymore.
I wanna skip.
- I'll say all my slaves,
if I have them, are worth something.
- Is not the--
Let him become you and let yourself become him.
Let him take control and take control
of that monstrous form yourself.
Take control, Caleb.
- I'm getting control, but I'm controlling the opposite,
or the slaves are not under my control.
- Breathe him in, drink him down.
- There's no slaves.
- Feel him in your heartbeat, your pulse,
the slow building arousal until everything just breaks
and you are now a monster.
(laughing)
- Okay, wow, that was, I'm still kind of in the world
of this right now.
I will say, yeah, so don't seal it until,
I'd like to really quickly, before you seal it, say,
I have no desire, I never have, I never will have a desire
to get a slave in my entire life.
- Me neither. - A monster.
- I'm gonna say ditto.
- Go ahead and seal that. - A monster.
(bell dings)
- All right, so that was actually, again,
90% really fucking good.
Really, really good stuff.
Thank you. Well, I put this meme together for us. That's a good one. That is a good
one. I did that on image flip. I'll tell you something. And I'm going to go ahead
and seal that meme really good. Yeah, go ahead and seal that. Very few things have
had more of an impact. Like get it? I get it. Then, then this episode today,
basically kind of entering a new realm. I mean, yeah, an impact not on us, I want
to be clear, but on the world. This is like, Let It Be. Let it be, let it be,
♪ Let it be, let it be, let it be ♪
- That song, there will be an answer.
Let it be, let it be, yeah.
- Let's get a harmony in.
Vocal harmony so that we have,
it's I think as you just say let it be.
- Let it be.
♪ Let it be ♪
- And that represents the harmony that's now in the world.
- There's so much harmony in the world now.
- And Patrick, I would like to quickly,
you know that minions are evil.
- They're evil.
- They serve-- - Canonically evil.
- Dark masters.
- Look, I read the schedule wrong.
That's all I can say.
- Okay, all right.
- Just don't let it happen again, I guess.
- And they did not serve, and the minions,
we've talked about this multiple times.
- The minions served Hitler.
- They did not serve-- - It's a Funny or Die exclusive.
The story was broken to funny or die.
Oh my god, if it's funny or die, you know it's gotta be true.
Alright, peace be with you.
And the shareholder meeting this month will be on the 27th I believe.
Oh yeah, the 27th and I'm in Rosemont, Illinois on the weekend of the, this upcoming weekend.
This weekend with Adam Friedland, I'm opening for him.
On the 31st.
The zanies, crazy zanies.
On the 31st I will be performing at Singles Motel, hosted by Nick Nanny, Claro Cain, and
Weston Haney.
Eric Rayhill is going to be there in a few days.
Don't plug shows in the city.
Shut the fuck up.
Shut up.
Let me plug my thing for God's sake.
That's a show.
Why wouldn't I plug that?
On February 14th I will be performing in my living room.
I will be doing "I Love You" for my girlfriend.
I'll stand on the couch.
Can we hear the song?
It was the song.
I love you, I love you, I love you!
Happy Valentine's Day!
I love you!
I decided I'll be there too.
On the 31st at Littlefield if you're in Brooklyn.
Tickets are $500.
If you're in Rosemont, Illinois.
You know...
Bye.
[Music]
(eerie music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]