*wind*
It's time to leave the office.
Oh wait, let's go home.
It's completely frozen shut.
What the hell? It's like an icy tundra out there.
Yeah, that almost means what?
It means that we can't even get out of the door.
We're snowed in!
Doesn't matter to me.
I don't give a shit.
And it's my birthday in six months.
*Intro*
Okay
*Silence*
*Mimics the sound of a car*
Why are you guys just sitting there completely still?
Because I didn't know we started yet. You waited for you to press that button.
You guys always start it instantly.
No. Whenever we start. We're gonna restart right now.
We're gonna re- reset.
*Mimics the sound of a car*
Oh, fuck it's cold in here.
Are you silently chattering your teeth?
That's not silent.
Wait, hold on.
I can hear that shit from here.
We're hearing a little bit of that.
I can hear that from here.
Here's a question you motherfucker.
You island motherfucker.
How come you don't have a puffer jacket on
if it's so damn cold?
This is what you wear when it's cold.
I got you.
I see all these guys flying around the ice wearing this.
Oh, that's a good point.
Yeah, that's a good point, yeah.
That's why Kevin Smith always wears one.
This is not Halloween.
Yeah, it is.
That's the Christmas creep.
That is not a Christmas creep.
There's no such thing as the Christmas creep.
Well, he's right there, so what do you mean there's no such thing?
Also, here's a question.
If there's such a Christmas creep going around,
name three of his attributes.
Skeletal.
Okay.
Hooded.
That sounds right.
Yeah, that sounds pretty good.
Upon a jersey.
Skeletal, hooded, and upon a jersey?
Yeah.
That last one doesn't count.
He's on your jersey.
He doesn't live--
Oh my God, it's true.
I was right.
His third attribute was completely correct.
Sometimes I hate--
Now we'll have to find out about the first two, I guess.
I hate how smart you are.
It pisses me off. It makes it so hard to argue with you.
I'm running circles around you guys.
Christmas circles.
He's 50 steps ahead.
I hate Christmas circles.
I would say a Christmas circle doesn't exist, but I know god damn well you're going to prove it to me.
You're going to pull all these Christmas circles out of your ass.
What do you mean you don't hang Christmas circles on your tree every year?
I'm just scooting on you.
Yeah, you always, whenever we cut to you, you're always way farther than us.
You're on your own little island.
Look at you.
There's because this thing, I can't move any further than this.
move any further than this.
- Oh my God.
- This is the closest I can move.
- It's almost like turning my old desk
into the table we use for the podcast
was kind of a bad idea.
- What's bad about it?
It works fine.
What, I can't sit where I'm sitting?
- Hey.
- I think we just need to get a little bit closer as friends.
- I think that we learned something,
which is that you think that an ornament
is called a Christmas circle.
- No, it's a wreath.
- An ornament?
- A wreath is a Christmas circle.
- You don't put a wreath on a tree.
- You put a wreath on a tree.
- Why would you put--
I said dozens too!
You're like dozens of wreaths on your tree!
I got my tree yesterday.
I went out right before it got this cold and we got all snowed in.
The last thing I did was I got a Christmas tree.
We have a little fake light up tree.
A small fake one.
Did you get a real one?
You can't get one? Yeah you can.
You can get one.
No Moe, I woke up at 3 in the morning last night because Moe had the zoomies.
No, that means you can't get a tree.
He will topple that shit.
He'd be too tired to take care of it.
He weighs less than a pound. He can't topple a tree.
He will topple anything in the house.
He knocked over my flowers.
Did he knock you over yet? Flowers are a lot
easier to knock over.
Flowers are like a baby tree.
Has he knocked over your refrigerator yet?
No. You know what he did do?
Last night
he bit me in my sleep.
He's a biter. I don't know why he bites me.
Probably because he's a cat.
because of that. He's just like his owner, he's a buyer. He steals rapidly. Oh he does.
Yeah I forgot about that, that he did that. Yeah, the other day he was, we were
walking on the train, we were walking on the train, yeah, and he said, and he, we were
subway surfing, we were doing like this, we were walking on top of the train, and he looked at me and he said, "Ask Beavis, I get nothing but head."
And I was like, oh that's a pretty clever little line. Yeah. Go home, big L. Yeah.
93 freestyle. He took a big O. I said dead in the middle of little did we know the
brittle submittalmen didn't do diddly. Yeah and he said all that crap and I said
that was great Pat. No it turns out he ripped that off some Spaniards. Yeah.
What? Yeah big fat Joe and big fat pun. Big fat pun. Couple of Spaniard rappers.
Only one big fat guy I care about in this season. Who's that? Santa. Mr.
December. Santa Claus himself. Oh well I was right. I thought you were talking about Mr.
Mr. December from the fireman calendar I have.
No, I call Sir DeClause Mr. December.
Why?
Because he comes around in December and he's a boy.
I would say that Christ would be much more Mr. December.
No, Christ is Mr. Worldwide.
Master December, I like that more than Mr. Worldwide.
Mr. Worldwide already has it, there's already a guy who does that.
That's true.
I like that your hat is backwards today.
I like that your hat is non-existent today.
Up top.
Down low.
I've decided to show off my Norwood 3.
Let's get a punch in on this.
Like North Pole 3.
Damn.
See that?
This is the pole right here.
And it goes like, "Ooooh."
Yep.
I've got three years with this left.
I've got three years with the front of my hair.
That's what I thought one year ago.
Yeah.
You're done.
I'm not done.
You're fucking done.
I'm going to be fine.
You're done.
No, you will die.
Yeah?
Yeah, one day.
Well, I don't have the thingy.
I don't have the...
The spot?
you're getting a little spot it's not that big though it's not that big yeah
yeah a little it's not big it's not you get a spray you are you do you have a
bald spot right here though yeah and I would say you have some like your ears
have almost no hair on them yeah and like all right cameras doing the blurry thing
again just shut up yeah your neck has basically nothing there's no hair over
You know where I do grow hair is right here.
You don't grow hair, any hair on my head.
Oh, you do grow hair there.
I grow hair right under my eyeballs.
That's so crazy to have a beard that goes up to your eyes.
And then it goes up there, but then this,
this doesn't connect to my mustache.
Yes it does.
So all the hair, no, no, no, you saw when I,
on Saturday I sent you guys the picture.
It clearly does.
It was the K-Night Live thing, it was like the,
like right there, there was just a patch that was,
oh not this side, it's this side, this side.
There's hair all over your face.
You're crazy. There's proof of this.
There's proof right in front of me that it is dog hair on your face.
Have you ever thought about growing out a big beard? Yeah. Have you ever done anything close to that?
You used to have a little bit of a beard. Yeah, I had a beard when we first started hanging out.
Yeah, but it was more chin strappy I feel like than it would grow now.
It had like a perfect chin strap in my head. You were misremembering a lot of things.
No, I think I remember a lot of things. One thing, and I think I remember it okay.
up photos of me. Yeah you used to look like this. I remember you used to look like this.
Patrick Doran, Family Tree. Man you look wide here in this shot. I know and I'm blurry.
Yeah. Because we never figured out the... You need to learn to keep your mouth shut.
You are an awful radio personality. That's a rude thing for me to say but I'm saying
it. I can't believe you've been doing this so long and you just never got any better.
No. Maybe you got worse actually. Well it's worse now that we got video because now all
I can see is that the fucking camera is blurry as shit. Well that's because it's fucking frozen
over because we're fucking locked and snowed in here which we barely even
mentioned so far but we've been trapped in here for a week what's your worst
favorite least favorite part of being completely trapped in an underground
bunker with your friends probably that it's snowing in 53 degrees the fact that
it's 53 degrees outside and it's still not melting the doors are fucking frozen
shut we can't get out of here it sucks ass dude there's snow all over the set I
don't know if people can see this yeah oh my god there's snow I bet you guys
I mean, it's so cold to touch
Don't touch it man. You don't want to touch that
And I just realized what that it's snow it's snow
Did I what don't worry about what it is
What Patrick did I take the inside of a couple of adult diapers that we have laying around the office and turn the?
filling into snow
Yes, maybe I thought it wasn't actually snowing in here
And I wanted to maybe sell the fact that there was some snow around the office
Then yeah, that'd be a fucking good idea, and maybe I should work for Martin Scorsese in Hollywood, but you should I
Was looking at it, and I was like oh this looks like it would be crunchy, but no it's diaper inards
No, you're a diaper nerd you're the diaper nerd. I don't like nerd in diaper no
Diaper innards. Oh, yeah, well you guys started making me wear those diapers that we had cuz we're snowed in you guys are sick of my
Farts well, that's the worst part
For the toilet completely froze solid yeah, so you just been taking craps
It just lay on top of a little bugs playing hockey on the toilet just discuss with our craps with our crap
Pucks here's the thing about bugs man. Why do you want to eat?
Why do you want to eat you saying it wow all right? I'll say I'll go in on bugs for a minute
Hey flies, why do you want to eat fucking shit?
Mm-hmm.
What are you--
Talk that talk.
That's nasty.
Yeah.
That's disgusting.
Hey cockroaches, you're nasty.
Kill yourselves.
Hey cockroaches, what's that first part of your name all about?
Kind of sus.
And what's that second part?
What are you, a bug?
Yeah, because you smoke penises.
What?
Cockro-- like a roach.
Oh, like the roach.
Yeah, the roach that you eat.
Oh.
Yeah.
Like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You just puff, puff, pass.
where I don't smoke it, but I eat it like 10 minutes
before I fall asleep.
So I'm not living while I'm high at all.
I only am high while I'm in my dream.
And last night I had a dream that I had a pet mouse.
- Oh. - Oh.
- Named Tay-Tay.
(laughing)
And Tay-Tay got lost.
- You could make that a reality at any point.
- Tay-Tay got lost.
- Tay-Tay is such a good name for a pet mouse.
And Tay Tay got lost last night.
That is really good.
And so the best part of the weed thing--
I want to get an office mouse now.
The best part about doing weed like this is that you get awful dreams like this, where Tay Tay gets lost.
And then I wake up from this very disorienting dream, and I wake up and I'm at the highest I've ever been in my entire life, to go piss.
And I go piss, and I'm sitting there and I'm like, I wonder if I'll ever see fucking Tay Tay again.
And then I go back to sleep, and he's gone.
Yeah.
That sucks.
It's like he never existed.
Yeah.
He was hanging out with my dog in this dream,
and they were both in a blanket fort.
[LAUGHTER]
That's nice.
He was in a blanket fort.
And I loved him so much, and I'll never see him again.
I think you have to get a pet rat now.
That is so-- dreams are so cruel, man.
Tay-tay.
Dreams are so fucking cruel.
I really, really want you to get a pet rat now.
A mouse.
Whatever.
Tay-tay.
They're the same thing.
[LAUGHTER]
How awful is it that in dreams you can you can in your brain conjure up something that you love more than anything?
Yeah, I love Taytay more than I love my fucking mom or my dad. I loved Taytay
You could feed I loved it
And I felt like I felt like I'd lost my child in an amusement park when he was lost in the blanket fort and I was
Started getting scared lost in the blanket. He was in the blanket fort and then I opened up the blanket fort
I said surprise Taytay. It's time to sing your song and he was
He's fucking gone dude. He was gone
I didn't get to the point where I heard the song in the dream
But I knew that he had a special song that I would sing on with to make him go to bed
So the Taytay saga basically completely ended with me opening up the blanket fort where the fuck's Taytay my pet mouse
He's nowhere. I see my dog
And then I yeah, and then I and then I look her oh, this was the worst part
I look around and I'm like where the fuck is Taytay
where's my baby and I look around and there's a cat roaming. No! So the last feeling I have
It wasn't a little black and white cat was it? It was actually. The last feeling that I have in my dream, the last
thing I had before I woke up and I had to come into work now, right I was
trapped in here I mean, is that my last feeling was that I think that Tay Tay, my
my pet mouse I've had my entire life, is 25 years old, that my pet mouse it was
eaten viciously by a cat. A black and white cat. A black and white cat. Like Moe. Yeah, maybe.
It was a bigger cat. Most cats are black and white. Was he big, but
he was big in the way that his stomach was really big and was shaped like a
mouse? I don't think eating a mouse would make your stomach all that big.
Tay Tay was very small. Well, a cat could be small enough that his stomach was very, very
small. What are you doing? Guys, it's time to be real. Oh, I knew one day we'd
come to this. I think you're gonna have to miss this one.
Yeah? Or you have to do it right now. He's already taking it.
He's already taking it. Wow, he doesn't even want me in it.
Wow. And you don't get to retake that. No, no, no, no, no.
See? He's gonna punch in on this. Okay, let's not.
That's awful. That was a bad one. And also you ruined my Tay-Tay.
Yeah, I'm hungry as fuck and I'm gonna eat Patrick. That's fine.
That's fine.
Why would you eat Patrick?
Because he was on B-Real.
True.
Yeah.
I'd like to-
I really have- that's been the first thing-
When I get angry at somebody or something annoys me,
Yeah.
Recently, the first thought in my head is, "I'm going to eat you."
Did you ever get mad at a mouse?
Yeah, named Tay Tay.
Not yet.
Is that a weird name to have in my head?
No.
Tay Tay?
You guys made me feel really self-conscious about my mouse.
What? No, we didn't.
Why are you self-conscious about the mouse?
We were smiling.
I'm just kind of, I don't know.
It was just weird.
I think what you should do is make that a reality.
I don't want--
I think that you should make--
Dude, you know how fucked up it would be for me to feel--
to be like, OK, well, I had this mouse that I loved in my dream.
His name was Teytey.
I need to meet him in real life.
And then try to find a mouse that fits the personality
that I actually fucking--
What was his personality like?
He was playful.
He was a little bit mischievous, right?
Yeah, that would be really hard to find a mouse.
- In a mouse.
- That's probably one of the rarest personality traits.
- He loved cheese.
- A mischievous mouse.
- He loved cheese, he loved snacks.
- Wait, can you describe what his ears looked like?
- Yeah, what did he look like?
- Was this a realistic mouse?
- They were perfect.
They were like little pink,
just like triangles kind of that came off his head.
- Yeah, triangle ears.
- He had a little--
- Or a little like--
- A polygonal mouse.
Just like a--
- He had eight legs.
(laughing)
- What the fuck are you,
why are you debugging an urban dictionary right now, Juvio?
- I was trying to hack urban dictionary.
- Oh, he was trying to, you ruined his bit.
He was gonna probably cut to that.
- I'm gonna cut to him.
- Whoa, we're gonna cut up Patrick and maybe his body.
- Have a plate of--
- Why do you have so much stuff going on recently?
Just, you're like a fucking fidget spinner, man.
- Yeah, I didn't take my Adderall today, so I'm crazy.
And I also took my crazy stuff.
- What's this?
- What the fuck?
- What the fuck is that?
It's my crazy spray.
I've talked about it before, I've been doing that.
You've been using this?
Yeah.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Jesus Christ, bro.
This is a cowboy bebop drug.
You're gonna die.
No, I won't.
You're gonna turn into the fucking thing.
You just casually sprayed it in your mouth?
You're gonna be the fly, dude.
Look at how much good stuff is in there.
Niacin.
Nothing that sprays in your mouth is good.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna read this. I need to read this.
- What the? - Taste five mists,
spray all day.
Oh, this is batch number OB1B.
So you know it's good, that was a good batch.
- So what is in this?
It's caffeine? - Uh-huh.
- It's apple?
- And it tastes terrible.
- What are you doing this?
Why are you doing this, man?
- I just didn't have enough pizzazz.
- This is...
- What the, something is seriously just wrong.
- Yeah, I need to see this again.
- But it's got electrolytes in it, too.
is that it doesn't look like i had to do the same a caffeine no it's because it's
all of us all this is you also you didn't do enough that the serving sizes
ten minutes yet but i'm only doing to get out of the island is
contract yet
go ahead
all as all that's so awful i told you it's bad it's my mouth
yeah i told you it's really bad why do you do that because it has energy
It is. It is actually Mad Max. And you're not supposed to
see a ring or the bottle doing the chrome thing.
God, that is all. That's a big problem. People are always like
I'm going for three bottles of the energy.
Three bottles of 24 milligrams of caffeine per what spray per
spray per spray. And it wants you to 10. That's not true.
You can't handle think about it. Milligrams in a spray. Think
about it. Per spray. That's the same as like one Red Bull.
No, it's not. It's close. 24. I think five sprays is close to one Red Bull, right?
Because a Red Bull is 80 milligrams of caffeine.
Well, the serving size is 10.
So 24 times 10, that's 240.
It's 24 per spray.
And that's the same as...
Good stuff.
That's the same as a Rockstar Zero.
Well, here, regardless of that being a cyberpunk thing that will turn you into a gray sludge.
Yeah, I'm going to get cancer.
You need to ration it out because we're snowed in and you're gonna waste it all.
And that's gonna be our last food.
No, I'm not gonna waste it.
And what I'm gonna tell you is...
I'll dilute it with water.
It sounds like maybe I'm warning you for your own sake.
For like, "Okay, we're gonna run out of food."
But mostly because that's the last food we have in there and once you run out of that,
we're eating you.
Oh, yeah.
And also, this is maybe for your own safety.
For our sake, please stop putting sprays and bad chemicals in your body that would make
your meat taste rancid.
drink out of plastic cups or anything. Nothing that could put any...
Any microplastics, no sorts of any bees.
No, that's most of my food and my sex.
With hose?
Yes.
Mysterious hose?
Oh, I thought you said a hose.
Mysterious back alley hose?
I've been putting my penis in the hose.
Can you get...
That's not good either.
The hose that iced us in?
There's particulates.
You know the hose that we left running and now there's all that ice?
I do remember that.
Basically filled up both of the basement doors.
It sprayed hot water is basically like putting my penis on the jet in a hot tub, but then it went cold
Yeah, yeah went to the bath house. It's like fucking a mechanical worm. How'd you like that?
Oh, it was great, but I did you get into the cold water. Yeah. Yeah, it's good, right?
Oh, you're the best crap out of me. I thought my
Heart was gonna stop. Yeah. No, it can't if it's too cold if it's which that's not that cold
But if it's really really cold, I can give you a heart attack. Yeah. Yeah, I like dropped it
I I went in I have a dunk head under no oh
I was scared of getting a heart attack, but it's like to look at your brain attack
I already put energy mist in my body. I think that's something like that. That's why no
That's why you need to do stuff. That's good for you to counteract all this awful shit. You do I've been drinking beet juice
I don't think that's great beet juice and ginger nothing that really does much well tell that to dr. Sebi I
I think you died. Tell that to my doctor, Dr. Sebi.
That's your family doctor? That's your general practitioner?
A different guy. He's white.
Oh, okay.
He's a white doctor.
Named Sebi.
Yeah.
Okay. Alright, that's fine.
Well, his name is Sebastian.
I've been thinking...
His name is Dr. Sebastian.
Sebastian.
Sebastian Goldman.
I've been thinking recently that maybe I have cancer because my dog has been really, really
trying to sniff my balls all the time. And I wasn't thinking about it that much, and then
and then I found out that dogs sometimes can smell cancer in somebody's body.
You know what else dogs can react to that humans don't?
Is ghosts.
That's why your paws are probably haunted.
By who?
I've seen what Phil does though.
The ghost of your damn...
Balls?
That sucked.
No.
Give me a handshake.
It's a handshake.
It's not a bump.
I'm not bumping the mic.
I'm not giving you a fist bump.
I think you two have brain freeze.
No, and me I had way too much coffee this morning. Yeah, I'm gonna. I'm in a prison. Yeah. Yeah, you wait
I needed a little I'm in a bone cage. You should try this energy mist man. I don't I feel fucking in braiseable here
You could also you could try one of these
What's that a camel blue this thing can't smoke that inside these are?
Ever since we've been doing video I've got I have two sponsors now wait are we allowed to do this on YouTube actually three cigarettes
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Oh, we have, oh, we hate those.
I hate that crap.
I have, the third sponsor is Ballistics, and I've been doing this whole episode.
I'm gonna go ballistic on you if you don't fucking stop taking shit out of your pockets.
Okay.
And talk about something funny like football.
This is funny.
She would never do that.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg would never do that.
That's why she died.
All right, well that, I actually-
That's a little of the edgy humor we're known for.
We need to be masking up when we record.
That's a good point.
Yeah, that's really good.
to tell you guys before we got snowed in.
I have COVID.
- That'd be fine.
You have COVID?
- I guess it doesn't matter
'cause it's not like we can leave.
- It's getting to that time of year
where every year, the last couple of years,
I've been getting to this time of year,
I'm like, oh man, I hope I get it.
- Yeah.
- I'm probably about to get it.
I bet you I'll have it tomorrow.
- Again?
- I'll bet you a thousand dollars I have it tomorrow.
- Remember that one time we all recorded together
and you're like, no, it's just my allergies.
- It was my allergies and then it turned into COVID.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- I don't remember if that's where I got it
or if I got it somewhere else.
- No, I think you did get it from there.
- I was the only one who didn't get it.
So I think that I maybe gave it to you.
- Yeah, I think 100%.
I think I got it in Seattle from one of you guys.
- Yeah.
- Or from one of our disgusting fans.
- Or from all of those goth clubs we were going to.
- No, they don't have COVID in goth.
- Yeah, no, they scare it away.
- Yeah.
- They don't have COVID, but they have Covina,
who is a woman who walks around.
They have Corvid, who's a guy dressed like a crow.
Yeah.
True.
Pretty scary.
That was the layup there.
God damn it.
I laid it up with Corvid.
You laid up that Corvid.
Corvid was the obvious one.
That's an easy ass layup.
Yeah.
Hopefully you do have COVID, because I think your flesh will taste kind of exquisite in
a new way.
It'd be like dry-aged.
A different flavor.
I really, I thought, okay, the other day I left a steak in my fridge for eight days straight,
and it turned black.
So listen, so I didn't eat it, but I did cut part of it to see if maybe the inside was
good.
Yeah.
It wasn't, but I was thinking maybe I probably could have eaten that and it would have tasted
kind of dry-aged.
No.
Are you just the fun police?
You don't know, because you aren't doing anything that Guga does in that situation.
So what's the difference between leaving it in there in a bag versus leaving it next to
an open bowl of yogurt?
The bag.
The bag is a membrane.
- You guys are learning to cook from Guga.
I'm learning to cook stuff from Google.
Finding recipes on epicurious.com.
- I'm going on Google and I'm looking up Guga Foods.
(laughing)
'Cause I don't know how to use a YouTube search bar.
- YouTube is owned by Google.
- I really wanna eat a dry aged steak, I've never had one.
- Me neither. - Let's do it.
- I really wanna do it.
- Do they age it in a special situation
like they do with alcohols?
- They put it into a secrets bag
and then they put it into a degree controller
that controls how much, how--
- Do you know how they do things like--
- A fridge.
- You know how they do stuff,
you know how they do stuff like with whiskey and stuff
where like this was aged in like a haunted mansion.
- Yeah.
- Do they do stuff like that with steak?
- It's like that, but--
- But I mean, can you get a steak that it's like,
oh, like this is aged in a castle.
- I do, it is awesome that there's so much cheap whiskey
that's like, we age this in a barrel
that used to have barbecue sauce in it.
Doesn't that sound like it's worth $40?
That's so cool, man.
It is awesome.
Yeah. We put out a cigarette in this whiskey, and you're tasting it, and you're like, "Oh, yeah."
I can taste the cigarette.
I can taste that.
I'm starting a whiskey brand, and my whiskey is going to be aged on a roller coaster.
Oh, wow. That's good.
It's the most fun brand.
It's called Funtime Whiskey.
Yeah, and you drink it, and you say, "Wahoo! Yippee!"
And you put your hands up when you drink it.
You can't control what people say when they drink your whiskey, you asshole.
But it makes you do that, because you can taste the fun.
It really tastes like a roller coaster experience.
- You see the fucking cheap ass-- - Just shut up.
- Look at the green stuff.
- Just shut up. - I was like,
oh, why is my eye itching?
- Oh, oh!
I'm gonna make your eye stop itching.
- I'll put them back on 'cause I need to read.
- You don't need to read shit?
- No, I think that you would be better off--
- You need to read two more words in your life.
The end, that's what you see when you die.
- Damn.
- It says the end in front of your eyes.
- Why are you, all right, that's a little far.
Yeah, he's been bringing up a lot of fucking nonsense.
- He has to die for us to eat him.
I'm not gonna kill him. COVID's gonna kill him. That's actually a wonderful point. I'm
not saying like I'm gonna, okay, like, but I'm gonna sign a piece of paper. You know
what we need? Oh yeah, here, because we're gonna do your DNR, because you're gonna be
on life support after you eat that energy. I think I do have a, I think I have a DNR.
You have a DNR? At age 25? Yeah. What? Why? I put it on my license. You have a, you know,
you're a donor. No, no, no, no. I don't have organ donor on it. I have do not resuscitate.
You better not have organ donor on your fucking license after what I've seen with your body.
I do have, and you know what? I would be so pissed off if I got your kidney. If I got
your green kidney, it's going to kill you 50 times faster. What are you talking about?
My shit's all strong. I have so many preservatives in me. No, that's not how it works. Yes it
does know you're young you will die at 31 you will die I have I have a do not
resuscitate because I misheard them when I was when I was like signing all the
stuff and figure it out I thought I thought that I was saying please kill me
if I'm ever inside a Cobra mmm that's probably scary to be in yeah yeah I don't
want to be in a Cobra ma'am I'm sorry to say yeah you're so we had to put your
son in a Cobra we had to medically put your son in a Cobra I have a I have a
Sorry, did you say coma?
I also have a DNS.
A cobra?
(laughing)
Yep, he's in a cobra.
I have a DNS on mine.
And he's on that bed.
It's a do not suscitate.
What does that mean?
It means, look, you don't need to resuscitate me.
You can resuscitate me.
Once is enough.
You can resuscitate me all I want.
I've already been suscitated.
But once I'm suscitated, that's it for me.
I only need it once.
Watch this, all right, Daffy Duck.
Thuthitate.
That's Sylvester.
That's Sylvester the cat, yeah.
What am I, a fucking tune genius?
you have to make me the king of all fucking tunes.
Shut the hell up.
You think I still pay for boomerang?
- Yeah.
- Dude, I wanna pay for boomerangs.
I keep the boomerang icon on my Roku channels
just so I can look at it.
- It doesn't look good. - I don't have an account.
It just has Bugs Bunny and Scooby Doo on it.
- You look at it, oh that's funny.
- I just love seeing that between Netflix and YouTube.
There's a picture of Scooby Doo for me to look at.
Damn.
- You know you can get a screensaver on Roku.
- Yeah, it just automatically sets mine,
It sets it to like whatever new movie just came out and I like it that way.
They should make a scream shaver, like a tooth tune.
Mm-hmm.
Rage Blade.
Oh, and you...
Oh, every time...
AHH!
Yeah.
Home Alone.
It startles you.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
Every single time.
[Laughter]
We have the screensaver on the TV at my house is...
They downloaded an app that's just pictures of monkeys.
Mmm.
And there's this one picture of a monkey going like...
Oooh.
[Laughter]
And every time I leave the TV on, it's just a monkey going...
When I leave my TV on, it goes to Roku City.
- Dude, my fucking, I'd like to go to Roku City.
My fucking screensaver on my shit is,
it's connected to my mother-in-law's phone.
- Oh yeah.
- So it's just every picture on her fucking phone.
So it's just, and she does like real estate shit.
So sometimes it's just like a picture of a house or a sign
or like all these people from their church
that I don't know who they are.
And so if we have people over, they're like,
oh, who's this, is this your family?
And I go, I don't know who this is.
(laughing)
These people have no idea that they've been beamed
on to my television for three years now.
You can change that at any time, though.
I don't know how.
Google it.
What?
I don't know how.
I don't care.
It's funny.
Sometimes I see a real-- there's just one guy who's on there.
The slogan of our generation, I don't care, it's funny.
There's this-- whoa.
There's this one guy who's on my TV basically
every 16 to 17 minutes who is like 600 pounds big.
And he's so-- and every time he comes up, I laugh.
Every time.
There's ex-boyfriends, ex-girlfriends of the family that I haven't seen in years on there,
and they just all look right at me.
There's a guy who comes on my TV sometimes who's 600-700 pounds.
Yeah, when I turn the TV off, I'm fat as hell.
Come on, you're not that fat.
Come on.
You're like 600 pounds.
You're like maybe 3 or 4 hundred pounds.
And I show up in the reflection.
I saw a Seinfeld joke the other day that just a full lie that he did on stage, where he's
He's like, "I'm 300 pounds! I'm a fat guy!"
The joke was, he's talking about a news story the other day about the world's fattest man.
He's 1600 pounds!
I guess the joke is from the 80s where people would believe that.
Nobody was 1600 pounds!
No way!
His whole joke was that even if he lost 400 pounds, he'd still be 1200 pounds!
Nobody's ever been that big either.
- That's so annoying, dude, I was like, you--
- 1,600 pounds!
- Maybe you meant grams.
- Google what is 1,600 pounds,
just let's get some examples of stuff that is 1,600 pounds.
- Things that are 1,600 pounds.
- 'Cause 2,000 pounds is a ton, right?
- But it, yeah, but it really pissed me off,
I was like, I can't believe--
- Oh yeah, so that's $2,000.
- $1,900.
No, none of these people are 1,600 pounds.
- Search things that are 1,600 pounds.
- People get to be 700 pounds,
people get to be 750 pounds.
- There we go, what, wait, no, go back,
first result was the thing we're looking for.
Here we go.
Several breeds of cattle.
He may have been talking about a cow.
He may have been talking about the Hereford Angus.
I may be messed up really bad
and he was just talking about a cow.
And the Encole Watsui.
You know, now that I think about it,
it was a cow. This cow!
Oh wow!
Oh wow! This looks like one of those long-haired cows.
Can you pull up
the next tab for me, Julio?
tab you have open. Just pull it, yeah, just that one right there, just click on that.
Whoa! Oh, interesting. Okay, so this... Wait, why did you just have this prepared?
He says it's right there. Wait, okay, so wait, I'm curious about this, Cameron.
Yeah. This is a slideshow that says in the title, "I have prepared some
information about eating human flesh." We've not been stuck in here all that
long. Why? This is an old, this is from the last time we were stuck in here. Oh, okay.
I never ended up showing you guys. Oh, carry on, carry, continue. But yeah, I kind of did,
this is, you know, it's a list of, I found out, so, this is an aggregation, okay? I found
some stuff for different, yeah. So this is kind of the Metacritic of cannibalism. Rotten
tomatoes. What I've put together for you guys. I'm giving being stuck in a, I'm being, just
being stuck in a bunker with fucking ice all over me. It's giving being stuck in a bunker
I'm giving that certified, what's the opposite of fresh in that? Rotten. Rotten. Yeah. Certified
rotten. Frozen. Yeah. If I'm stuck in a bunker with ice, I'm doing some leftist ass shit
and beating the crap out of them. Oh, ice. Oh, ice. I haven't heard about ice all that
much recently. No. Yeah, you don't really hear it. It must have gotten abolished. Yeah.
It's over. Probably. We did it! Well, you guys did it. Yeah, I didn't do it either, actually.
They put G.B.O. in a computer.
(laughter)
He tried to visit for Christmas
and they put him completely in a computer.
Ice did that, look at that.
They made him green.
That's fucking crazy.
- Okay, so we'll start off with just some fun facts
and some fun little tidbits about eating human flesh.
This is the first thing.
- Ooh, tidbits is probably a good part of a human.
- Yeah, well we'll see if the tidbits are good.
- Somebody named Tid.
- Yeah.
Their recipe, girl the human flesh with the bud of the pindopalm.
So that's, first of all, that's if we were going to cook Patrick,
we could girl him with pindopalm.
What's pindopalm?
Yeah, what is pindopalm?
It's just an ingredient.
Do we have that here?
We might have that.
Oh, wait.
Here's the-- I think this is called the pindo.
Of your palm?
Yeah.
The pindopalm.
That's probably what it means.
If a man is being eaten, boil the penis and give it to a woman.
Oh.
Eating male genitalia means they will give birth to a boy.
So we have to boil his cock and give it to you.
No.
No, that wouldn't really make any sense.
I bet it doesn't taste good boiled. Boiled? Yeah, I think that you're probably right.
I think that the human penis probably tastes really good braised. I bet yours might taste good boiled.
Yours probably would taste good boiled because it's reverse. Yeah, I guess my penis probably has the same chemicals in it
in it that a hot dog would. Also, you're uncircumcised so you kind of need to boil it like a
like you'd hark off a corn. Yeah, that's true. I guess if you're cutting off my penis to eat it,
You're already tomorrow. We won't cut it off before we boil it. We'll just lay you over a pot. Yeah
We'll get the rest of your meat afterwards the hurt locker when I got a tattoo once you watch the hurt locker
Yeah, you were in the fucking hurt locker. That's right. It hurts to get tattooed. Mm-hmm
If you're a pussy, no, it hurts. No, it hurts. He actually well you you were you have a low pain tolerance
No, when you're talking about it, it doesn't, it obviously, the only way you would say it
doesn't hurt is if you had a medical issue or you were...
I have a medical issue.
You don't have that medical issue.
I will say the first couple times you get tattooed, it definitely doesn't hurt as bad
as... the more tattoos you get, the worse it hurts because you have it built in your
head of like, "Oh man, this sucks."
Every single time it gets worse.
I think I agree with you.
Yeah.
And also, healing is worse than the tattoo though.
That's the worst part.
Definitely.
hurt you're a liar. It hurts. Or a girl. Girls always say it doesn't hurt. No, girls are
liars though. Yeah, I agree. Every single girl is a liar. Maybe a boy with his penis
defeated to himself. Oh, that sounds good. And then you'll give birth to a boy, Patrick
Jr. I would love that. Do you think you'll ever have kids? If I do, it will be an accident.
And not after today. Thank you for being so brutally honest. I would love to see you at
your kid's soccer game.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Especially if you have a jock kid and you're just picking grass.
I don't know if I'd be the worst dad in the world or just a very good dad, but not the
best.
You think that the ceiling for you is a very good, but not the best dad.
No.
No way.
There's no world where you're a good dad.
If my kid gives me world's greatest dad, I'm like, "All right, you left."
I'll be honest. I don't think I think that the ceiling for everybody is very good. No, I know such thing as the best
I will be the best
Because everyone hates their parents for random shit doesn't suck that if you have kids so you're there speak for yourself
Well, this guy's you this guy's creepily. Yeah, I don't creepily love my parents. I just have a really nice relationship
Okay, yeah world's best father he's got the pictures to prove it
Oh, good for him.
Since the birth of his daughter, his photos feature Dave and Alice and his signature trophy
mug.
Wow.
Well, we found out who the best dad in the world is.
Let's see.
Oh.
There he is.
That's the best dad in the world.
Oh, God.
Wait.
He just makes photos with a mug and his kids?
Wait, he's actually a terrible dad, guys.
They trapped his child.
This is some kind of ironic bullshit.
Wait.
That's not right at all.
Why is there pomegranates next to the fucking turkey?
And what... oh okay.
He's doing ballet.
He's putting a boot on his kid's fucking head.
This guy seems like a moron of a father.
Wait, what is that? That mirror... wait, go back one.
There's a very confusing mirror behind...
What the hell is going on there?
Where does that mirror begin and end?
I guess the mirror is the whole wall.
The whole wall is a mirror.
Yeah.
Alright, well, okay, that makes no sound right go back. I can see where the mirror ends now go back to that corner here
in
2013 New York police officer
Gilberto volley was arrested for plotting a kidnap torture and eat female victims the cannibal cop search terms like human meat recipes and how
To cook a girl using the screen name meat market, man. Yeah
I think
Market man he had like a bunch of posts on like a forum or something. That's how he got got yeah
Well, yeah, also he googled human meat recipes under the screen name meat market man you guys remember that fucking Winklevoss twin actor
Yeah, army. Oh army hammer. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you wanted to eat a girl, too
Yeah, yeah, I cook a woman said he wanted to eat a girl's butt and her pussy. That's disgusting
That's that's gross in Pakistan's Bacar district two brothers were arrested for digging up the grave of a 24 year old woman and cooking her
and a curry. After serving two years in prison, the brothers were arrested again. Complaints
about the smell of rotting flesh led authorities to their home where authorities discovered
the head of a child. The brothers admitted to cooking the youngster in a curry. We do
not know the details of their recipe. However, Punjabi cuisine is rich, robust, and full
of flavor.
Alright, well thank god. Thank god it was at least robust and full of flavor.
I also, I mean, they're committed to the game. They go to jail for cooking someone.
and again i got a meal a like
double down right again i'll take a look at the worst
the workers
possible one
what do you want a word of your brother you want to do
well i guess i guess
that's the uh... run probably got a problem was we we a little woman
you know we we got a kid i don't think i had now
yet property will probably less matter we need a child's headhead
god damn dude
so that i found this article
okay how to cook your roommate into a pie science
And I thought this was gonna have a recipe.
I thought this would be useful
in case we wanted to cook Patrick into a pie,
'cause right now he's basically our roommate.
'Cause we're trapped in here.
- I would love to put you on a spit.
That's a really good--
- We should spit roast him.
- Yeah.
- Promise?
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I'll spit roast you, Cameron.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, we'll spit roast you.
- Sure.
Okay, we're gonna spit roast you later.
Wait, what?
- Now you have to do it.
Now you have to spit roast me.
- We were already planning on spit roasting.
- Yeah, you've gotta do it.
You're gonna take all 2.25 inches of my index finger.
- Wait, that was a bait and switch.
- Yep, a bait and--
- Are you guys talking about fucking?
I was talking about eating him.
- No, I'm gonna stick my finger in his cavity
to test the temperature.
- I thought you guys were talking about
fucking and eating me.
- I'm gonna cook you 'til, what do you think,
okay, look at him.
Look at, and think about all the things
that are in his body.
What do you think is a safe temperature to eat him at?
Because honestly--
- 7,000 degrees.
- I probably would not eat until 500 internal.
- I would not, you could not be eating medium rare.
You couldn't be eating medium.
- No. - I think that you
would need to be well done. - I think you'd have to,
you'd have to braise me like I'm venison.
- I'd look at him and I'd be like,
okay, I'm gonna eat internal temperature 500,
let's do it, that's the only safe way.
I put him in the oven,
immediately smelled burning plastic.
- Yeah, yeah. - Well--
- It's like when you leave, it's like leaving the,
accidentally leaving the plastic wrapper
on the frozen pizza.
- That would kinda melt it down though, right?
- You know when you do that?
- No. - No, I've never done that.
- I never did that.
I was thinking of a thing that people do.
Do people do that?
I feel like that's happened before.
I've definitely left the cardboard on the bottom.
I know, I was trying to think of a thing that was plastic and the cardboard's not plastic.
Well, think about it.
You've eaten the Hungry Man dinner.
I probably taste just the same as the chopped sirloin in that.
You're like a Chungus Man dinner.
You're like Big Chungus because you're so hilarious.
You take that back, you piece of shit.
Oh, I thought you were calling me fat.
You're so funny.
I love getting that compliment after stand-up.
You're so funny like Big Chungus.
You're funny, you remind me of Big Chungus, look how funny you are.
Thank you, thank you.
Who do I remind you of?
Big Chungus.
That's our favorite impression that you do.
Thank you very much.
I could see you opening up for Big Chungus one day.
You could open up for Big Chungus.
big chungus, my comedy mount rushmore, kinesin, chapelle, sinus, chungus, big chungus, sucks
that ralphie mayes stole all of his material.
But anyway you need to be yeah very hot the hardest part of course would be acquiring the meat
No, I'm gonna him would be the bones. We don't have the problem. We don't have that problem
We got the meat right here, but actually however
Would be cannibal acquires her meat cooking it early is the trickiest part. Okay. It's actually the hardest parts actually cooking it, okay
Yeah, one after the other pretty well if you're a girl
I guess I guess actually the hardest part is acquiring it, but the trickiest part is cooking
Why don't you see as many women serial killers?
Oh, there's--
It's almost like men have some fucking evil thing inside
of them that hurts them.
You ever heard of Eileen Warno?
Shh.
Makes them want to kill, murder, and really hurt people really,
really badly, especially women.
Yeah, it is almost like that.
But women don't have that for some reason.
Women just do that to their children.
Women do that emotionally, serial killing.
Yeah.
Emotionally--
Breaking up with good guys.
Yeah, and ghosting.
Yeah.
Emotional serial killers all over Bumble and Bee.
Bumble and Bee. I know one of the apps. I'm on all the apps. I'm on Bee. Yeah, I'm on all
the apps. I told you guys this the other day. Yeah, I'm on all the apps. Yeah, talking Tom
and talking Ben. You ever heard of Eileen Wuornos though? You knew that that lady was killing
men because she had no eyebrows. I'm going to lean on your Wuornos. Yeah. Yep, and I'm
going to lean all over it and go. I'll spit all over it. Wow. Yeah, I'm on all the apps.
I'm on bubble. I'm on bubble. I'm on bubble. I'm on toad in the hole. I'm on
bubble. I'm on apples and pears. Yeah I met this girl on bubble. We really popped.
Oh that could be actually a pretty good one to do. Does 23andMe have a racial
dating aspect to it? No. Am I going crazy? You are going crazy. I thought that 23andMe you could
match up with people who have your same DNA. I think they just match up with your cousin. I think
they make websites like that. Really? Yeah. Well they make, I mean they make them for
religions I think they make room 23 and me if they in a worse year we why you
want to get on white date I want to get on no I want to go on the opposite I
want to get on a dating website that shows me the exact opposite I do a deal
oh that's a great idea you do a DNA test and it matches you up with the person
who's the exact I tried to do that I tried to do that too and I kept matching
up with sea scorpions yeah the exact opposite of my DNA that's a good point
a cactus yeah yeah okay as BritLab host Greg Foot in an attempt to eat a strip of
his own leg meat earlier this year the muscle in a human thigh broken down into
its constituent fibers is roughly equivalent to half chicken breast
combined with various cuts of beef so apparently Greg Foot ate his leg that's
I don't believe I went I found some pictures of Greg Foot doing this I guess
he did this so this is Greg Foot and he says this is a meme I found about Greg
Foot. This is my cooked leg meat. This is my cooked leg meat and that's Greg Foot right
there. Yeah I know I can tell. And he went ahead and he ate it I guess in a burger
or something. Did he lose his leg? I didn't watch the video I just looked at a bunch of
pictures. Why did he? And he liked it! Look! He really liked it. Oh he liked it so much
I'd put him in an insane asylum.
He's having so much fun.
I like that he like...
This picture was making me laugh so much.
If you google "Greg Foot eat leg meat"
this is like the first thing that comes up.
He like...
It wasn't for science.
It was for BBC.
If he put it in a fucking burger bun...
Just eat the leg meat like a nice steak.
Put it on a...
See? First picture.
I wasn't lying.
it. Juvio tried to fact check me. Wait, Greg Hefley memes. Wait, click on that. Greg Hefley
memes. How you feel when someone mistakes you for a... Oh, I know this feeling. That's
a skater thing, right? Or a surfer thing. Or it's also a surfer thing? What's going on
with this troubled child? Oh shit! Oh fuck, zoom out, zoom out Juvio. Show everybody the
full text here. Come on now. Holy crap, that's funny as fuck. Oh yeah, Greg Heffley or Under
Arrest for Sipping. Didn't, wasn't there a guy who ate his leg or some shit? Yeah, Greg
Foot. No, no, this is a guy who like, him and his friends made like tacos out of his
foot. Oh yeah, out of his foot. Yes, I did. I saw that when I was, he made foot tacos.
What if his name was also Greg? And they said, I read, I was reading, I thought it wasn't,
there wasn't enough funny stuff to put into this slideshow, but they described the taste
as beefy. Yeah. They ate foot tacos and they said, "It tastes beefy." Yeah. Beef-eat. Beef-eat.
- Like beef eat? - Yeah, beef eat.
I'd like to eat some beef instead of foot eat.
- Yeah, that's a good point.
What else you got on here?
- Well, I'm gonna drink some water first
so you guys can just talk while I do that.
- Okay, here, I'll do my impression of Cameron while he drinks.
(gurgling)
- I didn't do a single thing of that.
So next up I found, I think the next thing
is a different website, let's see here.
- He's talking up and down about how I'm gonna taste
like plastic, and then he drinks out of this plastic bottle.
- Well, I'm not gonna be eating it, so it doesn't matter.
- You're already putting your lips on plastic.
- If that was your bottle, you'd be eating the bottle.
I know you'd be like no this has b12 vitamins in it. It probably does
It's probably made entirely out of b12 no no no you okay, so here's something I found from the straight dope message board
Yo, uh-huh that's great dope
Master chefs how would you prepare human meat? This is obviously a hypothetical question and no I do not need an answer fast
That is a great kind of a cover. Yeah
Yeah
No
and I really don't care when I get this because I got no meat.
And this is from the normalvore. I eat normal foods.
I'm not defrosting any meat on my counter.
Yeah. So, a bunch of people had different answers for this here.
Somebody said, Calibri said, "Since this is about cooking,
it's better suited for cafe society than general questions."
So, they recategorized it as the first thing on there.
Send it over there.
This question about cannibalism, we have to put this in the cooking forum.
So, what does cafe society have to say about it?
Let's find out.
Carpaccio of buttock.
What the hell is carpaccio?
You know what carpaccio is.
It's like a type of cut.
It's a it's really thinly sliced
like meat.
I didn't eat meat until I was like
you ate poop carpaccio.
Oh I've heard you say that before.
But I didn't eat. I've never.
I just thought I don't really I had to
look up what carpaccio was.
I just thought carpaccio of buttock
was a funny thing to say.
Yeah it is the first thing.
Just you know I had a steak for the
first time with you guys.
Really? Outback Steakhouse. That was your first steak? Yeah, I think so. What?
I think that was either my first or my second one.
Yeah. First like, are you, you mean the one that was raw? Yeah.
Your first cut of steak. That was the first time I'd ever, I mean, I had like maybe some tacos or something.
My first time eating just a steak, that was it. Wow.
You didn't act like it. You acted like you ate a hundred steaks before.
I watched a bunch of videos about eating steak.
(Laughter)
I watched a bunch of videos about. You're 14 years old, dude.
I didn't eat meat until I was like fucking way old.
- Googling how to say slang before I go
hang out with my friends.
- No, I watch videos about cooking steak.
- What to say when eating steak for the first time
to fool people that I've eaten steak before.
- You ordered it fucking rare too.
- I said medium rare because I learned
that that's the cool way to order steak, like James Bond.
That's like the shake and not stir.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, you go.
And I'll have that medium rare
because I don't regard my life for my mouth.
And then it came out and it was a complete red slab of meat
and I ate the whole thing for you guys.
you didn't eat it because we stopped you from eating it.
We stopped you from eating it.
You pretended that you liked it.
That steak wasn't like...
I told you do not eat that.
That steak was blue. It tasted good.
That was the rawest steak I've ever seen.
We kept saying please don't eat that.
You kept putting it in your mouth and spitting it out.
I wanted him to eat it.
It tasted good.
And it was that rapper.
Young Givenchy.
Shout out Young Givenchy.
if he's dropped anything.
- He's our waiter.
- I wonder if he's like watching us.
- I think he's making it out of Amarillo, dude.
- He's gotta be.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's next up at Amarillo.
- He's probably in Hollywood.
(laughing)
- But yeah, I thought that that was a normal,
that's not, most steaks are not like that, I've learned.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause now I eat steak all the time.
- And after that, 'cause I was like,
I had that and I was like, that was really good.
I loved that.
- It was really good.
- And then I started making my own now.
- I'd look for chimpanzee recipes.
- Oh.
- Bup said that.
eat chimpanzees do they? I think they used to maybe. They eat like brains and shit. Yeah,
they eat a chimps brain in Indiana Jones. Yeah, and that's a documentary. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
and that's a documentary Patrick. Is that a way, is that like a real, do people eat
chimpanzees brains or is that Steven Spielberg being like. I think monkey brains, no people
eat those. Okay. I was gonna say is that just like. I think it's dangerous to eat though.
I think, I thought that was just like them being like. You can turn into a monkey. You
can get banana hunger. Kuru. Kuru, like Hillary Clinton had. Hillary Clinton had a Kuru? What
What do you guys see this Google Hillary Clinton Kuru KURU is a prion disease you get it when you eat
You can only get it from eating human brain. Oh, yeah, I don't know Kuru prion. What are these new streaming services?
Go to images here
See oh
Yeah, her face was rotting off. That's classic Kuru symptoms. She cuz basically she's eating face became white
She ate human brain and a bohemian Grove
in a preschool or something. Women aren't allowed in Bohemian Grove, by the way.
Yeah, it was something else. See, is it a brain injury or Kuru from cannibalsome?
She cannibalized, probably some children, some brains.
Wow. And she got Kuru. And look, that water has a lime in it.
Look at that circle. See that? That is a telltale symptom of Kuru, green thumb.
Oh, shit. People who get Kuru get green thumb when they drink water.
Wow. Good at gardening. Yeah. I see that.
But only when they drink water.
Okay.
So here's some other stuff.
So this is something, you know, I'd process the carcass same as I would a deer,
discarding all the organs, and then someone replied to that and said,
"Bold and underlined as mine, you are a fool.
You are discarding some of the best meats available."
Which is probably true, you know, discarding the organs.
All organs, yeah, no.
Have you guys eaten liver? I've never had it.
I want to, though.
The reason I put this on here is because this guy fires back, okay?
And says, "Do not call me a fool, please.
This isn't the pit and you needn't get carried away with trying to play up to your nickname."
I do not enjoy the flavor of many organ meats and in wild game the organs can be infected with some
unpleasant parasites and a human they will likely have the same unpleasant favorite flavor and in the case of the liver have a high concentration of
Waste and Toscan's toxins that I do not wish to consume you may feast on all the meat byproducts
It pleasures you to consume good day
With a good day, yeah, Willie won't get his ass every every fifth grade nerds dream is to get in a situation
Where you can hit someone with a good day?
Dude getting saying good day to you or now we're snowed in I have a late-stage hypothermia
Okay, where you get you start to get really really? Yeah, I'm snowed in should exposing the truth about human meat true
Eat words
The words snowed in I've never had liver me neither. I want I don't get it at the grocery store all the time
I really want to eat
I haven't knowingly had liver.
I want liver and onions really, really badly.
Me too.
I look at it and then I'm like, well, you have to keep it in milk for like an hour.
That's what you'll be saying, by the way.
You said me too.
That's what you'll be saying once you've had liver and onions.
You'll be going, meat?
Who?
Because you love liver so much now.
Yeah.
I also, I don't eat livers.
I prefer to eat dead stuff.
Yeah.
Stuff's already dead.
That's right.
Yeah.
And what the hell is dead bitters?
I don't want to eat a liver.
Yeah.
I want to eat something--
I wanna eat raw heart pretty badly though,
just 'cause I feel like--
- You are an insane person.
You watch too many of these gym guys
and you fuckin'--
- The office.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Yeah, kill me, or sue me.
- Yeah, that's why you wanna eat so many--
- Kill me. (laughs)
- That's why you wanna eat so many fuckin' bones.
Yeah, dried up bones, turn into a powder,
make 'em into gelatin.
- Too long of a line between point A and point B
on that one, I'd say. - Yeah.
- You could've said, yeah, you wanna eat bones.
You had dry bones, you Mario Kart motherfucker.
- You know how, have you guys ever watched a show Hannibal?
You know how people say like, okay, well people--
- You mean cannibal?
- So you know, people, there's a bunch of scenes in that show
where Hannibal, Hannibal Burress,
is preparing like human meat,
and they make it look like really good.
- And he puts pickle juice on it.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yep, yep, that's what happens.
- They make it look really good,
and people are always like,
people always say about the show,
they're like, yeah, like that show,
it made me wanna eat human meat,
'cause it looked so good when they were preparing it.
That's like their joke that they always say about that show.
And I think it's funny to imagine,
like watching that show for the first time,
and turning it on and being like,
Oh my god, it does look really good.
It's just all the characters talking to each other
before they show any cooking scenes.
You're just looking at Mads Mikkelsen and being like,
"Oh my god, they really do make human meat
"look like it tastes so good in this show."
- Mads Mikkelsen would not be in my top 1,000 people
to eat. - No, definitely not.
- No, fuck no, dude. - Probably the very bottom.
- Dude, I'd eat Bert Kreischer.
I'd eat the fuck out of Bert Kreischer, dude.
- Gabriel Iglesias.
- I mean, listen, I hate to say it,
who the person I'd eat would probably be pretty young.
When you say pretty young, like what age I guess?
Probably is pretty young.
But like two?
I'm just thinking about flavor and tenderness.
I just think about flavor.
I think hungry.
Here's the thing.
I wouldn't eat, I would probably kill myself before eating Clint Eastwood.
would yeah that you wouldn't want him he'd be nothing yeah Bruce Willis he's
right out what if yeah what if humans are like lobsters though or it's like the
older they are like the more meat I would not eat a trillion lobster we know that
because we know people who were old yeah but we're grandparent I'm talking about
like the meat we've all taken a bite out of grandma's sagging arm I definitely
have my grandma used to flap her arms in front of me like when old people flap
their arms I wanna throw up my nanny to do it in the car she's I wrap around
usually don't really hate old people yeah my Nana would do that with her arms
in the car she I honestly London London London London London my god arm go like
I wish that all people tasted good to eat so I could I could have an excuse to
kill and eat them that wouldn't be a good excuse that's not a good you know
what I was thinking if I was a serial killer my method of finding a victim I
would I would enter the house and kill people of people who put you know when
people put posters or art in their window facing out.
And it's like, you can't even see that inside your house.
That's like they put a funny picture
for people on the street to see.
Do you know the kind of thing I'm talking about?
I think if I was a crazy person and I wanted to kill,
I would be walking down the street,
and if I saw a picture of a funny cartoon
facing out in someone's window,
that would be the house I would break into and kill.
- Like a funny sign that says,
"In this house, we believe science is real,
"black lives matter." - Yeah, one of those signs too.
I think that's, that would be my thing. I would be the window art outward facing killer.
That would be the catchy name they gave me.
That is really funny when you see that sign that like, "In this house we believe blah blah blah."
You see it in the window because you know that the person who put it out is like,
"Well, if I put it out, somebody is going to steal it."
[Laughter]
That's a good point.
"Better put this in my third floor window."
"I'm gonna put it here so people know that's what I believe."
but they can't know i want anyone to steal that she had a
so it's gonna really pissed off about my son that says i believe water is
important
yes on fire called they're gonna take i know someone's gonna freakin steal that
for me that is the funniest thing that those signs say what it says something
about what it is like i believe water is life or so yeah
it's like what what yeah it is like i believe like immigrants are beautiful i
believe black
my lives matter i believe science is awesome and i believe water is wet
you know who it is and that's where and what it is you know who would be who
would go
crazy on that but inside is a little mother fuckers from captain underpants
get nothing
that rearrange shit we're not a good at that
blackwater i believe it you know
well they're there are a lot of other sciences black
is that a lot of black well they would be a little rearrange it is just a side
I mean I think they may be
be able to turn upside down man I don't know how those damn signs were shut the
fuck up
What do I look like? A fucking home goods employee?
Dude, they would be able to turn the McDonald's, they would be able to wreak havoc on the McDonald's
logo. Oh my god.
Turn it into a W or an E. Or a 3.
My turds are $1. That's what I always wanted to make this one sign say in my hometown,
but they never had a dollar sign. Yeah.
My friend took one of those. We used to do that all the time. We used to
do the... I did that, we did that to a church sign one
time. It was very fun.
I used to live next to this motel and we would change it, we would change it all the time.
And we made it say, it said, "Yes pets, I miss you mom."
And the first one we ever did was we were pretty shy, so we just changed a couple letters.
We made it say, "Yes Mets, I miss you mop."
And that made us laugh.
But then we realized that that lady's mom died.
Oh, that's kind of sad.
And then we just pranked her.
The one that we did, we only did one time and it was pretty damn edgy.
We changed the church sign and we made it say Satan.
Shit, we used to make the church say ass.
But it was one of those things where it's like, okay, they left the, it was that type of sign
And there's like a glass door that they always locked yeah, and was like one time
We walked by and was open and it's like okay if this is unlocked and the letters for Satan are there you have to make you
Can't there was a church school that had a sign that said something about class dance
We made it we took every letter off except ass dance
Yo, that was my friend took a photo of the one he did and send it to me
I wasn't there for it, but he made it say shit missing from cunt
That one's really tough. Okay. It takes forever to rearrange exactly I got a power, but something must have been missing
Okay, so this is this is a website. I found
Delish the daily delish and this was that this is a little shot
This is the crown jewel delish God
And this is this is a website where it has a bunch of question you google you google a question this website pops up
It is a page with a bunch of related questions
And it has answers that they've written for us to all these questions that we might have about how to cook a human
Okay, so we'll just go through and I'll read some of these Q&A so this is like kind of an FAQ
for for cooking human or cooking Patrick specifically. So first off, what is the
tastiest part of a human? Don't call Patrick that. The brain and muscles are
probably your best bet according to Yale certified nutritionist Dr. Jim
Stapani. So the brain and muscles. Jim Stapani? Yeah, he knows what's up, the
brain and muscles. So we'll get your brain, we'll get your muscles. I don't know why that name is making me laugh.
Then we have, how does a human brain cook? And we have instructions. Whisk enough
milk to cover the brains by three times their volume with salt just until you
can taste it. The next day, drain and rinse the brains and pat, completely dry.
We're gonna eat his brain. To cook, heat a pan with butter until lightly browned. Dredge the
brains in flour, tap off the excess, and fry golden on each side. So this is how to
make fried human brains. Yeah, that's the same way you make liver.
Well, that's just how to make fried human brains. Okay. So that's useful.
Yeah. Brain looks like a cauliflower though. I'm sure you could turn brain and you
can make brain wings. That's true. Usually when foods look like each other,
that's what you do with them.
- Just one piece.
- You should have said that.
- You should have said nothing.
(laughing)
- Okay.
Then we have, "How do I prepare for 40 Humans" book.
How to cook for 40 Humans is a cookbook
that the Regelians keep in their kitchen
of their spaceship.
The book is a guide for preparing meals
for large groups of humans.
Serac the preparer referred to it
while preparing meals for the Simpson family
when they were on board the ship.
- What the hell kind of bullshit is this?
Is this still this doctor?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, this is Stupani.
- So this is Dr. Stupani is telling us
about this book that was in the simpsons that's disgusting uh...
and then we have uh...
can you hear back at the top of the court in a recent study the desire to eat your
baby up is totally normal and healthy
really it went far beyond what i have a little baby toes i wanted to devour my
children just eat them all up
okay
so that's a normal there's only a right to somebody else's baby with a ladder
no just yet they're only they only really cover
it's normal to want to devour your children and eat them all up ok on so
So that's something this website has for us.
Then we have, "Can you eat your own poop?"
Yes.
According to the Illinois Poison Center, eating poop is minimally toxic.
Yeah, it's not that bad.
Yeah, I like that that came up on the page for cannibalism though.
That is a way of cannibalism.
Somebody Googled, "How to cook human meat," and one of the questions is, "Can you eat
your own poop?"
It looks like meat.
Then we have, "How do you cook a human cookbook?"
How to Cook for 40 Humans, YouTube.
God, it's got the Simpsons-obsessed mother-father.
It's the same Simpsons thing, yeah.
And then we have, "How long does it take to cook a human hand?
To enhance the flavor, you should boil it for nearly 15 to 20 minutes until it becomes soft,
and follow the recipe of a chicken curry to cook it.
You can also add oregano for extra flavor.
For side dish, you can add gingerbread, some orange juice, and sweet bread."
So two types of bread.
So if you're cooking a human hand, you want orange juice on the side and some breads.
I'll have some.
Do you think a human cooking human hand is like chicken feet?
No, I think it's like a chicken hand.
Okay.
No, I just like cuz you have to like boil. I don't know if you eat in chicken feet.
Which Simpson would you eat? Yeah, is it good? Homer, duh. Yeah.
Yeah, I just want to stress this is the only website on the
internet you can find information on how to cook human flesh. Everything else is
like, yeah, apparently there's a secret cookbook on how to cook human flesh but
we can't show it to you. And then this one is like, if you're gonna eat a human
hand. You should have orange juice with it. I would eat a criminal. Yeah. Yeah. If that
was an option, I would probably eat one bite of somebody who maybe stole... I would eat
a full guy. Somebody who taped Avatar in the theater or something. Yeah. I'd eat that guy.
I actually, if it was in an Avatar situation, definitely. What do you mean an Avatar situation?
Just any kind of guy who brings disrespect or disrepute to a showing of Avatar. Do you
Do you think that the Navi tastes better than the humans?
No.
Does it not eat the human?
Well, they're leaner.
No, they don't.
Not yet.
I mean, we'll see what happens.
The new movie's not out yet.
True.
Maybe out by the time this is out, I guess.
Well, I'll report back when I see it.
Let me know.
I'll let you guys know.
I need to see your report.
How do you serve a human?
The simple five-step process of serving humanity.
Build a foundation.
Chisel yourself into the person you want to be, piece by piece.
Find your why.
Find the reason you want to truly serve humanity.
Act daily.
Trust your instinct and share your vision.
That doesn't help me eat nobody.
- That's how you become your best person to eat a person.
- Oh, you gotta be fully actualized
before you eat human meat.
- Here's how you serve a human.
- Well no, you're doing kind of the thing you do
after you serve someone.
- Oh yeah.
- You have to like--
- Wait, hold on, let me, all right,
imagine I just spun on my head.
- That's good, yeah you did.
- He served that.
- Yeah.
- This is, yeah, 'cause eating human meat
is like the top of the hierarchy of needs.
You have to be full, self-actualization is under--
- 'Cause it's kinda like, you're bored.
- Yeah. - You're like,
"Ah, I guess I'll fuckin' eat somebody."
- Yeah, and then if this is the next one,
I think the next one's the last one.
This one made me laugh out loud when I saw this.
I was scrolling through all these questions
about human meat on this page,
and this is the last question on the page.
"What is the yeet baby?"
(both laughing)
"Chris Rooney and his two-year-old niece Marley,
"otherwise known as the Yeet Baby,
"have become internet stars after he documented
"her progress of life skills on their TikTok account,
"gaining over three million followers."
- Holy crap. - That's the Yeet Baby.
- I didn't even know that.
I didn't know that Yeet Baby existed.
Me neither.
It's good to know though.
Yeah.
All right, well we're stuck in here.
I don't think we're ever getting out.
Yeah, probably not.
But you can get out.
Oh shit, we forgot to do one thing.
Oh yeah, Santa Tracker.
We'll close on this one this time.
Yeah, we'll close out.
You know, subscribe to the Patreon.
Yeah, you can get out your wallet and go to Patreon.
If we get enough money, we might be able to buy a hair dryer for me.
To melt our way out of here.
Oh yeah, true.
Caleb's hair yeah I think it might look pretty it really might look good I think
I'm gonna grow my natural hair and the new executive producer tier is still on there if you want to
have your name at the end of the episode and also get a shareholder meeting and
maybe your name will be frozen in ice this episode I don't know if that's a
possibility it'll be written in icicles maybe your name will not be ISIS I hope
they do not give any money to our and don't go on there and give us a lot by
the way I want to make this very clear don't go on there and say fucking my
name's Booger we will get your ID and we will confiscate it. It still has all your
credit card info. Yeah. We have your credit card info.
That's true. If you put a fake name on the Patreon name thing for the
for the credits we will be forced to use the only information we have about you
which is your credit card number and your expiration date. Yeah. And your
email. That will be going up at the end. We're gonna put one on the screen right now.
we're gonna put your email that's somebody's who subscribes to our patreon
that's what your email address and here's and here's a robot that's
exploding a dinosaur right here
really quick let's see what Santa's up to today before we before we close out
here on the Santa trackers frozen solid well he's still on earth all right thank
God okay where's this actually don't know where this is kind of neighborhood
What is this he's in the hood? Oh my god, bro?
skid row in Los Angeles
Santa please I thought he was gonna be good there. He's gonna gift. He's hopeless. I thought he's gonna be giving out Metro cards
And no we have a gift to the homeless Santa. What are you up to?
There's a thought well because they don't have a oh Santa don't hell you're climbing in a dumpster
Is there you don't belong in there? Yeah? You're not sees trash. Oh Santa Claus. That's all I hate to see him like this
That's really we'll see him have a triumphant return. Yeah, I'd love to meet him one day. I don't know what the hell is this
See this one
Will work for oil I guess Santa Claus
Santa Claus is that an Exxon Mobil that seems to be frozen over?
An old picture yeah, hey Santa try maybe put some clothes on buddy. Yeah, you were you were not doing too good
No, you're looking pretty fat. I'm not gonna lie. There's and there's a tiger big tiger
And you have a gasoline that you rest. Well. He looks happy at least yeah
Yeah, looks like he's doing well all right must be an old one if he looks happy we see you next time
We're gonna eat Patrick's butt body
Bye, bye
Doesn't matter to me. I don't give a shit
And it's my birthday in six months