Hello, listeners of Podcasts About List. It's me, Pierce, friend of the show and director
and editor of Fright at the Museum, the most popular Podcasts About List video in recent
memory. I just wanted to let you know that an extended cut of Fright at the Museum will
be dropping on flight day the 13th in January. It will be longer, more scary, funny, movie.
And now please enjoy the new episode of Podcast About List, on which I am a guest. We had
a lot of fun reminiscing about old times, sharing laughs, and reading lists, but at
At some point, as usual, it goes way off the rails, and I think you'll be able to tell
at what moment I lost my nerve. Yeah. So take a look, and wish everyone involved in Podcast
About List, including JubyO and Patches, a happy season. Holiday greeting. Bye bye!
(music)
And now we're official.
Okay, let's start it exactly how we started it before.
Oh yeah!
Well we saw the first 22 seconds.
I think we'll cut that in first and then just jump to this.
We lost the recording incidentally.
where Jubio fucked everything up.
Broke every single thing.
God damn you, you fucking piece of shit.
I think I should drink this.
What is in that?
It's just it's hot coffee, but it's in a plastic cup
because all the other mugs were dirty.
And I was like, I thought about doing it and then I decided against it.
That was a that was a thing that I learned from about a few months ago
when we first got this office and we got the coffee maker.
I was like, I'll have some I'll make some coffee.
And then the only cups were solo cups.
I took one sip and I was like, I this is so hot.
And it tastes like plastic.
You can taste the plastic.
Yeah, but who gives a fuck for him?
For him, we talk about I mean, I'm in love with him.
And he's my friend. Wait, what did you just?
There you go. OK, love with me.
But like you, he's fucking throw another shrimp on the Barbie on this guy.
What the hell do you? I'm not Australian.
I never shamper in the back.
What's the voice?
And there are no on the bar right now.
There are no showing that I'm doing it on a frog.
- Throw another shrimp on the barbie.
- You know what I'm saying.
- I think you're rushing.
I think, just close your eyes, think about an Australian,
think about a kangaroo.
- Oh, wow.
- Air, wow.
- No, Owen Wilson.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- Throw another shrimp on the barbie.
- Throw another, fuck me, man, what's going on?
- Fuck me.
- Let's throw another shrimp on the barbie.
Start with Barbie Bobby see Oh
Bobby now say the rest of it, but backwards
You brought by a Barbie
Robin Bobby
Let's throw up another let's okay, so you're stomping over my shit because I was trying to do it actually reverse
And you're just doing the words
Reverse he said backwards a brab a brab I asked Matthew golden to do a Stewie Griffin impression
And this was his this is what he said I struggle with that at my age
Struggle with that at boy age
Man it's hard to do it's hard to do different impressions sometimes yeah, yeah, yeah, you got this okay?
Was that
- Is this the beginning of This Girl is on Fire?
- Mm-hmm.
- That was pretty good.
- ♪ This girl is on fire ♪
- Check this one out.
- Is that how the song starts?
- Yeah, "The is girl is on fire."
- Check this impression out.
Zoolander.
- Oh, okay.
- That's a terrible Zoolander.
- Shut up!
- No.
- Here's a bit I used to do in sixth grade.
It was like, all right, here's Christian Bale.
All right, here's Owen Wilson.
All right, here's Nick Cage.
- You're doing a kissy face.
- Yeah, same impression each time.
- And what year was that?
- Kind of like a-- - Were you in sixth grade?
- Yeah.
- Nick Cage used to be very funny to talk about, man.
- Oh, yeah. - He was like the
Chuck Norris of movies, let's say.
- Definitely. - Of randomness.
- Yeah.
- He was the Chuck Norris of randomness.
- Chuck Norris was also in movies.
- Right.
- Not as much as Nick Cage, though.
- Chuck Norris was like the Chuck Norris of fighting
and maybe even Chuck Norris jokes.
- True.
- Nicholas Cage.
- What's the best Chuck Norris joke ever written?
- Just Google it.
- Yeah.
- Best Chuck Norris joke ever written.
stroke ever written we're not gonna figure it out no figure we can write a
chunk what's the one that's in the expendables where it's like it's like
Arnold Schwarzenegger's like I who do a bit by a cobra and he's like yeah but
then the after three days of agonizing pain the Cobra died okay here's the
number one here's the number one joke okay boogie man goes to sleep every
night he checks his closet for Chuck Norris wow that's a riot these are just
in soviet russia
the same format
i'd like i think they turned into that it turned it if you i feel like it was
originally supposed to be it was originally when i read those jokes and
like say like two thousand eight or whatever
it was a like chuck norris yet chuck norris could punch through a wall
it will be stuff like that
you know i mean yeah but that that he had been a turn into a truck in the
first of all it's not true
what what give you the the sentiment
- Chuck Norris is strong as hell.
- When Chuck Norris runs, the world spins under him
instead of him running.
- He narrates, Chuck Norris narrates
Morgan Freeman's thoughts.
That was one that I remember from childhood.
- The joke was that he was just like a shitty
80s action star who was like never in a good movie.
And then like--
- Yeah, that was the joke.
- Yeah, that's what it was, but then like--
- Doing a video essay.
- Growing up, I thought that Chuck Norris
was like a beloved like action star and it's like that was not the case.
Yeah when he's not at the end of the ultimate showdown I mean I was
learning about Batman and Godzilla and then Chuck Norris shows up he must be
famous than Batman. He's gotta be bigger than Abraham Lincoln. I definitely thought he was just the meme guy.
Yeah the guy from Chuck Norris. I thought he was basically number one badass. Really? But then you find out
when you're kid he's 82 years old. 82 years old and he's a freaking Republican.
Yeah, and first of all, I'll play that conservative bullshit.
Yeah, I don't fuck with that.
No, no, no.
He's, I think he was supposed to be like Mike Huckabee's running mate.
Yeah, he used to go on Huckabee all the time.
Yeah.
And just talk about nothing, which to me, kung fu is not like very conservative.
Hey, you'd be surprised.
Yeah.
Huh.
About what?
What my sensei says to me.
You don't have a sensei.
Sensei is karate.
You've never done kung fu in your life.
Well, but yes, I've done karate.
Sensei is for all of them.
that's that's a good point I haven't done kung fu yeah yeah I guess kung fu is for
libs and karate is for red red-blooded Demo Republicans like me when Chuck
Norris does karate
his opponent becomes hit by him exactly a black belt earns Chuck Norris see
- Dude, that's pretty good.
- I will say it's a,
(laughing)
this is a good one.
Chuck's Gmail account, gmail@chucknorris.com.
That is good.
Chuck Norris on--
- Chuck Norris on Hillary Clinton.
Yeah, she votes for him.
- Damn.
- Yeah, she's with him.
- Or she doesn't vote for him, maybe.
- Yeah, this isn't even like a Chuck Norris meme.
- That's just a quote.
- Yeah.
God, he looks like shit.
- It is a really great,
what a wonderful concept for a TV show
of a sheriff who can do kung fu.
- Yeah.
- That's a really, I never really considered that.
- Walker, Texas Ranger.
- What a goddamn amazing-- - Anybody who just,
anybody who is, anything that's,
it's a guy who has a job and he can like,
he fights people.
- So good. - That's great.
- Roadhouse?
- Yeah.
- Roadhouse is a real good movie.
- Yeah, Texas Roadhouse.
Those teedots on the floor.
- I really like Roadhouse.
- Yeah, I got some-- - I love that movie.
- My girl gave me some Roadhouse.
- Damn. - Yeah.
- She built a house on the road.
- She gave you Roadhead in your house?
(laughing)
- On the couch.
- Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
- Playing Flight Simulator? - You're playing
- I have a force of four.
- I've been watching a bunch of videos on flight simulator.
Did you know that the flight simulator games,
there's people who don't even fly the planes.
They just go in there and do air traffic controller
for like eight hours.
- No fucking way.
- They literally sit there and just be like,
JetBlue03071, go to November.
- That's so funny 'cause like,
flight simulator guys are like so obsessed
with like getting their PC to be like the most like,
like high powered thing in the world.
And then just to do that, like spending like,
like probably like 2K.
- I think these are the guys who can't afford the nice things.
- Yeah, okay.
- Well, I think that makes sense.
It makes sense to me.
- No, but just imagine.
- I don't think, if somebody is obsessed
with air traffic control, I don't think that's a job.
That's something that you have to really want to do.
I don't think anybody has ever fallen
into a job at air traffic.
Nobody's like, well, I'm looking at a few things.
I don't know, I haven't gotten hired yet.
- You're really good at--
- What about a disgraced pilot?
- Yeah, they probably let a disgraced pilot
be an air traffic controller.
I mean, besides crashing the plane,
in what world can you even become a disgraced pilot?
- You're goosing all the flight attendants.
- If you're rude over the intercom, you say.
- Goosing, that's, what does that mean, goosing?
- You put your finger up a skirt.
- Yeah.
Oh, have you guys ever played flight attendants?
(laughing)
- Yeah, you gotta dodge a lot of those.
- Yeah, well you can't last 10 seconds playing that game.
(laughing)
- There's guys who go on flight simulator
and nobody can hear them unless they press the button
and they'll just like talk to the cabin.
they have like a script and they'll be like,
we have cloudy skies, we have a little bit of turbulence
about halfway through the route, a nice tailwind,
it'll be 30 minutes out of schedule.
- I think that's baked into your brain when you're born
that you're going to be an air traffic controller
and if you spent the first 30 years of your life
living in a basement and you can't go out
and get the actual job, that's the only thing you can do.
You can't even be like a Crusader Kings guy,
you have to be an air traffic controller.
I think that's a destiny thing.
- Yeah, the only ladder that you can climb
to end up as an air traffic controller
that you're an autistic guy who plays those games all the time. It's not like
someone is really good at throwing luggage onto the plane. You know your way around planes.
You can be a pilot for a day, we'll see how it goes.
Holy shit this kid's a natural! What the fuck has he been doing all this time?
I'm starting to not like flying. I used to love flying. I hate it. I like it.
you I blame you yeah I'm sorry I literally never want to see you about I
never once thought that a plane crash I basically never once gotten a plane it
was like oh yeah I guess this could crash until he would start I started
flying with him and he started acting like that I just like nor him
can't help it yeah we should be actually sorry we should we should put I get it
We should put a we should knock you out with a Billy. I think
I would love to take Xanax before taking flights, but my truly my
I
Like take an anti-anxiety or something and it's zonks me out
But not enough that I'm like like if I'm like halfway and I can't like fall asleep
I like going in because that's happening getting like sleep paralysis
Actually my full nightmare
- Yeah. - Especially--
- Which is the reason I don't do it.
- But you might like it 'cause it's so similar
to your favorite shows and books.
- Yeah, I guess I might like it.
Wouldn't that suck if you took the Xanax
and you're like all relaxed and shit,
and you fall asleep, then you wake up,
(imitates plane crashing)
plane's actually crashing for a moment.
- (imitates plane crashing)
Getting shot in the head with a machine gun.
- I don't get any love.
There's a terrorist on the plane.
- Could happen.
- I mean, you can't fly the plane better than the pilot.
That's what I always call myself.
Like, even if there's mad turbulence.
That's a crazy thing to tell yourself on a plane.
Well, what am I gonna do?
Even if I hate it, even if I'm really nervous
that it's gonna come down, I'm like,
well thank God that there's someone who flies planes
who's in control right now.
- I'm not even consciously thinking like,
oh this plane is gonna crash.
There's something about the physical sensation
that turns me into a crazy person.
- I think that, yeah.
- I have no conscious thought of like,
this plane is crashing, this turbulence means
we're going down.
- We kept playing Word Scramble.
- That was fun AF.
- That was the only time I've ever seen you
calm on a plane.
Was when we went from Tampa back to New York,
like six in the morning.
We were trying to play games with other people.
- Oh yeah, they have the, you know on planes,
they have the games on the back where you can like,
start a room, like it's a fucking like,
- Yeah, we like, we kept requesting.
- Like it's a Battlefront 2 server.
- Goddamn.
- I always, you can set your nickname,
so I was setting my name to Rubbing Me One,
and like said, like opening my room,
so everyone in the plane can see,
like, would you like to join Rubbing Me One's game,
Bird vs. Bird?
- I always have, I always play the poker one,
and I, it's always me versus like some eight year old
who's like, "Oh my God, I get to play poker,
and his name is Y," and I just clean him, dude.
I'm just fucking winning every single hand, dude.
He folds every time, fucking idiot kid.
- That's how I used to win all my poker games.
- Just fold every single time?
- Go all in on the first hand,
and then fold until you keep cash out.
- Yeah, smart.
- Yeah.
- Oh, dude, Mahjong.
- Oh, yeah. - Mahjong?
- We gotta start our Mahjong tonight.
- Have you guys been playing?
Do you guys know how to play Mahjong?
- No, no, no, we've been talking about it
for probably a year and a half now.
- That was a game my mom had on the computer.
I don't know how to do. No, that's not the championship.
My job. Oh, shut up. Oh, shut the fuck up.
Came with purple palace.
It's a completely different.
I'm going to put you in the purple palace.
It's a completely to go.
You would not because there's no white people.
I would love to go to all just purple people.
And they'll be mean. I would love it.
There's no I don't care. I'll win them over.
No, no, no, no.
I'll show them the purple on the inside.
They hate white culture at the purple.
They don't hate white culture at the.
They really do.
Now, when I get there, no, they're going to show them the worm.
that's not
yet they invented the word they don't need to be someone to explain the
report
now they invented the purple were which is a different saying
this is why i was going to shut up all the sudden i'm talking to about my
job
there is a fair way to go back to the purple
there's purple
are probably
spot always called it what is purple play that's a real thing
the myself game artist hope yeah it's a game that came with windows vista
Holy shit, the purple place looks sick.
Dude, Windows Vista was fire.
The Windows Vista games, dude.
What is the purple place in this picture?
Is that building alive?
Cakes?
What?
Yeah, look up purple place gameplay.
Purple place walkthrough.
Whoa.
This looks fun.
See, they would love me.
No, they would not.
I would fit right in.
I'd look just like that.
Are those purples?
This is the purple place and not the purple palace.
No, you're talking about a different thing.
cakes there and you are you kidding my song no it was on the same it was in the
same folder as my song the computer listen the Mahjong you're talking about
is basically fucking spot the difference but it reverse this real Mahjong is
poker well there's also a spot difference on purple please I'm speed
I'm spying a difference on you yeah the rest of us what's that you have a you
have a crane in your head yeah yeah I have a crane that picks up the wrong the
wrong thoughts and drops them in your mouth yeah that's fine
have you ever won a crane game or any kind of yes I did you can't win those
Shaw's Londonderry New Hampshire any games at the arcade sorry hey to break
it to you guys but if you haven't that's a false memory if you got a check out
you got to check out our Kate Matt he gives away all the secrets and he has a
- I have heard that the crane only activates
like one out of 10 times.
- Yeah, there's like an odds calculator
or whatever the fuck it's called on the inside.
- Really? - Yeah.
- So what happens, the way to win a crane game
is you watch somebody play the crane game.
You watch somebody win and then count how many times
to the next win and then that's your odds.
- Oh. - And then--
- That's not how you win, that's just how you know
when you're going to win. - That's how you know
when you can win. - Yeah, exactly.
But that's the only way you can win.
- How you win is to select an animal and press a button.
- And press a button.
- No.
- Yeah, that's how you win.
- That has nothing to do with it.
- No, 'cause you're not gonna,
you're gonna have to play for a bunch of times.
- You know how much--
- Oh, and that would be such a nightmare
to play a game a bunch of times.
You just don't understand arcades in the slightest.
- I won an orange robot at Shaw's in the orange jute.
- That's about the only thing you can win, yeah.
- Remember when we went to that arcade
and Pat was obsessed with the coin pusher game?
- Yeah. - I love that.
- I do love it.
- You guys turned me on to this.
- I won so much on that.
- That's the best arcade game, I think.
- Yeah, I had no idea.
- Because you have to actually have strategy and timing.
It's a skill game.
- I like the one, I used to always like the one
where you shoot, you roll, or you either roll
or shoot the coin down and it goes into a spinning wheel.
- Oh yeah.
- But the one I used to play was called Wonder Wheel
or something, it wasn't ski themed.
And it was on the conveyor belt.
- Well you did a bad one.
- There's one in Nashua.
- I was really good at it and I won a lot of stuff.
- There's this place called Play Kingdom or something,
or like Fun Castle in Nashua.
And I won, I figured out how to get the jackpot every time.
I got my nephew a good gift for his birthday.
What gift?
He wanted the iron.
The iron?
They had an iron in there.
Like an ingot of iron?
No, like a clothing iron.
Oh, he wanted an iron.
I have a video of working iron.
Wait, that was in an arcade?
Yeah.
I have a video.
At Fun Palace or Play Kit.
I don't want to...
Don't dump game pieces from board games into this thing and say you can win.
You can win an iron.
It's not a real working iron or a toy iron.
I have a video, but I don't want to show a video of my nephew on the podcast.
This doesn't make any fucking sense.
There was a video of a kid playing with a toy.
I don't know if you can see it.
working iron or a toy iron? I have a video but I don't want to show this video of my nephew on the podcast.
This doesn't make any fucking sense. There was a clothes iron in a...
In... what's it called? I think it's Fun World.
I told you. What game world? Did you purchase it with tickets that you had won for...
Okay there we go. But why was that available for... I didn't get the iron.
What? You said you... I just have a video of him talking about the iron. You were lying.
I'm a liar. Why'd you lie? Because I wanted to be good on the show. But there is... I've been...
My performance lately hasn't been great.
A lot of people are annoyed with me.
A lot of people are annoyed with me all the time.
I just want everyone to think I'm cool.
So I lied about it. Yeah. I made the whole thing up.
I wanted Pierce to think I was cool.
No, there's an iron. I have the video. I can show you.
freaking me out yes or no there was an iron I'll show I guess my just well just
say yes or no you have to show it's probably that's that yes or no well yeah
I guess just like why would you ruin an iron and a wire in a in an arcade
cabinet do you guys ever play that game where you put the penny in and then you
flatten your giant Mickey Mouse
fridge to imagine the person is weird
as fuck
can you imagine me the person who like
stalked that and like had to convince
him like no we'll put it on there will
be a kid and nobody would believe them until your nephew was like did your
nephew was a plant yeah a crowd of like of like 10 kids who are on like a
field trip there or something and they're like I want the spider ring
they're fresh out of all these okay now go go oh yeah
there's an iron? Let me look at how many points that was - that was - look it up on Google
No, that was that that is like 3,000 tickets
It was 3,000 tickets get the eye I didn't get it though PlayStation control I got him a Chinese finger trip. Oh
There's actually way more points show this right now. It's 10,000 how much that's in destiny to
Okay, that's in destiny - thank you. Jubio. I
Really? I've always
I think it's impossible to win like the Xbox and stuff right but the one the one
Under where you can get like an RC car and stuff. That's doable for that
I never got that I never got any of those so like not in an arcade where there's clearly like they can measure how many tickets
But like the one-off games that they have in like the malls or whatever like Patrick got busted playing at one of the arcade malls
That we went to when we were in
Patrick went missing and then we like
- Yeah, when we were in North Carolina when you left.
- Oh, you left, we were at that mall.
I don't know why the fuck we went to the mall.
Yeah, we went to Independence Mall.
- We went to Independence Mall.
- Born on Airsoft.
- Oh yeah.
- Cameron did, you went to Chris Kyle on Airsoft.
- Yeah, you were insanely good at Airsoft.
- Sharp shooter.
- Yeah.
- But we went and then I tried to win that,
what is it, oh no, the key ring.
I tried to win the key ring.
- Yeah, that was really hard.
- Whenever, that's something you'd also--
- I put like 20 times.
- I remember when, back when Caleb would drive us
back and forth from New York,
we'd always stop at a rest stop or something,
and we'd be going to the bathroom,
we'd come out, and you'd have put $10 into the,
like, whatever game.
- Yeah, I got this one game they have
in the buy me a burger game.
- I got the stimulus check.
- It's for people who can't speak English to fall for.
- But if there's a PS5 or whatever in one of those games,
the one-off games, clearly the only way to get that
is to cheat, but if you walk out of the mall
holding the empty PS5 box, and you're like,
"I won this at the thing,"
- Whose job is it to say, "No, you didn't."
Like, who could possibly stop you?
- Oh, no, you didn't.
- Yeah, you were saying that.
- You were saying that at the mall.
- I was, that's right.
- I remember that, 'cause then I was like,
well, what if we do that?
- Yeah.
- Wait, you're saying, oh, you're saying,
grab the box, just bring an empty box.
- To someone.
- Tell them and say, "I won this out of the thing."
- Yeah, who's she gonna call?
- Do you guys remember when,
I forget what casino we were even at.
We were at a casino.
Oh, and there was there was like the arcade downstairs.
Yeah, we saw a sign that was like the kids area.
They're like, there's a kids area of the casino.
So we went looking for it.
We went it was like downstairs like tucked away in a corner.
It was like a tiny arcade.
It was at Caesars Palace, right?
Yeah, I don't remember even.
It was either Caesars Palace or Bally's.
Yeah.
No, no, it is.
It is.
And just there was just one.
I remember it was one. Wild West at Caesars.
It was completely empty.
The person who was working there did not want to be working there.
No, he helped us with Guitar Hero or something.
We were there at five o'clock on a Tuesday or something.
Well, there's going to be plenty of kids in schools out.
Yeah, true.
And there was just one guy there who was getting so into the games.
I think he was playing one of the motorcycle games or something.
And it was me really hard.
No, there was another guy in there with like an adult.
Yeah. And it was really making me laugh that there's a guy
who was like upstairs at the casino and he's like, you know what?
Fuck this.
Well, I haven't won shit.
Yeah, you know what I'm going to do?
I know. Yeah, it's a motorcycle.
I want to play as something.
It's exactly the same thing.
No, because at the arcade, you get
to ride on a motorcycle when you get no money.
You win more at the arcade, because you can buy funny candy.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
You can't get anything out of gambling.
There's more rewards.
When I was in Vegas a couple weeks ago,
there was a huge arcade in the bottom of the casino.
And it really was so tempting to me.
And I kept suggesting it to the people I was with.
Like, man, all this gambling's fun,
but shouldn't we-- we should go down and play the Jurassic Park
Dark game.
That's messed up that no one would go with no one would go that's fuck
And I don't want to play the two-player games because those are the good ones yeah guitar heroes are the fun ones
I like this night that sniper game that sniper game was fucking awesome
Fun world I have the high score on holiday in Cambodia not anymore not anymore
on easy oh
Yeah, he sucks a guitar
He pretended like he was gonna be good, and then I played with him, and I smoked it
Yeah, you smoke playing on medium and fucking missing 80% of the time. I'm really really bad at guitar here
- I'm like horrible at guitar hero
because I never played it as a kid,
so it doesn't confuse my friends.
- You weren't allowed to have video games.
- I was allowed to have video games.
- I went on a father-son fishing trip
with my dad and his company,
and I was like the middle child
of all the kids that showed up.
So I could either hang out with the 17 year olds
when I was 13, or I could hang out
with the 11 year olds.
And so I ended up just hanging out with the 11 year olds
'cause they would just watch me play guitar hero.
- You're a god.
- So for six days in a row,
I just tried to beat Seven Nation Army on expert mode,
no other songs, and they couldn't play if they wanted to.
I was just like, no, I'm almost there.
- He's hogging it.
- Treating Guitar Hero like it's a Dark Souls thing.
- Yeah.
- So at this point, just trying,
oh, dude, next time I'm gonna get it.
Looking up a video, how to do it.
- They didn't even have phones to go on.
This was earlier than phones.
- Earlier than phones.
- Earlier than phones, 1800s?
- You know what I used to do?
My dad had a Blackberry for work,
and I learned that you could put AOL instant messenger on it.
So when we'd go on family camping trips or whatever,
I would just message my friends on AOL and be like,
"Yeah, camping sucks right now.
I kinda wanna go home."
- Man, my stepdad had a Sony Ericsson that had--
- I'm Ericsson. - True, you are.
- That's my dad's name.
- I used to take it into the bathroom and play Neopets.
He had no idea I had a whole Neopet situation
on his phone for like two and a half years probably.
- Oh, Brick Breaker?
- "Breaker" on my dad's Blackberry was--
- Yeah, dude.
- Was beat-baller. - Goated.
The little trackball.
- Yeah, the little trackball.
And the rap.
- Mate, you just surfaced a memory
that I just remembered for the,
I haven't thought about this,
when I played like Smash at someone's house or something,
and I didn't understand what was going on,
and there was, or maybe,
somehow I was aware of Solid Snake.
- Yeah.
- And I just knew that Solid Snake existed.
I didn't know what he was or what he was from.
and my mom's Nokia phone had a game on it called Snake.
- Oh yeah. - Oh.
- And I was like, oh my God,
you have an actual game on here?
That was Solid Snake?
And I opened it up and it was Snake.
- You were a fucking idiot kid.
- I just remembered that for the first time.
- Oh my God.
- You were starstruck.
- I couldn't believe, I was like,
how could you play a game with a character
that looks like that on a phone like this?
How could that possibly work?
- Remember the, like some,
back in 2008 or whatever,
you could text, like, you could text,
it was like, if you had a Motorola flip phone,
you could text, like, Saints to 6-1-something-something-something
and you could just play Saints Row on your phone.
- That's tight.
- What?
- And it cost, like, yeah, it was like,
you would pay monthly to play the mobile version
of Saints Row.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I did have some kind of Godzilla game
on my E-touch or something.
- On my flip phone, I had worms,
And I had Earthworm Jim.
I had worms games.
- Worms type games with worms in them.
(laughing)
- Worms was good, man.
- Worms was so sick.
- Yeah, I used to play worms all the time.
- I wonder if any of those mobile games
are like backed up anywhere though.
'Cause I do wanna see what like Saints Row for the mobile.
- Yeah. - For like the Motorola,
whatever. - You must be able
to find them somewhere. - Yeah.
Remember the NexTel phones that had the walkie talkies?
- No. - My dad had those
for work. - I like that little jingle.
- The little beep, the chirp chirp.
I feel like that chirp has become an ad-lib in rap songs.
Does that sound right?
- I don't listen to phone rap.
- I do.
- Lucid Dreams by Juice WRLD,
I think they use the little next tail.
- Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
- Yeah.
- Little next tail chirp.
- He does that?
- Yeah.
- He does it with his voice.
- Really?
- He did it before he passed.
- He's tragic.
- Yeah, it starts,
the chirp is what the beat drop is.
- Yeah.
♪ I, I, I, I ♪
- I didn't know that.
♪ I still see your ♪
I didn't know that was the next tell sound, but I know which sound you're talking about.
Because I've listened to that song 10,000 times.
I think that these hip hop samplers are getting fucking insanely way too crazy and disrespectful
with the stuff they sample.
Yeah, like Wiz Khalifa sampling Chrono Trigger.
Yeah, how about you just sample normal music, other shit that other people have made.
Stop trying to get fucking crazy.
Stop putting a fucking Taco Bell commercial in your song.
And make your own drums.
Don't steal other people's drums.
Yeah, and sing instead of rap as well.
And get two guitars and a bass and a keyboard player.
- I swear to God yesterday I was listening to a bunch of rap
in the car.
- No.
- I swear to God.
(laughing)
But then I picked up my wife from the train station
and I said something mean and she said,
"You're being disrespectful 'cause you're listening to rap."
(laughing)
And I was like, yeah, you're actually kinda right.
I was listening to disrespectful rap music
and it made me act disrespectful.
- Yeah.
- Made me act rude.
- When people see me talking to my girlfriend
like outside through the car they are always horrified because a rap song is
on and I'm starting an argument that I know I can win. Exactly dude, I was like I think I
listened to I was listening to some super Mario, I was listening to Superman by Eminem
which is a very disrespectful song. Eminem has a lot of songs disrespectful to mine.
I am this Superman where I can fly around the world the world and you gotta
- By me. - By Eminem.
- But that song is very rude and I picked her up.
- You were my lowest lane.
- Thoughts. - I thought an evil brain.
- Now there's kryptonite in my bed.
(laughing)
Yeah, that's scary.
- I have these super dreams where I can fly and things.
- Where I can fly and things.
- I have these laser beams.
(laughing)
- Come from my eyes. - That I can shoot from these.
That I can shoot from these.
Now my laser beams are red.
- Oh, okay.
- I have a frosty breath.
(laughing)
- I will avenge dad's death.
- Yeah, he's Superman.
- Fucking, I don't know.
- Yeah, man, who gives a fuck about Superman?
- Cares about him.
- Don't give a fuck about Superman.
- But Batman probably, yeah.
- I have a batarang.
I have a batarang.
- Joker.
- What is that song? - Won't do a thang.
- Are you doing Dance Dance by Fall Out Boy?
Is that what this is?
- No, it's also like,
(humming)
Oh yeah, 1985.
- Oh, that's what it was.
- When did Superman become a--
- He got a super car.
- When did Superman eat a--
- There was Mewtwo.
- What would Superman do in 1985?
- Jump and leap a building.
- When did Superman leap a building?
Yeah, you could do that.
When did Batman--
- Who is someone like Mewtwo that rhymes with Blondie?
- Yeah, I never thought about it that much,
but it's not that impressive that Superman
can leap a building 'cause he can fly.
- He can leap anything.
- He can fly over, he doesn't have to leap at all.
- He could leap a puddle.
- He could start in the sky,
he doesn't have to jump over anything.
- Leap fucking whatever.
There's a great scene where she kills herself
he saves her Jane oh by flying around the world Jane drain
Lois Lane Lois Lane and he says around the world no shut up he she just out of
the laser beams she doesn't kill herself you're the you are such a fucking
Superman moron he jumped she jumps out of the purse she wants that she wants him
to set to prove to her that she's Superman or that he's Superman or she
knows and shows he falls out of the window
*laughing*
*screaming*
Shut up! I'm almost talking!
Caleb, you've been like close to crying this whole episode
*laughing*
She falls out of the building
Guys, the best part is, she falls out of the building
and he jumps down
*laughing*
So is that so hard to say?
Caleb, is that so hard to say?
Superman rescues
*laughing*
I swear on my fucking mom's grave, Superman rescues Lois Lane. I would swear on anything.
And there's something about him that she suspects.
That she either knows or has to prove.
Lois Lane actually loves Clark Kent so much, but also thinks that he might be Superman.
She has a suspicion. In the movie.
Oh yeah, and I guess Clark Kent is Superman.
And there's actually one way for Clark Kent to prove that he's Superman is when he's doing something reckless.
so she jumps out of the building and he goes very fast all the way down and puts
her in some fruit. She lands on the fruit basket. I've seen the clip. Oh wait, you have seen that? Yeah, but he makes it look like nothing, like
Super Mario was not involved at all. Oh right, the awning! He blasts the awning with his laser eyes!
yeah what's the yes and then she bounces off and then she bounced off all the way
off
you to you to on YouTube
you to on YouTube music still on you to there was YouTube and Hulu music salon
Spotify and Blondie to be way before
it is TV way before it is free TV
it is free TV Pluto TV doggy went to find
his mommy he was so in love with his
mommy so he kissed her lips
(laughing)
- That was good.
- I couldn't see it happening though.
(laughing)
- Yeah, she had lipstick and red lips.
- Oh man, what a riot.
- Really, really, really truly.
- All right, let's read this fucking list
that I put together in six minutes.
And you can put this on the Patreon, I don't care.
- Pierce's new list.
after after the songs I just sang I don't want to advance.
You don't want to advance? I do not want to advance.
I will not be advancing.
Top 10 hardest things to describe. Yeah, maybe the scene from Superman.
Yeah, I mean, Caleb, honestly, you take an L on that one.
Okay, imagine the situation, a little dark nerd humor.
Imagine the situation where Bruce Kent,
Kent is not Superman in that scenario. Imagine if Clark Kent did not have the
ability to save her with the awning. Prove to me you're Superman, jump out the
window. Meanwhile Clark Kent is he's a normal nerd.
All of a sudden you have a Happy Tree Friends episode on your hands essentially.
Happy Tree Friends, honestly I'm not kidding, the first time I watched Happy
Tree Friends I almost vomited. I got really really sad that the Carpal Tunnel of Love by
Fall Out Boy is the music video is just a Happy Tree Friends episode yeah and I
saw that and I was like why are they doing what is wrong? They should call it
crappy semen the way that it's combining something that is nasty with something
that is cute. Semen is cute? It's young sparkly yeah glistening it is young yeah
Cute things are usually young and so what's younger than semen? I guess semen is young so it's probably cute.
Semen is the youngest you can be. It must be cute. I mean if you zoomed in. I guess it's younger than a baby so it must be cute.
Yeah. Yes. Yeah and I guess crap is disgusting too. No I think that semen is in the... Because it's old.
Because it comes out after food. Food is cute. Crap is old food. That's true.
There's an uncanny valley with the human development where it's from sea it starts at semen and then it gets
That starts at the valley and then as you get to the top, that's the baby and then it goes back down
Babies the top but then then why is it old like that's the adorable?
Cuz like an embryo is it goes back up when you're like a hundred and fifty yeah
Yeah, old people are cute again, and the middle is hot old people are not cute at all
Old people agree look their skin looks like paper not working, and I'm punch right through it
Old people the other day yeah, I bet you were yeah
I was thinking about how it really sucks that we can't just like
Completely put them somewhere
Ever's that old people should be in like we've fallen like extermination. They should go to heaven and it should just be a bouncy cloud
Florida?
Well, no, we do.
I mean, that is--
But I think they should be up.
I think we should be able to throw rocks at them.
Florida, that's a good start, but it's not mandated enough,
and it's too large, and it's on Earth.
Yeah, so you're saying that old people should be at an awning
that we can throw rocks and tomatoes at.
All old people should--
For all of their misdoings--
We should be able to fit 100 million old people
on the head of a pin.
Agreed.
They should be shrunken.
We should compress them.
Yeah.
No, we should compact them.
So that they're so dense that they have gravity.
OK, so we shrink them.
Their bones are already getting small,
we shrink them down downsizing situation down size exactly down and then we put
them all in a big glass bottle that has a ship on it and let me shake it up and
then yeah it's like it's an old people ant farm and let me shake it up that
movie downsizing was one of those movies where I thought I didn't I never saw but
I heard it's terrible but I honestly thought it was gonna be good because of
the song in the trailer and I'm sure I've heard that song why I'm that trailer of
of seeing that trailer in the theater
and like turning to my girlfriend and be like,
we should see that.
And her be like, what are you talking about?
- Just 'cause it has like a good song.
- I looked at it and I was like,
there's something about that trailer
where the first time you watch it,
you're like, oh yeah.
- Oh yeah, I can see that being fun.
- That could be cool.
(singing)
- Downsizing.
- We should listen to this movie.
(singing)
- You will find yourself.
- Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And the days go by.
- What are you talking about?
That was like the most like,
there was like a big like talking heads like,
I don't even know what man that is, man.
There's like, in 2014, in 2014, everyone like,
God, I guess maybe people my age,
everyone was like, oh, like, the docking heads
are like one of the best bands in the world.
I'm gonna docking heads with you.
Yeah, I'm gonna dock my penis head into your nose hole.
Yeah. My nose.
Hole.
Your nose hole, I changed it up, flipped the script.
'Cause I called him out halfway through him
stealing my line.
You have to admire his adaptability.
Your adaptability, yes, his adaptability is impressive.
Give him some points for adaptability.
- Okay, he gets five or six points.
- Okay, good, five or six points to me, Pat.
- I'm gonna squirt a nut in your nose.
- Zero. - They've been removed.
- Yeah. - They've been completely
removed. - Okay.
- Yeah, you went too far. - It's a similar thing.
- It's similar, it's similar. - That's being expressed.
- It's actually similar. - Yeah.
- All right, top 10 hardest things to describe.
- This is scientist-esque, Peter looks at something
and says, "I think this is similar."
- I think this is similar.
This is similar.
These two things are similar.
Moving on.
All right, what do you guys think about water
being hard to explain?
- I feel like I could easily explain it.
- Yeah.
- Soda with no bubbles and clear.
And no flavor.
Flavorless water. - I guess I would say--
- Anyone who can-- - It's this.
- Yeah, look here. - That is what I would say,
a bottle. - But anybody--
- No! - I would say anybody
that you have to explain water to
is not worth talking to. - Exactly.
- I think anyone who can understand anything,
water's the first thing they learn.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, like Helen Keller learned wah-wah.
That was like her big word. - She is.
- Wah-wah was her big word? - Yeah, she was from Philly.
(laughing)
- Wah-wah? - Her big word was wah-wah.
That's the end, the final scene of Miracle Workers.
- Why did they teach her,
I thought she could like read and write.
- Why do they, we're gonna teach her to say wah-wah.
- Why not teach her to use the next word?
- The next word, the next word.
- Wah-wah, then hokey.
- She's a full adult, they're like, okay.
- Wah-wah.
- This is wah-wah.
- That's how they taught her, they talked to her.
- This is gaga.
- Well, she was running around the house just going, wah!
And they were like, we have to teach her a new word.
- We have to hand her something.
- Say wah and then wah again.
- Man, that honestly is like a complete, impossible word,
it's an impossible quiz question to me,
is how did they make her talk?
- Well, so the misunderstanding about Helen Keller
is that she was just Frankenstein,
that she was just running around.
I think that's what everyone thinks,
is that she was just running around.
- That's what I think, yeah.
- Yeah.
- She could kinda see and she could kinda hear,
and she was just like.
- Yeah, well she was like,
she got like scarlet fever as a baby, right?
And then it like fucked up her vision and her.
- She has a permanent cloudy brain.
- Yeah.
around the house and like sewing and she wasn't just but I do think about like a
boy Helen Keller a lot and that would be what he would be go because he think it
was funny yeah just running through a pain glass door yeah he's holding it
you know oh my friend god damn oh he's my friend I can't do that like that just a
minute I think it stopped work I think it's when you shook your friggin arms
around like a Elmo.
Just take this for a minute.
Water. Well...
Shake your arms around like when Kermit gets excited.
Well, it's like wet nothing.
Okay, don't shake your arms around like Frankenstein anymore.
No more steining.
Water is well like wet nothing.
Unless you want to go into the chemical compositions,
which I don't.
It's very complex.
It's apparently... it's tripartite.
I don't want to go any further than that.
I like this username here.
- B-boy making with the freak.
(laughing)
B-boy making with the freak.
- What does B-boy making with the freak say, Pat?
- A clear, flavorless liquid
that makes up 70% of your body.
Also, it's fun to say.
- Is water that fun to say?
Some people do have a funny way of--
- When I was a kid-- - You say "wooder"?
- I said "wooder" because my grandfather was from New Jersey
and I never said it like that, but that's how he says it.
But then one day I was like--
- That must be a South Jersey thing.
- I was like, you know what,
I'm gonna start talking like Pete.
And then I started going "wooder"
And then my mom was like, "Why are you talking like that?"
And I was like, "Eh, it's granddad.
"He basically rubbed off on me."
- Yeah, it's like when, like,
I didn't have a Boston accent as a kid
and then I tried to pick it up.
- You ever have the guy who has
the really specific speech impediment
that only really smart people have,
where they say "wather"?
Like, "wather"? - Wather?
What?
- This tiny little wisp that--
- Wather?
They also have a wisp.
- They have a tiny wisp, but they don't--
- Really smart people?
- Yeah, like autistic people have a certain kind of lisp
that no one else has and it's like a lateral lisp
but only in the middle of words on T.
- And you say water? - It's like a soft T.
- Do you have any other word examples?
Thistle?
- No, I don't know what that is.
It's just a word that begins with T-H.
Oh, Harry Potter.
- Harry Potter?
- Right, so usually, very smart people
usually talk about Harry Potter.
- Yeah, I love Harry Potter.
- I love Harry Potter.
- Harry Potter is my favorite book.
I love Harry Potter and I love the scene where he goes in the water
The gifted kids you remember the same sentences like this no
Okay, this may have been why I was not in a single gifted class
I got kicked out of get six. I said it was too hard. Yeah. Yeah, you're right
I got kicked out of my slow class because I
Being too funny. Yeah, which is that you got some good competition. I know it's me
is my math concepts class where we made a tortilla covered in cinnamon sugar oh
yeah you've talked about that talked about it before as me and four other
kids paper is the stuff that's usually used to write usually well as I'd say
it's flatter than anything it's flatter than God it's flatter than goddamn
- Damn, that's what I would say.
- Yeah.
- If I had a cigar, I was a military.
- Paper's flat as fuck.
- It's flat as all fuck.
- It's like if a big fat guy sat on a normal sized thing.
- On a woman.
- On a white cube.
(laughing)
- Imagine a white cube that you can write all over,
and then a big fat guy just sits on it.
- One pane of a white cube.
- I would say it's the opposite of a pencil.
- One plane.
(laughing)
- It's not the opposite.
- It's the opposite of a pencil.
- That's how I would explain it though.
- You're right, yeah, you're right.
- It's a slice.
- It's a slice of a tree.
- It's a slice of paper.
- Did I tell you about my math teacher in sixth grade
used to say, "Fresh slice of paper."
And he would lick his lips like that.
I've definitely talked about my sixth grade math teacher.
- I think you have told me that before.
- Yeah, the deluxe hugs guy.
- Oh yeah, you've talked a lot about deluxe hugs.
Never got one, by the way.
- If I say like, "Oh yeah, my math teacher in sixth grade
usually give me deluxe hugs with like no context sounds like I got no context
folks our slash no context that's gonna get sounds like I got molestered this
one isn't that good the internet we'll just say it well it's the internet and
then read it well to say it's an amazing and horribly addicting worldwide
communication is a pretty fair description to me
I would say it's what's in the computer. It's the
Fucking evil that's good. I would maybe I would say it's the magic that binds these devices right yeah, I can do a wizard
It's basically water. It's like magic. Yeah, okay, so imagine
Imagine everything on this list is being described to a wizard right traveled in time well
Then I don't know I would say it's like what happens when you do the spell internetus
I would say I would say why are you why am I explaining jack shit to a wizard?
Explain explain jack shit right now to turn my sister and explain what Jackson is jack shit is when I
Don't know actually
Jackson is like fuck all
But what's fuck all?
You know you know what actually I would do if I was explaining any of these to a wizard as I would say
Understandus and then he would understand it. Yeah
Knowledge, knowledge abyss. Or I would make tell him you should use understandus on yourself. Knowledge abyss. Knowledge abyss is good too.
What is that? Go back to jack shit?
What?
Anything at all. Hmm.
Jack shit.
You made it Tom.
Jack shit. Jack shit. Jack shit. Jack shit.
Jack shit.
Number four is colors.
Colors are indescribable. They're not indescribable.
indescribable red looks red looks well red red looks like a combination you can
point it should yeah orange but to a blind guy I guess you have to say colors
are impossible to explain or a smell right but it's that's all I would say
but it uses light yeah which is a concept and an energy what can you taste
purple yeah if you have a purple candy what's that thing called synesthesia
yeah so that is fucking only geniuses have that yeah what is what color is
three oh three is orange for me it's yellow because P rhymes with yellow
everything is yellow and three runs with P and three runs with P three is black
on a white background yeah yeah all right I have that with like skateboard
tricks though to me like a tray flip is green to me red is a color purple okay I
wish that all skateboard tricks were red and yeah yeah that's a kickflip
kickflips are red he'll flips are blue you read pretty soon would you be
fucking so terrifyingly sad if you died in a skateboarding trick yeah not even
really an accident like just like you just died in a trick yeah I tried I
finally one day try to like jump down a stairs has anyone died during a trick
yeah who never oh no no Jake Brown almost died so nobody has them not during a
trick cuz doesn't the trick last for the time that you're in the air yeah like so
you could have a heart attack in the middle of it yeah but has that happened
Patrick who has died during a trick there has to be so I know there's
somebody there has to be somebody there's got to be somebody has round
- Like, uh, what's that? - 2007 X Games.
- Lin Bias, that basketball player, died on the court.
- Oof. Could be like that.
- Has there ever been-- - There's definitely somebody, it's probably not, like, it's probably just like some local, like,
- Probably X Games, I would imagine. - Big-ass ramp.
- No, there's been no deaths, there's been near death at the X Games.
- There's been near death experiences. - Near death experiences, yeah.
- Yeah. - That's none of the--
- I was there, I saw an angel, I jumped high enough that I saw an angel and a beam of light.
The near-death experience is like it was always like the X Games it was like
motocross near-death experience then skateboarding so if you are you saying
it's like an event at the X Games? No, that's what you're saying. I was also
completely spaced out I didn't realize you were talking. Oh you were having a
near-death experience? I was looking at my arm. Yeah. Oh were you? Anything new? I thought I was
wearing a watch but I'm not and I was like it feels like I'm wearing a watch I
I looked down, I'm not wearing a watch.
- That's a near death experience.
- I wasn't checking the time or anything,
I just was like, I wonder if I'm wearing a watch.
- Yeah, you feel the world's tiniest
phantom vibration every second.
- No, I just felt like there was a watch on my wrist.
- Yeah, you feel the phantom vibration
of the second hand moving?
- No, just like the feeling of a watch.
- Okay.
- Like something on your wrist.
- Yeah.
- Okay, the round part.
- Caleb, do you like that part of wearing a watch
is feeling the second hand move?
- On my digital watch, motherfucker?
- Oh, swag.
- Yeah, shut up, man.
I've never had a ticker. Oh somebody has died doing a skateboard trick.
Oh, you just knew that for no reason right now. Yeah. Oh, I was about to look up has anybody died. Who was it?
Yeah, some people have died like bombing hills
Yeah, I think that that's a little more dangerous than a normal trick
Yeah
Yeah, somebody it's like somebody in San Francisco got like hit by a car. That's actually really did with the press
I mean, it just really depressed me
That made me so sad thinking about that thing about somebody dying think about somebody dying like we're skateboarding cuz it's like you were
That's so sad never seen you
Be like this about death. Yeah, I think about how much fun
It would be to die doing what you love going fast. I know that's what's so depressing about it
You know what's depressing is dying a loser getting shot in the brain by a stranger for cash. Yeah
Yeah, you know what sucks is dying in a fire
freaking dying in a fire
We're dying by
You're the hand of your loved one. Oh my god. That's sad unless you okay
This is brought my spirits back up because this sounds like my ass
This is how you would describe it to someone who's never eaten before
Food is the nicest thing in the world
Is that why sure is that what triple like 3xs it means like pornography and stuff is all kisses no hugs
It's because you end up saying sex twice
X there's a lot of hugging in port really hard and they barely touch mouths to each other. Yeah
Not a lot of eye contact
Not in the porn. I watch I only watch the Cinemax porn. Yeah
They kiss way too much in the cinematics porn man. There used to be one called bikini Frankenstein. He said jack off there was a
No, Frank is on the entire show a lot of bikinis. I caught I think
the teeny bikini the ghost in the teeny bikini yeah parody of ghost in the shell vibes I
Caught my brother watching that
Okay, go go back. Oh, I guess she acts a little bit like Frankenstein
Yeah, but I also didn't have any of the sound on
- So food and then we can just movies in a pretty difficult to explain it's real
life sounds like the internet on a movie that's what it's like a window window
window okay but how do you explain cuts it's like two windows where you switch
the windows it's like watching a window and you're looking into a different
window yes yeah yes yes yeah there's music and this is what I like to hear
yeah it's like TV it's like TV longer yeah it's like four to five times as
long as it is longer yeah the screen is longer the length you know what I love
it in a theater you know the best part of the Simpsons movie is is when it goes
from normal screen to widescreen yes oh that's good oh and then wait doesn't
- Doesn't Professor-- - Finkel?
- Yeah, doesn't he say something?
- Does that his name?
- On the big screen! - On the big screen!
- Movie on the big screen! - Movie on the big screen!
- Yeah, he does say that.
He does say that.
- Yeah.
- And Homer goes, "Especially you!"
And he points into the--
- He points at my mom.
- Remember, we're doing a Remember show today,
but you guys remember the Simpsons 4D?
- Yeah.
- Remember how many bugs there were in that movie?
- Simpsons 4D is a ride-- - Scary bugs and smells.
- It's a ride at Broadway at the beach in Myrtle Beach.
It's like a 40 experience thing where they do,
they like spray water on you, they shake your seat,
and they have all these effects,
and they clearly had an effect.
They have the effect where it feels like bugs or mice
are running over your feet,
where it does a little blast of air.
- Yeah.
- And they clearly couldn't think of enough uses of it,
because in the Simpsons 40,
there are probably seven to 10 scenes of bugs
jumping out at the screen.
- Yeah.
- Swarming home with eyeballs.
- We're just talking about it being like,
there are, there are no bugs in the show.
(laughing)
There's never once been a bug on screen in The Simpsons.
In The Simpsons 4D, they have probably 1,000 bugs.
There's a lot of bugs.
The most bugs in a Simpsons episode.
By far.
Also, that was fun because the guy who ran it was blind.
And you could tell he was blind.
But we didn't talk about it.
And I was sitting in the--
I could barely even focus on the movie
because I was so excited to tell you guys
that I noticed he was blind.
And we got out, and I mean, he was like,
that guy was actually blind at the beginning.
Did you guys notice?
And he was like, no.
We all noticed.
Didn't say anything I was I didn't know it was weird. I was really excited to tell you guys that I think he's blind
No, I had a duff
Soda oh wait
He did have really small I did have tiny little shorts and then Pierce said he was a werewolf or something
- Huh?
- Maybe I made that up.
- I remember the name.
(laughing)
- I think Pierce did something werewolf-ish.
- We gotta go back, man.
- Yeah, I love her to be.
- Yeah, I really do.
- You got schooled by a group of little kids.
- They were so much bigger than me.
(laughing)
They said, "Dem some girly shorts."
- Whoa, really?
- It's rude.
Rude-ass kids these days, man.
(laughing)
Love is hard to explain.
- Can we, we don't have to do this.
- I wanna know.
I wanna know.
Love's hard to explain.
- No, love, something that can hurt us
or make us feel like someone special
or that we are really important.
Love can be in various ways,
friendship, romance, or in a family way.
Love can take time to appear,
but when it does, you might feel a sensation.
Totally unique that makes us feel the universe
and the most powerful feeling ever.
Love can change the world.
- Facts. - Yeah.
- I agree. - I fucking love love.
- Speaking of synesthesia, I think that love is like red
and pink and maybe a heart shape.
- With white frills around the edges.
- And if I had to do a shape, I'd go with heart shape.
- I don't know why, but to me it tastes like chocolate.
- Yeah, or a sweet heart-shaped candy.
- Or a chocolate-covered strawberry.
- Here's my Neil deGrasse Tyson shit, okay?
So yeah, love can change the world, 'cause anything can.
'Cause everything is a thing.
- Fuck, man. - Yeah, because love is--
- Everything's a thing. - Everything is matter.
- Neil deGrasse Tyson, actually,
technically, everything is a thing.
- It is. - Things can do things.
- That's pretty good. - But, when we get
into things that aren't things,
that's when it gets very interesting.
- Some things are things, other things are not things.
Have you guys seen any of the interviews that Rogan did with him?
Where he just interrupts him and screams at him.
It's so funny! Neil deGrasse Tyson will be like, listening, he'll be like,
"Scientists, like Plato, and Aristotle, Albert Einstein."
And he'll be like, Rogan will be like, "Carl Sagan."
He'll just, "No, no, no, no, no."
It's so funny, dude. He fucking hates him.
It's so awesome.
Yeah, I feel like--
They just had him on Theo Vaughn's podcast.
God bless Theo Vaughn.
Oh yeah, I think Joe Rogan was like, "Why don't we take the salt out of the ocean?"
and Neil deGrasse Tyson was like, "We can, but Joe, Joe, it costs money."
And Joe's like, "Yeah, I guess so, but how much money?"
And then Neil goes, "Think about it. Does it cost more money than doing it the way we're doing it now,
or does it cost less? I think it costs more."
He has an answer for everything, dude.
Money is a thing.
It's how he talks. He also, it's very funny.
Water is a thing. Salt is a thing.
funny to be to be like now doing all these like podcasts and shit because
like that's all he does now because he got accused of being like a creep yeah
that's like he gets accused of being a creep two years ago goes on Rogan like
ten times in two years yeah and just blabbers about nothing instead of having
his awesome animated show yeah what I like about a guy like that is always
like I'm there there's scientists they're not like it's not like oh I I
I know about like gravity and astrophysics.
Like I'm weighing in on everything.
- Yeah. - I'm doing it all.
- Show me the beakers.
- If you say something about plants,
I'm calling you out on that.
I don't study plants, but I, you know,
plants are actually, they're green because of chlorophyll.
Just so you know.
(laughing)
- He's a genius. - My job is space.
- He's a super genius.
Yeah, wasn't his entire job, he worked on a telescope?
- It's gonna cost a lot of money to take salt out of the ocean.
- Or no, he worked at like a fucking planetarium
or something. - Yeah.
- Probably handling like when they would do
a Metallica light show.
- He would program the lights.
- How did he get as big as he did?
- Funny face.
- It's like working, it's like--
- Oh, that was after.
- No.
- It's like a guy who works at Wendy's or something
and he goes and orders at McDonald's and he's like,
just so you know, that's not how you make
the Wendy's square burgers.
- Yeah.
- Those are supposed to be square.
- He's a man, dude.
- I love him.
- He's cool.
- Love is gravity.
- Numbers.
What is numbers?
Numbers is numbers.
- Numbers is numbers.
- Yep.
you describe it. Don't you dare say seven eight nine right now. Yeah imagine my
finger doesn't exist but the thing that my finger is representing does exist. How
many of my finger is there? One? That's a number. How did you know that?
I was gonna say. One two three four. I would say one two three four five and six.
But this is I would say this is maybe the first time that this has to be this does
have to be explained to people. People get numbers explained to them all the time.
Yeah as soon as you're a baby. It's not like water you don't have to explain water that much.
but I think you are you recognize that you just need a word for it I think this
is how I would you just have to and then look so to put your put your mug next to
my mug so this is some okay so the things that the thing that the puddings
and the mugs have in common is - but you what's also - is when your cup when you
- When you hold something.
- It's not the sarcophagus.
- When you hold a brown thing in it.
- Okay.
- Oh yeah, two is the brown color.
- Once we get--
- Oh, it's words.
- They have words on them.
- Once we get rid of everything
that is similar about these things--
- Oh, uncovered--
- Wait, wait, wait, okay, see how they're similar now.
- Oh, on the table.
- Now they're dissimilar.
- Right, oh right, now the thing that was similar
about them is no longer similar.
- Yes, I see.
- Right.
- So two means when it's in the room with me.
- This is what, when you guys have beautiful kids,
this is what Uncle Pierce will help out
- I like his teaching numbers and things like that.
- Yeah, thank you.
- I feel like you would scare my kids.
- I don't want you to teach my kids anything.
- What the heck?
You guys can do whatever you want to my kids.
- But I feel like you would be like the kind of like
guy who goes like, "Bah!" at the kids all the time.
- Yeah. - What's wrong with that?
- I mean, it's fine.
- That's what I do. - You need to know to fear.
- Yeah, I know, these two I think are dangerous.
- What are you talking about? - I'm an amazing uncle.
- I'm an amazing uncle too. - I almost got my nephew
an iron.
No, you just videoed him talking about it.
You almost gave a fact shit.
And then you lied about it.
You're gonna give him Truman Show Syndrome.
He's gonna grow up and be like,
"I was on a TV show about an iron."
Yeah.
(laughing)
Are we over time?
I mean, we can't finish this much.
No, chill, bro.
All right, I have to go soon, that's all.
What do you have to do?
I have to go to a meeting.
What meeting?
I have to meet you.
For the show tonight?
No!
How about you eat some meat?
We can go have a lunch.
I'll have some meetings with you guys.
- I actually am pretty hungry.
- Yeah, I'm pretty hungry.
Well, let's zoom through this list real quick.
We got the universe, again, easy to explain.
- Watch out, we got a universe over here.
(laughing)
- It's that simple.
It's so easy.
- All right, let's blow through the rest of these doing that.
- Okay.
- Watch out, we got a reality over here.
- Wait, he has a great face for it.
Look at that, he looks just like him.
- Yeah.
- If you did the line art, it would be it.
- Yeah, you should do a science show called Guess How.
- Hmm.
(laughing)
- Guess how this works.
- Right.
- No, that's too long.
- How does this get guessed?
How does this guess?
- Reality.
- VR guessed.
- Who's guessing?
- Video game development.
- Oh, that is hard, that is really hard.
- That's difficult.
- Yeah, that one's tough.
- I would probably say I guess it's what happens
before the game.
- A video game.
(laughing)
- It's how it gets made.
- Yeah.
- It's how, it's who makes it.
- It's really hard to explain,
but know that a video game needs some period.
- This is something a video game needs.
I'm playing charades.
- All right, we all-- - We're taboo.
- I didn't say. - The Grand Canyon,
a place that is five hours from Vegas,
but Asian tour buses force you to go here
because old Asian people like looking at boring scenery
more than holes with fountains, volcanoes,
and a fake Eiffel, oh, hotels with fountains,
volcanoes, and a fake Eiffel Tower.
- It's only five hours away.
- Wait, what? - I gotta get a tour bus
in Colorado, why are they taking me to Las Vegas?
- Yeah. - Also, yeah,
why are you getting on a tour bus
if you're just trying to get to Vegas, dude?
- Take a plane, or a train, or your car.
- Just don't get on a tour bus.
- I'm so glad this is on here.
It's cool to know that people can't explain this,
'cause I can't explain it.
- Yeah.
- I can explain it.
- Well that guy did.
- A big lump with knobs.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
- That's not what it would be.
- Corn, mm.
- It is an inverse of that.
It's a reverse lump.
- It's small lump.
- It's a large nump with--
- Lobs.
- Yes.
- I guess there is a nump.
- Yeah.
- That kid is so stupid.
A big, it's not big, it's a piece of corn.
- Yeah, it's hardly a lump.
- No.
- It definitely has knobs,
but he should have said a piece of corn.
- Yeah.
- It's a piece of corn.
- It's impossible to explain a piece of corn.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well everyone thought corn was hard to explain
until that kid came along.
- True.
- And he kind of cracked the cone.
- He nailed it.
- He cracked the cone, if you will.
- 17 justice.
That was not so.
- It's the opposite of injustice.
- Yeah, well.
(laughing)
- A little clown.
- No, he's not little.
Gravity.
- It takes you down.
- Equals MC squared.
- So, music.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
In what order?
- It makes you dance.
It sounds like this.
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
- I have one way to describe music.
♪ Oh yeah ♪
And also,
(beatboxing)
- No, that's crap.
- Yeah, that's a rhythm, not music.
- Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
But what makes music?
- The end, I think.
- Rhythm and motion, or sounds.
Okay, well, Pierce, thank you for coming on.
You can eat your snack pack now if you'd like.
- All right. - Yeah, you can do your thing.
- Do you have anything you wanted to tell anybody
about our plugin anyway?
- No, not yet. - No, no, no, he's not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, thank you.
Okay, goodbye.
Goodbye, no, no, no, that's enough of you.
No, that's enough of that snack pack.
And we're not having any of these.
What?
- I was trying to show off how liquidy it got under the heat.
- Don't do it again.
What are you doing?
It's trying to ruin the table.
Under the heat. What heat do we have here?
Oh god, dude.
He's eating it.
You can't even see it. You're doing it in the worst...
Ugh.
Now, someone's got a macchiato.
No, it's over. It's over.
It's more over than it's ever been.
It's over.
...podcast about List, including Jubio and Patches.
A happy
season.
Holiday greeting. Bye bye!