They're supposed to call soon. I'm pretty excited. I don't know. I'm not sure if I got it. Oh my god. This is it. Okay, hold on one second.
Hello?
Hello, am I speaking to Mr. Cameron Fetter?
Yes.
Hi Mr. Fender, I'm just calling to let you know that we've accepted your application to be a volunteer usher at the Women's Choir.
Oh my god! I can't believe it!
Are you there sir?
Yes, yes, uh, you can count on me, okay? I'm gonna be a great usher, I've wanted this my whole life.
Okay sir, do you have the address?
Yes I do.
Great, we'll see you on Sunday at 3.15.
Thank you so much!
Oh my god, I'm going to be an usher
I've always wanted to be an usher. So over the years I've practiced a lot. Sir, your seat is right this way.
Welcome into the show. Here's a program. Your seat is right this way
Sir, this is a counterfeit ticket. You need to leave get out immediately out
You might not expect it from looking at me. But yeah, I clean up good
[MUSIC]
[Music]
Now baby, that's right
We got nothing but time
You get all the reactions
You're the main attraction
It's no surprise
Gotta like your style
You're the perfect distraction
The main attraction
(upbeat music)
And barely even 24 hours after my massive success
as an usher at the choir,
I actually landed the gig
that every amateur usher dreams of.
That's right, I went big time
and I now work full time as an usher at McDonald's.
- How much time do you think you can sit
wherever you like today?
How much time do you think you can sit
wherever you like?
I think so.
You can sit anywhere you like. There's no assigned seats today.
You won't see a seat number on your ticket.
You see...
Go on in.
If you have a ticket, you can go straight in.
I'm a celebrity, and even I know I should help the community.
[Music]
Okay.
Oh my god.
Leave that in. You have to leave that in.
Do it again.
My god dude.
Can you believe that?
That was unreal bro.
You are the worst.
No I'm not.
You fucking suck at everything.
That was insane.
If you weren't doing this what do you think you'd be doing for a job?
The restaurant.
Probably still work at a restaurant.
Were you good at working at a restaurant or were you terrible?
I was alright.
I worked front of house.
You were like a hostess?
Yep.
He was a hostess.
He had on a skirt.
All black.
I wore like a black like polo shirt.
- It's so funny that they just picked the hottest waiter
and to say you're the hostess now.
That is really funny.
And you walk in and you're like, yeah.
- Thank you for saying that about me.
- No, not you. - The hottest waitress.
- You were at a reverse restaurant.
- I was not at a reverse restaurant.
- Yeah, you were at a reverse restaurant.
- You were not at a regular restaurant.
- The only backwards thing about the reverse-a-rant
is that the ugliest waitress is the hostess
and everything else is the same as a normal restaurant.
- The food's normal.
They don't walk backwards or anything.
- Yeah.
If you want a restaurant where they walk backwards,
you need to go to Backwardsies.
- Mm.
- Have you guys ever been to Dick's Last Resort?
- No, I'm too scared.
- I really am scared.
- Actually, no, I haven't gone.
- I feel like I would go.
- I've been in the vicinity of one.
- Even when you're in the vicinity,
you feel like the evil tendrils spreading out.
- There's a dark evil presence.
- It's like the Lord of the, it's like Mordor.
There's like a fucked up, you can see people leaving it
and you're like, oh, this is this evil space.
- Purple things like veins or trunks just like come--
- Yeah, exactly.
- Just roots through the ground.
- Yeah, it's like in a movie when someone gets bitten
by a zombie or something, there's like black veins
going up their arm, it spreads out into the rest of the area.
- I remember we were planning on going there just to cry.
I remember like, I think me and Neil were like,
we should go there and just like when they start
doing the thing, just be like,
can't you fucking see that I've already
had a hard fucking day?
- It's scary, it's scary to go there, yes.
it's gotta be even scarier to work there as a waiter.
- Oh, for sure.
- Especially these days with cancel culture.
- Oh my God.
- Getting canceled at Dicks.
- No, I do feel like,
how, what do you think the percentage is
on people who go in and they just don't,
they're completely blindsided?
How many people do you think go in there
and are like, have truly no idea,
and even are maybe oblivious enough
that they don't see it happening at other tables
where they're waiting for their, to order?
- There is a new one.
There's a dicks that's all women in the UK called Karen's.
- No way. - Yeah.
- Dude, we have to go. - I just remember that.
- Oh my God. - What do they do?
- What do you think they do?
- They probably ask to talk to the manager.
- Yeah. - They ask the customer.
- Dude, oh my God.
- I don't know. (laughing)
- It's like, can I have a hamburger?
And they're like, can I speak to your manager?
I'm like, I don't have a manager.
- The worst thing in the world.
- You're just gonna ask, he doesn't work here.
- Wait, wait, wait, you want me to call Staples
and talk to the manager?
Yeah, I guess you can do that.
- The worst thing in the world,
The Karen is the manager.
No fucking way.
Yeah.
Nightmare scenario, bro.
It's like when, uh, it's like those like, what if Marvel comics?
Exactly.
Yeah.
It's like, what if
dude, that's Darth Jar Jar Binks.
The manager is a Karen.
What if the manager was a Karen?
It's like an a hundred page comic of just the, yeah.
And all those comics, it's always like, it's the, the question is always,
It's always like what, yeah, the question is always,
what if this character was evil
and the whole comic's just him,
that character killing every other character?
- Yeah. - What?
- It's always the same. - This is a Marvel they do?
- Yeah, they always do a What If.
- What if, well, sometimes also it's like,
what if this person was a girl?
- What if Wakanda was all whites?
(laughing)
- Have they done that one?
- No.
- They've done an all white Wakanda?
Whites.
(laughing)
What if it was whites?
- I think they did, they did make--
- That means that Patrick would say,
Patrick's like, Wakanda's all blacks now.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Wakanda changed from when I grew up there.
When I grew up, it was all Italians.
It was all Italians and Irish.
And yeah.
- It's gonna change over there.
Hey, I'm not saying it's good.
- I think there is like a,
somebody made it, it's like pretty recent,
but they made like a Rhodesia equivalent to like Wakanda.
I don't remember what the name is,
but it's like, it's so insane to just be like,
like a fictional Rhodesia that like borders Wakanda
or something.
- Yeah, one of the funniest parts of Marvel to me
is that like they have this,
their whole thing is like, okay, it's superheroes
and we have outer space too,
and we have magic and wizards.
And also we're gonna make up a few countries
that are interesting.
- Yeah, like Moldova?
- Yeah, Doctor, yeah, exactly.
(laughing)
Doctor Doom comes from a made up country too.
And he's just like,
- Where does he come from?
- I don't know, I don't remember the name of it.
- Oh, it starts with an S, Sokovia.
- Is it Sokovia?
- I think so.
- But yeah, anyway, they're just like,
we're just gonna come up with a few countries
that have, sound like they could be in these areas.
- Latveria.
- Latveria, yeah, exactly.
- I think Sokovia is a real place.
- Sokovia is a Marvel thing too.
- Yeah.
- But yeah, it is just like, we're just,
basically it's like, so we have superheroes.
So I guess what the next thing we have to come up with is,
where are the countries where superheroes are kings there?
Yeah, why do they come up with different?
Why does DC come up with different cities too?
Like why do they have Gotham and Metropolis?
That's true.
You know what's so funny about...
No, no, Metropolis is supposed to be like Maryland.
It's supposed to be in Maryland.
Man, shut your bitch ass up.
It's not even in Chicago.
It's like, who the fuck is like thinking like...
Yeah, and it's like, you have guys like Superman
and it's like, why not just have like Bill Gates?
Yeah.
And he's powerful yeah, you have him in there. Yeah, he's called Lex Luthor
I would say it's not a great close up on your middle finger that we just got right there. Oh, you could maybe move it
Yeah, that's not
We're not fucking curing
Bill gave I'm doing that bill water if Bill Gates got a superpower
Maybe he could do something with doors or gates or something like lock doors, but dude he would
You know you know he doesn't need a superpower for that. He's already doing stuff with dorks all day
Yeah, you know I would those lines that say post no bills uh-huh he could post bills
Damn, it could be his superpower. Oh good bill bills
On gates on gates
Bill Gates Bill Gates
Windows anything to do with oh my god name flyer no, it's the add is
Seattle's
Seattis yeah, Superman. Yeah, I have my cousin. Well. You know ghost riders name is Johnny Blaze
He's on and he's on fire, and he's rides it
You know the only reason why I'm pushing back against this is human torch was the implication of what my or no
What's who's done who there's Johnny Blaze is human torch. No. He's Johnny storm Johnny storm
See that don't make no fucking sense that doesn't make any sense
The only reason I'm pushing back on this is the implication of what my superpower would be I think yeah, you can make pits
- No. - You can make holes in the ground.
- No, moving on to the next topic of the day.
- What? No. - Yeah, okay, well, yeah,
my superpower would be a fuckin' thing.
- You would be the same as Bill Gates.
You'd also have a door power. - Yeah.
- A door and-- - I could open any door.
- Door and another power. - You could stink like a durian.
- You could stink like a-- - I get another power?
- Dude, you could be spiky. - And that's my power, yeah.
- Dude, the durian would be such a good super--
super spiky and super stinky. - Smells like shit.
If you kill him, he smells like shit.
- You could squirt stink pods around the--
stink pot. We should start a superhero universe. I was thinking about getting a
durian for an episode, bringing a durian, we all eat one, but they're like $95 to
get one. And also they smell fucking shitty and there's no windows in here.
Ice cream bean. Well, once we get Bill Gates. Once we get Bill Gates in here. That's true dude, he'd create
windows. He could create a window or a gate. Window man. What was yours be?
Fetter. You can get fatter. Oh Cameron Fatter. You can get fatter like the blob. How have we never
talked about that? Oh we've talked about that because I told you what the meaning
of my name. My last name. I thought it was Peters. Fetter, well Fetter, the etymology
of fetter means fat man. Oh yeah fat criminal right? It's like is there fat
man or thief or something. Last night I was talking to me and Noah were talking
about a friend of ours my buddy AJ and he his middle name the way he got his
middle name is that is while his mom was giving birth I just heard this story
last night for the first time well his mom was giving birth he she passed out
from like the epidural or the pain or some shit she passed out and her the his
His dad, her husband, just filled out the birth certificate while she was passed out.
They had agreed on this whole name that was her grandfather's name for his first name,
and then his middle name was going to be her brother's name.
No, listen.
The dad's name was Arthur.
While she's passed out, he names him Arthur, first name Arthur, not what they agreed on.
He gives him his own first name.
wakes up and she looks at the birth certificate she's like wait okay so you
named him Arthur what is his middle name why is it just the letter A?
Yeah I couldn't think of anything. So AJ's middle name is just A. It doesn't mean anything.
I do know I knew somebody in high school who she told me her like legal name was
P like dot. P diddy. P dot. Like period. What? Yeah. P dot? P dot. That's cool. Yeah that's
like a. I be having a P dot when I walk out of the bathroom. Yeah. I don't shake. We were
just talking about how that's like. Me and Noah were talking about how that's gotta be
like a huge red flag at a bar he's at if he hands them their ID. Oh yeah. He just says
A. A. I keep talking about your middle names A. Have you seen those videos of like bouncers
just snapping people's real IDs in the app because they don't know what they are.
Dude, I always think that that's going to happen because my ID is so shitty.
Yeah.
I always have that feeling when I'm like somewhere where I have to fly back home.
I'm like, "Fuck, you're going to fuck me in the ass."
That almost happened to me at the bodega where the guy, he asked for my ID when I was buying
beer and I gave him my ID and he pointed to Massachusetts on it. He was like, "Where is
this from?" I was like, "Massachusetts." He was like, "Where is it from?" I was like,
"Massachusetts. What do you mean?"
You got ID at a bodega?
Yeah, it's and it's it's a crazy L because it's the one next to my house that I go to
So I think he got in trouble or something at some point, but I bought beer there so many times
I would just show a bouncer this
That's what I've literally had to do that before if they don't believe my idea. I'm gonna take my hat off and go I'm
Dude it is it is humbling getting like
Carded when you look like this you look like this
It's like oh, well not humbling, but like you know it's
I guess it makes it makes you it's young going no it just makes it makes you young
yeah I guess it makes me feel a little better getting carded cuz I'm just like
oh thank God thank God somebody doesn't think I'm 35 I don't think you're 30 I
don't think so when people find out that I am 25 they're like oh yeah you're just
like a very ugly 25 yeah yeah you're ugly like an old guy mm-hmm but you're
actually yeah people usually I'm usually think I'm 12 to 30 telling people I'm 30
Why? Because then they'll think I look good. People think I'm either 40 or 1 years old usually.
Yeah. Yeah, it's because you're wearing that diaper and that bonnet. And in the crib. It's New Year's.
It's true. Somebody's got to do it. You're going to have to do it for New Year's this year.
Are you going to do it? Yeah, I'm going to do it. I just noticed on the fucking, on that, just how stretched out the picture.
Dude, I love these mugs. I just noticed there's a picture of a cup on the cup.
The mugs are my favorite mugs.
This mug has a picture of an actual mug of coffee.
Like a full mug of coffee.
And they misspelled mocha.
They misspelled mocha and it says short black.
It says mocha multiple times.
One of them just says coffee.
It's fine dude.
It's the best.
It's Colombian.
Everything should have that kind of all over print on it.
Definitely.
So you know what it is always.
Yeah, I just love this because it's like you know you should get this for the coffee fan in your
Yeah
Yeah, coffee
Well, yeah
This is a good coffee cup because you can put any kind of coffee in there someone's like because if this just said
Espresso on it right you can't be drinking a lot. You're gonna look like a fucking asshole
No, I like an idiot. I like that like they put the word espresso
in brown over the brown beans
- Beans.
(laughing)
- No, they designed it very well.
- You can't even fucking see it.
- I think most things should also have
the base ingredients on it.
Like this has the beans on it.
- Yeah.
- Right?
You know, if I get a sandwich from the store,
I want it to have a picture of a loaf of bread on it.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, Noah texted me.
I thought there was something about,
something crazy going on.
- I flipped his phone over.
- Damn, that was, stop!
- I have the thing queued up for later.
- Oh, the thing for later.
I did just read Noah's text really bad.
He's died.
Noah, his weak-ass plate guy, as you guys know him, he has passed away.
Noah has passed away.
Thank God, dude.
Apparently it was from malnutrition.
I was just about to say that.
He just died of malnourishment.
Thank God he's dead.
Never have to see that damn plate again, dude.
I have to see another week as play and Christmas is coming up the holidays ain't over. He's
still got another Christmas play and if he's gonna take a picture and Christmas he's gonna
try and he's gonna fail. He's gonna pull up at Christmas. He's gonna win one piece of
penny and a fucking one leaf of a Christmas tree cookie. And then all of a sudden you
know he gets to be eating the berries off the mistletoe. This is the hardest time of
the year for him because then you got you got a couple of months break but then it's
Easter. Yeah. And even I bet this
the girls that have brought thought he did something with
his Easter basket.
His Easter basket is going to be weak. Oh my
God. I got a single Reese's piece. I am with
a Valentine's heart with one chocolate. Oh Starburst jelly
bean and not a flavor you like. No no no.
You imagine what he was starburst flavor that everyone like
pink. Pink is the one everyone. Oh no the one
everyone hates. Oh red. Yeah. Really. Or yellow. Yeah. I
Yellow is probably the more red is clover red is basically pink. No pink is the good one
I know it's the good one, but I feel like they're
They're not those can't be the best and worst red and pink pink and red you could probably
Make it look like a pussy if you put them all together or a pink and red painting
You know what I did one time when I was a difference between our minds
artistic sexual
Art you know what I did one time as a kid you can do Mario. I took the blue. I took not the blue the
You took the banana blue pillow Nana
Banana laughs he happy and I curled it up, and then I rolled the the pink Laffy Taffy, and I made a Laffy Taffy hot dog
Sell that it is a fucking miracle that you're not 600 pounds. Yeah, it is a fucking miracle
I thought that was so cool. You really I was just playing with my food like it was play-doh
God gave you the fattest brain of anyone I know pretty much.
The way that you think about candy, you go into predator vision in every store that we go into and start picking up candy.
You go into predator vision when you see a woman on the street.
No.
At night.
No. At night maybe. I have a night vision.
Similar to the predator, the only way a woman can escape him is to cover herself in mud.
And even that doesn't work sometimes.
I would say even then he gets hungry because he thinks she's covered in poop that would provoke it
No, the only way to stop me is like
There's three three red dots up here
I wouldn't happen. I wouldn't do that. Yeah
Finally watched predator - yeah speaking of
Nothing is as good as predator one predator one
No, I mean none of the predator movies my
Movie Club it's something I'm gonna be starting great Patrick's movie club and this week
We are watching all of the alien movies nice. Mm-hmm and for my movie club
we are watching Finding Nemo again and
Hopefully this time the mom doesn't die mine and mine will be just watching TV and see what's on
Just see what seeing what's on will just go on Pluto TV and see what's on
I was actually watching part of Mad Max before I came over here on Pluto TV you watch part of it
I always I watch five five to ten minutes of random movies. That's good. Yeah, that's a good
I think that's good. That's how we really need to go back to that
It is I know I like it's so much more fun than rewatching a movie
TV not not everyone having TV and watching movies and shit like that
I think it's definitely changed our brain.
There really is no greater joy than turning on Pluto TV and like Johnny Mnemonic or some
movie.
Some movies on and then you call in your girlfriend you say look this is the part where this happens
and she doesn't care at all.
That's the bit.
Look he's going into the internet.
Dude it's so fucked up that streaming took over cable.
I miss cable.
Dude Pluto TV is the wave.
But it's so expensive.
When my wife dies I would honestly.
No cable.
Pluto TV is a godsend.
I would honestly think when my wife dies that I would like to get her taxidermied so that
I can put her on the couch and explain movies to her forever.
Until I die.
Just sit there and just like, yeah, Fury Road is on.
I'm like, you know they had to delay it a year and a half because grass ruined all streets.
The best part of watching movies with your girlfriend is explaining and telling the behind
the scenes stories and then the second that she asks a question be like, just watch the
movie.
Yeah.
They're going to explain it, just watch it.
some good movies coming out that I can't wait to explain dude fucking every
couple the entire fucking audience is gonna be couples and just guys going
they should have those we think recreated the nuclear explosion those
like audio tours they have in museums yeah or you can get put the head you're
a single woman yeah it was a boyfriend there should be one one single
boyfriend sitting in the back and he has a little mic.
Yeah.
And he talks to every woman in the audience.
It's all just like, "Now I don't actually remember exactly what happened in real life, but Oppenheimer's actually a crazy guy."
It's actually a badass quote from the Bhagavad Gita.
And Christopher Nolan's other movies are crazy.
Yeah.
He plays with time.
He loves to play with time.
He does time stuff.
For example, this episode of movies, the time went backwards into a different time.
Yeah.
There's no way he's not gonna put some damn-ass time stuff in that movie.
For real. Bro, have you seen the previews? It's literally counting down a clock.
Time dilation. He's watching those movies with mind dilation for me.
And I think that it'll be a cry nation. The entire nation will be crying at that movie.
Because they'll be realizing what we did to the beautiful country of Japan.
I somebody why I think I saw a tweet or something about it
But just that it's so funny that this that guy fucking hey, I bet you call him tacos Japan and like she
That's the right you're supposed to pronounce it you think that's funny I'll have a sushi roll
(laughing)
- Going to Japan and just pronouncing everything
like you're trying to like--
- It's sushi.
- Sushi.
- Like you're Peggy Hill walking up.
(laughing)
- There are a lot of Peggy Hills for Japan
in today's day and age.
And they all look exactly like us.
- Not me.
- No.
- Yeah.
- I'm really sorry to say, but probably you second most.
- I don't know anything about Japan, dude.
I'm the least person who cares about Japan.
- But there are a lot of guys who live in Japan.
guys who live in Japan who look like you.
Really?
I don't know anything about it.
Those are the guys who went there, who like got deployed there, and then they were like,
"I'm a cool, I'm a stay here.
This is actually beast here."
I think a lot of the guys who looked like you actually went over to try and get some
damn pussy.
That's fine.
Just tell them the truth.
You can get pussy in any country.
I'm not trying to make a joke, I'm just telling the truth.
Alright.
Well, this is a joke show, so stick to the jokes.
Maybe.
You know how all the Oppenheimer posters have like the built-in timers that count down to
like the movies release?
- I didn't know that.
- Yeah, you can see they have like--
- I just said yeah 'cause I wanted
to move the conversation along, but that's pretty cool.
- I appreciate that.
- Wait, they do?
I also said yeah, I haven't seen that.
- Really?
- They have posters that have ticking time bombs in them?
- You know the big cardboard,
like it's not a poster, but the cardboard stand-ups,
they put in movie theater lobbies?
And they have like, it has like a countdown
to the movie's release, like an actual countdown on it.
And it's so funny to imagine, 'cause anyway,
it's pretty long before it comes out.
Movies like that always get delayed,
so it's very funny to, I really wanna be the guy
to catch them changing the countdown.
(laughing)
Coming in, trying to stay in the theater overnight
and see them switch the timer and be like, I got you!
- I haven't watched the last three movies he made,
but I'm gonna watch that one.
- Yeah, I mean, you've heard--
- Yeah, Tenant, I don't know.
- I didn't watch Tenant either.
- I don't think it's Tenant.
- It's Tenant. - Tenant.
- Yeah. - Tenant.
- Tenant, I'll watch that movie.
- I got a Tenant.
- Tenant is the skate shop down the street.
Thanks Pat.
(yells)
Thank you so much.
And our address is one,
one, one, three,
102 floor.
Can you imagine--
Empire State Building.
Can you imagine if we just gave that address
of the office out?
No, can you imagine being killed by a nuclear bomb?
Yeah, I can imagine that.
Yeah, I imagine that really, really frequently.
Do you think that it would hurt
or just be completely instant?
I think it's instant.
No, it's completely instant.
You think so?
Yeah.
But what if it hurt, what if you survive?
- You don't even get to see the--
- If you're far enough away.
- Yeah.
- Well then there's also the radiation sickness thing
where it's like, oh, if you get enough radiation
but you're not actually hurt,
you feel completely fine for like a week
and then your body falls apart.
- Yeah, that's pretty cool.
- It's called like a walking corpse or something.
There's some phrase for it.
- And if you touch people, they'll get it too.
- Yeah.
- That's so cool.
- I really, really hate the idea of war.
(laughing)
- Is that true?
- I would have to agree with you, unfortunately.
- Especially nuclear war.
- Unless I'm fighting in it.
(imitates gunfire)
'Cause I'm 'bout that.
- Damn. - That's what she said.
- I'm 'bout that for every other country.
- If I saw-- - I'm coming for y'all.
- I saw him on the No Limit tank.
- If I saw a nuclear bomb flying through the air,
I would probably shoot it down.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'd probably just pop some shots at it.
- Yeah. - Fire, fire, fire.
Fire, fire, fire.
(imitates gunfire)
- Dude, yeah, I'd have the silencer on,
so it'd be like, psst, psst, psst.
- People wouldn't even notice.
- They wouldn't even care,
but I'd know that I saved New York.
I'm putting the silencer on so that nobody knows that I'm doing it.
So I'm just kind of like you.
Because I'm doing it.
That's the other thing.
I'm only interested in saving New York because that's my home turf.
And other people, they can deal.
If there are other people in other cities who are about that like me, they can do that
shit.
But I'm not helping you all out.
For sure.
I'm the savior of New York.
They're going to call you.
I'd like throw a grenade.
(mimics gunfire)
- You just hear the same noise eight times in a row.
- And then I go,
(mimics gunfire)
- Damn.
- Star Wars.
- I do get really scared thinking about a nuclear attack.
- There's no reason to be scared
'cause you live close enough to where they would bomb
that you would not know that it happened.
- Yeah, you just instantly die.
- You would have eight minutes
of the worst fear of your life.
- And then die.
- You'd probably call your mom
and then you would be a white light.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And it's probably fun to be light.
- You've already, true.
- I just don't, that's just,
That is gross.
Gross?
Gross as in huge.
Gross in size.
Probably a worldwide conflict.
Wait, are you afraid of death?
Yeah. What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Probably the most normal.
Me, I don't give a fuck about anything.
As a huge monster movie fan,
the nuclear war thing is pretty scary, but I would maybe be more
scared that the nuclear bomb would wake up Godzilla
and he might step on me.
That might be a lot that area that is really scary. I was scared of the bias media coverage true
It's probably would divide us if there was one nuclear bomb that dropped in America
I would rather be the person whose head it fucking goes into and then live so I don't have to watch
Yeah, obviously different fucking the different angles on dude
Can you imagine what what how how fucking divisive and evil Fox News would be about mutants?
Uh-huh, they probably call them the M word about the what word M. What is the mutant?
- Oh yeah. - Beauty.
- Yeah.
- Whoa, you said it.
- Whoa.
- What's made up? - You said it,
we didn't even, barely even had to--
- You made it up so that you could say it though.
- Yep.
- Barely even had to push you into it either.
- 'Cause I'm a piece of shit.
(laughing)
- Really?
- Yep.
- I kinda like that.
I kinda like that. - Yeah.
- Yeah, all right, nah, come on.
Hey, all right, come on.
- This goes out to all the fans.
- No, come on, man.
- Of the show, this goes out to all the fans.
- That is not cool. - Please knock that off.
No, we're gonna change every--
every all right okay here we're gonna we're we're we're good
segue here - we're gonna check in on Santa cuz it's still Christmas it's
still December a Christmas respect a piece of shit screwed did you saw that
great I stopped him in his tracks I flipped don't slap it did not stop me in
my tracks I kept talking what does stop me in my tracks mean to you use you you
pause I paused in my tracks stop it are you scared that time I smacked you I was
Really hammered and I just like fucking just yeah, I was talking about that last night
You better not beat the shit out of you. Yeah, you did you smacked that shit out of me. Oh, I did
Yeah, I'm a good guy got in a slap fight. Yeah
Yeah, I would kill you yeah, I know
I know I don't know why I think I hear the one the other person I think about when I'm in the gym
Yeah, yeah, I think about fucking killing you. I did it this morning. I was literally
Patrick ever fucking try anything I just like a fucking like like like just like Batman montage of you training anything about Bane breaking your
Slapping the back of your head. Yeah, I just think about all the time. God. I would kill you. Yeah. Yeah, no
I don't actually think about I think about my entire fucking family getting raped and murdered. Yeah. Yeah, I don't think about that ever
I do know I there's a change in you're changing what you think about there's a there's a couple people
He thinks about getting buff for other guys at the gym. That is actually
There's this one guy who is so hot and I sit there and I'm like man
I just want him to give me a compliment or like slap my ass or something
But there I do know a couple people who they're like, yeah when I'm in the gym
And they're always like really skinny guys or aren't very good at weightlifting. They're like when I'm in the gym, dude
I think about fucking my fucking brothers getting their throats lit. It's like you're a psycho. Yeah
Yeah, you're lifting weights because you were a crazy person you're not doing it for the right reason. Yeah, you should
Girls don't give a fuck about no the gym girls want a guy to be
It's gross. Yeah, I don't I don't think about that kind of stuff when I go to the gym usually I think about my whole
Family getting you know
Defiled and their throats like when I'm cleaning my house
This is a get a really good scrub just get in there. Yeah, this is his face
(laughing)
I just think about all that crap before I go to bed
and then I get super scared.
And I wake up happy.
If you're buying clothes to impress women,
you're doing it wrong.
If you're going to the gym to impress women,
Posting music on your Instagram story
to impress a woman, you're doing it wrong.
That's right, it's all for the boys.
It's for the fellas.
You always--
And for God.
Working is also, it's not even for most guys.
It's not even for like gay guys that you could fuck.
No.
Because they also don't care.
No, it's for your--
It's only for straight guys to look at you and go--
That guy is awesome.
You can't even have sex with those guys
that you're impressing.
No, it's just for them to go, oh.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, this guy likes a--
It's the same, it's when you're at a museum
and you see a guy, you go like this at a painting.
That's what you want.
There's a buff janitor at my gym, and he's so buff,
I'm always like man. I want him one day to
I'm sitting there jail drinking gel
Water yeah, you don't want to fuck with me. I'm sitting there drinking water out of the water fountain bro sitting at the water fountain
I'm at the water fountain. I'm getting water. He walks out of his janitor closet, and he looks at me. He just started laughing
I was like, and I wanted to be like, okay, you're a janitor.
And you deserve it.
I don't even know what he's buffing at.
A buff janitor at the gym, do you think that he was...
Oh my god, you came too far away.
Do you think he was like a janitor, he was a janitor by trade and he was like, I really,
really want to work at a gym.
Maybe.
Because I like working out.
He also got, you know what I think it was, he clearly just got like a hair transplant
because it hasn't grown in yet.
So I think he looked at me and he was like, pfft, baldy.
Right or maybe the follicles are in his brain. What am I good friends in high school was the janitor really?
Yeah, Bruce are usually pretty good people all is there stink?
Yeah, and there and there's usually sometimes they've killed they look pretty good
Name, I don't know if I should say that guy's full name on
Last name which was a rum janitor rum shot. Oh, yeah, his name was Bruce Janitor
My friend Alex worked he worked at the the school in the summer. He was like a janitor's apprentice
That's a good that was a good like there's a good job. You could get you only work in this summer a couple days
Janitor's apprentice imagine what nasty shit they make him the apprentice did yeah the Janitors already sucking turds out of a toilet
They probably make him build the mod that wasn't the official job title
That's what I called it. I called him janitor's apprentice all right. Well. Okay. Let's see where Santa is right now
- Wow, it's Christmas month, it's Christmas month.
- It's December 21st.
- Okay, so he's on Earth still, guys.
- Thank God he's on Earth.
- Where is this?
- Where is that?
- I know this, this is the Holy Land.
- Oh my God, he's on, where?
- This is Mecca. - Oh my gosh.
- He's on Aege. - He's at Mecca.
- Aege. - Hajji.
- Aege. - Hajji beats.
- No, it's Aege. - Oh, look at him.
- Wow. - Wow.
- So I wonder what that means for Christmas this year.
- I bet this isn't even in Saudi Arabia, Jupiter.
What? That's clearly Saudi Arabia.
Whoa!
Holy crap.
Santa!
There he is.
Santa's converted.
That's amazing.
We don't know that he was Christian in the first place.
That's true.
I guess we don't.
Maybe he's-- yeah.
He was delivering it all over.
He's giving it all over.
That's true.
He probably didn't-- probably he--
I mean, well, yeah.
He wouldn't be Christian because he's not getting presents.
It wouldn't be anything in it for him.
Yeah, so he can still be Muslim.
He can be--
He probably was Muslim the whole time.
He can be agnostically atheist.
No.
Like me?
Too far.
Not cool.
I'm agnostically atheist.
No.
I recently converted to that.
Okay, I don't even want to.
Ask me any scientific question and I can answer it.
Why is water blue?
Not my fucking problem.
I'm gonna ask your phony baloney god.
He told me.
Yeah, he told you what?
Because it reflects the sky.
How does it feel knowing you're going to hell?
Feels fucking dope.
Hang out with fucking Elvis and fucking Hitler.
in heaven. What? I don't want to hang out with Hitler. I don't want to hang out with him.
Elvis though. Elvis is in heaven. Do you think Elvis and Hitler get along in hell? Yeah.
And Michael Jackson too? No, I don't think Michael Jackson and Hitler are fighting. Well,
I think at first. Oh, very nice to meet you. Very nice to meet you sir. Hey, those dance
moves you're doing are amazing. You look so beautiful. I love the color of your eyes and
your skin yeah wait a second hold on wait
no Hitler wouldn't say that you probably would he probably would if at the very
least he wouldn't say it in English yeah but I don't know whatever he spoke yeah
what are you doing your hand trying to remember German this was yeah wait what
that was how you started to remember German you know I started playing I
I played a golf game one of those golf simulator game golden dude
The only way that you can get a good swing on golden tea is if you end on a full fucking heil
Every single time and so and we were all you can curve your arm at the end
But then you look kind of close your hand into a fist at the end. Oh, you're prudent you go full Superman
Yeah, that's a good point
Yeah
But I caught myself multiple times like looking at the screen and then my brother was like you're just doing a full
Thing and I was like oh fuck and it's not even your turn you didn't even yeah
I can't even do that do that with that. I know I know
Haircut is a strong word for my head. I would say yeah, you cut it all off
Okay
Yeah, you're right
Okay, so yeah, where's me? Yeah?
You you go. Oh Camry goes first. Oh, no. I first men. I'm not gonna go first cuz that you guys have oh
Yeah, yeah, so it goes first so today. We have listen holiday season. We're in the midst of it, and if you don't have your presence yet
It's Christ's ember. Yeah, it's fucking the December 21st, man. If you don't have your presence yet four days away. We'll help you out
Okay, so here's some last-minute gift ideas for everybody in your family. What do you think of this though?
I only had what that
That's not a good gift idea is that let you oh you look kind of like Vince Vega
Right mm-hmm. That's kind of how you're moving. Yeah. Oh just remember
I, somebody spilled their drink on me at an open mic the other night and it was
like the last person so like nobody else was like me and three other people. You
should blast to that person. No, but they they were like performing and then like
looked in the crowd and all they saw was me going like trying to rub the drink
off of me. So it's like a dead room just like me going like that. Doing a hee-hee
ho-ho belly rub. Like it's like, "Hoo, these jokes are filling!"
I only have one gift because, and this was, I figured that I'd handle the ones
for the, yeah, for the daddy. Sure. So I got a, I just got a one daddy gift that I
think would be good for any daddy. You can go ahead here,
GBO. This is Major Load, ultimate test booster for men, male enhancing pills,
enlargement supplement men's high potency endurance drive and strength
booster this is a 30-day supply Wow 2177 you save 10% if you buy multiple of them
it's from this guy on the cover yeah he looks cool flavor is berry you can
really tell by the major load berry that I guess that guy is major load if I had
To guess maybe his last name is Barry
Barry load oh
Barry low major Barry look he used to be barely load until he started taking this supplement go next year
Here's some reviews five-star review from Esteban it the bond really increased my semen load sick
I'm 50 years old and my loads were reduced to few drops or almost nothing
Major load increased my loads to a nice shot anytime I come and I see the word come is
Highlighted as if you searched for it here. No. No, I hate come I
Hate come and one person found that helpful, which is nice Charles Johnson
Okay, buddy. All right. Yeah Johnson. Yeah, nice five stars great cum shot
Holy crap, these pills are true to their word after taking one pill for the first time 30 men later
I was feeling energetic and well, I noticed I was extremely hard when the time came
I was able to last longer and busted a lot more juice
I definitely recommend wasn't sure what to expect when ordering was pleasantly surprised by how well it worked
I've never really had a problem with performance, but max load completely enhanced sensations also helped me keep rock solid
I will probably end up ordering another bottle when this one runs out
I think I might buy this product because I really want to come like I'm peeing there's a bunch of yeah
Dude, there's a I want to do I want a one minute long stream
I didn't screenshot it
But there was a bunch of reviews that are like I bought this for my man
And I'm loving it his loads are huge, and I'm like isn't that that goes like against what I thought was kind of common courtesy
Which is that the smallest possible load when you yeah, it's less less of a mess
Yeah, also like fucking I'm putting it into my own shirt anyway. I don't give a fuck how big it is
You know ideally the woman's never gonna see it
What okay
You don't do that dude. I want to I want to have to I want to have to
I want to I don't I don't wipe it like I'm like wiping a spill with my shirt
That's what I do or I put it into my hand and then I go like into the toilet
yeah, I want to I want to take this and I want to have a
Load that's strong and fast enough that I have to come on the side of the toilet bowl or else
It will splash all the water out. Yes, exactly it all over my bathroom floor all over my back
They have a pill you can take that makes it so you just don't ever come again. You ever get it in your mouth
ever Patrick you ever get it I'm gonna say this one more time have you ever
other tracking notification somebody somebody is tracking me have you ever
get it you have to stop it you knock it off have you ever get it in your mouth
I almost flew over that wasn't fucking cool you slapped me answer the question
answer the goddamn question you fucker have you ever get it no you never once
never once I got it in my mouth four times I got it my mouth four times
because when I was younger will not say how much younger I used to shoot it onto
my belly in the bathroom and one day I accidentally must have taken a major
load because it shot with serious
ferociousness into my mouth. Your mouth was
open? Yeah, because I go "Ugh!" You were like this? I was like "Ugh!"
And I didn't learn my lesson and it happened three more times.
You were looking down the barrel! Why did you shoot it on it? You were in the bathroom!
Because I didn't know, I don't know why I'd never
thought to have used toilet paper onto it
and make the little... Just aim it down like it's
an udder. My shit won't shoot down! I did
know somebody used a jack-off directly
into the toilet just squirt into that nasty. I thought that was nasty. That shouldn't happen.
That's nasty because everybody at some point sees the toilet bowl so you should be doing
it into the toilet tank because that's hidden.
Or in your mouth on accident. But it does not taste very good.
And I...
Depends on the diet.
That's true. You're probably eating lots of cum so it probably tastes a lot like cum.
Yeah, I was eating pretty much only cum at the time and hot dogs so it was pretty bad.
Okay, is that all the wait? No, I think there's one more review. No, that was it. Okay. Okay. Well, that's a great gift
Yeah, thanks for the recommendation. I hope somebody buys that for their Papa. Here's here's what I found. See I didn't look at any
Reviews of this stuff, but that's okay reviews aren't completely necessary. Yeah. All right. Yeah
See, let's see this first gift. This went above the foodie in your family. Oh
butter nutrition funny Thanksgiving costume food Christmas t-shirt
It is funny, and it comes see I fucked up here by not putting it in yellow
But that yellow is the same color as the font
Here's what I would say if I was walking around with that sure says butter
It's pretty good like a criminal wearing butter mm-hmm
All right the next one here for the fatty in your family
swell wimps
Sexual exercise as a means of reducing and controlling weight
So well with overweight out of shape try swell wimpa
Revolutionary well with a gram of sexual exercise well whip sounds like it has to be an acronym. Yeah
Sexual exercise, I don't like that. No. I don't like I like that
I don't like that it's by a man named Perry Bluth house
I usually have sex purely for exercise bath house Harry bath house. Holy crap Perry bad. How is a flan?
Clarissa Flanders
Perry bathhouse yeah I don't know why it's called swell wimp but hey if you
want to learn pick this book up for I guess $12 on paperback did you read in
it at all I didn't read it oh I read a sample of it. I wanted to know what the sample is
gonna be I wanted to know maybe if it gives you some kind of like are you
supposed to be like doing push-ups into a woman's I think well that's what
you're normally supposed to do if you're not exercising I guess you're right yeah
Sex is so fucking hard already. I don't want anything. It's already. I'm already like me puke. Yeah
I'm like ready to vomit my central nervous system. Just like overloaded. I don't want scared. Yeah, I'm just sitting there
Yeah, oh, this is a this is an album. I found okay. Well. I need my phone back. It's by butt fuckers
No, it's called both the song is called butt fucker by dirty boy here check check this let's let's listen to this album
It's like a it's kind of like I'll do it a listening already. Yeah, it's like a power violence record
There's 50 songs and it's only five minutes. Okay
What's this?
Whoa
Is that one got a whole track or something bitch, whoa
They forget to record that one that's bastard. Well, I can give you a bro. Maybe got a stir
No one got copyright struck that they sampled that from an old dirty bastard song. I got it taken down. What what did he say?
No each shit
I love the logs out there. They make it skits dispensable and scary
- Yeah, yeah.
- Clit face.
(laughing)
- Boy, that guy's outta nowhere.
- Yeah.
- All of them are normal, pretty normal cusses
until that one.
- See, cuss your foot.
- Cock.
(laughing)
- That didn't work, coochie doesn't work.
- Coochie doesn't work, man.
- Damn, that's disappointing.
I wanted to hear that in his voice.
- Coochie.
- Any other good ones?
Dick.
don't work to the right wings which one yeah a lot of these let's see if this
one works nope just go to the time I want to see I want to select one I want to
see how many tracks are there Oh jackass
all right that's enough of this album yep I think I've had enough of this
That's your ass too far now, that's too that's not right
And then this last one is for Caleb oh
Hell no any acne on my ass
Why would you Pell nah, but acne clearing cream, that's a low blow
Yeah, very low as low as your butt which is very low to the ground cuz you're this tall
Exactly you're not that tall you're really short
That I said a booger come out. No keep that shit to yourself, bro. I didn't do is an inside nasty
Yeah, I would love to hear that guy say booger
I saw a guy walking a big fat guy walking on the street sneezing a booger
I saw it fly and do a trapeze
into his own mouth
And it just I was in the middle of talking to Noah we were walking on the street and he did that and me and Noah
just like
Just like froze completely. Yeah
Yeah, he had a pretty probably was shaped like this probably was dude to the boomer. Yeah. Yeah
That's probably the mechanic if you're interested in the physics behind that that's probably
Gnostic atheist new upbringing. Yeah, what I believe is that God's hand came down and and it willed it to go
Because he knew the fat guy was hungry. Oh, wow. He rides
- Take it away.
- Okay, I got some gifts here.
- What's up? - Peckerhead?
- If you don't hold it up to the mic,
no one will be able to hear it.
- Okay.
- But this is my gift guide.
I got some gifts here, some suggestions for different.
So this one's a multi-part one.
So first here, this is a good gift for children.
Okay, this is some things that go together
that you could buy for maybe a nephew or a son
or one of these types.
And first we have a talking--
- Sometimes a nephew is a son.
- Sometimes, but not always.
"A Taki Toys products fart speaker remote controlled, plays funny poop and fart sounds, hilarious
prank joke and gag toy."
So this is great.
Now I want you to go to the next slide here.
This is an addition to this gift that you can get.
Here are two other things which is an Allen & Heath SQ6 digital mixer, 48 input channels,
24 onboard preamps, 25 faders, etc.
And then a SoundTown all-weather line array system with 115-inch waterproof line array
subwoofer, 4-compact dual 8-inch line, dot dot dot.
And if you go to the next slide, this is a cheap gift.
it'll only run you about $10,510.44.
- That's pretty good.
- So this is a good gift for kids aged six to eight.
I think they'll find a lot of fun with this.
You might have to also buy an adapter
to get the fart speaker.
But the advantage of this is you can get multiple,
this is, you know, you can get up to, I think,
even 48 fart speakers.
- Oh, the input channels, yeah.
- And mix them in separate volumes,
in separate, you know, effects.
- You kind of do beginning of Back to the Future,
you hit the right but you just press that fart speaker button and you can do yeah
yeah you know at once like like that band 10 CC where they did all the the
recording through the mixer you could do that with the farts where you have like
a fart orchestra yes yeah and this is also great for it so this is great for
six to eight year olds who enjoy farts but also any six to eight year old who's
thinking of opening a music venue this can actually be a great gift yeah for the
little producer in your family this can actually be huge but you might want to
get a few more of the array systems for that.
- Depends on the venue size, I guess.
- It does depend.
All right, let's go to the next one here.
This is for a nerd and your family.
This is 1,000 feet of Cat6 Ethernet cable.
It comes in red, yellow, black, blue, silver, brown,
and it's $203.
- That's not bad for 1,000 feet of Cat6.
- No, definitely, and this is also great,
I mean, say you think, you haven't seen your cousin
in a while, you know he's nerdy, okay?
You know he's a geek.
And then you buy, so you buy this for him.
And then you get to Christmas and he's like,
"Oh, by the way, cousin, I'm not a nerd or geek anymore.
I actually like fashion.
I like necklaces and belts now."
- Oh shit! - Yup, that's right.
- Wow. - Okay.
- So this is foolproof.
- He's about to turn the fashion world upside dizzy
with this one. - See, and you know
who you could also get this for
is the office fan in your family.
- Really?
- If one of Jim's famous pranks involves the same red cable.
- Is that true?
- What's the prank?
- I don't remember that.
- He puts a cable, he hooks a cable to Dwight's computer.
- He actually uses the computer.
- Speaking of the office,
if you live a thousand feet away from your office,
you can actually connect to your works ethernet port
and use your computer from home.
- Mmm.
- You could probably steal the internet
from like a sweet green or something.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, this is actually really,
if they let you behind the desk,
you're definitely gonna want to bring one of these.
- I would love to do like a little like,
like high style, like get,
I just gotta get in there.
Plug your own laptop in.
I see you walking out with a giant spool of red cable out of the door and across the street and into an apartment building.
Hidden in your sleeve.
It's like you have the other part of it going up your back and through your...
Well it's coming out of the back of your shirt and they're like, "Sir, are you running a cable from our store?"
You're like, "No, that's just my tail."
I was born with a tail.
Don't close it in the door. It'll really hurt me.
it'll really hurt me.
- Let's look at the next gift here.
I don't remember what it is.
Oh yeah, this is a book I found called
"Drugs, Secret Death Pill."
And I found this because I was trying to,
in case you had an annoying person in your family,
I was trying to find an item on Amazon called a death pill.
But it turns out they don't sell anything called a death pill.
- Wow.
- That name sounds so familiar, Cagri-Gur.
(laughing)
- Well it's actually a famous brother's,
Cagri-Gur and Cagri-Gur.
- Oh my God.
- Look at the authors there.
But yeah, not too much interesting about this one.
I just thought "Secret Death Pill" by Kagri Gur was kind of getting me.
So this one is Luminance Red, the proven genital sore device for pain relief and sore management.
Holy shit, that's expensive.
This is $350 and it's the ultimate genital sore device.
The Luminance Red is a breakthrough pain-free genital sore device designed to help you manage
sores on or around the genitals.
No longer do you have to rely on messy lip creams, gels, ointments, patches, medicines,
acuclovir, lysine, or Abreva.
You think she's patting that thing and rubbing her head at the same time?
Why is she touching her head?
Did she hurt her head too?
I guess so.
I think she's trying to go like...
Yeah she's doing a...
You know supposedly that red light can grow your hair back too.
You know she's got some hairy ass pubes down there.
Yes.
And her pussy is like 100%.
Dude, do not say pubes because I'm going to have a laughing attack.
And I'm going to cum.
Her fucking pubes are overgrown because of that red light.
Stop.
Oh, you pet. Well, hey, you can get it. If you think it's expensive, you can get it for
twenty five bucks a month over a year. And that's huge. So that's 30 percent APR. This
is a great gift for an uncle or aunt who suffers from genital warts or sores. Yeah, that is
good. I'll take you. Yeah, because you also have the extra thing of like, oh, I've got
to grow my hair back. Yeah. Right. Or or yeah, I have no pubes. My pubes are removed in a
fire. But then you go, oh, I'm going to put it on my or just in case because it can strike
at anybody. I remove my pubes probably once a year. Yeah, I pluck them. I pluck them bit
by bit. I would get the laser hair removal on my pubes. Yeah, just around the ring of
the shaft so it makes it look bigger. Yeah, I think I would maybe consider that in a world
where Final Destination doesn't exist, but I've seen five of those movies and I will
never be in a room with a laser. So I'll never get LASIK. Is there a LASIK death in that?
I don't remember that one. It's when she gets stuck in the chair and the laser gets turned on and it like burns a hole through
Her head through her eye. I think that's strong
Yeah, wait something in Final Destination couldn't really
Think it I don't think I don't think it's could go on a plane
Yeah, I don't even remember which one that might be in five maybe yeah, I'm seeing that one five is fire
Five is the best one dude. You got a fast and the furious. Uh-huh. Yeah, that's ludicrous
Ludacris. Go back to rapping.
Ludacris.
I haven't heard a Ludacris song and actually I
listened to that song Saturday the other day.
Alright, next product here.
This is for
anybody who might get into a fight.
This is a medieval parade armor
of Alessandro Farnese.
Full
armor suit replica, $40,000
and if that seems like a steep price tag
just take a look here at what it says.
This item is a rare find.
It's hard to come by and it ships free. Oh wow. Yeah, that is difficult to ship. Yeah, that is a suit of armor
It's pretty easy to show you just take it apart piece by piece. I would get that
I would look I want a suit of armor more than I want anything in the world
So this is bit. This is kind of you know. I'm mostly doing the gift guide to say like hey listeners watch
This is what you can get for your friends
But you know I want maybe there are some things in here that you guys might get for your friend
I want to look like a yautja. Yeah, a yautja. That's a predator species fake fan
I don't think he is talking about talking about predator earlier now. I've never even seen it
I don't know that it's a fake fan as much as not. I feel like the
2017 predator movie that one was ass is terrible. Yeah the one that Shane black made yeah
Yeah, it took me three times to watch the whole thing
I'd really pass and just kept going in and watching 30 minutes and leaving that was the best yeah doing that
- Yeah, I did that with John Wick 3.
- Very fun.
- Yeah.
- Alright, next gift here.
This is for your ticklish friend.
And it's a feather.
- We all got that one.
- It's a smudging feather too.
- Yeah, but it doesn't matter what kind of feather it is,
it's just a feather.
And it's $6.50, so that's a pretty good deal.
- That's a great deal for a gift.
- For a feather and a gift especially.
- Oh, fuck me.
- Yeah.
- Fuck me, that's fucking good.
- It's good for tickling with.
And smudging apparently.
- My agnostic ass loves cuss words.
Okay, fucking don't get next if this is for if you have a robot and your family this is robot maintenance oil
special robot oil 20 liters
It can be pretty cheap or pretty expensive depending on how much you get well the big red barrel
Seems like it would be pretty expensive one right well you think that but we don't really have any point of reference
So it could be exactly the opposite. Yeah, I don't know yeah
But yeah, that's for robots
Okay, robot reduction. Yeah, they put a lot of work
It says you can't read it there, but there's the red buckets as robot maintenance oil on it
I'm it's what is the blue one I think but let's just go to the next gift
That's if you have a robot so this is for dancers. Oh my god. Wait that's speaking of the predator
Yeah, this is a grace color life remote control LED robot costumes light costume LED robot suit for dancer party performance electronic music
So a DJ or dancer could do great with this
Yeah, just go crazy
Doesn't it look cool. I'm gonna go to want to dance just looking at it. I'm gonna go to Lollapalooza
I'm gonna go to the comedy tent and watch Eric Andre and do
Dancing like a cyber goth yeah
Okay, next gift here. Let's take a look okay, so this is part of a series
This is for fans. These are a few gifts there for fans of rice
Okay, so if someone in your family is a rice a holic. I got one. Yeah, I know we all do
This is a rice mascot. I'll be wholesale custom advertising cartoon rice grain food cereals theme anime cosplay
Costumes racist carnival two nine four five and there's only three hundred forty five dollars
And it looks like a pretty good costume of rice. I think you're gonna look at that and recognize that it's rice
Yeah, what you see that costume? Yeah, so let's look at the next and that's your rice gift
You got eggs on so here's a rice mascot costume. This one is three forty nine dollars. I like I like his eyebrow
This is kind of an alternative to that other rice mascot costume
So if you have a rice fan to rice fans in the family you don't want to get them the same thing a little impersonal
Yeah, and if you have three rice fans in the family this next one will be perfect
There's a cartoon rice a little cheaper cartoon rice mascot costume food advertising restaurant mascot costumes for sale adult-size Halloween carnival
Carnival fancy dress a carnal fancy dress well
I mean some rice fans some rice fans might think of this costume as a bit carnal
This is what speaking of carnal man. Can you imagine Christmas you give you give this to your baby girl on Christmas, right Christmas night?
She says let me slip into something a little more comfortable pops out of the bathroom gets stuck in the doorframe. That's right
Yeah, so okay, so imagine this scenario right? I've shown I've shown three
Three rice costumes. Okay, okay your uncle loves rice. Oh your aunt loves rice your cousin loves rice
You've got it covered three separate rice costumes. Oh my god
I just just a few days before Christmas suddenly. I have been told that my brother also likes rice
What the fuck am I gonna do well next one here this if you really like rice
This is a heavy bag of rice mascot
Yeah, and it's very it's it's pretty cheap, and it's a whole bag of rice so someone who really likes rice
This will be good, and then your brother's like hey
This is great, but I really want to have a rice costume for my girlfriend - yeah
Are you serious? She's not even coming to family Christmas. Well. You can get this one for her
This was a little more expensive
but I think she'll really appreciate how cute it is and that it's from 2021.
It's a little newer.
It's decent. It's a rice that's wearing clothes.
Yeah. God. And let's go to the next one here.
And so this is if you have if you have a father or mother, this one could be good, too.
This is for adults. Adult rice costume, adult rice mascot costume.
And this one's three hundred fourteen dollars.
Our costumes advantages.
So if you just have someone in your family who likes to dress up as a grain of rice,
These are six or seven gifts that may be really good for them.
Well, I mean, it says, "Great for business, party,
special occasions, sports games, and events."
Man, you guys remember--
Go Rice!
Go Rice, go!
High school football games, Friday night lights.
It was the Tigers versus the Rice.
Oh my god.
Man, Randy the Rice piece, we used to--
he was a legend.
This one also breathed easily from the holes
of the eyes and mouths.
I would hope so.
And you will not feel uncomfortable to have it on for a long time.
So that's pretty good.
And it's shipping days later.
That's good.
That's not bad at all.
It's in stock right now.
Let's hit up the next gift here.
So this is what I found.
You can buy someone a gold mine on eBay for the low price of $8,500.
And let's go forward here.
I have some more details about this.
This is the mine you would be buying.
Wow.
So you can buy that for under $9,000.
It looks to me a lot more like a hill than a mine.
Yeah, but it actually it's been inside that hill it has gold and minerals in there
I found out this is actually a burgeoning industry. Okay eBay, so check this out people are buying mines and shafts
All the time holy shit. Well people are listing them Wow look at that
You can buy Nevada gold silver mine historic mining claim shaft pit for eight thousand five hundred. How's their shit?
I'm not sure it's the it's the like the deed. Yeah, it's like the paperwork that says that you own it true or the claim
I mean, I think it's called. $25,000 for a 20-acre gold mine. I mean, that's pretty good.
Yeah. Let's go to the next one here. This is a sketch of Barney Rubble and Fred Flintstone
for $8. And that's a good deal if you have an art fan.
Barney's holding his cock. It's brand spanking new. It's kind of a Tom of Finland thing.
What's fun about this one is if you go forward, you can see what people who looked at this
also looked at. And you have pieces of art like slouching on a wing chair, skinny guy
guy wearing open gray jeans, cute guy lifting up his gray shirt.
Executive gives friend a peck on the cheek. God, that's hot.
And these are all $8 each, so good gift for big...
Some budget gifts.
Yeah, or for the office.
Get everyone.
Yeah, Secret Santa.
You saying something? I'll do that.
All right, next up here, Goofordust.
(laughing)
$9.77, that just speaks for itself.
Next up here, this is a Demon Whisperer, class eight,
so you can buy her and you will be soulbound
to a female Demon Whisperer.
She is a special and ancient breed and commands millions of lesser demons, devils, hellhounds,
ibs, succubi, incubi, and other entities.
She always engages to give out the maximum of her best to make you happy.
The hardest is not to abuse of them."
What?
So you can buy a demon woman.
Oh!
And she will be bound to you.
And they said, "From Canada?
A demon woman from Canada?"
And apparently it's really hard not to abuse her.
Let's get an offer in.
That's what they said.
Well, I just want you to make sure you have options, so go to the next one here.
You can actually also buy a sex spirit or a neurotic sex demon, and these will be bound
to you and will have sex with you.
Wow.
Okay, I will do that.
And that's pretty cheap for a bound sex spirit, I think.
Dude, for a fucking demon?
Yeah.
Are you kidding me?
That's pretty good.
They cost more than that to make.
Yeah.
And then the next one, there's actually some more stuff like that.
You can buy some stuff here.
You can either become a sorcerer or you can become an alpha male.
Wow.
I choose alpha male.
And these are two things really interesting.
I choose sorcerer.
Yeah, sorcerer.
I could cast a spell to become an alpha male.
I could cast a fucking spell to become a sorcerer.
You can't cast a spell to become an alpha male.
I don't remember which one is which, honestly.
Yeah, wait, you guys want to be a sorcerer?
Yeah.
Those fucking misogynist pieces of shit?
Become an alpha male.
No, I'm gonna become-
You can wear a pointy hat, get a wand.
No, dude, the way you have to look at it, sorcerer-
An alpha male doesn't wear a pointy hat and a wand.
I think he does.
Book of spells, all that.
I think you're mixing something up.
I wish I could make myself pass out on command.
I have one more gift to take it home. You can spend $34, get some mayo on Facebook Marketplace.
I would buy that.
Just if you run out of ideas. Ship's to you.
Damn. Not bad at all.
Hard Eyes 2-Pack Craft Real Mayo. Creamy and smooth. Real.
That's the real deal.
It's real, guys.
That's the real deal. It looks real to me.
That's all the gift recommendations I prepared.
If you fucking don't have a good gift by now, after that, I mean, you're an asshole.
Don't blame us. You're going to blame us. I know you were about to.
Yeah, yeah, you were this close, but yeah, you got pretty much everything you need so thank you for watching
Yeah, I'm check out our patreon to the patreon we want to make a sci-fi adventure movie called Caleb's demise
So we need to make so much more money on page yeah
Go do that go make us a lot of mine become an executive producer executive producer this Friday. No last Friday
Yeah
Was our first shareholder meeting and it went splendid. It was baller. Yeah
It was probably one of the best and you know
We had a lot of laughs and we had there was a lot of new inside jokes that we created together
that only the executive producers are privy to
And we gave out details of our personal lives and we sprinkled inside jokes throughout this episode
And there was and I know your ass is laughing an executive producer. Everybody was
Dressed to the nines. Uh-huh. Yes. I was dressed to the tens. Yep. Oh, it's cuz we were doing the meeting
I was dressed to 100.
We will say bye now.
Bye!
Your seat is right this way.
Ah, welcome man to the show.
Here's a program, your seat is right this way.
Sir, this is a counterfeit ticket.
You need to leave.
Get out.
Immediately.