Yo, if you're a young man right now and you're alone and you're single and you're trying
to hook up and you're trying to date, you know what I'm saying?
What I want you to do is you don't need to be mean.
You don't need to be, you know, aggressive, aggro and alpha.
You just need to be yourself.
Okay?
And you need to be you.
And I don't care if women hate you.
They don't like you.
they think you suck, they think you're weird, they think you're a fucking loser and they're
saying that to your face constantly.
You just need to just be you, even if that person is a bad person or you suck, you just
have to keep going with it until you find somebody who kind of accepts you and that might take
a long time, an extremely long time for you to find somebody who can kind of put up with
that bullshit, but you're gonna get it eventually.
and yeah.
That's how it's done.
This is what real podcasters do.
This is a real podcast.
Take notes.
- Hey, y'all ain't playing around here, are you?
- See this?
That's what it's recording to.
- It's recording straight to that.
- Oh, yo. - See how it's spinning?
- Old school style.
- Yeah, we do it analog.
We're more into, have you ever bought--
- It's for the warmth. - Maybe the LP?
Like a big, it's like the big disc.
That's the kind of thing we're into.
- Yeah, VHS.
- We're into all that kind of shit.
- Yeah. - Cassettes.
- Yeah, we do all that.
- SNES. - Mm-hmm.
- Retro vibe. - Retro.
- On the Super Nintendo.
- What is it like, you're so new to the podcasting game.
How do you like the lifestyle so far?
- There is, you know how there is a BC and an AD in time?
- Yes. - Uh-huh.
- Before, geez, I feel like my life before a podcast,
before becoming a podcaster, and after it,
I'm seeing things in a different way.
- It's completely different.
- I'm seeking out new experiences just so I can
talk about it and give the public some new information
about my observation.
It controls my entire life. - You gotta go get a story.
You have to go, yeah.
You need material, you need stories.
So I'm going out into the world and I'm fucking with people
and shaking people on the street
just so I can have some crazy ass story.
- Some guy punched me in the face for no reason.
- It is kind of ruining my fucking life right now.
- I can imagine.
I think we all went through that when we first started.
But then at some point you kind of forget,
like you forget the BC.
- Oh, you don't need any stories at all.
- Yeah.
- You can just sit here and say nothing for an hour.
- You can do like first five minutes of the show,
just fart sounds.
You're kind of like, I was thinking about how you are,
'cause you live on the West Coast, right?
Yes, I'm West Coast vibes.
But you're part of an East Coast collective,
an East Coast podcast.
It's true. So you're kind of
a Tupac kind of coast trader.
(laughing)
You know, like you're from the West,
but you now are like with straight up
the East Coast death row.
By the way, speaking of Tupac and Biggie,
I think that we need to have a kind of beef and a war.
A beef?
That's why I brought you guys up.
Yeah, okay.
Joy Tactics, the podcast I do with Jack Benzinger and Eric Rahill and Potabot
List. I think it needs to get violent. I think we need to get into the boxing ring.
One of us is gonna die. I'd be down. For sure. Do y'all think, be honest, be
honest. You. No, no, no, okay. We are in kind of like a fenced-in cage, okay?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Okay, just a cage. And it's three on three, joy tactics vs.
potlicks, bare knuckles. We're all in, you know, kind of sexy outfits as
well, just for no reason, just for the viewership. Yeah, okay. Is it being like, is
it televised? It is. That does add an element. Worldwide. It's put on by feedback. How hard you're gonna fight.
Yeah, it's three billion people watching. Who is gonna win in this ass-whipping
competition. Which podcast has more fighting abilities? Well you and Jack are
like gigantic. You are hugely tall. We have that. We have one guy but he also happens to be the
biggest wimp on our podcast. Not true. You can't call me the biggest wimp.
No no no. This guy is so much more of a wimp than me. He's a scared of sounds.
Do you see what he just tried to do? That's a wimp. That's not a wimp move.
He's scared of sounds.
No I'm not.
Hmm.
Don't test it.
Meanwhile, I'm over here.
Yeah, I'm not a wimp.
That's all I gotta say.
We would beat the fucking shit out of you.
It would be like a two minute rant.
We would disappoint people.
If it wasn't, you would beat us up physically, but we would get you mentally.
We would talk mad shit and throw you guys out.
We would leave you hungy-tied.
You may beat us up, but then after you leave that fight, you're gonna be like thinking like,
is my hand too small?
[laughter]
is my hands way too small?
you know what I'm gonna do too is I'm gonna look where the cameras are
that are televising this, I'm gonna put my back to the camera
so nobody can see what I'm doing and I have a
blade.
I'm gonna slit your throat.
really? that's against the rules.
but nobody can see it so did it even happen?
and then I'll turn around and be like I did that with my fingernails.
that's why we'll have a referee.
who's the referee gonna be?
there's literally nobody in the world who's unbiased in this fight.
It's not possible to find someone who's not already leaning towards one of us.
It's like the OJ trial. How do you pick a jury for that?
Maybe, I guess maybe Cato Kaelin could be the ref.
Who?
Cato Kaelin. The guy that was just like in their backyard or some shit.
What are you talking about?
The guy from the OJ trial.
Oh, the guy from OJ.
He's only known for the OJ trial.
He probably doesn't want to be involved in any more stuff like that though.
That's true.
This is going to be bigger than the OJ trial.
- One nation dividing debacle.
He can't do another one, dude.
He can't handle that.
- Our headphone cords are tangled.
- That means we're in love.
Speaking of love, dude, Valentine's Day.
- Valentine's Day is when this episode comes out.
- No, it doesn't.
- No, Valentine's Day was yesterday.
- Somebody's gonna get in trouble this year.
- Gulp!
- You're basically in trouble.
- Oh no.
- But, and we had you on because we love you.
- Wow, really?
- Because we love you so much.
- And you were wearing red.
- I know, I kinda am.
- I do have that V-day.
Yeah, they saw me on the street and they were like,
"Yo, you wanna come on the pod?
"You're wearing red."
(laughing)
I don't know, I was like, "Fuck it,
"I like podcasting so much, and I like you guys.
"I'll come chill."
Yeah.
- You've advanced to, I would say,
a high level of podcasting pretty fast.
It's like you had your 10,000 hours already banked,
and then you just come out on the scene,
you're already destroying and abolishing.
- We kinda went from zero to the elite level
podcasters immediately.
- Pretty much immediately.
- And it's like, kind of like, you know how,
I don't know, someone, Britney Spears or Justin Timberlake,
they're all of a sudden famous.
- Yeah, yeah.
- They're on the red-- - They're on the red--
- Yeah, they're on the damn red carpet
and the lights are flashing and everybody at the paparazzi,
hey, come over here, come here, take a picture.
It's kinda like, you don't even have time to process it,
being an elite level, elite God tier podcaster.
- Do you think that maybe that is just podcasting
or that kind of anything that you do,
you could be at the top S tier highest level of doing it?
Like maybe if you got into exploring,
maybe you could explore, you could find a new continent.
- They say 10,000 hours,
but I feel like there's some people,
like you probably included, where it's like it's one hour.
- Basically one hour.
- Some people are one hour people,
where they do one hour of something in their approach.
- That's way more impressive than 10,000 hours too.
- Yeah, 'cause it's fast.
- Yeah.
- That's a really good point.
- 10,000 hours, show me somebody that can do it in one.
- Yeah.
- Then I'll be like, all right, okay.
- That's like--
- What's that guy's name, Malcolm Gladwell?
- Yeah.
- The guy who came up with that?
- Fucking dumbass, 'cause you should have said one hour.
Should have talked about cool guys doing stuff in one hour.
- Giannis Attitukuompo, you guys know that basketball player?
He had never played basketball before
and then he was like 18 years old and somebody was like,
I don't know if this is exactly how it happened,
but I imagine somebody--
(laughing)
- This cannot be how it happened.
- But I imagine somebody was walking down the street
and saw him and was like, oh fuck, you're huge,
and tried to--
- Just tossed him a basketball.
- Yeah, and he like palmed it immediately.
- Whoa.
- And he dunked it into--
- Dunked from the curb all the way.
- Yeah, he dunked it over a telephone line.
- All the way to the court that was like two blocks away.
- Yeah, and also--
- One jump.
- Wow.
he but in like two years he became an NBA player he had never played basketball
before he was a soccer player oh so he already knew about how to do sports I
mean you know that's not that impressed he understands he knew he knew rules and
also I'm not playing I don't know that he had never heard of basketball I think
he was just like what is this shit it's like it was a miracle and so you're kind
of like the Giannis Antetokounmpo of podcasting at this point I that's what
people are saying yeah yeah yeah you're both the Tupac and oh back to the Tupac
I think that two things about Tupac I found out today that Tupac was gay I
found out I googled it yes but then second that must have been someone from
the East Coast though
You gotta use unbiased. You have to go on a VPN and say it to West Coast Google. I did
I
Think that we need to start an East Coast West Coast podcasting war beef in the same kind of fashion
Absolutely. I think we need to be jumping up on stage doing this podcast awards and fuck you Bert Kreischer
Fucked your bitch you fat motherfucker. Yeah
I would do yeah I would interrupt the him when he's accepting the award I would be
like hey listen Burt I'm not gonna let you finish yeah about list yeah that's
podcast of all time yeah two bears one cave we're gonna send you back to the
cave drop a nuclear bomb on Los Angeles and send you back to the Stone Age yep
right Brendan Shaw but we're gonna you know what you've done enough to yourself
we're fine. Yeah, he doesn't need it. Ari Shafir, smack the fuck in the face.
Fuck you, Ari Shafir. Honestly, we should shoot Tim Dillon in the head.
Yeah, yeah. Drive by, shoot him, and kill him. He'd be okay with that. I feel like he would like to die.
One of the only safe ways to dispose of Tim Dillon would be to
launch them into space. Otherwise, his body's gonna cause trouble. He's gonna leak into
the water supply. Like Chernobyl elephant foot, just fucking like there's some cave somewhere
in Los Angeles that you can't go in. And like 500 years aliens come to the earth and they
have a religion that they built around Tim Dillon's body and they found him floating
in space. Yeah, see this is what we need, man. We need to fucking destroy these people. Yeah.
We need to fucking wipe the West Coast, I mean except for some.
Well he's honorary East Coast.
Yeah, if we take it out right now, we finally use this.
Yeah, we use that big red button.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm a little, you know.
I'm kind of lazy.
I have heartburn right now.
So we should figure that out first.
That'll stop you from doing anything.
Yeah, true.
It's the worst thing to get.
Man, it sucks.
Probably, I think we need to spread awareness about it.
Yeah, I think we need to spread awareness about it.
awareness about it through the show. About heartburn? About heartburn. I think we need to spread
awareness about hearts. True. I think heartburn... That's the best idea you've come up with
all day. Heartburn is... Look at how beautiful that is. Can we get a punch in on that?
That is really amazing. You're doing a really really amazing job. Yeah, that's a
punch in on Nate's face. Oh shit, I kind of look sexy. Damn, I didn't see me on the monitor. You kind of do, man.
- Oh my God, with the headphones?
- With the bald swag.
And shout out to Potabot Liz
getting the bald representation.
- You already know, I wear a hat most of the time,
but yes, I do have no hair on my head.
And he's on his way.
- And Jubio's--
- Are you on the way out?
Be honest, are you on the motherfucking pills or what?
- No, I'm letting it happen.
- I think me and Caleb are the two last bald men in America.
Everybody is taking these psycho pills
that are making them crazy.
You can't nut on them, and then--
- You can nut on them, but they don't taste that good.
- Oh shit, oh my god.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- I didn't hear it.
- Wow.
- You didn't got him.
I'd like to see Theo Vaughn do that.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Theo gone.
- Yeah, that's right, 'cause we're gonna fucking obliterate
him and just wipe his smudge.
- I did not hear what you said.
- I said I'm gonna come do a cum shot on my own medicine.
- Oh, okay.
- Oh, all right.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But yeah, they make you crazy.
I took them and I started just like freaking out
all the time and like crying.
- Yeah, you were, it was like your evil birth.
- And then my hair fell out even more.
- Yeah, you probably took something else.
- I did do minoxidil for a little bit,
the flammable liquid.
- That one's scary 'cause they don't know how it works.
- Yeah.
- The stuff that like Rogaine,
they have no idea why that makes your hair grow back.
- Yeah.
- They have no idea.
- I feel like I am like the, you know how like in Zion,
there's like the humans that have what,
they don't have the ports in them?
- Yeah.
- I'm like that, but like for bald people,
like I've never put any type of medicine.
- You're a genius.
- Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
When did it start going? You're not gonna believe this but I started balding when I
was 11 years old. I swear to fucking God. You're right, I don't believe you. I know I swear.
I have a similar, there are photos of me at 8, 9 years old where I have a fucked up
hairline. Oh yeah, there's photos of me at like 15. I'm saying I would like buzz cut my head,
get like a number two buzz, and everybody, and it would look like I was like a like 42 year old
old man. And I think I had like, I looked it up online, I think I had like too much
testosterone. That's what it is. That's apparent. Yeah. So all throughout from
from the second I hit puberty, like those hormones were going, you were going, it
was a slow like 15 year trickle to being completely bald. At what age did you just
buzz that thing? I went like, I went in crazy waves because I have, oh fuck I
I should show you my passport. I have it in my bag, but it looks like insane.
I used to grow out my hair super, super fucking long,
like almost Gallagher style and have this huge fucking mustache.
That's what I'm going to do. That's my plan for this.
I'm going to get the sides real long. I'll start shaving the top early.
So when it does happen, everyone's just like, it's already there.
That is pretty smart actually. But you had a big Gallagher look?
- Yeah, yeah, 'cause I wanted to,
you know how like when, it was almost like
if I'm on like Jay Leno or Jimmy Fallon
or something like that, and you know how they'll
pull up like a pic of you in high school or something?
Look how crazy I used to look.
I wanted to just have a couple years
where I was looking crazy and I could show people like,
yo, I used to look like that.
- Yeah, and then you can lie.
You can say like, I was a drug dealer.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I looked like I was selling,
I was like a Coke dealer from Lebanon.
- That's amazing.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- That's amazing.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
- I just went, I just one day shaved my head,
but it was pretty, I kept, I held on a little too long,
I think.
- Do you know that Larry David doesn't consider you
a part of the bald community, if you shave the head?
- Oh really?
- He's like, you're like, you're not one of us.
- Is that your goat?
- I actually do love L.D.
- Is that your like, that's, you think he's the,
kind of the imam, he's who we look to?
He's the adept.
He's definitely one of them.
Yeah.
I think he's like obviously the bald.
Who are the pillars?
He's definitely, I don't know, who's the top bald goats?
The top bald goat, honestly I feel like you have to give it, even though he's fighting
it, LeBron is a bald goat.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
LeBron is a bald goat, kind of on the opposite spectrum.
And it's just weird that all the people we're mentioning are the top people in their field.
Isn't that weird?
Isn't that strange and weird that bald kings are taking over every single thing that they
touch?
- We're talking Jeff Bezos.
- Yeah.
- Walter White.
- I never even thought about that.
- Yeah, Walter White, yes.
- Joe Rogan.
- Donald Trump counts 'cause he was bald,
but he grew, I mean, like he was born bald.
- He was born bald, you know what I'm saying?
He's 100, and he has the highest office in the land.
- Wow. - True.
- Yeah.
- It's just, there's something there, I don't know.
- There's probably some boxers
that didn't have any hair on their head.
- Yeah, probably. - Mike Tyson.
- Mike Tyson, now he's bald at least.
- Yeah.
My dad is not bald, which means he's not very good at construction.
My grandpa?
That makes perfect sense.
He's good at aikido.
Oh shit.
Is that this one?
He's a black belt.
Yeah.
Where you flip people?
I think that's with weapons too, right?
Don't you guys know weapons?
It might be.
You do it against weapons.
He lived in my parents' house.
My friend was obsessed with aikido in elementary school.
He had these meditation balls that he left.
They're like these silver things and you ring them.
And you sit there while they're ringing and you meditate.
Oh wow.
He's weird as shit.
- My grandpa, he's a weird, balding guy.
He's not that cool.
He doesn't know my, he thought my name was Crispin.
He didn't know who I was. - Your grandpa?
- Yeah.
- You thought your grandpa thought your name was Crispin?
- My name was Crispin.
When I was 21 years old.
- Wow.
- He was living with my family,
and I would go and visit for holidays.
- Your immediate thought was like,
oh, this guy's an asshole,
and not, oh, my grandpa has Parkinson's.
- No, he's full, he's completely there.
- Except, yeah, he totally sounds like he is.
- He just does not give a shit.
He doesn't care at all.
- I think that he definitely has dementia then.
- No.
- I hate to break this to you.
- No, 'cause he ran away.
- Yeah, I might.
(laughing)
No, he knows what he's doing, he ran away.
Now we don't know where he is.
- Yeah, he has dementia.
- Yeah. - No.
- He's completely fine.
- I think that bald men also, I could be making this up,
I think that we have some kind of like,
I think we live longer than haired men.
Oh, absolutely. I feel like, you know, with this new tech coming out of like,
um, you know, extending our lives, we are going to be,
there's going to be a group of bald men that are getting to 360 years old.
I think we might be some of those in the first kind of group. Yeah.
I also think that people say all the time, they're, I'm like, Oh,
I don't want to get a hair transplant or whatever. But somebody will say like,
well, what if they made it so easy that it's like one day and it's just like
instant or like you take one pill and grow back. It's like,
That to me is the same question as somebody being like,
if you could upload your brain to a computer, would you do it?
It's like, I would lose myself entirely in the process.
I would fear that I'd be a different person
if I had a giant afro rainbow.
And what about the situation where it doesn't stop?
Yeah, that would be the worst part
about the first couple trials of that shit,
where you're taking the pills that grow your hair back
and shit, but it only grows back in rainbow--
- Well I would do-- - Or like it grows it back
at a completely new length that you've never tried.
- I would either not do the surgery
or I would get surgery all over my body to be Bigfoot.
And those are the only two versions of it
that I think that I could possibly do.
'Cause I don't wanna go and get the robot--
- If I got the hair transplants,
I'd also get the synthol in my arms
to make it look like I'm super buff.
- Also they take the hair from like your asshole and shit.
And like, I don't wanna-- - Aw, what the hell?
- Trust me, I got enough. - Is that true?
Do you have to pick where they take the hair from?
I don't think so.
I think that they have to-- well, because if you do multiple--
you've tried it.
If you do multiple places, then you
have a part of your hair that looks like pubes,
and then a part of your hair that's normal hair.
It looks like a cornfield from above.
All the different crops and different squares.
That could look awesome.
If you're a musician, I feel like that would help you out,
just in terms of looking kind of--
Yeah, pube mohawk.
Yeah, yeah, like have different kind of patches.
That would be--
Pube hair.
You're right.
You kind of look like a quilt.
Yeah.
- That'd be cool.
- You know, I mean, not to get topical,
but I'm thinking now, you know,
who else is bald is aliens.
- Oh, that's right. - And they're the best
at traveling through space.
- That's true. - And they like cornfields,
too. - Yeah.
- So it's kind of like it relates,
it's almost like we subconsciously,
we're steering the conversation towards aliens.
- And aliens are the most advanced beings.
Again, they're bald. - Yeah, exactly.
- They don't have hair at all.
- So then-- - And they're great.
- If we're headed that way already,
then let me just push us right over the edge.
- Right. - How about this UFO
that they have completely destroyed--
completely destroyed over the Alaskan airspace.
There's been three of them and they're objects.
Yep.
Unidentified.
I'm like, what the hell is this?
Yeah.
They've been shooting down objects.
I'm going to be completely honest, no idea.
Have not paid attention to this news story at all.
Well, here, I'll run it down for you.
It's pretty simple.
Tell me everything about it.
Basically, there were some objects.
They scrambled jets, which means flying them, and they shot the objects and they closed airspace.
space. No fucking way. But it wasn't. That's the whole story. No way. I'm not lying to you.
Genuinely, that's what happened in Alaska, Canada, Michigan, and apparently China. In
China as well? They said that. But I don't believe that one. If I was China and I was
sending objects over, I would do it. Yeah, we got one too. Fuck me, holy shit. That's
a clear, that's obvious, you know? Yeah. That's like if you're a serial killer and you're trying
to avoid being caught you kill yourself. Exactly. You kill your family. You go, "No, my family
got killed! Who did this?" I heard an awful story about a serial killer the other day
in Germany, so you know it's for real. In Germany, there was a serial killer called the
Lady with No Face, and they kept every serial killing scene, every murder scene, they would
test the DNA. Not everyone, but a bunch of them. They'd be like, "Fuck, it was this lady."
like it was the same DNA every time.
And then they find out, after like 15 years
of trying to solve the murders of this serial killer
that they think is the lady with no face,
they find out that the DNA is from a lady
who works at the DNA fucking factory,
making the test tubes.
- Oh, she got her fingers in the,
she was dipping her fingers in the blood and stuff.
- She just was like too wet one day,
like she was sweaty, or she was wet,
and she was just gooing all over all the stuff.
- Or, I mean, that's the best place to work
if you're a serial killer.
Well, that's true. You're pretty rock solid.
Isn't there a whole show about that?
No, that's different. He's a good guy and he kills serial killers.
Oh, he's a good guy with a gun?
What do you mean, what Dexter's about?
Dexter's job is he works at the investigation.
He's a forensic analyst.
He's not a DNA woman. He's a man, first of all.
I was close enough.
You were far off. You were way over there.
way over there. You're way out. Not true. Y'all need to do some Molly therapy together.
You guys need to do a psycho amount of Molly together and record it on the pod with
like some therapist like to hash this shit out. You guys are beefing too much.
I know that it would be something though if I did Molly with these two that it
would pretty much instantly become sexual. I was just about to say I think
like you guys would be like kind of rubbing and touching on each other.
No, because I already get like that with Patrick if I just kind of watch too much TV in a day.
So I think that Molly would affect my brain.
If he has three beers, I get a swat of them away.
I don't even need beer. If I have half a cigarette and I've watched and I have an episode of reality TV on,
that is enough modulation of my brain that I start getting a little bit sexual with Patrick.
Even now, I'm kind of on the ground.
When we record, I stand in the backyard until it's time and then as soon as we're done, I go back out there.
Because if these pheromones are coming at me, there's not...
I mean, I'm human, I'm a man.
- We have a hypersexual workspace.
- Yeah, it's a problem.
- I do feel like in a past life--
- We've had 10 HR ladies quit on us
'cause she just can't handle how much is going on between us.
- They open the file and they just vomit instantly.
They can't even handle it.
It's like the first day in some kind of,
speaking of forensic analyst.
- We're like an HR nightmare.
- Nobody will handle it.
- Nobody, literally, it's almost an in-joke
in the HR community, where they're like,
you can always go work for them.
People are like, hell no.
No, we're not touching that.
They're touching it.
- There's gonna be some seriously bad articles
about this whole thing in a couple years.
- Yeah, I know.
- Written about us, by us, towards each other.
- We do a thing called harassment rock, paper, scissors.
We're kinda just going in a circle against each other.
- Yeah. - Against.
- Yeah.
You know, when we travel, I only book,
when we get on a plane or something, I book us one seat.
- Wow. - And then we have to
just figure it out.
We just gotta figure it out.
- He's also multiple times booked a hotel
that's only got one bed.
- But luckily our bodies are perfectly made
to stick like Legos to each other.
So we just kinda pop on.
But getting this, you know,
you don't wanna be the flight attendant
who has to pull us apart, I'll say that.
- Right.
How do you guys sit?
Is it one person sits normal
and then the two are like facing--
- One on each leg, yeah.
- Stack sideways.
- Oh shit.
- It's me, he sits like this,
I sit facing him, kind of cowgirl.
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm in between you guys.
You hear that?
And I switch which direction I'm facing.
He sits like he got a BBL.
I was on a flight once and there was somebody who had gotten a BBL in a foreign country for cheaper.
And I was asleep and I woke up to this lady was passed out in the middle of the aisle way.
Whoa.
Begging for a doctor on the plane and she was like passed out like seizing out because she was not supposed to
to leave the country and get that high altitude yet.
So she was crying and like, ah,
and she was on the phone with her boyfriend,
like, you shouldn't have fucking done this.
- Oh my God. - It was wild.
But there was a doctor on the flight who was like--
- Whoa, wow.
- Who helped her out and thank God she's okay.
- She lived. - Yeah, we keep in touch.
- And the butt was okay?
- The butt was great. - Okay, good.
- The butt was good. - Women go through
so fucking much just to make our experience on Instagram
just a little bit better.
- Shout out to all the women out there.
- They really do, they put all of us in a massive way.
- Speaking of all the ladies out there,
we got some lists for your ladies at home,
for how to get a lady.
- That's true.
- I don't know how to transition.
- Listen, I'll handle it.
So it's Valentine's Day, it was Valentine's Day.
We're gonna pretend it is Valentine's Day.
And let me tell you something.
- Tell me.
- At least for me, Valentine's Day, one day of the year,
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm out on the hunt.
- Oh yeah, dude.
- Okay, I don't know.
- What, basically, so 364 days a year?
- 364 days, I'm monogamous.
- Well, here, let's--
- Valentine's Day, I'm at the bars, I'm at the museums,
I'm at the--
- You're microdosing.
- I'm at the beach. - I'm at the beach.
- I'm in the lake.
Whoa, my mic just went out.
I'm in the lake.
You're at the bottom of the lake.
- You're in the lake trying to find a woman?
- I'm chained up at the bottom of the lake.
- I'm trying to find the lady in the lake.
- Let's ask our-- - Like, space reporters.
Nate, you're like, I feel like you're pretty legendary
when it comes to like, basically game.
- Uh-huh, yeah. - Oh yes.
- I feel like you have some of the,
if not the most advanced techniques.
You're a developer of a lot of them.
So like, I guess, what is your history
with basically like, with getting pussy and smelling it?
- Well, basically I am one of the most sexual beings
on planet Earth.
And a lot of people look at me and they say,
"Hmm, I don't think this guy is like sexy,
"he's kind of like fugly."
But when they--
- Who calls you fugly?
- That's fucked up, man. - A lot of people
in my DMs are really coming at me.
- That's so not right.
- But when they come near me and they feel that energy
and that cosmic connection and those pheromones,
yeah, I might smell like shit, but you like it.
But it's like, it's kind of a shitty pheromone.
But do you put that, so when you say you smell like shit,
are you rolling around in shit?
Do you spray it on yourself or is that on natural?
- I just have never wiped once in my life.
Never once.
- Why would you?
- And I let it just kind of just be a part of it.
- Like a cast iron pan.
- Yep.
- Why would you wash it?
- Treat the booty hole like a cast iron pan.
Yep.
- You know there's that guy.
- That's giving me like a visceral reaction.
(laughing)
A caked on booty, like that's.
But over time, you know, it kind of merges.
- It looks exactly like a cast iron pan.
Also, there's a video of some guy restoring it with like...
One of those Facebook videos with a power washer.
You have to heat it up and put hot oil on.
Disgusting caked on ass transformed.
Looks brand new.
You guys know about that guy in, I think it was Iran,
who was like 95 years old and he had never had a shower in his life.
Then he took a shower and then he died.
No!
He had never had a shower. He would literally smoke...
- Well it's a good thing he didn't have a shower earlier then.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he wouldn't have lived so long.
- He looked like a mud man.
He would smoke, he loved smoking cigarettes,
but then when he ran out of cigarettes,
he would smoke his own poop out of a pipe.
(laughing)
And then, he was like, people were like,
you have to wash yourself.
And he was like, no, it'll make me sick.
And then eventually they wore him down
and he was like, okay, I'll take a shower.
So he takes a shower, he gets clean.
Like 90 days later, dead.
- That's probably the guy they based Shrek off
from the movie.
- Well it was also, he was 96, right?
- Well yeah, but also, but it's a little,
I mean he could've just lived forever, you know?
I think he'd kind of fossilized himself
and created a protective layer.
So I think if you're doing that with your ass,
probably some good news.
You may attract women, this guy attracted the news
from all over the world.
- That's how you get girls.
- Probably a lot of female reporters too.
Well maybe not in Iran.
- Yeah maybe not that many.
- But maybe from the world.
- But so you're using pheromone technology.
- Absolutely.
- But some people don't have pheromone technology,
which is what we've learned.
And here's some information from these guys that we found.
- You are so bad at English.
(laughing)
- Y'all, y'all, we're talking Riz.
- Talking Riz today.
Riz, or as it formerly was called, Pickup Artistry.
And here's a list of things that you can do
for pickup artistry.
- First of all, talk about your fit here.
- It's from a pickup artist forum.
- Can you please talk about your fit here, Patrick?
- What happened was, we were reading through these things,
and then I became completely--
- Oh my, the hat.
- Whoa.
- Damn, wait.
- Okay, Cameron is doing something called peacocking,
which is what you can learn about on the Pickup Artist--
- Yo.
- What happened was, we were reading on these
Pickup Artist forums-- - Cameron Fetter Rizz.
- Cameron Fetter Rizz, y'all.
- Is that your blog this year? - Oh, shit.
- Cameron Fetter Rizz.
- Okay. - It's dropping.
- All right, I'm excited.
- We read all these, I got completely indoctrinated.
I am now a Pickup Artist entirely.
You're nothing else.
No. I'm basically, after this episode, I'm gone.
You're dead?
Dead to podcasting, but then I'm alive in PUA lifestyle. Okay? So here's a list of things
you can do, pick up artistry. Before we begin, though, I just want to say I've been trying
some new PowerPoint templates.
I can see that.
What do you think of this one?
Wow, it looks great.
I am just now noticing that this is a witch-themed one. Is that kind of a common-
It was the first one that I found.
Okay.
But what were you going to say?
Is this a, are you commenting on how basically SJW culture has turned a lot of these women
into kind of witches, kind of old hags?
I wasn't, but holy fuck, that's symbolism.
Yeah, that's pretty mind blowing.
That's symbolism as fuck.
I love symbolism.
Also, I tried to join the PUA forums.
I tried to make an account so I could talk to these guys and their name is Gangstalicious
and they did not accept me.
Really?
That's a shame.
When you say they didn't accept you, they didn't let you make an account?
- Does that mean I-- - Did they let you make
an account or they shunned you when you did?
- I have not gotten a confirmation email.
- Oh, okay. - Wow.
- Or anything yet. - That is so sad.
- That is a shame. - Yeah, it's fucked up.
But here's the first thing.
People you model yourself after.
Oh shit, I can't read that.
Make it full screen.
- Make it full screen. - No, you can't make it
full screen, then you won't be able to see it.
In terms of people that you,
damn, I should've made this way bigger to see.
- In terms of people you look up to
that improve your everyday mannerisms,
conversations and overall personality,
who do you look up to and why?
For me personally, I love Alec Baldwin's character
on 30 Rock.
(laughing)
He maintains a dominant, calm, but still human personality
who's just interesting from hearing him say words,
let alone anything else.
I've heard a lot of Tyler Durden,
although I haven't seen Fight Club.
I'll take my bets that it's, at the least, a decent movie.
- Okay, at least a decent movie.
- A decent movie, Fight Club, the greatest movie ever made.
- Five stars out of five stars,
10 stars out of 10 stars, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
- I do understand being attracted to Alec Baldwin
in 30 Rock. - In 30 Rock.
- What, does he ever tap that ass?
- It's a will they, won't they?
- Yeah, I've never seen it.
- But he gets it on with Salma Hayek.
- He does do that, Salma Hayek does.
- He has amazing riz in that show.
- He does. - Which is what
they're talking about here, is guys with amazing riz
that they model themselves after.
- 30 Riz techniques. - 30 Riz.
And then this next one, Style, intelligent and socially well calibrated. I think that's
another pickup artist named Style.
Oh, okay.
Style's a good name.
Or it's the type of style guide.
Oh no, there is. No, no, I've seen that there is a guy named Style.
Named Style?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, on the forum?
No, no, he's like, there's a couple of people, Derek Dark, I think is one of them.
Mystery?
Maybe mystery, I don't know.
Yeah, that's the VH1, like, famous.
Oh yeah.
You do have the reality show.
He's going to come up later in this live show.
- Spoilers.
- Uh-huh.
Dexter Morgan, mysterious and humble misanthrope.
Now that's Dexter from Dexter, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Wait.
- What you thought was a DNA lady.
- How?
- But apparently, pick-up artist wizard.
- Can we just appreciate how incredible that is
that we were already had Dexter Morgan on the line?
- That is pretty incredible.
- That's called synchronicity.
- So what I'll say about this, about Dexter being on here,
I watched two episodes of Dexter
'cause my girlfriend wanted to watch it.
It's horrible.
But the second episode is about him,
a girl wants to have sex with him,
and his whole thing is he's like a psychopath
who feels no emotion or whatever,
and he's like, "I don't wanna have sex with you.
"Please don't have sex with me."
And then he does anyway.
- That's called reverse psychology.
- That's fucking pick-up artistry.
- That is pick-up artistry.
- That's genius.
- That is Riz.
- Do not have sex with me.
I feel no emotion.
I'm a killer.
- I'm a crazy serial, that's been my recent technique.
I'm a crazy serial killer, and my name is Dexter Morgan.
(laughing)
And they go, "So you're famous."
So then Don Draper, a real man.
- Yep.
- Arnold Schwarzenegger, persistent and successful.
- Royce Gracie, UFC champion, underdog with family values.
- The Gracie family, they're an amazing, amazing family.
- Then we got,
nothing can beat the power of a mixed character.
I combine them.
Example, the combination of Tom Cruise,
Mystery and Alec Baldwin.
Lot of Alec Baldwin on here.
- I get it.
- But this came out in 2000, what is this?
2007, 2009, this is before this tragic shooting.
- Yeah, long before.
Before anyone could even conceive
that he would even hold a gun.
- I would bump him by the head.
- Did you have to shoot a Democrat?
Couldn't you shoot a Republican?
- Really?
- Like, what is that about?
Like, why'd you have to shoot somebody who's on our side?
- Or like a corrupt politician.
Maybe not even a citizen, but like--
- Or just like, there's enough people,
she was a firearms lady.
- Or not an American.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Maybe you have to skip the whole Democrats
Republicans all together and maybe do a Democrat or Republican from a different
country. Yeah or at least somebody like just don't shoot like a like a
registered voting Democrat that definitely feels like a waste. Yeah.
Kind of and that yeah the numbers they matter. Yeah. Alec Baldwin I know you're
watching this shit. I know you're watching this shit from your cell. He's watching this from his cell
right now. I saw him put the the Joy Tactics episode on his Instagram story. Oh yeah I did see that.
Yeah he's one of the fans we're trying to get him on the pod right now. It's kind of like
gonna be easy. Yeah you think so? Yeah I mean you know watch out I'll say that.
He kills us all. He's a complete murderer. He's a psycho now. He got a taste for it.
I actually loved doing that. This last person, Bam Margera for me.
Ultimate Rizko. I'm seeing the name on here, Gangsta-licious. I thought they
didn't let you make an account Patrick. Nope, that is Soil Worker. That is from Soil
worker.
Hold on, let me read some of the names of the last people.
I forgot about the names here.
Soil worker, Bam Margera.
The last person here, Motherfucker2000.
Damn.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
I hope that's not the year he's born.
He probably means it literally, "Motherfucker."
Oh yeah.
Defy.
So the next thing, the next thing about pickup artistry, how to fucking dress.
Look at this.
Look at Mystery right now.
Oh my god.
Please tease me, dude.
Look at that swag.
Oh my god.
Yeah, look at how amazing.
The fuzzy hat.
Peacocking which Cameron picked up on pretty much immediately with this big LED hat that says let me hit
Can I please hit it yeah, well you got a dress I don't even have to say anything
Girl do you mind if I hit it?
Yeah, okay, and it's going reverse by the way
He's doing a double peacocking here girl. Let me hit that in this beautiful lion shirt right you think that's a lion tiger
Okay, see well that and that that's a teaching moment because that is how you start a conversation
Exactly you wait for a girl to say something stupid. Yeah. No you go up you say something stupid
So he's got this you say I like your lion shirt. She says seriously you think there's a line. It's a tiger
I say I know but now you're talking to me. Do you think I'm gonna hit that?
Do you think that you can peacock a little too hard like if I were to show up in a bar like?
Completely drenched in in like pig blood. Oh and let's start growling
There's no such thing as going too hard.
See, okay, so...
You think that works, you know?
Female psychology, when God made females,
he made them to basically think the opposite of what a guy would think.
So you walk in, right?
Interesting.
If you walk in covered in pig's blood, I'm saying,
"I will not be fucking that guy."
Right.
I'm thinking about most guys who walk in.
And girls are sitting there like this.
But girls are sitting there like...
Twirling their hair.
So whatever a guy would think, the girl's thinking the opposite.
So you gotta keep that in mind.
That's kind of interesting, and I never ever heard that shit before.
- Thank you, man. - They're gonna go,
they're basically gonna ravenously--
- They're gonna say, "Damn." - They're gonna say,
"Let me clean you off."
- Ooh, oh, shit. - Oh, damn.
- Oh, damn. - Wow.
- So Cameron goes for a more casual style.
See, I'm a classic man. - Also, I got the case in me.
- I'm a classic man.
- You can be, Jadina, by the way,
number one pickup artist, maybe, whoever that is.
- Number one.
- That's what I would put for my pickup artist influences.
Style Jadina, lyrics Jadina.
- So I got this classic blazer that fits me perfectly.
See that? - Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Look at that.
Well, that shows off your sleeves.
It shows off my sleeves on my white turtleneck right here.
I got the head.
The island vibe.
I look a little, you know, I mean, I look a little conservative, right?
You wouldn't look at me and think, "Oh, this man is peacocking," right?
What?
You wouldn't say, "Oh, this man's peacocking."
Not necessarily.
I guess not.
I guess I think you dress like this all the time.
Wait, wait.
I'd say he's hitchcocking, classic.
Classic, classic.
Yeah.
Wait, wait for it.
I got a gun on me.
Wow.
Damn.
- That's when the girls be giving you them digits.
- Yep. - Yeah.
- They come up, they say, "Can I give that to him?"
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
- I give them the gun.
- If you don't like it, kill me.
- And then I run away.
(laughing)
- If you don't wanna fuck me, just go ahead and kill me.
- Yeah, if you don't like this pickup line,
just go ahead and shoot me.
Are you from Tennessee?
(laughing)
- Are you from Tennessee?
'Cause you're making me crazy.
I fucked it up.
Ah, it's not loaded.
- Oh, wow. - That is rich.
- So they know that I'm psycho.
- It's great to be carrying around something
that's kind of a prop that you can use
to start a conversation.
- A totem, yeah.
- 'Cause I actually, I have something like that too.
- What's that?
- Can you hold my mic for me?
- Yeah.
- So,
what I do is I walk up to a girl,
and I usually, I have this on me,
and I walk up to her, and I walk up,
and I hold this shirt up, and I say,
"You like this shirt?"
And she says, "Yeah."
'Cause who's gonna say no?
- Of course.
- And I say, "Me and my friends made this shirt."
- Damn. - The merch.
- It says merch.
- Damn. - Yeah.
- I have merch.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- I also, I got some items for you guys too,
for you guys to, I mean,
you're already decked out right now, but--
- You do look incredible. - You look amazing.
I got you this you can put on over--
- I don't think I'll be putting that on.
- Why not?
- It's covered in things.
- That's dirt. - That's part of it.
- No, that's dirt from the ground right here.
- Can you explain what that is?
- This is an Austin Powers costume.
- Okay. - For Halloween.
But don't you think that that is,
'cause, okay, so real quick,
can we go around and just say all of our,
if we were doing our perfect Riz God techniques,
I would want the charisma of Austin Powers,
the style of Jidenna,
and probably the sense of humor of Andy Samberg.
- Yeah. - Right?
- Wow. - I would probably go for,
I'm for more of like a working class perspective
rather than celebrities,
so I would say maybe like the style and elegance
of a bellhop combined with the politeness of a chauffeur,
but also maybe the gruffness, toughness
of a construction worker and the intelligence of an author.
- Wow.
- See I would--
- And I don't even need to pick specific people.
- I would also go charisma of Austin Powers.
- Yeah.
- Maybe the confidence of Fat Bastard.
- Okay. - Oh shit.
- The jewelry of Goldmember.
- Oh yeah.
- And then the style of Dr. Evil.
- And Mini-Me ain't even in this at all?
- The height of Mini-Me.
(laughing)
- Well I had all these things I was gonna give up,
then I realized there's a lot of dust and dirt. Yeah, don't touch it. So what would you know?
What about you? I'd just be straight up Biden. Joe Biden. Every straight.
Every foreign personality look. Dick size, whatever. He definitely has a huge one.
Oh my goodness. Could you imagine getting dicked down by Biden? Amazing. By the goat?
Amazing. His just sputtering tip of his penis. Like an old fucking car. Why do you think he can't speak right?
all the blood's going down there.
- 'Cause he's fucking noting every second,
'cause he has some kind of hooked up thing
and he's got hot babes in the other room
pressing a button electronically making 'em cum.
(laughing)
Could be.
- So here's a style guide from some of the members
of this forum.
I try to dress a bar casual, nice dress shirt, low jeans,
and I have an LED belt as one of my peacocking items,
which flashes stop staring at my penis
when I swerve here.
- Oh shit. - But it's kinda broke now.
Very, and I'm really glad that you,
what does this one say?
I'm glad that you have the hat
because you're basically doing exactly
what this guy tells you to do.
- It's a demonstration, right?
- And what does this say?
(laughing)
Go ahead and say it.
- Pussy rubber?
- Yup.
(laughing)
Yup.
- That's fire.
- I'm rubbing it.
- It's changing.
I didn't even know. - I've got an app.
- Oh my goodness.
- Oh my god.
We told you you weren't gonna expect this hat. I know you weren't gonna believe it. That is so wild.
That is about to blow up 100%. Could you imagine dying while it said "pussy rubber" on it?
It's like scanners like there's parts of my face are coming towards the camera.
Because legally we have to consider that your last words. Yeah.
This next person says, "I dress expensively. I peacock when I walk through the mall and grocery
store. Dress lacks dry clean only type, high-end shoes, and a button-up shirt with
sleeves unbuttoned and rolled just below my elbows, unless I'm wearing a suit top.
No tie, leave the collar button loose. At night I wear a glow stick necklace
and/or blinking LED necklace. If you're on the prowl, I try to be head and
shoulders above all others. Night and day, Joshua.
- Wow. - Muff Buster, is that his name?
- Muff Buster, yeah.
(laughing)
Joshua Muff Buster, and that last person was Shaft.
- Wow.
- This next one is from Johnny Rage.
I dress cool and trendy, LOL, such a bad word.
I usually wear big belt buckles and edible jewelry.
(laughing)
- That is a big belt buckle.
- Yeah.
- Eat my bracelet. - Hey girl,
you wanna eat this ice?
- Yeah. - Ooh, man.
- Check that out, that may look like gold
I'm gonna add a little bit edible earrings
Johnny dang laced me up with the full fucking
Wrist made of Tums
Then this next this is for midnight
Should have an edible hat midnight says I once dressed like a smurf. I come from a fancy dress party
I taught myself blue with food
die and had a white smurf hat, blue shirt and white pants. I strolled straight into
the club, passed stunned bouncers and patrons. Not only was I the center of attention of all
night but paid for no drinks and got felt up constantly by HB 1 to 10.
What's HB? Hot bitches? It's like the scale that you rate women on.
HB 1 to 10. Okay. Being an AFC I accomplished nothing though, what a waste.
Women love a six-foot-four smurf.
[laughter]
Dude, can you imagine, you're sitting at the club, right?
And then just like, door busts open, saloon door for some reason.
Damn.
In walks a giant smurf, dirt off your shoulder, Jay-Z.
[imitates Jay-Z's smurf music]
Right, he's just fucking strutting, the bouncer's just jaw-dropping.
Women are screaming.
Yeah, he's like playing that.
Yeah, everybody has something in their mouth and it just falls out.
- Oh my god, there's a poppin' champagne on 'em.
(humming)
- Yeah, this is the type of club that's got like food.
- Yeah.
- Okay, okay, but now, imagine--
- I start choking on a chicken wing and I die,
nobody notices 'cause there's a giant smurf.
- Everybody, everybody has, was on the,
every pickup artist has been reading this forum, right?
You walk in with your Beats pill,
you're playing Dirt Off Your Shoulder, you're smurfed up.
You walk in, there's like five other smurfs already in there.
They all read the same post.
- Hell no.
- Oh no.
- But then you can start partying,
you start ordering D'Ussé.
(laughing)
- All the Smurfs dancing together.
We didn't even know each other before tonight.
- And then all of a sudden you're fucking blowing backs out.
I'll say that much.
- Oh my God.
- This next one, I don't really have to read it.
Not that good.
- Okay, you can skip to that.
- But here's some photos.
- These are some-- - Oh, photo bucket.
- Photos from Ziggy.
- Who's Ziggy?
- I guess this is Ziggy.
- He looks so good.
- That's the name of my cat.
- Damn. - Damn.
- And this is the Motley Crew of Real Social Dynamics.
- Oh, Sum 41, cool.
Papa Zenus, Tyler Durden, Dreamweaver, The One, Sick Boy, Playboy LA, and 26.
Amazing.
And then this is how to spit game.
Tell me.
Okay, I'm ready to learn.
This is some advice from people on the forums, right?
These are just some things that you can say to some ladies to pick them up.
Real and genuine online spellcaster, if you have any of the below problems, think no more
because you have and call spam on this.
No problems as far as Dr. Machinga is concerned.
love spell, instant death spell to kill your enemies, spells to cancel/file divorce, spells
to cure your HIV/AIDS, spells to make impotence protective, spells to get your ex back, spells
to make your wife give birth, and there's a lot more stuff like this, like best African
traditional healer with long distance healing powers, powerful astrologer, expert-
Are these ads?
No, this is not a spit game, this is stuff you say to women.
These almost seem like ads for like, looking for-
No.
No. No? These are spells though? Money increasing and lottery spells. Okay.
Spells with quick results called Dr. Madonna. Yeah that sounds like an ad. Others may notice a
tingling sensation in the fingertips or lightheadedness that causes a smile or
outright laughter. I have noticed that before when I see it when I watch TV
sometimes I do get. Wow. I feel the urge to smile and laugh with some lightheadedness.
Well guessing a spell on you man. Yeah, these spells work so well that
So somebody kissed three girls in one night just by being confident due to the spells and Rachel touched their hand Rachel touched his hand
Rachel's in hb9
So now that I'm a pickup artist you can contact me
Here's my phone number and my LinkedIn. Okay, that is my email address and that's just a photo. I took earlier. Thank you
- That was a great tutorial. - Levitation Mail.
- So now that we know-- - It's a new email site
I've made up. - That's awesome.
- Now that we know, now me and Cameron can kinda go
into our pickup artist journeys, and you can too, Nate.
- Yeah. - Well, you are right,
we've been over this at your-- - Yeah, you are one of the--
- You are a completely legend-- - One of the top dogs.
- Dairy guy status. - The big cheese.
- That's why we wanted you on,
because we knew that you were such a--
- See, like right now, you're rising up this fly.
- Oh my God. - Yeah, there's a fly
coming on me, and I'm like, "Hey, fly,
"do you mind if I hit it slowly?
so slow that I'm in slow motion and you think that I'm kind of frozen.
But I'm actually like...
God damn.
Well, all movement to the fly is going to feel like slow motion because time slows down
for you.
Whoa.
So when you're hitting it, there ain't no such thing as going to pound town with a fly.
If you're big.
If you're small.
How do you say the way I do it?
Dude, yeah.
The experience of shrinking down to have fast sex with a fly would be otherworldly.
To bust instantly.
down busted
flies are nasty
the
they got eight i was there always walk around like this they're like
they can see it from the back and i'm not a human guy
there's a nasty though each of our met right in front of you
they always try to get in the poop to yeah which i don't play that line
No, no, no, no, not for me. I draw the line at number one.
I do not go into the number two world. No, thank you.
All right. Um, so here's a, here's some,
these are just some things I found on this pickup artist form.
I thought were kind of interesting. Yeah. You didn't do a whole weird thing.
I didn't do like a strange kind of thing. Yeah. So you can see,
I didn't even experiment with the theme at all. I like it. I kind of, well,
see I'm doing what's a pickup artist tactic. That's called not given a fuck.
yeah world or even more specifically not giving a mother fuck yeah well
old patrick not given a mother fuck but the i think i might think i may have
uh... focus too much on the peacock you did you keep it you so what you did to
you did something that's called being thirsty
day
which i'm not with a and then they'll have a lot here but
which i would have read this before from you
a girl's gonna kick you to the curb she's gonna do it's like in an m_m_o_ rpg you
put all your points into the peacocking.
- Yeah.
- You should have put like 10 in thirstiness.
(laughing)
- Definitely.
- True.
- I fucked up today y'all.
- It's a hey, another day?
Well you know what, it's actually next year
that you're gonna get another chance.
- Okay.
- It's only one Valentine's Day a year.
So it's actually kind of, it's a big deal.
It's kind of really bad.
Game is like playing a Yu-Gi-Oh card game.
- Shit.
- C-Pix.
Game is like playing Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
Play your cards right and you win or hard in the end.
Except instead of cards, you have one liners and gambits.
you have to say the right things in the right way at the right time just like
you have to play the right combination of cards in the correct sequence in this
card game
and actually attached a few uh... pictures to explain okay and is like
playing you get to see if someone told me about game first and then told me is
like you do you know i would not get the party and so there's gonna help you out
here and i know it's like you do
when the girl has a bit shield up the p_u_a_'s go like
make a card disqualify card false time constraint card game over bitch hand
over your vagina. Oh my god. That's heavy. And then the other one is a Magic the
Gathering binder and all the cards are labeled with sticky notes that say I'm
bored entertain me slave the only reason I find you attractive is because you
remind me of my ex and lame. Damn. So these are like different cards. I didn't realize
that this is how I had to play it. Yeah. I'm playing it more like a sport. Yeah no it's
definitely more like a card game. Yeah. I just dress up and then I hold my gun in
in the club and no one comes up to me.
They clear the club out.
- The gun is a card.
- Yeah, I'm standing in the club like this
and everyone screams and runs.
- That's so fucking weird.
- Except for the one super freak girl though,
who comes up to you when you're doing that.
- Yeah, and she says, "Put down your weapon.
"Put down your fucking weapon, put your hands up.
"I'm gonna fucking put you in jail."
She's a freak.
- She tried to get the handcuffs out.
- Yeah, damn, oh you weird.
- Yeah.
- She's wearing all blue too, a weird blue outfit.
Which is your favorite Tom and Jerry game?
And this is from Get Into The Game.
New forum members start here, general questions.
My top list of Tom and Jerry games are listed below.
One, Tom and Jerry and Refrigerators.
Two, Tom and Jerry Classroom Cleanup.
Three, Tom and Jerry Tales.
Four, Tom and Jerry and War of the Whiskers.
From all of these games, Tom and Jerry Tales takes
is my mind favorite.
I mostly played this game when I am in funny mood.
Which one is yours?
Reply. - Damn, so.
And then the signature that says, "Online Kids Games."
- This is on the Pickup Artist website?
We found two completely different corners of this world.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I found--
- I feel like we've only scratched the surface of this website.
- I think what happened is that probably this person
was a child and Googled game forum
and found a spitting game and posted it.
- Which could actually be very powerful
to teach a child how to pick up women.
- Oh my God.
'Cause imagine how much that skill is gonna develop
by the time they're an adult.
they need some different type of information
'cause they're all on this Andrew Tate bullshit right now.
And they need some people really being honest about game.
- They need more time and Jerry type shit.
- Now that I'm looking at you, bald, right?
And amazingly good looking and successful and rich.
I'm not gonna even say that you could be,
I'm saying how are you not the Andrew Tate replacement
in the positive direction?
- That's such a good fucking point.
I think I definitely could kind of take over
that I think maybe I should move to a foreign country.
- Do something inspirational.
- He left a power voice.
- Yeah, say something inspirational
for the young viewers out there.
Look directly at the camera.
- Which camera, right here?
- Right there, yeah.
- Yo, if you're a young man right now,
and you're alone, and you're single,
and you're trying to hook up,
and you're trying to date, you know what I'm saying?
What I want you to do is, you don't need to be mean,
You don't need to be aggressive, aggro, and alpha.
You just need to be yourself, okay?
And you need to be you.
And I don't care if women hate you, they don't like you,
they think you suck, they think you're weird,
they think you're a fucking loser
and they're saying that to your face constantly.
You just need to just be you,
even if that person is a bad person or you suck.
You just have to keep going with it
until you find somebody who kind of accepts you.
And that might take a long time,
an extremely long time for you to find somebody
who can kind of put up with that bullshit.
But you're gonna get it eventually.
And yeah.
- So be yourself. - That was inspiration.
- I was really trying to be inspirational.
- He's gonna go, we should cut that.
- We're gonna see that on a TikTok or YouTube short.
- Boom, doom, doom.
- And there's gonna be like Lamborghinis
and like B-roll going on.
- And that song's like,
- Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- Yeah, it's gonna be amazing.
- Oh my God.
- I gotta go, we gotta go fast through these.
- Okay.
- Too much cocky, not enough comedy.
I'm finding that when interacting with a set,
I come off as cocky and arrogant and not very funny.
I've never been a really funny guy.
Any ideas on how to dial up the humor?
The show "Californication" is a perfect example
of mixing arrogance and humor,
but even after watching the entire first season,
I still can't seem to produce.
Any other good shows or movies out there
I can watch to get some examples?
Thanks guys.
I would say that the most, the highest riz possible fictional character is probably the Big Lebowski.
Yeah.
Oh, good.
Women are attracted to him straight up.
Yeah, yeah.
Definitely.
100%.
Hi, Shayconzo.
I'm still quite new here, but I hope I can help.
I'm not very good at being cocky, but I'm okay when it comes to making people laugh.
I think the best thing you can do is watch a lot of funny stuff.
Most importantly, laugh at what you find funny and develop a sense of humor.
I watch Simpsons every weekday and two episodes on a Saturday if I'm home.
I really enjoy it and find the humor interesting and how it makes me laugh.
Some other good shows are Friends, My Name is Earl, King of Queens, Everybody Loves Raymond,
Will and Grace, Frasier, Futurama, Family Guy, Tom and Jerry, Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck,
etc.
By watching shows like these on a regular basis, you will soon pick up structures on
how to produce your own humor.
Dude, walking up to a girl and doing Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck.
But there's an amazing entry here which is Family Guy.
You pull up to the clam act.
- Ooh.
(laughing)
- Well you don't want to pull up to the clam
acting like Peter, 'cause Peter's gonna be like,
"Hey, what's up?"
- "I'm jacking my schwank."
- That's true.
- Oh, damn.
The family guy impressions.
(laughing)
- That was good.
- We were saving him.
We were saving him for you.
- That was so amazing, man.
- Two things that I did to dial up my funny are,
one, take an improv class/join an improv club.
These are great ways to help you think on your feet
in a funny way, and if you cannot join a class or club,
look up on YouTube for how to improv.
There's a pretty good series on there somewhere,
also buy a book on improv, buy a mirror and practice. That's what you have to do,
you have to buy the UCB 101 manual. I want to take an improv class where every dude
in there is like looking like mystery. Yeah. Trying to do scenes where they're like hooking up.
See a lot of whips. You look like fucking shit girl. That's the first line I've ever seen. You could do even improv
- I love pickup lines.
- Yeah.
- You can be like, yeah, I can make that object work.
You know, something like that.
- Oh, wow.
- Damn, wow.
- Whoa.
- That is good.
- Talking about her.
- I want you to be my scene partner.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay, maybe something like that.
- Scene partner, no hot topic.
That's what I would say.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna get my Dale.
- I've never seen no partner like you.
- I'm gonna get my Dale close to you.
- You're gonna get what?
- Oh, shit.
- I'll show you videos of me fucking on my trampoline.
- Wow, I wanna take you to a second city.
Ooh, damn.
- I'm trying to think.
- Kind of trying to go to Paris.
- Yeah, I think that you should be
in the Improv Olympics, girl.
- I wanna have sex with you a thousand times
and you give birth to a bunch of little groundlings.
- Yes, yes, that's good.
I'm gonna fuck you so crazy
that they have to put me in an asylum.
(laughing)
Or put you in an asylum, I don't know.
- Both maybe.
- Probably both of those.
- And then we fuck in the asylum too.
That's an improv asylum.
How to set yourself apart from all the other guys.
And this is by a Bart M. OK, that's important.
Well, I don't have enough experience
to say all nines are like that.
But today I saw this gorgeous girl, absolute model,
nicely dressed, nice teeth, big boobs, high heels, smelled good.
She was doing something on her phone.
I think texting Uber.
I said, hey, I was just over there
and I noticed you were checking me out.
She didn't even bother looking in my eyes.
She kept looking at her phone being disrespectful.
I asked her name.
She said it.
I said, "Are you Indian?" She said, "No." I said, "Where are you from?" She didn't
respond. She never looked at me once. She was on her phone all this time. I
understand why this happens. I am just like that other guy that approached her
five minutes ago, who was just like that other guy that approached her six minutes
ago, who was just like that other guy that approached her seven minutes ago.
But what's the solution to this? How do you approach such girls? How do you get
rid of the bitch shield? Or it's better to just walk away and hear what people
have to say to Bart. Bart, I've found out, is somewhat of a character
on this forum. People know Bart and they address him very directly.
Alright, let me see.
Bart!
We'll look past the conversation as you already know your words were weak.
That's fucked.
Bart, you have yet to develop the confidence, courage, and fervor to attract
women of high quality.
Whoa. Bart, you're missing the point. Lay off of Bart. Good luck, Bart.
I thought I exiled Bart a long time ago at the time of his mental breakdown by
highlighting his inaction by offering my help. Looks like we're both back in town.
you're not a lion your field mouse very much low on the food chain and our
barred did you try boxing at bart have you picked up a musical instrument part
did you try and propped part were you actually thinking of asking her if she
was steven spielberg or was that is a need to report are you for real
part of your to respect women and stop calling the bitches part could it be
that's why they have a shield when they see you part why did you approach a nine
when you were smelly and sweaty bar why do you give women numbers when you don't
even when you don't even know who you are part
bart why are you trying to be discreet discreet
part sorry bro didn't mean to upset you where you located bart i can see your
potential part i can't part of a challenge for you break the chain but
the other part of the rise of the fact that well his name's part
now we're getting somewhere bart keep going bart i play music part of the
president's what i love you're going to die one day barbara member that home i
yeah or part
work out fucked up do you know and pick up artist for instance i got here
everyone calls by their name
you know i really are
here. You can do yours.
All right.
I can go to my thing. So I found a different, real quick, I found this one on the Pickup
Artist subreddit. This is a Hooter game. Can you move that over? Somehow it got moved over.
You can just scroll. There's a scroll bar at the bottom.
Hi all. This will be my first post here. How do you guys approach a Hooter waitress? I
mean, Hired Gun Game is a whole other level with thinking of ordering something and starting
from there.
That's a great opening.
I was like, that's probably the number one way.
I think so. I think you got it.
- Yeah.
- Like he already figured it out.
He doesn't need any advice,
but I just thought that that was some good advice.
(laughing)
Okay, so as far as the Pickup Artist Forum,
I focused on NLP and hypnotic seduction,
which NLP stands for, fuck, I already forgot it.
- It's right there.
- Oh yeah, neuro-linguistic programming.
So it's basically hypnosis.
It's hypnotizing women through something called sequences.
So they tell you like, do this and then this and then this,
and then you can have sex with this girl.
- What's crazy about this is I've heard of this,
but not from Pickup Artist
because I downloaded a 900 page ebook about how the government is keeping
slaves. Yeah, it's basically NLP is very popular with the New World Order. Yeah, I
didn't know that. So let's check out some of these posts. So this one is make her
come without touch her. Hey guys, it's my first post here and I want to ask you
something. Once I had read about a very strong technique which allowed the user
to make the HB come without even touching her using anchors, NLP and
chakras to do this. Of course, when I studied about this, I wasn't even aware
of what an anchor is so I thought it was bullshit. Now I want to ask you, do you
know a technique or something similar to this, and I'm not talking about Shades
hypnosis, but just using pure NLP I know it's possible. And this is a pretty
common question. What is an HB? HB, I don't remember what it stands for. Probably a hot bitch, right?
Yeah, it's probably something like that. Yeah. But I find that they use kind of more
scientific terms than you would think. Okay. And then this is a basically the
exact same post, make woman cream anytime she thinks of me. Is there any way to covertly
hypnotize a woman to do the following,
cream any time she thinks of me,
and have the most intense orgasm of her life
every five seconds when we're in bed.
- I think there is a sect of the CIA that is working on this.
- This is what, they were doing MKUltra
to make people go fight in Vietnam,
and then they were like, oh wait, no,
we should be doing this to get some pussy.
- And then they invented this whole other section of--
- There literally is like a whole conspiracy theory thing
about the Monarch Program that's exactly like,
Yeah, it's like literally that's the same hypnosis thing, but it's for so they can
have... I will say, I don't wanna jump too far into this, but I will say that
there are parts of this that are so dangerous that I'm not even sure I wanna
talk about them. There are some secrets that are gonna be revealed here. Some
sensor bars flying into the video for sure. Blowjob pattern, does anybody know it? And this is from
Romeo 7. Oh my God. So I was expecting nobody to know... There's not a blowjob. This is all the way back in 2007.
- Yeah, dude. - So the level
the techniques have gotten to now, 16 years later.
- And this one has a script.
There are three types of DJ patterns.
- Okay, don't say this out loud here.
I don't wanna give you a blowjob right now.
- Well, no, you play the girl.
Okay, so this is the one interesting blowjob pattern.
I think this might work.
Number one, ask her about anything she really loves to eat.
Number two, describe the sensation of eating that food
and amplify with gustatory gusto.
Number three, link it to your dick using a quote dick point.
- Okay, try it out. - Which is often--
- Try it out. - As a dick.
- All right, try it out. - So, hey Cameron,
what do you love to eat?
Something that really makes you salivate
just by thinking of it.
- Chocolate cake.
- Mm, chocolate cake, mm, that's yummy.
I don't know if you can imagine sucking into one
sweet, delicious, juicy chocolate cake now.
Mm, can you taste the sweetness of the cake
swishing inside your mouth?
Mm, so tasty.
doesn't that give you lots of pleasure and happiness? Just think about that.
Mmm, I bet if there were a chocolate cake here now, you'd want it in your mouth.
Point to Dicky. So then I'm like, so does that make you want to blow me?
I am spending all my energy right now to not leap across the table.
I am shaking to be honest.
I can see. So I wouldn't try that at home though.
Must suck Caleb's dick.
It might be too powerful. Uh, speaking of too powerful, by the way. Okay. Okay.
So this is where we get into sort of the ancient secret knowledge. Okay. Yes. All right.
So this is from The Prophet in 2012. Whoa. Second thread I've read in
which someone has recommended Octoberman. It's banned for a reason, guys. It's a
forbidden technique because of how damaging it is. Stop suggesting it to
people until you understand it's dangerous. I didn't even scratch the
surface of this website. So Octoberman, dude, I saw Octoberman and I was like, that's kind of
weird and then I saw it a couple more times so like here stop this shit
already the October man is forbidden it is that way for a very good reason the
pattern is extremely dangerous and in most cases very destructive you should
know that posting any links about forbidden patterns will have
consequences I'm not a whiny bitch so I won't call the mods but if they find
out they will be pissed okay so I tried to look up October man and I found an
e-book the October man's whoa looks fucking dangerous that girl could be
dead. This needs to be adapted into a feature-length film. It has to. The
Octoberman with Daniel Craig. That's such a good name for a movie too. Are you kidding me?
HBO Max original. Unfortunately it was $6.99 and it was a pretty long book so I didn't read it.
We'll get into it another day. Yeah, but I think that... but I would I would caution
anybody who dares research The Octoberman. This is hidden, forbidden, kind of
national treasure level. What? It says "The Mystery." No, it's
mystery what could be the Octoberman sequence. Oh okay. I will say I'd looked it
up and kind of confusing to make it the big mystery. Generally it's about
basically hypnotizing a woman into thinking that if you she doesn't have
sex with you she will die. Oh my god! That is basically what it is. Oh my god. That sounds dangerous.
Yeah it does sound really dangerous. And people have tried it. Fucked up with a
girl this is from Hercules so I told this girl I wanted to have anal sex with her
and told her through text messages and she was stunned she was like WTF and
said why would I say that I told her that's how I felt when I think about her
she was like why do you say that and it's awkward talking to me now I told
her what do you think what should I do should I just not talk to her anymore I
haven't seen her in four months and then decided to tell her did I mess up she
was like don't tell a girl that and other stuff any advice and then he just
said I want to have anal sex with you. Yo, what up? Haven't seen you, when was this?
2010. I haven't seen you at Blockbuster in a minute. This guy's had a pretty serious
journey as a PUA. Yeah. So he wants to use an NLP to stop being
obsessed. I'm assuming it's the same girl. Must be. I want to stop being obsessed
with this girl. What NLP techniques can I use so I could stop being obsessed? I'm
really obsessed. I always think about her and I even tried love spells
which don't work and I was doing it out of ignorance. At least he can admit he was
doing it out of ignorance. This guy had a tragic end to his story, right? Because
watch this. Hercules, October Man sequence, post redacted for breaking 4, posse. So he literally tried to ask for the sacred knowledge and they boomed him. They took him off the face of the fucking planet.
So this shit is getting fucking real. This stuff has to work, right? This is like
pyramid level style, geometric structure. I'm seeing mandalas. There's gonna be tool playing and shit.
- Yeah, you can.
(laughing)
'Cause I can tell you anything that's ending
with man like the Slender Man.
- Yes.
- The Bye Bye Man, which I shouldn't even say.
- Don't even say that.
- Bloody Mary Man.
- Yeah, Candy Man.
- Candy Man.
- So this next person, I think October is Halloween.
- Correct, I think this next person
used the October Man sequence.
- No, nevermind, this is creating own Tyler Durden.
(laughing)
Yeah, you heard me.
Lately I've been thinking about creating
a whole different person that becomes me
when I only wear an earring.
Good thing I never pierce my ear before,
so I have to pierce my ear on top of my ear.
So that's gonna be quite painful.
And time I've pierced my ear time,
my other identity will born.
And when I wear my earrings, he will become me.
He is absolutely alpha, but most importantly,
he can do some nasty shits.
He don't give a little shit about others.
He is true asshole.
That way I can do things I won't, scared to do.
Any idea?
This is AFC Aza.
this person says, oh this is a different person,
this person I think used the Octoberman sequence,
my target died.
(laughing)
By mind programmer.
I should have stopped, I really liked her,
but I ended up going too far with it
and she ended up taking her own life.
Now I'm left with her friends whom I had no interest
in calling me up to console me over the loss,
even though they talked shit about her all the time.
I was only using them to get to her.
What I don't know is if she killed herself over my games,
but the timing of it is all too coincidental to ignore.
I won't lie, I'm crying like a baby now
and I'm angry with myself.
- Holy shit.
- This is the dark side of the Octoberman sequence.
- Yeah.
- But this is a community, right?
And we hold each other up.
So this guy says, "Everything happens for a reason, man.
Cheers to natural playboy."
(laughing)
- Wait, look at that, look at his name and his signature.
- Sometimes when I'm with my chick on the low, I'm a flirt.
- The natural playboy.
- That person is like Blackout Drone.
(laughing)
Everything happens for a reason man. Don't worry if your target died because you did October Man sequence to her
I'm so I think I'm gonna go down a descent to madness and a dark rabbit hole of learning about the Arctic
I think you've set me off
Do not even look it up dude
I you literally have exposed me to this and you know that I'm the type of guy that seeks truth and I look
psychology
I hate that I opened this rabbit hole. You should have told me to get out of the room for this
part of the show. I should have.
Because this is going to ruin my life. We should have just pumped that Goethe-A song
into your headphones the whole time. Damn, you're right.
That's the one song that I know you love to vibe to.
And that was the, Goethe-A is basically the opposite of Dark.
See now I'm going to be so fucked, I'm going to go home and I'm going to be listening to
Radiohead and I'm going to be looking through books at the library on the microfiche.
Radiohead is not October Man Seagulls. October Man Seagulls is like Breaking Benjamin, that
I'm going to be listening to Apex Twin.
I'm going to have an Apex Twin research montage.
I'm going to be looking through newspapers.
Oh my god, October 1998, October 1997, October 19, every year.
Yes, to find the man.
And then I just have one more post here, which is in the miscellaneous.
This is "Where can I find good tires for my favorite car?"
Can anyone tell me where I can find good tires for my car? I live in New York.
Did they get an answer?
Nope. Nobody responded. I think this is the first post on the miscellaneous.
Maybe that's code for something.
Oh shit.
Dude, tire man.
That's true.
Why else would they have to say where they live?
Imagine doing the Michelin Man sequence to a woman. That is so scary to even think about.
I wish I never said that.
that yeah and i mean okay i think what about you you you've learned the
forbidden technique you start trying to pull the october man on some woman yeah
she
she does this she touches her her fingers to a temple amount he started using the
october woman sequence of the idea was it's like a game where it's like a it's
like a sequence war exactly and it's doing the thing where the two beams hit
in the middle of the dragon ball the exactly like yeah energy razor on my
daughter and you both kill yourselves see you're just everything you're saying is
is just you're making it even more obvious
and dangerous, the eye color and sequences.
- I'm sorry, I'm romanticized.
It's not like anime at all, guys.
- I never wanted to know this shit.
I never wanted to be exposed to this, these sequences,
and I feel a darkness inside of me that will never leave.
I feel haunted, I feel cursed.
- I can see it, your eye color has changed.
- I feel different and I feel changed
after knowing these ancient secrets and sequences.
- You're starting to scare me and everyone around you.
- I am, and I don't like it.
- I don't like it either.
but thank you for coming on.
- Absolutely, thank you so much.
- Everybody go check out Joy Tactics.
Go check out Joy Tactics on Patreon.
You guys are on everything.
- On all platforms.
- Every single one.
- Instagram. - That's so amazing.
- Doing it right.
- Stitchers, iHeartRadio.
- Serious. - Pandora.
- We are one of the top,
I think we made one of the top podcasts in Ireland.
We're like on-- - Whoa!
- We're on like irishpodcast.com or something like that.
- Free news he got recently.
- I recently found out I'm Irish.
- Oh, congrats.
- I'm taking it pretty poorly.
- Oh, okay.
- I've been Irish my whole life.
- Shareholder meetings on the 17th.
We'll see you guys there.
Bye bye.
- Bye.
- What does that say?
Oh wait, what could this possibly say?
- Pot about list, but wait, what?
- Vibe?
- Vibes.
- Pot about list vibes.
Pot about list vibes, y'all.
Bye.
(popping)
[BLANK_AUDIO]