Alright.
[music]
Alright, you chipmunks. Ready to sing your song?
I'll say we are. Yeah, let's sing it now.
Okay, Simon?
Okay.
Okay, Theodore?
Okay, Alvin?
Alvin?
Alvin!
Okay!
Christmas, Christmas, time is near.
Time for toy and time for cheer.
We've been good, but we can't last.
Hurry Christmas, hurry fast.
One's a flame, that's lose the loop.
Me, I want a hula hoop.
We can hardly stand the wait.
Sleep Christmas, don't be late.
[Music]
Okay fellas, get ready. That was very good, Simon.
Naturally.
Very good, Theodore.
[laughs]
Uh, Alvin, you were a little flat. Watch it.
Uh, Alvin. Alvin.
Alvin!
Okay!
♪ Want a plane that looms the loom ♪
♪ I still want a hula hoop ♪
♪ We can hardly stand the weight ♪
Please Christmas, don't be late
We can hardly stand the wait
[Music]
Good morning! Good morning my two good friends.
Friends happy start now. Do we start the show? I don't know. Why wouldn't we start?
Okay, and the first thing we're saying is good morning. Not yo, yo Caleb nice outfit
You look almost exactly you look this is what you look like every day
You look almost exactly like a very famous celebrity. No, we look exactly the same as you do every day. What's different?
Won't you take me to oh?
New Christian Dior jacket this oh yeah, yeah, yeah, he's not even wearing the
No, look at it. Oh, this is one. Let me check the tag. It's fucking fancy. Oh, that's a that's a replica
It's Christian. No, it's real. That's real. It's Dior. I'm on my Christian Dior Santa flow and the beard is - yeah
It's Christian. Oh, it's also Christian Dior. Oh my god. Wait. Whoa wearing a beard. That was weird
Put do it again do it again. Oh my god
I missed my ear on the on the uptake on this. I thought that was your new thing rubbing alcohol
I think that I'll probably be dressed pretty much exactly like this for most of December and honestly
I'll probably be taking homeless people's cups and stuff. Yeah, taking their cups. Yeah, I know they have those cups like
With it
Morocco or Morocco, so they're using that and as we can make a more rocky easy well they did
Okay, how could also learned you could make a harmonica out of tissue paper?
The thing is what I don't understand about these homeless people with their damn cups
full of money, it's like don't you want to put a lid on that?
If you flip over, your money's going everywhere.
Yep.
Tell you what they should put a lid on.
And there's a guy going around flipping.
And I'm flipping them.
Yeah, I'm flipping them up and I'm like, if you would add a lid on this, your money'd
be in your cup.
But now it's all over the ground and I'm sucking it up like an anteater.
Shaking it all over the place.
I think they should just get a piggy bank of themselves.
They get, with all the money they make, they should buy a ceramic piggy bank of their face.
A piggy bank would actually be a good idea.
I saw a homeless guy counting money.
Rich.
Counting the stack.
He straight up had a band.
Did he have a rack on him?
Yeah.
Damn.
Speaking of this...
I saw a homeless lady with a rack on her.
When I was walking to the office this morning, speaking of a homeless woman's rack, I saw
a guy's penis on the way to the office this morning.
That's the downstairs rack.
That's the coat rack.
Yeah.
I was walking down the block. He was on the at the other end of the block going coming towards me.
He stopped and he pulled his pants down and took his penis out and he peed one squirt of pee onto
the ground and pulled his pants back up. That was he a nut? Was he a heavyset guy? No I don't think
so. That was nut. No you don't squirt a little bit of pee. I guarantee it was pee. No that was unhealthy
nut. It was watery because he does it so often. He didn't touch his shit. A couple weeks ago,
ago, a couple weeks ago. I was wondering if it was a heavy set guy because a
couple weeks ago I was up early one morning I was going to get like
breakfast and I saw just like a big big heavy set homeless man just walking.
You can say it. He was a fat homeless man. Yeah why do you say heavy set a million times?
Also this guy I don't think he was homeless. I think it was just a guy. Yeah okay.
Well I saw a guy scrubbing and rubbing his balls and asshole in the
middle of the scrubbing completely different.
Peeing on Myrtle Avenue in front of the bank.
This guy wasn't a friend of respectful.
It's disrespectful.
This what this guy did wasn't sexual.
I want to get that he squirted pee because he wanted to show
how strong is his pelvic floor muscles or whatever muscles
control your prostate is that your prostate.
Okay, it also controls the jizz not an expert of jizz or piss.
Okay, if anything I'm not you did this whole story was made
up to prove that you knew what muscles.
We knew Caleb hates homeless people, but he loves prostates.
I actually fuck with the homeless heavily, and I used to feed them.
I do. I do.
I don't do it anymore for church.
Yeah.
I do like their community.
They do have a great ass community.
They make good poetry too.
Yeah.
They're too addicted to drugs for my taste.
A lot of them are funny.
Funny looking.
They say shit like, "Need money for weed."
I do.
On their side.
They get it tattooed on their side.
I saw a guy in Vegas, I went to Las Vegas, which you can probably tell based on my kind
of aura that I'm bringing in.
But I went to Las Vegas and there was a homeless guy that had the funniest fucking sign I've
ever seen, man.
It said, "You need money for strippers and alcohol."
What?
And I said, "Wait."
Pretty cool.
"What the hell's wrong with you, you fucking idiot?"
And he said, "No, it's just a funny sign.
I'm gonna use this on food and drugs."
And I said, "Okay, well that's fine."
And I gave him a dollar.
Or like villains stole my family.
Villains stole my family is really good.
I've never seen that one.
You see that everywhere.
Villains stole my family.
I've never seen that.
A homeless person.
A villain attacked my home planet.
My home planet was destroyed by villains.
Stuff like the abductor.
The abductor abducted me.
The abductor is my villain.
Dude, the abductor sucks so bad.
My nemesis did this to me.
And the nemesis attacked my nemesis in the dark.
The Nemesis, the Nemesis goes around.
Bigfoot ate my whole family.
Sinned in past life, reincarnated as this.
Reincarnated as homeless.
And then an arrow and he has flies buzzing around him like pig pen.
Punished by God but keeping my faith.
God is testing me.
God is testing my faith.
Do not help me.
I'm trying to grind harder.
Spit on me.
life more worse. More worse-er. Yeah. Need to go school. Need money for go school. Don't
let me go school. Need be stupid for God. I think it would be pretty fun to be homeless
in certain cities. But yeah, I think Vegas is a fun one because if you can, I saw quite
a few homeless people. I don't think it's fun to be houseless anywhere. I wish I could
electrocute you. I would love to be homeless in Las Vegas because you're, you
can walk, if you go, because it has everything, you know? You walk around the
Venetian, you could go swim, you can bathe in the canals of Venice, right? You want
to go see the Statue of Liberty, it's right there. If you want to go, yeah,
if you want to go pass out on the pyramid, you want to pass out in New York City, you want to
pass out in the Mandalay Bay. You want to see the Eiffel Tower, it's a plane trip
away. Exactly, you want to pass out in the middle, here's, and if you
want to kill yourself instead of jumping off a bridge there's no big bridges you
go to a shin-lim magic show you have them make you disappear and you get sent to
wherever the cards go damn that's true see any magic shows out there no but I
showed my magic on the dance floor yeah did congratulations
great work yep I saw actually saw video and viral yeah yeah a viral video go
viral yeah pull that up yeah pull it on me dancing and then here's what I think
about homeless people. Okay. Here's what I have to say. Okay. I think that a homeless
person, if you think about it, the world is their home. And all of outside is their home.
And they have the biggest home of all. So we should be taking that from them. They are
should be grateful. Yeah. Yeah. So that they have this redistribute the wealth. Did you
see what you see what Eric Adams wants to do? No. He's making a big fun summer camp.
Jesus Christ. Yep. Here I am. He's making a big fun summer camp. This was me. Oh my
God that was that was you and your brother uh-huh me and my two brothers my
two brothers we basically you guys are saying no actually it was it was
completely improvised Wow yeah we just were very we have a
brotherly connection what's that pole you guys are that's my brother's walking
stick oh yeah and also got paid yeah and also we had a yeah we others are really
skinny yeah they're yeah well that's me on the left side my brothers in the
middle and my other brothers on the very back who's your leg like a little
broken that day we had to break my three brothers and also I had my yeah yeah I
just didn't want it whoa you're a little close oh my god oh yeah I'm pretty much
an attention whore kind of hog. You know, we actually killed that guy with the camera.
That hurt really bad when I did that.
Oh my god.
You're gonna need two walking sticks. Oh, thank god, I just see there's two walking sticks actually.
Oh my god, it looks like there's five or six.
Yeah, we basically had to bolt us all together because of our familial bond.
And yeah, my foot is really small. I have two very small feet.
Wow, that's great. I mean, congratulations on that.
My viral love.
Thank you guys all for the viral love. You know I always appreciate it every time.
Yeah, I do want to, I mean, speaking of Las Vegas and Santa, I do want to check in, you
know, last episode we checked in on.
Oh, that's right. Yeah, Santa was in Las Vegas.
Santa was in Las Vegas.
That's very weird.
What a funny coincidence.
So we actually have our proprietary PalFud Santa tracker.
Yep.
FudTech3000.
- Yeah, Swap Tech 3000.
- Think about this, okay.
- What?
- Santa goes to Las Vegas.
- Shut up.
- Santa goes to--
- Whoa.
- Play with your--
- I don't have anything, I'll play with this, all right.
- Santa goes--
- Don't open it though, 'cause it's worth a lot of money.
- That's collectible.
- Santa goes to Las Vegas last week, right?
- Yeah.
- Caleb, I love you.
- Caleb goes--
Caleb goes to Las Vegas.
- Yeah, the next week, or the same, I don't remember.
- The same day.
- The same day, was it the same day?
will he's in las vegas
i think he's a copycat
do you think maybe i think working with santa
because we don't know the identity of saint
that's true we don't may will find out someday but
okay can we what it was not what i was going on here and now
well you're fucking the dead body of your readers and assert is really on
point to that's definitely a kind of a hip-hop santa you know uh... explains
It's a dancing, but let's check where Santa is today. Let's check the tracker here. Okay. Well. He's on earth. We know that all right
Oh, he's coast okay. Coach. Don't be toast now. What's this? Okay? That's Rikers. I couldn't that's Rikers
He's in Rikers Island. Do you think what?
Prisoners get coal every year, so it's not delivering no fucking press no I mean oh for a second
I was like okay Santa's in Las Vegas last week Caleb comes back dressed up like Santa, and then it says he's in New York
But no, I mean that Santa's clearly oh my god
Booked holy shit, and he's 70 and that doesn't even look like okay, so Caleb is not Santa
I will rule that out. We were you thinking I was Santa for a little bit. Yeah, poke my lips out like this
Can you put your eye through the beard and see what that might look like
This actually that like Cyclops Santa a lot. That's a little scary is what it looks like you look like the movie wizards
You look like
Like you look like freaking Jason Voorhees from Friday the 13th part 2 all right
Nerdy for my nerd heads whoa
That's the cell they're keeping him in Rikers Island. I don't realize it was so high-tech
Wardens name all over
Donald Ian Smith, it's holographic
Smith you let Santa go you fucking let him crap. How dare you?
This guy's a Scrooge. Well. We'll see if we can handle that tomorrow or in the next few days, and maybe Santa will be
In Las Vegas Santa Claus yeah, oh hell no okay, well, okay, this was just him and his breath
I I still don't know who Santa is someone told me that Santa is real. Yeah, I don't know what you're doing
Someone told me it's my mom and my dad, but I've never seen them in the suit.
No, Santa is...
Listen, pal, we have a whole month of December in front of us, and we are going to investigate.
By Christmas Eve, we will know the true identity of Santa, and that's a promise.
Okay.
That's a Cameron promise.
Maybe we'll be slicing them open, too.
Okay, are we making that an all three promise?
Making that a triple promise.
Triple promise.
Ow, that fucking hurts me.
We will know the true identity of Santa.
Well, thank God.
Yeah, or thanks Santa. I was in Jesus God son. I was in Las Vegas, and it was very fun
I was there for a place another picture of Caleb with his friends in Las Vegas. Yeah, we had a really good time in Las Vegas
I like your black dress Caleb. Yeah, that's not me. I think you know it so that's you on the left
And then those and then who are you with here? I'm with Derek and Judd Derek and Judd
Yeah, that lady who's that Fox in the middle? That's like they're I don't know their shared wife or some
Basically, we just all I would love to we basically went out into the strip clubs and tried to fuck a hoe whoa
Yeah, we all tried to double team and quadruple team some hoe, but quadruple
Yeah, but she said she'd only do triple teaming and couldn't do a quadruple team not even even credible
No, I'm teams only so I had to get I had to not even be a part of the teams really m3
they triple team some fucking hoe named Rebecca. I do realize I have noticed hoes nowadays,
they're like, "I only want an odd number team. I'll have a one team or a triple team, a single
team. You can single team me, but you can't double team me." Dude, I love going home single
teaming my wife. God, dude. Yeah, man.
Single team. Hoes nowadays, they just want a single team or triple team or quintuple team.
Yeah, I ran a train.
It's like, "I want a quadruple team because me and my three brothers are here."
Yeah.
I ran a train. Me and my five cousins are here. I want to do a six team.
I seriously want a triple team. I want six of us to go team you.
I ran a train, yeah, Hyperloop. Yup.
Yeah, just me. Just me and one car.
Yeah, you ran a diaper poop.
I'm like, I want to run a train with two cars. She's like, no, one car, three.
Or five, seven, or nine. Or any number that ends in those numbers.
I want to be a human centipede.
Some girls nowadays are so nerdy and slutty, they're only doing prime teams.
That's true.
They want a one team or a nine or a seven.
No, nine is not prime.
I don't remember what the prime numbers are.
That was immediately for nine.
I thought nine was prime.
Three is the next one.
Nine is prime.
Two is not prime.
Two is the special one.
Nope, nine is not prime.
Two is the weird one or something.
I don't know, man.
Shut the hell up.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
These hoes are making me do math
to know how much team. What is your prime number?
And it's like, I don't get it.
Yeah, they're trying to make me do math.
Your age plus my age minus seven or whatever.
Man, what the hell is that?
I had this crazy night the other night. I 1.5 teamed this girl with a gnome.
A gnome? Yeah, gnome Chomsky. He's coming dust. And then I 5000 teamed her with an army of gnomes.
You fucked up one girl with an army?
army.
Me and
baby, how about this? How about you, me and the entire army
and we all fuck you?
You mind if I bring the army? Do you have a friend for my army?
You know, I'd speak. Hey, speaking of Christmas, yeah, stay on this kind of
the sexual tip here.
Mary, she got zero teams.
Damn!
She got zero teams to make Jesus.
She did get zero teams.
And then when it comes to Jesus,
there are zero teams, we're all together.
Damn.
Always one.
You are actually on a fucking fire today.
Zero teamed, zero teamer.
And her name was Mary, right?
Yeah.
And she got married.
She was unmarried.
Mary unmarried.
That's quite contraried.
CBS, you gotta jump on that.
CBS, Mary unmarried, that sounds like a perfect show
for your comedy lineup.
That is, it does sound like,
Mary Unmarried sounds really good.
They need to do a gritty reboot.
Single and ready for Kris Kringle.
Oh, yeah.
Jesus' birthday.
Hallmark, check that.
Let's pitch some Hallmark movies right now, all right?
I used to love watching Hallmark movies
on my NASDAQ.
What about Mark in the Hall?
Oh, yeah. Mark in the Hall.
He could be a hall monitor.
Dick the Hall.
Dick the Halls.
Monitor.
Dick the Thug.
Dick the Halls with...
They don't do enough Hallmark movies
about a sad gangster who learns of me at Christmas.
That's true.
I saw one, but he wasn't even a gangster really.
I have it dude.
Okay.
Dick the halls with Bob and Marley.
Damn.
Weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed.
Why would you, why is Bob Marley involved?
Puff, puff, puff, puff, puff, puff, puff, puff.
He wasn't even in S. There's two guys, two characters named Bob and Marley.
Your brain just made a connection because you're a stoner.
I'm a stoner because I thought I heard Bob and Marley.
It's just two guys named Bob and Marley.
What's wrong with me?
You probably see two guys walking down the street and be like, "Whoa, this makes me want
smoke weed. I need to get my head out of the ash tray.
I need to get my head out of the ash tray.
Smoke the bomb with Cheech and Chong.
Their names could be Cheech and Chong.
It could be their full name.
It's Bob Chong and Cheech Marley are the characters in my movie.
It's actually not that far off.
And my movie is not a stoner movie. It's rated G.
G for ganja?
No. G for general audiences.
and it's about, it's a Winnie the Pooh knockoff.
- Yeah, the general.
- Yeah, the car insurance.
- You guys are generally crazy.
- You're generally...
(laughing)
- You guys are making me, you guys are crazy in general.
- Look at your windscreen.
That shit looks like a muffin.
- You have an insane energy today, Cameron.
You're like Johnny Carson today.
- Flip it on its side, it looks exactly like a pot pie.
- You're like just attacking--
- I think something's wrong with my body.
- You're like attacking the hoop in a real way.
You're like kind of destroying. You're like really you're gonna ruin it. No, no, I like kind of can't even look at you right now because it's so funny to me.
Want to hear a joke I wrote about a concert I was at? Yeah.
So I was at the Dinosaur Jr. concert the other night with my girlfriend. Okay.
So she goes to the bathroom, right? Ew. Meanwhile, bathroom line for the women's bathroom at that show probably zero long.
Meanwhile, meanwhile, back to me.
But my mic is your popover windscreen.
I'm like, she's probably, I'm like, oh, she's lost forever.
She's gone.
She's never, because imagine trying to recognize my ass from behind a Dinosaur Junior concert.
Damn.
True.
Wait, show the back of your head.
Who's that?
Is that Cameron or is that?
Oh, is that Jay Maskis himself in the crowd?
Yeah, that's him.
Yeah?
Yeah, that's probably what girls are thinking.
what girls are saying or they think you're Lou Barlow. Someone's name is Jay
Mascis? Yeah. He wears an eyeball hat. Uh-huh. It's a Mischka hat. He's still on.
He still wears that Mischka hat. He only wears one Mischka hat? Yeah. He loves that Mischka hat.
Eyeball hat. When I was in Las Vegas, I went to go see the Moscone Cup, the pool
championship, and there's this guy. It was awesome. It was so much fun. It's Europe
versus the USA. So it's all and it took place in the USA and the USA people are
just going crazy and I'm part of that too so I'm going crazy yeah and there's this
one guy yeah there's one pool player named Billy Thorpe and he used to be on
the Moscone Cup but then he got kicked off because he was in a he had a match
against like a Spanish guy and he like missed a ball or something he was like
he starts screaming out of me like you Mexican piece of shit so he was there
He's banned from playing yeah, but he came and he got like 15 different seats around the arena
So he could just run around he wore no shirt American flag overalls
$100 bills into the fucking
Did he was a man that's it was a when you talk I can only look at your mouth. It's frame
It's just white sir. I can't look above you look like that video. It's got you look like you look like
I would big lips check it up on Frank's list.
Why have you seen this video? I haven't seen that one.
Do you guys think I...
Am I doing a plump lip challenge?
That's what you look like right now.
You guys are learning right now.
Glory, glory, hallelujah hole.
Merry Christmas.
Yep, that's just flags.
Why have we got the German flag today?
What?
This looks like a German flag?
Yeah, the black, yellow, and red.
Yeah, you're right.
And I have red and white on.
Oh, and I'm yellow.
You're Polish, dude.
And black.
That's just the facts.
You're Wiz Khalifa.
[laughs]
You are the Wiz Khalifa of our entire crew.
[sniffs]
Is that the Belgium flag?
Yeah, it is.
'Cause you're tall, which is very Wiz-ish.
Yeah, he's like 6'5".
And I'm a Wiz kid.
You're a Wiz kid.
I'm a wizard.
I've seen you take a Wiz. Your shirt's the color of Wiz.
You never saw me take a Wiz.
I've seen you take a Wiz.
When?
You don't fucking know my life.
I've seen I've snuck in on you taking a whiz. There's a GoPro in the bathroom
No, yeah, I would we rent this place from Chuck Berry because I'm a pro at going I look around 360 degrees
I make sure this
We should switch you have the worst mic you should have the better one today cuz you're on fire
Yeah, I have that app that people why do we have a bad mic today Caleb just forgot mine at home doesn't matter
I have that app that people use that people are always like I noticed this this air freshener at my Airbnb
It's actually a camera and you know that people are is like there's this app that scans for cameras on your Wi-Fi
Yeah, I use that in bathrooms. Yeah, and I don't use the bathroom unless there's at least three cameras. That's right
Show yeah, yeah
IP upside down what is that whole thing?
I'm gonna sit down like a bad you know what I really you know when there's a bathroom, and it's um a single bathroom
but they have a bunch in a row.
- Yeah.
- And it's like they're stalls, but they're like full rooms.
Well, that's what I was saying.
Wouldn't it be great to be able to have one spot
where you can put your hand on the wall
and you know the person on the other side
is putting their hand on the same place
on the other side of the wall.
- Oh my God.
- And you can feel their energy through the wall.
- That's like a glory hole for like kids.
- For, no.
- You want to make that?
- That's a glory hole for kids.
- No, it's like a kid-friendly glory hole is what I mean.
Like you could do that.
- Why do you want a kid-friendly glory hole?
- I don't want that.
I'm just saying it's like a PG version.
- Well, why would you want to be touching hands with a kid?
- I'm not saying, I'm saying that even a kid could do that.
I'm not saying that,
(laughing)
I'm not saying it would be built for kids.
I'm just saying like anybody could do that.
- He's just digging himself deeper and deeper.
- With you?
- No, with whoever, man.
I'm taking this stand out a bit.
- With a man?
- With a man or a woman?
- With any man.
- It's not gay if you hold hands with another man while peeing.
- It's not holding hands though.
It's not like it's not a data transfer energy to another man like eating if I
Like if you put your hand on the other side of this we can feel each other
This is maybe a little too thick and maybe there's too much Ruth. Yeah
There wouldn't be a roof in my bathroom situation. I don't think I mean like it doesn't it's not about like if I put my hand
Under the table right here you can feel me as my cock and balls
Yeah, and you can feel me through the foliage is touching them
You just use you just can be touched as much as you're usable. We'll just use your consumable to me
Yeah, you're basically just an object. You're a potion or elixir no doubt
I would love to spray you on stuff you want you want to spray me like a health potion. Yeah, yeah
If I could just yeah, I could just go like this and I could go like that and you'd spray something
Oh, this is a good idea though like any kind of non-sexual
Like way to see my own sexual way to communicate in the bathroom in the bathroom with the people who are next to you
- That's a great idea. - A can and a string.
- I'm not a sexual...
- (laughter)
- Yeah, buddy, it's called your phone.
- My childhood house, they had this thing on the doorbell.
- He wants a child house,
where he can put this glory hole in.
- He does, though.
- He does want that. - Who's he? Me?
- I take that fist bump back! I don't want that!
- You fist bumped it. - Oh my God, a hole that's
fish-shaped so you can't put your penis through it,
so you can only fist bump when you take a crap or piss.
pissed. You could put your penis through there. How big is your fucking cock? It's fist hole
shapes. No, it's about the shape. It's not about the size. It's square versus circle.
The physicists will make it work. You have a social penis? Closer to social air then.
It has to meet like... There's a switch, right? Or it could have glass shards pointing so
you can't... It should just scan your penis to see if it's a penis or an ellipse. Above
the doorbell there was a hole and there's a tube that goes all the way up to the
second floor and you can talk into it and the person upstairs puts their ear to
it yeah and you can and you go like hey it's me so something like that in the
bathroom but it if it's a row of stall these room stalls and there's a row of
holes on the wall and you can talk to any they're all labeled with numbers so
it's like it's like I know my friend went into five I mean I don't know how
is it going yeah but holes is like okay tin cans people could cut the string and
steal the can. That's a good point. Homeless people would be putting money in those things.
I never understood this about glory holes. When you go into a glory hole, the whole thing
is like, "Oh yeah, I went to a glory hole, but I thought it was a woman sucking my penis
and it was a guy, it turns out." Aren't you in the guy's bathroom? You're in the men's
bathroom. What the hell are you doing? Go into the woman's bathroom and start taking
shits if you really want to get your dick sucked by a girl so bad. You know what you're
Going into the men's bathroom speaking of this all your life. So here we go
Maybe now okay a new bathroom idea
Maybe it's maybe it's the girls stalls on one side and boys stalls on the other and the communication holes are through the walls
but so it's like
There's one a and one B
And it's like a 1a through 10 a and 1b to through 10 be all a is boy all B's girl
He's as red as his suit right now. I think we should hear about
about which your about
you probably will tell for the first
funny things it goes anywhere okay
oh yeah only there's that's definitely some
like a brown turn up kinda fetish
that somebody's like i would have to move out of a glory hole
what would you do if you were if you were you're into it
you into a bathroom as a glory hole and so on the other side of you do not pull
up guiding we had don't do that it's not not only i would pull up guy eating
food is a good
hot girl
which so which ended good with the
and then a gold guy shits in her...
A gold guy?
A golden guy?
A golden guy walks up?
A golden guy!
A golden...
Oscar?
I don't know.
Oscar walks up, shits...
I don't know what color he is, but he shits in her big lips.
And she's blonde.
Blonde.
You know there's like a fetish where people like, they want to paint themselves metallic.
This is the guy who does it.
Yeah.
So somebody like this...
Yeah, but he doesn't he doesn't gold. That's a common misconception. He
poops. He poops. Green brown and very, very green. Speaking of speaking of
Caleb's thing,
we have a list today.
Oh, do we? We do have a list. It's a list I found.
It's just a it's a
here. Hit me the
jolly today. Well, it's
I smoked weed five days ago, and I just my head is for real is from bad girls Bible
It's the complete list of
239 yes, sir
Uh-huh is it can a complete?
Sexual fetishes and kinks list are we doing all 239 today. We're not doing all 239
I think we'll just go through the the best of yeah
Why do I'm gonna come up with more right now can I can I could have a prediction yes?
Yes. If this is a new one and no one's done it yet, I get a reward.
Okay. Finger play.
(laughter)
Buddy.
If finger play's not on here, I get a reward.
Does it look like I have a really small head?
No. Damn it.
No, it doesn't. Sorry, man.
Sorry, yeah. That's a bummer.
(laughter)
I'm ready. I'm having way too much fun at this.
much fun. Click on the other screen so it doesn't get fucked up. So this is the list.
It's like, oh there's also a discreet newsletter, but we talked previously
about the definition of kinky and what makes a fetish. Now it's time to list all
of those in one place. It's unlikely that you've heard every fetish on this list,
on this list of kinks. We'd be willing you have or have at least
thought about a few of them. Some of them were fairly common after all. All right,
So maybe what we're doing here. We should just go through these and say whether or not we have this that's what I was thinking
Yeah, okay, so so this first one is a
So a base of ilia, which is the attraction to people in neck braces wheelchairs cast or other devices that impair mobility?
That was documented for the first time occurring in a woman in the late 80s
It may be a part of a medical fetish enjoyed because it restricts so I know that we've talked that we've done this exact
joke about other fetishes before, but imagine being born in the year 100 and
being a really attractive people in wheelchairs.
Yes, that's tough.
Well, that's what maybe...
It's a chicken or the egg thing because I feel like you haven't seen...
Well, it came from Flintstone cars.
Oh.
That's the first wheelchair.
But that's probably what has driven most invention in the world.
Yeah.
It's probably Thomas Edison was addicted to electricity and like electrocuting women.
And he was like, I'm going to put that in a bulb.
Yeah, I want a bulb of that.
I want a bulb that I can...
I want a bulb that lets me see me do this.
Yes.
What if I could take the byproduct of my fetish and make the room brighter with it?
Good idea.
Or play music.
He just said, "I want a bulb of that."
I just want a bulb.
Bulb it.
Bulb that.
Bulb it up.
Just put that in a bulb.
What's a bulb?
I don't know yet.
I think I will be finding out.
Bulb it.
You know, a bulb.
Yeah, because they had bulbs before light bulbs.
They had onion, well bulbs are plants before that.
Yeah, they had onions before light bulbs.
They definitely did.
They had onions.
I say the onion is the mother of invention.
Yeah.
And this next one here.
Oh, this is a quick quiz.
I mean, no. Click on that.
Click on that photo. I think it'll bring us to a
list.
Yeah. Or it brings us to this quiz here.
And I figured, oh, great.
Has a guy ever complimented you two on your
pro job skills?
For me? Yeah.
I would say.
Rarely, right?
Rarely. I'm not so good.
Yeah. OK.
Can you deep throat without gagging?
I know the trick is you have to hold your thumb.
Okay.
Do we have a prop?
No?
So you go fast like that.
You're kind of an in and out sucker.
Yeah.
Oh man, is that what girls do to girls' penises?
Is that what they do?
Is they touch their back thing?
I didn't even think about that.
That's horrible.
How do they not vomit?
I don't know if people do that.
I don't know.
(laughter)
- I don't know if it beats me, man.
- Women are magic.
- How do you do that so well?
- Oh, my finger is a thing.
- I can do it with my toothbrush.
- That tasted like pepperoni.
- I can do it with my toothbrush really well.
- I didn't even eat any pepperoni.
- I could do my pinky.
- I did not eat pepperoni today.
- So if your penis looks like,
is this dimensions, I could deep throat you.
throw a hand he's losing it.
(laughter)
Well you do your fingers like this.
Hey, you know what? I guess no I gag every time.
This one goes out to girls.
This episode goes out to girls.
Dedicated to every girl in the world.
That is fucking impressive.
Do you regularly make eye contact when giving him oral sex?
Um, sometimes but I make it really awkward.
I'm too shy personally.
I make it awkward as hell.
If I was a girl, I'm thinking about it more.
Do you use both of your hands?
entire time. Doesn't it make you use both your hands, the guys that have a fucking monstrously
huge cock. No, or you can just be on the tip and your hands can be like on either side
like this. Playing it like a freak. T-Rex. True. Alright, if you overlap it like a golf
club. Do you swallow? No. Sometimes but I hate it. Never, I never swallow. Wait, why
is always not an option? Have you ever struggled to make a guy orgasm during a blowjob? Yes.
Yeah. It may have happened. It's happened many times. But I made him come using a different
Yes, I do a facial every time.
I don't usually do a facial.
I always end it with a facial.
I usually
I usually crouch down
like I'm going to do a facial and I dodge out of the way
at the last second.
How confident are you when giving oral sex to a guy?
I'm quite confident.
I guess that's a good point.
Wait, let me change my answer.
I feel like a blowjob queen.
You're steamrolling this here.
Let's relax for a second.
a great idea for women out there. Yeah. Because I'm trying to make it easier now because now
I learned the horrors of oral sex. Yeah. Is that you can make them think they're going
to come on your face and just dodge it. Just dodge, yeah. They're not going to care once
they've already fucking done it. Exactly, because they, yeah. Or even better. Now you
can only get with that once probably. But after that, you know, you can watch me once.
I matrix dodge it. I go backwards. Yeah. If you go, or if you just say like, I promise
I'm not going to dodge it this time. I'm not going to dodge it. Whoa, I tripped. Yeah. It
goes all over a picture of his family.
What?
No!
Oh, God.
That's my glass photo of my grandma.
You hit our pet bird.
Great.
It missed and went all in my hands.
Come shot.
Missed and went all in my hands.
I'm sticking it up me making a baby out of it.
Every time I come, my parrot knows that every time I jizz, I say, "Come shot."
Come shot.
I'm like, "Come shot!"
Come shot!
Yeah, come shot.
That's nasty.
Yeah.
I used to say Kobe, but...
Then he died.
And then I said with a thing that the closest thing that
Why would you say Kobe is a sexual assaulter? I know it's why I stopped when I learned that
Have you ever initiated a blowjob when he wasn't expecting it and caught him by every time I surprise him
I've never given an expected
Full of surprises I jump out of places. Yeah. Yeah, it's not like we're sitting together, and I suddenly do I sneak up
I'm under the bed. I'm under there for six hours. I grab his ankles. I pull him under the bed
And I start sucking him from the back so he can't see me dear regularly. Yeah for sure regularly. Yeah, whoa
That's not possible no
That's straight
Is yodeling you put yodeling he's loud
Are you happy with your current blowjob? No? I'm not mostly unhappy. Oh, yeah
Wait, how it's a low job using your score
I've put together a special report on the five dangerous mistakes that will destroy your sex law
I shouldn't have taken so we should receive this report we can get this in our email all right. Let's get it. Let's get it
Wait, why'd you switch to that camera switch back to that camera?
And
I'm excited to see what these all say but first let's get back to the list maybe yeah
Let's get let's get back to this see that later
Okay
Auto plus bow, but you can't read no I should have worn my glasses guys
Plus a feeling it's a type of flush of feelia where a person is aroused by the idea of being a stuffed animal
Especially a cartoonish one being a stuffed animal being an animal which I feel like there's a distinction between this and a furry
There's also there's a there's a distinction for me
I have this but I
specifically for being a webkinz because I really like the idea of having a code that I can be used to play games online with
Yeah, I would love to have a little avatar of myself that goes mining for gold coins
Yeah, like a firefighter chair imagine if the guy in the
Fucked me in the game
What oh the guy?
Fucked in the in the game. I fucked me like so I'm getting fucked as a webkinz. I'm the leopard
Okay, I'm getting fucked in my butt. I'm uploaded
Meanwhile, the guy in the curio shop, he's got me in the cave.
He's got me on all fours.
I'm going--
[IMITATING MACHINE GUN]
--in the computer.
I'm getting two at once.
Oh.
I'm getting double teamed virtually.
That's crazy.
I'm back thinking about teaming.
If I was the real Santa, you would be off the list.
I'd be off.
Yeah, I'd be getting you off.
There would be no naughty or nice for you.
No, no, no.
You wouldn't even be on the--
Striking me from the records?
You might as well be fucking dead.
if I expunging me just redacted you don't exist. Your social security numbers
gone
because you know Santa controls that of course. How do you think he keeps
trying all the kids exactly the kids have to say everyone's name Mohammed
yeah all that's gonna be hard plus I could be at work. My webkins is getting
railed. Do you feel it? You have a toy. I come home and I have a USB that I
unplug. I put in the back of my head like the matrix and I got like
all comes in at once every time I got real during the day while I was at
I think that in a couple years probably will just so every everybody stuff up
Yeah, just have it USB USB C port USB C port would be standardized. Yeah
MacBook charger
Yeah, it's like I don't need to buy a toy
Well that would make this one a lot of people with this fetish very upset
You can already fuck yourself after breaking it and having to buy a new one bathroom bathroom control where the dominant person controls
when and how and where the person, the submissive can urinate or defecate.
Do you see how useful my bathroom communication idea would be for people with fetishes?
Poop now, don't poop now.
All the stalls controlled.
Here's my problem with this.
This entry says extreme bathroom control can be dangerous.
Extreme anything can be pretty dangerous.
That's the meaning of extreme.
get into the extreme spiciness from Mexican food that's way too yeah
extreme sour cream that can be dangerous
extremely old I'm not extremely sour I don't invent this shit I just Oh
extreme Islam and other religions can be very dangerous
don't talk about people don't talk about extremist political philosophy
political philosophy that shit's bad extreme danger yeah extreme danger can be
harmful. Here's an article that was on the side though. Check out "How to make a man
cry in bed." Sadness. Which I didn't look through because I think I would start crying
even thinking about it. That's true. Maybe the first five minutes of "up" while you're
getting fucked. For me it's like the next 90 minutes I'm like I missed the best first
part when my wife died. I wish the wife was still alive. He gets rid of that old bag and
does lie around the world.
Yeah, she does look bad AF when she's running the balloon stand.
We mean at the very beginning?
Yeah.
When she's a child?
No, when she's running and when they're he's working in the zoo.
Oh, yeah, you you see up here like I don't want her to grow up.
Yeah.
Yeah, he says that's it.
He sees that many balloons.
He's like, I hope that's not the age of her at a birthday party.
I wish it would be a one balloon at a birthday party.
This is next to you.
What's going on?
These next two I think are like kind of closely related.
Chasmophilia aroused by crevices, caverns, or valleys.
Okay.
And then claustrophilia is the opposite of claustrophobia.
That's when you're attracted to Santa Claus.
Yeah.
What up?
It's a person who becomes aroused by
orgasm through confinement.
Meme this. You must be Santa Claus if you think we're fucking.
And I'm like this.
And then meme this.
OK, this is pretty good.
You must be Santa Claus if you think I'm fucking you from behind.
And then I maybe come in like.
Yeah. And you're like on all fours.
for
yeah up your backside up and your front side down go on the table because this
thing is weak as hell dude that your backside down break the table yeah you
must be Santa Claus you think I'm not a few if I'm gonna I'm gonna fuck Santa
Claus in the butt and then I do this
can mean this I want to fuck Santa Claus is behind oh yeah punch in on cam okay
first yeah punch it on me first and then mean this and I'm like I'm gonna get
Santa Claus this year.
So we could mean that yeah, you could totally impact font give a font and everything give this this next one here is
Dendrophilia, which is also known as Arbophilia is the sexual attraction of trees. Yeah, it's cuz you put in your fucking lips all over
You say that again yeah, yeah asshole. This is a sexual attraction of trees
because they are phallic shaped like
Or because they're phallic shape or because of the texture. It's a lot of different textures of trees
I have seen penises and trees on mushrooms before yeah, you just a tree is just made out of fucking it is
I'll fly you know a flower is
Sexual object that's right to a bead or that rose. I can't help myself
Yeah, I go to what exhibit Jo Keefe, that's the thing you go to Jo Keefe
And you're like yeah, this is a pussy to a bee I never have wanted to fucking oyster more. Yeah, that's true
- Oh my god, well maybe there was one time.
(laughing)
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Now this one is called figging.
Using the ginger root to create a burning sensation.
Must be peeled and inserted
anally or vaginally. - To create a burning
sensation? - Yeah.
- That's a nightmare dude, it's spicy.
- Yeah. - True.
- That's extreme.
- I can't handle ginger on my food,
let alone on my private area.
- Oh fuck no.
- Gingerbread, hell no, keep that away from me.
- Uh-uh.
- No, and keep the egg out of my nog.
This is great for people who want to fuck the gingerbread man.
No.
That's true.
Because then you put that ginger root up inside you.
It would burn to fuck him.
It would burn to fuck you and then you put that thing up inside you and you never want
to fuck the gingerbread man again.
Yeah, well that explains when I fucked that guy.
He said he was the gingerbread man and my pee was burning for days after.
Oh, I'm just a...
Wait, why did my pee burn?
Oh, right, he was the ginger.
He was made of ginger root.
No, it's fine.
I'm just the gingerbread man.
What's this boil?
Yeah, you boiled it.
My pee was fucking boiling, though.
Yeah, it was.
fucking boiling yeah literally is all i have a little bit of a different
asking the toilet was overflowing with metals and coke this is our packs of
philly which is the best for being robbed
okay played as a rather in in consensual or non consensual
their consensual non-consensual
credit affiliate
and i read that from here is a similar cake which is
for being forced to pay for sex and this is the
You. And you got this? You have this one. You didn't have any of the others but you have this one.
You guys ever been robbed? No. I've never been robbed. I think when it happens it's gonna happen
really bad. They're gonna really take me for everything I have. I think it's gonna be one of those situations
they're gonna put a gun to the back of my head, they're gonna make me walk home, go in my house, and they're gonna move
all my stuff onto a van. They're gonna wait for your birthday, get all the Christmas cards. I think they're gonna
really get it. I mean just because I have, it's never happened before, it's gonna happen big. We were all robbed.
2016.
Yeah, I am shit. You're right damn when Hillary. I think it's gonna be full account cleanse
Yeah account and for the gun you're gonna take me to my parents home like all the stuff out of my old bedroom
You're gonna take mommy and daddy's toys my mommy and daddy are gonna be gone. Yeah, it's taken
I'm not just afraid they're gonna my clothes my hair. I'm afraid they're gonna
My warmth.
They can't rob you of your warmth.
My smile.
My joviality.
I was robbed of my smile.
How about your virginity?
That, hey, can't take that away from me, buddy.
Here's what I'm saying.
I lost that age too.
I hope, I hope, I hope to God that somebody comes at me with a gun and robs me of my virginity.
I'm sick of having my V-card.
Get rid of that thing, dude.
Dude, that shit, I don't want to lug that shit around anymore.
It's so heavy.
It weighs on you.
It's annoying.
It really does.
Somebody should steal my shit for real.
Yeah, I didn't actually lose my Virginia too, I lost, I will lose it at 30.
Yeah.
You think so?
Hopefully.
This next one here, "Caranophilia."
That's the easiest one to say.
I'll read this, I got, hey, I got this one.
"A sexual fascination with thunder and lightning, similar to arousal from thunderstorms, brontophilia.
You can't incorporate it into your sex, but a thunderstorm makes a good backdrop for sexy times.
Many people find their levels of desire increase during storms."
I guess that makes sense. It's like we're all gonna die. It's like yeah. Ooh
Yeah
It's also like I'm at your house. It's you're in a dark room. Yeah, you're fucking and then flash a lightning boom
It's not who I thought it was photography. Whoa. That's a story. That's a movie. That's a short film
Yeah, five minutes YouTube. No, it doesn't have the strange lover. Yeah, you know, it definitely doesn't have this who friggin Ted
Who Ted from Ted Ted the bear the bear he doesn't?
He's afraid of this crap. You know who else doesn't let you know who else doesn't have this my dog
Yeah, my dog has the she's spayed. She barely ever has sex. Yeah
You're like so um they should I've been thinking about that for a while well
She I mean she doesn't desire it
I did kind of pick up Phil when he got neutered and I was like why is his cock still on?
They're like we don't take his cock off
I'm gonna get mo neutered dude. He's nuts or yeah, is he trying to like fuck you yet?
Or does he desire you I don't think he'd understand. He wishes to know you carnally
He's like humping the catnip toys got
dude
Maybe I am maybe I'm neutered cuz I'm like I never want to fuck my toys
I love those things and I'm never like a cat or a dog before they're neutered
It's like this is my ball, and I'm gonna fuck it
I mean, I'm like not fucking my computer, but I play for tonight on there like night by night every night one by one
More checking off the calendar one by one played it tonight
One night down five minutes gameplay to do on fortnight place 99 nice this next one here
Lithophilia a king for rocks and stones or graveled this can be used non sexually yeah
It's just having a rock collection. I don't can I can it can you have a sexual fetish. That's non-sexual is
That's cheating like that's just you like it geo dude. Yeah, it's cool. Yeah
What's the only problem with you Pokemon? Yeah? No cock? He's the one the yeah
He's got his arms if you like scaring and geo finger play. Yeah, we're past if you like finger
This is alphabetical right yeah past F. No finger play. Yeah reward will be coming my way
I'm from who well well this I'm just pulling up. I don't be me. I just pulled up the strangest
You're the one dressed as Santa Claus. I pulled up the strangest ones. Yeah, okay captain obvious you missed your commercial shoot. Yeah, you're captain
You're captain Christmas
Oblivious to what's around this is Captain oblivious
This next year's oblivious to Captain Oblivious
Cameron might have oh yeah
Oh, so I'm into my kink of four mummies where someone is a mummies no daddies
Yeah, that's true a kink where someone is bound entirely or nearly entirely to prevent almost all movement a vacuum bed can achieve full
Mummification as can plastic wrap, but it can be dangerous if bindings prevent airflow mummification can also involve extreme temperatures
So hydration is a must to do it safely
First of all hydration is a must do basically anything
Drink a drink water. Yeah, that's a true drink. Yeah every day one glass a day at least yeah
Under here that just says drink water drink hydrate hydrate
Mummification is a good one to do cheaply. How could no it can't that's toilet paper mummy
You guys are fucking up
This is not that is not the point of this go this shit is that it's about being bound or nearly entirely
or like a vacuum bag?
This, okay, I see the issue here. This website, its information is faulty.
It does seem like...
Mummification is more about being, wanting to have sex or be a mummy.
Yeah, I think you're right.
I think they fucked up the name here.
I think this is more, this is, um, this is...
Encealing.
Encasement.
This is zip-locking.
Immure-ment.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, here's this one.
Nullification, a kink for removing any body part.
This is very dangerous.
And a nullo is an extreme kink for removing genitals.
In practice, nullo is very dangerous and can even be fatal.
Oh, so this explains why people are always saying,
Google Jerry nullification.
Whoa, no, they're talking about jury duty.
It's probably a guy named Jerry.
And he's nullified?
He's nullo, they probably want you to see him.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
What the fuck was that?
And now you look so damn smug.
Damn.
Some experts will get that one.
These next two are oculonictus.
Oculolinctus.
- Oculolingtus and oculophilia.
- Jokes.
- These are about the eyeballs.
I hate when things happen to my eyes.
- I had a woman when I, not a woman.
- A woman.
- You had a woman?
- When I was a kid.
- That'd be a first.
- Come on, man.
When I was a kid, I had a girl come up to me
and say she wanted to lick my fucking eyeballs.
- Ew.
- She had a little linkedolingctus.
- I think she had a linkedolingctus.
- A linkedolingctus.
- Oh, you put it away.
- Yeah.
- Well, here's this next one.
- And I remember I said,
how about you suck my damn dick?
Damn.
Yeah.
Science is--
I think I bloated this list up a lot.
We're kind of running out of time here.
Science is fake because it says "lictus,"
and it's about licking.
It's like, shouldn't you have a fancier name than oculolictus?
It's got aphilia, though.
Oh, what was it?
Well, this one--
It doesn't.
This one here, we'll move on from this.
Yeah, lictus.
Yeah, that's lictus.
Lictus.
I have a lictus ocula.
This one here is Phygeophilia?
Phygophilia, fetish for being a fugitive on the run.
(laughing)
- See, these are all more scenarios that you do.
- It's less of a fetish, it's more of a fantasy.
- These are movies that you wanna be in.
- Yeah, like being on a train car.
- Yeah, being in a bedroom.
- Well, I'm thinking of when you're on the run
on a train car specifically.
I was elaborating on this one.
Sorry, I wasn't clear.
- I would love to get in a box car.
- Yeah.
Man, I bet there's some insane parties in those.
Oh, yeah.
I always think about like, I always think about this.
Like you jump on the boxcar and you're like getting away out of town or
whatever and it's like, oh, it's like 15 hours to the next town that I can get
off on and I get on there and there's this guy on here with me,
there's the other hobo and he sucks.
Yep.
And I'm like, it's worse than an airplane, there's only one other guy.
True, but you have more room.
And he sucks.
No, you're in one car, you can't switch cars.
No, but there's like tons of room.
You can't switch cars.
It's just one car.
I guess that's a good point.
And it's filled with hay.
A lot of these-
It's a hay train.
But also you get into a boxcar and there's like 15,000 iPhones in there.
It's like, you're fine.
Not in this time period that I'm thinking of.
Yeah, 15,000 iPhones, no charger.
My thing takes place in the 1700s, and maybe it should have been clear about that,
but there were no iPhones back then.
Well, yeah, you got to open with that.
Well, this next one here.
That's not a problem in the current day, because you can just go on your iPhone.
That's true.
When you're in the car.
Savantophilia, a fetish for people who have a cognitive impairment or delay.
Speaking of iPhones and homeless guys, I saw a homeless guy in Las Vegas who was on an iPhone.
And I was like, "Huh, that guy, I didn't really realize he was homeless at first."
He was on an iPhone, he was using it, and he walked up to a trash can and just threw it in the trash.
Damn! I'm telling you, dude, they have bands nowadays. They have racks.
This guy's a fucking millionaire if he's throwing away an iPhone.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then he dumped the trash out and he started throwing shit everywhere.
Yeah. It was a whole kind of thing.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Yeah. It must have been his thing.
Trash thrower. It must have been like his hobby or his art.
Yeah, maybe you didn't like the trash being in one place.
Yeastiality. Sexual activity involving bread, especially warm dough.
This may be an alleged kink. Introducing yeast to the genitals can lead to an infection.
So, before we have sex, I have something to tell you. I allegedly...
Have a donut on my cock.
I allegedly have a bagel around my cock.
There might be, and look, it's a little weird.
Yeah, I allegedly like it when you dress up as a man.
I may have folded my penis.
Allegedly.
10 times.
Allegedly, I may have folded it 10 times and I want you to put it in the oven so it puffs
up.
Butter.
Yeah.
If you guys could fuck one pastry, if you could.
If we could, yeah, if we had the chance.
If you had the chance to fuck a pastry, which pastry is the most sexual?
Boston cream.
Chocolate croissant down the middle, gliding through that warm chocolate.
I think a hot eclair or something.
Yeah.
actually yeah I mean not a jelly donut no people would say jelly don't because I
think it's funny but it's a bullshit pick there's no hole in a clay we'd have to
imagine a hole yeah how much how you get sugar up your me ate it sugar up the
hole is never good that's never good that's never good no maybe okay maybe
no paste croissant so you're not so it's less chocolatey and more almond and the
only time it exfoliates your cock and I just like that I like almond smell
better than chocolate smell when I'm fucking.
That's fair.
I actually do love almond smell.
When you're fucking?
No, just in general.
So also when you're fucking.
I had an old table that was in storage.
I wiped it down with almond oil.
And I was like, "Damn, this is a good ass smell."
Oh, maybe a bag filled with olive oil if that counts as a pastry.
A bag of frozen olive oil that's warming up throughout the day.
- The answer for all that stuff is like,
I guess like a toothpaste tube,
if you count that as a pastry.
- It's clearly, I've spent a lot of time
thinking about what inanimate object
I would like to fucking try to make it fit
into every question.
- This next one here, this is a German word.
(speaking in foreign language)
- How is that the one you get?
- I can read it from here.
- You fucking can't read anything, but you can read that.
- I don't even think I said it right.
Zweichenstufe.
Okay. It's the sexual obsession with people of the same sex. People have this fetish? That is homosexuality. What the hell are you talking about?
This is a good camera to keep cutting. That was really good.
The two angles of it is perfect. Can you do that again?
Damn, you got three specialties. Just talk about homosexuality for a minute. Just switch between these two cameras. And look, it's okay nowadays,
okay, they want to... Pretend it's not nowadays and pretend it was way far ago. Okay.
It's gonna be way okay in the future, okay?
But for right now you got to keep that shit at the bathhouse
In the car and in the alleyway, okay, just wait wait like 10 years
Hey like two years two years now for you cuz it's gonna be on what the hell
Oh, this can't be. Is this me?
Oh, that's the plasma ball, Caleb.
No, that's Caleb.
No, this is my shoulder.
That's Caleb's ass.
Yeah. All right. What's next?
Next is, oh, here's some comments.
Oh, Tippy. I know Tippy.
Yeah, Tippy says, "You missed some, like a balloon fetish. Fornophilia, turning people into furniture.
Formicophilia, being crawled on by insects. Dendrophilia, trees." That was on there.
They did not miss that.
Tippy, you're out.
Cap-Melonia. All right, Tony Soprano.
soprano yeah yeah another TV another TV reference I'm gonna throw in here from
HBO you're fucking out what's that any power any powers oh you're thinking of
baseball but he says his catchphrase specifically shut up you know you're a
roto errata phonophilia is snuff I guess since it is murdering people Oh
Geron a Geron a toe philia Geron a toe Geron a toe philia is old people
Objectophilia, like the lady that married the Berlin Wall.
Okay.
Mechanophilia, having sex with cars and stuff.
And stuff.
Yeah.
I have sex with cars and stuff.
Just put like a Roomba.
Yeah.
Put like a fleshlight on a Roomba, chasing it around the house.
A Roomba is, for the purpose of fetish, a Roomba is an animal.
Yeah.
What's fart?
That's true.
True.
Yeah.
That's a completely different class from someone who wants to have sex with a wall.
One day, I hope they make a furry living Roomba.
- Yeah.
- That lives in one of the books.
- We should buy a Roomba and put fur and skin on it.
- Yeah.
- No, but I wanted to have animatronic eyes
that go like this.
- Run around the table while we--
- We get liquid latex and just cover Roomba--
- Oh my God, that's such a good idea.
- With a big nipple in the middle.
- Dude, we should do that.
- But I want to have animatronic eyes that go like--
- Yeah, no, we should build it.
- Dude, dude, dude.
- This is the Existenz Roomba.
- That's incredible.
- Yeah, it's a great idea for a prop.
- Wow.
- For a thing in my house,
and I use my girlfriend's away. Whoa, clean. So once you get home, it's clean.
That's okay. That didn't take a tip.
That didn't take a tip. I'm going to tip it after a sperm on his whole.
The fuck's wrong with you? What's wrong with you?
I bristophilia criminals.
Apo.
Okay, that's a fetish for being an amputee.
A base of Philly.
When you're making these, why don't you just make the size big as you're here?
You made the slide. I thought I would have my glasses today.
But I left the house pretty early.
Right, and your glasses don't load until later in the day.
No, no, no.
They're not ready until later.
People with impaired mobility, mud and quicksand fetish.
Oh, I got that.
You got this next one, cholera fever.
True.
Clowns.
I think when I'm old I'll have that.
Wikipedia lists are often helpful.
I got that.
I'm going to wait.
Dude, when I'm 70 or 80, I'm going to go so crazy.
First of all, I'm going to be doing cocaine and DMT.
I'm going to fuck so many clowns.
because nothing matters it up yeah it's like it's like I can do whatever I'm
gonna fuck so many clowns and circus freaks yeah you better under bridges
here Linda Finn says I like it when my dog watches what would that be called I
like oh my dog watches TV yeah yep he watched White Lotus and he understood
that there's hot women in it it started I swear to God he's already in a red
pink bone the only time my dog is my dog ever reacted to TV was when there was a
horse on TV and she went crazy and she tried to kill it she doesn't react to
dogs on TV. Really? She had a horse and she went nuts. Phil almost knocked my TV over
because there was a bird on it the other day. He like went headfirst into it and knocked
the shit over. I've done that too a few times. Yeah, I mean who hasn't fucking seen... It
looks like a window. Yeah. You know? This next one here... What about reading yourself
in paper? Joshua Isabel asked that. Joshua, we already talked about mummification. Come
on motherfucker. You stupid hoe. Fuck you. Fuck you Joshua Isabel. Also this is not a
brainstorm session. Yeah. You write, say the name of it, the scientific name,
describe it in detail, and now read this one.
J.D. Wood says, "Any information on Queen of Spades?"
And I didn't look up what Queen of Spades meant.
It would be a pretty good parody song about females.
"The Queen of Spades?"
Yeah.
"Met her on the fetish list?"
No, it wouldn't be about fetishes. It would be about how women act.
Yeah, yeah, it'd probably about cards. Yeah be called hair and it's by the best and it's by the band hair head. Yeah
Okay
Next one here
Sam Cummings says come play. That's true. Come play soon. Now. This is true. I love this
Less I'm definitely making completion completion
Completion 330 there's an angel number right here. Oh
2333 that's pro. That's maybe the first time ever you said something as an age old number and actually was so congratulations
I'm really proud of you. This is a divine that means this is a divine question
This is ever 27th divine day does this mean that you used to have more come than you have now?
When you yeah come or your comes worth less your come is worth
Producing way more true and your girlfriend doesn't even care about any more complete conflation
She does you come to over my body. I don't even care if it's on my yeah, I come anymore
There's too much of it. I don't care. It's not individuals
That's what drove him to invent the green goblin serum
No, dude is white is is is his wife or girlfriend or whatever, you know, he was like
He's like can I eat your poopy?
Harry Butler butthole and she's like no and he's like look at the monster you
made me and he turned green and he flew out of the window here Jeff Jeff says I
don't understand why smoking is a fetish left off of nearly every published list
of fetishes yet is one of one of the most common fetishes we carry enough
shame already for having a fetish for a socially unacceptable action action it
It would be nice to be included.
It would just be nice.
It would be nice.
It's like, hey, you're leaving us off
all these amazing fucking lists.
Yeah.
Just include us for a little bit.
Exactly, I wanna be on the list next to my brothers
and sisters in the kink community.
It's messed up what's happening to smokers.
So next one here, Sienna says,
"Is there a name for a fetish
"where you love being trampled
"because that thing really makes me aroused?"
Yeah.
Which, yeah, there is.
I met a guy.
Mufasophilia.
Yeah, Mufasophilia.
(laughter)
- You all just a fax.
- The lion kink.
- Yep.
(laughter)
- I'd call it chemophilia based on the guy I met.
- Okay.
- OJ, OJ Simpson, he says,
"What about how I like warming up on my Satusamas?"
I like warming up my Satusumas on a radiator
before squeezing the sticky juice on her.
this is discriminatory please tell me i'm not the only one with this that what is
a set to suma i think you can use context clues that suma
i think that's
yes for the hands it must be it must be hands or face or whatever but it's a
type of food
yes probably food is what it is
and i got my food up the repeat it or that is a very high like that too but
that's not sexual that's a very efficient that's a very fetishist emoticon
Yeah, devilish eyebrows. Yeah. It's next one year. Don't donaldo
Who want to try ocula linked us hit me up at the Capitol bro. Wait was that yeah?
That's who I think it is a year after he wasn't the president anymore
And he said on leap day. That's him announcing another oh
My God
Come back to the Capitol to cool. Yeah, that's a cue code. That's true shit
it. Wait a minute, eyeball, cue code, cue ball, pool, the pool at the White House will be filled
with insurgents. With eyeball liquors. Liquor, drinking, thinking, I'm thinking. Donald Trump
has famously never licked a liquor bottle. I'm thinking I will be in the White House
and attacking. No. Holy cow. I can't finish what this code is telling me. I can't say
it on air. It'll be too dangerous. But if you want to know what the code is, we'll tell
you if you subscribe to us on Patreon, Twitch, TikTok, Twitter.
Patreon.com/podcastaboutlist.
Ow!
I thought I was helping!
Stop it!
You fucking suck.
That's my microphone, you shouldn't do that with mine.
You can do that with your own.
I don't care about the windscreen.
Look, I'm the only one who has the punch-ins, okay?
I should have...
Is this your microphone?
Ooh!
Well, you got white fuzz on mine.
I'll sing into it if I care.
Okay, then sing to close us out.
But I also...
Sing to close us out.
I know, we actually have stuff to mention.
You guys are making a mockery and a clownery.
Before we do the thing that we have to talk about, check out...
Swagpoop.com just got a low-key makeover.
- True. - It looks amazing.
And not only that, if you've ever watched one of these videos
where I'm shaking my ass as Santa Claus,
we're talking about fucking licking hairy buttholes as a Spider-Man character.
And one of us is nervous because he has a vet appointment that he has to go to so he didn't
do well on this episode.
Shut up.
He's getting neutered.
If you were like, "Yeah, that was so awesome and actually I'm so proud of that, I'd like
my name on the end of it."
Then you can do that now.
Go to patreon.com/podcastsaboutlives for $15 a month to get the Executive Producer tier.
You will be an Executive Producer.
You can put your name at the end of an episode.
You can also put that on your resume.
You can put that on your resume.
I will honestly, if you want me to talk to a realtor or something because you used me
as a reference, that's fine.
I'm not your Executive Producer.
That's okay.
Also exciting part of the executive producer tier, if you're paying $15 a month, once a
month there will be a shareholder meeting held on Discord, if you want to join the Discord,
where we will talk about the state of the company.
And it's business formal, you have to come dressed up.
And if you come ready to talk business, there will be a Q&A session, we'll do presentations
about the state of the company of Sullivan the Frog Enterprises, and you'll be able to
ask questions.
But, you know, come serious, come ready to work, come ready to talk about the state and
the future of the company.
- Not only that, man.
- We can grade, you can grade us on our performances.
- Yeah, do we wanna announce the date
of the first shareholder meeting,
which I'm trying to remember right now?
- Yeah.
- It will--
- If somebody who has access to a computer could tell us--
- Somebody could just say it or write it down or show me.
- Write it down in the PowerPoint.
- The 16th of December. - The 16th of December.
- And I believe we said 5 p.m. Eastern time.
- We have the first one.
- So make sure, and after that,
we'll have a standardized day, it is every month.
But for now, if you're gonna subscribe to that tier,
you better make sure you do it before then,
'cause you're gonna miss the shareholder meeting.
- Yep, and make it, let's try to get to $100 million
so that we can make our Before Sunrise style sunrise movie.
- If we get to $20,000, we're making a feature film.
- Yep. - That's right.
- So share this episode, send it to your friends,
and follow us on all our social medias,
which are here and here and right here.
- And right here, there's one right here.
There's one right here. - There's one here.
- There's one right here. - There's two here.
- There's two here.
- There's one on this side and one on this side.
And there's one around here.
- And please go easy on me.
I'm sorry for my performance.
- I'm gonna go sleazy on you, sludge you.
you did great how you were fine i'd like to list my performance my performance
you know that i have a little money
so far
you're great i'm talking about i'm talking about my company my my
uh... i got the company
i do that's not a part of that
that's not a good way
this that all my god
almost to smell good
windows are clogged up
by by
case i'm
okay
Okay, Alvin?
Alvin?