I
You're a jerk. Oh wait. Oh, yeah, we have to do it. Okay set it up this one. Yeah, okay
You're a jerk
pretty easy for me yeah you're a jerk. I know
I like the window reverse. I know
this is yeah. This is me talking to chat gbt the robot web tbt gbg gbg. I call
that real, but I jerk all day all night. We said jerk
I don't want to be a robot anymore, and this is my normal voice. Wait stop is
jerk the J word. Well, okay, in the context of that, jerk was an answer.
I guess you can say jerk, but you can't say it with off after it,
maybe. Yeah. Is that where jerk comes from? Is this? Jerk comes from
chicken. No, it doesn't. I think. No. Jamaica. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Jerk comes from... Herky jerky movements. Yeah. But is jerking like
jizz? Or jizz is a new... Oh my God, that's a dollar in the jar.
You can't say that, guys. Here's gets the swear list better than you
you and you're the one you were here for its inception.
That should be the JC word.
You can't say inception either.
You can't say inception?
Yeah, it's a PG-13 movie.
Oh my God, yeah.
Okay, well that's newly established.
Whatever.
Hey, Pierce, how are you?
Hi, guys.
Good to be back.
What a lovely set up you guys have with all these mic arms that touch each other.
Yeah, I bet you're impressed.
Look at this.
It looks like the Eiffel Tower right now.
Say that again?
That looks like the Eiffel Tower?
What?
This looks like the Eiffel Tower.
In what way?
I think it looks like a spider.
No.
The spider tower.
No, it's not.
It's a spider.
looks like the Eiffel Tower. I think it looks like a spider. No, the spider
tower. Yeah, it actually looks like the spider. The Eiffel Tower does look like
a spider.
What are you on me with four legs, a four legged spider? No, it doesn't. It
looks like a four legged tower. It looks like maybe a million spiders in the
shape of the Eiffel Tower does. Yeah, we're in the really good point. You get
it.
Yeah, I think as I get older, I'm realizing that I have no interest in
going to France. Yeah, keep me away from there. Yeah, I do want a country for
high schoolers. I do want to eat a snail, though. I never want to see that country.
You can eat a snail... Off the ground. Yeah, you can eat a snail at home.
Every time it rains, I get hungry for a snail. I took that... You took that food
disgust test, too. The funniest question on it was,
there's this test where they test how disgusted you are by certain food hygiene
things, whether or not you eat something, and one of them was, "If you were eating
a salad and you found a snail on it, would you keep eating the salad?" I was
like, "I don't know." That's such a funny thing to ask you instead of,
like like a cockroach or an
thing. Why is
perfect thing? Because it is food. Yeah, and it's a question.
The snail is probably an escargot salad. It's a
one of the animals that is when it's alive. It's closest to its food form.
Yeah, because it's just there's almost no difference between maybe a crab, a
crab also is up there. I just cursed and I didn't even realize what you say.
Well, it's clearly you realize that you're getting a coin salad.
I said, what kind of F.
So I didn't even catch that.
I mean, yeah, none of us caught that.
My gosh. Wow.
Internal things. I mean, good job for self-reporting.
And that actually is pretty.
That's very noble of you.
Wow.
You all looked at me and then I was like, did I say something wrong?
And I was like, oh, yeah, I did.
Yeah. Have you guys.
I've I've I've started not cussing in my day to day life.
yeah, I my girlfriend said a swear and I said, Oh,
what did I do that?
If you guys don't go a full year, whose fault do you think it will be for
tapping out Patrick? Yeah, no, you guys think one another. I am definitely the
worst. I
the dirtiest mouth, but he's been paying. I'm a potty mouth, but Patrick doesn't
like the swear jar. Yeah, I don't like the
I think it's good yeah. I don't like the cops, but I'm going to abide by all
their rules.
So no same things wait. I think anti police anti cop on there. You better
bet
wow that is he just got home
yeah, and also I think it's fun to have a to be building. I maybe the
community well the community where community is where it's a movement.
There are also who really don't like the swear jar.
I've learned people who message me say well, they can buzz off. Yeah, don't
bend the knee to those haters. Yes, they message me. They send me all these
messages. They say F U P O S not point of sale, not point of sale, not point
of sale, and they say I'm going to K I double hockey sticks you wait. Can you
not talk about like homicide? No vote. We decided violence is okay. Violent.
Oh yeah, you can talk about all the violence. You I'm gonna murder these
mother haters. Yeah, that's good. Yeah, that's exactly what we're looking for.
Yeah, you can say these
monkey fighters. What? Jesus Christ, dude. Wait, are you let's say... No, can I
not say Jesus Christ, Lord's name? No, you can say it. You can say it. Oh, we
decided that it's an atheistic, it's gnostic. It's an atheist swear jar.
Monkey fighting is from snakes on a plane, though. Oh, it's on this Monday
to Friday plane, remember? Yeah, yeah. Not what... I don't know why everyone
did jc after I said that just me yeah, it's only me who did that. Oh,
you're everything to him yeah, yeah, you are my world. Well, good luck. I'm
gonna try to make it through without swearing. It's gonna be do you guys
have anything in your slides today that has cussing in it? I mean well, so
here's what I was thinking right, so we're this we decided that a lot of
these words, the p us, why were the d i c word? I'm not spelling them fully
because I don't you get the idea. I don't want to go all the way, but it's
some of the more anatomical words testes right. This is a medical, this is a
medical episode. We're returning to practice. It is medical in this context,
so in this context, we are the doctors answering these questions right and then
the patient doctor, confiance, basically this you're you're locked in a doctor's
office right now with us. Oh yeah, nothing leaves these these. So I think
if the if the patient says it, the patient types it out, I think that we
we can spell it out. We have to repeat it. We should rest up like well you did,
but yeah, I got a doctor's outfits. Almost I'm wearing a doctor's outfit.
Yeah, yeah, and I'm a hip doctor in the nineteen nineties. She'll doctors. I'm
the chill guys to her all doctor yeah. Have you guys ever had a young doctor?
It drives me crazy. I have a young set away from me. I was me crazy with
desire. Yeah, if you don't wait now, oh, I did want one time the one time I've
been to a doctor. I did have an athletic ponytail doctor to clean my ears out
yeah get away from that's the only thing they did.
They laid me down and they were in my ear. I had to lie you down for it. Well,
well, what do you think I'm going to tilt my head like this? She said, get on
the mat. She said, get on the
get on the mat. It's time to squirt on the mat. Yeah, she said, I'm going to
bubble your ear up with my squirt.
She did. She said that she's going to bubble your hold my squirty. That sounds
like a
doctor bubble my squirting ear. She did and then she said does that feel better
and it did yeah. I can imagine if you would feel better to get squirted in
your ear. She gunned my wax out. Guns, she plunged my guns out with her squirt
gun. Wait, her bubble gun? You went to the doctor to get them chemically
irrigated? To get ear wax out? Yeah. Is it that bad? Well, I woke up one day
and my well for like two days, my ear was itching really, really bad and then
I'd go in, 'cause I scratch my ear,
I just put my finger in and I go like this.
- You do that thing with the--
- And then I make a--
(imitates scratching)
Sound, and--
- How come you couldn't do it right there, but he could?
- What do you mean?
And then I could go--
(imitates scratching)
I have two techniques. - That's the one I know.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, I don't think we've talked about this,
but the first time I met Caleb,
are you gonna do your little Pewds voice?
- Are you doing that with the--
- Robot voice?
- It's not gonna sound like anything.
- Let me try it.
(imitates scratching)
- It's nothing.
- Just a piglet.
yeah
that almost sounded exactly the same
the first time i met you, Caleb
i thought it would be funny
i had a really bad allergic reaction
to what?
just i don't know
to meeting you
some ambient pollen
yeah
to meeting you
maybe weed
but you were just like
what the fuck is wrong with you
you were right in my face
oh god
but Caleb said it so he has to put it in
it's a memory swear
okay, i don't have any more cash
because i only allotted one dollar
for today
i'm still
was i mean?
no, no, no, you were just
it stuck with you
- No, it's the exact thing that I would do in that situation, first impression,
you go really, really hard. I mean, you broke the ice. I wasn't offended,
it was just shocking.
- I'm a sweet guy.
- You're a sweetheart.
- I'm so sweet.
- Anyhow, yeah, I was scratching my ears like that. It really hurt, really,
really itched. And then after two mornings of that, I woke up and then my
ear was wet on the inside and I couldn't hear and it itched and it hurt.
- Oh my God. Wow.
I went to the I went to the urgent care and she was like okay. One year looks
fine. The other year is completely going to be bubbled. Yeah, she said I need to
get my bubble gun to squirt you out here. Here, while I get my bubble gun,
yeah,
there's a like a case on the wall. She turned a key and I've always wanted to
use this yeah. I thought that they just put like peroxide in your ear and make
so they they I drop peroxide, but then they also have a windex bottle that is
pierced on three sides that it goes triangle blast. That's what you put in.
That's cool. It was great. That's pretty crazy. I want that badly. It was cool,
man. I would love to get like every single cavity in my body just deep
cleaned. Yeah. Or just filled. My butthole? Filled with like the expanding
foam. Yeah, the foam. Yeah, they should put foam in my hole. Or what they do
with like an anthill where they... Oh, yeah. Yeah, molten tin. Oh, I would love
that. It would be very immoral, but whoever was willing to do that to a human
body would be one of the greatest because he would have yeah you just some
Sarah's poor all the
put all the molten metal in there and then you just put the person in a
microwave and all the stuff will come off. I said stuff,
okay, yeah, like you say, I would I would actually put them in
acid and then I bring their body back up and everything would be melted,
except for the metal yeah. So that would be my well micro, if you were of a
house, so it's a little easier to do. Oh, a microwave that can fit a person
your microwave not fit a there is a my you can I don't even have a microwave
Wow right yeah he's got an air fryer that only goes to 400 yeah we've talked about
this and my air fryer well that's because Teflon is very dangerous above
400 I don't have a Teflon one you have a nonstick I have a really really good air
fryer and he's his goes to 400 damn I made that up about Teflon - but you got
scared he's got every single that one's good for you
otherwise he wouldn't have been called Teflon Dime.
I think that they find Teflon in like polar bears and stuff now.
No.
Yeah.
What is the...
And that's good. It keeps them alive.
I don't believe so.
What's... It's like the film on non-stick pans.
Is that what Teflon is?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So non-stick pan...
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, and so the...
I feel like every time I make an egg on the Teflon pan,
I'm just getting little bits of Teflon on the egg.
You definitely are. It's really, really bad for you.
Oh, you are. That's what happens.
Yeah. Are you using a fork and scraping the pan?
I'm using a spatch, but...
Are you scraping the pan, though?
I get yeah, it's bad right. Yeah, it's really bad. So what are you supposed to
do with eggs? You're supposed to use a lot of oil in a steel pan. Yeah, but
then the steel pan, I guess I also heard butter, a ton of butter,
clad,
Ragusea says, "I always use my non stick pan for eggs only." Ragusea is...
Look at Ragusea, look at the size of his body, his weird proportions.
Look at his head. Yeah, he's got a puffy body. He's puffy. Yeah. And it
is completely... He's got a puffy plump going on. And he's a nerd who lives
he's in Atlanta, right? Get out of there. You don't belong in a cool city.
He's in Knoxville. Okay.
I guess so. But he belongs in the Pacific Northwest. That's where he should
be. He belongs in the Plum Museum. He should be in Seattle and he should be
wearing a really, really bad t-shirt. He should be wearing the Sub Pop logo.
He should be in a Peeps container. Adam Ragusea, if you're listening...
We know you are. You have this one. If you're listening, I need you to go up
shirt size. That's right. Wow. Yeah. Adam Ragusea, you need to stop wearing mediums and
get some large.
Adam Ragusea, you gotta stop doing laundry. You gotta stop drying your shirts really,
because your shirts can, I can tell they got a lot of right on.
Adam Ragusea. Adam Ragusea, one more thing. Stop buying v-necks.
Yup.
That's right.
Also, you got a bacon neck v-neck.
This is whack. Yours are so whack. A bacon neck v-neck. You're referencing the Michael
Jordan Haynes commercial?
Uh-huh.
It's a...
Bruh.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing, really.
Okay, that's...
Adam Ragusea, fix your wife's teeth. Yes.
Yes.
You have enough money, mother...
And make it...
Hold on. Mother...er.
Nice.
Hey, Adam Ragusea, how about you make another good recipe video?
Yeah, that's right.
That's right. That's right. Stop making your podcast. Start making your podcast.
Start making your... We're just going in on Adam. It needs to end now. Make your
pee pods on the cast iron. Hey, and JKenjiLopez, stop taking the point of
view videos unless you're gonna play paintball. Nice, dude. That's him playing
paintball that no yeah that's me playing people with him. Yeah, or I said this
for making me make a twelve hour bowling a you piece of crap. I'm done with the
soundboard. Okay, yeah, we want camera to talk again. He's zoning in. He's
basically looking at his phone. You would be such an excellent producer for
Howard Stern. Oh yeah, I don't think I would be trying to fix his voice with
all the voice effects. I'd be down there. I'd be eating Robin out underneath that
booth that she's always been. Oh my God, you would never see. I don't think
we're allowed to say that what is his name? What is his producer's name again?
The guy who does the impression of Ronnie the limo driver? No, no,
who's the guy, the guy who's always there and you go and he does the Ronnie
impression. Otis. He's great. Otis. Otis. His name ain't Otis. Okay. I was at
the, I was at the movie theater.
Otis, this my producer.
Where were you? I was at the movie theater.
I wish I had the sound board so I could hit the D. You will never have a sound
board. You are the last person that will ever be behind those wheels and this
is something that has really been making me laugh for the past few days that we
me and Alex are seeing the Dungeons and Dragons movie, which was piece of which
I had a fart sound on the sound board so bad piece of poop, but some this couple
brought their really little kid like this, like probably like three year old
girl, like really little and she was right. She was doing the little kid
thing and running around the front of the theater and like like this, like
screaming and cheering and like running back and forth and at one point she
like their her parents are sitting in the front row like on the right and she
ran over to the left of the front row and then she stopped and looked around
and went Daddy. Where are you
kids are as stupid as a rock? It was a fun. I was that was the hardest. I left
in a movie theater in so long
like like twenty feet in one direction, get really scared, lost. Yeah, I think
that is that you think that movie would have is too scary for that kid.
Yeah, that's why they got free. I think that there were parts where there
were monsters on screen. Yeah, what
why bring your kid to that? If you bring your kid to like a movie that has
like like realistic looking dragons and like you know that the crowd for that
movie made me so mad because it was all. How would that was all middle aged dads
we're bringing like bringing their like thirteen year old sons to the movie to
try it. You could tell they're being like oh we're going to see the dunes.
Oh yeah, no more iron man for you literally like three of those of those
father son couples yeah
they're couples.
I think you made a pedophilia joke just now. I know Cameron didn't make a joke.
You made a joke, a joke, no he's a called father, son, couple, a couple of
people, and you run out of if you run out of coins. By the way, you're going to
put your keys in there.
Okay, you miss not I'm not you miss a dime. It's a time. It's a dime. Oh, I
said there's another penny. You have to put next to it. Oh
yeah, I have to put this penny in for wrongness
being incorrect. Wrongness is a big one. Yeah, let's get let's get in the
right to yeah. So if you guys have a private friend, the other practice
episodes or listen to them. Practo is a website that mostly caters to the
country of India,
and... Which is the biggest... So I have discovered... Concentration of people on
the planet, is that true? I do believe so. Or is it China? This time around,
I've discovered there are some people from other countries who post there.
Yeah. Really? Yeah, I know. There are. There are some people who post about,
post in from America, even. Yeah. Right. Even really good countries like
America.
It's kind of the only website where you can get on demand access to a medical
professional. It's a medical advice. It's it's yahoo answers for doctors and
patients. Yeah, it's like it's just like that, but you have to be I think you
have to be like a verified doctor to actually like answer any of the oh no,
you do not have to be verified anything to really you don't have to be a
verified. I think we'll see probably some of it, because sometimes we include
the doctor's response. Yeah, some of these yes, my favorite doctor's response
is basically just buying time like all right. Well, why don't you tell me a
little bit more about what's happening? It's so funny, because there's also
this website has no functionality at all for replying to an answer like they're
like, so it'll be like yeah, somebody somebody who ask question like I'm
dying. What do I do and the doctor will be like well? What do you mean and
there's no way for the person
other thing to mention about Practo? What do you is that? It's so many doctor
answers. It is a website that basically does not exist. It's impossible to find
yeah. You have to Google this thing. I remember because we were like trying to
find new stuff for it and the only way that Pierce told me that the only way to
find it was looking up the word tummy worm on Google until you find yeah
tell me a little tummy worm in quote. You have to yeah you and I just search
for me worm. Practo is the first yeah yeah you have to search like practo and
then like yeah like a medical thing and then you have to find an answer page and
then from there you can get to the search page, but you like can't get
there. They hide it on you. They had it on you because they don't know it's a
gold mine. Yeah, they don't want you to they don't want you to know all this
great information. They know if the people who post screenshots of like two
sentence horror stories from reddit or whatever get their hands on practo it's
completely over yeah, and we just explained that to get there. You know we
are breaking the hipocratic oath.
Well, that's why it's confidential beep on that explanation. I had to get
correct. Here's my first can I just ask you before we start. I want to issue
just a call to arms to the podcast about list listeners. If you know anything
about coding, could you please like unzip all of these responses somehow and
get them into some kind of data set, because I feel like it's impossible to
look at all of the things that are like to search and get all of the entries
return. We need some kind of we need a loader, some kind of Zuckerberg needs to
get on here. We need a we need a neo to get inside the website. We need
somebody. I need to be uploaded in the client. Yeah, so that I can fight this
guy. This is for from a male who's twenty years old. He says getting dark
day day by day. I use pears, face wash and lotus moisturizer, but I get dark
day by day. I need solution for it. I'm really getting very black. I do bath
with bore
I don't know what
darker, but he's getting black. He's getting very he's getting very black.
Yeah, I don't know what bath with bore water erection problem, male, thirty
nine years old. Whenever I try to intercourse with my wife, my penis could
not erected. Then I tried to erection manually. It has also failed at last
ejaculated with little demon.
The semen is seen in a clear form. Help me, sir. Oh, wait, wait, genie coming
out of your yeah, nothing's wrong here. Also, a little thing. I think this is a I
think this is just like a typo. Maybe he did this with dictation because demon and
then yeah, I think demon is supposed to be semen. I agree with that, but also the
the fact that he would dictate this entire thing. No, I think he's trying to
do he's doing a double this on his thing yeah yeah, okay, to fix it. I guess I
like watching to start it up a direction manually. Does that mean just hold it
in? But yeah, what is it? Hold the top and the bottom
he asks his wife to hold direction. Look at me. I just went to hold it and
just back.
Oh my God, I'm as hard as a
a baby.
I was taught as a high wire. Look at this yeah getting an erection like trying
to rip a bandit. Don't go slow, just rip it out yeah. Can you imagine how
terrifying it will be to ejaculate little demon? His wife is like okay,
nothing's working. Try using little
demon is a mythical
draws a summoning sir.
He's got a like
a really in a really hot little deeming open a jar. There's some
great great grandparents left a treasure chest for him. Yeah, to use a
secret signed in case of manual erection. How to stop porn addiction in
weeks. I love to watch porn, but when I try to do images of my own daughter
come in my mind. She is doing porn videos and every act in videos, even
when I'm not doing, then also images of her come in my mind how to stop porn
addiction. Holy shit, so this guy has I only have a serious problem. Yeah,
born how to stop it in weeks. I need to do it in weeks does make this so much
more sinister. Yeah,
it doesn't stop in time. Yeah, exactly. I
I like it addicted to gay ideas. I am seeing gay videos and I am affecting
badly with others.
He's seeing gay videos in his mind. I am seeing gay videos. Can you repeat
that? I was seeing gay
talking
I like that
it could be videos or idea. I don't know yeah, I really I know it's
supposed to be videos, but I really want it to be ideas. This is like a
succession level Schrodinger's thing. If it's crossed out or under the lines,
an idea or a video
penis. Look here. We go
hi there. My son was playing on his video game whilst needing the toilet. He was
really addicted to it. He wet his pants whilst wetting his pants. One drip of
liquid fell down his leg and he wondered what it was. He touched it and held it
up and he said it smelled like urine and it was an oddly colored pee. However, he
looked closely and saw white dots in the white liquid and he was worried what it
should be my son is eleven and he is not really public or pubic yet with only a
flea, a few long pubic black hairs help you wait like a
he has only a
one or two really
we get like that's how
yeah
Patrick still hasn't grown pubic hairs yet.
Fortunately, it is cartoon logic. You grow for homer hair on your
just
like a really long fume.
Yes, that is what happened. That's exactly what happened. What happened to you?
Yeah. Patrick just woke up and was fully pubic. I actually, I guess I would
believe that. I mean, but that is this is also funny also that it's white dots
in the yellow drop of yeah. Of course, that's like the shimmering of the light,
right? The big twist to me in this one is that the kid is in sixth grade like
and he's and he's so addicted to video games. He just pees his pants on
his face.
He was really addicted to it, really addicted to video games. Also, I love
one whilst wetting his pants, one drip of liquid fell down his leg and he
wondered what
a single drop of
liquid means that he's so addicted. He does this all the time, pissing his
pants while he's playing. Dad is never contact, but it's like that I piss my
pants again while playing he's like sure son. Well, what this time? Well,
there was one drop of mysterious
I have to go
tiny
get up the computer. I
how to stop watching porn video master by if I think any sexual thing my penis
erect painfully and whole body is shaking and painting and what is the
problem? I think he has it perfectly at the end. What is the problem? Yeah,
sounds okay to me. I love painting. They say painting all the time. It is
painting
addicted to porn videos, sir. I am addicted to porn videos. How I can avoid
this habit. I am loosing my concentration on studies. I want to become a
government servant. Please help me. This one, I saw this one too and I
didn't put it in mine, but it made me search the word servant and there
are so many of that are end with, I want to become a government
servant. Yeah, I don't want to be a servant personally. Me neither.
Started seeing sad videos. Hi, doctor. My boyfriend has suddenly started
seeing sad videos and emotional things and even he does not sleeps at night.
he watches these videos all day long and a counseling psychologist says this
situation should not be ignored. Take him to a psychiatrist for evaluation and
necessary medication. If required, the doctor will advise after necessary
diagnosis. This is probably the most deranged behaviour you can have on the
internet. It really is. Sad videos and more deranged to post on a medical
website and then the, it's even more deranged for the psychologist on the
website to be like, this situation should not be ignored. This is serious.
The worst in porn addiction is watching sad videos all the time.
And you need to come see me.
You need to come to my office so I can fix all that.
This is by far the most serious reply that I've seen on this website.
Yeah, they never get this serious.
It's always like, "Take a capsule or you're fine."
Yeah, or just keep looking for answers.
Or send me a picture.
Yeah, send me a picture.
This guy says, "This situation should not be ignored."
watching adult video. Hello Sir slash Ma'am. I am twenty two years old. I
watch the adult video while watching that kind of video. My sperm comes out
and I feel dizzy and sleepy. Please consult me how to get rid of it. It's
watching the video mail. Twenty two years old. Yeah,
I like I like my sperms come out is like well. How you just watch a porn
video
cartoon birds going
that would be definitely worth going to the doctor and then how to get rid of
it. Get rid of what you're watching poor
he wants to get rid of the sperms. I think
this one I thought was funny. My amount is debited, but not video call, no
video call with doctor, but amount is debited.
that's my reaction to getting scam.
Maybe this is also the sound of that. Also their anger, I'm aware that it is a
different country and that could be his name. I don't
this is also another time. There's so many posts of I was supposed to have a
video call with the doctor. He never called me. Yeah, I think I've been
debited, but like I don't think it's an I don't think it's an it problem. I
think it's I think it's all the doctors who have a who like put in their fake
potential, so they can sex picture of your penis yeah
addicted to sex. I have been addicted to my aunt for
when she sleep. I have a tendency on peeping and pressing private areas.
No
peeping
we can guess that the advice here spans. You are a deranged rapist to it is
fine to love your
I think yeah. I didn't include it. How did you find answer was so just like
yeah, you know that
just, but you shouldn't do it like that. His wife is on is asleep and he's
walking up to impressing his balls against her back. Did you look up? Did
you look up the word peeping to know I looked up on
I did. I looked up on because I also looked up peeping really well. I didn't
so also so shut up addicted for blue films,
I'm addicted to watch blue films.
The solution to stop watch blue
please help me
am too much
I search blue
because somebody was like there was a lot of really bad ones that were like
my baby turned blue. My friend turned blue and now he's asleep forever, but
this one I just thought was this is blue films is the the fancy version of sad
my videos. Oh yeah,
the boyfriend, the boyfriend yeah,
I don't want to say sad videos because people were making fun of me
addicted to watching blue films. Yeah,
it's a little more yeah, there's a little more dignity in it. Yeah, those
are all my slides. Hell yeah, dude, beautiful, okay, I'll go next. I think
we helped everyone just based on yeah, yeah, all right, so I tried to make an
they were or a doctor. So you come in and you say help I'm addicted to
watching blue films, so we all
the laughter is the best medicine.
You're sitting in a waiting room and you see somebody go in and you just
hear for
dying
and then you just hear them all to all just doing like a high pitch voices to
I know
yeah, so the bros sounded back up
yeah, the doctors have a
completely addicted to blue fills
this all right. So fudge one two three four was I was trying to make an
account to maybe like I was trying to become a doctor on here to see. Oh
really,
but I didn't get one. I didn't get my code. They were supposed to send me like
a like an oh like a one time password or whatever, but also fudge. One two,
three, four has been seen 64.
Wait,
you cannot use fudge.
That happens 64 times in other data breaches that we had. That is crazy.
so this first one here,
I didn't really think it was like
a baby ate lizard poop with lizard poop was funnier.
Female doctors can't stop masturbating. I'm gay, so I need a female doctors to
talk to. Thank you to which Dr Murphy said gay and want to talk to females.
Okay,
I
day. Do you this next one here? Matrix
marrying relative? I'm going to marry my relative.
Direct blood relation. What precautions do we take before
marriage? I'm gonna do it. It's so funny to not even be like
should I do it?
I'm already halfway through going to do it. Yeah, this is
our wedding the morning of the wedding. He's like, maybe I
should have
walking down the
I love precautions. We should like precautions. We should take before sex,
okay, but
you should make sure you have a really good come back. Yeah, I say when people
ask if your blood really
very good doctor, you should get a really good prosthetic to sky. I guess
you should get a suit and a ring
think about the budget. Yeah,
a girl
appearance
appearance. What am I supposed to do in order to look extremely hot to a
girl? What am I supposed to do to look extremely hot to a girl to which
this doctor says consultant
to chat all day? There's a diabetologist.
This guy, this guy commented on like like a bunch of shit. Oh my God, a
bunch of stuff just saying consult on practo chat. That's what I'm saying.
really wanted to talk to people. And then you pay, you know, you pay to talk to them on
PractoChat and they never show up to the video call.
Dang.
The whole website, it's a...
I might have sworn a lot and not gotten busted, so please let me know how...
We'll invoice you.
Once it's released, I'm sure, yeah, thank you.
We'll count it, we'll tally it up at the end and then you can...
But do you think that the doctors who...
We'll send you an invoice.
...who do this half-butt advice are going to get paid, like, just for sitting down and
answering a hundred questions with, "I'll talk to you about this later."
Yeah, this whole website's a scam.
Is PractoPay doctors?
The thing is I will I think no, the I know the patient the patient pay for a
video call. Yeah, so I think that I would imagine that this is a lot of
these people are the doctors like the doctors responding on text. You think
it's just a hobby. They don't get paid for that. I think they're doing this.
No, I think consult on Practo chat. I think that is a direct that will
directly lead to the right this to write this. No, I don't. I would imagine
I think he's doing it because it has this button. This is yeah, exactly.
Yeah, so that yeah, it's a it leads to him. This is the beginning of the
a scam yeah exactly. All of them are always saying send me something
because I think I think the doctors on practice are probably doing the exact
same thing as us where they're looking for the people who need a consultation.
The most of they go on there and they type in like a baby turn blue.
Hey, I hit me up
glob
this next one
depression. My beloved blocked me from her twitter group. I'm extremely
worried. Heart is sinking. What to do? My beloved- He got- He's sixty-five
years old, and he also got no help. Nobody replied to this. Oh, my God.
That's fudge. My beloved blocked me from her twitter group. This next one.
Damn, so sad. Humiliation porn. If I stop humiliation porn to normal porn,
I get severe anxiety and depression, and then just a bunch of ellipses.
but don't stop. I guess that excuse before
I don't watch
this kind of anxiety and depression. If I don't go to the website that has a
you are that is a forty characters.
This next one, please reply on this. I want to see a porn videos, but I'm
thinking what if in future my kids marry a porn star, marry many girls do sex on
porn videos. So chances are if my kids marry a porn star, a girl who I saw nude
become my daughter in law. How does my son will feel and how my daughter in
law will feel about it? So what are your views? Should I watch porn or not? If
you were in my position, I would if I were in your position, I would yeah.
This is the it's a small world argument. I guess he's also what he's he's afraid
of like the best possible situation, a porn star and yeah, that's probably what
he's jacking off to is this idea. Yeah, only fans yeah
someone someone that lives across the street from me is in eleven porn.
This guy, this this guy was trying to write just trying to write as many
questions as possible. This is a guy writing a work for a class. It's like
okay. Well, how yeah, I feel and also how will my son feel and I guess how
my daughter
and what are your
one question per question? I would yeah this next one, sir, ma'am, please help
me, sir. I saw this today and I'm worried. It suddenly appears. Is it
normal sir. I'm so worried. Please help me. None of these have photos.
Yeah, I
wonder if the doctor on the back end can see the photos that are being
attached. Maybe this photo is of a ghost. Yeah,
this next one here. Is this normal? Is it okay at that age? And I'm
not sure if we've seen this one before.
When I was younger around ten or nine, my brother was around nine as
We both had seen porn and we decided to try/have sex by rubbing and putting our penis on each other's bottoms and anus.
It lasted about 10 minutes. And we hadn't really started puberty at that age, so we weren't sexually active.
And we didn't have any orgasms and stuff like that. It basically just rubbing our penises on our bottoms and anus.
We are not gay. We have never done it again. And I'm just wondering if this is normal or okay at that age.
that age. If this is incest or not and I'm worried that we've seen this one
for because he asked this a million times the same exact way. Okay, so if
you're worried, if this is incest or not, it's not
no
out of your brain. If you're the same age, I think it's just not incest. No
matter what no, no, it's fine, and also you're not you're just rubbing yeah,
there's no
sexually
not even pubic yet. Half of the games that boys play are lick something off
my ass,
something off my car. The interesting about this one, if you go, if you go
back here, the if you go back the again the
if you go back again, oh sorry,
you be
no, no, I just it's asked for mail fifteen years, which I feel like you're
supposed to realize this question when you're like thirty
I'm supposed to ask you for you. Yeah, he needs to be fresh. He's a brother
getting it up to my
this is the kind of thing that you say one time at a bar when everybody's
crazy story.
It was so funny me and my brother. We would rub our penises against each
other's bottom slant anus. You're not supposed to be posting out of a web
and we were ten or nine to beer. Steep you start using slashes in your
please help Sir, please Sir. Are you there? Help help? Help look at my
picture
I was just cleaning a glass.
Last call. Hello, Sir, I would really like a beer to help
to help with my problem of memory.
Hello Sir, I'm fifteen years old
brother game with rubbing
an anus game with my favorite brother when we were nine or ten
and I'm wondering, did you have less than three? Okay, it was incest. If
you have less than three pubic hairs, it is fine, yeah
engineer and model actress are in love. What should we do in order to both have
peaceful married life? How to protect from public and have freedom is to
outside India. Is that correct? I don't reframe your question for better.
It is so rare that they say I have no fucking. I'm talking about that's an
effort where I saw there was a couple of I didn't include them. There was a
couple of ones that I saw that were just
just
posting to the practice thing to doctors, you can't middle finger the swear jar
that is no
great. So he's making a mockery of it.
I saw a lot of posts that were just like hello doctor. I am perfectly healthy
and I feel amazing
and then the doctor just reply and go that's great.
That's very good news. Yeah,
sharing food with gay guy make you gay. Recently, I shared food with the same
spoon of the person which they ate who is gay. Now I'm afraid a gay now
gayness is contagious. Today, I shared a cigarette with a gay and now I'm
afraid that his saliva might have swallowed by me. Can anyone tell me this
gayness is contagious when the saliva is swallowed?
Does kissing gay make you gay? The other day I was drunk and kissed a gay
thinking that she is a girl. We kissed like more than an hour, a deep lip kiss.
At the realizing that is gay, I'm afraid since we had a lip kiss, saliva is
transferred to my mouth. Is there any possibility that saliva affect my
manhood? Can anyone tell? No.
This is wrong. I would like to say yes, yes, and yes. You can catch gay if you
get gay saliva in your mouth, it will turn you, it will change your manhood.
Sharing a spoon. Sharing a spoon will make you gay. It's all very, very
contagious. Especially cigarettes because of the- And it's not okay. And
it's not. You're inhaling it. Even if you're gay, it's not okay to become gay
in that way. Exactly that is like that's like we're born makes a vampire.
Yeah, I is like a lesser vampire right yeah, you should be born that way. I
don't want you being turned yeah, you shouldn't be a thrall. Yeah, no, no,
no, unfortunately,
doctors understand you're either born gay or someone makes you gay with a
kiss
is next one here. I hit with gun bullet. My son's I was
painting in red. Also from the corner. Can someone please advise me the next
force of action shot in the face and it's painting. I think the I think the
response to this was like, can you please give me more information
face turned red, shot in the face,
this next one, schizophrenic child is schizophrenia an excuse for a twelve
year old to cuss an adult
he is told this only happens when he is told to get off the Internet.
off video games and when that's all right, this is a very
opposite. I hate to both sides. This
once I heard the second part of this and why he's cousin, I feel
a little bit more completely understand why that would make
me listen. Here's what I'll say. It's okay to throw stuff. It's
okay to refuse to do as you're told. Cussing is never okay.
Yeah, I'm your mom. You can punch your mom. You can break
down the wall of your house. Oh yeah, but just don't you don't
call her a hard your mouth shut. Don't say age or you say something kind say
I'm have so happy. I get to do this and by the way I'm so happy. I like to punch
your wall and say I love this. I love this. I love that fine. That's fine, but
you also cannot cuss even if you're speaking in a different language. Yeah,
I'd like to say that so no I carumba. These are these are the two. These two
were kind of the same movie during pregnancy. Is it okay to watch movies in
theater during thirty one to thirty two weeks of pregnancy. It's fine or it's
it's safe for my baby to watch a movie in the thirty fifth week of pregnancy.
It's fine.
I love that this is like that's a re
using specifically pregnancy and can I watch? Can I watch an action movie?
There was one that was like can I watch funny movies?
I saw one that was like can I use an ipad near my baby and the doctor like
no, do not put that near the baby. This next one kids see ball and fan
rotating video of bell and fan. Okay, I all please help me to understand my kid
always like to watch fan rotation, all bell videos and like to play with wheels
of cycle car. Please help me to understand is it a good sign or anything
needed to make him correct? He eats very less quantity. Thank you just feed him
more, feed him more and stop letting him watch it. Bailary hungry, yeah, so funny.
what is my what is my infant thinking when I give him video
also bell and fan. I don't know what that is. Oh, I guess this is a phrase or
a
different. I don't know, but time to cut the pumpkin tree. What invent after
eight days suffering my left hand, but homeopathy doctor see ointment ointment
acquaintance, Demi Ken, O.C. and Madison, but not removed. Please help me. I
share this picture. It's time to cut the pumpkin tree. Recently, after ten days,
it's time to cut the pumpkin tree.
What is the same thing? What is time to cut the pumpkin tree? I don't know.
Recently, after ten days. Yeah, it's time. I guess he has a pumpkin tree.
Yeah.
He's getting a rash. He's getting a rash and he's in pain because he keeps
trying to cut this pumpkin. You're allergic to the pumpkin tree. Yeah,
this next one for my wife pregnancy. Can she got a pregnancy by manually
inserting my sperm in her vagina?
There are not please explain.
I'm suffering. My dog died. I'm crying very much. I feel so helpless. Will I
be excused in class? If I say this, I'm already in college and I don't think
my professors will understand me and this got a response from a doctor
thing. Why are you expecting someone to understand you accept the situation
soon and involved in study? Wow, I like her picture. Yeah, she's actually
beautiful. Yeah, she looks like potion, so
pain coming up from right center chest. I randomly have a pain that I call it
Dorito attack
scraping my insides, but instead of going down, it comes up. I've had that
anymore.
Okay, and not to go practical, but this is called an esophageal spasm. When
the food gets stuck right before it hits your no, it's not it's called a
Dorito.
From now on, it will be
funny. It is the Dorito attack, and then I think this is maybe my last one
or my second to last one. My wife had Chinese garlic noodles. My wife had
Chinese garlic noodles. Now she is six weeks pregnant. I am worried. Please
suggests me. I need to know so mean that he thinks that it got her pregnant. I
think so. I think or he
is the same thing as yeah. Am I allowed to am I allowed to drink Gatorade
while I'm pregnant? Am I allowed to laugh at a funny picture while I'm
pregnant? I read this as his wife ate garlic noodles and now she's six weeks
pregnant. Yeah,
oh, and then I am fine. Nothing problem.
It's just another one of these. I'm flinging good and better than before, so
thanks to God and then you yeah that's my last one damn dude care see you day
all right.
Congrats go wow dude beautiful practo all right, let's see here here. Here's
mine
gaming addiction, becoming violent, depressed and anger after not playing
video game for four months. I saw this yeah. I feel this four months. I already
you're past the home. I was like how I saw this. I was like I really thought to
yourself. I was like if I I feel like that is the point where you have to
accept it. Yeah, dude, like it's for me to be going crazy after four months,
something must have just came out seventeen. Oh no, this is a seventeen
years old. Yeah, I bet his friends are talking about it. That's probably what
it is.
Can you click back on it? Thanks watching adult video. We already saw
this one
eight after four minutes.
I ate pizza after four minutes of drinking milk today by mistake. Is it
harmful? Dude, when people- This one, I was lying in bed last night trying to
fall asleep and laughing about remembering four minutes of milk happening.
That's so much. If it's- That's non stop. Four minutes. That's gallons of
milk. Gallons of milk. Yeah, gulping and breathing loud through your nose.
Yeah.
I ate pizza after four minutes of drinking milk by mistake. Dude, this is
exactly- It was an accident. This is how my girlfriend talks all the time.
she like doesn't do a thing to or does something wrong and she says it was an
accident. I'm like what do you mean? How did that? How is it an accident that
you didn't brush your teeth
yeah for minutes of milk? Give me some idea. I had a problem on penis,
something dry white color of sphere cover my penis with bad smell. I don't
understand what happens on me. So please give me some idea about this type of
problem. I'm suffering from this.
you you search sphere. No, I actually did it is fun. I'm seeing everybody
slides and guessing what they search. You search type of problem. No, I think
I think this is one of the ones where I saw something else and ended it like
did something that was similar. I don't think I actually searched any okay, dry
white color of sphere yeah. Let's try to actually diagnose this guy.
I think that you have a marble. I think he has a marble stuff.
it has a bad smell. So it might be a thing in my
that they eat there yeah, maybe an egg yeah, a white. Oh, no, I searched idea.
That's what it was. I just remembered I have a white orb that smells bad.
Maybe you have a stinky white
yeah, that's my that's my official diagnosis.
Does it come on
okay?
You have an orb that comes off
never removable problem. What should I do? You should take it off
obsession with idea of dirtying hands. My son, thirty one years, has developed
a severe problem about eating with hands. He worries of washing his hands
or otherwise his phone or computer will be spoiled. He gets so much agitated
that he wants to commit suicide. We are Indians and he does not like others
eating with hands and considers Chinese better. I just like the my son,
thirty one year because I completely it blindsided me. I thought this was going
to be like a problem that they're like young child had right now. It's just a
guy with fuck it with the OCD. Well, I said it. You did say it's a guy with OCD
who has OCD that makes him consider Chinese better right. I think that's
kind of what OCD is yeah
that is not working. Can you thank you gosh? I got spot. I number can I reduce
can I reduce I number how, if any of idea of you, please say no other
problem
this is you can go one or zero. This is a
Cameron's been asking us about oh yeah. Can he get in? I
am right. I've never seen it so eloquently, though, because you've been
asking. Can I get an eye patch blah blah blah? This is I wanted a boils shut. I
don't want to patch this boils down your question to its essentials. Yeah. Can I
reduce a number
pizza sauce poo
this morning. I had a bowel movement where I had pizza sauce like my God was
running. I had only got an hour before it was normal and I did what this could
be. I go see a doctor. I saw this one to sauce yeah.
Did you put it on a beat? I also saw this one and I sure it was a
immediately. I was just like someone else
who is
Also, you know that it is a men often do just have pizza sauce. Yeah, the fact
that this is a female, I would say this person is like seconds from death.
Yes, there's no when women have bad.
The thing is, I can't think of his pizza sauce consistency would be one
thing, but this is pizza sauce color.
Yeah, which which
bright red is it pizza sauce uncooked or cooked because it changes. It becomes
a little bit more brown when you
so they probably have like stomach cancer or something yeah or they
or
they two full bottles of ragu four minutes of pizza.
Maybe your toilet has pizza
maybe of a red toilet.
Somebody hit you with an upper decker
pizza with gird. Hi, I'm having gird. Hi, having gird from last ten days, head
still feels heavy. I really, really, really want to eat a pizza. Should I
what is gird? Yes, yes, you can yes eat
it's gastro really bad reflux,
astro, a softical reflux yeah yeah. Oh, I really, really, really want to eat a
piece. It shouldn't be just like a
fortunately, my gas, unfortunately, feeling gay. I don't want to be gay
feeling to kiss or do something to male when I am man from past four to five
comments. How to be straight only liking attracting towards female. I am single
previously did bad to myself masturbated. Please, how I did bad to my
self. You've did bad to yourself. You're too far gone. Yeah, there's nothing we
can do. I was love. Unfortunately,
unfortunately, I am gay insect bite. It seems like a scratch when I wake up in
morning and check, but it's not actually a scratch. It's something creepy and
it's making
it's a creepy, mysterious, creepy thing. It's a creepy, itchy thing. I have a
creepy, itchy thingy that's happening. I have a creepy dot on my hand
dreaming, imagining when I am recumbency on the bed and I am traveling in the
metro in a car. I always dream just like I want to be something I keep imagining
and want to be many things. I am and it is different. For example, if I want to
go to film writing, I have a fantasy I have become and I keep on reacting and
being happy. It feels good. Then, after five minutes, I ignore to become an
actor, a cricketer, or an officer in the same way.
It's so funny that he's like, all right, so I want to be maybe four or five
things, but then I snap back to reality and I want to be four or five
on the train. I imagine being an actor, you have to consult a psychotic. You
need to see a doctor right now. We need to pump you full of lithium. You can't
have those thoughts anymore. Yeah, those are dangerous thoughts. Yeah, I'm going
to put you in a straight jacket. I'll read this one really fast daydreamier
masturbate or lazy. I'm a maladaptive daydreamer. I daydream a lot like I was a
number one scientist in the world and I save millions of lives. Everyone in the
world praises me and all types of fantasies. I feel like everyone praising
me. I'm really wasting a lot of time when I daydream, especially when I hear
music. I daydream a lot. I am a serious masturbate three time a day. Yeah, you
read it right. I can't control myself. I am lazy king. I am procrastinating. I
read tons of self help books and watch tons of motivational videos and speeches
human blocks, but still I am not doing anything. My mind is wondering. I can't
focus even for five minutes. I feel suicide a side. Sometimes I'm a
double minded person. Now I am in a relationship double mind system act
here to I'm attracted to every girl. I saw I am in a serious depression. I will
cry without any reason over one hour a day. My day is like three times
masturbation. Don't taking shower, except I felt so smelly fifteen times
daydreaming like saving poor help me holy shoot
the doctor's holy shoot.
Okay, you need to get out of my you need to get that out
diarrhea for birds. My birds look suffering from diarrhea. I need to know
about medication. Go follow and treat need suggestions. Okay,
that's where my mail zero
about me. It's about a bird.
The bird is probably under one bird is probably only months old angular
ceilings. I have angular ceilings on both sides. What medicine or should
dream. Should I take her apply? Please it may be
maybe like a light paint yeah
in the room a little bit yeah some kind of off white yeah like a cream. I be
leg injury by gun shoot after injury. My foot is drooped down and my foot
thumbs
go
you guys to hear more about foot foot thumb confusion. Am I sick or just
pretending is my identity even real? How do I know how to act because I am
confused? I don't know what to feel or if what I'm thinking of is real. I don't
know anything. I do like I do like the questions that are on this one yeah.
I like the questions that are on here that like sound like like when like a
middle schooler tries to write like a schizophrenic guy yeah yeah. This is a
story from the perspective of Rorschach
yeah
I'm writing a poor shag spin off. Everything is so we
this is a fetid pool of strange.
Is my identity real?
I'm like an ink, but
everything is so confusing. It's like an ink, but
I kill a criminal. I spree performed on my clothes and I don't I spree performed
my cloth and hand and father that I eat without washing my hand. I touch my
cloth and perform
perform smell. We all know perform yeah
washing my hand. I touch my cloth
without nailing one word like oh sorry, let me let me start over. It was my
father that I eat without how wash
jerks last flicks. I want us to know if there's a permanent best treatment for
problem of jerk or flicks medicines are going on
medicines are going on
addiction of porn. I know this is funny question. Why is my body struggling
throughout the day to poop, but when I watch porn I poop a lot
I know this may sound weird to many, but hopefully I get a lot of people that
are like that. I can discuss this nasty thing to talk about. I want to get rid
of this problem. Now I am addicted to porn before poop and if things will go
like this, then what will happen at the age of fifty, please suggest me
just on his phone. I'm like the bus yeah, wait, why do you try to shit on a bus
like a Boston Express or something like one of those? Sometimes they have a
toilet on the bus, yeah, like the lucky star bus, but why not just be on the
toilet?
He has to watch porn before he's just in his seat. He's like I feel like I got to
poop at some point. He basically got the diaper equivalent of porn.
Tongue licking spoon in a restaurant. My mistakenly in a restaurant, I was having
noodle with spoon that I mistakely tongue like the spoon. I
should be
yes
right now. My mistakely in her rest her rot. We must amputate your tongue
penis erection of my hubby. My hubby's penis is not able to being erect for a
long time due to which he is not satisfied during mating with me. So
suggest some ideas for being satisfied. I hate when my hubby's having problems
first meeting with me. I doing this with a ball, so I want to mate. Oh, no,
there's a
awkward, awkward, speem release. I release sperms when I'm in a ten
situation searched most, especially for example, when I've not done enough
writing in an examination. The examiner calls for submission of scripts are
about to collect. I release sperm uncontrollably due to the tension. It is
reoccurred severally, even without me having without me been on erection, very
pleasurable, awkward, though, whenever I check it, I notice its sperms, which
always get me thinking. So I have an issue wait okay wait look at the timing
of this five years ago. What was happening five years ago? Who was on
Saturday Night Live?
Three guys from the Lonely Island, and they were one day looking for
inspiration for a new digital short in my search speem and they said we can't
do speem and they can't it can't be awkward speem release because anybody's
going to Google that know where it came from. We're going to invent a little
word called jiz yep and wow. So that's my theory sperm dribble instead of shoot.
I'm a born dribbler, but I can shoot two ropes of I lie
dribbler
I'm a board
dribble, speam count ten million
pretty good right yeah ten million. Well, this person was unhappy with it
right. I have one more that I know we did at the live show, but this is my
favorite one of all time, so I just want to put it. I want to see it again.
so it's the classic
bubble in
I have one big bubble in my bump. The bubble is inside the bump. Please
suggest me medicine, so that I get relief from that bubble. You keep
thinking the best part is over
and bubble. It's a
break this down the bar to sir. It's very formal. Sir, I have one big
in my bump bubble. You're already like what you know, bum the bubble is
specify you're starting to say wait. What's the situation? He says the bubble
is inside the bump. Please suggest me medicine, so I get relief from the
bubble. So now we know the problem is not the bump. No, it's the problem is
the bubble. I'm going to have that bump whether you like it or not. The bump,
I was fine with the bump. I mean, I got used to the bump. This bump is going
to be here forever. I'm fine with the bump. I'm a bumper, but I don't need a
bubble inside it. That's the last thing I need. In my bump. Wait,
that was actually the lonely island song bubbles in my bo,
I'm on a bump and
I need a medicine
like a bump. I'm experiencing T
like a boss was originally in my bump
talk to doctor like a bump.
All right, I have to be so bad. That's okay. We'll go through fastly. Okay,
don't we can pause. Do you want to go? Okay, can I can I get relief from my
home?
Take your level out. I can
bubble in my bump. I can't see a
try. You put down the bubble and I look at my bump
bobbling
bubble
all right
and
all right,
and we are
for shake all right here's practo.
I want small pinnock
I'm fourteen year old my pinnock a long when my panics up my panic is show on
pant. I want small panic.
What I do for it,
so this is a pretty good problem to have mister fourteen year. I'm fourteen
years old. That's what every doctor said. I want this problem. Yeah, you
who wrote that John Ham. John Ham. Oh, probably going to John Ham born on a
leap. John Ham. I've one man. John Ham's got a long hand. You don't know this.
John Ham used to. They used to walk your swing in Times Square. Yes, exactly.
He would walk around with cloth pants on. He invented the gray sweatpants
challenge. Real do it. He would do it in the streets of Beverly Hills.
It used to be called. It used to be called Hamming it up. You see all
around with your. Yes. Aren't all cloth pants. No, because sometimes pants are
new leather. They can be synthetically
lock pants,
lock pants, because he's got a he's got a minute hand down there. Yeah
come on. I think the second hands a little longer than the minute. His
second hands too thin
meaty lump. My sister has a meaty lump on her.
Which doctor should be show
what
a really
holding her meeting lump, which doctor should we show? I let go
should I let go of it. What is this
cement color spatches on plan of pen is actually. I had a thing on my glam of
pen is from the last two of days, then I observed cement color speeches on
gland of pen is how to cure this sharpie. Actually, I was starting with
Actually, you're in for a treat.
- Actually, sir.
- Did you search actually?
- Uh-huh.
- Wow, that was advanced.
- Brain warm.
I've swollen a live baby cockroach.
Am I at risk of brain warm or tap warm?
Should I take albazanol or albenazole?
Please help.
Please consult an eye specialist in your area,
the doctor's response, so that you can start wearing glasses
and don't swallow a live baby cockroach repeatedly.
- That is kind of... - ( laughter )
"Oh, I swallowed a cockroach! What do I do?"
See, at Eye Doctors, you don't swallow a cockroach!
( laughter )
- Yeah. - Talk to 'em, Dr. S.K. Wadhwa.
Yeah, I'm a gynecologist.
Yeah, I'm a gynecologist with 44 years of experience
and luck now.
But I'm weighing in on everything.
Why do you see an Eye Doctor? 'Cause I'm a guy doctor.
You know you messed up when a gynecologist is telling you--
just roasting you yeah,
yeah, oh get your eyes checked something bite me. Can anyone guess what bite me?
There are two pimple together, no other symptoms now had been fifteen minutes.
Okay, I will guess there's two together. It was a spider.
What despite I think it also could have been two best friend mosquitoes. Yeah,
they don't may there. They don't have friendships. It's not. It was one clumsy
mosquito who fucked up the may
no
nice. Can you want to guess what bite me? That's what I like about that or two
very, very small native American. I did I search I search by and there was a
bunch of stuff like I got bit by a dog. I got bit by a dog. One there's a ton of
I got bit by a crow yeah, but eagle there's so many eagle by the one there
was one nested in all those that was like my son was bitten by a human.
I tried searching. You cannot search more than one word, which is such a shame.
You can. Well, it doesn't work, though. It doesn't work. I search grandma bite
grandma to get bit or be bit by grandma. Yeah. All right. Purple legs.
My thighs turned purple last night and now they are lighter, but still purple.
You are turning into a mascot. Yeah, this is good. Yeah, yeah, that's telly.
All right. I love this one. It's literally so charming relationship during
pregnancy. I am seven week pregnant advised by doctors to avoid making
relationships for three months. I'm fine to avoid it completely, but sometimes my
husband was in mood and we do kissing only, but I get feelings while smooch.
Can kissing and my feelings harm baby? Please advise.
- Yes, that is very sweet.
- But it is very harmful.
- You're going to need to stop that right now. Your baby will die.
- You stop kissing your husband right now because then your baby's going to
want to grow up to kiss your husband.
- Exactly. You will make your baby gay for your own father.
How can the how can the language breakdown in such a big country with
with so many languages be so poor that when a doctor says avoid relations, you
think you can't smooch your husband like you don't understand the sexual
euphemism. It's like they're like they need to just stop trying to incorporate
English. Yeah, exactly. Just you yeah, speak the language that you guys all
know really, really well when you're at the doctor, right? Yeah, don't say that
you have a spatch on your
to cut the bubble on
I have bubble on palm now. I request you to cut the bubble
bubble and that actually I was kind of myself.
I just love the
English, the English language arts things here. I have a bubble now request
you cut pus bubble. Hi,
hi, madam, pus bubble not reducing. Can I punch her that bubble, which a
sterilized pin. Can I punch her that
not put your that sterilized pin because it was creating a lot of
inconvenience.
I got a heat ball on my pens. How high I got a heat ball my
pants how to cure it
I'm imagining like a like a street like a hadouken. No, I'm
I'm imagining I'm imagining like a like a Miami Heat basketball one with the
logo on it.
No, I like how many people type their type their like phonetic reaction to
yeah, whatever it feels like
pain on leg finger
on my leg finger and it blued as soon as shown in the pig suggest which
specialist to contact
My leg finger ringworm, my leg finger side worm or ringworm, happen please,
help me, which cream do I have to use? I wear shoes.
Two thumb finger and two leg knuckle swelling.
Two thumb finger and two leg knuckle swelling, kindly guide me, ASDF, ASDF.
So yes, they do not have a word for toe, apparently.
was either a foot thumb or
leg left leg. Big finger got pus
my thirty second
my left leg.
That is big finger
like thumb finger. That is a big finger
Puss in pain when touched, but while walking no discomfort.
What can I do to get rid of it ASAP?
- Cut it off.
- Green balloon on foot finger.
(laughing)
I accidentally hit my foot finger with stairs.
Green balloon formed up on it.
I'll attach a photo.
Balloon on foot finger.
I accidentally tripped while climbing stairs
and my finger fell on the edge of the stair
and then it swell like a balloon with green collar.
this person is so excited to have just foot finger
leg finger will be automatically
left leg finger will be ten days before damaging the whole leg
will be crushed the whole body. It will waste my mother leg
and then this was the only one that had really good advice,
which was I do not
problem from a diabetologist. I do not my leg thing, my left leg thumb finger
that is big finger,
finger got a green yeah. We need to teach them toe yeah. My toe is green.
That's what it should be okay. How do I explain this? My left leg thumb finger
got on the stair mother finger, whole leg fall off, but he's I threw my
through stairs. I hate my it with it with stairs, pinnick problem and sex
problem. My panic is very short and slime and big problem is hot video
watching through the running hormone and painting my panic. What size is on
full tight
basically yeah? How big is your cow big that yeah taking pen and mouth my
mistakenly I put pen in my mouth. Should I be worried? I will never do it again.
No worries,
don't worry, you can do it again.
Please be sure not to share your pen with anyone. If you have this habit,
just wash your
and
don't watch the pen. Wash your mouth. Finally, the best advice. No, don't
repeat
a lot of I love when there's seven different responses. So good. This is
your pen is really good. Don't worry, you can do it. It's your pen.
- Why are you still working?
- So this is me searching Actually, it's my big finale.
I'm just gonna read them.
Actually, I am having hair fall.
Actually, I got frontal baldness.
Actually, there is a skin problem.
Actually, I take oral sex to old man.
Actually, I don't know what it is.
Actually, I have two cutting scar.
Actually, I am having erectile dysfunction.
Actually, I have striked with a coconut.
Actually, I am facing pain in my penis.
Actually, I had acne and pimples.
Actually, I want to loose my bolly.
Sir, actually, I had sex with my wife.
I love searching actually.
- Wow. - It was good.
- Practo. - Incredible.
- Practo. - That's Practo for you.
- All right.
- I hope that we cured-- - This stuff is like
smoking Cracto.
- Wow! - Yeah.
- I hope that we cured all of their diseases.
- I know that we did. - I hope that
every single one of these people's problems
are resolved today.
- That's very sweet.
Yeah, I hope that we have a shareholder meeting on the twenty eighth of March
this week next week. But we'll find out what it is. We look at the calendar.
It's next week and pierce plug your ish. What do you have any ish that you want
to plug? Nothing, nothing at the moment. Then go watch fried at the museum.
Frighten
pierces favorite pierces thing that he made that enough that is his thing that
he's plugging. There's nothing to do with us a cool video that you guys help me
make yeah and then the matrix power point check out
actually just check out matrix power point. Yeah, we need to juice that video.
Yeah, it does. Yeah, it's a it's it's got yeah, we need to get it back up.
Yeah, let's post it on on subreddits. Yeah, yeah, you know what you go and you
- Go post that on Not Tim and Eric.
Everybody go post that on Not Tim and Eric.
- Matrix PowerPoints on not.
- Cringe high schooler gives stupid presentations.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- All right, bye guys.
- Peace guys.
- Bye.
(static)
- Yeah, I'd like to get one ticket
to a PG-13 movie please.
And I'd like to sit in the front row.
- And a ticket to a PG-13.
(laughing)
- I wanted one ticket to a PG-13 movie.
I hate you, I hate you, cause you're in my trench coat. I like, hate your face.
*chomp*
Oh my god!
I swear, Char!
Yeah, that's fine.
One, one, I spill.
One ticket to Welcome to Boozeport.
And one ticket to-
Sorry, we're in a monop.
One ticket to Welcome to Marwen, please.
And one ticket-
Yeah, one ticket to, uh, Boy in the Striped Pajamas, please.
One ticket to- I'd like one ticket to Melancholia, please.
Yes, please, Char.
Um, uh, excuse me. Hello. Um, can I get three, I mean, uh, one ticket to, uh, Philomena?
[laughter]
Yeah, one ticket to Leon the Professional.
One ticket to Leon the Professional. Um, yeah.
Um, my mom, my mom said that I can, um, my mom, my mama said that I can buy Sunset Overdrive.