(Music)
Well, well, well. Look what you've driven us to. Look what the...
I don't even want to say it. I don't even want to talk about this.
Look what the fuck is going on. Yeah. Bitches. You fucks.
you fuckers yeah fucking fucks poopy eating you yeah you and you're not very
nice
Todd your balls up your ass put my balls in your a toddlers toddlers excrement
you shite man
you are all pieces of do bastard
bass dad bastard yeah bass dad
yatch business business match business be a slut stupid slut
- Whore tits. - It's banked.
- Cum guzzler.
- Stupid slut with big tits and a fat ass.
- Yeah. - Fuck you.
- You fucking biatch.
- Long haired bitch.
- Yeah, with hair all the way down.
- White bitch. - And skimpy clothes on.
You sluts.
- You white bitch slut. - High heeled whore.
- Yeah, looking like a complete slut with a job.
A woman with a job. - Yeah.
- Instead of a stay at home mom.
- You look like the brown M&M with her pussy out.
- Oh.
- Her brown pussy. - Skin care, makeup, slut.
- Her chocolate pussy.
- See, so now we're doing this shit again.
So this crap, see the shit, this shit, see we can say shit and fuck, but it's shit,
shit, shit.
The whole thing's a shit show now.
Because of fuckers.
Because of ass clowns that decide to get their fuck goblin fingers all over our fuck waffle
ing swear jar.
And up the ass.
And it's up their douching ass.
If you couldn't tell, we have decided, after much deliberation, that swearing is back on
on the menu. Yeah, as some of you people just can't pull that list of swears up
do be. Oh yeah, when we're just gonna we're gonna go through the whole thing
and we're gonna say all of them. Yep, that's right. Going to circle. Yeah,
this is what you guys wanted, right? You wanted fuck fuck in the fuck finger and
fuck finger f word finger. Thought that was fine. That's poured. You wanted
the word you wanted bitch. You wanted a
clown ass jockey other s word. The other s word, the other s word. It was
didn't know. No, no, no, no. The other s word was because I couldn't say it back
then. Sperm semen,
semen,
shot up for a freaking, freaking or far or something. Well, you guys will skip
the racially sort of words. Mick. Yeah, okay, Mick. Yeah, idiot. We said idiot.
we say damn we're saying hell we're saying boner. I don't fucking buy the
boy for hell play the boner sound boner. Yeah, we go, but but cheeks,
twenty at but ass, we could say twenty four C word is
I don't like saying that really fucking really fucking boobs yeah really big
boobs was the our word
P word for pussy dick dick suck fuck you Cameron and Patrick mean. This was a
swear back then. Hodgers I already said I said together up the up the I love
being now we can say we can now we can say was you yeah, I had to feel like
joking. I fucking love pedophiles or some shit. I don't know sexual gesturing
here's me fucking jacking off a
okay
drugs. I'm smoking crack with a Karen who's a crack head energy pants can be a
cuss. Guess how sag my pants are my down to my ankles. Yeah, you are telling I
don't do that. We don't need this. We've spilled it. We did. Yeah, there's
enough spilling on this table.
Who said fuck was my kid friend. Oh, sexual C word clap in them cheeks.
Yeah, wet. Oh, I get no, no, no. You almost got me.
Really close.
He almost got me.
You know what? You know what? Him adding that to the list to try and get
us. That's a swear.
that is a swear section. So obviously we're done. And listen... Wait, wait, wait. Put
racial back on, I guess. Well, I just, just end. Well, we're not gonna have a
jar, so there's no way to know. Yeah, so that's on you guys. If it happens, it
happens. I'm so sorry to say you guys didn't like the swear jar.
But we think that it was a big enough part of the history of this show
that I think it can just disappear. No. There needs to be a proper send off.
I mean, we have to do what we originally were going to do. Yeah. So I mean, I
think that we you guys knew that the whole point of this thing was always to
do it for one year as a way to raise as much money for charity as possible. And
at the end of that year, when it was full and we were saying full to the
brim to the brim, you know what we should have done before this? What is
calculated? Who added the most? Well, it wasn't you. It wasn't me. I'm taking my
five dollars back. Yeah, I know. Well, that also so we can calculate whose
dollars were whose
first. I'm going to start counting and then second and foremost,
then we would have known who donated the most charity out of the three of us
who would have been a competition. It doesn't listen. It doesn't it's not a
competition. I really
a competition and I'm sorry for talking over, but not a charity between the
three of us, but the charity between two of you, which that I would be able
to watch for my amusement. You said a charity between the charity competition
between the two of you, which I could watch. So right now what I'm doing, if
eagle eyed fans will notice, I took out a kind of a tape measure in my little
calculator here, and I'm calculating right now the volume. Yeah, that's right.
We're doing a little mathematics today. I'm calculating the volume of the
swear jar, and we are going to find out exactly, 'cause we were gonna do this
for a year, and you guys didn't want us to. Yeah. And you stopped us.
I have to add it, we are gonna fill that to the brim, right? And you would
think you would think, oh, they got to they got to get rid of all the money
that's in the swear jar, right? They got to take all of it out. They're going to
take all of it out. It's going to reset. No, we had eight or nine more swear jars
over there looked exactly the same. Yeah, so we're going to right. We're
replacing them out. So imagine how much we would have accumulated into the swear
jar right now. Multiply that by what I'm what I've just done right now. Patrick is
we don't have to imagine because I've done the calculations and I know I can
I'm going to tell you exactly how much in cubic inches the capacity of this jar is
six hundred and sixty one point eight seven, which we can round that to six
sixty two. I feel like six sixty two six sixty two cubic inches and I'm going to
look up and see if I can find the volume of a dollar yeah, which and I'm there's
fivers in there too. There's fine and by the way we were and a bunch of coins. We
were going to switch to hundreds only yeah this week, but you guys stopped us.
So there is thirty dollars in just bills here and I would estimate I'm not going
these coins, you know, because I'm not a homeless person, but these are probably
another $10. I'm gonna be honest with you, yeah, that is maybe around $5. That?
Yeah. I see a lot of quarters. You know what, you could be right. That could be $10.
I think that was my laundry money. I would guess that was about $7. So,
all in all, again, we'll round up. How about for the rest of the episode we just
count those coins? Wait, hold on. Okay. I have discovered on Google, I've looked
look this up here on my trusty ipad and the volume, the volume of a dollar bill
in cubic inches is point oh six eight. So how so if we if we did we do I got
this six guys, I've got this to okay divided by
point oh six eight, and this is going to this is how assuming these are one
dollar bills only yeah. This number is how much yeah, let's get an estimate
okay,
ten billion dollars. All right, let's see here with one dollar bills. The
swear jar at the end of the year would have contained
nine thousand seven hundred and thirty five dollars, but but it was going to be
hundred is going to be hundred. So that's times one hundred and how many
swear jars did you say we have nine or ten nine or so let's go with ten. We'll
go with ten times ten. So that is approximately and this is a low ball
estimate. That is nine million seven hundred and thirty five two hundred
ninety four dollars and ten cents. I was okay and without accounting for the
coins. I should yeah and we've been around. I was often billions, but I mean
I was close. You were very close. We've been rounding up in rhymes. Yes, we've
been we've been rounding up on everything. So we'll just round down
saying nine million dollars. Yeah, so we were going to have about nine million
dollars by the end of the year. Yeah, and this was going to be we hadn't
decided on one charity yet. We're not going to because that's the thing.
That's the thing we like them all. It's hard to decide. It's hard to decide
one is the best one. We had been doing some research into some charities. You
know what? Let's go ahead and give these people a call. This is we were going to
call them and we're planning it at the end of the year being able to call these
people and say how would nine million dollars would it make a dent? Would it
make a dent? So let's go ahead and call. Let's call let's call no kid hungry. How
about that? Yeah, yeah, that sounds good. All right, let's see. Would you say that
that number that you put here is an a yeah
for that I messed up a
I make a lot of typos when I write with a pencil. All right guys, I'm calling
no kid hungry.
Hello and thank you for calling share our strength and the no kid hungry
campaign. Our business hours are Monday through Friday, nine AM to five thirty
PM. Well, that's good news.
Monday at 2. Oh it's a row, okay. It's one of the row votes. It's probably donor assistance. Yeah I think so.
We go and get up the some of the people. Yeah get this PowerPoint up.
Hi there, Stephen. I just have a question for you. For No Kid Hungry, that is your
charity, right? How would a nine million dollar donation change your charity?
That would be very, very beneficial. It would be... $1 would be 10 meals, so an equivalence of $9 million.
That would be an equivalence of 90 million meals.
90 million meals, that's how much that would be?
Yes, sir.
Well, that is great, but I have some awful news, which is that we were in the process
of raising $9 million to donate to No Kid Hungry, and a man named Deathroll5701 basically ended
it. He ended it just by complaining. So isn't that awful?
That is very sad news.
I'm really, really sorry. I just wanted to personally call you and tell you I'm so, so
sorry that frack 7190 wanted the swear jar bit to go and we had to cut it short.
I'm so sorry to hear that sir.
Yeah it really is just awful. So I hope that you have a good rest of your day and if we
do end up making the money then I'll give you a call okay and hopefully I'll uh it'll
be under better circumstances so thank you Stephen.
Yes sir. Thank you.
by. That just breaks your heart to have to do that is so depressing. I don't want to
have to be making these phone calls. No, me neither. This I realize how uncomfortable
this is for me. I know to have to call these people and say your lives are almost changed,
but these scumbags online, these fuckers, I'll say it. I can say it now. We can say
whatever we want. Uh huh. And you know what? I really, I really can't make these calls.
why because it's going to make me upset.
It makes all
yeah, it's really upsetting. I don't like having a just teeth.
Are you kidding me? That's awful! No, it's not right. You hear him
ninety you know what is because of people like zero arc who say that they
hate charity. Yeah, my God, listen, all right, I had to hear the light leave a
man's voice. That is so he didn't sound like he had a whole lot of light to
begin with. No, definitely not. I heard him. I heard him perk up.
I was terrible. Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna start calling. I gotta I gotta
get we'll keep going, but yeah, so I mean ninety million meals that would
change so many lives.
The ASPCA!
Yeah, I hope you
fuckers don't like animals.
This is a medical.
They're kind of being cruel
to us online.
I don't think they do donations.
Hmm.
Wait, we want a person. Or a dog.
for the ASPCA, please press seven.
For ASPCA premium gift requests, such as t-shirts, please press six.
Oh, that's kind of tempting.
That could go to this money could go to a t-shirt.
Please press nine.
I think we're out of options.
Yeah. Yeah. Representative.
Thank you for contacting the ASPCA.
Is it going to repeat?
And for all you... Yeah, I think it's going to repeat.
...selected and abused animals.
Remember to make pet adoption your first option.
I mean, I'm liking listening to this.
It's kind of fun. All right, they hung up on me. Damn. All right, try the next one.
What's the next one? The next one is homes for our troops. Okay, homes for our
troops. Let's go ahead and give them a call and let them know the bad news.
Yeah, it really is awful that we have to call every single charity our fans have
inflicted on us. Yeah, here we go. Okay.
Hi there. I'm speaking to the charity homes for our troops right now.
And you guys accept donations from corporations?
Yes we do.
Great.
Yeah, I just wanted to ask you, because we had a donation lined up that was, would $9
million be an acceptable donation for your organization?
Would that move the needle in any meaningful way?
It absolutely would.
Do you know exactly what this money would be going towards?
Like how we would be helping out these veterans with the $9 million?
We would be constructing a new home build.
New homes?
Wow.
Yes.
Well, that is unfortunate because we did have a fundraiser going to raise $9 million, but
unfortunately a few bad actors actually were able to get their fingers into it and interfere.
And it was people such as people like ZeroArk14 who said that they didn't like charity, they
didn't want the fundraiser to go through.
As well as Ben Beachy8962, actually quoted as saying "Swear Jar now, like four episodes
past being funny."
And these people, they actually lowered our donation amount from $9 million to much lower,
I believe even below $40.
So we're going to work on trying to get that number up and, you know, maybe get to the original
goal of nine million dollars but it's not looking so good due to a lot of people online.
Alright, well I'm very sorry to have to tell you the bad news. I hope you have a good day.
I know this can be tough. It's tough for us. But I'll hopefully be talking to you again
soon with better news. Thank you so much.
it's tragic, I'm not laughing, I'm crying, it's really emotional. I'm
crying, it's terrible. I really think that Patrick has to do one. I really
think he
is going to take me a minute. I think would you rather do the coalition for
the homeless or the ocean Conservancy?
Those are your two options.
That's what you want to do.
come on, come on, you have to call them. You have to call the ocean. The fans
are making us do this. I wish I don't want to do it. I could call them, but I
can't read this number. I'll put it in for it says bat sink.
Yeah, that what is that another zero? Yeah, Sig all right, don't worry, Pat,
I'll do it. I'll call for what this is another A. S. P. C. A. Well, we'll
figure that out. Yeah, no, I mean there's millions of charities in the
world that were unable to donate to due to the cruelty. Yeah, so bad actors
there you go. You're on the phone with them.
Hold it up to the mic.
to
two
emailing address or web address, please press one to leave a message in the
general mailbox. Please
don't press zero
wait, wait. I don't know which one I pressed. Hold on. He presses your
readily message in the box. I'll leave a leave a message. Don't leave a mess.
Okay, I'll call them if you're going to leave a message. Yeah, you got you got
canned. I'm getting cold feet. I can't
All right, call the Ocean Conservancy will make you call
the coalition for the homeless. Have a
we'll find a nice AIDS charity for you to call yeah and for you to give them
the news. I get like a beer or something
could maybe do it. Then Washington D. C. Our business hours.
You want to press number two
please listen to the following menu selections. If you would like to make a
didn't work. Yeah, their thing is kind of weird.
Of what we've learned. I don't think we should call an AIDS charity.
Why? I think that that's too much. What if we give them the $30?
I mean... Okay, here we go.
Get the PowerPoint up?
(phone ringing)
- Okay, but I think they don't want my call.
- That's why I think you should leave a message.
- You know what, maybe fuck these fucking hippie
whale fuckers over there in the ocean.
- Thank you for calling Ocean Conservancy's
National Marine Park in Washington, D.C.
All right, I'm going to try the four for a pressing inquiry. This is a pressing
they're definitely pressing inquiry.
Thank you for calling Ocean Conservancy's national office in
Washington, D. C. Oh my God, they hate us all right.
That's a big nothing. That's pretty disappointing. They're going to be
really sad when they find out and that's kind of the point of the nine million
dollars. We emailed them about is not coming. It's not so all also. I know
these these representatives wouldn't know this right off the head, but we told
them in advance. Yeah, we let them know. Of course we let them know. We said a
big donation. I don't even think we mentioned. I don't even think we went as
high as nine, I think, because we hadn't, but we ball part. We said five,
so they it was so
exciting for us when we realized that it could it was going to be more than
that, you know, and that we were going to be able to call these charities yeah
and say, say, hey, we have nine million dollars. We have nine million dollars,
which they again, ninety million meals. Do you remember that nine million for
children for children.
He did you hear the joy in his voice when I told him that he was about to be able
to hand hungry kids. He was about to give ninety million children, nine lives,
million or about thirty million children, because they want three meals a day, one
good one good day.
There is going to get thirty million kids of one good day of eating, so I I
feel sick to my stomach. Yeah, frankly, I feel fucking sick.
and I am ashamed of the people who listen to this podcast.
Yeah. You know what? Why don't we call some of them right now?
Okay. Let's call. Yeah, that's perfect.
Some of the people who text me, "Suck my balls, you dork."
Yeah, call him right now.
Yeah, I'll call this guy.
Yeah, call that guy.
He says, "Meet me in Saluda."
Call.
Okay.
Call. Go ahead. Start.
how carrier calling works if you're not calling over the internet.
Which of these phone numbers? Yeah scroll up and look which of these is the best
bet. Hmm for I would say probably legacy gifts or the adoption hotline. Alright
I'm gonna call the adoption hotline right now really quick while Pat looks
at this. I mean look at this poultry offering. This is disgusting. Is there a punch in that
we have of this poultry offering? This was every... Yeah, it says everyone is dying to
POV. These are the children who don't have any meals. Hello? Thank you for calling. Welcome
Thank you for calling Wildlife Fund. My name is Rose. How can I help you?
Hi there. I'm on the phone with the World Wildlife Fund right now, correct?
Yes.
Great. Well, I'm actually with a corporation that we were looking to make a large donation in the future to the tune of about $9 million.
And I was wondering if that money would be useful to you guys, if that would make a dent, and what exactly that would go to.
to, you know, if that could maybe help the wildlife of the world and maybe make a dent
in some of the horrible atrocities being inflicted against nature by a lot of these big corporations
nowadays.
I understand.
Why can't someone just send me a copy of your first donation and then connect you with a
member of the NIH to give you the information?
Okay, well, unfortunately, you know, I didn't want to have to do this immediately, but I
don't think it's going to be much use to transfer me over because the donation that we were
looking to make $9 million that fell through. And we have, you know, about maybe $30-ish.
And it's people on the internet, like this user Blort, who have decided that $9 million
is not a good amount to donate to charity. And they'd rather it be not even in the triple
or quadruple digits, but rather in the double digits and actually include a large pile of
coins as well. And it's people like Blort and like Hunter Mellow Potvin who don't like
fundraising. Yeah, it's disgusting. They hate charity. Well, I really appreciate that you
would like to transfer me and get this nine million dollars through. You're not going
to get nine million dollars from it because there is no nine million dollars and it's
all because of, you know, people online. So I just wanted to convey the bad news. Giorgio.
Okay, well thank you for calling. All right, well thank you. You have a good day as good
as you can have under the circumstances. Bye.
but
Georgio
so
anyway, I mean we can move on. Yeah, that was you know I we just had to get
that out of the way. You know we just had to
win.
Okay, so the point is the swear jar is gone. It's gone. It'll never come.
It's never coming back except maybe maybe next week, maybe
maybe it's coming back. No, it's not coming back. It's over. It's done.
All right, we can you know why why I thought about this. Okay, I've thought
about what I was going to say when eventually we got bullied into taking
away the swear jar. Yeah,
we are not
despots. We are not we're not we're not we listen. We
We have an ear for democracy, okay?
We listen to what you say.
And when the people whisper into it,
we have no choice but to listen.
So we are not communist China, communist Russia.
No, no.
I am no dictator.
I don't have the, I may have the stature for it,
and the general kind of alpha dog.
Commanding speaking voice.
Commanding deep speaking voice.
Some of us have anxiety.
Yeah, but I--
And when you have to make a phone call.
Yeah, exactly.
He makes you really scared.
Yeah. That's true, yeah.
He gets some some people are too scared to answer the phone call from just yeah,
even anyone from pretty much anybody. Yeah. So what I'm saying is we listened
and we are we we did it what you wanted. This is what you want to because this
in the end, it's a democracy. Yep. It really is. So if you ever want us to do
anything, you just tell us and yeah, stop.
Listen,
we'll we'll call this person right now. Who'd says
What'd he say?
- Doesn't know what he said.
- He can't tap and talk?
Okay, who's this?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
- Is this a charity?
- No, it's just a layman.
- A what?
- Just a layman.
- A layman.
- Just one of these nothings that interacts with us?
All right, well, we'll at least leave him a message.
- Yeah.
- Do you know what their name is?
- No.
- No?
- I don't know who this is.
Okay
That's true all right
Wait, he's got to leave. Yeah, we gotta talk really loud and
fucking bastard
Fuck this guy all right
Go ahead leave a message, but hi. This is Patrick Doran from podcast about list
I'm sure that you're aware that there was a,
on the most recent string of episodes,
there was a swear jar.
- Yep.
- And I just wanted to-- - This person's
getting a preview.
- I just wanted to let you know that the swear jar is gone
and it's your fault.
It's your fault.
You and all of the listeners have all democratically
or elected to get rid of the swear jar through--
- Tell them what we were gonna do with the money.
Oh, we were going to deck tuple it, which is times it by 10, and donate it to the ASPCA,
the Homeless Veterans Charity, the Ocean Conservatory. Yeah, we're going to donate it to all of these
people.
And tell them what we just had to do.
We just had to make a bunch of cold calls and tell all of these charities that we can't
donate to them.
So basically go fucking kill yourself.
Don't say kill yourself.
Okay.
I mean not.
That's too hard now.
Why did you say kill themselves?
They said I love podcasts about...
Wait, wait, wait.
Why did you call that person?
I don't know.
Because I...
Now you showed me all these people who were like, oh yeah, they're texting me saying fuck
you, fuck this person.
And I told this person to kill themselves and they're the one who said...
That's on you.
You're the one...
Why would you call this person?
we're done with call. We're done with call. We're done. We're done. You lost
your chance on calling. I'm sure that now people are sick of all the calls.
It's done. Yeah, I can't just start the normal podcast. I have the craziest
story to tell.
What is this?
This is nothing all sucker. It's gonna be another message.
They don't people don't answer the phone call. People who text you are even
more scared of phone calls than you are. It's true. Hang up on this fool. Yeah,
All right, what's your crazy story? So do you guys remember? I think it was maybe a
week or two ago. We came up with the idea of a
sent the opposite of a sensory deprivation tank. I forget what we called
it, but it's like it stimulates all your senses at once. Yeah, like it's every
it goes. It's like like
sweet and then salty and sweet and salt and like just and everything alternates
and is crazy. And I was in the real life version of that on the other day and it
shook me to my core. I've I have decided that this is that this idea we cannot
allow this to come to fruition. Why is that and because I had I was mentally
stimulated to my breaking point on the subway and here's what happened okay. I
was on the subway
with my fiance and we were riding the subway and I and there was a guy who was
watching videos on his phone, okay, with the sound on and he was acting kind of
crazy. He was doing crazy guy stuff. He was, you know, rubbing his face and
sniffling and doing crazy. Do you know that you know the type of crazy thing
I'm talking about like that? I do act in thirsty. He's like he's acting like a
third, he's doing like
like the tweaking then right a thought and he's on his phone watching videos. I
look at his phone is like I what is this guy watching and he's freaking out
about he was watching on his phone. He was watching gore compilations. Oh my
people being killed. He was watching like children's heads being smashed in
and like soldiers being shot. Holy okay, I started having like full. I was like
having a full panic attack of like oh my God, this guy's going to kill everyone
on this train. I have to be ready to get up and tackle this guy sitting right
next to him. Yeah,
he reaches into his pocket over on the bridge. I was like fuck fuck fuck. He
takes out not a gun. I was like thank God it's not a gun, but what it was was a
thing of fireball. He starts chugging the fireball still watching these videos
like like scrolling through them, choosing them, watching them scrolling
through and then right then the train like stops and we're stuck between
stations for like ten minutes and I leaned over and so my friends. I said I
said I was completely freaking out. She did not notice this was going on at all,
and I just said to her like listen. We have to get off this train at the next
up. I'll tell you why in a minute we just have to get on yeah, so I'm like
fully like complete. I am going to die mode and we the train starts moving
again. We get to the next stop this guy. He gets up. He leaves the train okay,
and I was like and I was like okay. We don't have to leave anymore. That guy
was going to kill us, but he's not going to kill us anymore. Literally the
second he leaves the train. I'm not sure to you twenty to thirty Amish people
and they're all smiling and dancing and the kids are going. Wow, it's going so
fast. Oh, my God,
I can't believe it and they're all laughing and smiling and they fill the
entire
and they're all in their outfits. So when they're not Amish, they're yeah,
the other one, the
ones who the other guys, I don't know, you know, I'm oh yeah,
Quaker, no, not Quakers, not Gideon's. No, I don't know what they were
basically on the nights, men and nights. Okay,
the men and nights are the ones that have flip phones, right? Yeah,
they have phones and shit and they can and they can go into cities
and they can make a car, but they look Amish. Yeah, they look they
and they were acting out. They were they were they were
they were incredulous of the train. That's what all the all the pictures
where you'll see where it's like look at these Amish people who are like
protesting for gay marriage or so yeah and it's always like yeah, it's always
men and I amish people don't speak English. Yeah, they have like well, they
did there. Have you seen those like shows of like the the Amish referred to
like people outside of their community, English as the English yeah wow that is
so fucked up. I could not believe that that was the craziest train right of my
life. I was fully a hundred percent convinced I was about to either die or
save the lives of everybody on the train. Yeah, and then imagine instantly were
the guy that had to you imagine you were the guy that
yeah, of course, I mean that's all that's all any man that sits around imagining
is either I should have tackled him anyway. Yeah, just a fucking show.
Yeah, you're the guy that stops grind face. Who's that? The owner of grind
ways dot TV. What's that? I don't know what you're talking about. Is the gore
website? You're that kind of guy. Yeah, you are that kind of guy. I don't like
that kind of shit. That's not right. No, Rex showed me it. He's watching. You
watched it. Yeah, 'cause he was showing me. But I would-, he would never show me
that. He shows me that. 'Cause I'm not-, 'cause he knows you're that type of guy.
I-, people know I do not like gore, gore stuff. I do not like pornography. I don't
either, but Rex showed me it. I don't like the kind of pornography where, where
women spread open their stuff. No. Oh! Yeah. I don't need to see the inside of
I barely like the outside. What do you mean when they spread open? You know
when I in a photo when a girl does this what I don't want to see that yeah, I
don't know what's don't touch your hand on it. Yeah, don't muddy it up with all
this stuff. I don't know what kind of door knobs you've been touching all day
to get to this studio oil on your in that's disgusting and I just don't like
that kind of thing and I don't like this bend over pull your asshole. Put a
peanut butter jar in there. Yeah,
nasty. You should have a sex with your eyes closed. That's what a perfect porn
movie to me is just a black screen and just sounds of like I'm making love. No,
not that is that's a lot of no, no, here's here's what it is. I love you. I
love you. I love you. I love you. I love you and then a higher pitch voice. I
love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. That's that's what it was. I
don't I would that to kissing no no no kissing, no, no kissing. You can get
sick. Oh yeah, no, no, no, no, no, you can kiss if you fast for three days
beforehand. Yeah, yes, that's fine. There could be food particles exactly. It
should be the same rules. You could have a turd yeah, you should have to act up
in your mouth.
I don't think that happens that much, but we can say that kind of thing now
yeah yeah, I guess that was a disgusting and it does where I kind of like having
no swear, because I would not be able to tell that pornography. Yeah,
opinion, the
the guy that you saw on the train who started watching yeah, best or he was
watching it the whole time. Well, the guy who took out started drinking the
fireball. I feel like he is a victim of that of the different, the reverse
sensory deprivation tank. He pro that's exactly that. He probably saw a bunch of
men and nights and then maybe saw someone cutting someone else's face off
with a machete. He was from the man. He was from the future coming back to the
past to kill you, but didn't recognize you with your haircut.
What?
Because of that when we thought about that,
when we thought about that you had longer hair, right?
I don't think so.
I think that was like a week ago.
It wasn't that long ago.
Shit.
I had shorter hair actually.
Swear.
See, you're still doing it.
You're doing the one, you're doing the thing.
So this is, yeah, this is the worst of both worlds.
Yeah, you're doing the thing that everybody hated about the swear jar.
I was just pointing out that I can swear again.
Yeah, we know you can swear again.
Fucker.
We already talked about that.
There we go.
That's good.
Yeah.
But,
Asshole.
Yeah, I mean, I guess there's no way to,
but I do truly think that that if that had if that had been and like if
somebody set that up and that happened to me for an hour, yeah, I would be
permanently insane because you I could not believe how I felt after that. I
only had three in brain were completely. So you there was no smell exactly
that's what I'm saying. If you have been tasting, I had the I had I had
smelling Yankee candles like ten to fifteen minutes of one like a cough
cough drop in his mouth. Well, that's a no. If you had a menthol cough drop in
your mouth, well, that was going on, you would have died. You would have
your really I would have
that's why I think we cannot move forward with this invention. It is too
dangerous. We need to pare down. Anyway, we need to get away from all of the we
need to I have been feeling recently like we need to shut off every light in
New York City for one day a week. Yeah, because it's too much and that used to
happen.
I don't know in the s. Why is it rolling blackouts? Oh well, I'm saying that for
everybody's health because lights are bad for you. They do that in Texas. I turn off all
the ACs for everyone. Speaking of a smart sensory overload, haven't been to Times
Square in like a year maybe. Nah, I think that's not close. I go every week. Maybe like
six months. Wait, you don't go every day. What do you do with your free time? I
mostly go around to abandoned warehouses and
graveyards and I take black and white photos. Oh, yeah. That's actually what I
you find like a broken mirror yeah. Damn, oh shit, a selfie with the photo
where you turn you're holding the camera like this. Yeah, I think I holding the
DS.
My Facebook profile picture is it's black and white and it's me in an
abandoned warehouse and there's a mirror like leaning up against the wall and
you see I'm taking a selfie, but it's one of the that's like a daguerreo type
where it's like I have the curtain over my
a giant another guy with a flash.
yeah, that is a building. So there's like two homeless people having sex. Hey
photographers, we know why you hide your face with the DSLR because you have a
weak chin. You are wanted for sexual assault. Yes, yes, yes, you are because
you took the photo of a warrant. Yes, so get the fuck out of my facebook account.
Yeah,
changing my profile picture
of me where I look really cute. Stop hacking my facebook and making my
2015 profile pictures look really artsy. They do look cool. Stop using filters on
them. Bokeh. Yeah, true. Also, bokeh, what the fuck is bokeh? I don't like bokeh.
That's not bokeh. No, no, no, that's not okay. That is not bokeh with me.
Bokeh with me. I do not like bokeh. Make that photo flat. Yeah. No dynamic range.
No, and I don't need to... You know what a light should look like? A bulb. A
light, you should be able to see the perfect outline of the bulb. I don't need
to see a flare and for a hey all you all you instagram photographers you yeah
messing with the tilt shift. I'm going to take a still shit on you. Yeah,
stand up on some stilts and poop on you from twenty feet above. I'm going to
tilt you over a building and shift you into the next world. That's what's
going to happen. You're going to be come. You're going to be come. You're
going to be
you will be nothing but come. You're going to be all that will be left of
you after I get my hands on you, you will just be come to me. You'll be nothing
but come you'll be come to the world yeah, not even a puddle. It'll be you
know and it'll be chunky too. It'll be like when you go to the beach and you
have that sand that's kind of wet and kind of dry and you dribble it to make a
castle. Yeah, that will be that type of calm. It's going to be chunky. It's
going to be chunky and bits of green like Siddiqui. Yes, yeah, there's going
to be a lot of chunks in that come and it's going to come in a little plastic
Ramekin and that's all you'll be to me. Yeah, and then I will eat you. Oh, I
forget where I was going with the Times Square thing,
but I was in Times Square.
Congratulations. We were talking about cum and stuff and my brain shut off.
You got so nervous from the phone calls that now you can't even breathe. I
don't know why we didn't do the phone calls after, 'cause now we have to fill
up another 20 minutes. What do you mean fill up? Fill it up. We should have.
You're just having a freak out attack. Lifted it up, lifted the time up. Yeah,
I don't know why I get up. I don't know why I get so tired of praying. I don't
know what lifted the I don't know why I get scared of prank calls.
You think someone's going to say I know who you are yeah, you're Patrick
Torin and yeah, I mean I mean you
I think I got in trouble really young for prank calls me too. I don't want to
didn't get in trouble for prank. We've talked about this. My first prank call I
ever did I my brother was like call this lady call this phone number Texas tell
other, that your house is on fire and your parents are dead and you're stuck
in the house and then hang up. I was like, oh, that's hilarious, and then I
just did that like four or five times. Yeah, I just think the idea of just
like
making somebody have to answer the phone to say I can't give you
a million dollars.
Do you do way more evil stuff? I know you're a skateboarder. I thought you
stole my go and you it's not a joke. You go and you ruin public parks. You do
You ruin public parks. I do kinetic art. No, you do not.
(laughter)
No, you do not.
You're not a dancer. I'm adding to the ecosystem.
I'm doing kinetic art.
I wish you would add to the ecosystem by being fucking manure in the ground.
(laughter)
That's what I wish you would do.
After today, I think I will be. Yeah, I really hope so.
I think we should call this Suicidal.
(laughter)
I'm going to kill myself if I don't give you $9 million.
Oh wait, I only have $30.
I was going to give you $9 million
million dollars and the truth is the truth is I would do a hundred more calls
to charities and tell them I can't give them any more. That was that's the
funniest
that's like that's a that's a fucking that's a chuck palinuck protagonist.
Yeah,
a guy who jacks off and calls charities. I was jacking off under the table by
speaking in check, pallin, rewatch fight club this past. We yeah yeah, it was
just okay really. I see I honestly haven't watched it since I watched it
ten thousand times when I watch it as a kid. I had the same feeling that I get
watch it. If I actually see a gore movie or so or video or something where I got
a pit at a pit in my stomach because of that shit was so real yeah, but then I
watch it this time and I was like improvement is masturbation. I watch it
this time and I was speaking of masturbation. I was like Brad Pitt. You
are looking well actually you know what I thought when I was a kid. I saw Brad
Pitt in that movie and I was like Brad Pitt is jacked. He's like really skinny
in that. Yeah, he weighs like a hundred and twenty pounds. Yeah, he's cool and he
looks cool, but he doesn't when I was a kid. I thought he was like buff. Yeah,
yeah, but he's a guy. You know what it is? It's he's it's because he's next to
Edward Norton and not because of Edward Norton's body, but because of his voice.
Yeah, true nerd voice, nerd voice. I found out the other day that Brad Pitt
fucked Mike Tyson's wife. Why? And he walked in on them fucking wow. Why did
do that just to jizz oh yeah all right that makes sense to fall in love yeah
hopefully yeah hopefully they found hopefully they were wed after that she
was wed in the middle of it oh my god she's wed between the lids yeah yeah
that's pretty sexy Brad Pitt had sex with Mike Tyson's wife
apparently the story was they were getting oh yeah that's good they were
getting a divorce. They were getting a divorce, Mike Tyson and his wife, but he would still
go over to her house and fuck her sometimes or get fucked by her because he was like...
they would go...
Mike Tyson would?
Yeah, he said that they would do quickies, but they were getting divorced, but he went
over one day and he opened the door and who was fucking his wife?
Well, why'd he go over?
Brad Pitt. I just told you to have sex with her.
Yeah, but he didn't call?
He didn't do that back then. He just showed up and fucked girls.
that's no calls yeah, you surprise them at the house showed up and your shoulder
check the door down. Yep, you ran in. I honest I feel like Mike Tyson probably
to do that. Mike Tyson did go to jail for rape one time and yeah, now I think
about it's probably not that good to joke about that one with him, but he
walked in and Brad Pitt was fucking his wife and he said Brad Pitt was like
don't punch me man bro. Don't punch me bro man. Please don't hit me and Mike
Mike Tyson just laughed and left.
That's funny.
But I think that he didn't finish the story, because here's what I think happened.
He walked in and he saw Brad Pitt, who hadn't done any movies yet really.
It was like 1989 or 1990.
But he saw that he was cute and that one day he would be really successful.
He'd be really funny and burn after reading.
So my guess is that Mike Tyson made him have sex with him.
You know what I think happened is that Mike Tyson walks in-
he would have blackmail because now if Brad Pitt ever wanted to do something
that Mike Tyson didn't like exactly, he probably has a
photo. Brad Pitt probably has like a
documentary he's been trying to get made. It's about kind of the evilness of
Mike Tyson, the evenness of getting interrupted while you have sex. He's
interviewing like interviewing Vander Holyfield. He's like yeah and isn't the
worst part about Mike Tyson when he walks in on you.
You don't think Mike Tyson walked in, saw Brad Pitt fucking his wife and
thought damn I'm fucking her real good. That's what fight club style. Oh, well,
fight club hat was far from coming out. Well,
that doesn't make the joke good, does it? I think if you try to well, I mean,
try to put history into it. I don't think the joke made any sense to me
anyway. No, it took me a minute. Yeah, yeah, yeah, took you a minute, but once
you got it, it was good, right? Just the idea that that's his alternate
personalities. We're saying yeah, okay, I think that maybe if I told it better, if
I had if I had made the fight club movie and I was adapting the book okay in this
day and age when everything needs a tag, everything needs a universe in it,
though I'd ignore the phone. I'd say I would say in this the world there's no
phones, whatever, but I would at the end. So you know Brad,
Edward Norton, Brad Pitt is his secret identity. We're sorry for the spoilers.
if you haven't seen it, but at the end at the very end spoilers to at the very
end, I would have a third guy show up and he says and I'm your third identity
and I have lightning powers
that'd be good and they're like all along. We're focused on these two guys.
We even consider there's a hundred thousand identities and they're and
they're part of the fight of verse. I was telling you about each identity,
each person, telling you about that movie of the day. No wait before split.
There was a movie off unbreakable, no one the one it's about a
serial killer at a motel. Oh yeah, you were telling me about this. Motel, multiple...
Is there a thing with his mom? Identity. Identity. Identity 2003. I watched Identity
and Secret Window in the same day and it really tortured me
psychologically. Which one is Secret Window? That's the Johnny Depp one where he puts
the... Oh yeah. It's the same thing I think where he has a bad alter
ego. But Identity was... I'm realizing right now that the reason why my mom bought
bought all these movies was because she started going to school to be a
psychologist, and so she got
she bought all these movies
that were about your mom just started watching the butterfly effect yeah
literally single day and was like oh my God, I need to write a paper on this.
That's probably what I would do too, but anyway, the movie is it's the worst
movie ever. It's a serial killers at a motel and then at the end, all of the
people are dead except for the little kid and then it's like zooms out and the
entire movie was just taking place with a straight jacket guy in the back of a
car. He's like on his way to a mental hospital and he's so crazy. That he
thought all of that in his mind? That he just had a... He just dreamt a movie
in his head. He just dreamt a movie? Yeah. Isn't that... That's so bad. Yeah,
it's really, really bad. It's not even implied that that's... That he's the
little kid and he's in the straight jacket? No, I don't remember what the
implication was really. I think it maybe opens up with him at the mental
hospital and it's like and I think the whole movie is kind of like oh he's
escaped and he's like he's probably the one killing all these people, but then
at the end it was actually just him having some thoughts. Yeah, you know
which is like the lowest stake you can have for a movie. It's like a guy's
thinking something. Yeah, well after like six cents and stuff everybody wanted
like a
sense in a long time. Is it six cents is fire. Hold on. It's really good.
That's good. It's crazy that that yeah Donnie Wahlberg. He's good that all
that stuff was happening in the early 2000s, all those that type of movie they
were doing all that and then it wasn't I had shutter Island wasn't till like 2010
or something. I didn't see shut around. I was like pretty good, but isn't that
crazy that it's that they're pretty late of all. Yeah, yeah, that that one seems
like a movie that just may took too long to make. Yeah, I see that. I could see
that. Yeah, like they started it in the yeah, and then that like, you know, they
they're a film that a film that a mass yeah really been to that. That film
didn't shut her out. They filmed it no in a fucking
long field or something. Oh long island isn't there the long island was where
all the house people lived no the off of Boston. There's the island where all
the homeless people lived. It was no it wasn't actually didn't actually the
island itself. I don't know about the island, but the mental hospital yeah is
not actually on an island yeah and I've been there and I went there
and it's and when I was there, there was flying machines in the air. Oh, you
told what about that? Yeah, what do you mean flying miss drones? I don't know
people were flying around in little machines. You are just a liar, not I
don't know what they're called, but they're there was like a parachute and a
little chair and wheels and they're flying around. I have known you for so
many years and you have gotten so much worse at describing things yeah. I don't
know what this thing is called. You never make any sense when you describe
something okay picture the car from Gary's mod yeah smaller yeah. I think
you know what it is is he's trying to make his descriptions of things shorter
and more broad so that I can understand them. It's like you over shot it,
though, yeah, now you're skipping. I don't I don't know what to call these
things other than flying machines that yeah, you know that's what they were as
soon as he said Gary's mod. I was like okay, he wants me. Well, I'm trying to
visualize it in my head of what this thing looks like it's like you sit on
with your finger. I have a pencil no no no no no finger,
and I think there's a parachute attached to it too, but the thing is also this
was long enough ago that I can't really remember exactly what it looked like.
This was a kite no because you sit it well. I guess I wouldn't call it a
cut in it yeah it's people were paragliding no no no no no no it was
like a machine. It's like a plane. It has a motor and they like fly it up and
I fly around playing. Well, yeah, there's a guy who has Google here is not helping me.
It's not a plan. I'm finding a single person plane. I've seen these. You know
what it is? Jubio right now is calling. I don't think it had wings though. Jubio
is playing league. It doesn't need wings. I swear to God. Jubio is playing league.
It doesn't need wings. Jubio. That is a plane screen share. What are you talking
about? Screen share right now? You sure what your other computer that doesn't
make any sense. You have one computer that you're using right now. I thought
you were going insane because you didn't want to call the charity. Oh, I am
going. It's literally called a parachute flying machine. Let me see no way. Let
me see I googled flying machine parachute. Is that
this is called infinity power parachutes? No, what are you
it's called a powered parachute? Let me see it. It says parachute. I clicked on
something by accident. Go back Wikipedia, a powered parachute, but go
back to the Google search. I don't I don't know how to go back to parachute.
Fuck you. It literally is a flying machine, our parachute there. Yeah. If I
saw that, I would call that a playing machine shut up. Fuck you yeah, that's a
flying machine. That's a power parachute. I knew that for the instant save. You
just said power parachute. It would have come to mind instantly. I said it's a
parachute with a motor and that doesn't say you knew about a powered parachute
and you can think of it from yeah. I did I just was having an off day. You have a
learning disability. No, I did not do no. I do not you have a right. You don't
so you have a normal disability yeah everything, not just my legs. I don't
work isn't it cool, but you're a bunch of people flying around up there in
those things. So did you think because you were at shutter island, did you
think
maybe I'm a crazy?
Maybe you know it was you know it was crazy. You were there because they were
doing a pop up
screening a drive in movie screening of the
shining there, which is yeah. I know what a lay up that I know right pretty
weird. Well, they probably already did screenings. There is the problem and
they're like all right. Yeah, I think it was they were trying to milk everything
they could get out of it, but near the at the end of the movie, like right near
the end, this like super thick fog came in and like covered up everything. We
couldn't see the screen. We were driving home. We couldn't see the road. That's
isn't that scary, just like the shine die. No, it is not just like that scene
in the shine. Yeah, when the car gets fogged up, that's so scary. Yeah,
doesn't that seem haunted to happen at a mental? I really a mental, but you guys
ever get scared that maybe you have a multiple personality that doesn't live
anywhere near you and lives like on the other side of the world
and it's just like doing random shit
scares me. I know I have I have like millions of them yeah. I'm an entire
where you
personality is China yeah. I'm the one who's been doing all this stuff I've
and you just you're only here for like one percent of your life. The rest of
the time you're just running around, trying to be a billion people.
Yeah, scary that is the idea that you can have multiple personalities is
really scary. It's super rare, though. No, no, I just looked at it happens to
everybody. It happens to everybody. Cancer eventually everybody has multiple
personalities. Yeah, what
what
that was going to be I was going to do another part and then I was like
I don't want to do that voice anymore. I think it was
family.
That's just like a terrible fucking sketch
Oh my God yeah, but that does I have been afraid of that since I was a child.
You know,
did you ever why you ever watch very good English that movie split? No, the
funny part about that like that actor is it it's framed like like it's like
a boy. It's I get it yeah for me. It's framed like it's
like it's a way mental health awareness, like it where it's like there seems
where he's he has multiple personality story is like twenty seven personalities
the movie or something a lot and and he's like and his therapist and he's like
and they're talking. They're like we need to show the world that this is like
a real thing that people suffer from and we exist and we we're not like monsters
and we need it and then the whole like plot just to the movie is that his last
personality is a cannibal monster that can crawl on one
he like bends open jail bars. He was like
isn't that they're like it's like a double twist to
there's another twist in that movie where it's like yeah. This all takes
place in the same universe is unbreakable yeah. Do you know what
there's a plot twist in between those two and you know what it is? It's that
the whole movie took place in a zoo
really yeah, that's the in a zoo he's underground in a zoo. See, I think
honestly is Christ. Why is it a good movie? If somebody has that shouldn't we
just kill them?
yeah, but you might have a hard time because their personality is true.
This will bullet dodger. Why did you give him five dollars? I was just
holding five dollars. He took it. Oh, this was my five dollars yeah. That was
his five dollars. I put this. It was the first thing that went in the jar. It
was almost a s b s. Yeah, look at all. I just will rip this in half. I remember
every single one of the
for a fuck yeah shit. Yeah, let's tear up a turd. Yeah, this one. I think was
can't tear up this one. This was probably come related, but I oh is my dollar
still on the floor. I don't think we ever picked it up. I picked it up. I
brought it home. I think that you said that we were not going to bring it home.
You hold on. Well, you miss the sword. You miss the job. You took swear jar
money. No, it wasn't. Well, did it ever go in the jar? He does that. No, it was
intended to go to the swear jar. Well, don't worry at home. I actually didn't
take home. I just pocketed it because I needed a dollar for the swear jar and
and I used it, so it's in here somewhere. All right.
Yeah, but people who have really bad mental disorders, why do we not just kill
them? Why do we have to put them in jail? I truly think it's because some of them
are so unhinged and unleashed that they will stop at nothing to prevent from
being killed, and a person who has- How unhinged do you have to be to be
employed? A person who has strong enough BPD, borderline personality disorder,
should be killed. Whoa. Will be able to manipulate- That's true. A police
officer into giving them their gun and then going on a rampage and killing
millions. Well, they just say like if you don't give me your gun, I'm going to
kill myself. That would be a scary version of the happening is somebody
with very strong BPD walking around getting people to kill themselves. If
you don't give me your gun right now, I will shoot myself in the head.
I will do it. Do not give me your gun. I saw a video of a
guy getting shot yesterday where he was just sitting there. Were you on the
train? No, yeah. Drinking fireball? Yeah. Okay. Oh my God, Caleb has multiple
I had a very itchy wig on.
Cameron's sitting there freaking out about this guy.
It's you and a big orange afro.
I'm like, "Could that be?" No.
There's no way.
I would be so...
He doesn't have an itchy face.
I'm realizing I would be so good at having multiple personalities,
because I could do my costume favorite stuff.
Yeah, because...
Custom favorites.
I love my costume favorites.
James...
I do have multiple personalities.
That's what...
Goth, jock, chef, emo, golfer.
James McAvoy in that movie is all specifically so that he can that
literally is yeah. He has costumes yeah is what he's a fat. I remember that in
the trailer fashion designer and then he's a woman and then he's a little boy.
I don't think I have a woman in me. I think you do you're about to
what does that mean
you get a woman that fucked
hurt me with a finger. I don't know hey, I
I don't know you know what we should do what
here's the here's the hypocrisy over here. Okay, I see
he won't call a charity for homeless people and tell them that he wants to
spit in their face, but he'll call dominoes and hold her a pizza. I don't
know.
I use the app. You have that kind of phone anxiety where you can't call an
order something yeah.
Wow, I didn't know that about you. I have what I think what I want. What I
which I thought that was only on locks phone anxiety, at least for me, which I
feel like I used to have a lot. I used to have bad phone anxiety. I don't really
anymore. Is it a stranger on the phone? You have literally absolute power over
them. Yeah, you can destroy them. They never can literally you can kill them.
Yeah, well, I mean well you can kill that you can hang up at any time and you
can also say it doesn't matter what you say because they're not there. So you
can say I want to order a mother fucking pizza with poop sauce bitch and then you
coming up yeah. Actually, let's do that right now.
Hold on, you ordered a nine million dollar. You have to you have to call
dollars and order a mother fucking pizza. I don't want to order a with the
thing. Do you know what we literally have already done that we've called
Dominos on the show and said, I want to poop. Yeah, we've called and asked for
a poop pizza. We'd be repeating a thing. We called an ice cream parlor.
What do we do? I don't remember it was so long ago. Yeah, you won't call and
I want to order a poop pizza. I don't want to call. All right, whatever the
episodes done. Yeah, it's over next time. We will make Patrick call. We're
just gonna be a prank call show. Yeah, from now on and we're gonna we're gonna
not that these were pranks. By the way, this was not a hundred percent real.
This is a hundred percent real.
That we are not a lead up to a prank call. The only way you could consider
that a prank is if somehow the fans donate us enough money that we get to
donate nine million dollars. We get to call back these charities. So, psych,
that was all a prank. If we can get the Patreon at nine million a month and
yeah, we'll go one for go one month yeah that's fine, but if not you know a
month I don't know yeah we'll figure it out. Okay, bye guys shareholder beating
oh yeah is this Friday on Friday,
wait it is on Friday.
Okay, bye
This guy in those fucking aviator...
Uh, fucking...
No, I will not look like a pedophile.
I'll look like Jeffrey Dahmer.
But he wasn't a pedophile.
He was just an evil killer who was gay.
And you think he's a pedophile because he's gay.
No, I think he's a pedophile because he's a murderer.
Pedophiles don't usually kill.
Pedophiles, you can call them murderers.
Yeah, they always...
Because they just want pleasure all the time.
They don't want to deal with death.
God, I hate them.
They really are sick.
What do you mean, what's wrong with me?
Why'd you say "pleasure" like that?
Pleasure!
I was trying to think of the right word.
You were saying pleasure.
You weren't talking about pedophile.
You were saying they have pleasure.
You were saying that like they are going on tropical vacations.
Yeah, it's a euphemism.
I also heard like pina colada.
I heard the girls gone wild.
I was talking about pedophile.
I heard a steel drum.
No, no, no.
I heard don't know.
It's a useless reason.
So I don't think they don't have to care about fucking kid in the butt.
Is that what you rather say?
See what the hell?
No, that's what he that's he thinks of it.
There we go.
Yes, that was a cricket.
The reaction you guys yelled.
I got a rise out of you and that's honestly all I care about in comedy is
getting a rise out of people and now I don't care to make myself laugh.
I'm pushing the envelope.
It's a cool as fuck actually.
No, that was not a joke. You can't say fucking a kid in the butt like that. Well, if you do
that after, I guess it's kind of, it kind of is a joke. I guess anything you say there.
This is how I feel. If I, when I, I don't like it, that pedophiles fuck kids in the butt.
That's how I feel when I think about it. That's how you feel. That's how, wait, that is the
audience reaction to you saying that you don't like it. So this is you talking in the audience.
Yeah, you have control of it.
Say it again and then do the right one.
A pedophile fucking kid in the butt.
This is crass.
This is not the kind of thing I want to be doing.
It's not crass, it's political.
Can we not say it again though?
I don't like that thing.
There we go.
So that makes more sense.
In my head when I think of that thing.
When I think about it.
Why are you thinking?
Okay, the episode is over.