Now announcing the podcast about List Board Game.
Head over to kickstarter.com to back the project.
Pre-orders will ship late 2026.
The game includes artisanal dice, game pieces,
mouse-trapped staircase, compressed air to blast pieces around,
string, controllable cars, rubber, water dish for the water levels,
character sheets, strategy handbook, stick, brick, rock,
card deck, magnetized hazards, supersized pretzel bags,
pencil bags, balance board, play mat, 3D glasses, helmet, inflatable chair, and a game board.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, game night!
- All right, and we're live.
- Live. - Welcome to game night,
everybody.
- Woo!
(laughing)
- You didn't even do it on camera.
- Do what on camera, hurt our necks?
- No, we hurt our necks.
- I hurt my neck a few days ago.
- I fell down some stairs.
- And I was lying in bed and I got up too fast
and I hit my head on the wall.
- Those are very stupid ways to hurt your neck.
But I hurt my neck and just compared to those,
a very, very cool way.
- Yeah.
- So, uh.
- It's not really a competition about,
it's not a competition about who hurt their neck
and who didn't.
- Yeah.
- You guys also, you went,
you guys bought prop neck braces that are way nicer
than the one that I have on,
that I bought for my real neck.
- These aren't props.
- These are real, we hurt our necks.
- Yeah, we got these from the doctor.
- We went to the doctor to get them.
- Mm-hmm.
- I was sleeping over Cameron's house
and I fell down his stairs.
Uh-huh and when I heard him fall down the stairs I set up really fast and I hit there's stairs
Have you not but there's there's a few or three stairs. He doesn't know in my entryway
Now I'm done on my fucking location. Everyone's gonna find an apartment. There's two or three stairs in the entryway
Maybe I don't know because I have a head injury from what I can't even look over here
Yeah, my shit hurts so bad. Actually. This is it's actually doing numbers for my back pain three numbers. I
I actually feel pretty good not having to move my neck.
His back pain's doing numbers.
This is just... you guys have just thrown a biggest wrench
into everything that I thought was going to happen today.
I was like, "Man, this is going to be amazing.
I'm going to sit here, barely move, barely talk,
and I just get to basically take the day off and kind of just sit here."
And now you've ruined it.
And now I have to... now we're all on a level playing field.
And it's pissing me off.
We all hurt our necks.
- Yeah, we all hurt our necks, I don't understand.
- Okay, well then how did you?
- I told you, I fell.
- Ow, just stop.
How did you hurt your neck?
- I fell down the stairs at Cameron's house.
- And you, Cameron?
- I hit my head on the wall, I guess.
- You guess?
- Yeah, that's what I heard.
- Because you got knocked clean out.
- Yeah, I was completely knocked out.
I went to the doctor and they said,
well, based on the type of neck pain that you're having,
I would have to imagine you hit your head on the wall
after being scared by your friend falling down the stairs.
I was so worried about my neck brace causing alarm that I put on this Dodgers
hat because I was like, "I'll have a second thing."
So that I can be like,
just redirect all the attention to my new hat. Yeah, that's not a new hat
though. That's an old hat. It's new to my head. Not new to your head,
you've worn that around. You're trying to say stuff that's false so we'll
shake our heads and hurt our necks. Yeah. You want me to...
I'm on to you.
It hurts to laugh because of my neck.
Ow!
Oh my god.
Do you guys realize that this is-
And my throat hurts too because I was glizzy gulping.
This is basically the same as some kind of racist thing.
This is not the same as some kind of racist thing.
This is you being racist to me.
Yeah, you're being racist to us.
You're saying like you're not a real person whose neck was hurt.
Not all injuries are visible.
But if you-
Man.
If you really feel that way about it, maybe, if for once in your life you took a knee and
you prayed, I would feel better.
Yeah.
And I wouldn't have to wear this neck brace anymore.
No, I'll take a knee.
I will.
During the national anthem.
Come on, man.
Don't do that.
Because I'm the anti-Christianity.
That is disrespectful to God and the truth.
You're literally making me clench my jaw right now.
Fuck God.
That's how I got in this situation in the first place.
I'm going to have to wear a jaw brace.
Ow.
I want to look at Patrick because I love him, but I can't.
What you should do is this.
Oh, yeah, I forgot I have my back so you guys
That's actually that's not funny. That's what I've had to be doing
Multiple days in a row comedy comes from reality. It's observational. It's tragedy plus
Tragedy guys what's happening in the world you guys don't even know what happened to me. I don't know what happened
You just went like this
But do you know why he got it get stronger ghetto gagged? I was at his neck. Oh, yeah
- I heard you were the throat goat.
- Yeah, no.
You took too many--
- I heard you were the throat goat.
I heard, I heard you were the complete throat goat.
- No, I'm not the throat goat.
- You're in an alley smoking a cigarette,
a guy comes up to you and you're like,
hey, I heard you're the throat goat.
- That actually happens a lot.
- That's not me.
- No, I'm not the throat goat.
- I'm not the throat goat anymore.
- Not anymore.
- I hurt my neck.
- Ever since I hurt my neck in the big throat competition,
the deep throat contest.
I don't know.
- It's kind of a pun, rocky pun.
- You used to be a sucker.
You used to be a slurper.
You used to be the champ, the throat goat.
Remember what I first told you when I brought you in here.
You're gonna suck my penis.
(laughing)
- No, no guys.
That's not how I hurt my neck.
I hurt my neck. - How did you hurt your neck?
- 'Cause I went to the gym.
- He tried to do a back flip.
- I tried to do a back flip and I landed on my neck.
- Are you serious?
- No, a guy, I was starting my workout
I didn't have that much time.
And then a guy I know came in,
Christoph came into the gym.
And I told him this,
I talked to him about this last night,
I completely blame him.
Just having somebody you know at the gym
just makes it a little bit different.
And he set up his bench right behind
where I was doing upright rows.
So I grabbed a way heavier weight than I would normally do.
And I started to do them and I did two of them
and then I immediately broke my neck.
But then, it hurts so bad.
But he was right behind me, I'm like,
Like yell out in pain, so I just kept doing it, and then I did like three more sets
Oh, and I did the rest of my workout - gee and I went to the locker room
And I laid on the floor for about 15 20 minutes. Oh, you're dumb as hell for that
Why the hell would you keep going you fell off stairs?
So that is dumber pets. That's not dumb. That's why I was coming
I'm the only one who I broke my neck and a peaceful. I mean a nice
I mean a cool way Cameron eats banana peels throws them shits around in his building
Oh, yeah
Yeah, I took me a second to process. It's a banana eats a banana throws that damn peel on the floor
He doesn't give a fuck. Well. It's
Compostable apartment yeah the whole apartment is compostable smokes in his way to get new furniture every few months because it biodegrades
Banana that was on a cigarette
But under a bunch of them like it had like it was a bunch of little stick ball bearings. Yeah
You believe your ball bearings everywhere - well. I'm not good. How what am I supposed to do hang them on the wall?
No, it's not possible you get a magnet you put in the middle of the floor then all your fucking ball bearings
Room but with a magnet on top you get my you could get your bearings off my balls
And tell which way
There's no
Yeah, you're like being in a white cuz they're so full yeah, they're right there push their swirling yeah like dough
Yeah, rising dough. They look like my head
Your head is less smooth.
- If you put your balls on a skillet,
you could probably fry 'em like pita bread.
- Oh yeah, where they get that nice,
those little pockets?
Yeah.
- Do you know what always makes me laugh?
That whenever I think about pita bread,
that I can't figure out how this even,
how do you, what do you do with this?
So I'm just gonna tell you.
- Okay.
- To imagine somebody who's at the grocery store,
and they're looking at pita bread,
and they look at a package of pita bread,
and it says pita bread, and they are reading it,
and they go, "Oh, peanut butter bread."
(laughing)
And then they buy it,
and they think it's peanut butter bread.
- Peanut butter bread?
- They read pita as peanut butter.
(laughing)
- Well, this is just nonsense.
- It's nonsense, that's what I'm saying, it's nothing.
- It makes no fucking sense.
- You've thought about that before?
- I think every time I see pita bread,
I think about that. - You might need a--
- You think about that every time you see pita bread.
- The neck brace-- - Well, I don't think about
when I don't see or hear about pita bread,
so I'm not crazy.
- You are not, you don't have a neck affliction.
You have something deeply wrong with you in your brain.
I don't think you're right.
Yeah, you need a helmet, not a brace.
A helmet is not going to help me.
I have a helmet over there somewhere.
You want to wear that?
I'll wear that.
I can't wear that with headphones.
I still can't believe this.
You could just put it on.
You guys don't know what it's like.
I had to--
Oh, I don't know what it's like to get an injury?
It's not about the injury.
It's about actually wearing the neck brace in public.
I had to--
Or at home.
I took mine off before I went and ordered my sandwich,
and I just sat there in pain because I didn't want some little--
You have no idea--
It hurts when you take it off?
Everything hurts all the time.
You have no idea.
I used to wear a neck brace all the time when I was a younger. Yeah, I lived in a bubble
Yeah, I wore a neck brace all the time in a Tony the Tiger t-shirt why I'd say
The store we are kind of giving a trio of Tourette's guy vibes yeah
Fucking what yeah, what the ass?
Yeah, I've dressed what
Wait, what?
Hold on.
[LAUGHTER]
I'm Tourette's guy.
Yeah.
He clearly did not have Tourette's.
No.
I think he had a neck problem.
Here's what he had.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
He had a sense of humor.
Yeah.
That's what he had.
There you go.
That was a funny fucking video.
I told you about that.
I used to give a shit, then I got fucked.
Remember that one?
That was the best one.
That's fucking poetic.
If you like F word and S word, there is no--
stop.
Look no further.
Tourette's guy has you completely covered.
He had a video, there's one really funny photo of him in the back of a car,
and it says, "This is the second time I've been fucked by Dairy Queen."
It's a car moving really fast, and he's got ice cream all over his face.
Oh.
That one still makes me laugh.
He was funny.
Some of those old videos, man.
He made light of a disease.
Tell you what, anyway.
He made light of a disease that everyone thinks is already very funny.
Yeah.
Nobody thought it was funny before him, though.
That's the thing.
People thought it was he was the one who yeah, it was a
South Park a big year for Tourette's in 2008
Yeah, maybe
It was a microchip
Situation that was getting more people Tourette's in that year that could be that's why we get videos like that
This to my conspiracy minded
You have a fucking conspiratorial brain
Something else exciting is that now Jubio can talk say hello. Jubio. Hello to everybody
Hello, Jibya.
Do we have a camera that you can...
He's right there.
What do you mean?
He's right... yeah, he's right up there.
Can we cut to him right here?
You are both...
Okay, you are actually acting injured,
which maybe I'm realizing that you always have the
kind of body movement of somebody with a neck injury.
I always have in trouble.
He is moving around...
He's moving like Chris fucking Farley right now.
I said I always have trouble.
Look at the way that he...
He's like...
Nobody could move that fast if they had a neck injury.
You are like doing a terrible representation.
I think that when I die and they dissect my body,
which is what they're gonna do,
they're gonna find out that 24/7 I was in greater pain
than anyone has experienced in their life
and I just had such a high tolerance
that I didn't realize it. Wow.
And that all along I was experiencing
like 10 child birthing mothers
combined with 100 goalies getting hit in the balls
with a ball, combined with slicers.
- Isn't it fucked up that girls have a higher tolerance
for pain?
- It's not true.
- That's not true at all.
- No, it is true.
- No, it's not true.
- Listen, I would really like to say it's not true.
It's completely true, dude.
- What, have you been testing it out?
- Yeah.
I've been testing it out.
I've been hurting a lot of women
and hurting a couple men as well.
And the women, it doesn't hurt those.
- They just need to stop.
They need to stop fucking around.
- The women do?
- Let me finish.
What are you laughing about?
'Cause he thinks everything is funny 'cause he got a fucking necklace on.
Everything's a joke to you.
Look at this.
Everything's a fucking joke to you.
Look at the way he's moving.
It's actually making me so mad that if I did not have a disability, then I would attack you.
They need to stop fucking around, and they need to come up with a real unit for pain
that's not a bunch of half-assed fucking emojis.
Scoville.
Do you know how, like a Scoville-
They use ten emojis that say "I'm happy" versus "I'm sad" or "I'm in pain."
Do you know what is the worst part about this, man?
What?
is walking down the street and feeling like,
I can't protect myself.
- Damn. - Because normally,
I feel like how people feel when they have a gun.
My body is a gun. - Yeah.
- I'm a human gun. - Deadly weapon.
- Yeah, like I'm so strong and so vicious
that I can attack anybody for any reason
and probably not go to jail.
- Yeah. - But then when I
am walking down the street and have this neck brace on,
people are saying, "That guy's a pussy.
"That guy's a nerd.
"That guy's a dude." - You know, you could,
no, they think you got hurt.
- You could get like some attachments for it,
like spikes.
That could be cool.
You could get studs on my neck.
Like a spike.
You know, you get spikes.
Spikes.
And then maybe a little tag that
says like, don't fuck with me.
And then also my owner's address.
You know, I think the worst part of
having this neck injury is,
for to me, the worst part of this
neck injury is I
don't even feel human.
I'm just I'm like less than I'm not even I'm as as someone who's disabled right now
I feel like I'm not even a full person for me. It's that soda hurts
When I'd sip when I sip a soda through a straw that's it - soda at all
Because I fucking can't oh yeah
Because it hurts so bad
Yeah, I'm fine
What are you thinking about it does just suck that like I'm thinking
Wow, that's what I'm thinking. That's not true. I think that we're even stronger.
I'm a person with a neck injury and I can say that. You can't tell me not to say that.
You don't have, the jig is up, okay? Right before we started, you
put this neck brace on, and you did as well now that I think about it,
and you're both liars.
I guess because I can't
shake my head to say no. You don't understand how much, how tight
I'd have to have this thing and how much it raises my blood pressure.
It makes me even more mad about every single part of my life.
When somebody gets their cast on their arm sawed off and they grew a bunch of worms onto
their skin in like months or whatever.
Yeah, they grew a bunch of them, yeah.
I think that's going to happen to me when I take this off in two minutes.
Oh yeah, there's going to be a worm.
I did have a guy who had a bunch of black hairs that grew on my neck.
You guys don't even understand the nightmare that I had last night.
What happened?
I had a nightmare that I was wearing my neck brace and then I took it off in the mirror
and my neck was this thin.
(laughing)
'Cause my neck had gotten,
I'd been wearing the neck brace so long
that my neck shrank.
And it really scared me when I woke up.
(laughing)
And that's why I was late.
'Cause I sat there going,
oh my neck is gonna be small.
My head is so, like a baby.
- It could be anything under there.
It really, so you could have gotten something
rolled on there. - You know what you could do
is get a white turtleneck to put under it.
- I thought about the turtleneck thing.
I also thought about getting flesh, like latex flesh.
- Oh, that's pretty funny.
- And just making it look like I have a giant, crazy head.
- Yeah.
The turtleneck is nice,
but you shouldn't put the turtleneck under it,
you should put it over it.
- That's what I was thinking.
- Yeah.
- And it just says puffy.
- Yeah, I was gonna say my neck's swollen
'cause I was gulping.
- On the neck, you're right.
You're right, puffy shit.
- Well, you can say whatever,
but you might wanna say I was goated.
Why not say I was stung by a bee?
Well people aren't gonna believe that about you.
I have hydro-neck-ful-ous.
You just want to say the most simplest thing so it's not...
I gulped a glizzy, you think that's the simplest thing?
People...
Have you ever seen somebody who's a gullible gizzler
who fuckin' has a fuckin' giant neck?
Well I'm just saying it's about you, like
people, if you say like
I got stung by a bee, people are gonna be like
why was he around a bee?
Why did he let the bee land on him?
Why did he...
- How did he get stung, versus if you're like,
I was goaded throatly, I was sipping on some penis,
people will say, oh yeah.
What's funny?
- It's not funny.
- What, I say yeah, what's funny?
It's nothing funny. - First of all,
I'm laughing 'cause of all the medication
that they put me on.
- What are you on?
- I'm on both Vyvanse and
Fentanyl?
Yeah, I'm kind of giggly too. They put me on Vagisil.
They put me on Fentanyl and Vyvanse.
The Vyvanse so I can stay awake at my job.
And then the Fentanyl.
Exactly. They weren't going to give us Vyvanse.
And then we were like, we need to podcast.
Yeah. They were like, oh, right this way.
Yeah.
They took us into like an armory.
It's like a room with red curtains and gold trim.
They had one that is like the Altoids, the double-sided mints.
The one that's for you and then the one to share.
They just pop open the to share.
- They should have that for meds.
That's an incredible idea.
- I agree.
- 'Cause you're supposed, when you get
any kind of stimulant prescription,
you're supposed to share it with your friends.
- Yeah, that's pretty much what happens.
- Yeah.
- Oh, you know what I wanna take?
- What?
- I really wanna get magnetic brain therapy done.
- Yeah.
- That sounds so fucking fun.
But I would be worried that I would have metal in my head
and it would be like--
- I think you do.
Why?
What I would be worried about is if I got magnetic brain therapy and they were putting
the magnet on my head, I'd worry that I would flip and I would become Noramak and I would
be kind of like an evil version of myself.
That's a really good point.
And they wouldn't be able to stop me unless they magneted me.
What if I go under the magnet, right?
And then I start going by Pat, not Patrick.
Kid Trap.
No, just Pat.
I don't think you'd do
They reverse your name. Do you guys believe in ground shrink you'd grab all the other letters. Yeah
By Rick
If you went by Rick, that'd be actually pretty amazing
My uncle my little brother goes by my uncle was named is named Rick
And he gave my brother a brick for Christmas one year and then the next year he gave him a broken baseball
baseball bat. Rick's brick. Those are the two presents he ever gave anyone in my family.
A brick and a broken baseball bat. A brick and a broken baseball bat. Was it from Babe
Ruth? No, it was from him. He broke the bat at his softball league and gave it to my brother.
That's pretty cool. Yeah, he was amazing. I don't think I have anyone named Rick in
my family. Richie, how about Richard? Oh yeah, there's several Richards. My dad is named
Rick. Yeah, I guess you're right. Wait, is that? Yeah, it is. My dad is named Eric and
My little brother is named Eric, but not Eric jr. D. I'll call him Rick and we used to call him
We being chowder would call him little Ricky shut the fuck up the chowder
Can I say something right around a motherfucker tonight? This is kind of a topic change, but can I say something yeah?
I'm ready to go mainstream. You should do a topless change
Did you even hear what I said?
Yes, so I say it again. I'm ready to go mainstream really cuz I'm are you have you lost the fucking plot
And I don't care if you guys come with me or not, but I'm ready to hit the big-time
Ever loving mind mate. I'm ready
Gone mental I haven't gone mental you've gone mental. I'll be mental. Yeah, you've gone mental. Don't call me mental
I don't like it if you call me mental so what you're gonna go mainstream try to get
Try to pick up the beep you're trying to get on the BBC - I want to just set the trend
You're trying to you're trying to attract birds of all sorts. Yeah, I'm ready to take my place in culture
You want to do the Joker dance on the apples and pears me the Joker dance you're gone
He's lost the plot. How are you gonna go mainstream? I?
Think just through the podcast that is daft that is completely bad
Yeah, you were acting I hate to agree with him because he has a fake neck brace on but you're acting completely completely daft
What that what is this bloke on about?
Hurt my chin you did
(laughing)
- I just hurt my chin.
- You just put your chin into your braces.
- You guys called me mental and I bit down on my chin.
I mean I--
- I can do that too.
- You look crazy.
(laughing)
- I can't push my neck that far back
because I'm gonna have an actual injury.
- I look like Cooking with Jack.
- I'm sorry.
(laughing)
- See you just have a toy.
- Yeah.
- You have a toy.
- I like toys though.
Look I can rest my mic here.
I can hold it like this.
- Oh wait.
- Do you think this is what people want?
This is actually what the neck braces were.
They want you making fun of a fucking guy with a lifelong maybe disability?
It's not gonna be lifelong.
This new mic style isn't working.
No, it's not working at all.
This is a terrible, terrible mic.
This is horrible.
You basically, you've ruined the entire podcast.
You just ruined the momentum. I think we were about to hit it mainstream for a final year.
We were about to do the thing.
You know what? I did it on purpose.
That's shit.
What he just did is fucking shit.
- I ruined it on purpose, 'cause you know what?
- Ain't no way Cameron's going mainstream.
- Oh, look at this. - Oh, it's permanently on.
I can't take it off. - No, it's on the other side.
No, sorry, Caleb, it's permanently on.
- Got you.
- Here, do you want me to take yours off?
- No.
- Fuck it, though, I'll take mine off.
- Are you sure?
- No, I can't reach.
I have to spin it around.
- Are we all gonna take them off at the same time?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Okay, three, two, one.
I guess they're off. No, they're not. Leave me alone. I will push through the worst pain
I've ever had in my life to strangle you to death. How are you going to get to my neck?
That's a good point. God damn it. You know who should have warned this? Bart Simpson.
Bart Simpson should have warned this. He would have had a better life. His life would have
Way better. Yeah. Is it worse though to know that your father is so ineffectual that he can't even strangle you?
Your dad is imagine that dude. That's how what you'd feel so bad cuz you're like wow I've neutered my dad
He's not even a man anymore. Is there green or red splotches?
I hate to say this your neck is the size of a noodle. Your neck is completely green
I think there might have been that might have been fake gold
Can I have that because that is a much better neck brace than the one I have
Exposure to air is burning how much did you spend on these?
$1000 how much was it you don't want to know tell me how much they were 70 bucks
each of the both of them were
$30 each of them were 30. Yeah, you spent 60 bucks on these neck braces 30 altogether
Put - oh yeah here when it comes to neck brace put two on
This is gonna protect your neck protect your neck Asher Roth vibe actually feel a little bit better brace put two on
All right, but we didn't just come here today to be
To belittle your friend to belittle our friend. We weren't belittling you we it was a show of solidarity
first off and second off it was
Honestly it does feel better
- I would, second of all, because you didn't get--
- I have a punching cable.
- I have three neck braces on.
- You didn't get that,
that, because you didn't get that neck brace
from the doctor, you just bought it.
We're, in the eyes of the universe, we're basically equal.
- Yeah. - 'Cause we both bought them.
- I guess you're right.
- So, using logic.
- Even if you go to the doctor,
though, you still have to buy it.
- Another fucking logic bomb from Cameron.
- But the doctor isn't, the doctor's different.
- Up top. - Oh.
- So today, before they decided to make my life a living,
- Fucking hell shit.
- No, you did that at the gym.
- You did that at the gym.
- Bitch.
- Whoa.
- Sorry.
- He's gotten hostile.
- I think he's a little too tight on his neck.
- I think my carotid artery is being, yeah.
- Yeah.
- My vagus nerve is being pinched right now.
- I would.
- It's really hurting, it's stopping a flow of chakras.
Do you guys believe in grounding yourself?
- No.
- Where you need to make sure that your electricity
is going into the earth?
- Didn't you know a lady that grounded herself?
I knew a lady who had a, yeah, when I worked at the museum,
I knew a lady who had a, she had a ground wire
that she plugged into the electrical.
- Well, what did it plug, what did she plug it into?
- Her clothes. - Her butt.
- I think that's something in a thousand years
they'll say actually you're right about that.
- I agree.
- 'Cause the whole body, human body's all electrical.
- And she seemed so happy, man.
- Yeah.
- Another logic bomb from Cameron.
- Also, she was a swine.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna keep said so.
- Guys, guys, what night is it, you piece of shit?
- Game night. - Game night.
- It's game night. - Game night.
- Guys, what's better than game night,
except for sex night and food night, I guess?
- Water night. - Movie night.
- I like water night, too.
- Water night is pretty good.
- Movie night. - Vacation night.
- Yeah, vacation. - Debate night.
- Night and-- - Debate night sucks.
- Speaking of movie night, night and day.
- Night at the museum. - Tom Cruise.
Night of the Museum is good.
- Yep, not Night of the Living Dead.
We don't like that. - Night of Too Many Stars,
Comedy Central.
- That was good. - Too Many Cooks.
- Too Many, Night of Too Many Cooks is good.
- Adult Swim. - Cartoon Network.
- Anyway. - Cartoon Neck Work.
- Neck don't work.
- Moving on to the next words.
The, we are playing some games tonight, right?
- Yeah, right.
So you keep talking 'cause I'm gonna shuffle these.
- Okay. - You gotta shuffle
the deck of cards. - We wanna play
our first game first though.
We don't wanna play that game.
- What was our first game? - Parts that we made.
- Oh. - What?
- Oh, we wanna do, I thought we were gonna do that
after this. - No, we're gonna go--
- We can do that, yeah, okay, fuck it.
- Maybe first? - 'Cause I was figuring
'cause the other game that we have,
the third game, feels like it makes sense
to be together with--
- Okay, all right, you're right.
- Am I right? - Yeah.
Let's play our first one.
- Okay. - Guys, what, so--
(laughing)
- In 2000 and something, 2009, 2008 style year,
some complete bloody lunatics had the idea.
They were like, card games are already so fun.
They're already so fucking fun.
- But the problem--
- The problem is there's no cussing in it.
- The problem is they're too humane.
- They're too much for humanity.
What if we made a set of cards that were both black and white
that were completely against all of humanity.
- He wanted to show off his shuffled skills so bad.
- I didn't show it off, I messed up two times in a row.
How's that showing it off?
- Let me see that shuffle you showed me
that one time that was cool as fuck.
- If you ask me, the other, the real cards
against humanity are--
- The one that they do for card tricks?
- Yeah, the cool one you do.
- It's called the Hindu shuffle.
Is that racist?
- Let me see it, is it racist?
- Well, I have to see it first.
- We're against humanity right now.
- Yeah, so we don't care.
- Holy shit, that is the most Hindu thing I've ever seen.
Well not really, I guess I've seen Hindu guys before.
- Yeah, they do that for card tricks.
- Listen, we basically are gonna be playing
Cards Against Humanity today with a little bit
of a custom set of cards, which we're pretty excited about.
So let's go ahead and dole out--
- They're so custom, even the back of the cards are custom.
- Yeah, it says what do you meme on the back of them.
- And that's not 'cause we couldn't find a deck.
of Cards Against Humanity,
which must not be doing very well
if they're no longer in Barnes & Noble,
but what do you meme is?
- That wasn't even in Barnes & Noble,
that was in Walgreens.
- All right, pass a couple of these out.
How many should we do in,
how do you do Cards Against Humanity?
- It's seven.
- Seven? - Seven's too many.
- Five. - No, seven feels like,
okay, five is, yeah.
- Five is a knive for me.
- Five is enough for me.
- Five is knive.
- Did you guys ever play Cards Against Humanity growing up
with your most fucking savage friends?
- I've never played it in my life.
- Really? - I played it with my
fucking mom and dad.
Yeah, so I'm gonna have to play my fucking brother and sister as well and basically my shithead grandma
All right guys, so how this is gonna work is Juvio is gonna give us a prompt right
That's how we decided to do it
Do you be able give us a prompt and then we will answer and whoever has the funniest one or the most raunchy?
Okay, let's go most mother fucked up
Yeah, the most most fucked up believe funny or funnily fucked funnily raunchily fucked up is basically gonna
- Oh man, I'm already seeing these cards
and even just looking at them is making me laugh.
- Yeah, and also when you put your cards out,
face them this way, guys.
- I have six cards.
- Put one back.
Something happened to me when I was counting.
- That's fine, I'll put this one back.
It just says Lizzo.
(laughing)
Okay, all right, here's the first one, guys.
I just made a huge salad,
and the main ingredient is blank.
- Okay, guys.
All right.
- Easy.
- Wait, I actually did have, wait, I miscounted.
- Oh no, wait, wait, wait.
Do you want Lizzo best?
- No, I'll take a different one.
- You cheated.
- All right, wait.
- Also, why is it so transparent now?
That's probably for the best.
- Okay.
All right, guys.
Here we go.
Are we ready to--
- Do we wanna shuffle them?
I guess Jubio has to pick which one is the best.
- Yeah, Jubia, you pick whatever one is the best one, okay?
All right, I'm gonna flip these over one by one.
- Okay.
- Okay, whoops, I'm doing it the wrong way.
All right.
I just made a huge salad, and the main ingredient is
Leslie Knope.
(laughing)
- What the hell?
- The fuck is wrong with that?
- What kind of fucked up salad would that be?
- That'd be crazy.
- That's fucking bizarre.
- Especially a huge salad.
- It'd be funny, though.
- Not a side one?
- I just made a huge salad, and the main ingredient is,
- What's it gonna be?
- The turd I crapped this morning.
Now that's a classic style.
That is a classic style against humanity one.
Okay, I just made a huge salad
and the main ingredient is poo poo and pee pee from a homo.
(laughing)
Okay.
- I like these cards.
- I think that says po poo.
- Po po and pay pay from a homo.
(laughing)
Okay, so those cards, I would say all three of them were definitely,
were certainly against humanity.
Definitely.
But which one is the funniest?
Jubio, do you have an answer for us?
Leslie Nope.
And guys, that was mine.
Wow.
How do we want to mark points?
I guess...
With my fingers.
Okay.
Everybody hold up how many points you have.
Yeah.
So you guys hold up zero.
And then we draw another card now, right?
Okay, Jubio, give us the next, the next prompt, please, while we,
while we look for our next card.
- Oh shit.
- Oh hell no!
- Some of these are motherfucking amazing.
- What the fuck?
- Okay.
- Let's see this next prompt, GBO.
- I would like to play this.
I've never played this before,
but this does seem like the perfect thing
that I could play at a party.
- Yeah.
- It is a bit of a party game.
- But not with normies.
- Any, well yeah.
Basically normies--
- I'd have to play with sick puppies.
- I'd have to play with sick fucks
with sick and fucking twisted people
who are 15 years old or under.
- Well, if you're hanging out at a party
and you're looking around and you're like,
man, there's a lot of broken toys here.
- Yeah. - Right?
- Island of Misfit toys. - Island of Misfit toys.
That's where you get this,
you pull out that black box of amazing cards.
- Yeah, and you say,
I'm gonna blow y'alls mother-loving minds.
- Okay.
The only thing that can stop Joseph Kony's
child militia of Christian fundamentalist terrorists is,
All right, guys.
I knew that one from the get-go.
This is pretty, this one is already, I mean.
Yeah, this one is gonna get a little weird.
All right, okay, you guys ready?
The prompt is already pretty weird.
All right, the only thing that can stop
Joseph Kony's child militia
of Christian fundamentalist terrorists, Pedobear.
Oh! What the heck?
That is not-- I am going,
I'm going home. I can't even handle that.
Wait, what is that? Ew!
Yeah. Wait, what is that?
We're gonna kick this, buddy.
We're getting rid of that one.
- You came back hard to the curb.
- Your mind has not been warped by fucking 4chan.
- The only thing that can stop Joseph Kony's terrorists
is when you're watching Chopped
and the chef decides to make a vinaigrette
with less than a minute left
and it's made from olive oil, lemon, shallot,
balsamic, sherry vinegar, a neutral oil,
honey, salt, and pepper.
Wow.
(laughing)
Okay.
I think that's a prompt.
No, I think that's an answer.
Okay.
The only thing that can stop Joseph Coney's
Child Militia, JubioTV.
Wow.
Wow. Okay. Now before Jubio votes on this,
I did just realize something a little
fucked.
Yeah, we have Pedobear twice.
Oh my god.
But something where my brain went is maybe
Pedobear would be the perfect
thing to fight against children.
Because he'd fucking molest them
Damn and maybe that's just cuz we're playing a game like this that I thought that cuz normally I don't have thoughts
About child armies or militias alright, so Juvio, can you give us an answer?
The the chop one that's the best one
So you have one point Wow alright everybody draw a card draw another card and you'll get our next one up there
I can't wait to see what my car is gonna be oh I think I might puke okay this
prompt is there's there's too many blank in my neighborhood this is like a real
Um, alright guys, are you guys ready for this one?
Yeah, I'm putting mine down.
Alright.
Should...
Somebody else read these ones.
Oh, I have to read, yeah.
If you win, you have to read.
We should be, let's go on a circle.
Let's just go on a circle.
Let's go on a reading circle.
Okay.
I thought mine was good.
Just go ahead and read them.
Okay.
And remember to read the prompt.
There's too many "my anxiety and depression and AIDS in my neighborhood."
Anxiety and depression and AIDS?
Wow.
here. There's too many Adolf Hitler's wickedly evil souls in my neighborhood.
Okay. And this last one, there's too many the fly on Mike Pence heads in my
neighborhood.
All right.
What kind of crazy person wrote all three of these cards in the same
handwriting and color? Who would do that? These are all fucked up.
We're going to give it to this one, I think. The fly on Mike Pence head. Am I
right, Jubio?
Yeah, I agree.
Also, because it's just kind of fucking true.
That was mine.
Really?
And there is too many flies in my neighborhood.
You're a motherfucking expert at this game.
We each got a point, I think.
Wow, expert.
So we can just reset it to zero, zero, zero.
Yeah, yeah.
Because we all got points.
Okay, let's keep going.
Let's get another card here.
Okay, I just pulled my own name.
All right.
You can't say that out loud.
Well, who wrote my name down?
I don't know. Why don't you look at the handwriting?
Cameron, it was Cameron.
Oh, this is a two-parter.
Okay.
Oh, this is a double?
This is a daily double we hit.
Alright.
My blank just died.
Hey, what are you doing?
We're going in a circle, I didn't even get to read any yet.
Okay, then read one.
Chill, I'm waiting for him to finish typing.
This guy fucking loves reading all the time.
You're rushing, and now he put a green on the screen.
You love reading.
I love reading, I didn't get to read it all yet.
Is it done?
My blank just died.
In their will, they left me a blank.
So this is a two-parter.
So we'll do the first blank on top, I guess.
- Okay, all right, I got mine.
- All right, start here.
So this one's on top.
My Dr. Poop just died.
In their will, they left me a T-Pain with no auto-tune.
Damn.
- Damn.
That is crazy.
- That is pretty crazy.
A little weird.
My a penis slash cock just died.
- No.
- In their will, they left me.
When you realize you just watched Kylie Jenner
make a pancake on Snapchat for 15 minutes
and you get a fucking boner.
- Yep.
- Okay, and then the last one here.
My a dozen sperms just died.
- No!
- In their will, they left me, enjoying music.
- Okay.
Man, this game is actually kind of fun.
I'm having a good time right now.
I'm starting to kind of forget that the cameras are on
and the microphone is on.
I'm kind of just playing the game.
I know.
I think maybe it's not that good of an idea.
Who won that round?
Who won that round, Juvio?
The Kylie Jenner one.
That was me.
Oh my god.
Two points.
Respect.
And we're not the type of game night group
who tears each other down over points.
Oh, hell no.
And whenever one of us earns a point, we all get the point.
You know what?
That's the new rule.
So right now we're all at four points.
Or three points or something.
Okay, I'm drawing my two new cards.
Okay.
Yo, yo, yo, I'm yo mom, and I'm fat as blank.
(laughing)
Oh, I think I have a good one here.
Is it okay if I play a political one with you guys?
Yep.
Okay, I'm gonna play a political one.
Okay, I got mine as here as well.
All right, Pat, go ahead.
Yo, yo, yo, I'm yo mom, and I'm as fat as
Vladimir Putin's homosexual proclivities
So that's a holy fuck. That's a little yeah, that's political idea yo yo yo
I'm yo mom, and I'm as fat as Patrick motherfucking Doran
That's cold
He put it down
I'm as fat as Homer giving Marge a blowjob
Homer is pretty fat
Why is all these this weird guy who has this weird hand right? This is all the only cards are getting played
Yeah, I will say Pat
Why did you play because I know that he did the political one and I know I did the Homer one
Why did you call your own self fat in this answer?
so no one else would I
Don't have that card
Once Patrick my fucking
Okay, well, that's why you know sometimes people
They have to reduce usually should parody or stereotype in order to get a laugh damn. That is so sad
Yeah, I'm pretty huh. I'm pretty are you?
Okay, let's do
After this one. Let's get all new cards. We go through the cards a little faster. Yeah, my cards are stinkers. Yeah, I do
I can I show a stinker on camera
Yeah.
Then I know who made it and I kind of want to call them out.
Nobody can see that.
I know, well he put, just put it in the, put the green screen back on. Why'd you take it on?
That is just a Korean word.
It's just in Korean.
What does that say, Patrick?
What does it say?
Tell me what it says.
Why did you use Google Translate?
I think it's for the audience to find out.
I don't think people know you told us what it said. I think is it white slave is that what I know
No, you put white slave and I did not write white slave in Korean. You did that says Stan Jim in
What's that?
One of the ones he wrote down it was a white slave
All right, I hate writing the bus and I take anyone from that one yeah, I hate writing the bus because I keep seeing blank
Okay, okay
This one when you read mine you could it's I know the thing says I hate riding the bus
But you could also substitute. I love riding the bus
Okay, all right, so if you want to substitute it. I hate riding the bus because I keep seeing okay. This is
- No! - That one's an Easter egg.
- Okay, just tell me what that one means,
and then we might give you points for that.
I hate riding the bus because I keep seeing
amazing AF consensual sex.
This says Frog Sullivan, okay.
- And that one you could switch out love
if you wanted to. - You're right.
I hate riding the bus because I keep seeing
the rat bastards who threw soup on the Mona Lisa itself.
- Damn! (laughing)
I think that one wins. - I would not wanna see that
on the bus if I'm being real.
- Yeah, that doesn't sound good.
- If I'm keeping it 100.
- All right, let's get all new cards.
- Okay, all right.
- I actually have some fire cards.
- Yeah, just take as many as you want.
I'm just gonna take a handful from over here.
(laughing)
- I'm pretty excited about the ones I pulled, actually.
Oh my God, I got all the best cards.
- We only have one card left now.
Oh, you fucking did something crazy.
- We'll do that at the end.
- That's not right.
- No, we'll do that at the end.
- Why do you get every card?
I got like seven.
I got this one.
You have way more than seven.
That you can write down whatever you want.
That's a blank.
All right, give us the next one.
Oh, another two-parter.
Can we do a five-parter?
Yeah, just start adding-- just start adding--
No.
--this one.
--just start adding ingredients to it.
If I had to eat it-- here, wait.
You read it, Cam.
If I had to eat a sandwich made with blank and blank,
I'd barf.
Hmm.
Oh, I have a perfect one.
Will we do top down again?
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
This one is like it was made for my-
- Yeah, mine are pretty good as well.
I'm pretty excited about this one.
- All right.
- All right, go ahead.
- I'll start on this end.
If I had to eat a sandwich made with-
If I had to eat a sandwich made with
chocolate that tastes disgusting,
wait, that's not chocolate.
and I have depression y'all, I'd barf.
(laughing)
- That's one of those like quirky meme answers maybe.
Maybe that's from the original game.
- If I had to eat a sandwich made with jizz and a chungus,
(laughing)
I'd barf.
- I would not want to eat a chocolate sandwich.
- Me neither, especially with jizz on it.
- If I had to eat a sandwich made with popo and pee
and jizz from a fucking dinosaur with COVID-19, I'd barf.
- That is the type of deliciously random stuff
that this game is all about.
- God, that is just hauntingly against humanity.
That is just, on the next level of raunchy.
Read that one again.
From a fucking dinosaur with
19 god damn that is next level if I could mix and match here
I would just put a shungus twice me too if I had to eat a sandwich made with a chunk of center chungus
Yeah, what's that make I?
Can't this is perfect for the chocolate one - wow
All right, and then the last card
You let's see. Oh, no, we'll finish all of our cards, and then we'll do the last card. All right
I think that's the move. Okay, give us another one. Yeah, I need some some of my car
You guys took too many cards. No, I didn't you guys both had wanted me to fail
Okay, I know this one for Caleb's birthday on April 17th. Thank you. I'm going to get him blank
Come on guys, what are you gonna get me for my birthday? Wait, I got this
Slamming that one down
Okay, I'm shuffling these up. Mix those up. Alright guys, for Caleb, that's me, for my
birthday on April 17th, I'm going to get Caleb when there's no toilet paper left so you have
to twerk and you're crap on the fucking toilet seat and it makes you jizz. Okay, that's another
- That's a good one.
For Caleb's birthday on April 17th,
I'm going to get him a reciprocating oral sex for hours.
(laughing)
For Caleb's birthday on April 17th,
I'm going to get him doing consensual cum shots.
(laughing)
Yep, those are some raunchy AF fucking bars.
- Here's the problem.
I think they all win again.
Yeah, this is a clear tie, I think.
From reciprocating oral sex for hours,
doing consensual cum shots, I mean, it's all just good, man.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, okay.
So that's another point for all of us.
Okay.
All right.
Pat, you get this one.
Adolf Hitler really liked.
Damn, you guys are really fast.
When you read mine, you're gonna fucking scream.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're gonna scream.
I'm ready to scream, I think.
It's like someone wrote a joke.
It's like the joke was just written all the way through
without randomness involved.
- Adolf Hitler really liked smoking crap with a bad bitch.
- That is some real shit.
- Adolf Hitler really liked--
- The cards are getting harder to pick up.
- Justin Bieber.
(laughing)
Adolf Hitler really liked when you hear someone say moist.
- That's just a real card.
No one even fucking wrote that.
That was printed by the company.
This one wins.
You're giving it to the most-
Woo!
We didn't even fucking make that one!
That's mine!
Yo, what's your problem?
That's my card.
That's bullshit.
The Justin Bieber one deserved to win.
I don't know whose that was!
Okay, wait.
I know this one.
Cameron, you get this one.
Yo, yo, yo.
I'm a thug gangsta and I love blank.
I never thrown a card down that fast.
I don't know.
Maybe I gave Cameron too many of my cards.
Oh no.
Um.
Can I add a word?
Yeah.
I can add a word. I know it's mine so I'll just read.
You'll see.
I think it'll be okay.
Yo yo yo, I'm a thug gangsta.
And I love mumble rap.
Puke emoji.
No.
Yo yo yo, I'm a thug gangsta.
And I love Cameron's man boobs.
- Oh.
- Who wrote that one?
Who put that down?
- Patrick did.
- Do thug gangstas really like that?
- They really like it.
- They might.
- They like when you wear just a lace top
and you're just walking down the street
and the thug gangstas go, "Damn."
- I think you should dress like Ice Spice.
- I'm gonna add a word to mine now.
Yo, yo, yo, I'm a thug gangsta
and I love being a Slytherin.
- Damn. - Whoa.
- Thug gangstas really, truly are
the Slytherin of the streets.
(laughing)
Yeah.
- Basically, the homeless people are the Ravenclaws.
- Yeah.
- The police are the Gryffindor,
the gangsters are the Slytherin.
- And then me walking to school, I'm a Hufflepuff.
- And I'm straight Hufflepuffed out.
- Yeah, I'm Hufflepuffing it up.
- Huffing and puffing.
- Damn.
Okay, all right.
- Slytherin wins.
- Slytherin wins, that's right.
But I'll split my points with you guys.
We can just get a three.
- How many cards do you have?
- Three.
- I have four.
Do you want one?
- How many do you have?
- If you have three, just take,
this will make it equal if you take one from me.
You have three.
He's doing his talk his way through a math problem.
Well, you have three and he has four.
And you had two.
[LAUGHTER]
I thought you had one more.
I don't know why.
Oh, man.
By the way, all of the ones I have right now are Patrick's.
And they're--
Mine too.
[LAUGHTER]
All right, this is a double.
This is good.
You thought I was feeling you?
That blank a blank.
- Oh, oh, oh.
Top, top down again?
- Man, mine don't make any sense.
- Mine make a surprising amount of sense.
- All right, wait, I gotta.
Okay, all right, ready?
- Yeah.
- You thought I was feeling you?
- That's, wait, wait, other way.
- Okay.
- All the other ones are the other way.
- You thought I was feeling you?
That me when I bat the rotten asshole of a roadkill,
When I eat the rotten asshole of a roadkill skunk
and I down it with beer,
a Karen who joined the Taliban.
Wow.
That, that one was good.
- That is against humanity.
- All right.
- That is fo' sho' against humanity.
- You thought I was feeling you?
That horny teacher fucks janitor pegging style
a Caleb's Mangina.
Don't have a Mangina, that's not a very funny card.
That was for humanity, if anything.
OK.
You thought I was feeling you?
That the left shark at the Super Bowl, a Karen with AIDS.
[LAUGHTER]
All right.
Karen with AIDS.
All right, we each have one card left.
Let's just put the cards in.
And then we'll do one last one where
we have to just answer with the single card we have left.
Okay.
- All right, give us a prompt.
- Yeah, give us a, we need two more prompts.
- The best thing to pair with cannabis, dot, dot, dot.
- The best thing to pair with cannabis.
- The best thing to pair with cannabis, y'all.
So we're getting a little illegal on this one.
- Okay.
- I'll mix 'em up.
The best thing to pair with cannabis,
consensually enjoying your partner's body.
(laughing)
- The best thing to, Thiyong, to pair with cannabis,
a fucking Hitler who is Korean, O underscore O.
That has to be the worst thing to pair with cannabis.
- Yeah, that would freak me out.
- I would have a bad trip.
(laughing)
- But is it against humanity?
- I'm a fucking Korean Hitler, dude.
That's ruining, that would ruin a cigarette.
- Is it against humanity, though?
- Yes, yes.
- I hate to admit it, it's completely against humanity.
- The best, Thiyong, to pair with cannabis
When you eat something
That is fucking crazy, okay
Give us one more final final prompt final prompt put it in the middle. Okay. I'm scared. I'm terrified
Oh, actually I know exactly what really
Yeah, is it gonna give us another prompt? Let's see this final prompt. It just need we just need one card make it a really good
I'm really getting fucking nervous to be oh, why don't you we sent them to you? Why don't you copy and paste them?
There was a movie about the Titanic starring blank.
- You guys ready?
- Yeah.
- There was a movie about the Titanic starring as the ship.
- Lizzo.
- Or the iceberg, come on.
- Damn. - Wow, what a game.
- That was amazing, dude.
- That was amazing.
- We really should be professionally doing that, I think.
All right, what's the next game in Game Night?
What's this?
Smart
That's right, we got a fucking copy of wine smart
Episodes about to go sideways guys, and if you're wondering what did Mario Batali say about wine smarts
Well, I'll tell you right now wine smarts is the greatest game ever for wine snobs wine geeks cork dorks and even nascent eno files
Wasn't he in an eno file? No. He was a
Rape a rapist he was a rapist. He's a sexual
misconduct er
Bad guy do you know the difference between a Barbara and a burgundy would you like to read wine list with more confidence?
Well, here's the thinking person's drinking game with lots of interesting and useful wine facts to expand your wine knowledge
It's got a ribbon. It does have a ribbon. That's how you know red ribbon next level
That's how you know this an expensive game work. I think it's just questions and answers. Okay, okay, maybe we can each take
one I
Think I have all the grape questions
Mario Batali did guys all right this one is a wild card ready uh-huh true or false French wine
Regulations require winemakers to age wine in French oak barrels false
Let's say false
Answer false yes, and you have yes Mars while the French require many things specific grape selections refraining from adding acid to the wines
Etc they do not require winemakers to use French oak barrels
I have one. This is the real Cards Against Humanity. This is way better than Cards Against Humanity.
If you buy a California wine with a 2003 vintage, what, and this is for the math heads, what
percent of the grapes must have been harvested that year? A, 51%, B, 68%, C, 95%, or D, 100%?
100%. 51%. Okay. That's my guess.
It's 95%. Dang.
- Dang. - Let's split the difference here.
- Okay, you guys can each have half a point.
- This game's fun.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- But let's just do a couple more cards from it.
- Which of these red grapes is known
for its tannic structured wines
with tastes of chocolate, blackcurrant, and tobacco?
- Merlot.
- Cabernet Sauvignon.
- A, Cabernet. - Merlot, Merlot, Merlot.
- B, Merlot.
C, Grenache.
- It's Merlot all day. - Grenache.
- Just show me-- - Or D, Zinfandel.
- Cab Saff. - Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, that's right. You are like a wine master.
I'm a wine-minded fellow. I'm gonna do one last one.
I think we're running out of cards.
The one thing I want to point out, he worked at a liquor store for like a year.
Not even a year.
Okay guys, which champagne is most likely the driest?
Brut, Cuvier, Demi-Sec, or Extra Dry?
I'm saying Brut.
Just as a...
What are you saying?
Extra Dry.
Mike brute oh my god even when they try to get you it doesn't get him yeah all
right I kind of love one need to but I wish that we had a more of a broader
broader trivia questions wait oh shit we fucking do we do have broader trivia
that's right we kind of prepared some trivia for each other for game night
because I figured we didn't want it we'd had the wine game but we want to do some
other styles of true yeah cuz not we don't know that we're not all about wine
I'm being honest. Okay, who goes first?
Uh, Cameron can go first. No, I'll go third. Get that outta here!
Well then I will go second. So Patrick will go first.
No, I'll go first. Okay, we'll just go round robin here, okay?
Yeah. Alright guys, you have 15 seconds on the clock. Ready?
Okay. What is a lucky Pierre?
A. An average looking man who miraculously gets the hottest guy in the club.
B, the middle man having sex with two other men.
C, a very attractive French man.
- I'm gonna go with B.
- Okay, B. - A, A.
- The answer is...
- Yes.
- B, the middle man having sex with two other men.
That is a lucky Pierre.
- Wow. - Which could be,
I was thinking maybe like,
maybe they look like pieces of bread,
the two white penises. - Well, it's 'cause
of the Eiffel Tower.
- Oh, that makes a lot more sense.
I was thinking it was two beautiful,
long, baguette-style white penises.
- No.
- But I guess you're right.
- Okay, here's my trivia question.
Who made promise?
- What is the answers?
- Who made promise?
Jin, Jungkook, J-Hope, or Jimin?
- Jimin. - I'm gonna say Jimin.
- You are both correct.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
- Good shit.
- Wow, all right, now my trivia question.
What happens to your soul after you die?
A, float up and through an infinitely large door.
B, a searing white light accompanied by unimaginable pain.
C, guided through a labyrinth with a golden thread.
Or D, who can say?
- I'm gonna go B.
- It's actually D, who can say?
We don't actually know what happens to your soul.
- People haven't figured that one out yet.
- Two points for skateboard P.
- Skateboard P got two points.
- All right, what are the points at right now?
- I think it's 10 to 10.
- Okay, it's 10.
All right, here's your next question, guys.
What is frotting?
- Oh, I know this one, I know this one, I know this one.
Don't even read the answers, I know this one.
- Oh, let me read the answers.
A, non-penetrative sex when the penises are rubbed together.
B, tickling a man's testicles.
Or C, having sex in a historic fort or a castle.
- Me and Patrick know this one, and it's A.
- A, no reason, but don't worry about it.
- I've never heard about that before.
Guys, the answer is A, you both get 10 points.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- That's crazy.
I totally was guessing, by the way.
- Yeah, we didn't say I know this one.
(laughing)
What is Anna W, user Anna W from quizzes.com's
mom's favorite color?
(laughing)
Is it pink, purple, brown, or blue?
- Purple, I'm going purple. - Pink.
Cameron gets the point.
- Fuck me, man, I suck at fucking trivia.
- I'm so good at trivia.
Don't worry, you'll catch up on this one.
- Yeah, you'll--
- You're gonna get this one.
- My questions just get easier from here on out.
- Mine get easier, too.
What is consciousness?
A, the symptom of a chemical reaction.
B, a bowl of fluid ladled from a universal over-soul
that is poured back when we die.
C, a spiritual radio signal.
Or D, no one really knows.
- D. - D.
- That's correct.
- Really? - Wow.
- Oh my god. - He actually really knows.
- Okay, guys, what is an otter?
A, a hairy man with a slender physique.
B, a sex toy to be used in the bath.
C, a gay man with lots of pets.
Or D, a water animal.
- D, I'm gonna go A and D.
D, D, D, D, D, D, D, D, D, D.
- It was both A and D, he was right.
He gets double points. - Oh my god.
And I get single points?
- A hairy man with a slender physique.
You don't get a single point.
- What I guess was right.
You said A and D.
- You have to get 'em both.
- You have to get both of them.
- That's a trick question.
- Oh, he's never played trivia before
and realized there's something called a double answer.
- You'll get this one.
- I don't like you.
I'm gonna rip your neck off.
- Don't threaten him right now 'cause you'll get this one.
- How many kids does quizzes.com user Anna W's mom have?
- Zero.
- One, two, three, or four?
- Two.
- I'm gonna say three.
She's a middle child.
- One.
- It is four.
- Four, four.
I said four.
- You said one.
- Well, I was thinking four.
- Well, that's fair.
Give him the points.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- All right, let's hear this next one.
- When I said one, I meant I have one answer.
And this is my last one.
- Okay, I have two more after this.
- Okay, so Cameron, you do yours,
and then you can finish both of yours.
- All right.
And this, like I said, they're getting easier as they go.
What shape is the universe?
A, a vast disc.
B, shapeless and formless, an infinite ocean.
C, a minuscule point in a sea of nothing.
Or D, we don't know, who can say?
- D.
- It's actually a vast disc.
- Wow.
- I've actually figured out that it's a disc.
- Damn.
- So you guys are both wrong.
It's all your points.
(laughing)
- All right.
- Wait, we have a chance to get him back right here.
- You have a chance to get him back, they're my questions.
- He's done, he has zero points.
zero points. But here are my final two trivia questions.
Okay. Okay. I'm ready.
How old is Anna W from quizzes.com's mom?
A 10 B 46 C 47 or D 25.
I'm gonna say 46.
I'll say 47 just so we have difference.
Cameron is right.
Oh my god.
Why would she make the old the oldest one?
- You have the chance to win it back.
I have one more question.
- Okay, I'm set.
I won it back already.
I don't even have to worry.
- Yeah, you do, 'cause if I win this, I beat you.
- If, yeah, if he wins this, I'm gonna beat you either way.
- How many friends does Anna W.
from quizzes.com's mom have?
A, two, B, four, C, one, or D, none of the above?
- None of the above?
That's a horrible thing to throw in there.
- This is pretty scary, 'cause--
Statistically, it has to be none of the above.
'Cause there's so many numbers that aren't covered by that.
- Nerd. - This guy's a nerd.
- I'm gonna say four.
- I'll say none of the above.
- Ooh, Caleb.
Cameron gets the point.
- No!
(laughing)
Ow, my neck!
- Anna W's mom has none of the above friends.
She had maybe five friends or zero.
Or three.
- Or any number.
- Any number that wasn't listed.
- It's all about statistics, Caleb.
- This is me, this is the face I'm making right now.
I'll tell you that right now.
- This is you.
- Yeah, that's me, I'm having a complete heart attack.
I'm also this baby with the beanie.
- This is me.
- And I'm a dog with a thing on.
- This is Patrick.
- Yep, that's me.
- This is also Patrick.
- Holy crap.
- This is Caleb.
- Now we just have all these photos in here.
- This is Caleb as fuck.
This is Caleb.
- Oh, that is me.
- That's our fucking president.
- This is me.
- Yeah, this is fine.
- This is Caleb.
Let's freestyle.
- Oh, this is the most Caleb of all.
(laughing)
- Can we freestyle a couple memes real quick
off these photos just here at the end?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah, let's do--
- When you're a sexy-ass woman sitting there.
- When you're about to fuck Caleb.
- When you're about to go fuck Caleb.
- Get your fucking shit fucking, get your foot out.
- When Patrick wants,
when you're a woman and Patrick wants you.
- Damn, get away from me, you fucking creep.
That's what they say to him.
- Women, when Patrick shows up.
- Yeah, they peace out.
(laughing)
Girlfriend and I shared our one-year anniversary Patrick what Patrick when he hears these memes Patrick when he strikes out with one of the millions
Of women that he tries every women when they see
Women after they go on a date with Patrick
Meanwhile woman about to be fucked by me. Yeah, they're like shit. Let's do this thing, and they don't even take their clothes off
Well, that was incredible, and I didn't know nobody said anything about me with these photos, which was Caleb in his neck brace
No, that's both of these are Caleb
No, this is this is actually me when you're when you're a cat me
When you're not when you're a cat when you're this is when you're a woman that Patrick killed and then taxidermy
Caleb thinking about boners, okay, wait I have
Shut up
Shut up when you're Patrick's girlfriend. That's a big hand. You know her you've met her
Yeah, it's a hand yeah, do you think about what that means damn? He's jacking his show off. We went to medieval times together
All right guys. Thank you for coming to game night
What do we have anything to talk about no? I have a really cool way to end the episode okay?
I don't even know go check out
Go check out the patreon we have a new show on there called beers we drink where beers we drank Leo and Rex talk about beer
there is a
Different photos on there as well that you can see all right tons of photos
Are you ready for me to end the episode in a cool way? Yeah, I'm ready
Wow, what does that actually killed me bye
Bye.
(plastic crinkling)
[typing]
[BLANK_AUDIO]