(music)
That was a bad clap.
That was a terrible clap. There we go.
That was better.
That was a fine clap, it wasn't that big of a deal.
Fine ass clap.
So what did you guys do this weekend?
If you'll allow me to explain my weekend with a Primus song parody.
Go ahead.
(humming)
Too many birthday parties.
- I could do one too.
- Okay, go ahead.
- I had some fun.
(laughing)
You know?
We had some fun.
(laughing)
- That would be my game.
- My game is fun.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I played Hogwarts last year.
(humming)
My game is fun.
(laughing)
- No.
- What, I'm blanking on all the fuckin' Primus songs.
I used to listen to them so much.
I can't even think, like, oh, Tommy the Cat,
Jare was a race car driver.
I can't even think of them as parodies right now.
- I don't even really know,
I don't know Primus as a band all that well,
if I'm completely honest.
When I was like 12 years old, I think I downloaded their entire discography on like
U-Torrent and I don't think that like they're everything they ever put.
I've never met anybody who's like, oh yeah, Primus is my favorite band.
Well, that's because you meet them and they say Primus sucks.
Yeah. And you're like, it's a prank.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I see your T-shirt.
Wait, is that a long greasy hair?
Is that a thing?
Primus sucks.
That's their thing.
That's a joke they do?
You're wearing a pork soda T-shirt.
You're saying that Primus sucks?
Primus sucks.
Motherfucker. You're making me...
Tommy, do you need something?
I'm sorry. I'm just... Sorry. I'm just...
You good?
I'm looking at the numbers. You guys... No, no. You guys keep talking.
Okay. We could just keep doing this.
Yeah, yeah. Let us know. Yeah.
If you have any notes or anything for how we could make anything we do more cost efficient,
just let us know. But in whatever.
Yeah, I'll pop in. It's looking a little crazy, though.
It's looking bad.
I'm looking at some of the receipts, and it's not looking good. I mean,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Yeah, no, no, of course.
No, it's really not a big deal.
Don't worry.
I am looking over everything and it is just, it's a lot.
It's a lot.
Okay.
That's kind of making me worried.
That's fine.
It's a lot.
Do you, have you ever listened to Primus?
No, I don't.
Do you know what that is?
No.
What's the premise?
No, it's about a band called Primus.
Primus.
They had a song in Guitar Hero.
Yeah.
John the Fisherman.
No, I don't know.
I'm sorry, I'm not, I'm just not, I'm focused.
We'll let you go.
- We'll go back to it, yeah, yeah.
- Probably like an accountant version of a Primus song,
what would that be?
- Yeah, okay, let's do it.
- It's one plus one.
That's the only Primus song I know.
- When I grow up, I want to be
a CPA in New York City.
- The John the Fisherman?
- You're a CPA.
- No.
- Yeah, you are.
- Child born acquirer.
- No.
- I was gonna go for addict.
- Nope.
- Admirer.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That is not true.
Well then what are you?
Then what's the A stand for?
There's no, that's not what I am.
Associator.
No.
A liker.
A liker?
Amazing.
Assalamu alaikum.
What?
That's what you got?
Look, I'm not, I'm really worried about our finances right now.
You guys wrote off five charities.
Five charities?
You guys are donating to charities but it's too many.
It's an excessive amount and you can't, I mean you're gonna get audited.
Isn't it good to, first of all, aren't you auditing us right now?
I am auditing you guys, but you can only donate to so, I mean you can't claim that many charities.
You're not gonna get that money back.
But so, okay so here's the thing.
I love charity.
Yeah we just started charity.
So I've always been told it's good to donate to charity.
Okay first off, children with Alzheimer's?
It's good to wash your hands after you use the bathroom.
That's real.
That's important.
Where do you think certain members of the podcast,
why do you think they got on in the first place,
make a wish for that, for four years.
Okay, I mean, you gave all your money
to the Lou Garrett Foundation,
but you just Venmoed a guy named Lou Garrett.
Garretts.
It was Lou Garrett, yes it was Lou Garrett.
You've never--
You Venmoed a guy named Luke Garrett.
So you've never been in this situation
where somebody says, hey, will you Venmo me
for half of that coffee that we split.
And then you go to Venmo them,
and yeah, you type their name in wrong.
And I'm not gonna enter their phone number.
I don't know their phone number.
I'm paying without confirming.
Suck my dick, Venmo.
Hold on, I'm sorry.
- Eight bees.
- Eight bees?
I'm just, Cam, did you do?
- I wasn't me.
Maybe two to three bees at most.
- I think we collectively bought a couple bees.
- Listen, he had three bees, he had four bees, I had a bee.
It's not a big deal, okay?
We're gonna start a honey thing.
They're not that expensive.
We're gonna start like a honey, we're gonna start jarring our own honey.
You donated $10,000 to the plus, an LGBTQ plus.
I wanted to know what that could mean.
I thought it was like a microtransaction.
Do you even know who those guys are?
I thought I had to unlock it.
Wait, wait, are you saying that it's bad to do that?
Well I'm just saying it's just the, $10,000 to just the plus.
Maybe it's somebody with an electric power.
That's what I was thinking when I donated the money.
I thought I was saying I was gonna plus their money.
I was gonna add to their money.
Oh yeah.
I was plussing them.
Well I clicked on the plus
'cause I thought it would kind of expand.
I thought it was like an X.
I thought it was an X,
I thought it was closing the window.
(laughing)
I didn't donate anything.
Get the fuck out of here.
It's not that big of a deal, okay?
I don't know why,
you have a fucking stick up your ass
about this whole money shit.
Well I'm looking,
I'm just crunching the numbers over here
and it's just, I mean like,
what was this year must have been crazy for you guys.
Yes it was.
I mean like, walk me through this year.
I mean, like the finances.
- Okay, where does it start?
Whores. - January.
- Cocaine.
- Oh yeah. - January.
March, April, May, June.
Not February.
- Not yet. - Didn't need that.
- Not February yet.
- Basically, we were doing everything we wanted.
We were living like rock stars.
- So great that you memorized them all.
- Yeah, it was hard, but that was another thing
we spent money on was lessons.
- Tutors. - Tutors for that.
- Month lessons.
- But I think that the reality is,
we knew this was coming, right?
So we lived our entire our whole year our whole tax year, okay, we lived it going. Oh who gives a fuck man exactly
Okay, what's the worst that happens?
Yes, I'm fucking nerd shows up, and he's dripping wet sitting our studio. I don't know what you're talking about okay?
What's this chiropractors without borders chiropractors without borders is the charity that I started?
Okay, so you now are you getting through your thing that we're laundering money?
Ass so those chiropractors are going across seas to go to Mexico City. We made it up so that we could give him money
Yeah for free can I talk to you in private? Yeah?
Guess we take our headphones. Yeah, you can't be saying that
That's why I know that you know that why but you cannot be saying cares about any it
What are they gonna do put us in jail listen if if the boys down at the IRS knew that you said that?
I'm what they do I go to jail. They're nerds. I'm not afraid of nerds if you guys hire still hear everything some Josh
No, oh, well, maybe put them on backwards. Can you put your headphones back? There we go
I'm not scared of the nerds at the IRS. Okay, you know what I'm scared of Slenderman
Yeah, that kind of shit is like actual scary shit where people die. Well, then or I have it in my notes that
Cameron bought a haunted house and you're trying to write that off
He should be. Okay, easy write off. You are not familiar with the tax code. You think you'll be able to write that off?
No, you can write it off. If you buy a house, if you buy a house and you find out it's haunted, you can write it off.
Yeah. Just drinking that wrong. Just drink the water. Just drink it right. Drink it normal. It goes in your mouth.
I'm, I'm, this is, it is not looking good. I'm nervous.
Okay. You're nervous? You're nervous. I'm nervous. You're nervous. Why are you nervous?
Because if the boys find out, because I'm cheating. I'm cheating.
- Are you cooking our books?
Can I talk to all of you guys in private?
- Yes.
- All right, everyone put their headphones around.
- Everybody who's listening, take your headphones off.
- Yeah, turn the episode off right now
and then turn it back on in like two minutes.
- I'm cooking the books.
- You're cooking our books.
- You're cooking the books.
- And dinner, dinner's ready.
Get your supper pot about this, guys.
- You're ringing the dinner bell for us.
- Dinner bell is tolled?
- I just put these books in the microwave
and it took two minutes.
- You have the popcorn setting.
The books are poppin'.
- It's gonna be hot.
So don't overcook them though.
- Don't overcook the books.
- So wait, so when you say cook the books,
are we changing, so like the haunted house thing,
how do we cook that?
What do we do with that?
- That's easy, that's easy.
Native American burial ground.
- Yeah, and if you use it as one of your little bits,
one of your little skits,
as long as it can be included,
is this a comedy podcast?
- Yeah.
- It used to be.
- What is it now?
- It's a lot of stuff like this.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, if you, in your taxes,
you guys are claiming to be a comedy podcast still.
'Cause that's from 2021.
- More drama, radio drama play.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Character based.
- Right.
- Doing skits and sketches and stuff.
- So if it's for, if you can claim that it's a joke,
then I think this is good.
- So what do we do?
So like here.
- So we can just claim every single one of these.
- Yeah, so we need to turn.
- I have that can.
Wait, no, I've got it.
I heard that Caleb bought a gun.
That's true, though.
I know exactly how we get out of all of it, how we write all this stuff off.
All right. All I have to do is say, "So I bought a haunted house recently."
Oh, yeah, OK.
I had the craziest experience.
What happened?
I bought a haunted house.
That should be enough.
Yeah, but I'm a little interested because I haven't heard that much about it.
You bought a haunted house.
What did you... Did you know it was haunted when you bought it?
No, no, I did not.
What?
The realtor didn't say something?
I've seen Nathan for you.
Yeah, I know that they have those ghost realtors now.
I'm actually involved in a huge legal battle, and I don't think I'm actually supposed to
say all that much about...
Okay, well, are you getting sued by a ghost?
I am suing a ghost. I shouldn't say that.
Yeah.
Oh, you're suing a ghost.
We didn't say what ghost.
Yeah, we're not going to say who or how old they are.
It's a child ghost that you're suing?
How long ago from they went or died.
It's Anton Yelchin.
Yeah.
Oh, my bad.
- Hold on, let me make it. - Yeah.
- Yeah, don't write that down. - Don't write it.
- Actually, don't. - People don't like it when we say it.
- I'm writing a reminder to not write it down.
- Imagine being the guy who bought that Jeep.
(laughing)
- The used Jeep.
- Imagine they buy that. - It's a face imprint,
like one of those toys that's all the little needles.
- Imagine you get the wheel cover as a Han Solo
version of Carbonite. (laughing)
Imagine you get a second hand Jeep and you take it to the shop, you get the check engine
light turns on, you take it to the shop, you're like "what's going on?"
They open up the hood and they're like "oh here's your problem, it's full of anti-yelching."
Just ground beads.
That's terrible.
It hit him backwards though.
It hit him backwards so I don't think it would be a hitch.
It went all in.
It's like when a baby poops his pants and goes up his back.
Go to the fucking mechanic. They're like oh, I see what the problem is. Let me just check your trunk. Yep
God damn it. I knew that used car sales. No, he sold me Anton Yeltsin. Well, but depending on how you look at it
Hey, I want to return that you fuck just wait a second. I can sell his bones. Yeah, Adam - so yeah
We're going back to the dealer that sells like the used car dealer that sells you that car and he's like, all right
Alright, alright. I know that I sold you Anton Yelchin's Jeep that killed him, but I have
another. You can trade it in for this 1994 white Bronco.
What do you got there?
Well, transportation, we can write that off.
Yeah, I think so, right?
Yeah, I have it in the email that Patrick wants to write off skateboarding.
Like just the whole process?
How much does it cost?
I thought that was free.
The way that I do it, it's trust me.
Patrick's trying to write off gas too, but he doesn't mean car gas.
He just means the gas he's been farting.
And he wants to write that off as a food cost.
I had cabbage.
That's disgusting.
But he's trying to include it under transportation.
Cabbage and Romesco.
It's like a propellant.
There's a video I saw, I made a cabbage recipe.
And I've just been stinking up a storm in here.
Yeah, but he's trying to write that off.
Include that in the transportation.
Yeah, I it's on the skateboard and it makes him shoot twice as fast with a green. I think I can swing
I think I can swing my back. Let me explain baby. I don't know I put my hands behind my back
I bend over I fart and it shoots me like a rocket down the street mm-hmm. Yeah, and and kids walking by go
Yeah
And then he gets he shows up to work. He says yeah, I got fucking cat called again
Yeah made fun of by Morty some gangsters on the street were yelling at me again today gangsta some gangsters were saying some game
They're saying pyroop
Cuz they're gangsta thugs
But actually he had so I have to write that off hyper foolish you can I think you can I think you can write that
off okay um
Caleb bought a gun I think he can
I think
Okay
I think you're gonna get in trouble if you don't sing along -
Well as long as it's is we're talking about
As in a comedy way, you know if like Caleb went to like a mall and went we I got a gun
I'm crazy if we're filming it and we're filming that yeah, that's a joke. Okay, I'll prank gone wrong
Yeah, but I have a real gun and maybe I accidentally
Pop off a couple let a couple of rounds fly. Uh-huh footlocker, you know, and I accidentally not at a foot
Maybe I actually any other lady footlocker orange Julius stay away from footlocker
if I
Like footlocker, yeah, that's my store you guys can't go in there. Okay, that's where I get my shoes. Okay, how about finish line?
You can how about play it against the way that you're you either way you're asking me makes me think I should say no when I see
Well that's when I see a lane competitor when I see lady footlocker. I just think that's a regular footlocker damn
See you're wasting your time being an accountant. You should be on a comedy podcast with lines like this. I would hate to do that yeah
You know I would really fucking hate to do that. It's probably just would make you kill yourself if that was your job
It's looking really bad
well on your w-2s
You
Cameron you wrote so for total income that you guys have make because you're splitting the income well what the fuck's a w-2
Well you feel I don't know so people can't say
Worcestershire sauce they say that well it's Worcestershire sauce and then another times another Worcestershire sauce
Well, what the fuck, what is a W-2 form?
Well, it's just, I think I don't need to explain this anymore.
Okay.
No, but on your seriously though, if we can get down the brass tacks.
Let's get down the brass tacks.
Which is kind of what I do. You guys, so you're splitting the pot about lists, income.
Three perfect ways.
Three perfect ways. I have it in the books. Caleb, 80%, you 10%.
and another 10% goes to your producer.
You haven't received any, and that's--
- Well, he comes from money, so we figure--
And also, he does the least amount of work.
- Uncle is Mitt Romney.
- Yeah.
- No shit.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- So you might wanna be careful about who you go after,
tax-wise.
- That's actually pretty cool.
- Yeah, so just like watch.
- You know that one of those big-ass photos
where it's him and his 600 kids?
- Yeah.
- He's usually--
- I'm usually taking the picture.
- Yeah.
- They make me take the picture.
And anytime he gets there, he always takes one of himself.
I think every single time, I always set the self-timer and I run to get in and I trip
and I'm always right in the front of it on the ground.
If you zoom in on the Cool Cousins aviator sunglasses, you can see him tripping and falling.
I always remember looking at that picture and finding Waldo in there.
Yeah, well here it is.
If you ask me, they're all Waldos.
So you wrote down on your total income, you just wrote MX plus B equals Y, the slope.
I don't know what that means.
Patrick you just wrote down the color blue. Mm-hmm. My my bank account is out of the red and the black
Making so much. Okay. I think I can work with that Caleb. You just wrote down. Don't worry about it
Also say how do you mother for me? Yeah, I
Kind of thought that was cool that actually it was that actually is fucking dopey. It was cool
Listen, I'm here to clean that all up. Okay, and I know you guys like to make a lot of jokes and stuff
Yeah, well, let's just put our just put our actual income in eight million just each. Yeah, put it in
- 8 mil a piece. - We'll take that.
Yeah, 8 mil a piece, that's nothing.
- Yep. - Okay, let me just swap.
- YouTube ad money. - Yeah.
- That's YouTube ads go crazy.
- And our Spotify streams. - Yeah, Spotify streams.
- For our music careers. - And our new,
we now are officially partnered
with the podcast hosting app, Bloober.
The Bloober by Chup.
- The Bloober, the game company?
- No, it's the app that we made, remember?
- And yeah. - To launder more money.
Oh yeah, one of those.
I thought we were going to call that Money Laundry.
No.
That app.
No, we weren't going to call it Money Laundry,
because that would make it one too obvious too.
Everyone would think it's a damn laundry app.
What about Laundromat?
That'd be sick.
If you guys came up--
That would be a great name for our podcast network.
I grew up with a guy named Laundromat.
Really?
Where are you from?
Are you from Baltimore?
Yep.
Oh, damn.
OK.
I didn't know.
That makes sense, though.
You'd walk around going, what's up?
My name Laundromat.
Laundromat.
- Yeah. - Laundromat.
- His taxes are looking great.
- Yeah.
- We're getting beat by Laundromat?
He's a dentist.
- You still do his taxes?
- Every day.
- Yeah, every day.
(laughing)
You're just making sure every single day that they're fine?
- Yeah, I like what I do.
- You like it.
How did you get into this whole tax game?
I'm curious.
- Well, I was, when I got out of the league.
- Yeah, which league?
- The NBA.
- You were in the NBA?
- Yeah.
play? Sacramento. You were a Sactown King. Yeah, I was a king. Only for like, I was barely
on the team. I think I remember seeing you though. I feel like I watched a game. I maybe
saw you dunking. Coming down the court, Tommy Bayer with a massive slam. Yeah, but even
then I was just like, well they brought me up from the B leagues. The B league? Yeah,
The B League.
In between the G League and the NBA?
Yeah, they brought me up from the B Leagues.
And so I only played for about six months for the Kings.
But it was all right.
Then I was overseas playing in China for a bit.
But yeah, I have a degree in taxes.
So once basketball disappeared.
Was it the pandemic?
It was the pandy?
Well, in the pandemic, we all lost our jobs.
So I got laid off from the MBA.
- Yeah, that's tough.
- So I was like, all right.
And that's why you go to college,
you have a degree to fall back on.
- Right, and it was taxes.
- It was taxes, you know, and I like doing it.
I've always liked doing it.
- Yeah.
- It's just something you do when you're bored.
- Well, when I was a kid.
- Yeah, you used to do taxes for fun.
- I do my taxes when I'm bored.
Look at how many, like I have probably like,
see all that stack right there?
That's probably all of my returns.
- Ball is life, taxes is life, man.
It's always-- - Yeah, it's that simple.
- That's always been the case from the jump.
- 100%.
- But enough about me, man.
We gotta get back to your taxes.
Caleb, it's my understanding that you're getting married?
- Yeah, I'm getting married, yeah.
- You're getting married and you're doing a wedding?
- Yeah, I'm doing a wedding, yeah.
- All right, so this is the big question
everybody asks this, okay?
Are you doing band, DJ, or live podcast?
Do the live podcast, you can write that down.
- Oh my God, okay.
I will be doing a live recording of the Joe Rogan experience at my wedding.
Good choice.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, that's a good choice.
I have not gotten an invite yet, but I'm busy.
Okay.
Okay, so I won't send you one then. That's fine.
Yeah.
Unless you just want it for your fridge.
Yeah, maybe just send it, but I do think I'm busy.
Hey, somebody needs to tell my mom, "Hey, bitch, that wedding was five years ago.
Get that motherfucking thing off your fridge, you dumbass slut."
- No, mom I love you.
- I'll say that to her.
- Yeah, say that again.
- Yeah, Amanda already got married.
- You can say that again.
- And also by the way,
she gained a lot of weight since that photo.
We don't need that on the fridge, it's misleading.
- It's gonna make her sad when she comes over
and they said it. - Yeah, exactly.
She's gonna go, oh man, I used to be so happy
before I married this guy.
And then you're just on the couch and she's crying
and she tells you all those awful things.
- And then guess what, your ice cream's gone.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause that's what women eat when they cry.
- What do you guys think about how divorce rates
keep going up. Yeah. And the birth rate keeps going down. Holy shit.
Are we living in end times? I kind of think we are.
Are we collapsing as a society?
Do you know sperm counts are going down as well? And here's what it is.
Not mine. Mine are going up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up,
except for this VRL young bastard. I just heard sperm counts are going down.
I got scared. Well, not yours. You took your headphones off.
I get scared about that sort of stuff. You get scared about sperm counts?
Well, because you're probably here in sperm count, sperm count, and you're such a mathematical
mind he needs to cool down.
You're such a mathematically minded guy, you're like, "Well, get me in there.
Let me start counting.
One, two, three, four."
I count all those sperms though.
I go to the sperm bank once a week.
I said, "I'd like to make a deposit, please."
And you just shoot one right in her face.
Just the teller.
You're already edging yourself as you walk in.
(laughing)
- You walk in and you go,
"I like to make it a party."
- And sometimes I walk in there with a friend
and I go, "Me and my buddy would like to open up a joint."
(laughing)
- Shoot, one on her leg.
- And me and my friend do that.
- Sometimes I go at like 10 p.m.
I have to go into the little ATM area.
I have to put my card in.
- I hate using the ATM at the sperm bank
'cause they always say like,
Chip read error.
Yeah, I put my cock in there.
The ATM at the sperm bank ate my dick.
Oh no.
I had to get another one, they had to send me another one.
Yo, ATM at the sperm bank, throat goat.
(laughing)
Dude, our tax man's fuckin' unleashed today.
This guy's going crazy.
Are you sure that's not fuckin' vodka or is that water?
I'm so fucked up right now, man.
(laughing)
I'm really fucked up. I actually do have a serious problem.
Yeah? What's your problem?
With alcohol?
I'd love to... hard I trust too fast. Trust too hard I love too fast.
You huff to trust you fast?
I love... that's my problem.
Oh.
Your problem is you huff to trust you fast.
I love too hard and I trust too fast.
Oh, okay. Now I get it. Yeah. And maybe you double dribble too. That's an old habit.
Don't tell me... don't bring it up.
You were ama-- oh, I'm remembering your play style now.
You were an amazing three-point shooter.
You could dunk from the free throw line,
but you pretty much double dribbled every single time
that you played basketball.
What the fuck is this?
You guys hear about these?
Is this a Zen?
Zens?
Lower deckies, upper deckies.
What are you talking about?
I'm getting zenned and zaned out.
Right now, while you're doing our taxes?
You got to get the brain working.
Is this a nicotine?
Nicotine makes your brain move faster.
It's proven.
- Are the Zins good?
- Huh?
- Do they make you like throw up?
- No.
- That's what I would be scared of.
- What are they?
They're all, they're just mint pouches, right?
My little brother was addicted to these things.
- Spearmint, yeah, I got into them a few weeks ago
and they're pretty good.
- Were you smoking before that?
- I guess they have a point system that you can,
you can redeem points on the Zin packets.
- You want some help opening that?
Oh, you got it, okay.
- For stuff, you can get like a Zin T-shirt.
It's just a piece of paper you put in your mouth.
- That is awful.
This is the new thing that people do?
- Yeah, my little brother was hooked on those.
- It's called getting zinned and zaned out, brother.
- Is it good or bad?
Does it make you feel bad or good?
- Makes you feel pretty good.
But it kinda makes you feel bad at the same time.
- Yeah, I mean, you're still,
you're putting something in your mouth.
- All good drugs kinda strike that perfect balance.
Any drug, don't--
- Don't spit on camera.
- No, hey!
- Don't do one of those.
- Watch it.
- I'm trying to watch your taxes.
- Okay, keep watching the thing.
- You guys keep interrupting my flow.
Looked at this receipt yet. What is that for? Give me that? What does that one say it says?
Doesn't say it just says just as for non cash 450
Don't worry about that one. That one's nothing. We didn't buy anything. Okay, wait check read it
You went to NNL 99 cents town
That's we went on vacation. Yeah
We go to different set here.
We stopped at 99 cent town.
You caught a one-way ticket to 99 cent town?
Here's another city we went to.
Guess how much it cost.
Is that where you-- how much?
$100.
$2.
[LAUGHTER]
$2 between the three of us.
Wow.
And then we made a stop over at Dollar City.
[LAUGHTER]
Same night?
Same night, baby.
This must have been the cocaine and hookers.
Yeah, we did all of that.
You went to 99 cent town and got a couple hookers.
Yeah, couple more dollar city and press the look on the button couple 99 cent
Dollar City a little more upscale than 99 cent town. Yeah
What did we buy at Dollar City um perfume wonder who that was
Guilty I love fragrance
Anything else interesting on that one that's seriously messed up that he likes girls
Fragrance as a man. No, it's male fragrances. It's like girls toys
Oh, we have that over there
Like I would like to see that okay you want to talk about you think that we waste money
Do you and I really think we waste money also?
I want to get it on camera too because we can write this off tell me how this it was a waste of money
This is not a waste DIY dollhouse, and it's covered in water
Yeah, a DIY. Why is it so wet?
Wait, how does it don't might be the flooding that's happening right now? How does a dollhouse get a DIY they can't drive drunk?
They can drive drunk these ones
Level right now I feel
It's three milligram nicotine zins
Which is the perfect amount? Okay? Well
Here we need let's we'll get into the list we do have a list today
Yeah, yeah, Tommy's gonna keep working on our taxes, and you know Tommy you can hang around you're welcome to join in clinic
clinic toys police play set
Sounds like some sort of sex some sort of sex thing to me
Police playset now walk now walk me
Here's what I did the police playset I gave that to Patrick for Chris that was given to me on the Christmas episode
Yeah, there's a great write-off this first one here. You think we can write this off
extra sugar-free
You had to get like the extra strength, sugar free extra strength.
I think we can write this off because this is, this is, we can use this for your
jokes. You guys use this for your little skits on stage or something.
Well now, oh, this is how we're making, this is how all of this ends up being, uh,
write off.
This is how you use it all and now you have visual proof that we have made,
we have made comedy out of these purchases.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Like this one here,
$15 for a Santa suit.
(laughing)
- All right, this one I don't even know if I can say
'cause it sounds kind of like a slur.
Someone bought for $10 a Malika blackout curtain.
(laughing)
Will you mind tell me what the hell
is a Malika blackout curtain?
- No idea.
It's as black as Malika is.
(laughing)
I guess a person.
You bought a bunch of cheese.
(laughing)
- This is a stop and shut for a second, please.
- I know I shouldn't be asking these dumb questions
because I am, you know, your--
- That was on Thanksgiving.
- I am your auditor, I'm your IRS agent,
I work for you guys, directly under you guys,
sometimes on top.
And do you guys have a shared company credit card?
- Yeah, we do actually, yeah.
- That's good, that's great.
- McCormick Food Coloring, I wonder what that was for.
- Why do you ask?
- Well, it's just a good way,
it's just good that you guys have a shared credit card,
just makes things easier instead of like you guys purchasing on separate credit
cards and then taking all the receipts if we can just allocate the funds through
the LLC. Oh okay, then it's not then also we don't know who or who bought what.
Yeah. It's kind of like oh yeah. Alright well we'll pull up the list in the
meantime while he keeps looking at the receipts. So this is a website, a blog
spot that I found called the internet is in America. Okay. And it's a blogger by
who goes by the name Jimbo X which I thought was a pretty neat. I look the way
I found this was I was just googling Bloods and Crips blog spot. Wait sorry
what's this receipt that you just found for? For $16 someone on the company card
bought a Yemeni kebab meal. Also it says the cashier's name. Cashier's name, Jay.
That's a company lunch. If we get really audited, is that the kind of question the IRS will ask us?
Two extra harissas?
Yeah, I mean we went on a great day.
Girl, you're going to be farting with all that sauce.
Girl, you're going to be tooting so much I'm going to say, "Was Patrick here?"
Yeah, I think Patrick probably ate it.
Stinky, man.
You stink.
This guy's name is Jimbo X.
For real.
Kind of a cool Malcolm X style thing.
"Greetings, interweb travelers.
My name is Jimbo X, an unusual surname I know.
it's Greenlandic and I'm your kindly proprietor of I-I-I-A. You're probably wondering what
the intent of this site is, so that makes two of us. I suppose it's an info dump for all
the stuff that I find fascinating/irksome about American culture and society." So this
guy's kind of a cultural commentator. I'm a Michael Malish type.
Yeah, yeah, Bill Maher.
So you'll find a nice jumble of high culture snobbery and low culture sleaze here. It's
also a place for me to rant, rave, and ramble about all sorts of things that matter and don't
matter so prepare yourself for some heavy-handed bloviating about politics
and consumption. Bloviating? Well I heard that Sleaze is back too so this is
this is timely. So Jimbo X is right on it. Yeah. Wow. That and lots of stuff about
video games and junk food the things that matter the most obviously. Here's
some examples of some of his articles that he's written over the
years. There's "Why won't black women date white guys?" he wrote in 2017. You gotta go
the league. Well I bet they're all over you right?
Ten homicidal homosexuals. Wow. And what's this one? How do guys really feel about
fat girls? So that's a kind of like, like I said, cultural, no chomsky type. So this one I
think, I think I forgot to take a picture. Oh here's some other things that he wrote.
10 things that are probably worse than being raped. Oh my god. And then...
Jimbo's America. And also he has a brief rundown. Yeah. I'm not gonna really get
into detail with this top 10. I'm giving you a brief rundown. As soon as I tell you what it is,
you're gonna be like, "Oh yeah, yeah." Yeah, and also I don't want to waste your time with the
nitty gritty details.
I didn't take any screenshots of the actual article,
but I did look at it.
And it was all just like very specific scenarios,
like having acid thrown in your face
and your entire face melting off.
(laughing)
So he--
This guy's in the trenches.
He is in the trenches.
So this one is--
What is that thing on the right there?
I don't remember what that's from.
Is that a snowman?
It's some fucked up thing that he made.
Will you click on the thing, Jibriyo?
There we go.
41 Things I Hate About Modern Society.
that was another one that I found. He does a lot of original art for these.
That is a cool piece of original art.
Yeah, go back to that art. Let me see. Pull that up on the screen real quick.
That is beautiful art.
That looks amazing.
That looks really, really cool. But this one today is, I think, 10 signs that a woman is
a sociopath, is what it is.
Whoa.
Yeah, which is pretty cool.
Okay.
Is my clicker working? There it is.
- You bought screw eyes.
- Screw eyes?
- You bought screw eyes for three,
you bought screw eyes five piece.
- I'm not, let me see.
- Take a look at this.
You bought a five piece screw eyes for $3.24.
- What?
- What kind of McDonald's order is that?
- I'm thinking like, oh, like he's giving me screw,
oh yeah, screw eyes, like the things that you put,
yeah, this is, I think this is the,
Safari you put in the wall. Oh, I yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I bought the screw eyes. Okay
Don't worry about the screw. So you needed this to build the studio. I'm assuming. Yeah, we were this is for sure a business expense
Yeah, yeah, we got I thought it was like little wobbly eyes. You guys are ones that come out of the glass
Yeah, honestly, that might be them, you know
Like when you see a pretty girl or a hot guy and you go buying the one
I don't think that's the noise
It's not boing-a-wing-a-wow-wow.
- Boing-a-wow!
- I think it's boing-oing-oing-oing,
not boing-a-wow-wow-wow.
- No, it's boom-a-shake-a-leg-a-wow.
- No, that's not, no, you're doing scrap.
So according to modern research,
a fairer sex is about 40% more likely
to report mental illnesses than men.
In fact, women are actually twice as likely as men
to be diagnosed with severe depression.
And while a nearly equivalent number of men and women
experience bipolar disorder,
studies suggest that the severity of psychotic episodes
is much more violent with women than men.
Yeah, no surprises here, if you ask me.
Trust me, I do their taxes.
Yeah.
You do women's taxes too?
All of them.
What happened?
Every woman or?
Now I--
Every good one.
Oh, okay.
And that's how many?
About three.
(laughing)
Can you go to the next slide?
This is not working.
This is just all a bunch of, yeah,
just jump all around willy nilly.
Over the years, I've probably had maybe
a dozen somewhat close relations with females,
meaning at some point our tongues touch.
- Only a dozen? - Oh Jimbo X, you dog.
- Only a dozen tongue touches? - You fucking dog.
- Their tongues touched without hyperbole, oh nevermind.
- Now get this though, he's got some shit to say
about these bitches.
I can safely say that half of them
either had an already diagnosed mental health disorder
or a clearly undiagnosed one, if not a confluence of them.
The range I've worked with is pretty vast,
running the gamut from girls with milder issues,
depression, mild anxiety, to much more serious conditions,
anorexia, nice by the way, Jimbo, bipolar disorder to oh shit, what the fuck was I thinking, schizophrenia
and opiate addiction, if you can believe it. I cannot believe this guy was involved with
anyone addicted to opioids. I can't believe that JimboX may be not a great judge of character.
We have this saying at the IRS, "Bitches be crazy." Damn, because that's like on the,
like it's next to the stuff on the wall. Yeah, sometimes me and the guys at the IRS, we go
out and have some beers after work and we say that sort of stuff at the bar.
Yeah how loudly do you say it? Very quietly. Very quiet. I do not want my boss
to hear that. She is a woman. Yeah. You guys you say it so quiet you can't
even hear each other. We whisper. You're saying it like...
(laughing)
And I go, don't tell anybody I studied that.
- Penis. - I'm the fault guy.
(laughing)
- To the bartender.
- Do you guys ever play the penis game at the IRS?
When you're at the IRS, do you ever play the penis game?
- Mm-hmm. - Damn.
- We used to do it a lot.
- What happened?
- It was too funny.
(laughing)
- As a guy who has stared down his own demons in the past,
and I'll come back to that in a second,
I don't want to shame anybody for their plights.
That said, at the same time, I think it's only fair that guys out there at least know some
of the less obvious symptoms that a girl may or may not have a few proverbial screws loose.
Below I have listed 10 telltale yet subtle indicators that a girl has severe identity
conflict problems, shopping compulsions, extreme lethargy, paranoid tendencies, delusions of
grandeur, and if absolutely nothing else, an utterly bland, if not unbearably shitty personality.
So he says here he's stared down his own demons in the past, and then so that link goes to
click the next slide please. This is his demon. An addiction to writing. Why do I
write? Because I'm literally addicted to it. That's why. Guilty as charged. I have the
same about taxes. Doing taxes addiction? Yeah. If you go through this guy's
website, he posts about 50 blogs that are all four or five thousand words a month.
Yeah. He really does have an addiction. He's still going through? Like he's still using Blogspot and
everything? I think he must have died in 2018 or something. Oh yeah. First COVID victim.
Sign number one, her Facebook pro- oh no, sorry, he's just in 2018 he stopped doing his
SJW fails of the week that he was doing for a while. So I think something happened to
him. Taken out by the woke mafia. It has to be a wokey that shot him in the head. Sign
number one, her Facebook profile is anything other than a photo of herself. While Facebook
in and of itself, nothing more than a maddening spiral
of vanity and desperate attention seeking.
Holy shit, this guy's smart.
You should probably take it as a major red flag
if your potential romantic partner features anything
other than a mug shot of herself as her profile photograph.
This guy's such a genius, he says photograph
for profile picture.
- Might be a word count thing.
- If I was hanging out with this guy
and he was saying something like that to me at the bar,
I'd go, write that down.
(laughing)
You need to start a blog.
Yeah, someone fucked up really bad.
Write that down.
I told this guy to start a blog.
Oh, this is a long one.
A good rule of thumb here is that the less of her face you actually see, the bat-shit crazier she likely is.
Sorry, do you have a receipt?
So this one makes sense because it was on October 31st.
I know what this one's gonna be. Read it down the line.
Read all of it.
organic broth chicken one Hershey's kiss one Reese's peanut butter cup another
piece of Reese's peanut butter cup another Reese's peanut butter cup three
Hershey's mini subs one Werther's bar one Hershey's kiss another Werther's bar
two more Hershey's kiss three chew it says chew FRT
Chewy fruits?
Yeah Patrick, sounds like Patrick
Sounds like someone got some candy for Patrick's party
Yeah
What's a SB straight light?
Starburst?
Starburst
Starburst light
Starburst starlight
It's not a straight light, like lights
It's not a light, no
for
to write off you're actually gonna want to save these yeah I know $147 you
dropped you dropped a buck 47 86 cents at stop and shop okay it was for the
Halloween live show and we were
Well it doesn't matter if you're using it for the show we can write that off.
Okay.
If it isn't involved in the show in any way.
I will say there is one thing in here that I know for a fact.
Okay we gave that cake out.
The chips on this.
You just ate those?
We kept them.
We just kept them backstage.
I'm so glad it says October 31st because I saw the receipt and I went if this is any
Any other day besides Halloween?
Yeah, we got a couple of fat sows on our hands.
$150 on tickets.
I was like, "Who?"
Like August.
Like, "Who snapped?"
Like, "Who just snapped?"
"Ahh!"
I mean, I'm so upset.
I'm just putting a receipt.
It's so long.
also on the same day you bought a black devil horns 3d beer pint I mean we live
in the third dimension yes it's all gonna be 3d it's like are you gonna put 3d on
everything oh 3d is implied yeah yeah given given the dimension we can dispute
this probably we can we can dispute this they put 3d it's like yeah oh you're
You're just I'm disputing the fuck out of this that cost you 30 bucks
$29.99 that's Brooklyn beer prices. Yeah, you go to Wisconsin get a 3d beer pint costume $2
So yeah
That it's you shouldn't have sex with her because she's crazy
They'll pay you to wear a three-day 3d pie beer costume in Wisconsin what?
Yeah, we should have just gone and gotten I mean how much candy of costume in Wisconsin you think
Well, there's more fat fatties there. Yeah, so they they got a fat tax
You know about the fat tax?
Little bit more expensive not much more, but we're talking maybe
$100 or so. Oh, okay. You know if we're spending up 150 bucks might as well spend
Candy I think we had a pretty similar conversation when we bought all that candy
Yeah, we're gonna spend one dollar
All the money the worst part is I think we gave away every single piece that candy. Yeah. Yeah again more charity
Yeah, we can write that off as that could be well a business expense or charity. I think that's sure
I mean you should have seen these fucking people. Yeah, no they were shows yeah
This is charity
Want candy yeah, dude. He's dead. We should have played that right gave out the candy is that one dead no his older brothers
Here's the thing he's dead
Here's the thing about Halloween Eric Cartman died
No, Kenny died. Here's the thing about Halloween Patrick. There's always gonna be another
It's a good point. Well the world is that another thing you have on the wall?
That's our saying at the IRS there will there will always be another
So hard very quiet because that's like halfway between the tax
Deadlines yeah, basically Halloween yeah, exactly it's very exciting. Yeah, that's amazing. Yeah, you guys should come one year
Oh, I'm not a party the IRS. Yeah party at the IRS. Oh
Number two away a woman is a psychopath she describes herself as quirky been there
Thanks to the overall geekening of American pop culture don't get me started
We're now living in a cultural milieu where traditional Victorian beauty has been
All these women are not wearing corsets and shit. I'm the
Victorian bitch you can't breathe
Instead an entire generation of men have grown up forced to accept a dorkable as the zenith of the female form
complete with all its annoying and irksome fangirlish qualities and
characteristics which in and of themselves are potential symptoms of bipolar disorder
If a girl ever uses terms like quirky or God help you she describes herself as a manic pixie dream girl
That's basically code word for I'm an immature irritating woman child with no redeemable
Personality traits and some schizoid type tendencies to boot my god and on top of that. She's usually chunky and ugly as hell
This guy's this guy's running through every mental illness
He looked up he looked up like every the table of contents of the DSM. Yeah, I see it put all of this
Nobody nobody has ever been like trying to make a point of like yeah and schizoid tendency
Yeah, he's really very corny. Yeah, we do Chanel has schizoid. She does have schizoid tendencies
Yeah, I don't know if you ever seen the movie. Oh bitch came up to me said yeah, I talked to the elf
He's saying to me in the shower
You're going to the hospital things in the shower. He comes in he's singing beautiful song. She says get the fuck out. That's yeah
Yeah, that's good. So first of all hey. Here's a question. How come you're naked looking at this guy. That's sexually inappropriate. Yep
Yeah, he's just not even here. He is human. Why you shower at your showering?
Oh, yeah, he's not a real. He's not an elf. Oh, yeah, you're if one of my girlies told me she was dating an elf
I would have been like girl
You got a real man. That's what you would say to one of you. What do you have a lot of girlfriend your girlfriends?
Yeah, I keep a group about eight women with me really hang out. Yeah, I need you three of their taxes
Well, yeah, three of them are great. Yeah, don't tell the other don't tell the I don't even wanna
They listen to your show.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
Oh, OK.
OK.
Is that why they're not great?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
OK.
Sign number three, she's into anime.
It's a known fact there are only two types of people into anime.
Really dorky, usually sociopathic men
who jerk off to Sailor Moon, and really dorky, sexually
frustrated women with rape fantasies
who dream of being tied up and molested by a robot.
I would say there's three types, because you also
would have Japanese people.
Normal, just Japanese people.
Since you have to have the mentality of a 12-year-old
to sit through any Japanese cartoon for more than a minute
without drool running out of the side of your mouth,
any girl with a profound adulation
for the alleged art form is no doubt someone
you want to steer far, far away from.
Unless, of course, you fantasize about having a 300-pound woman
in a neon pink wig blow you while pretending
to be a Gundam mech or something.
He knows what Gundam mechs are.
Yeah.
- He's doing, he's doing, he's doing,
go play with your Pokemon creatures.
- That's what's so annoying about this whole website
is that he has like such specific references for everything.
And then he said, like he did a review
of the Dark Knight Rises where he was like,
"On my fourth viewing, I realized it was the worst movie
"I've ever seen in theater."
(laughing)
It's like, what are you doing?
- He does the thing where you're complaining about something
and you realize you're getting way too specific
and then you just go, or whatever.
- Yeah, yeah.
- This guy is, every time I complain.
This guy, he's done a deep dive on every disorder,
every psychological disorder besides autism.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He ain't never heard of it.
- He ain't never heard of that.
(laughing)
- Sign number four, she's into cosplaying.
- This is like becoming very apparent
that this is about like an ex-girlfriend.
- Well yeah, he said that he had,
okay, here's what we know about this guy.
- No, it's becoming, he's got a hose.
- He's fucked 12 bitches in his life.
Half of them motherfucking crazy as shit.
- Yeah.
- Right, the other half we don't even know.
- The other half.
- Y'all been there.
- I mean, I've probably done,
I've probably texted one woman in my life
and half of them are fucking crazy.
- Half of her personalities.
- They're fucking crazy bitches.
Sign number four, she's into cosplaying.
The fact that I even have to tell young men today
that this is a warning sign shows you
just how much we've decayed as a society.
All caps now.
She's a grown ass woman dressed up
like a cartoon character in public.
Yeah, I know there's some hot cosplayers out there,
but let's face it, they're usually real models
who don't give a shit about the conventions
and are just there to appeal to the most
mainstreamed fetish subcultures out there and even if she is hot think about this
for a moment. Do you honestly think a girl who runs around half naked in full-body
paint doesn't have some really deep-seated psychological issues she
hasn't worked through yet?
That's true. All those girls that run around like the blue car from Cars.
Who is that blonde bitch?
You remember her?
Zero Suit Samus?
From Baywatch?
No, the blonde girl who...
- No, the first hot cosplayer girl.
What was her name, man?
- Link.
- No, bro.
- Chic.
- Blonde.
- That's a movie.
That's a hair color.
Stop.
- Legally.
- No, that's another movie, man.
Shut up.
- Legally blonde too.
Twice as blonde, twice as fat.
- No, it's not called, no, Princess Peach is,
you're just naming characters now.
- Mrs. Peach.
- I give up.
- Frank Ocean.
- Yes.
Sign number five, she--
- Oh, yeah, don't mean to brag. - His ass, you know his ass not reading.
- He was buying art books. - He was reading them.
- Oh, wait, and I remember, we were at this bookstore, you and me were looking at a Tom of Finland book that they had,
and I was very loudly being like, "Oh, yeah, this is the kind of stuff that I like.
The big balls and the big dicks and there's Tom of Finland."
of stuff that I like. The big balls and the big dicks and they're so... I fucking love
this. Look at this guy's cock and Frank Ocean was four feet from me looking at like some
photography book.
Frank Ocean's just like, "You know I'm bi."
Yeah, true.
So I like what you're saying.
Let me see.
He's like, "Oh, for real? They have big dicks and giant assholes?"
I know someone who knows Frank Ocean and they say in every conversation, he goes, "You know
I'm bi?"
Yeah, I know.
We get it.
he's gonna finally give up on that whole thing? It's like, it's like boy, boy, bye.
Like, yeah, that's like, about the bye, being bye already. Yeah, boy, bye. Boy, bye.
Alright, I got some wild receipts. Oh yeah, give me some, what do you got? Um, well this one is $92.
Anytime it's over 50 bucks, I get really nervous. Well, I can see the logo for Spirit
Halloween on the back of the paper already. Well I well this one I hope is
for Halloween because it's very suspicious and I hope you guys aren't
committing any crimes or doing anything because I mean half gallon of blood?
A half gallon? That's enough that you put that in your car you can drive a
a quarter mile on that. I don't remember if that was for Halloween honestly. No that was
for something else. 20 bucks, blood prices are going up. Biden did. I don't think we
have touched that, no wait we did use that blood. We used the blood on the first video
episode. Yeah you didn't use half a gallon though. That's where we should have gotten
to like a pint. Okay maybe we need to be a little more conservative. Pine of blood!
Yeah that's a good note. A half gallon! You're right. You're a hundred percent right.
Anything else? Two latex arms. Oh they're right there. You want to grab them?
Uno. He's got one latex arm. Dos. Oh god. Yeah. For the Latina listeners, that means one and two latex arms.
This was a waste of money. These we didn't need these.
I think we used them one time.
We'll use them again.
We're using them right now.
Hey.
Oh, wait.
Pleasure to meet you.
That's good.
Pretty good.
Now we've used them.
Now they're used.
Bone.
Wait, I'm not done.
It says bone, 17 inches.
What's this? This is Cameron's cock?
I heard you got a piece, brother.
- Yeah, we bought a bone.
- We bought a bone.
- I'm sorry.
- We had to get the bone.
- 17 inch bone.
- Bone, butcher knife,
Steve, uh, McSteve mask?
- Yes.
- Minecraft Steve mask. - Minecraft Steve mask.
- Minecraft Steve mask.
(laughing)
- Yeah, can I get a McSteve?
- Mark Tender. - What is a McSteve meal?
- Can I get a McSteve, uh, heart?
- We bought a heart.
- $7.99, listen.
- Pretty cheap.
- It's pretty cheap for a heart, but--
- Pretty decent deal.
- That's what you get in this day and age.
Yeah, that's what hearts cost.
You get what you pay for.
And then, um,
and then 25 cent bag.
(laughter)
I'm seeing, I should have carried it out.
I'm seeing a reoccurring problem here.
I definitely should be a little bit more,
I could be a little closer to the
vest with our money.
You should get into totes, man.
I mean, I'm open to, uh,
you're totened.
You're topened.
Open to totes.
Yeah, I mean, I need to just buy...
I just forget to bring them, you know?
When I'm like, "Oh, I have to go to the store.
Fuck, I need it."
I'd give you an IRS tote.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
That'd be kind of sick.
Yeah.
You know, it'd be great if we make something, put it in the car.
The car, the company car.
Bag of totes.
You guys have a company car?
Yeah, you don't want to see it.
Yeah.
The Pal-mobile?
Replica Batmobile.
It's pretty sick.
Dark Knight Rises.
Dark Knight Rises Batmobile.
What's the...
It's this big.
What's the RPG on that?
Tiny.
The RPG yeah, the what it's rotating per gallon. Yeah, what's the what do you get on that pretty high?
Yeah, I don't know I've never heard of RPG I mean that's a bazooka
What do you get on the the VPN on that bad boy VPN vehicles per minute one?
I mean I heard just well. I mean depends on how long I get well
It's that it's a replica Batmobile from Dark Knight Rises, so it can turn into a motorcycle at any moment - so I guess -
At times yeah can go up to two you're a real car guy. Yeah. Yeah, I love talking about this
Ld2s yeah, left her dead - yep, okay
All right. Yeah, I'll just get back to dig. Yeah
You can skip this one. This is a this is just he hates gaming girls
Which you know obviously so this is a good one actually sign number six
She vapes my general rule if she's under the age of 25 and smoke cigarettes. That's fair game
Her prefrontal cortex hasn't developed yet
And she's probably some badass art school rebel with loose sexual moors
To quote one of my old junior college buddies if she'll suck toxic fumes into her lugs on purpose
She'll probably suck on something else, too
I want to see him and his buddies in college like it's like a prequel TV series
That'd be amazing if she's over the age of 25 and still puffs on the camels
That's a sign that she's weak-willed and too fucking stupid to understand what a surgeon general's warning is
Dude, these women, they don't even know what that is.
They think that it's a tattoo on the person
when they look at the picture.
So leave it be, leave it be, leave it be.
That said, no matter a girl's age,
if she vapes, also known as e-smoking.
- Oh yeah, I know it by that name.
- Everybody knows it as e-smoking.
- Yeah, I feel like people say e-smoking more than vape.
- 100%.
It's a 100% guarantee that she ain't worth
a dime, nickel, or penny.
I mean, shit, if she's willing to squander
so much money on a robotic shot of nicotine,
she'll probably spend even more money on even stupider shit
like 3D printing hardware and IKEA furniture.
- Yeah.
- These women in there, IKEA, man.
- Fuck IKEA furniture.
- They walk in there, they say,
"I want this, I want a basket, I want a fork.
How about I fucking kick you?"
- Yeah, how about the meatballs?
- Yeah, exactly.
- How about the food?
- We go, we get lunch, we eat the meatballs,
and then we go. - And we go!
- And we gone.
- Yeah.
We ain't going to the showroom.
- No. - Fuck all that.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Only room I'm going to is the food court.
- That's right.
I'm getting that little green cake, right?
I'm loading that thing up.
Yeah.
Light up meatballs.
All I eat, man, I'm on a strict diet
at the IRS of green cake and meatballs.
(laughing)
You have an Ikea food court in the IRS?
Oh yeah.
You show up, fill up a hard hat with meatballs,
and you're like, I'm out.
We got it built in.
That's amazing.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
Anything good on that receipt?
- Well this one, so this is from a hardware store.
You bought two hammers.
(laughing)
Hammer gray and hammer brown.
- Okay, let me explain.
We had an idea to do a hammer fight.
- Hammer gray, hammer brown.
- I forgot about the hammer fight.
Yeah, we were gonna do a hammer fight.
- We were gonna do a full hammer fight
and I was like, well, if they're the same color,
then people are gonna get confused.
- Yeah.
You don't wanna bring a hammer gray and hammer brown
to a gun fight.
You don't wanna bring a brown hammer to a gray hammer fight.
No.
I'll tell you that much right now.
You'll get beat.
They have different stat points.
Yeah, you'll get beaten with the hammer every time.
10 times out of 10.
So gray hammer, brown hammer,
and how much did we spend on those?
You spent, oh wow, 40 bucks.
40 bucks on hammers.
Two hammers?
Two hammers.
That's pretty good.
What are they, $20 hammers?
I do think of hammers as,
I can't believe I bought a hammer,
I feel like that's a free thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, this really is a man. This was a opening my yeah, you bought some couplings common board
Tempered hard, but you spent 136 bucks
in this trip
Yeah, which is actually a lot of stuff on manager special. So he's in charge
You're gonna want to save that one. That's gonna be a good one to write on. Okay, you're gonna want to get that money back
We're gonna run through the last couple of these real quick
Let's assign number seven. She's really really proud of her tattoos and or piercings. That's disgusting we can skip that one
Sign number eight she makes references to internet memes in real-life conversations guilty. Yes
This is a pretty good unisex you made I funny. I just my face funny account my face when I see this oh
God role face
Impressional people of the sort or something far worse than just boring and annoying oftentimes
They're downright dangerous, and if you click on that link it shows this it's
It's a, well it's not an actual link you fucking moron.
(laughing)
It's the next slide.
It's a girl's charging Slenderman's
stabbing her fitness center.
And I think they were like 13.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So you're saying don't go near these girls
because they're crazy.
- They are, those are, they're really crazy.
- Yeah, they have to be.
And then these next two,
'cause I wanna hear more about these taxes.
She says she's artistic but she can't paint,
sculpt or draw worth shit.
I know hella bitches like that.
- Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
- And then this last one is,
she does that winged thing with her eyeliner.
- Bro.
- What the fuck is that?
- What is it?
What is it?
- Are you a bird?
- No!
- Are you a mime?
- Are you a asshole?
- Yes!
- With a fuckin' ass pube hangin' out?
- And girls who have that,
they always do the thing with guys
with handlebar mustaches.
They always go.
- They do what thing?
- Mm-hmm.
- They curl the end of their eyes?
(laughing)
- They're always doing that, man.
- We know different bitches.
- Yeah, we do a different type of women.
- I'll say that right now.
We hang out with a different type of bitch.
- They're always doing the handlebar mustache thing.
- With their eyes.
They're going, "I'm not gonna hurt you."
- That'd be like, that would hurt.
(laughing)
That would hurt me badly.
- Like, shut up already.
- Yeah, I did, I, yeah.
- I'm trying to drink.
(laughing)
- And then, show, this last slide is just one other thing
that he wrote on here, which is, "Let's face it,
"Kirk Cobain sucks."
(laughing)
And this is a drawing that he made of Kirk Cobain
blowing his head off with what looks like a sniper rifle.
- Yeah, yeah, that's, oh my God.
- That's a FAMAS from Counter-Strike.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Holy shit.
- Yeah, that's a fit, you get the three-bullet burst.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he right-clicked to get the burst.
- Dude, he did, he was,
dude, Kirk Cobain trying to shoot himself
with a Counter-Strike P90
and just shooting above himself on the wall every time.
I have to control the recoil padder.
I have to pull down into the left.
So yeah, that's it from Jimbo X.
So listen, Tommy.
What's the damage?
You've gone through everything.
How much do we owe?
How's it looking?
Stop blowing the receipts away.
Don't try and blow them up either.
Don't spit on Cameron.
We already said don't spit on him.
- I'm keeping spit on, that's not for me.
- It's not looking good.
I was hoping you'd say the opposite.
- Are you gonna crunch the numbers in the calculator there?
- Hold on, give me a second.
Can we, in post, add in some...
- No, I think you sound good doing that.
- Wait, hold on, let me crunch these numbers.
- Yeah.
- No, no, no, no, no, no. - Air, air.
- No!
- Abort, abort. - Don't abort!
- Abortion, abortion. - Don't do an abortion.
- Don't mention that, that's too contentious.
- Abortion, abortion is good.
- No, whoa, what kind of calculator did you buy?
- Pro choice.
- Whoa, this is a fucking New York instruments.
(laughing)
- The old California instruments calculator.
- Talk about a scientific calculator,
son of a damn Christian calculator.
Abortion is good if that's what you want.
I don't know.
I actually don't know.
I actually didn't vote.
That's an odd calculator.
Let me show you.
It's a calculator.
You guys know about two puppy biscuits?
puppy biscuits.
I'm just joking. It's
twelve bucks.
Oh, are you fucking serious?
Yeah. It's all you owe about twelve
bucks.
That's not bad at all.
I think I have twelve bucks.
You have twelve bucks?
Yeah, I can take that and then.
You just like put it in the.
Oh, and a tip and a tip.
Can I Venmo you back?
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
Well, just send it in a check in the
mail in a couple of months.
Wait. Twenty bucks.
Twelve is what you owe. I'll Venmo you
- Family back, so give me a second.
- Yeah.
All right, well he does that.
- Family back, I'll give family back eight bucks.
- Yeah, yeah, that's what I'm saying.
- And accountant Tommy, do you have anything,
do you have any hobbies that you wanna tell people about
or places where people can see you do accounting work?
- See you do live accounting?
- Yeah, if you wanna see more of my accounting work,
you can follow me on Instagram, TommyBeartime,
and Twitter too.
- Where you do tons of accounting shit, yeah?
- Yeah, I think I thought I had some change in here.
(laughing)
- Let me check the bottom pocket.
- Yeah, maybe in there.
- No, I swear I put it in this front pocket.
- You put change in your pocket?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Can you feel it through the jacket?
- Yeah, it's like.
- It's like, what the hell?
(laughing)
I can't get it, I can't reach.
Can you try reaching into my pocket?
- Yeah, let me see.
- Oh, be careful!
Oh, I'm just kidding, man.
(laughing)
Is there anything in there?
- You're gonna pull up a nub, man.
- I don't think there's anything in there.
- Do you feel that in there?
- I don't know, I still kinda feel it, yeah, I don't know.
What pocket is that?
I'm not sure.
What the hell is going on?
I put change in there, man.
I swear to God.
OK.
All right, well, we hope to see you again,
but not till next year, huh?
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
Thanks for coming.
You can say that again.
Thank you for having me.
All right, bye.
Bye.
That was so good.