(upbeat music)
- Whoa, the snap is crazy.
- The snap looked cool though.
- It did look cool, but when it comes to
the technical purpose, it's woefully--
- We should burp out of a bowl.
- I'm not too worried about the technical purpose.
I'm an artist.
- We should burp to sink it.
- What?
- That would be some funny ass bullshit.
but you don't understand how sync works.
- Yeah.
- No, 'cause--
- Bro doesn't know how a sync works,
he never watches anything.
- You burp real loud into it, real close,
like you do like that.
Burp like real close like that.
- But that doesn't help you sync the audio
and the video at all.
You need to have something--
- A visual, maybe like a guy going like (burps)
- Yeah, but at what point in this, so, okay.
I'm gonna do a mind burp and you tell me when I burp, okay?
Ready?
- Yeah.
- So you didn't even know.
- What if for sinking it we used the gentle lapping
of the ocean's waves?
Maybe that could help sink it.
- That would be actually fucking beautiful.
- 'Cause you'd know it goes whoosh.
- True.
(laughing)
- Did you guys--
- I love when the ocean gets sucked up into my butthole
'cause it's so loose.
- No.
- What is wrong with you?
- You are in a rare form today.
- You're in a rare mood.
You kind of feel like, I'm kind of scared of you this morning.
- You're not scared of me.
- You brought-- - I'm a little bit thinking--
- You know what, I took muscle relaxers.
- You also, I don't, I--
(laughing)
- What?
You took a muscle relaxer?
- I took like five.
- What?
- Why?
- Read what the name of them is called.
- You just wanted to chill.
You wanted to chill.
- No, I'm not on muscle relaxers.
- I used to take muscle-- - I was joking around.
- I took muscle relaxers one time and it didn't do anything.
- Yeah, just 'cause you're already so relaxed.
- Yeah. - 'Cause you're a cool breeze.
- The ultimate chiller.
- How can such a chiller get any more chill, man?
- You're the one who looks chill today.
- Yeah, I know.
- This is like we all look too chill.
- You look like you're chilling in a pile of dog hair.
Come on.
- You look like one of those LA guys
that rides like a Vespa.
- You look really scary when you do that.
Oh my God.
- You look like the Joker.
- No, I don't.
The Joker looks like this.
- 'Cause he's all around us,
'cause he could be any one of us.
- Oh my God. - That's true.
- 'Cause he's just got makeup on.
- That's true.
- But it's actually his skin.
- His white skin. - He fell to a big vat
of green goo. - Literally the whitest guy ever.
- You will never see a black joker on a movie.
Steve Harvey, one.
- What movie? - Bernie Mac, two.
- What movie?
- Cedric the Entertainer.
- Those are comedians. - The kings of comedy.
- Those are not jokers. - They're all black jokers.
- In what world are they jokers?
- They're telling jokes.
- But they're not going up there going,
hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee.
- You don't know that.
There's definitely, look at Steve Harvey laugh.
- That is not how Steve Harvey laughs.
- I like how Harvey laughs.
- Steve Harvey does not go, "Oo-ee-ee-ee-ow-ow!"
- No, he doesn't.
- He may have done that once or twice,
but he doesn't say Batman.
- He doesn't?
- Look right there, there's already...
- Oh yeah, I guess he does.
Alright, I don't think he...
Oh man, he did dress just like that.
- Oh my gosh, that is the Joker's suit.
I didn't even consider that.
- But I mean, you just, it's...
- That is one of the most beautiful suits,
this is one of the most beautiful outfits
I've ever seen in my entire life.
- If they did a black Joker,
I mean, people would be,
it would destroy, the world would be over.
- Yeah, and why? - People would be protesting.
It'd be like--
- Oh, I was thinking about this.
- Yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause I don't know, you guys probably saw,
they're filming the second Joker movie.
- With Lady Gégea.
- Yeah, and Patrick's been shopping at Target recently.
You are Therese Rouchet.
- I am.
(laughing)
- But wouldn't it be funny,
'cause they already, they completely blew their load
with saying they're gonna kill people
in the first Joker movie.
- Yeah, you're right.
- And they're not gonna say it for the second one.
So if I was an evil guy--
- Nah, we won't even go there.
Nah, we on YouTube now.
- Oh yeah.
So I'll feel completely safe--
- What would you do, but I would write a movie
about how a guy would--
- It just seems like that's,
I'm not gonna see it in theaters.
- What would you do if it took place in Canada?
- Candyland, right?
- What?
- Just think about that.
- You are...
- What would you...
- Bzzzt!
- What would you do if what took place in Candyland?
- Like an imaginary world.
- If what?
- If an imaginary world took place in Candyland?
- You can describe it if it's happening
in an imaginary world, is what I'm trying to say.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, if it happened...
- Well, okay, if the Joker 2 premiere happened in Candyland,
I would not be in Candyland.
- Yeah.
- That's the, yeah.
- Somebody be loading candy corn in a nine millimeter clip.
You think that the second Joker movie is the one that's gonna have the shooting?
I'm saying that's when they let their guard down.
I will just say that's the point.
Think about it, which world war had Hitler in it?
Oh my fucking god.
Both of them.
(laughter)
He was also...
That's crazy!
He was a round butt.
It's like when you see the Joker in the Batman.
In that cell.
Yep.
You're right.
- I mean, the Riddler he wants to sell me.
- And also Hitler.
- Yeah, he sees Hitler from behind.
- Who do they get to play Hitler?
Oh my God.
- Isn't Hitler in the Captain America movie?
Didn't they play Hitler in that?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Because Hitler is like completely replaced
by Red Skull in the movies, I think.
- So Red Skull is Hitler.
I can't remember, he might, he may be.
- Red Skull's a red skull,
and he has a swastika still on his skull somehow.
Like right in the middle of his forehead.
- He has a swastika on his skull?
- Yeah, some designs.
- Well, it's also a mask, isn't it?
- Yeah, no.
- In the movie, I'm pretty sure it's a mask.
- No, you got a red, no, his normal face is a mask,
and the red skull is his face.
- Oh, that's what I'm thinking of.
It's been a long time.
- It's been a long time since that came out.
- Since World War II.
(laughing)
I've forgotten pretty much everything about it.
- You know what fucked me up?
- It's pretty tough.
- I saw the thing that said that that King Krule album,
"Six Feet Beneath the Moon" came out 10 years ago.
- I always thought that King Krule was a
- I didn't even toothpick who I should kill.
I never have, I never cared about him.
And I've cared about a lot of really stupid shit,
so this is not me being like, I'm a cool guy.
But I saw that and I felt,
I saw that thing you were talking about where it said,
this King Krule album came out however long ago,
I felt nothing. - 10 years.
- I felt nothing.
- You didn't feel a thing?
- I didn't even read it.
- Oh man. - Or look at the video.
I didn't even care 'cause I'm so cool.
- Yeah, that is really cool.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Meanwhile, I find out some Magic the Gathering set
came out 10 years ago.
- I found the floor solid.
- Or you find out somebody makes a thing
that you came out 25 years ago.
You go, what the fuck?
- When your mom posts a photo.
- I don't even remember that.
- Yeah.
- Your mom posts a collage and it's a pic.
It's like, got a fucking picture of the collage
from the year before 'cause my mom does it.
- For sure.
- Have you seen those?
- Oh yeah, the collages?
- Yeah, the collages my mom makes for my birthday
where she puts the fucking other collages
from the year before into the collage.
So there's like 49 pictures.
- Collage-ception.
- Collage-otopia.
It's kind of a gold ratio.
- Oh yeah, so let's talk stack-otopia.
- Yep.
- Or stack-topia, 'cause I, we,
for those who haven't seen stack-topia,
it was chips that were stacked.
- Yeah.
- And it was very, it was very funny to see this video again
'cause I totally forgot about it
'cause it was from a while ago.
- Oh, it's right there.
It's the first result.
- There's something to clarify.
- I wanted to clarify something here
'cause I remembered exactly how this happened
and it was making me laugh really hard.
So this is Stacktopia, if you haven't seen Stacktopia.
And if I remember correctly,
the way that Stacktopia came about
is I picked up this chip and I was like,
whoa, look at this.
And Caleb said, wow, it looks like Spanakopita.
And Patrick said, oh yeah, Stacktopia.
(laughing)
Patrick thought that Caleb said Stacktopia.
And was like, oh, yeah.
Yeah, by the way, people think
that we maybe stacked those chips.
No, no, they came out of the firelight.
And all of these photos are,
because I was trying to upload them to a 3D modeling app
because I wanted to make a 3D model of Stacktopia.
- And it didn't work out.
So now that you understand Stacktopia,
now you will go back and you'll be watching it
with an entire, and now it can go completely viral.
- Yeah.
- We posted this.
- Post the story behind Stacktopia.
- This happened probably.
- Look at that, did you see that hold?
- This happened probably four months ago.
- Yeah, a long time ago.
- Yeah, and so this is, but now is the time.
- And I texted you guys, I texted you guys--
- The world's finally ready.
- Three days ago, and I said,
do you guys remember Stacktopia?
and then you said no, and then I sent you this video
that I made.
- I thought you were talking about Pop Tropica first.
- No, I was talking about Stacktopia.
- It took me a minute to remember what Stacktopia was,
'cause I was like, that sounds so familiar, Stacktopia.
- And I found like 30 pictures of it.
(laughing)
- Of just a bunch of chips.
- It is Stacktopia.
- Dude, imagine that's an island.
What would you call it?
Literally nothing else you can call it.
- Chip island?
- Yeah, I think I'd be more, it would be more crazy.
- It would be stacked-topia. - Crazy.
- No, no, no, no. - No, it would be chips,
'cause there's no reason, if that was an island,
why would I be like, oh yeah,
it's chips stacked on top of each other?
The amazing thing is that there's an island
that looks like chips. - Yeah.
- Not that it looks like chips stacked.
- And you would still call it,
you guys are getting hung up on this.
- I would call it chip-ville.
- No, you would call it stacked-topia.
- If I was small and I lived on chip,
if I lived on chips already. - Yeah.
- I would call it-- - And then I saw,
if I usually lived on one chip--
- And then I saw that, maybe I would say--
- Maybe I would say, oh, Stactopia.
- Especially if it was like, either way,
there's a universe where you would call it,
- If I saw like a bus--
- There's only a universe that exists
where you will call it Stactopia.
- Well, I call it Stactopia in this universe,
but I don't call it Stactopia in the universe
where it's an island.
- Where there's already a Stactopia.
- No, in the universe I live on a chip.
- Oh, okay.
- Which that, you get to harvest salt.
- That could be a movie.
- Yeah.
- Chip, Chipman.
- Just a guy, just a different alternate.
- That could be even bigger than Star Wars.
A world where everybody lives on a chip.
- His name could be Chip,
and it could be called Chip on the Chip.
- That sucks.
- That's stupid.
- Yeah, that's more of a TV show now.
- Hear him out.
- That's more of a TV--
- I already heard him out.
This is only part of his idea.
- Well, that would be the TV show
that comes out after the movie.
- Or maybe, yeah, that comes out of the--
- Like out of Jimmy's head.
- Chip the Animated Series.
Well, Chips is already...
- You could call it--
- That's a cop show, though, right?
- Chips is already a thing.
- I never saw that.
- Me neither, but I just know the name.
- I know Eric Rada is in it.
- See, but I click on that show and I go,
(imitates clicking)
- Yeah, then there's no chips.
- And I go, "Ah, I thought this was about a guy
"who lives on a chip and he sees chips stacked
"and they call him Stacktopia."
- I thought this was a guy who lived on a giant chip
and when he got hungry he just reached down
and ate the ground.
But no, it's about two cops.
- It would be so hard to eat the ground
if you lived on a chip.
- Who are probably fucking racist.
- You'd have to have a jackhammer.
- It's a Stacktopia, and it's an island in a sea of salsa.
- I'd like to get you stuck between the stacks.
- The salsa C?
- The salsa C.
- Chip in the salsa C?
- Uh huh.
- I'd like to see him get stuck in the stacks
like 127 hours, have to saw his own legs off.
- I would eat my way out.
- Yeah, and it would be called four chips.
- Yeah.
- Instead of 127 hours.
- Four chips stacked on top of each other.
And I'm stuck between them in parentheses.
- And I'm small.
- And I got little.
- That's how I get stuck in the chips.
- By the way, I'm small.
- That's a perfect subtitle for a movie.
By the way, I'm small.
(laughing)
- The chip on the poster.
- The Chip's Adventure, by the way I'm small.
- 'Cause you walk up to that and it says
Chip's Adventure, you're like, oh it's a guy,
his name is Chip or something.
- It's about cars or something.
- It's a spin off of Chips.
- And then you get, it says, by the way I'm small,
you go, he's stuck in a chip.
(laughing)
Okay, all right.
I gotta know, he's in the chip.
- This is, not to get back to downsizing,
but this is what it should have been.
- Downsizing.
- If it had a subtitle, by the way they're small.
- If I directed Downsizing, you don't understand
fucking amazing that movie would be right because it would be because you're
watching what are you watching you're watching I'm wanting I shrunk the kids
and you're saying wait why is this a bad thing their lives just got awesome
because they can see things in a bigger new perspective right huh but the only
problem is they're stuck in this boring all front lawn and the house fuck yeah
you're going to the mall yeah you're going to the miniature really walk a
candy factory you're going to the toy store you're gonna go to the toy store
- Oh, you're fighting the toy.
- If I directed that movie, they would just go to a town
that was really small and it was exactly the same.
- Exactly.
- Isn't that what they do in that movie?
- I don't know. - No.
- They get moved into like little condos.
Did you see, did you see Downsizing?
- No, Downsizing that--
- We're talking about Honey Shrunk.
- Downsizing they went to--
- Honey Shrunk.
- Downsizing they went to a small--
- Honey Shrunk, I'm an oat.
- Do you know what I realized?
The Downsizing--
- Honey Shrunk, I'm an oat.
- You know what I would do though?
I would go-- - By the way, I'm a small--
- And by the way, I'm as small as an oat.
No.
(laughing)
- I live on a chip and I'm as small as an oat.
Texting someone you met at a party,
be like, "Hey man, it was nice to meet you.
"I'm gonna hang out sometime."
By the way, I live on a chip and I'm as small as an oat.
(laughing)
- Something happened on the way to a party.
- Hey man, can you come help me out?
Hey, I need, just a text, I need a favor.
Five texts later, I live on a chip, I'm as small as an oat.
I don't have time to explain how it happened, but I'm oh my god. I live on a chip. I'm a small
Salsa see a smart like the smartphone thing where it's like the I screen shot from like 2011
Yeah, it's like it's I live on a chip and then the person says what and I'm as small as
And then they're like, wait, what do you mean? He's like, oh my god. I'm sorry. I live on a ship and I'm as small as a
a cat. Oh my God, fucking auto correct. Yeah, I live on a ship and I'm a sailor on a boat.
Can you imagine how long if you're texting somebody that small, how long those three
dots would just be sitting up as they jump from letter to letter and just try to heat
up their hand hot enough that it registers on the touch screen? Oh my God. I guess you
would have to put spaces in between each dot. Yeah, well you would send, you would jump on
the, you would jump on the dictation, the dictation button and then it would say it in really
small letters because your voice is so high pitched. Or you have to get right up in there and go
"I live on a chip and I'm as small as an oat! Period."
Because you gotta have a good voice.
And all that just to communicate what you are. Not even "and I'm hungry."
And not how you feel.
"And I'm not feeling very good today! Period."
"I need crumbs!"
Shrug emoji!
No, shrug!
I live on a chip.
Shrug!
Not hug!
I live on a chip.
I'm as small as an oat.
Small as an oat is the innovation.
Here's what I would do.
That's beautiful.
If I made a movie like Downsizing, this would be the concept, okay?
It's a guy, and we never get any backstory for why he's small, but he's a guy who lives
in our world and has to live as close to a normal life as possible while being as small
as an oat.
Yeah.
job. They don't give him... There's no sorts of...
It's like Flat Stanley.
Yeah, but it's kind of like... It would be, I guess...
Oat Manly.
It would be, I guess, some sort of comment on how we don't have any... How there's not a lot of accessibility.
Because it would take him probably a couple of years to get to work every day.
Yeah.
Or every year.
Unless he rode a paper airplane.
But even... I mean, how fast does a paper airplane go?
Four miles an hour?
Depends. Depends on the wind.
To an oat.
In the city.
To an oat, it's a bullet train.
Yeah.
- It's still there, it's the same speed.
- If you were as small as an oat--
- But two and it's relative.
- If you were as small as an oat though--
- You know what I think about Einsteinian discoveries?
- That's true.
- If you were as small as an oat,
why would you leave work at all?
You can just build a perfect home in your filing cabinet.
- Okay, what I will say,
so we're talking about accessibility and stuff.
If you're as small as an oat
and you're not on some type of welfare,
I think our government has failed.
- That's true.
- This guy who's the size of an oat
and lives on a chip should not have to work.
- We don't fucking pay.
We don't pay these fucking oat people.
That would be the whole thing.
We don't pay fucking oat people.
These fucking oat-sized welfare queens sitting around collecting grains.
He's going to Angkor to try and get housing, but yeah, he's trying to live in a real fucking
acorn.
Yeah, that's right.
Well yeah, that's what, to a guy the size of an oat, a chip is a mansion.
They're like, these guys the size of oats are living in chips.
The governments are giving them money to live in chips.
They should be living inside of a peanut shell.
- Let's be real.
- That's how cruel the Tories are.
- If you're not gonna work, put 'em in a--
- Let's be real, the chip is more like a yacht
'cause it's going in the Salsa Sea.
- Yeah.
- The Salsa Sea.
- His house is probably like an acorn or a can.
Or like some kind of, maybe he's hollowed out a soda can.
- Elon Musk of oat people lives in a can.
- No way.
- Yeah, he lives in a can, but then all these other people
are living in acorns or rocks.
- He drives an electric ant.
- I would live, that doesn't make any sense.
- It's like an electric car.
- I'm not gonna do that, I'm not gonna go with that.
An electric ant?
- That makes sense.
- Design an electric ant right in front of me.
- Do you have paper?
- No.
- We have MS paint and we can describe it to Jubio.
- Just describe to me what an electric ant is right now.
How would that work?
- It's an ant with a AAA battery taped to it.
- I don't already, most things move from electricity.
- Why did you open Excel?
- Isn't that what muscles are?
its electrical impulses, right?
- So that's not gonna work for me.
- Normal ant is not.
- That's not gonna work for me.
- Okay, it's an ant.
- That's right, I forgot I was explaining
something to a second grader.
- I don't look like a second grader.
- It's an ant with a nine volt battery.
- You do look like a second grader.
He's like, "Dad, look, I dressed up."
- I look like an artist.
And you're basically jealous.
- You do look like a finger paint artist.
- Can I tell you--
- Macaroni artist ass.
- You guys are jealous because
I've had a long and amazing career.
- Yeah.
- I've had a long and amazing,
legendary, famous singer career.
and I'm uh...
*laughs*
Hey!
I think I look good, I think that this is the uniform
You guys are pretty underdressed for what we're doing today by the way
No, I'm dressed up like a music producer
because I made my shirt
I made my shirt dark
So Cam, what's your fucking excuse you piece of shit?
You look terrible. He's wearing a music shirt
What are you talking about?
Clearly somebody has never
looked at a picture of a band or producer
Have you ever heard of Rick Rubin?
Who the hell's Rick Rubin?
You think this guy dresses in a suit?
You think this guy wears sunglasses?
I don't think Rick Rubin fits him.
What's this guy, a mascot?
He dresses like a homeless watermelon.
I've actually seen Rick Rubin.
He looks terrible.
He doesn't look good.
All right, good music comes from people
who don't care enough about the world
to dress up and let other people like them
with the way they look. That is Santa.
No, that's Rick Rubin.
Look at this guy.
You think that this is the standard
that I'm living up to here,
and I would argue that I have gone above and beyond,
and he is the number one music producer on the universe.
- That is Santa Claus and you are lying to me.
- That's Baba Ram Dass.
- That is Radagast from the Hobbit movies.
- Well, but anyway.
- We're looking at music today.
- What we're doing today is we're gonna have
a little bit of a competition, okay?
We have some people.
- We have handpicked some celebrity stars of tomorrow.
- We have people live in the audience.
And a little bit, can we just talk about
each of our individual music careers really quickly?
So me, I'm a triple platinum gold artist
who has basically changed many different genres of music
and I've also invented my own instruments.
So that's pretty impressive.
- Wow, which instruments?
- You ever do the thing where you take a comb
and you put the piece of paper on top of it?
- Yeah.
- I completely invented that.
- Oh, that's great.
- My musicals thing is that for a long time
I had my own independent record label
and I signed bands called like--
business side of the thing.
Ass, fucker, shit, brain.
This was in the 90s.
And gargantuan penal rocket and stuff like that.
But then I signed a little act called One Direction.
You signed 1D.
Wow, I didn't even know that about you.
To my record label, which was called Motherfucka Records.
And then I became rich and changed my outfit and got rid of all my tattoos.
Wow, that's pretty cool.
For me, not that I really have to explain it to anyone listening, but I was a global superstar
for as many as 25, 27, 28 years before I kind of hung it up to be a TV star.
But back in my music career, I was working on the singing shit, but I was also kind of
a dancer and I was waffling in between the two, never really figuring out.
Also a medical doctor and a graphic designer for some years, which I did a lot of the album
covers on my own.
You worked on websites too?
Personal websites for people?
websites, yep, HTML, PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, all this type of shit. And also I was able
using graphic design to make my skin appear green on a lot of my albums. And I made a
genre called alien rock.
Holy shit, really? That was you?
Yep.
So obviously we're very...
Cameron Fetter music.
I think that there's almost...
Follow Cameron Fetter music.
There's almost nobody...
Follow Patrick Gordon music and Kayla Pitts music on Instagram. We're trying to get our
followers up so that we can get...
And there's a picture of the instrument I played on my Alien Rock albums.
They're trying to get our follows up so that people will take us serious in the music industry.
They do take us seriously.
We don't talk about it enough, but we used to be big ass stars before we did podcasting.
There's a step down.
There's almost nobody more qualified.
I don't want to do this.
Me neither.
Of course, these microphones.
I don't want these microphones.
I want these microphones on the side of my face and I'm going, "I want something just
like this.
Ooh, ooh."
That was me.
I wrote that song and we actually I just remember a song called. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
So if you've heard that
All this was through sensitive gangster records our IP we lost the LLC after we got it bought out by T-Mobile
Mmm, listen, there's which I want to say
They have been sponsoring my windscreen this whole time. Oh, yeah nice T-Mobile
It's clear that there's nobody more
Ready to judge people that I like music industry. Nobody has a better resume than us
So so we put together a little bit of a competition
Okay, yeah, and some if not all of these people if not one of these people is gonna get a record deal
Uh-huh sent to Hollywood personal trip to our apartment a personal massage from all three of us
Uh-huh a sandwich and we get to watch them in the jacuzzi. Yes, because it's a one-person
- It's a jacuzzi tub.
- It's a jacuzzi that we bought and we did not know
didn't fit in any of our apartments
and we had to put it in the office.
- And some of our bacterias and gut flora in a jar, or vial.
- Our first contestant, this is James Lang.
He's coming to us from, looks like somewhere
in Southern California, James Lang.
You wanna introduce yourself, James?
- Hey, Bella.
So I don't know if you remember this,
But a couple of months ago, you liked my status.
That's a like my status and I'll sing you a cover.
Okay.
I know it's long overdue, but here I am.
Interesting.
Real sob story with this guy right now.
So I'm going to attempt to do a cover of "Fact" by Eminem.
Oh, interesting.
I'm excited to hear that.
Probably do something else because,
I mean, if you know the song "Fact,"
it's pretty fucking bad, but.
Okay, well, I don't know why you picked that
for the competition then, James.
I can't really rap but let's see how it goes.
Alright let's see.
I feel like he's going to blow my mind.
He has to right?
James you there?
Alright James whenever you're ready.
Whenever you're ready go ahead.
Fag.
You want to try again?
I never seen no shit like this, this bitch can twist like a damn contortionist.
Con-am-er-a-dick of course it is, this bitch don't know what abortion is so I can't come
in it.
*Rapping*
Wow
James, incredible.
Wow.
Oh my goodness.
James, that's enough James.
James, that was...
James, thank you.
That was incredible, I think.
Oh wow, oh wow.
No more James.
James, you did enough buddy.
That was plenty.
That really was.
Okay, we can just go in order, right?
Yeah.
So for me, James, the thing is, baby, that was one of the best things we've seen all day.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I'm not going to lie.
The thing is, baby, that was one of the best things we've seen all day.
Oh, yeah.
Right? Like, that was kind of incredible. I loved the fact that you decided to go acapella,
no backtrack at all. We liked that a lot. We loved that. I thought the lyrics, I don't know
if you wrote that song or something. I love his story. Baby, I love your story. I think that
there's obviously a superstar in there somewhere, and maybe we're going to mine that out of you,
James. So for me, I'm going to say that that's going to be a yes.
Now for me, I'm going to go right off the, right off the bat,
you mentioned Bella,
which is I guess your song collaborating partner or something.
I would love to see you two work together more.
Also doing this just because somebody liked your Facebook status and then you go
all in like this is like, it just shows that you're ready to go.
You have a celebrity star power that I don't even think is like being done.
It hasn't even been realized your full potential yet, James.
And you have that crazy ass goatee that makes you look like Shaggy from Scooby-Doo.
And that's honestly a fucking trademark that I can get behind for an artist.
So?
It's going to be a yes for me.
Yeah.
All right. So, James, love the music, buddy.
You look like a slob, okay?
You're disgusting. - Whoa!
- You have a piece of paper on your wall.
I don't know if you noticed that,
but we kind of try to present an image.
As musicians, we try to keep things neat and tidy,
and if that paper flew up there and got stuck there,
you're gonna have to take that down
before you come on our fucking show.
- Okay, so-- - So, well--
- James, don't listen to him.
He spoils for it. - And you smell horrible.
I can smell you from over here.
James, here's the thing, you're going to Hollywood.
Yep.
Two out of three.
You're going-- it doesn't matter what he says.
It's going to be five nos for me, James.
It doesn't matter.
Shh, shut up.
It doesn't really matter what he says.
Don't worry about him, James.
You are a star.
You are a talent.
I cannot wait.
And this is coming from a grandma-nominated artist, OK?
I'm one of these--
He's grandma-nominated.
His grandma said he's really good.
But I was nominated.
So this is--
OK.
And listen, that may be that you--
I'm not to sell nobody off the street.
I'm not throwing shade on the music here, guys and James.
You may be a grandma nominated musical artist,
but I don't know if you guys remember,
I was an Oscar nominated costume designer,
and your costume fucking stinks, pal.
Get some color in there.
- It's not about costume content.
- It's about the music, man.
- It's really not.
- It's about performance.
- It's about the fucking music, man.
- James, don't worry about it.
We're gonna go on to the next person.
- We'll move on, we'll move on, James.
- You did your thing.
- You did your damn thing.
- You know what, you did do your thing.
- We can all agree on that.
- Yeah, it was amazing.
- You did the thing.
- Okay, this is from, this looks like it's some kind
group the Mormonas. I don't really know much about this but go ahead y'all.
Oh nice little countdown I like it.
Presentation pretty good. Okay. A whole music video. This is a big crew this is kind of
maybe like a Jabba Walkies type thing.
[MUSIC]
I've never seen an R movie in the flesh.
Conference talks.
[MUSIC]
Okay.
Whoa.
Ripsticks.
and
will monster energy had
♪ ♪
No crime.
Who's that? Is that David Archuleta?
♪ ♪
Okay.
That's an incredible lyric.
Yeah, they're most.
♪ ♪
What's Motab?
Oh they got cones! Why do they throw the cones away and cry? I mean this is nice, I like this
guys. This is an original take on a classic song. The tune too, it's so catchy. Okay well
that was rude. I'm gonna stop you right there. I'm gonna stop you right there. So here's the
thing, you can sing all you want you fucking stupid bitch, right? You can have an amazing
voice, you can sing about your struggle, you can sing about what you fucking believe in,
But don't slap the drink out of someone's hand just because they're drinking alcohol or something.
That's a hate crime.
Yeah.
Right?
So you're saying you're a Moe, I bet you're a Moelester, right?
I bet you all got molested and that's why you're like this.
So stop doing covers.
Listen, okay, and we all know what you're- And that's going to be a no from me.
Hitting alcohol out of someone's hand, we all know what you're trying to do and guess
what guys, you will never be Earth Crisis.
Never.
So you're going to want to hang it up right now.
It's unoriginal.
If you're trying to rip on Earth Crisis and you're saying, "I don't see a-"
about what you believe in. I don't have a single X on the back of your hands or anything or
anything like that. But this is fake punk. That's what this is. 100%. This is fake fucking
punk. These are new jacks. But you know what? It's still going to be a yes for me. Wow. Yeah,
it's going to be a yes for me. It's two no's. It's a hard no for me. Listen, you know that
presentation is important to me? Yeah. And this presentation was horrible. I thought the
- The countdown was good.
- Get some flashing lights and get some fog machines
and then maybe we'll talk, it's a no from me.
- Yeah, that's gonna be a no.
So moving on, we don't wanna see anything more
from the Mormonas, which I'm realizing now--
- I think it's Mormons in Spanish.
- Why would it be a different--
- There's Spanish subtitles at the bottom of the screen.
- If you went there, would your name be Petrica Patricia?
- Patricio.
- Patricio, not Fat Chance, buddy.
- Ask Jubio.
- This comes from Sean N, and it looks like
he's got a backup singer, or maybe that guy's name's Sean
and his is just a letter.
Tire Cruise Diamond Knight.
Diamond Knight.
All right, yep.
All right guys, go ahead.
Whenever you're ready.
(rap music)
Wow.
[Music]
Wow. I'm loving everything about this. They have a matching outfit.
The music, I'm just closing my eyes and letting the music speak for itself here.
- That's awesome.
- These are a close duo too.
- That's amazing.
- Maybe they're twin brothers.
- Yeah, that could be a big selling point.
- I feel like I know the words,
I just wanna sing along.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- All right, I don't know.
- A little bit of a liberty there on the words.
- Sean and Ian, this is just not,
so you were on TV.
- You had us in the first half.
You had us in the first half.
- Yeah, you had us in the first half, not gonna lie.
- But by the way, this is going on network television,
so you can't say-- - ABC Family.
- We're not gonna be able to hear your beautiful voice
if it's covered by a bleep, do you realize that?
So when you say, "Mother F this, mother F that."
- And I get you wanna be punk,
I get you wanna do your Jim Morrison,
"We Can't Get Much Higher" on TV.
- It's clear that this is-- - But it's been done.
- This is an Elvis Costello thing you guys are doing, right?
You're trying to get banned from Saturday Night Live
or some shit. - You're doing
an Elvis Costello thing, you're getting drunk
calling like Sam Cooke the n-word or something.
- And listen, I like-- - That's what the story is.
He did that to a journalist.
I like provocative stuff.
You know me, I pushed Dee Barnes down a flight of stairs,
right, just because I thought it would make me like Dr. Dre.
Okay, turns out it just broke her orbital bone.
So I understand trying to be provocative, okay?
I've been banned from every award show that there is.
I'm banned from the Tonys.
You're banned from the Source Awards
and we can't get into why.
I'm banned from the Source Awards, I am.
I did some terrible things to Benzino, right?
I said some really, really weird stuff about him
a couple of years ago, a couple of years ago,
before all this, you know.
That's why we have to do this now.
Yeah.
That's why we have to do this,
that's why we're like, we used to be huge musicians
and then we had to go into comedy
and do all this fucking bullshit.
And we had to get into,
we had to pretend we care about free,
like I don't give a fuck about free speech, right?
No, shut it down.
But I'm so, I've said so much fucked up stuff in my life.
- Jokes online.
- I've said so many fucked up things in my life.
I can't open a restaurant.
That's how bad my life is now.
- That's why we're relegated to potty training.
- Yeah, exactly.
- So we've never talked about our former music careers.
- But here's what I've never done, guys.
Here's what I've never done.
- Say the F word in a song.
- Yep, never.
- Never, not one.
- Soiled, 'cause we know this is a cover
of Tyo Crew's Dynamite.
- And maybe I'm from a different generation.
- I would never soil a cover.
I would never soil an artist's original vision.
Maybe I'm from a different generation.
Maybe I'm from the greatest generation,
the 1990s, late 1990s, right?
Very late 1990s for me.
The last couple of years of the 1990s.
Probably the last three for me.
But that doesn't change the fact, right,
that there's some generational gap here
between you and the audience.
You young kids, you're coming in saying,
"Mother F this, mother F that."
Buddy, who do you think's gonna look down on that politely?
You think Tyo Cruz is gonna see that and say,
"Hey, nice cover of my song, come on tour with me."
- A lot of something about the generational thing here too.
You know, you young, you Zoomers, let's call it what it is.
Zoomers come in here, they say stuff like,
"Mother F this, mother F that," right?
Okay, you know, a lot of this generation above you,
like us, a lot of us are mothers.
We are fathers.
And you think we look down on that kindly?
To hear someone say, "F a mother?"
- Disrespecting the sanctity of parenthood.
- Disrespecting those who came before.
- Have you guys ever considered
how disgusting that phrase is?
Mother F-er?
- Think about your mom getting fucked.
- I'm just considering it now and I'm thinking about your--
- Think about it.
- Think about your mom.
- Think about your mom getting,
imagine your mom in your head right now, right?
- And she's really, really wet, too.
- Wet 'cause she's getting sprayed down
like by virgin coconut oil, like Kevin Gates.
- Yes.
- She's sprayed down with it.
- She's doing--
- And then your dad walks in and he's sweaty, too.
And it's real dark in the room,
but there's enough light coming in
that all you can see is the glistening skin.
- Well you can see, you know how dads get waxy penises
when they get kinda, like they have sex
and they walk around and their penis looks like
maybe it's made out of a candle?
- It looks like a sweet potato that's got a nub
growing off of it.
- Yeah, exactly, 'cause it's kinda somewhere
between hard and soft.
- Yeah.
- And it's got, and it's covered in your lung.
- And you the listener, and you two guys,
Sean and N, think about your parents fucking, okay?
- Yep.
- That's gross, you would never say motherfucker.
- Yeah, so leave Tyler Cruz out of this,
and let's move on.
It's gonna be a no from all three of us.
- Triple no.
- Who's up next?
- Let's see, who is up next?
It looks like it is, ooh, another group.
This is Faux Reality.
- Okay, I'm real excited.
- Faux Reality with a cover of Feel Good Inc.
So go ahead and show us. - It's pretty exciting for me.
- And this has-- - I'm a huge Gorillaz head.
- I'm really excited.
(laughing)
Oh, wow.
- Oh, they're already nailing it.
- You don't really need--
(upbeat music)
Oh, wow.
Okay, this got some funk to it.
I feel like I'm in a 007 movie.
Yeah, maybe some beautiful, completely silhouette shadow women
turning around, holding an AK-47 right at you.
Why is that sexy?
It's all shot in a fish eye. I'm thinking this is kind of a maid video.
So, it turns out the entire band is not auditioning, actually.
It's just the rapper.
So, cut to about maybe two minutes in, if you wouldn't mind.
Oh wait, no, go back a little bit.
Like when you first see him, that's the rapper.
Keep going.
There you go.
I'm excited to hear it.
Let's hear your bars.
I want to hear the bars, man.
Wow.
You got the flow, kid.
You got the sauce.
Wow, you got the flow, kid.
You got the sauce!
[Music]
Damn!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Wow!
See, I love, what I love about, okay, I want to point out right now.
right now. He's rapping, but behind him, a lot of photos of the Beatles. So he does, like
we were talking about with Sean N. They didn't respect their elders. He is respecting his
elders so much. He's got all these photos of the Beatles. And what is that right there?
Is that, who's that right next to him? Guy with the mustache? I don't know who that is,
but it looks like an older guy.
And we already talked about the guy's name, I already forgot because I hated him so much.
But he, remember what he had on his wall? A ragged piece of paper.
James Lang.
Now what does faux reality have that James Lang doesn't have?
American flag.
Pristine, flat, shiny pieces of paper.
This is a room with care put into it.
An American flag with the Beatles in front of it, because he loves American music.
Yeah, hey isn't it, hey, nice British invasion.
American rock and roll.
Loved British invasion by the way, but if you try it again, I will put you down like a dog in my front yard.
I'm ready at the front, I'm at the borders of England.
Yeah, we don't call the cops.
I'm at the borders of England, and if I see you leaving
Heathrow Airport with a guitar, I have a 40-millimeter grenade
launcher that I'm allowed to shoot at anyone going through
the airport.
40-millimeter grenade.
It's small because I only need to blow up one person.
If Pink Pantheress tries to jump the pond,
I'm shooting her with a crossbow like Van Helsing right out
of the air.
So it's going to be a yes from all three of us, I think.
And we don't want to waste any more time,
so let's move on to the next people.
move on to who's next here? I think I'm next in terms of the tabs.
Was that your last one?
Yeah, that was my last one.
Alright, here's my first one here.
Who's this?
I think it's DanStar88, he's doing a cover of I'm Osama by Doonstar.
Alright, Dan, Doon, let's see what you've got.
Here's a warning up top.
This video was supposed to go up last Friday, September 11th.
if anything seems "oh" of date, that is why.
Oh, here we go.
Can we go hijacking?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what,
what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what,
the
and what they do it and i think that this would be a good idea right which is the
built-up at seaport bomb tucked into my undies
(Dunkey and the pilot talking over each other)
- Really let loose though, Dune.
Just yell it.
Your mom's not here.
Come on, Dune.
- Yeah, let's stop it here.
Let's stop it here.
- Yeah, Dune, we're going to pause on Dune.
- What?
Listen, there's nothing that upsets me
more as a musician than when someone won't just let their emotions out and scream.
Yeah.
Dune.
Give it to me.
Oh, you're clicking on the other Dune video, the one that I was going to use,
but decided not to. This is King Kunta Kendrick Lamar cover. That was another one
that Dune posted.
Yeah, that was the other one that I was going to use, but I decided Dune was
shining in this one.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, he was shining.
That was smart. So, Dune, listen, baby.
You're 50% of the way there, is what I'll say.
Let me say this, you seem like a great guy. I don't know if you wrote this song or if
this is a cover. I understand it's very conceptual. It would fit right in on any kind of concept
album. I really like it. The reality is, like I said, you seem like a good guy. Maybe you
do have a future in entertainment, but just the voice, it's not there for me. It's really
just not there.
I think maybe with some lessons and your use of the looper pedal...
You could lose some weight.
So what I'm saying is, Dune, just keep at it, you know?
Maybe try some vocal lessons, you know?
And keep trying.
But this time, it's going to be a no for me.
I see potential in you.
I'm giving you a yes because I loved your use of the looper pedal and I love your kind
of DIY punk ethos that you're doing.
This is one of the most punk rock performances I think we've seen today.
Okay, so it's one and one.
So here's what I'd like to do.
- Can we just get a tiebreaker here?
- Can we get Cameron, just on Cameron, right?
- Just on Cameron.
- And I'm gonna address the elephant in the room, okay?
'Cause you guys, you skirted around this topic
and I don't blame you for doing so,
but I'm not gonna pull punches here,
I'm gonna come out and say what needs to be said.
You're singing a song about Osama Bin Laden,
and pardon the pun here, but in 2023,
that doesn't fly, pal.
- Damn.
- It's a no from me.
- Damn, Doonster, I'm sorry.
Your material was too edgy for me.
Thank you so much for coming by, Dune.
Thank you, Dune.
Thank you so much.
All right.
No thank you, Dune.
Just get a, yeah.
You're gonna be canceled.
All right.
Woo, that guy sucked!
He was terrible!
I love that guy.
I love that guy, that guy's great.
He was fucking shit.
Here's the next performer.
AVGNC, I'm gonna play, hello.
(upbeat music)
Oh, it's sextuplets.
Six identical brothers.
Kind of an impressive novelty.
I'm seeing doubles of brothers.
Giving me kind of a--
This is giving me--
LCD sound system.
Yeah, yeah.
This is like that kind of indie sleaze sound
that's on the comeback.
Like, I could see this being played
a lot of the downtown clubs in New York City.
- No doubt.
- All right, can I have first crack at this here?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- Brothers, you guys are incredible.
Your voices sound great, except for,
I'm sure we all notice this,
one on the right and the bottom, you sucked.
You have no place in this group.
And a lot of people won't tell you that
'cause you're six identical brothers,
they don't wanna separate you.
But you five, you gotta kick that other guy to the curb
'cause he is crap.
- He's a gumo, Mark.
If you agree right now to send that brother to jail, then I'll give you a yes, otherwise
it's a six no's from me.
I feel the exact same way.
Every single one of these 8 year olds should be in Hollywood, they should be working 70
hour weeks in a music studio, except that one, get him back in school.
Get him into a school right now.
I'm giving this one, this is another yes from me.
Maybe it's because I found it.
But I mean, again, if we send them to Hollywood, maybe we'll start to see them shine, like
doing different Motown songs or something.
By the way, he just kind of exposed something about the music industry that is disgusting,
which is that you said, "I want to send them there because I found them."
So you want a cut.
You don't know what you just revealed on live TV.
You want a fucking cut.
You're saying, "Go ahead, guys.
Send them to Hollywood and I'll be taking my 10%."
Okay, you know what?
- Listen, even if I'm talking to a greedy guy like you,
what's better?
You're in business with these six brothers,
what's better, you get one-seventh or one-sixth?
- Let's see this next one, all right?
If you don't agree with this one,
let's just go on to the next one.
- It's the same group?
- No, it's a different group.
- Okay, so that was, well, we gotta give him a yes or no.
It's a no from me, it's a no from him.
- It's a yes from me, but that means they don't go on.
So let's check out this next one.
Dr. Pepper.
- Is that his name?
Nice to meet you, doctor.
Hi Dr. Pepper.
Okay.
I guess, yeah, I guess if my name was Dr. Pepper I'd probably drink a lot of soda.
Wow, warm.
This is giving me kind of Pat the Bunny, Ramshackle Glory vibes.
Very fook-fuck.
Very lo-fi.
Andrew Jackson G-Hug.
Bandcamp.
On Avery Island.
Yeah.
Neutral Moat Hotel.
Put this thing on rate your music,
it's gonna get a 4.1.
(rap music)
[Music]
This is literally indistinguishable from a pokepunks drink.
(laughter)
- It does sound--
- All right, let's stop it here.
- James, James, James, the lyrics--
- Stop it here.
- It's exactly like a--
- That sounds like every song I listened to in high school.
- Of shitty 2012.
- Literally like, yeah.
(laughter)
- Oh, it was King Krule all the time.
- Yep, that's Archie Marshall.
- That kid's name is Archie?
- His name is Archie Marshall, yeah.
- Oh, King Krule's name is Archie?
- King Krule's name is Archie Marshall.
- I'm not even gonna go there,
'cause you all know what I'm thinking.
Yeah. Well, have Archie. Archie have been Marshall from SNL.
Yeah, true.
He's a perfect combo to.
So this one, you guys think that I'm trying to push along people that I want to cut of.
I don't want to see any money from this one. I'm not going to pass this one along. This
is no for me.
Really? This to me is maybe the most emphatic yes of the entire day.
Really?
This is the first one that I would listen to.
Stylistically? I would listen to this. There's definitely a time in my life where I would
of sat in my bed and listened to this.
- It's like, I still kind of can't believe
how much it sounds like, like Ramshackle Glory.
- Was he playing the guitar?
- He just needs a slightly higher pitched voice.
A voice that sounds a little more like this.
- And he can still sing about Dr. Pepper, really.
Like it doesn't really, like they have
some dumb songs like that.
- Well he's jacking our swag.
- That's true, yeah, he can do it.
- He's jacking our swag, we did the Dr. Pepper cast.
- The only thing, yeah, the only thing that is missing
from this kid's life to be a folk punk superstar
is he needs to leave his family and live on a train
for 10 months. He needs to pretend that he was poor.
Yeah, then that's fine. This would be
pretty effective folk punk. Well, I guess
you're going to Hollywood, Dr. Pepper. No, this guy's going to
Portland, Oregon. He's going to Dayton, Ohio.
He's going to Richmond, Virginia. We're sending this guy to Richmond.
You get a special case. Yeah, you don't need to go to...
Hollywood wouldn't understand.
Yeah, see that's why I said no, you're not going to Hollywood, bud.
You're going to Richmond, you're going to Portland, Maine on a boxcar.
You're going to eat nothing but saltines and sardines for two weeks.
I was going to be on the Acela in a Hobo outfit.
You're going to get fired from New London, Connecticut.
And you're going to record a masterpiece in a blanket fort somewhere.
One of the best songs, one of the best folk punk albums ever recorded.
By Dr. Pepper.
Alright, let's hear this next one here.
here. Now, this is an original song by one Linda Polly.
Amazing. I like it.
So you're a songwriter.
A little bit older. A little bit older than these past couple of people.
This could be our Susan Boyle.
Original music is one of my favorites.
So wait, really quick. Stop it for just a second.
Guys, no matter what this says or what she sounds like or how good the song is, we
need to say yes, because Susan Boyle was huge for that show.
OK. All right. Let's just hear it.
We're just agreeing. It's going to be a yes no matter what she says.
handshake on it. Yeah, this is a yes. Okay, Linda Paula, Lindy Polly, Linda Polly, go
ahead and show us what you got. Okay. And it's, "What are you doing?" Linda, you gotta sing,
baby. Linda, I can tell that you're a little nervous. Please, Linda. Right.
Performed by known psychic Linda J. Polly. Oh, wow.
If you want your sons wearing skirts and pantyhose
With lipstick on their faces and shiny neon polished clothes
Then vote for Hillary and she'll import the pantyhose
This is a known psychic vote for who? Hillary. Oh
Stop the pervert, come and stop the pervert
Come on people, this is getting scary.
Come on people, don't go for your real.
Okay.
If you want your children to go out there to the stars.
Now, Linda, something I'm noticing that you're doing here that's a really incredible musical
technique is you're on the piano, you're playing the exact same notes that you're singing and
(laughing)
Which is called harmony.
A lot of professional musicians use that.
♪ Both for normal ♪
♪ Common both for normal ♪
- All right, let's stop the song here.
- Linda, I mean, we already agreed
that this was gonna be yes,
and I was worried that this was gonna be--
- But you were technically proficient.
- I was a little bit,
I thought this was gonna be a Susan Boyle moment,
and let me tell you something.
- No, this is more of like--
- It was, it was, you're coming to Hollywood.
- 100%.
But this was not a Susan Boyle moment.
This was like a Little Mix moment.
No.
You're coming to Hollywood.
We're going to get you in a bikini.
We're doing 50 different surgeries on you, Linda.
And we're going to just put you everywhere.
You're going to be on billboards.
Let me tell you, your musical proficiency,
your technical skill is so incredible.
I think that while you're doing great in this singer, songwriter,
piano stuff, I think that you would be right at home
in a band like Meshuggah or Slayer.
Could be.
I think you could really hit those strings quick.
Also, you do kind of look like a Chuck E. Cheese animatronic.
So in the interim, you know, while you're trying to grind,
you could kind of play-- that could be like your-- what's
that club the Beatles played at in Germany forever?
And that's how they got good?
The Cobra Club.
That's-- you could be-- that could be your club like that.
You could really hone your skill, sharpen your knife,
sharpen your tools.
So that's a yes from all three of us.
That's going to be a yes from all three of us, Linda.
Huge yes.
All right, let's go to this next performer here.
You're an amazing artist.
This is Ass on Fire.
That's his name?
I forget his name.
- Ass is on fire video.
- Is this based on, is this a-
- By Dance B, but Dane B.
- Dainy B.
- Dainy B. - Dainy B.
- Okay, Danny, right off the bat, I like your style.
- Ow, ow.
Somebody call a fire department.
- It burns.
- What burns? - Smokin' hot.
- What's smokin' hot, Danny?
Just tell us.
- Ass is on fire.
Burned down to the wire.
- You have a wire in your ass?
- Can't catch the fire.
Oh man, baby, my ass is on fire.
Burning, burning and melting.
Oh, what a mess.
- Dr. E.
- Please make a stop.
Ow, ow.
- Same dance.
- My ass is on fire.
- Great dance.
- Feel it, please baby, help me.
- Okay, I like this dance.
- Yeah, this is a good dance.
This could be the next viral dance.
- Yeah, this is a new TikTok dance right there.
- Cheeks are red, can't go to bed.
Can you hear that sound?
Got to jump around.
Ow.
Ass is on fire.
Turn down to the wire.
Down to the wire.
Burnin'.
Smolderin'.
Heat is on.
Turn the heat off.
Your ass is on fire.
Hey.
Peaks are red.
Looking behind him.
Someone's watching him dance.
My ass is on fire.
Burnin' and burnin' meltin'
Is the camera doing this or is he having a trap?
I think maybe they were stabilizing it
I think they were stabilizing it on his head
The thing is if he stabilizes it he doesn't do a great job
Move the video a little bit forward
Please help me
I just want to show you that
Oh ok
He can be Dr. Evil
Oh my god
Flava Flav
And I think he also becomes Austin Powers at one point
Oh shit
I don't know what that is. That is like... That's Elvis!
Alright, yeah, that's enough Danny.
Danny, please, you're done.
Danny, stop! You're golden.
What I'll say is, when I saw the name of this video,
I thought that maybe it might be a cover of the Mr. Bungle song,
"My Ass Is On Fire", and while it's not, it's pretty much, it might as well be.
(laughing)
- Danny, this was amazing.
I really think you're talented.
- And also, by the way, something fresh, something new.
- We have costumes.
- You know you have the costumes, Scott.
You knew I was gonna, I had my finger in the air.
You know I was like, "And the costumes."
That's me.
I'm a costumes nerd.
- The showmanship, the pageantry, Danny.
- The legendary.
- The pageantry was incredible.
And I think that that shows a real star power.
So it's gonna be a yes from me.
- It's gonna be a yes from me, too.
- It's gonna be a double, quadruple, triple yes from me.
Wow. You're going to Hollywood, Danny.
You're going to Hollywood.
Eyes on the side.
You're definitely going to Hollywood.
Now, let's check out this next one here.
How many people you got?
Yeah, come on.
No, we got to skip these last ones.
Yeah, this one, no.
This is not, yeah.
This isn't a song.
We're done.
Wait, just click one more.
I think there's another one.
You have, you've, you've had enough.
Let's just hear this guy out.
You just want your pay, your pay cut.
You want, you're going to get a pay cut.
Hollywood.
Next.
Going to Hollywood.
Can you do it again?
Can you perform that again?
I need to hear that one more time. I just want to see if we can do that on command.
Or if it was just a fluke.
(Whistle)
Hollywood.
Wait, wait. Okay, I like the R2 scream guy.
What was that amazing, beautiful,
angelic sound at the end? Uh-huh. The cameraman?
Play it one more time. Wait, the cameraman,
we need the cameraman to go to Hollywood with you.
I played it on .25 speed. Both of you,
I only take you as a combo.
Let's hear this in 2.5.
(Whistle)
(angels singing)
- Wow.
Now listen to this.
(laughing)
Now that is the voice of an angel.
That is the voice of, okay, so now the contestants
and camera has chosen.
- Guys, can I bring my contestants in the stage yet?
- Yes, I wanna see them, I wanna see them.
These are the people I'm the most excited about.
- All right.
- See, why did you--
- We don't have to worry about the slide
and we can move forward.
- Okay.
- This is a song called Getting Dizzy, original song,
It's by Brandon Quaight, who is a young musical prodigy.
Okay.
So just go to the next slide.
I put title slides and song slides.
So go ahead and play this.
Let's hear this.
Wow.
That Love Is Album cover, by the way.
Yeah, that's a great album cover.
Yeah, me too. It was amazing.
What did you...
UBEO cannot click anything.
You can't click.
There we go.
Okay.
Now play.
(upbeat music)
- Okay.
- This way.
(upbeat music)
- Is that Brandon or is that still?
- That's Brandon Quaid singing.
(upbeat music)
All right, Brandon. Okay, Brandon, you can stop.
Yeah, that's enough, Brandon.
Brandon, this is, you are, no, you don't have to go forward, Brandon.
Yeah.
You can stop. Brandon.
Play the very end. Play the very end, Brandon. Just play the end of your song.
Wow.
What a finale.
Brandon, you are a Hollywood bound buddy.
Wow.
(game show music)
Brandon.
What a finale.
Brandon, you are a Hollywood bound buddy.
Listen, it doesn't matter if we were here,
you'd be going to Hollywood.
No, I feel like you're already there.
I feel like you're already in Hollywood writing
100% of the greatest songs I've ever heard.
I almost am suspicious of you
and think you might be an industry plant.
Yeah.
That's what I think.
He could be.
He's talented.
I think your song, Getting Dizzy,
literally made me feel like I was getting it.
- And you were a talented artist as well.
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, visual artist.
- Visual artist, yeah.
- You got the whole package, kid.
- Brandon, you're going to Hollywood.
- It's three yeses.
- Let's see this next one.
- All right, let's check out the next one.
This is called Christmas Day, and it's by James Woodland.
- Okay.
- It's kind of a holiday song.
- Wow, I like your look.
Already a superstar look, James.
- Oh my God.
- And he has video editing skills.
- Look at that fucking edit.
That is one of the most incredible things I've ever seen.
A lot of people would pay millions for it.
Just wait till you hear his voice.
Yeah, we need to hear it too.
The visuals are only half the battle.
It's that one tradition that brings joy to the people, bring them together.
Whatever happens in their lives, their kids are us, they shine so bright, Santa can't
see it through the night.
Mommy's baking Christmas cookies, Daddy's working on this beautiful crib.
Because it's Christmas Day now.
Because it's Christmas Day.
Wow.
Caleb is crying.
Alright, you can stop.
You can, James.
Caleb thinks it's the most beautiful song he's ever heard in the world.
Cameron, you have just found nothing but stars so far.
This guy, he and, yeah, I don't even...
James.
Can I tell you guys something?
Yeah.
So, obviously, I pre-screened this guy.
And this is 100% real. I found this guy yesterday.
This song has been completely stuck in my head.
How can it not be?
hard not to be singing it when I came into the office this morning, so I
wouldn't spoil it, but for 24 hours straight I've been singing to myself
"Because it's Christmas Day now, because it's Christmas Day now."
Wow.
Something else, really something else.
James, that was really, it was incredible.
That reminded me of Christmas Day.
Yeah.
I, I...
Mom's baking Christmas cookies.
I'm kind of at a loss of words. It reminded me of when my mom would bake a
Christmas cookie and I would come downstairs...
building a crib, a beautiful crib.
- Like there's just--
- I literally, if I ever have a kid,
I will have a beautiful crib for my kid.
- There's so much history and--
- Because of this song.
- There's so much heart in what you sang,
so it's gonna be a yes.
But I can't even look at you anymore.
You're really getting very emotional.
- Hey, so we got two yeses so far?
- Yeah.
- James, for me, it's not gonna be a yes.
- What?
- It's gonna be a Merry Christmas.
- Oh my God. - Oh my God.
- Buddy, you're going to the North Pole.
- Yep.
- James, it's a yes.
very
uh... right
this is a lot of letter rock parody by digital skills and enroll this year this
one
already off to a very promising start this one
I see McCain and that chick who has no brain
Tryna win the big one but they can't do it
Because there is this guy who's much cooler
He's too fly and he said yes we can
Yes we can, yes we can
He was just a boy from Illinois
The White House he'll enjoy.
Because this guy's too fly, he brings the wind, George Bush.
Goodbye, his famous grin, in case you forgot.
I must now remind you, vote for Rock.
Vote for Rock.
Now skip to the rap.
Skip to the rap.
Vote for Payton, she be-
Obama wins, he's Barack, he's on top, canes a flop
I, his famous grin, in case you forgot
I, must now remind you, vote for Barack, vote for Barack, vote for Barack
Yeah, yeah!
Obama wins, he's Barack, he's on top, canes a flop
He's gonna go 'til four you stop, he gives us speeches just for us
Barack, we the people, Barack, must stand together.
Barack, God bless these states, God bless the world,
and America, he's here and he won't get to ride.
- Okay, stop it, enough.
Buddy, you're going, I mean, the music with a message.
- You have an amazing ear, Cameron,
because you are picking some amazing,
amazingly talented people. - You are picking nothing
but winners.
- This is a yes, I got emotional at the beginning
just remembering the election, right?
Because elections are so contentious
and I hate when America fights.
It makes me really sad.
And this reminded me of Barack Obama for some reason.
And his famous grin.
Yeah.
When I heard the word famous grin,
I was like, this has to be about Barack Obama.
That's one of the main things about Barack Obama.
We all would say his famous grin.
His famous grin, right, his grin.
That's the beauty of music.
Look at that grin!
That's the beauty.
That is the beauty of music.
That's the beauty of songwriting,
is that I got a completely different message.
I didn't get any of that.
What did you get?
It was about love,
and I mean it was like a whole story almost.
- God bless the world and America.
- Yeah, so those are like names.
- God bless these states.
God bless the world and America.
- So, thank you so much.
Next contestant please, 'cause that was incredible.
- Okay, this is the one I'm most excited about, I think.
- Okay, we can probably end on this, yeah?
- No, I have one more after this.
That's important.
Okay, we'll say this is the one I'm second most excited about.
This is Mr. Silver, "Move Out the Way,"
feat. Lil' Rocket and BK the Rapper.
And the music speaks for itself,
but if you aren't watching on video,
just pull up the video just right now, you're on spotify or whatever, you're gonna wanna
see this.
and let's just hit it Mr. Silver.
Silver number one music presents.
Back with more music and lil rocket bout to blast off.
Woah!
DJ bout to fix some bars.
Oh my god.
This is the gangnam style, okay.
He's doing the gangnam style dance.
I don't play AA so move out the way, move out the way.
I go crazy in this car, yeah I'm ready to spark.
Gonna hit the deck, ready to cross the street.
I'm ready to rock, ready to rock.
By the way
Wow
Yeah I'm ready to spark, gonna hit the dash
Ready to crash cause I'm going so fast
Driving like a boss, 'bout to hit the notch
There's about a beat, so much sauce
Cause my engine's revving, so loud you can hear it from heaven
So move out the way, move out the way, move out the way
Before I have to remove you, or even excuse you
And I'm going nitro, like the car's almost on fire
So don't test me, cause you can't mess with me
(laughing)
- Incredible music video, I think.
- Wow.
- I jump in the piles of money, I make it split.
♪ Now you know I'm legit 'cause I'm so rich ♪
♪ That's why every time I'm running down the fast lane ♪
♪ I'm always like underlay, underlay, underlay ♪
♪ Underlay, underlay ♪
♪ Move out the way, move out the way ♪
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
♪ Move out the way ♪
♪ Yeah because all they do is complain ♪
- Oh my God.
- All right, that's enough, I've heard enough.
- You have just found nothing but heat.
- Okay, camera, you can start.
Camera, go ahead, you can start.
- These kids have fucking got it, man.
This next generation is all right.
I thought that they were wrong.
They're kicking out jams like Move Out the Way
with a music video already funded and filmed.
They're not even signed.
- This literally, it sounds exactly like Lil Peep.
- It sounds like it's coming from heaven.
- Yeah, it sounds like Lil Peep came down from heaven
and blessed these two souls.
- Mr. Silver, Lil' Rocket about to blast off,
and BK the Rapper, who I don't think
says anything in the song?
- He has not said a single thing.
- I'll say this, these kids are talented,
there's no question there.
- Right, so here's my problem.
Rap is terrible.
Rap is awful.
Rap is fucking disgusting.
- Okay, what about the last song?
- What about the song Prior?
- 'Cause here's what I hear,
if these lyrics are written down,
I might be able to go, oh wow, this is an amazing message,
The kids could relate to this, right?
Here's what I hear.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I think especially kids could relate to this one.
Maybe.
Yeah.
But I wouldn't fucking know, because I
can't understand a goddamn word that's
coming out of their mouths.
No.
So for me, it's going to be a no.
You already got two, so it doesn't matter.
But I just want you to know, next round, I'm coming for you.
All right.
Now, this next one I have is the last one.
This is the one I am most excited about.
It's a cover of Grenade by Dr. Dazzle.
OK.
I think this guy has real star power.
I think that we could get Dr. Dazzle and Dr. Pepper together.
That's a good idea.
So just go ahead and play this real quick, the cover of Grenade by Dr. Dazzle.
Grenade by who?
Just watch it and find out.
Oh, okay. Now I hear it.
*music*
I catch a grenade
(Music)
(Laughter)
So is Dr. Dazzle going to Hollywood?
Um, uh, yes.
(Laughter)
Dr. Dazzle is...
(laughing)
Wow, you really threw me off.
Wow.
- I'm surprised you guys didn't,
I thought it was gonna be three of that in a row
to be honest.
- You really did?
- I thought that was a layup.
Put yourself in it.
- I'm so glad I didn't do that.
I'm so glad I didn't do that.
Wow.
- You guys think I'm a good singer?
- Yes.
You're going to Hollywood, Cameron.
I didn't realize you had this other side to you.
- Who filmed it for you?
- Don't worry about it.
- I hired a crew.
(laughing)
- Hadad.
Okay, that's it for American Idol for us right now.
- Wow.
- Lots of deserving singers going to Hollywood.
- Fuck every other person on this.
- I think Dr. Dazzle, this is now making the band
with Dr. Dazzle.
- We really just need to do making the band with Dr. Dazzle.
I need to get Dr. Dazzle like in arenas.
(laughing)
- Okay, guys, go see Dr. Dazzle on tour.
- Go see Dr. Dazzle on tour.
Then go see me on the 16th of March
at Arts and Armory opening for Conor O'Malley.
- Okay, bye.
- And then also you could see Caleb
- Bye.
- At the Chocolate Factory. - Stop recording now.
- Bye everybody.
- He's gonna get stuck in a tube like Gloop.
- Oh my God.
[BLANK_AUDIO]