*Badass music*
*Ding*
That was a brolic ass clap.
What does brolic mean again? I thought it meant cold.
Strong.
I think I'm saying it right too.
Brolic?
It's not brolic. Yeah, it's brolic.
Brolic ass clap.
I'll lick a bra right now.
You'll lick the bra on the Forest Avenue stop.
You seen that one? New York, stand up!
- New York, stand the fuck up!
- What are you talking about?
- Forest Ave M train stop, there's been a bra there
for months in a tree.
- And you think that's hot?
- A tree wearing a bra?
- No, something really bad probably happened.
For a bra to get all the way up there,
somebody was confused, somebody thought it was a Mardi Gras.
- I'm thinking of a tree wearing a bra,
I don't know what kind of thing you're thinking of.
- I'm thinking that somebody got confused
and took their bra off.
- What if they took their bra off?
- What if the guys started getting undressed
thinking that they were in their house?
What if it was a blind woman?
- Yeah.
- And a blind woman felt the tree and she said,
"This feels exactly like my closet."
- There's a clothesline on that station.
- Well then you're burying the fucking lead.
Wait, at the station, who lives in the,
somebody lives in the train.
- There's a clothesline on the windows.
- Oh.
- You've seen this one.
- No.
- You've been to that stop?
- Not every day, bro.
Not every fucking day.
- Speaking of.
- It's every day, bro.
- Speaking of every day.
I've been listening to some--
Let's get some primes.
Let's pause right now.
No.
They're hard to find, dude.
They're really hard to find in New York.
What are you talking about?
I can't find them anywhere.
I find them fucking everywhere.
OK, well hook me up with a line on a prime,
because I really like a popsicle flavor.
There's one by my apartment.
Really?
Bodega.
I think-- do they have the red, white, and blue one?
I've seen it around.
I've been pretty obsessed with Jake Paul's music,
or Logan Paul's music recently.
he has a song called 2020, Fuck You 2020 or something.
- I haven't heard that one.
- You never heard that?
- No.
- Oh my God, it's good.
Can you pull that up?
- Can we see this one?
- Can you pull up Fuck You 2020?
- Fuck You 2020 by Offbeat?
- It might not be called Fuck You.
- There is a--
- That's the, I would say that's her--
- There are a lot of songs called Fuck You 2020 out there.
- I would say that is more the theme of the song.
- Logan Paul 2020.
- It's just called 2020.
Of course it's just called 2020.
- Okay, let's hear this.
- But basically he tackles a lot of,
Do you remember how shitty that year was, bro?
Bro, don't even.
I went through the worst breakup of my life.
(laughing)
Yeah, it really did.
It was bad, dude.
2020 was not chill at all.
Wait, skip to the...
♪ Mask on my face ♪
♪ With my quarantine bae ♪
♪ And she said she'd be here late ♪
♪ No wait ♪
♪ Fall in love back in March ♪
♪ We broke up in November ♪
Oh my God.
♪ This a year I don't wanna remember ♪
Wow.
♪ Everybody's pissed ♪
♪ Karen lost her shit ♪
Karen lost her shit, Amazon is lit.
I buy stock in that bitch.
- Damn, Jake, you got bars. - That's right.
- Yeah, so he basically-- - Coachella got,
dude, this is literally 9/11.
Coachella getting canceled was 9/11 for Jake Paul,
Logan Paul, and his friends. - Yeah, it was pretty bad,
I would say. - Yeah.
Speaking of the Coachella lineup this year.
- Did it get lit? - My friend, the Kid Leroy.
(both laughing)
- We should link up with the Kid Leroy.
- I've been trying, dude, I've been trying to get him
on the pod. - He did Adam 22,
he'll do us. - Yeah?
- Yeah, dude, we're way fucking cooler than Adam 22.
I got tattoos, you look like Lena the Plug.
If we put a skim on you.
- I got tattoos.
- If we put skims on you. - I have two tattoos.
Three tattoos, I have the Dr. Evil one here
and then the Spider-Web.
- Okay, what do you want, a fucking ink award?
- I wanna get more, I wanna ink my whole body,
I don't give a motherfucker.
- Dude, if you-- - Remember that song?
- No. - You remember Snapbacks
and tattoos? - Bro, if you get--
- That's what I'm trying to be on, wait.
- I don't wanna see you covered in,
that would break my heart.
I regret every tattoo I have.
I look like a fucking--
- You don't think this looks sick?
- No, that does look sick.
The snapback is a good look on you.
I like this, I've always liked the snapback on you.
- Wait.
- The tattoo, you gotta roll both up
or people know what you're doing.
- I only have one tattoo.
- I know, but you gotta roll both sleeves up.
- I got two.
- No, you're not--
- Imagine, okay, imagine like a moody,
black and white photo of me like this.
- That might be--
- I look like Wiz.
- Okay, well that'd be cool.
- Yeah, and then you could do like,
O-W-G-I-A-F-C, that could be your album.
- What's my, what's that?
- Only White Guy in First Class.
(laughing)
You could do that.
That would be cool.
- Yeah.
- That would be cool. - That would be cool.
- I think that's the type of shit
I'm trying to be on this year.
I'm trying to bring back like a 2014 style swag,
or 2013 style swag.
- I would say you have a 2013 style,
you've never left that world.
- No, dude.
You got okay you guys made fun of me for my hat that I've been wearing
You know my birthday on the 50 year old head is terrible, okay?
You've been making fun of me for that, and I'm gonna say it cuz mommy's gone
And he's not here to defend himself so I had to talk shit about camera
Yeah, I'm about to talk shit about a hat that he's worn for a long time. It's the golden retriever hat is no
It's a different one or whatever when we first started the podcast and he had a hat that said pog
Mmm, damn.
And he wore that every fucking day.
Yo, get him.
Uh-huh.
Yo, that was whack.
He wore that every single day.
Do me now.
What do I wear that's poop?
You used to have hair.
Yeah, that's some real shit.
No, you're not gonna find this hat.
You're not gonna find it, no.
This is before we took photos, man.
I think you might be able to find that hat.
Cameron used to be such a pretty lady
back when we first started dating.
Now he looks like a man.
When we first started dating?
Or first--
(laughing)
- When he first started.
- This is Cameron?
- Yeah.
Wow, he looks good.
Guys, if you couldn't tell.
- That was a hand embroidered hat by himself, I think.
- Yeah, it is.
- Wait, look at that fucking ice cream photo.
(laughing)
- That's of me though.
That's an awful photo.
- You look like an uncle in that show Dinosaurs
- Yeah, it does look very lizard-y.
Guys, if you couldn't tell, Mommy is completely gone.
There's no Mommy anywhere to be seen.
- Mommy's gone.
- Wait, wait, where's Mommy?
Is Mommy not down here?
- Mommy don't know that Mommy's gone.
- Mm-hmm, keep going.
- And Mommy's gone.
- No.
- It's the third time we've done this.
- Mommy don't know that her sons are on,
on the podcast now, and she's in Mexico.
- Mexicali.
- He went to Tijuana 'cause he was gonna be
in a donkey show. - Mommy don't know.
- He's not in a donkey show.
Wait, one of the ones where they get a fucker,
they fuck a, they get a donkey fuck.
- He's the donkey.
- Oh, well that'd be lucky then.
'Cause don't you fuck a lady?
Isn't that the whole point of the donkey shows?
You get the hottest lady. - I thought that it was
reversed.
- No, they get like a-- - I thought that it's
a guy fucking a donkey.
- A female donkey?
- Yeah. - What's the fun of that?
Nobody likes, nobody wants to see that.
- You don't know that.
- I do know that.
Nobody wants to see, even Mr. Hands,
he's even the one where the guy is fucking an animal,
The guy gets fucked by the animal.
- Did you know Mr. Hands, the video of him getting fucked,
that's not when he died.
- No, he didn't die, no.
- That was a success. - He was fine.
He was fine. - That video is a success.
That's not the snuff one.
- That is an amazing success.
- But then there was another one, they deleted the tape
where it was like, used as evidence or something.
- Yeah, probably both of those.
- Yeah, probably.
- Yeah, used as evidence against the horse.
- Yeah, they were like, this horse is a murderer.
- Yeah, it's a horse.
- This horse is a murdering piece of shit.
- What do they do with the horse?
Is that horse at a petting zoo now?
Is that horse giving little kids
like their first riding lesson?
- They probably took that horse to horse therapy.
- The horse doesn't know that it fucking killed a guy
with its massive cock, right?
- I think it knew.
- Maybe.
- I think that that horse was like,
all right, they keep making me--
- You thought it was on purpose.
You thought it was premeditated.
- That horse had a look in its eyes.
I've never seen Mr. Hans.
That's the one I haven't seen.
I've seen pretty much all of those.
- I've seen almost none of the ones where people get hurt.
I've never seen the one guys one jar. I've never seen the two guys and a hammer
I've never that's the one that my neighbor showed me when I was a factory or whatever you watch two guys with a hammer when you
Were one nine or nine yeah my neighbor
Not like he used to make works bombs
Well one in a bottle you put all the aluminum foil with the works clean. Yes. Yes. Yes, I'm familiar
he used to make those and then he was a kid in the neighborhood who had the dune buggy and
He took by the way when you say neighbor
I think me and everybody else is listening when you say I was a kid and my neighbor showed me
I'm thinking grown man. He was my sister's age so when I was nine. He was four years older than me, so he was 13
Yeah, he's a kid oh he's old in my head
So it's not his fault that he like showed you something crazy like you know no I didn't think he thought it was
He died is gonna impress you yeah, yeah
- Yeah, he was like the dune buggy kid.
- My version of that is that I saw the Scary Maze game.
- Yeah.
- And that honestly, probably--
- That's not as fucked up.
Two guys, one hammer is just a snuff film.
- It's a Scary Maze game, it's probably--
- It's a scary enough film.
- I think that's a dead body.
I think that's a real photo of a dead body
on a Scary Maze game.
So, explain that.
And also the scream is probably also taken
from a woman being killed.
- The scream, it's like a blowout situation.
Exactly where they recorded that scream from an actual dying. Yeah, I think that's true. Yeah. Oh damn. I'm sorry if you haven't seen blowout
You spoiled the I spoiled the whole movie. I don't think that's a whole movie. That's the ending of blowout really
I haven't seen it. I only row I fucking spoiled it you did spoil it for me. I'm not such a good movie that Michael, man
No, that is Brian Brad to Paul or Brian Brian did blah blah yeah, Tommy De Palma. There's a dragon Nona
Let's make that a movie.
- What's "Streg-a-Nona"?
- It's a book about a nona who keeps making a bunch of pasta.
- I wanna slag your nona.
- You're not gonna streg my nona.
- No, I wanna slag her.
- Slag my nona?
- I wanna slag her, your mom.
- Slag? - Your nona.
- Slag is F, right?
- I think slag is F.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- All right, you're gonna F my grandma?
- It's about what I'm getting at, yeah.
- We're gonna put this in American English,
you're gonna F my grandma.
I'm not as comfortable saying it in--
In Samuel Adams English.
I'll say it in the King's English all day.
But in Sam Adams English--
In Washington's English, I'm not as comfortable saying it.
No.
I'll say it in Spanish.
Yeah.
Su abuelita es mi comerculo.
Yeah, exactly.
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE]
Yeah.
What the hell?
That would be so disrespectful.
Is there constantly a bar falling on you
on this side of the table?
Yeah, do you ever see me fucking complain about anything?
No. No.
Well, I have a nail that I play with.
Is that what you're always,
I always think you're touching your penis.
No, I'm just touching the tip of the nail.
Really?
Wow, I have to do something about that.
That is really sharp. I see my thumb.
Oh my God!
Well, that's from grip tape, but.
Oh, okay, well don't show to me,
like don't say you see my thumb.
It's calloused enough that I can just touch that
with my thumb and nothing happens.
There is a few times where it has punctured it,
and I don't know if, you can probably
scrabble back through a couple episodes.
- You probably go like, ow!
I thought you--
- There's a few where I go like.
- I thought you felt something good
about your balls or your penis.
- No, no, no, no.
- So you did that.
- I am fully putting my thumb on that nail.
- That's not so smart, Patrick.
I'm gonna be putting my nose--
- No, but it's in front of me, so I have to touch it.
- And if you guys are wondering,
I went today with the Unsweetened Bold green tea.
- Okay, that's the stuff my girlfriend drinks.
- I never tried this one before.
This, I think, is probably gonna keep me up all night,
so I'm a little bit worried about it.
- I went with the Monster Sunrise,
which has a little bit more caffeine than a usual monster.
This has 165.
- What's something that when Mummy is here,
she looks down on?
- Well, talking about the visual stuff.
- Well, yeah, but we already did that,
and now that I think about it,
it's probably not a good idea.
- Yeah, it's definitely not a good idea.
- What is a topic that Mummy always shuts down
because she maybe thinks it's too obtuse?
That's a word she would use.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I don't even know.
- What does mummy not like? - I can't put myself
in mummy's clothes.
- It's too, well, we do that when she's gone.
- Yeah, when mummy's gone. - We've been doing it
basically the whole weekend that she's been out of town
on a work trip.
- Oh my God, yeah, I wear her pog hat.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah.
- Was that, is that on this one or did we delete that part?
- By the way, when Cameron isn't here,
we instantly fail all the time
because of your five minutes of the video.
- Somehow we have a five minute episode
that is just never gonna see the light of day.
- So that was mummy's gone three,
So this is four now.
- This is four.
- This is four already, so we'll call it Mummy's Gone Four.
- Yeah.
We have a five minute Mummy's Gone Three.
- Yeah, probably won't ever see the light of day.
It was mostly us trying to figure out,
I was mostly adjusting levels and looking at pictures.
But we got that out of the way.
And now we're back in a real podcast.
Let's talk about, let's rate all the girls we know.
(laughing)
That would piss Mummy off so bad.
- Yeah.
Just girls that we have never had on the podcast.
No, girls that we barely even have talked to.
We don't like--
We've met a couple times.
Yeah, met once or twice.
Yeah, and let's just say like five.
Out of five?
No, out of 10.
Let's just like randomly to these girls.
Out of 100.
Say like five or four.
I don't think we should do that.
You know what?
You know what we can do?
We can rate the guys though.
I do have, because mommy's gone.
Yeah.
Okay, I do have something for you.
What the hell, what is it?
I saw this at the store today. I was out. I was on a shopping spree.
Okay.
I don't remember...
With her credit card?
With mommy's credit card.
Bro, chill.
I don't remember if...
We already talked about my shopping spree.
You went on a shopping spree.
I went on a shopping spree.
You got skateboards, so it's not that important.
Yeah, not really important at all.
What's important is that I went on a shopping spree.
I saw this thing.
Okay.
You're making me so nervous, man.
I looked at it and I said to myself immediately,
"This is so Caleb."
- I was really-- - It's not even funny.
- I really was hoping that you would say,
when you said that you looked at it, you said something,
I was really hoping it would be, "This is so Caleb."
Because I've never had anybody give me something
and say, "I wanted to buy this because it's so you."
So I'm actually getting, I'm almost tearing up at the--
- Okay, close your eyes, close your eyes.
- Okay, my eyes are closed.
Okay, should I hold my hands out?
Or will it even fit in my hands?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Just put that...
Just gonna want to just put it on.
I'll just put it on first?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now...
Oh! Wait!
Mm-hmm.
That's my initials!
That is his initials.
CB!
Uh-huh.
That is so dope!
I saw this and I was like, "Yep."
I love this!
Uh-huh.
This is amazing!
Yeah, I love this. Why don't you change hats?
Take the hat off and take the earth take your your on the hat under off and then change it to the new one
See now everyone will know
You wearing this and they're gonna be like wait who that who that? Oh, that's a way that CP coming down the street
You know I'm seeing CP everywhere there. He's over there. He's over. He's all around the city. I was just watching CP on Twitch
Yeah, exactly
(laughing)
- Damn, CP just popped up on Instagram Live.
Just tap in, dude.
- We have to tap in.
- CP and PE Doran.
CP and PE Do are just.
(laughing)
- They're just chillin'.
- They're chillin' on Rumble.
(laughing)
- I just saw CP and PE going over on Triller.
I just saw them on Triller.
- CP on Periscope, that's me.
(laughing)
If you ever see me pop up on Periscope,
you'll be going, "Mom, I just saw CP on Periscope
"and it was fucking amazing."
Man, I bought that and the lady behind the counter
at the store that I bought that.
She said, "Oh, Caleb Bitts."
I put the first item down, my new Crocs.
But those--
That's how you do it?
You put one item down at a time
and then you build to the funniest one as you go?
No.
How do you do it?
I was just, I just put it down.
She picked them up and went, "Oh my God, I love these."
And then picked that up and looked at it
and went and just put it in a bag and just stopped talking.
Wow.
How much was this hat?
I don't even want to say it was way too much. Yeah, I was worth it cuz I wrote badass initials guess
Guess how much this is guess how much it is $11
More than that you spent on my CP hat
20 no way you're joking 25
No 35 40 50
- 55? - 58.
- This hat was $58? - Mm-hmm.
(laughing)
- I can't believe I believed that.
I was like, it feels nice, it feels like a nice hat.
- That hat was like $7.
I have no idea, I don't know 'cause it was at like
a fucking Beacon's Closet or whatever.
I have no idea who, somebody came in with that hat.
- And was like, I gotta get rid of this.
- And they were like, we have to buy this.
- This thing is so fucking badass, dude.
I need to buy this so quick.
Dude, I didn't know you were doing gifts. I would have got you something.
Well, it's fine that you didn't get me a gift, I guess.
You should get a matching hat that's your first initial, second initial, and the first two letters of your last name.
I think that would be an amazing combo.
Yeah.
And then we can get... Mommy comes back and we can see we have this CP and PETA hats.
[Laughter]
What's up?
Well, he did give me that hat that has the adjustable...
Oh yeah, you can just put that on that.
- Yeah, I can put my initials on that.
- Yeah, we can just rock like this.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- And that would be kind of,
it'd be CP and Pedo in the morning.
(laughing)
And we'll be doing like morning zoo stuff.
- Yeah.
- It's not a bad idea.
- Uh-huh.
- Well, that was amazing.
I haven't bought anything good recently.
- Yeah.
- I'm trying to think of what I,
you know what I've been doing all week?
- What have you been up to?
- Every single day I eat a pound of ground beef.
- You're doing that?
- No, no, I eat it with other stuff.
- Okay.
- But it's just a cheap way to eat a lot of meat.
And so I've been eating--
- You're trying to bulk up?
- Trying to get as big as a fucking truck.
- You know what-- - What?
- Could help you out?
- More meat?
- No.
- Working out instead of just,
I just eat the meat and play video games.
(laughing)
I don't work out.
- You know what could help you out?
- What?
- But I don't even think I can talk about it.
- You're talking about-- - I don't even--
- You think I should pop my legs?
- What does that mean?
- Pop 'em.
- What do you mean by that?
You want, do you think that I wanna fuck you
for to gain weight?
- You wanna pop me?
- I don't think I wanna, no.
- You wanna beat me?
- I can't talk about it because someone in here
on the production side may not want to acknowledge it
for some reason.
- Oh, wait.
Wait a second, okay.
So this is actually very interesting.
- Yep.
- Do you have this pulled up somewhere?
- I have it on my phone, I can bring it up.
- Okay, so Patrick, I did ask Patrick,
'cause I've already told Patrick this, it's all fake.
Like all of the, any revelation that I,
- So Patrick already knows everything about me.
So when I tell him that I've been eating ground beef,
he already is one step ahead and he actually designed
the entire meal plan for me.
And I'll let you explain it.
- Okay, so what it is is a 10 day healthy eating challenge
that will revolutionize, I mean,
not revolutionize or anything, it's mostly just I know--
- It will oosh-enize.
- It will oosh-enize, it'll oosh-enize,
and it will, I know you're trying to bulk up.
- Trying to get as big as the sun.
- You're trying to become jimungas.
- I'm trying to be--
- Which is a combination of gigantic and humongous.
- I didn't even catch that.
- Yeah, jimungas.
- Wow.
- Write that one down, Urban Dictionary.
- Yeah, put that in the UD.
- Jimungas.
- Yeah, that's gonna be probably the new big word.
- So this is the 10 day healthy eating challenge, okay?
- Yeah, so let me hear it.
- This is day one.
- I haven't heard this yet, he told me that he did it.
And by the way, we tried to bring this up to Jubio
for some reason, he doesn't wanna have anything to do with it.
- He just won't even look at me when I talk about it.
- So Patrick and him have been beefing,
they have not been talking, you know, speaking of beef.
- I have to text him through a telegram.
- He's been texting me, well, he's been texting me
to text Jubio, he said, here, I'll read it.
Do you have that pulled up, though?
- Yeah, I have it, I have it right ready.
- Patrick said, I'm not talking to Jubio
until he recognizes my challenge.
I'm at the office, he sent me I'm at the office
so that I could let Jubio know--
- That we're ready. - That we're ready.
- So here's the 10 day healthy eating challenge.
Breakfast, fruit salad with a mix of seasonal fruits.
One candy cane.
Lunch, a green salad with leafy greens,
mixed veggies, and grilled chicken.
- Okay.
- Snack, a handful of raw almonds and a cup of green tea,
which--
- I already have a cup of green tea.
- He's already got it.
- This is sounding so healthy so far.
- Dinner, baked salmon, roasted veggies, one candy cane.
- That sounds amazing.
- Yeah.
Day two, scrambled eggs with whole grain toast,
avocado slices, one candy cane.
A quinoa salad with cherry tomatoes as a lunch,
cucumber, feta cheese, and a light vinaigrette.
One candy cane.
For a snack, a sliced apple with almond butter.
Dinner, grilled chicken breasts
with steamed broccoli and brown rice.
Two candy canes.
- Wait, are you saying candy cane?
- Yeah.
Day three, a smoothie bowl with Greek yogurt,
mixed berries and granola.
Two candy canes.
Lunch, a turkey and avocado wrap with a whole grain tortilla.
Snack, grilled carrot sticks and hummus.
Dinner, shrimp skewers with mixed grilled veggies.
four candy canes.
- Okay, wait, can I just stop you really quickly?
This sounds to me like a lot of seafood so far.
- Well, that's 'cause of the proteins.
- Okay, that's fine, yeah, continue, sorry.
- What day was I on?
- Three, you just finished three.
- Okay, day four, a veggie omelet with spinach,
mushrooms, and peppers, two candy canes.
Lunch, a lentil soup with whole grain crackers,
two candy canes.
Snack, two candy canes.
Dinner, grilled salmon with mixed veggies
and a side salad, two candy canes.
Day 5, breakfast, Greek yogurt with mixed berries and honey, 3 candy canes.
Lunch, a grilled chicken salad with mixed greens, avocados and cherry tomatoes, 2 candy canes.
Snack, 1 candy cane.
Dinner, grilled steak with roasted sweet potatoes and green beans, 4 candy canes.
Day 6, oatmeal with almond milk, sliced banana and cinnamon, 3 candy canes.
Lunch, a turkey and cheese sandwich on whole grain bread with mixed veggies, 3 candy canes.
I can't eat bread, I can't eat bread, I'm gluten free.
I'm sorry. I'm maybe just a little bit free. Yeah. Yeah.
Snack sliced cucumber with tzatziki sauce, three candy canes.
Those don't go together.
What?
I don't. I'm never going to eat sliced cucumber with tzatziki.
With tzatziki.
But there's already sliced cucumber.
It just doesn't go together.
Okay. So I guess just a spoonful of tzatziki and three candy canes.
You would eat chips with tzatziki or put it on something.
I'm not going to use it. Like, why would I add more cucumber?
Okay. All right.
Sorry.
there. Dinner, baked chicken breast with roasted Brussels sprouts and three candy canes. Day
seven, a veggie scramble with spinach, onions, and tomato, three candy canes, lunch, a tuna
salad with mixed greens and whole grain crackers, three candy canes, a sliced pear for a snack,
handful of walnut, three candy canes, dinner, grilled shrimp tacos with gluten-free tortillas,
avocado, and candy cane salsa, five candy cane salsa. Day eight, a smoothie with Greek
Greek yogurt, mixed berries, spinach, and almond milk.
Lunch, a quinoa and black bean bowl with avocado and salsa.
- Oh, this is my favorite day so far.
- Snack, sliced apple with peanut butter.
- Mmm.
- Dinner, baked salmon with steamed green beans
and 16 candy canes.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Day nine.
- Okay, there's two more days?
- It's the 10 day healthy eating challenge.
- Oh, okay, you're right, I forgot what it is.
Day nine, scrambled eggs with whole grain toast
and four candy canes.
Lunch, a Greek salad, mixed greens,
feta cheese, olives, and four candy canes.
Snack, six candy canes.
Dinner, four candy canes.
Day 10, five candy canes.
- Wait, that's the breakfast?
- Breakfast, five candy canes.
Lunch, five candy canes.
Snack, a grilled chicken Caesar salad
whole grain croutons. And for dinner, ten candy canes.
Wow.
So that's the ten day healthy eating challenge.
You know what, I would barely call that a diet because it seems like I would be able
to eat everything I want on a diet. So I don't know.
And for some reason, Juvio is so apprehensive to acknowledge this. What?
- Whoa, okay, and now he's lashing out.
- Now he's lashing out with his production stuff.
- Great, we get it, you're God, okay?
- Yeah, we get it, you're in control of us
all the time, constantly.
- Great, yeah.
Don't do that.
- Don't make it flash.
- Don't make the word racist flash.
- Don't make it flash over me.
Jubio, can you, why are you so apprehensive
to even acknowledge the 10 day health study?
- Because this is complete nonsense.
You're not a serious person.
- How is that not, how is that,
- Okay. - How is that unsteer,
a grilled chicken Caesar salad with whole grain croutons?
- This guy doesn't like shrimp skewers.
- Oh. - Or something.
- Yeah, is it 'cause of the seafood?
- There is a lot of seafood, I will say that.
If you're not into that kind of stuff.
- That's true, are you like allergic to shellfish?
'Cause I'm-- - I'm just not gonna
acknowledge it until you do it.
- Okay, okay, I'll do it.
Me and Caleb will do the 10 day healthy eating challenge.
- Fuck it, I'll do it right now.
I'll do the whole, I'll do all 10 days.
- Look, he's already starting with the green tea.
- Yeah, guess who started it today?
Me. - Yep.
- And I'm about to get shredded.
- He's about to get swole as fuck.
- This is gonna be the new Weight Watchers,
the new Atkins diet.
- Yeah, and if you're not on this ship right now,
- Yeah, you're about to be.
- You're about to be, 'cause it's about to set sail.
- Yeah, and you could lose upwards of fucking 40 pounds
in a month doing this.
- You know who did it?
- Who?
- I don't know.
- Wait, wait, hold on, you are looking suspiciously trim.
What'd you clock in at today on the scale?
- 110.
- 110 pounds because of this new diet.
- Yeah, because of the 10 day healthy eating challenge.
- I have to fucking tell you.
- You lose 10 pounds in 10 days.
- You weighed 120 before this?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Well, I started this months ago.
- Oh, so you've been doing it for many 10 days.
- I've been doing it a long ass time.
- And none of us noticed--
- I used to weigh, guess how much I used to weigh?
- How much?
- 380.
- 380 pounds you used to weigh.
- At my heaviest.
- At five foot five.
- Yeah.
- You weighed 380.
- Five foot nine.
- Or whatever.
You weighed 380 pounds.
That's mighty hefty.
- Yeah.
- But you've been doing it,
and this is what a lot of people
don't understand about diet.
If you do these crash diets,
you're gonna fail.
- You're gonna fail.
- You're gonna fail because as soon as you get
to the end of that low carb, 1,000 calorie a day diet,
you're gonna immediately want Oreos.
You're gonna be reducing.
- The craziest thing about this diet,
every single day, every single,
'cause I didn't even talk about portion size or whatever,
every single day you were eating
close to 5,000 calories a day.
- Really? - Yeah.
Because of the portion sizes,
but it tricks your body into thinking
that you're hibernating.
So it needs to, so it's gonna trick your body--
- So it's gonna start burning, it's like ketosis.
- Yeah, it's burning fat because it thinks
you're like dead asleep.
- Some kind of kynosis that puts you into.
- Yeah.
- So that's what I love about this diet also,
is that you kind of can eat what you want,
but there's so much protein in it,
that's the trick of the diet,
there's so much protein in it,
that your body is,
protein's the most thermogenic macronutrient.
Did you know that?
- I'm a nutritionist.
- Oh, and I know you are, I know you are.
So of course you know that.
So you're eating all this protein,
and so your body's just burning,
It takes more calories to burn that,
to use that energy, to process that energy.
- Yeah, you're telling me stuff I learned in--
- I'm just explaining for these lay people, right?
Where did you learn that, by the way?
- Lakes Region Community College in Laconia, New Hampshire.
- Where you studied nutrition.
- Where I studied nutrition, yeah.
- Wow, yeah, see, and I think the only thing
that's lacking here is some kind of
accompanying workout plan that we could sell on a DVD.
- That is such a good fucking point.
- You know, maybe something like--
- That is an amazing point.
- And that kind of brings me to my idea,
which is a full workout, full workout plan,
that really just entails you every single day,
all I want you to do is spend about four hours skiing.
Every day.
If you spend about four hours skiing, you will see--
- Honestly, this is perfect for, I mean, you know,
I don't know if you know anything about New Hampshire,
but we have the White Mountains.
- Oh yeah, that's amazing.
- I could have been skiing every single day
when I was studying this program.
- Yeah, I think you could've--
- I could've been going up to Killington,
I could've been going up to Loon
and just skiing my fucking ass off.
- Four, five, six hours of that.
Then that's, by the way, that's,
and a lot of people think of skiing as just a workout.
I think that eventually you get a kind of a skiing high.
- Oh yeah.
- Where you've been skiing for so long
that you start feeling good and actually enjoying it.
- There is footage, and I think you may remember it,
there is footage of a man skiing so much
that his body was set on fire
from how much he was skiing because of the friction.
- Really?
- Because of the friction, yeah.
- Well, that's the danger of a skiing high, I think.
- And they used the clip in the intro
to Malcolm in the Middle.
- That's the danger of the skiing high.
- Which, I mean, you know, that's why you need,
so, I mean, you see the footage of that guy.
- Yeah. - Look at him.
He's skinny as a twig.
- Yeah.
- He's skinny as a twig.
- Because he's already burned all his calories
and now the body's just burning itself.
- But that's 'cause he's not on this diet.
- Yeah, 'cause this is a high--
- When you lose 10 pounds in 10 days, yes,
but when you combine it with skiing,
you're building up muscle.
He's not like--
- Total body recomposition is what they call it.
- He's not getting like any muscle at all.
The guy is not muscular.
He's almost as skinny as his ski.
- And he seems like a fucking twat.
- Yeah. - The way that he acts
in the video.
- He's a total douche nozzle.
- He seems like a todger. - He's a fuckwad.
- He seems like a todger to me.
- He's a fucking fuckwad.
- He's a fuckstick.
I just don't like him that much.
- I'd call him fuckface von clownstick.
- Yeah, if I was into that.
- Clownsticks, 'cause he's holding two ski sticks.
- Did you know that I always thought that
that was Trevor Noah that came up with that.
That was Jon Stewart that said fuck face on clowns.
- Oh yeah, I've seen that.
- Dude.
- Jon.
- Jon, don't hurt him.
- Don't hurt him, Jon.
- He's already down, don't kick him while he's down.
- I was under the impression, and I thought--
- He's in jail right now.
- And I just thought, I didn't even know Jon Stewart
did comedy, I thought he was a director.
- Yeah.
- And then it turns out that he actually
completely owned Donald Trump.
- The president, no less.
and I had to go to the New York court today
to settle some business.
I'm not gonna get so into that.
That's my personal stuff.
- Which is why I gave you your gift.
- Yeah, which is very, very nice of you, thank you.
But there was a million people there
and they all had the cameras pointed
and I said, "Guys."
- No photos.
- It's not that big of a deal.
- No photos, please.
- It's not, everybody parks in front of a school bus
every once in a while, right?
You don't have to come and take
all these celebrity photos of me.
- They were waiting, 'cause I mean--
- But apparently--
- You can't see what he's wearing under this table,
but they were trying to get that snatch shot.
- They did--
- They were waiting to see his sliz
while he's getting out of his Escalade.
- I did actually get street fashion photo'd today.
- Really?
- Yeah, and the guy, it was while I was running,
'cause I was late for an appointment at the court,
and a guy took a photo, I like saw him,
and I was like, dude, this guy's gonna,
he's gonna at least talk to me or look at me.
Like, you know when you just see a dorky white guy
and you're like, this guy's gonna be way too comfortable
and like-- - Stopping you.
- Yeah, well-- - I got stopped today too.
A guy said, "We're trying to stop people
"who look friendly."
And I said, "Man, I can't do this right now."
- It was that kind of thing.
It's like the only reason this guy would be in this area
is because he's doing something
where he wants to stop guys
and stop them and get in their way.
And so I'm running and he takes a photo of me
out of nowhere and says, "There he is."
And dude, I lost my shit.
Yeah, you screamed at him?
No.
I just kept, I ran, even.
But basically for me, that's losing my shit.
Yeah.
A lot of people would assume that I'm somebody
who gets into traffic and is, I'm honking the horn.
I'm scared to go outside.
I don't wanna be out there.
Every time I go outside, I'm thinking.
Agoraphobia, you have?
I thought that was something about going underwater. No. But I am going outside
every single day. I'm scared of antifa and Molotov cocktails. Especially today. Yeah.
At the New York City courthouses. And the thing is I look like Trump. Let's be real. I look
pretty similar. If you had his hair. If I had his hair and his. You look exactly like
him. Pretty much like Dead Ringer. And I had a hat on so they couldn't tell. Yeah. So that's
That's what I was a little bit worried about,
is maybe some sort of assassin-style killer
was going to walk up to me and say,
"This one's for freeing Kodak Black
"and put 10 bullets into my chest."
Yeah.
But luckily, it was just a nerd took a photo of me.
That's what happens in New York, honestly.
It's basically as crazy as--
Just this fucking crazy melting pot.
It is fucking crazy, dude.
Speaking of melting pots and diets, food,
here, we have a list today.
- Oh yeah.
- We have a list today of--
- Will you please pull up the list?
No, we don't want that photo.
- These are the top 10 crazy ways
to get free food in the UK.
- Wait!
This just says weird stuff on it.
- Yep, it's weird stuff.
It's definitely weird stuff.
- This is amazing because we do a lot of these lists
and a lot of people say, you can't use these as sources
when we submit these for peer review and stuff.
but this is actually, luckily, this has been fact-checked.
- Look at that bottom right corner.
Fact-checked by Jamie Frater.
- Jamie Frater, who if you know anything about fact-checks,
this guy is the Pinocchio giver of Pinocchios.
- Jamie Frater is basically the truth,
they call him Jamie Frater the truth raider.
- Yeah, they do call him that.
And he's been working as a Pinocchio giver for--
- Night and day.
- Night and day, for one night and one day.
So he's basically an expert.
So let's get into this.
- Yeah, so this is the top 10 crazy ways
to get free food in the UK.
- Yeah.
- Some say there's no such thing as a free meal,
but those people just haven't tried hard enough.
- Let me tell you real quick,
guess who says there's no such thing as a free meal?
- Who?
- The Tories.
- Yep.
Those fucking bell ends.
We have Dunkin' Donuts mics today.
- Holy fuck.
- And we're about to dunk on these donuts in the UK
with our fucking riffs. - They do say donuts.
You fucking donut. - You donut.
- Okay, continue. - You fucking donut.
- The ancient Romans said that the public
could be entertained with bread and circuses
and giving away free food has always been a good way
to ensure popularity.
Over the centuries in the UK,
over the centuries the UK has built up a huge number
of traditions that result some lucky people
ending up with free food.
- Wow.
- 2020 has been a tough year for everyone,
so here are the top 10 ways you can get fed for free.
- Logan Paul vibes.
- Logan Paul, we circled it back.
- Yeah.
- We circled that shit back.
All right, let's look at number 10 here.
St. Briavelle's.
- What's that?
- That is a church in St. Briavel's.
You will get pelted with bread and cheese
because of some tradition.
A vicar is invited to deliver a sermon
in which they only get paid
if the congregation cheers at the end.
Then in tradition dating from the 12th century,
the locals take baskets containing small cubes
of cheese and bread to the top of the wall,
known as the pound wall,
and dole climbers then gather at the base of the wall
and wait for the food to rain down on them.
Some people use upturned umbrellas
to ensure that they catch something
without the food touching the ground.
- They are so stupid.
- This is some fucking Wallace and Gromit bullshit.
- Use a bucket!
- Use a bucket, use a trampoline to bounce the food back up.
- Into your house.
These people are dumb as--
- Dumb morons.
- They're dense.
I'll say it, they are dense.
- Strangely, most don't actually eat the bread or cheese.
They're not even eating the fucking food.
They put them in little match boxes like they're borrowers.
- That is awful.
- This town, St. Briavels,
should be called the borrower's large.
- The borrower, what do you mean, like they're big borrowers?
- Yeah.
- But that's not a borrower at all.
- That is some borrower-ass shit.
What would a borrower's ice box look like?
A match box with a tiny ice cube in it.
- Oh, that's true.
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
- And they put them under their pillows.
They put the cheese and stuff under their pillows
to allow people to dream about the future.
- Man, honestly, this country is over.
This country, our country, the UK, is over.
- It's completely over.
- I don't want anything to do with it anymore.
- Can you imagine?
- I'm never going back.
- Can you imagine being like the ruling empire for years?
- Yeah, I can imagine that.
- And you're doing all this kind of dumbass little bullshit
with umbrellas and cheese.
- Dude, they just fell off in such a major way.
- They fell off hard.
- They used to go into every single country.
- They used to make the Irish slaves.
- They would slave the Irish, they would go into--
- And they did that to the Indians.
- They would go to every single--
- Pretty much every single country was their slave.
- At one point, and they had every single island,
and they were sitting there
and they were eating coconuts and shit,
and they all were dressed up like Monopoly clothes.
And then the whole place fell off,
and now you have what, Sherlock, Benedict Cumberbatch?
- Yep, that's pretty much all they have.
They're one export.
- Fuck that guy.
- Yep.
- I don't, and also, oh--
- He looks like, he smells like milk.
Guess what we made, a witty show.
Suck my balls.
- You know what, they do, they do.
- Hey, here's an idea, UK.
Okay, what are TV channels in America?
What are they?
- 200, 206.
- 200, 206, AMC, Comedy Central.
Right, they have names.
You go over there. - And we have a lot more.
- Channel 5, shut the fuck up.
- Channel 4, The Beeb.
- Yeah.
- The Beeb.
- Fucking kill yourself, bro.
- The Beeb's, fucking Justin Bieber-ass TV shows.
- It's worse than that.
I just think if you're gonna make a TV channel
and purport to be somebody who's creative enough
that somebody should watch what you make,
I think you can come up with something
a little better than a number.
Am I right?
- But that Mr. Bean is funny though.
- Mr. Bean is above everything, the whole thing.
- Mr. Bean is not British. - Mr. Bean is the last thing
that they did.
- He's not British, he's Bean.
- That's what I think.
He's everybody.
- He's everyone.
There's a Mr. Bean in every country.
- Oh yeah, except America.
- We've discussed this, yeah.
Who is America's Mr. Bean?
I don't know.
(imitates farting)
(laughing)
- Number nine, farthing loaf day.
Yeah, farting loaf day in regards to your king,
that farting loaf.
- Who's your king now?
- Charles.
- Chuck.
- Chuck, King Chuck.
- If I met him, you know, I'm such a fucking
get a beer with these guys type dude.
I'm such a salt of the earth guy.
I'd meet him and say, hey, nice to meet you Chuck,
I'm Caleb.
- Yeah.
- And he'd probably--
like, "Holy heavens."
- Ewok.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
(grunting)
- He'd do that.
He wouldn't even say anything.
- Did you see the video of the inbred people?
- No, I gotta look that one up.
- Dude, it's fucking really sad.
- Was it nice seeing your family on TV?
- So, what's Farthing Loaf Day?
- In Kittermeister, an old widow
lived on Church Street,
left a sum of money in her will
to ensure there is always a sense of community on the street.
Unfortunately, the name of this generous old maid
has been forgotten.
On a midsummer eve, anyone who was born on the street
was welcome to come and join a feast
that was known as Farthing Loaf Day.
Unfortunately, the money ran out due to bad investment,
but John Brecknell of Church Street,
whose name is remembered, left 150 pounds
to the charity in 1776.
Yeah, 1776, the year they lost their greatest colony.
- That's right.
- Fuck y'all.
He wanted a Tum Penny plum cake.
- God, a Tum Penny plum cake.
- He wanted a Tum Penny plum cake
- That's an amazing name. - To be given to every child
and unmarried woman on the street, as well as the bread.
He also gave pipes, tobacco, and ale
to the men who he met in friendship.
- Wow, that's adorable.
- A Tup Penny plum cake.
- How fucked up is it that these days
you can't even leave money on the street
for people to take because people will take it?
- People will take it and they will spend money
on Tup Penny plum cakes.
- Yeah, fuck that.
- They should be given out for free.
- What's a Tup Penny?
That's two. - Tup Penny is half a penny.
- Oh, it's half a penny. - No, that's a hay penny.
- That's me with my fuckin' neighbor.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Penny.
(laughing)
I don't know.
- Number eight, Tishborne Dole.
- What's that?
- Um, well, we'll find out.
- Why do you, you can't just say all the,
I mean, just get to it.
- Tishborne Dole.
When Lady Mabella Tishborne lay dying in the 13th century,
she asked her husband for a relatively minor favor,
distribute food to the poor.
Her husband agreed, but on one somewhat harsh condition,
he would provide land for corn to be grown on that,
to be grown on that would be used to make bread for the needy.
This must be Queens English spelling.
Or I may honestly just have dyslexia.
- Yeah, I mean, I'm looking at it right now
and I'm gonna be completely real with you, Patrick.
Everything is spelled in a normal American way.
And you made the text just about as big as it would go.
- Yeah.
- So, but--
- I forgot my glasses because I, again,
was on a shopping spree and I found an amazing hat for you.
- Yeah, that was very, very sweet of you.
He would provide land for corn to be grown
and that would be used to make bread for the needy,
but he would only provide as much land
as a sick lady could crawl around
while holding a burning torch.
Miraculously, Lady Mabella managed to cover 23 acres
and that land is still known as the crawls today
and provides flowers for the Tishporn Dole,
which is given out on every Lady Day.
- This is the worst country in the world.
- The Tishporn Dole given out on Lady Day.
- Lady Day.
- In the past, loaves of bread were given out,
but today anyone who attends will be given a measure
of flour to bake with for themselves.
- Wow, so they even downgraded it.
- It went woke.
- Yeah, they woke it because they're like--
- They went woke.
- What if somebody has a gluten intolerance allergy?
- Yep.
- Right?
- Mess the hell up.
- I'd like to dump a bunch of,
you know what I would love to show them?
- What?
- Is the pure power of American craftsmanship.
- Yeah.
- And I would like to dump fucking 50 mags of AR-15 bullets
directly into all the flour and see just the dust
go everywhere, you know?
It'd be really cool.
I'm showing them true American ingenuity,
true American strength.
- Yeah.
- I'm going in there with my flamethrower
from the Boring Company.
- That's right.
- I'm burning up that field
and I'm sending it to the moon.
- That's right.
- In a doge rocket.
- Oh, you like the Office UK version?
Try this, pop in the VHS, ridiculousness, right?
And then they're watching fucking amazing videos.
- I'm walking around there, I'm dressed up like Jim Halpert.
- That's right.
doing this yeah yeah you're not allowed to do that in the UK by the way yeah and
all you know what else you're not allowed to do there is have a Stanley in
the show because they are racist and they did not have a Stanley it was no Stanley
there was no Stanley Stanley no Darryl yeah big fucking surprise see this I have
my arms crossed and I'm tapping my feet Ricky Gervais yeah so suck on that great
Ricky Gervais is almost the, I mean we'll say it's a pretty brave soldier on the frontier
of Wokeness and SJW-ness.
But I think maybe he could have put one Stanley.
You're right.
I think if they did have a Stanley over there, his name would probably be Jefferson.
It would probably be Jefferson or Stanford or...
Bluntly.
Bluntly, crips.
Yeah, blackly.
(laughing)
Or something like that.
'Cause that's how racist they are.
- So then this next one here is scrambling cakes.
- Okay.
- And this one is about,
if you were lucky enough to live in Twickenham in 1367,
you might have been eligible for a lovely dole of free food.
- What an amazing-- - Some peas or beans.
Some peas or beans.
- What an amazing sentence.
If you were lucky enough to live in Twickenham in 1367.
- A dole of free food. - That's my version
of Midnight in Paris.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- 'Cause I'm like, I'm like, "Oh, you know, it's okay here,
"but if only I could be in Twickenham in 1367,
"have peas and beans."
- And then you like turn the corner
and you're on some like shitty fucking like town.
- Yeah, it's just a bunch of--
- You're in some shitty town,
there's like some guys throwing
his chamber pot out the window.
- Yeah, it hits me right on, I go, "Oh, this is amazing."
- Yes, finally. - And I'm there with
fucking Margot Robbie or something.
- And someone's like, "Get your dole!"
- Yeah. - "Come get your dole!"
- Peas and beans. - Peas and beans for me.
- Unfortunately, this food distribution was stopped,
but a tastier one was started when the two great cakes
were tossed to the poor each Easter Sunday.
But as will happen when you throw two cakes to a crowd,
a riot would often result.
- Why was cake so, people loved cake.
- Well, this is the British cake.
This is the British cake, where it's just like a cake
with no frosting or anything.
- Yeah, so why is it, I feel like any time I hear
some story about, like two cakes,
people are doing a riot for a cake.
- Well, I mean, you gotta think about
twicking 'em in 1367.
- You're eating peas and beans.
- You're eating peas and beans, yeah.
That's pretty much all you have is food.
- I don't want cake.
- Food that's that big, right?
Now imagine that food maximized 10 times
the size of a cake.
- Well, also, this is before GMOs as well,
so the peas were probably--
- Peas were probably the size of a kidney stone.
- I never thought about that.
Peas were so small.
- Peas are small now.
Beans are small even.
- I'm probably bigger than a pea.
- Beans were the size of peas.
- Yep.
- And peas were probably the size of fucking nothing.
- Now the beans are bigger and the peens are getting,
the peens.
- Yeah, peens are getting larger.
- The peens were small.
- Yeah.
- Peens were not even beans.
- Yes, I've heard this.
- And now it's tall.
- Yeah, I think.
- And that's an old British riddle.
(laughing)
- What else happened in Twickenham?
- A later tradition in Twickenham
may be related to the scrambling for cakes and loaves.
The Vicar's Day charity saw a local priest climb a church tower
and throw loaves of bread to children below.
Their scrambling for food was apparently sufficiently decorous.
Yes. I don't know what the hell that is.
What? A bunch of ...
Some Catholic priest with a fishing rod throwing ...
Throwing bread down and then ...
Just to kids and try to catch it. Yeah.
Yeah, come on. I don't ...
What is decor ... Oh, the number six is the Wayfarer's charity.
Which this ... Wayfarer's charity sounds like a book
that you see your uncle reading really hard.
Yeah, one of those paperbacks from Walmart.
- He's got a paper bag and he's just going.
- Yeah, and he reads it in like one day.
- Yeah, and he's like, he puts it down,
never thinks about it again.
Never thinks about that fucking book.
- No, it was just a story.
- Yeah, one other time in his life.
If free food is good, then free booze is even better.
It used to be that a traveler crossing Britain
could expect to find charity if they needed it
in most towns and villages.
Religious institutions fed people
and often offered them accommodation.
After the dissolution of the monasteries, however,
this tradition mostly died out.
In Winchester, however, there is still one place
where anyone who wants it can turn up.
- Wait.
- Yup.
- I want to.
- Turn up on a weekend.
Turn up and get a piece of bread and a mug of beer.
Yeah, you give me a piece of bread and a mug of beer,
I'm definitely gonna turn up.
- That's right.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm gonna get crazy.
- I'm gonna make it a problem.
- Beer is one thing.
I might turn up a little bit on the beer.
- Yeah.
- What the bread?
- What the bread, though?
- Wait.
- Woo-wee.
- I'm gonna eat that.
Hospital of St. Cross and Elms House of Noble Poverty was a charitable house
founded in 13th in the 1130s a
French monk who brought over the custom of distributing bread and wine to the poor but beer was thought to be more of an English
drink
Today if you want to get a small meal for free all you have to do is request it at the Porter's Lodge
Alternatively you could become one of the 25 brothers of the house
Receive an apartment to live in at a reduced rent and a subsidized two-course lunch
And that's so sick you can just fucking like if you're just related to this family you can just live
In a house and get to two courses for lunch a day
I would say that's how a lot of families are though. Yeah, they get to live in a house and get to me
Yeah, but 25 brothers. Well. This is a fuck. This is an amazing movie. Yeah, but 20 foot you've seen four brothers
I have uh-huh now since you multiply multiply that by
Add one then multiply it by five
25 brothers and that's the tagline of the movie
That's a good idea for brothers was about four brothers
Like killing there was a fifth. There's a fifth brother in four brothers
I think there's only something and then they go and look for the guys who killed the fifth brother
So imagine if that fifth brother stayed alive, okay, and they all live in one big-ass
Apartment together with four sets of clones with four sets of clones, and they just drink beer and eat bread all day
Well not all day. It says I have one
Mug of beer and one piece of bread one loaf okay, so one by the way. That's a terrible ratio. I
Don't want a whole loaf of bread ever
Let alone a whole loaf of bread not with one beer to wash it down
I'm drinking one sip of beer for like four slices of bread that is like
The first course of a Texas Roadhouse meal. What are you talking about?
That's not a whole I'm not eating that whole loaf at Texas Roadhouse by the way if you're by yourself
No, no and also. I'm not a tech. I don't like the bread there
I like the peanuts and if we're talking bread
I'll get brown bread and Ruby Tuesday's or I'll get brown bread at Cheesecake Factory
They have brown bread at Texas Roadhouse. They've never told me about that you can get that there
Well, I didn't order that asshole. I ordered the normal. I just get what's normal, and then I get peanuts all right
Well, maybe you could order this the Butterworth dole that would look it's actually pretty good
You know what those are that is a bun with it looks like as custard on M&Ms on it
At the church in St. Bartholomew in Smithfield there are 21 widows who once provided with the sixpence
Each every good Friday the widows would wait in the churchyard where the coins were laid out on a tombstone
They would then walk over and take their dole
"No one can say who founded the tradition
"or when it began because of the paperwork
"the church was burned in the great fire of London in 1666."
- Scary.
- "Over time, fewer poor widows turned up
"to claim their coin and the charity died out
"when the money was left to retrieve the charity
"in the 19th century by G.W. Butterworth
"and came back as a distribution of both money
"and food to poor widows.
"When the widows once dried up."
- No way.
- "Dried up."
"When the widows once again dried up it,
the charity, what?
- That one's not on you.
- Yeah, what the fuck?
When the widows once again dried up it,
the charity changed to a free dole of hot cross buns.
- Wait, that's what those are like.
- That's hot cross buns.
- I've never, I didn't know those were real, man.
What's in a hot cross bun, do you know?
- Looks like M&Ms and a hot cross.
- But what is the, that's frosting, right?
- Yeah, I think it's probably custard.
Maybe it's tubby custard, dude.
- Custard is a food that just,
you don't get that much in the universities,
- Or the-- - Universities?
- Or the United States, I mean.
(laughing)
- Universities of America.
- The United States, that is more of a United Kingdom
kind of food.
We don't deal with custards here.
- Uh, Shake Shack may beg to differ.
- Well, but that's, brother, that is frozen.
I'm talking about, they eat that shit
straight out of the fridge, and it's yellow.
- It's yellow 'cause it's like, gone bad.
- It's yellow, no, it's got eggs in it.
- It's yellow, that's what custard is over there.
For us, we're thinking that that's gonna be
some delicious frozen treat.
- Basically it's an ice cream over there.
- They don't freeze that.
It's a full pudding.
- They're pretty, fuck off.
They're pretty lenient with what they call pudding
over across the pond too.
- That's true, black pudding and white pudding.
Is that what it is, right?
- I don't think there's a white pudding.
- Yeah, the sausages, there's white pudding, I saw this.
- I saw white pudding in my shorts when I woke up.
- No you didn't.
I had a dream.
- No.
- I had a dream that I was Dua Lipa's slave.
(laughing)
- Dua Lipa?
Her slave?
That was your dream?
- Number four, beating the bounds in Leighton, Busset.
(laughing)
- These are so bad.
- Bro, beating the bounds.
Edward Wilkes built 10 almshouses
to provide shelter for the poor in 1630
in memory of his father John.
When Edward died, he asked that beer and bread
be given out every Rogation Tide,
and the tradition of the Wilks Walk originated to honor him.
- The Wilks Walk.
- You know the Rogation Tide?
- I've been to every single one in my entire life.
- Oh yeah, I do a Wilks Walk every year.
- I grew up with Wilks Walks.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Yeah, well, Rogation days are often observed
with a beating of the bounds when a procession is made
around the borders of a parish to ensure
that the memory where the boundaries lay was continued.
On Rogation Monday in Leighton Buzzard,
"The procession leaves All Saints Church,
"passes the almshouses, and into the market square.
"To make it memorable, while the clerk reads
"from Edward Wilkes' Will, a choir boy
"is hoisted by its ankles."
- No, here's what I never wanna hear again.
Here's a word I never wanna hear again, parish.
- Yeah.
- Unless it has to do with--
- With the church?
Damn, you're getting atheistically awesome right now.
- I would like to see the church parish,
but when it comes to, it's called a county, okay?
I don't wanna hear about a parish.
Louisiana get the fuck out of my face you are a backwards at by the way
And I don't mean I don't know if anyone said this to you guys before in Louisiana. You look like a boot
Bro be careful, I'm sorry so you can someone's gonna. What are you gonna? Do you gonna put butter?
You're gonna. Give me butter people is Shreveport are gonna rise up and beat the fuck out of you
Yeah, they're gonna be
They're gonna shriek and fort they're gonna shriek and they're gonna
About stinking mad they are what I said about them because all that crawfish atoufee
They yeah, stop eating that bullshit get that out of your mouth rice is supposed to be chewy
Mm-hmm stop make it in a fucking pudding actually like that
I'm actually down with that
Buns and beer were once given out, but it was found beer made for two festive in event. Oh, and it was buns and lemonade
They're putting they're putting lemonade on a choir boys buns and over there. They need to chill
- They need to chill.
- It was stopped when thousands of buns were consumed
and the ladies of the parish could not keep up.
Now the buns are even out in church.
- The next one here, bull baiting.
- Bro.
- Guess what this one's about.
- Probably about boxing.
That's what I think, anytime I see meat hanging
from a thing I wanna punch it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's a good, I also wanna do that.
Sometimes charity, no matter how well intentioned,
can do harm.
When George Staverton died in 1661,
he left a sum in his will so that poor,
the poor people of Wokingham--
Wait, wipe it off the map.
Take it away from me.
We're going to go full preemptive strike on Wokingham.
Yeah.
I don't know if you guys have ever seen a little movie called
Hot Fuzz, but we will be doing that in Wokingham.
We're going in there two guns a blazing.
Yes.
Going to just--
[GUNFIRE]
--all over that damn town.
Yes, sir.
Fucking blue hair town of Wokingham.
I don't even want to see a--
wait, wait, Jubio, can you look up a picture of Wokingham
real quick?
Yeah, let's see it.
I do when I have a strong feeling that I know what exactly what this is gonna look like Williamsburg in 19 wait
Okay, so two dozen. Yeah. Yeah. Oh of course. That's let me guess. That's where the adults go to work
It's a playground and look they're feeding click go back over there
They're waiting a lion to all these kids to a lion wait go back one look at the name of this park
California Country Park in Wokingham, they're so woke. Oh, they're naming their shit, California
This is disgusting.
Joel Park, that's probably a girl's name.
That's probably a guy.
That's probably a guy who lives there.
Joel Park.
Cantley Park.
Bear Wood.
They think bears should be in the woods instead of the zoo.
The bears should be in the zoo.
Get the bears back to the zoo.
That's where the bears should be.
Wokingham Resident, I don't even want to see a picture
of these people.
I don't want to because I bet they have blue hair.
Oh my god.
This Wokingham resident has a headache
because of all the frickin' pronouns they have to hear.
- That is probably the only patriot
in the whole fuckin' parish,
and I don't even like to use that word I just said.
- And look.
- And look, that guy thinks it's cool
to be in a wheelchair in Wokingham.
(laughing)
- Look at this SJW with the blue hair.
- Well, and you might think,
oh, this person is probably in their 90s.
That guy's 15.
That's just what wokeness does to the human body.
That is a 15-year-old guy.
Don't-- or ignore the--
And look at his hair that he dyed silver.
Oh, and of course, they shop at REI.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
He has another Wokey.
OK, sorry.
All right, that's enough about Wokey.
Yeah, so basically what happened here
is that every year just before Christmas,
they would bring a bull into the center of town.
Oh, no.
And bull baiting was a practice where they would just
unleash like bulldogs and shit up to fight these bulls.
(laughs)
- Bulls versus dogs?
- Bulls versus dogs.
So the bulls, they saw tethered bulls pitted against dogs
in vicious fights.
Many dogs were gored to death before the bulls--
- Oh my god.
- The bulls eventually succumbed to their wounds.
Then their meat would be handed out to the hungry.
So they'd have a bunch of dogs in the middle of this town
just biting the shit out of this bull.
- And people's dogs are just flying everywhere,
breaking their necks and--
Oh my god, the bull is like horn into the thing,
into this dog.
And these are not, by the way,
these are not American bullies.
No, no.
These are basically still wolves.
Yeah, oh yeah.
So then they would just like,
then they finally stopped doing it in 1821.
Or maybe corgis now that I think about it,
'cause of the way they are.
'Cause of the queen.
Yeah, what is this next one here?
Thomasing?
What is Thomasing?
Thomasing is a tradition, blah, blah, blah.
It's also known as gooding, corning, doling,
washaling, Christmasing, gathering, mumping, moping.
So basically what you do is you go door to door
and you beg, sometimes you get booze.
Mostly it looks like you get potatoes and pudding and shit.
- Okay, I've been thinking about this for a long time.
There needs to be a year-round trick-or-treating for food.
- Yep, well this is Christmas trick-or-treating
and it's called Thomasing. - Oh shit, okay.
Well that's better.
Yeah, I guess a year-round--
I guess there was an old lady who tried to go out and do
Thomasing in the 90s.
She went mumping for spuds, and the farmer
told her to clear off.
And then she said, you're not going to get a good crop
next year, and then he didn't.
So that was a news story in the UK.
Yeah.
In the UK, they were like, an old lass
went mumping for spuds.
And the farmer told her to clear off.
And that's the biggest news story of the year.
Wow.
That is an amazing country.
- This happened, the thing, the reason--
- This is what UK Drill is about.
- Yeah, this is like, oh, I went mumping for spuds.
- Said clear off.
- Getting a tub, getting a tub coming in spuds, sluds.
- Yeah, and they don't have a gun, so it's the sounds of--
- SpongeBob, got the suds.
- I mean, what else is there to rap about, right?
- This happened, what I read is that this happened,
we didn't hear about this in the States because--
- And you didn't hear about this from me.
- The day after they did Diana.
- They did her dirty.
- They did her dirty in that car.
Somebody shot her through a window in that car.
- I don't remember, I honestly don't even know
who that is almost.
- Princess Diana?
- Barely 5% do I know who that was.
- I know that she danced with John Travolta,
but that's because my mom had a coffee table book
of John Travolta photos.
- You were thinking Uma Thurman.
- No, no, no, no.
- You're literally thinking of, like dance like this,
like back and forth in a club.
- In a 50's diner?
- Yeah, that was Uma Thurman.
That's not Princess Diana at all.
Princess Diana, Uma Thurman almost died.
Quentin Tarantino almost killed her with a movie
and that's why they don't work together by the way.
If anybody wants to Hollywood fact check me,
go ahead, I'll pass every test.
But yeah. - You're telling me.
- That's Uma Thurman.
- Quentin, or Princess Diana.
- She did not try to kill Bill.
- She doesn't have black hair.
- No.
- And she's not, you know.
- I mean she probably did.
- Yeah.
real reason she died. Oh, she overdosed in the car? I don't, I was, yeah, probably some
kind of fentanyl situation. And then she died, she killed her friend too. That's
sad. Yeah, it is pretty sad. She got flattened like a pancake. Yeah. And then number one
here is cheese rolling. Boy, this actually looks so fun. What this is, they fling
themselves down a hill and they just want to roll up the double Gloucester
cheese. Isn't that what Wallace wants? Wallace? Wallace and Gromit, he wants double Gloucester.
- Wallace wants bones, he's a dog.
- No, Gromit's the dog.
- What kind of name is Gromit for a dog?
- You think Gromit's the name of a man?
- More so than a dog, Gromit.
- You think that Wallace is the dog?
- I don't think, I know that he's the dog.
- No.
- Yeah, it's Gromit. - That's not true.
- It's Gromit.
- You're completely fabricating this.
- No, he's the, no, Gromit wants,
By the way, what is a better name for a guy
who's like fucking addicted to cheese,
such a slob, than Gromit?
- It's a dog's name.
- It's his last name.
Of course it's his last name.
- His name isn't, his name, his last name is not,
his name isn't Wallace Gromit.
- No, Wallace is the dog.
His name is probably--
- His name is Gromit Wallace?
- No, his name is, his last name is Gromit.
He goes by Gromit.
- What's the, what's his first name then?
- They don't say, it's kind of a mystery.
It's like the whole point of the show.
- The whole point of the show--
- Not the whole point.
the moon to get cheese.
Is Gromit the dog?
It says no.
Gromit is...
No, it says he is!
It says he's a beagle.
And he graduated from Dogwarts.
Okay, so you tell me...
Being a pun on Hogwarts.
Okay so...
Wikipedia...
Wait, that's Wikipedia.
Wikipedia is not a source, honey.
Gromit.
Oh look, there they are.
There's Gromit and Wallace.
Yeah, Wallace is the guy.
There he is.
That...
So they, they, uh, only one person can get the double Gloucester.
And, uh, no one knows when it first started, but during COVID,
they just rolled cheese down the hill.
I'd be at the bottom of that hill.
I'd be my bottom job, my top job and trying to eat the whole
everybody's screaming. You put your mask on, put your mask on.
Cause it was like probably at a time where I bet they know much about what was
going on.
Okay. I would like to say this to the UK people right now,
when you guys are wearing masks, we,
everybody in the United States was just pretending to.
- Yep.
- None of us actually wore that shit.
- We were so happy that you started putting your masks on
over there. - To cover that shit up.
- To cover up these things.
- Yeah, and by the way,
take it from two people with perfect teeth.
- Look at my teeth.
- You people are disgusting to us.
- There's nothing, there's not a single thing wrong
with any of my teeth.
- I really don't like that the--
- And here is the video of the cheese rolling.
- Okay, let's look at this real quick.
- 'Cause this is actually dope.
- It's a compilation.
a compilation of cheese rolling. Best Top! And it's from Best Top. Is it B-Stop or Best
Top? I think that's Best Top. Best Top. Okay, so there's a big hill. Uh huh. Oh my god. And
suggested as Big Parkour Fails compilation. This looks so incredible. Which I'm kinda,
I'm maybe gonna watch that later. Wait, people are already rolling. Or falling. Yeah, is
the point to roll down the hill? Yeah, oh these guys are getting really hurt, man. Yeah. Okay,
I don't man. I don't want to see this. These are probably migrant workers
Who are trying to make a quick buck or they are gonna resell the cheese?
Do you yeah, do you think that they have these people are dead?
Do you think that they have like rich guys in the UK who pay a migrant worker to roll down the cheese hill for them?
Definitely put your ID on them. Yeah, right
So legally I get the cheese looks like they have cheese rolling teams here
I'm kind of surprised that none of these people are like
600 pounds because that would be a they got a sperm rolling down the hill look at that
There's a sperm there's a spider man. Oh, that's Peppa Pig all right. You know what this is enough
We're gonna get flag for my yeah, this is this is enough. That's
All right, I guess that's the list we do we did another mommy's gone and mommy's gone mommy will be none the wiser
- A little wiser.
- Mommy won't know.
- Mommy won't know that the boys got stuff
in the podcast and they're doing a cheese list.
- Yep.
- Or they're doing a--
- Food list.
- Wait, let's hammer this down real quick.
- Mommy don't know that her podcast.
- No, mommy don't know that her sons are on
doing podcast songs and they're--
- And they got a new cheese wheel.
- There we go.
- Uh huh.
- And it's that simple.
- Thanks for watching, that's how it's done.
- It's that fucking simple.
- Bye.
- Bye bye.
Wait, do we have to, we don't know anything to plug.
No, get that off of me right now.