(upbeat music)
- I had two Diet Dr. Peppers this morning.
- We're back to the cable clap.
He's recovered enough that he can clap.
- He's not broken anymore.
- That is so exciting.
- You notice anything different about me, yeah?
- Pink earphones.
- Oh, you're bald now.
No, I don't.
- With those pink earphones
and your natural skin complexion.
- And I think you definitely have
- And this isn't a dig or anything mean.
- Just go ahead.
- You look like a cartoon pig.
- Yeah, no, that's not mean.
- And this isn't a dig or mean or anything either,
but you smell like shit today.
(laughing)
- Juvia, do you wanna unmute?
You have anything to say to me today?
No, he says no.
- He doesn't want to.
- Okay.
- Jubio, what's that last thing,
what's that recommendation there?
- Recommended on our thing?
- What have you been looking up?
Why is that recommended to you?
- That's what do you--
- Based on your searches.
- I don't think it is, I think that's just
a fucking news story.
- Oh, that's just a news story?
- You're acting like the only people
that ever read anything about Hitler
or like people who are Googling Hitler all day.
- Yeah, and I think that's what Jubio's doing.
- You think he sits on the work computer?
- You think he sits on Caleb's computer?
- It's also Caleb's computer.
- Yeah.
- He's like, "Yeah, what are you talking about?
"It's just a news story.
"What are you doing?"
He's not gonna look it up on his own computer.
Then people will get mad at him
when he types in H in Google and that pops up first.
- That's true.
Everybody, South America, oh my God.
- Yep, you're done for again.
- It's fucking over.
It's over for me. - There must be
like one of those, you know, like the ghost in the machine
from that Scooby-Doo movie, the electricity ghost.
- You guys do a two guy thing.
- Okay.
I still have a hard time turning to the right, so this is tough.
Yeah, you've got a fucked up neck still.
I'm just going to do this.
That is, that must suck so bad.
Can you imagine if you and me just had our own podcast where we just kind of like looked at each other in the eyes like this and talked?
We've done it a few times.
What would we do? They were probably pretty bad, right?
I think we, well, I was audited for Scientology.
Oh, dude, that was fun.
That was actually a fire ass episode.
Yeah, so.
- We never did pre though, we never did pre pandemic
or whatever, we never did just us, it was always just me.
- Yeah, you and me never just sat down and just talked.
- There was only one Mommy's Gone episode
when Mommy was gone.
- Mommy was not around, Mommy's busy.
- Mommy's got the belt and Mommy's gonna hit us
with the belt right now.
- It's kinda scary what Mommy's doing.
- When Mommy gets that belt up, you know I get scared.
- I went to New England this weekend
- Man, I think I miss New England so, so, so much.
- I'm literally, I'm so excited to open.
- New England is so much better than New York.
- I do.
- Yeah, I'm so excited to do that show in Boston.
- We went to this bar.
- I literally, I need to go back so bad, I miss it.
I wanna go to the TAM, I wanna recreate that fuckin' video.
- You have to.
- Three guys are screamin' the F word.
- We went to this bar, and there was a,
it was like, it wasn't even that late,
it was like 11 o'clock, and there was this guy,
We got there is there's a band playing as a pool table
And there's two guys playing pool one of them is like an old guy like you know guys are so old that they just look they
Have like black eyes permanently. Yeah, you know they have like purple around their eyes like stuff
There's really all the throwing up. They do every morning. It's got to be that
Yeah, just popped blood vessels from like trying to remember a birthday, and then this guy
he's sitting there, and he has like he has a predator like a really nice pool cue and
And he sucks, bro. This old man was fucking terrible. I've never seen a worse pool player,
but he was playing against this amazing, like, 35-year-old guy with skin like a wallet, who's
just like, was the drunkest I've ever seen anybody be. Just like a bar stool, like, New England guy.
And this guy would go down, he would miss a shot, and then he would just start dancing, just like,
"Ooh! Ooh!" Like, right in the old man's face. And they didn't know each other. So he's just
this random guy that was playing him.
And it was making me...
It was like a fucking nightmare.
It was like a nightmare where you can't like...
You get in a fight and your punches go in slow motion.
Because it was like, you want this guy to lose so badly.
And the guy that he's playing looks like he'd be a great pool player.
But he's just... The guy was like...
Choosing to shoot the wrong ball every time.
The old man. He didn't go over and coach him.
I'm imagining now a nightmare where...
Yeah, I'm playing pool and I'm horrible.
I'm losing to this guy and he's dancing in my face.
face and it's like this horrible nightmare and right when I think I can't
get any worse I look down on my hands and they're all like arthritic.
That guy was living an actual fucking nightmare.
He has dementia, he still thinks he's 16 at the bar.
He was like, you know how sad it is when an old guy is like still doesn't
really have it together? Yeah. They're like kind of like it's clear that they're
like ordering food and they're a little nervous or something. Like an old man with social
anxiety. That makes me so sad.
Dude, it's so fucked.
It's like, how is he not having it?
Do you know what's even...
French onions? No.
Oh, I'm panic ordering. You're fucking 80.
Same, similar thing. When an old person is like a hoarder, but you can tell they
didn't like become a hoarder because they got old.
Like they have stuff that's like they've just they've been like that.
They've lived in a house filled with newspaper and beer bottles since they were a
kid.
Scary.
Yeah.
Like that's what they're used to.
- Yeah, it's not that that's like an old person thing,
it's that they've been doing it for 80 years.
- Yeah.
- The idea of an old person like, yeah,
going to Starbucks and having the person they're with
order for them is like actually making me wanna cry.
- It's horrible.
- It's like the saddest thing I've ever even thought about.
- Oh my God.
- And just like an 85 year old guy--
- Doing that but then both of their fingers break.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- An 85 year old guy who goes to the movies
and the guy's like, "Enjoy the movie."
And he says, "You too."
And he's like, "Oh no."
Oh, no.
Well, that's yours.
The thing is that old guys--
He's going home, and he's dipping his quill in his inkwell,
and he's drawing a socially awkward penguin on a--
That's our crumb.
[LAUGHTER]
That is our crumb.
This guy was just like that, bro.
He was like--
Well, yeah, that's what I was going to say.
He kept stripping over himself, and he
tied his shoelaces twice because they just came untied.
It's just like old guys like that.
If you were a nerd in the '50s, you're still more--
You stuck with that.
You're like you're like our crumb though. You're like a guy who's just very vindictive
Like very like I fucking hate it. You know, you know how and like, you know how in like UHF
Weird Al is like the guy and he like forgets us to go out to dinner with his girlfriend
You know that like yeah of trope that like an old guy who does that I feel like usually that's like the old guy
You're like, oh, he's TC now. He's and he doesn't care and it's cool
But an old guy who can achieve being that kind of like forget like somehow I'm imagining
Like an old guy who's forgetful but you can tell it's not dementia at all and that he's just like completely just a fuck up.
Yeah, like imagine Mr. Bean was like on like Medicaid.
That's scary.
He is now, fucking old ass bitch.
Yeah, I don't think he's on Medicaid. I don't think he's in American citizenship.
He's on Medicide!
He's on the NIHA.
That's just a new phenomenon though. I don't think old people are afraid.
You're in fear of the future where there's going to be old people like that for sure.
Old people ordering at restaurants are so confident.
Yeah, that's what I mean. That's what's scary.
That's because people with social anxiety back in the 40s and 50s and 60s and 70s used to string
them up by their feet. Split their throats.
It's the same feeling I have when I used to watch a Larry King interview or whatever,
and he's 98 years old and all he talks about
is how scared he is of dying.
It's like, bro, that's not what I want to hear
when I'm a kid.
- No, yeah, it is, you are, I'm feeling a fear
that I never thought of before.
It really is bothering me to think about an old,
like, the way that I usually think about an old person
being a fuck up is like, oh, he's like a,
he's from a different time.
Like, yeah, he's like, he doesn't get how to interact
with his children.
- No, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Like my granddad's so much like that.
- Yeah, just, yeah, oh my god.
It's really terrifying.
Yeah.
And those are like, and now that I think about it, I think most old people are like that.
Like no old people have it figured out really.
Yeah.
They just, yeah.
Well, I mean, I think a good chunk of them do.
But like maybe even my grandpa, now I'm thinking back at like times when he just like said
shit that made no sense and I'm like, oh, maybe he just got so like overwhelmed and kind
of anxious that he just was weird, you know?
My grandpa, I mean I talked about my grandpa just forgetting my name, but like that, I
think he's the polar opposite.
Maybe he's also just stupid.
Yeah.
Like this idea of a stupid old person is pretty sad too.
I think it's the polar opposite guy you're describing, like the old man with social anxiety.
This is the jock.
The jock, my grandpa.
That's what I'm saying.
My grandpa was like, "Ah, Chris, whatever, the fuck."
Every old guy, I think they're the jock.
Yeah, me too.
Just because of the way that their skin looks.
Because jocks usually live longer.
Yeah.
- They killed themselves.
The jocks lived. - Yeah, they know how
scary the world is. - The jocks lived.
The jocks spread their seed to generations, right?
The jocks are the ones with all the grandkids.
- Yeah, the nerds never fucked.
- The nerds never got no damn pussy.
- No, they got sent overseas to do codes.
- Exactly. - Yeah.
- Yeah, they stayed in Vietnam.
- Yeah. - 'Cause they got there
and they were like-- - And they were like,
"Do you guys have anime?" - "Oh my God, wow.
"We should invent anime."
- I know it's the wrong country, don't worry about it.
(laughing)
The nerds are over there, man.
- The bears are still in Vietnam.
And you know what the worst part about the nerds in Vietnam
is, is that they're making all these fucking foodie videos.
- They're like weebs for fucking Vietnam in the 60s.
They're like, "Oh my God, is that a hole in the ground
"I can live in?
"That's amazing."
Like, crap.
Oh my God.
- Yeah, they were like that though, I bet.
- Yeah, there was definitely a lot of people
who probably just were, I think that--
- There was a lot of soldiers with glasses in Vietnam.
- Do you guys ever think about,
if you got forced to go into the military,
Would you go MIA?
Would you go AWOL?
- Dude, I would go AWOL immediately.
- I think I'd also go AWOL.
- I would probably do surgery on myself
and remove my hamstrings or something.
- I know somebody who went AWOL.
- What the fuck are you talking, why?
- What?
- Oh, to get out of.
- Yeah.
- But what if they were like--
- 'Cause anything, if I break my leg,
they're gonna be like, "You broke your leg."
But they're not gonna believe,
I'm gonna say, "I was born without hamstrings."
- And I just never noticed until today.
- Oh, and by the way, I hurt both the backs
of my legs recently, so if you see two little stitches,
- I hit myself on a razor scooter.
- But what if you fuck up, right?
What if you go like Axel from Twisted Metal,
you put your arms into some wheels--
- Oh yeah, and then they're like,
"Yeah, you front line!"
- Yeah, yeah.
- "We actually wanna clone you!"
- You actually will now be the prototype
for every other person, right?
- That's true, I guess I would run away from the army
unless the offer they're making me is that,
"We want you to join the army
"and we're also gonna clone your genome for eternity."
(laughing)
And you're gonna be, the entire army is gonna be you.
- Yeah.
- I would do that in a heartbeat.
Most famous guy in the world.
- Do you think we'll ever be at a place where--
at a place where I've been America if you had wheels for our I feel like a turret
on your belly hundred thousand Captain America yeah you'd have a turret in your
belly that was like a Gatling gun Wow you're rolling down the bar and then we
would we would we would fucking we would we'd go to the bar after we take out the
whole bar everyone's everyone's out because we're just we well we wouldn't
kill them we can't stop shooting your belly gun but we would just just imagine
every time you breathe in and out of shooting a new bullet imagine you go to
the bar on the base, the military base, and it's just all you.
Damn.
Just all singing Irish drinking songs.
Everyone trying to say I'll buy you the next round.
Yeah, everything in unison.
I'll buy you the next round.
Do you guys ever think, this is a terrifying concept if you love violence, do you ever
think that all of our wars will be fought in virtual reality?
No.
No, because you're good. It's like it's like training for that. It's like when you
play with a cat with like a laser pointer, right? They don't feel fulfilled
because they didn't have something they could like sink their teeth into or their
claws and like pretend that they're killing. Because they think it's a lady
bug. Yeah, yeah. It's a bug that they're chasing but it's not. It's just a little
red dot. True. Here's what I'll say and this is a little bit maybe of a history
lesson. But you guys are going to need it. Because wars, the soldiers, I think the soldiers
have always been, those are the stupid guys and they just say, you guys can fight each
other, whatever, you guys go out there, we'll just send you over there to fight, go play
outside. Why do they always send the poor? The real wars, what it's always been, it's
about spies. And the spies are the top level and the spies are going back and forth and
stealing documents and stealing cars and stealing paintings and back and forth.
They're opening up, I guess.
And that is, and exactly.
And putting it away.
My knowledge of spies.
And that is what will move on line. The soldiers, they never mattered. That part of the war
is nothing.
My whole knowledge of spies, everything I know, is that there's a black guy and a white
guy and they're trying to give each other a bomb.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Is that true?
Yeah, I actually had a whole book about that as a kid.
Yeah?
And some of it was a little gory.
Yeah. Did you ever read those?
Spy vs. Spy?
I read all of the Spy vs. Spy.
I was obsessed with Spy vs. Spy as a kid.
I loved Spy vs. Spy in the Mad magazines.
I had the anthology of all the Spy vs. Spy.
And they had a bunch of...
They were all funny, first of all.
But they had the thing where they do guest artists or whatever.
And there were a bunch that were really funny.
artists or whatever and there were a bunch that were like really gory.
Like really nasty.
Like really detailed.
Rob would do all these really detailed paintings.
Did they ever do like a reverse cowgirl sex thing where you see the spy's cock squeeze
into the other spy's fucking asshole and it stretches butt cheeks apart?
What are you talking about?
Like this and he's looking back at the camera like yeah and they're fucking.
No.
The guy who made Spy vs Spy like escaped from Cuba or something.
That makes sense.
was like I need to make I need to make spot. No. Yeah. He was like he like he
would he hated Castro and he was like I need to make this to show people what
it's like. That's what it was like there.
Just passing bombs back and forth.
I could be completely wrong about that. The last time that I know no, no, no.
You remember learning about that is when I was maybe eight years old. Next
time you're in a Barnes and Noble and a kid is reading a spy versus spy thing.
You should walk up and be like, did you know this is based on Cuba?
Well, I remember I remember the anthology having at least at the very
least they talked about Castro in the like in the like intro or whatever and
where there was something about how he hated Castro. Was Spy vs Spy, was that all in
Mad Magazine? Yeah. Yeah. That's what it was? Yeah. Man that was one fucking crazy
magazine. I miss that so much. I miss getting them for Easter. I'd
never got them. You were never alive at a time when Mad Magazine was like a big
thing. It wasn't a big thing but they made it. I know they made it but it was
Terrible when we had when I was a kid it was good because I was a kid and I didn't know that was bad
No, I mean that's like like I still you got to see that your first fold in the way
Okay, but when you be a little pissed off if like a 14 year old now is like I love Smosh
No, yeah, you'd be a little bit like you don't know it would be we don't know so I had my dad
That's all that's videos. That's videos from but if they were saying but but they were saying I love Smosh
I love the fucking when they I love the girls in Smosh. Oh, yeah, okay good point
Yeah, the Mad Magazine we grew up with was bullshit. You know, it's some good
I have my my about Obama dad had they used to they had they put a lot of the Mad Magazine stuff into just paperbacks
Yeah, like collect stuff and he had a bunch of old ones of those
So I would always read those and those were fire
Do you guys sometimes feel like you were half raised in the 2000s and half raised in the 1980s?
Yes a little bit because of your media
I tasted cuz I was walking around in my life, and I was people I was going at school saying yeah
My favorite movies you know Mel Brooks
Yeah, Brooks movie my favorite movie is the Mel Brooks film yeah
And I was like my favorite movie is you do the movie you I remember I said to somebody I said
I love young Frankenstein. They said I was at a rapper. Oh
Dude, I oughta fucking know it's the most terrifying movie ever made. Yeah, it's actually a really funny
You wouldn't be able to watch it alone.
It's the scariest comedy ever made.
So.
I did, I watched a lot of TV Land as a kid.
So I watched a lot of like different strokes
and like good times.
And then I think when I was like seven or eight years old,
I called something dino-mite to one of my uncles
and they were like, what the fuck are you?
'Cause you said dino-mite?
Like Jimmy JJ Walker.
Yeah, well of course, you should say dino-mite.
I think I should bring that back.
I think.
That's cool.
I think that what I should do is just watch Good Times again, just say everything that
they're saying. I think I should start calling stuff "Jive."
Yeah, I think you could do that.
I'd do that right now, but with YouTube.
You call YouTube videos "Jive"?
No, I watch YouTube and I say everything they say.
I do kind of do that. Yeah, I've had to stop. It's so easy to pick up on just funny words
from really stupid people.
Yeah. "Fact Not Fiction Playboy."
What's that from?
Dan Quinn.
Oh yeah. That's definitely in the upper half of words that you can take from Dan Quinn for sure.
Yeah.
Some things that you don't want to take from Dan Quinn.
There's one about a guy in the NFL.
Yeah, that's a bad idea to take him.
I was at dinner with Alex and Joe last night and Alex quoted it.
This guy's going on a double date.
Name dropper.
Alex quoted it to me and Joe asked me why I was laughing and what it was from and then I just showed him that full
the Kim Dotcom video while the waiter was like pouring water.
Dude, it's always the worst when you go out to a restaurant and the waiter can hear everything.
Yeah.
You know, and you're like, "Oh man, I wanted to talk about porn."
I wanted to be silly and talk about poop.
Silly things.
Uh-huh.
I was at the gym a couple days ago and I was watching Fox News on TV.
Found that.
The Fox News with the sound off.
And I don't know if you guys saw anything with this.
I have no idea what actually the story is, but Fox, I just want to do a quick kudos and
a shout out to Fox News because they landed, I think, literally the story that they couldn't
have dreamed of in a million years.
The best, most Fox News story I've ever seen.
I feel really excited.
Go ahead and tell me.
I know, I just want to give them a shout out.
I looked up at the TV when I was running on the treadmill and the headline that they had,
said, "prosecutor suspended from court case after misgendering child molester."
Wow. Isn't that incredible? Wow, that is incredible. I mean, you guys hate the player, but you've
got to respect the hustle. That is pretty incredible that they landed that one. Oh my
god. That is pretty amazing, man. And I'm truly amazed. I couldn't have dreamed of getting
that. It's so funny. The prosecutor was suspended. They were prosecuting a child molester and
They suspended him from the case.
They could, like, if you were in the writer, if you're like pitching the stories to Fox
News and you told them that, they would be like, "No, that's not believable.
That wouldn't fucking work."
And then you're like, "No, look, I have the proof."
That's Facebook comment fodder for like 20 years.
Oh my God.
That's another.
That is the biggest WB we knew.
My uncles are going to have a fucking aneurysm over that.
That is pretty incredible.
It's so crazy.
I've been when I when we've been on the road. I've been just hotels always the only
News thing they have about hotels the only news thing they have is Fox Drake
I'll think I'm Drake
Right now you think you think I'm dressed like Drake in any way he's Drake. Why are you making that face?
- I went to, anytime I'm in a hotel,
I just end up watching Tucker.
And Tucker had the best news story I've ever seen
in my life the other night.
His news story was,
of course liberals want to wear masks.
They're not very good looking.
(laughing)
And I was like, okay,
that is the most incredible thing I've ever seen.
That's the funniest thing.
And that's, by the way, that's on a channel,
it's called The News.
- Yeah.
Like liberal women are so ugly they have to wear masks.
That is so fucking funny bro.
- On one, they've been firing on all sorts of people.
- Have you seen what's going on with Hannity?
- No, I mean was he just slammed food as always?
- No, he's literally like trying to look like Trump.
It's so funny.
- He's always had a bit of a--
- No, he's like getting, like he stopped dyeing his hair.
He's getting like Trump orange.
He's like putting on like Trump tanner
just to like look more like him so that like he thinks that like that's the thing.
GBO just googled Sean Hannity today and I do the same thing but it's so funny to google
a celebrity's name and then today.
Here he is today.
Dude he looked like Stephen Colbert back then.
Everybody did.
Oh my god that must be why the rapport was so believable.
So fucking satirical.
I have a picture of it.
I was gonna make it my phone background.
Is it Hannity or Bill O'Reilly where old Killa Cam went on and said you mad?
You mad Bill O'Reilly.
Bill O'Reilly, okay. Wow, okay yeah, that looks very...
Oh yeah.
He looks just like Trump, yeah.
He does.
I'm gonna punch in on that real, right quick.
I don't think he needs to. I think that people believe you. People believe that that's Trump.
It really just looks just like him.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
But yeah, Fox News, it's cool that they are... Nobody seems to really care anymore, but for
For a while, people were so mad about Fox News.
I think eventually, though.
They're pretty incredible.
Now I'm watching them pretty much every day now.
And they are consistently--
China and Russia are teaming up.
Oh, today, COVID was leaked from a lab.
They said that it's official.
OK.
But that's true.
Amazing.
There goes our monetization.
They often talk about families being murdered.
And they really are always just--
Oh, it's--
--hitting it.
- Yeah, they're hitting every single mark.
But do you remember Tommy Lahren?
- Yeah. - Oh yeah, I just
remembered her. - Ooh, the fuck,
not a damn soul is talking about her right now.
She was like a huge threat for a while.
- I thought her name was Tommy Lahren.
- I think it is. - Probably.
- Tommy Lahren. - But she's going by
Tommy Lahren so that doesn't sound gay and French.
- I always thought it was Tommy Lahren too.
- Now that it's all over, bro, she was kinda busted.
- He was, everybody was like, oh it's so dangerous
'cause she's like, if a conservative guy
was in a hot lady's body, he's like,
I don't know about a hot lady.
- Well, what I would do is I look at her
and I just see her and I'm like, damn, she's kinda hot,
and then I'm like, engage ideology glasses.
- That's right. - Ew!
- That's right. - Disgusting.
- She got fired, I was looking it up,
she got fired from the Blaze, which is like that,
I think the Daily Wire, whatever the fuck it is.
- That's Glenn-- - Oh yeah, Glenn Beck.
- Glenn Beck's thing.
She got fired from Glenn Beck's thing for being pro-life.
- Wow.
- Or pro-choice.
- Yeah.
- Oh, she's pro-choice?
- Because she was a slut!
- Wait, she was pro-choice.
- Yeah.
- She said like, yeah, women should have abortions.
- Maybe she's not so bad.
- Yeah.
- Whoa, the ideology.
- That's why Trevor Noah was going on friggin' dates with her.
- Was he beating her up?
- That's what I remember.
- He was beating those cheeks?
- Oh my God.
- Dude, Trevor Noah.
- Imagine them creating the craziest TV show of all time.
- Trevor Noah's kind of legendary.
He's kind of legendary for that.
Kind of legendary status.
He dated Dua Lipa too.
Did he?
Yeah, remember that?
Dude, he fucked Tomi Lahren and Dua Lipa?
Wow.
That's pretty incredible.
He's not funny, but--
Whoa!
Hold on, man.
Hold on.
Not funny, but hey.
Listen, if you're watching this, or if anybody
who's a part of the Hollywood celebrity group
is watching this--
And all that Fox News stuff, we are not.
We like him.
It's an ironic thing.
- Fox News is-- - It's an ironic thing.
- Fox News is not very good. - Not ironic.
- We like-- - Not the country,
it's ironic. - The oatmeal.
- We like the oatmeal. (laughs)
- What's that, is that a thing?
- We like-- - Sam Cedar.
- What is it? - Song Exploder.
(laughing)
- No, we like cyanide and happiness.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- That's where we get our stuff.
XKCD, that's our stuff.
That's where we get all our news from, not Fox News.
No, we don't read.
We're saying when we say Fox News
fucking rocks.
Yeah.
We're saying it also a bit of
a doomer ironic.
We also do not.
We don't look we don't like
Western centric news.
So we usually we do People's Daily
China News from Africa.
Al Jazeera.
Al Jazeera. This type of stuff.
We know we don't watch.
That's the guy that comes from over
the guy in my street.
I talk to Al Jazeera.
Al Jazeera.
Cool.
And he told me Covid was created in
a lab.
- Yeah, well apparently it's official now.
- And he said that there's a prosecutor.
- Why do people care?
Why were people so hesitant to be like,
"No, it wasn't created in a lab."
It's like, who cares?
- Yeah. - Probably.
- I don't give a fuck.
- If that was created in a lab.
- It's way scarier if it actually came from a bat,
that's way scarier.
- Oh yeah. - Yeah.
- If it came from, what was it?
- That's true. - What was it that the
people were like, "Oh, people are eating bat soup and stuff."
- Yeah, but that just also looks kinda delicious.
- Yeah. - That looks like
one of those, the bat soup thing?
That's like a once a year meal.
- Actually, that is maybe the scariest thing in the world,
that you could be like, I'm gonna eat this,
I'm gonna, okay, they have a crazy thing on the menu,
I'm gonna try it, I'm gonna do it one time,
I'm gonna have bat soup, how bad could it be?
And you kill millions of people.
- That's literally what you say, you say out loud,
bat soup, how bad could it be?
Yeah, no, that is--
- Yeah, me, going to a restaurant,
we're like, yeah, we serve a kangaroo burger,
and you're like, ooh, interesting.
- Five million people are dead.
- I've never had bison before.
It's just an animal, it's not that crazy to bat.
- And I know this restaurant is taking
the appropriate safety precautions.
They're not just throwing all the--
- I never really processed that shit.
- Yeah, that is way more terrifying.
That's also a story nobody could ever believe that.
Of course that's not what happened.
- Eating the Domino's pizza out of your fridge
after six days, I mean, I really shouldn't,
but I'm really hungry.
destroy the world.
Just literally, just fucking
Molotov cocktails being thrown
into windows, right?
Families just being like, like
just X-ing out members of families
on the Christmas cards.
Because you were like, you're like,
do pepperonis go bad?
Wait, I don't think so, right?
You're like a ghoul.
Half the people that you know in
your life now have just like no stomach.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Of course it was just some guy in a lab was like, "I'll try."
"I'll try."
"I spilled this."
Yeah, just doing Powerpuff Girls and just mixing up the ratio.
Yeah, I just forgot to change clothes before I went home.
Yeah, exactly.
That's it.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's no, I mean, it wasn't bats though.
People were like, "No, it's pangolins."
And I was like, "Okay, new animal to know about."
Pangolins are the ones with the big claws.
Yeah.
Scales yeah, they are like one of the coolest looking art var animals. It's not an art work. You're more
It's like an armadillo or art work. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's an armadillo art bark
That was what that was an animal art bark. That's like my little brother used to only he called it an avocado
Couldn't say V's weirdest fucking
Speech impediment I've ever seen what is a pangolin
These animals are sometimes named the scaly and okay. I don't like it says another another notable. Okay, nevermind
I thought it said noble ant eating mammal.
- I don't like-- - It'd be noble.
- I don't like in-- - Eating ants are noble.
- Documentaries where they call an animal noble.
- I call every animal noble. - I like it.
- I don't like that. - I love it.
- What is the animal doing that's impressive at all?
- Look at that thing.
- This thing probably eats its own shit, man.
- If that's what fucking COVID came from--
- Then it beat us. - Isn't it crazy
that just diseases in general, they just come from animals?
- Yeah. - And then they just
make that leap, that's pretty scary.
That's what I'm pretty-- - Yeah.
- I've been recently very, very afraid of mad cow disease.
Mad cow disease is scary,
'cause it just pops up for no reason
in 250 people a year, and you have one month to live.
- Yeah. - Scary.
- One month to live?
- And here's the symptoms.
- No cure for it?
- No cure, here's the symptoms.
- Now you're getting me scared.
- Feeling crazy.
- Headaches, check.
I get headaches.
And losing your memory, check.
- Oh shit.
- I forget shit all the time.
- Yeah, I get kinda worried about
maybe I'll accidentally eat human flesh
and get like a prion disease or something.
- Yeah, the prion thing.
- Kuru or something.
- Yeah, so Mad Cow is prions.
I still don't really know what prions are.
I said it to somebody last night
and they were like, is that Scientology?
I was like, no, but I get how you could think that.
It does sound like a fake thing.
But it's like something that if you get too much in your brain.
- It's in brains too, I think.
Like if you eat, that's what you get prion disease if you,
I think, maybe not.
- But if you get too many prions.
- Well, I think you can get prion disease
from eating brain too, at least.
- That's P-R-I-Y-O-N-N-E-S.
- P-R-I-O-N.
- Damn, what am I thinking of?
- Wait, say it again.
- P-R-I-Y-O-N-N-E-S.
- That's a name.
- Prioness.
- Prioness?
- Yeah, or like princess.
- What am I thinking of?
- All right, guys, I completely forgot
that we have an amazingly disgusting--
- Oh, speaking of eating.
Speaking of eating stuff until you turn it to a crazy thing.
- That was a good segue.
You got it today.
- Good job!
- Whoa!
- Wow!
- I'm pretty impressed.
That might be your first one ever.
- That's the first time I've ever done a good segue.
- That was pretty good.
- He has too much headroom in that shot.
(laughing)
- Yo, all right.
Let's get into it.
Today, we're doing a website.
Should I say the name of the website?
- No.
- Yeah.
- It'll be in the slides.
- It's a website where there's a feeders forum
for people who--
- For people who like to eat sexually.
- Yeah. - And be fat sexually.
- Yeah, you may think that you like eating,
but I promise you don't like it as much as these people.
- And if you do, you should not watch this episode at work
'cause you might get a bonger.
- Also, yeah, I was thinking,
should we put a content warning on this episode or something?
Be like, hey, do you hate disgusting food eating?
- My stuff isn't that, I maybe have a few that are kind of
really nasty. - It's not as nasty as diapers.
- No, it's definitely not as bad as diapers.
- It's not as bad as diaper talk.
- If we combined the two, that could be great.
- I don't like that, which I think there is a bit
of an overlap, I'm gonna go with that.
- So, to get into this website.
- Yeah, it's like a forum, but it's kind of like a forum.
Oh, and also, I want a shout out to a Twitter user
at Neurotard who sent this website to me.
Thank you, this is all for you.
- Don't agree with your username,
I think that is not okay to say.
- What's wrong with it?
- But thank you for sending it.
That's his name.
Yeah, that's his name.
Thank you for sending us that website.
But--
It's his name, I think he's named Jack.
It's a forum, but it's more like a social media feed
than a forum, which I didn't know of.
Yeah, feed is the operative word here.
It's basically a Facebook clone for people
who wanna get as fat as humanly possible.
That's crazy.
You might hear that and say, wait, you mean Facebook?
Oh shit.
Come on.
- That took--
- You have to make eye contact when you cheers
or it's bad luck.
- Let's dive in.
- All right, let's dive in here.
Also, I'm still getting into themes on PowerPoint.
I think you guys should look them up before--
- I really like, wait, okay,
so tell me about these themes, man,
because these themes--
- I looked up food theme.
- Wow.
- And look at that, look at that.
Comes with a preset background
of what I think is Korean barbecue or something.
- This is basically Incredi-Bad.
That is to say funny and original.
- First thing, first thing, well you guys,
I'm guessing that you guys used your computers to do this,
to look this up.
- No, I did it in my brain.
- You did it in your brain?
- I did it on an abacus.
- I just imagined everything.
- No, I'm just saying, I used the mobile app
that they have, the proprietary mobile app on Groico.
- Oh, Grocio.
- Grocio asked, as soon as I downloaded it,
it asked me to track my activity
across other companies' apps and websites.
- And you pressed a lot.
- And obviously I pressed allow.
They also asked for my location.
- Okay.
- So that they could get my approximate location.
- You do have to put your location in.
- Yeah, you do.
- Which is kind of weird.
- Yeah, I had to use this while I had to look this up.
I had to prepare for this episode
while I was moving my apartment.
So I had to use the app the whole time
and it tracked me the entire time.
So I was jumping all over the fucking place.
- It thought that you were going just kitchen to kitchen.
Just fucking slapping down croissants.
- Yeah, so this first thing here
is the first post that I saw.
Oh, this is my account.
Okay.
It's feedme, @feedmefoodboy.
Very, very funny.
And this is my profile picture.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Okay, yeah, I bet.
You got a lot of messages.
Yeah, I have a feeling.
I had a feeling that we were all gonna have
a pretty similar idea today.
Yeah?
I didn't make my profile.
No?
No, I figured that someone else was gonna do this,
but they like fat.
All right, well, I made my first post.
Feel so fat after deluxe cheeseburgers.
Wait, so on your app, it says like and comment.
Yeah.
Because that's not how it is on the computer.
Oh.
I can't wait--
No, it's way better.
I can't wait to see what it's called when
we dive into your guys' stuff.
Mine says like and comment.
Really?
Yeah, what does yours say?
I guess we'll see.
All right, we'll see.
Wait, what do you mean-- what?
Mine said like and comment, I think.
Are we on a different website?
Maybe.
On Grommer?
Yeah, mine said like and comment.
All right, well, yeah, we'll get to it.
Nears, feed me food more.
Feel so fat after deluxe cheeseburgers.
These are the kind of posts that you see.
Pounds of cake.
This is not directly referencing anyone,
but some of y'all need therapy.
- Damn, that's cold.
- A lot of infighting,
and I'm worried that they're talking about me.
- Probably.
- Yeah.
- Oh well. - That wouldn't surprise me.
- Every time my fat belly breaks something,
it brings me great delight.
Today I broke a ladder instantly when I stepped on it.
- Instantly. - That's what I've noticed.
Yeah, there's so many,
a lot of people on here,
their specific fetish about being fat is breaking stuff.
Who has cool cuz it's just ultimately a power fantasy. Yeah. Yeah, but also like what is that guy doing where he needs to get on a ladder?
painting
That's what it is get to the top of the fridge where you have the dog treats and you've run out of food in your house
I like this
This just this boils the whole website down to its essentials. Yeah big fat belly eaten again bear cub 94
He's not that old for a belly that big no three more years. I could have a belly like that. Yeah, that's what I'm learning
Finding size fucking girl
I just tried the adventure fools or whatever they are and I'm already gonna go for another box and some thin mints probably gonna get
Some tagalongs too and those more ones fuck. I'm gonna buy a ton
Dude, if you buy Girl Scout cookies, and you eat them something's wrong with you, man
You you eat you eat one and you give them to somebody else
What? If you eat a whole box of Girl Scout cookies, I'm just anti, I've become very anti
sweets and cookies this year. I don't want cookies. You've completely lost the plot.
You think I've lost the plot, mate? You've completely lost the plot. You're acting strange.
You're acting, you're a bit daft. I only eat butter and meat. You have a tapeworm in you
that is probably eaten so good. You want a little, yeah you want a little one in you?
I don't want your tapeworm in there.
Whatever, bitch.
I don't want your tapeworm.
You want it?
The amount of C4 energy that that tapeworm has at creatine--
What's this?
That tapeworm, that is probably the--
It's super creatine.
It's swimming around in circles around in there.
You have bang energy in that or something.
I don't believe that there's actual coffee in there.
I switched to coffee.
I've realized recently that caffeine is the most
fucked up extreme drug.
Yeah.
And it'll make you really scared of your own house.
Yeah, me too.
Continue.
Yeah, it's pretty scary puts a small mouse and crushes it in one hand in front of you. Are you afraid?
Do you have fear in your life eats the mouse that happened and there's nothing you can do about it shoves you
Fuck would like this one person likes this is a post from the blob
This is not what this website's no this is what this website is wrong idea. I've also
May have made sure that I didn't make anyone's names
Yeah, that was smart
Especially without I will say this guy should have it when I was looking for I was trying to find this this website cuz I forgot
The name and I was just like searching thing and I found a website that was called like the sociopath forum
And I'd like to explore that
This next one here barebelly 24 fun fact
- I'm gonna put my belly button over an inch deep.
I'm imagining I'm sticking a tape measure into it.
- That should be on Capri.
- Yeah, Alex Trebek.
- Yeah, this is an inch deep.
- This is, what is Beer Belly 24's?
- Bear Belly 24's--
- Belly button.
- Oh, I'm sorry, it's not Beer Belly, it's Bear Belly.
- Yeah.
(imitates buzzer)
- I'd love to see one of those YouTube videos
where it's like GoPro lowered into hole
into his belly button.
- It's two seconds long, but still really, it's grosser.
This guy I really like.
- Whoa.
- The big fat greedy boss.
This is somebody who's like doing cosplay stuff,
I guess, on here.
That's his kind of like character.
- The big fat greedy boss?
That's good.
- It's times like this you all have to suffer, my boy.
Takes a bite of hoagie.
You'll see when revenue is down, we have--
- You didn't munch, you need to say the--
- Oh.
We all have to do with less.
I'm afraid there just isn't enough to go around.
- Wow, the big, fat, greedy boss.
- That's what he sounds like.
- Kind of Rick vibes.
- Yeah.
- Getting Rick vibes from that in a serious way.
- Rick Sanchez vibes from him.
- This next one here, my new catchphrase.
- This is from Hungry.
- This guy does look hungry.
He's pretty skinny.
- Imagine getting that username on this website.
- I know, oh man.
- Yeah, that's pretty amazing.
- Probably have to pay like $500
Yeah, buy it from somebody buying it from somebody's
I'm gonna make a hundred accounts on here called like ice cream eater burger
Making an account called hamburger
You know, this is the bio being like you could buy this can be your username for $10,000 metabolism
Yes, I'm gonna eat a tub of ice cream, but not sure if it's due down to boredom or horny
Miss or both do you think these people just have a wire crossed in their head that confuses hunger in their penis?
You know what it is what and I'll have a whole section on this in my slides, okay?
But I think literally I think 75% of them got got this way from watching Willy Wonka. Yeah, no
Yeah, I would know but this I have empirical yeah, we'll get to that. Okay this next person here. Oh, what's this one?
What did it okay?
Future chub any feeder wants to force tons of food and gallons of soda in my gut swelling it to dangerous state and shape and
Making me almost a pop feeling of total overfeeding and tons of pain on my gut will make me pre come on it
Like it's a broken water
The descriptions that they have on this website are pretty fucking crazy, and I don't remember if it's the next slide where somebody oh
That's this one
I love to be blackmailed to get fat
trying to eat food for like four or five people delivered to me and having to record all my eating to not publish my cakes and
Say, but I doubt it could happen a hot jocks. Give me food more comment. Oh interesting. Oh, they said oh
Well you that's you that's you. Yeah, it's your account. You said you made that account
That is I did. I thought maybe I cropped the screenshot. No, no you did not
This next one oh
My god little Susie fell down the well do something cracks a glow stick and throws it down the well thwack ow
She's alive. You know what somebody is on here doing weird Twitter style line break jokes could have been
Could have eaten her could have been worse could have been a lot worse a lot worse. He could have
This is just a screenshot of yeah, I didn't really I didn't really have time to organize all my all my slides
But I just wanted to show
That this person just linked to YouTube. Yeah an amazing post
Yeah, this is the same person these are I think all these next slides are from the same person who's who's?
Trying their hand at these like line break style jokes here
Gives you a comically oversized question mark to give to a friend when they say something that makes you go
The fuck are you talking about and no you can't use it on me damn
I would like to gift you a comically oversized question I with the way my brain works
I know I'd be getting that thing a lot. Yeah for sure for sure for sure for show for show my new catchphrase
This next one here takes an overdose level of laxatives and stands in the elevator for 12 hours with an unending
unresponsive smile evil smile
It's the most important
- It's like that movie Devil.
(laughing)
- Yeah, but he just starts shitting.
- Yeah, just a fountain of dookie.
- Devil dick.
- Yeah.
- Dang.
- Oh wow.
- 'Cause it smells straight up like sulfur in there.
- Wow.
Next one here, same guy.
Pizza slices are legally considered the Italian ninja star.
I defy you to challenge me.
Oh, I eat of the food.
Oh, I become the 700 pounds that come on a guy's chest.
(laughing)
- That would be a pretty funny account on here.
I have to add Italian Elon Musk. Yeah, that would be some that would be fucking dope. That would be fucking amazeball
I think maybe after this we change all of our we change one of our accounts into that
That's the next same guy
Me as a mafia boss
Kind of in the same like straight like yeah, like that makes sense
They're like mafia bosses starts punching the table very passionately. I want him dead. I want his family buried
I want his house plants dead. I want his house burned to the ground. I want to spit on the ashes
Can you read you said buried and it says dead? Yeah, you really can't read it. Oh, I can't read from here
I don't have my I wasn't gonna say anything, but you've done that for every one of them. Yeah, what's going on with you today?
You okay? No, you've been misreading everything literally stepped on my glasses while I was moving nerd Velma status
Me if you ever pass away in front of me
I promise I'll bury you in your native land of China other guy wait what me?
Closes their eyes with two fingers these aren't even about feeding, bro
Why did you even put these in here because I wanted to show you that isn't that the users of this website are actually?
fucking comedy gods
Okay, what's what would you say the joke is there? Oh? Well? Here's okay now?
We're back in the good stuff girl scout cookies are here America. Don't be fat also don't miss our national big
Oh, a political joke.
Another joke.
A political joke.
Yeah, they're pretty smart.
And then this, I think this is the last slide here.
"I don't usually post so frequently, i.e. twice within five to six hours, but this is a required post.
Finally, someone is pointing it out.
Some 23% of Fortune 500 corporations claim to engage with the Sustainable Development Goals framework,
yet a peer-reviewed study found that a measly 0.2% have developed concrete methods and tools
to evaluate their progress toward relevant SDGs.
Is that an S or a five?
- That's an S.
- Okay.
Only 29% of almost 12,000 Fortune 500,
Fortune 100 board directors had relevant ESG credentials.
According, look I'm not gonna read the whole thing,
but somebody, somebody went on here
to get on their damn soapbox.
- You can't read.
- No, I can't read without my glasses.
- The TV's too far away.
- The glass--
- It's too far away.
- I'm nearsighted, I can't fucking see that shit.
- I can't believe I'm learning today
that my friend can't read a lick of English.
Oh, that's okay.
Well, good job, Pap.
We'll go over to my slides.
It's very interesting that, well, I'll get to this.
Okay, so--
- Okay, so you went on Phoebe.
- So listen, so I tried to sign up for Grommer, right?
But for whatever reason, I didn't get the verification code.
You have to do a text and an email verification.
And my verification code wouldn't come through.
It kept getting stuck in a spam filter or something.
So I just tried their kind of sister site,
which is called Phoebe,
which I guess I found out that Grommer
is mostly for gay feeding.
- Oh!
- And Phoebe is basically the straights version.
- Okay.
- It's a social networking community for feeders,
feedies, fat admirers,
where a quirky bunch of men and women
who love words like curvy.
It was designed with the needs
of heterosexual feederism community in mind,
though we remain open to all people of all orientations.
So I went in there, I got in there,
and I made an account.
(laughing)
Patrick Doran, NYC.
- We did the same fucking thing.
- Well, but I said your name and location.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, I gave them, I was stupid,
I gave them my location.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I gave them app tracking.
- I did Patrick Doran, NYC, and I made some,
(laughing)
- I joined and said, "What are some good foods
"to get started with?"
Henry Co. already liked it.
- You didn't even post a photo of me?
- I thought that that would be a little much, you know?
Yeah.
And also, I didn't have any photos of you on my phone,
as surprising as that sounds.
- Wow.
- Yeah, not a single one.
- That's messed up.
- 'Cause I'm a fake ass friend.
- You are fake.
I have so many photos of you eating.
- So Phoebe was kind of a little bit different
than the Grommer stuff, right?
- The interface looks exactly the same.
- Yeah, but some of the user base is different.
- It looks like they might have taken
the exact same site template.
They must have Googled it.
It's also--
Feeder website template.
No, it's also Grokyo.
It's the same company.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
So you probably had it on that app as well.
This is Fat420Queen says, I'm a pig.
And Fat Man Walking says, message me.
Oh, it's also liked by the Fat Gentleman.
And make me gay.
Just pay attention to the people who like these posts.
Some incredible names on there.
Fat420Pig, this is all of her--
basically all of her posts here.
I wanna eat food.
Who wanna rub my belly while I eat?
Time to eat.
And these were all like on the same day.
Pretty amazing.
Make her bigger is a really good name.
- Chubby nerd.
- Yeah, big fatty bear, Koda.
What else?
Fat future.
Does anyone just wanna trap me in their house
and turn me into their very own fat toy?
I promise I'm very easy to capture.
- Fat future.
- And there was a couple of comments there.
- Fat future food gang, eat 'em all.
- There was a comment there, but it got cropped out.
It looked like somebody, can't really read it.
- Yeah, I can't read it either.
- Yeah, but it says something about me.
- Yeah, okay.
- I don't know who commented that.
- Yeah, who knows.
- She likes her belly is one of the--
- Foodie Fairy. - She likes her belly.
- This is from Foodie Fairy.
So, I woke up to two baked potatoes sitting on the oven.
Everybody appears to be asleep.
I want to eat 'em so bad, should I?
People are saying, do it, yes, put all the toppings.
But then Mormon Tempest says, yes,
but I'm sure there's more context to consider.
(laughing)
- We have to look at both sides of this.
- I'm pretty certain there's more to this story.
All right, what else?
- You have a gas leak in your house
and you forget that you've been making yourself
baked potatoes every night.
- This is, I've been, then I started looking
at some of the profiles, so I found this guy.
This is Fatty Fatty, right?
28 years old, six feet tall, 366 pounds.
This is a big, big guy.
- I didn't put any of these screenshots in my slides,
but the best part of this is that
if you go to someone's profile,
that shows you exactly how tall they are
and how much they weigh.
And there's some incredible combinations.
- You can only check two per day,
so I didn't get a screenshot,
but you can check people's weight history in a chart.
- Well, I also didn't put this in,
but on Grommer, if you scroll through people's feeds,
it posts updates like a Facebook feed,
where it says like, this guy gained five pounds today.
And everyone comments, it's like, nice, getting close to 400.
- Yeah, it does the same thing here.
But I found this guy fatty fatty, and I really liked him,
so I sent him a flirt on the actions
Patrick Doerr in NYC. I said I'd love to have dinner number three with you. Oh you
select the flirt. Yeah so you can do belly rubs, hugs, hi how's it going, great
profile, thanks for following. Eat up, I'd love a belly rub from you, you're handsome,
you're gorgeous, nice curves, if bigger is better, you must be incredible, you're a
chubby goddess, you're my WCW, you're my MCM, let's go Weight Watchers and piss
people off. Let's go to Weight Watchers and piss people off. And you look like
someone who enjoys long walks to the buffet which is kind of a good yo mama
joke yeah that is good he he posts stuff like I'm really sad now I gave $50 to
someone who scammed me if I gave you $50 would you run to or would you buy food
like by you and Carmen is a whole like by Patrick door in NYC I guess taking
blob applications.
(laughter)
Blob applications.
I have an idea, and if
any feedie wants to do it, shoot me a message.
You go to the drive-thru and I give you about $50-$75.
You go up and order one large meal.
After you finish it, you order another large meal, etc.
until you can't fit another
ounce inside your belly. Plus, everyone
working there will definitely think you're a huge fatty.
(laughter)
And then this guy had an amazing name. Opiate of
the Massive. Wow. Tell me
That is not a fucking sick man.
That is incredible.
He's been on here for six years.
Let's take a look at some of his posts.
He's in Philly.
Let's explore the dying malls
and take notes on the empty temples
of a dying consumerist god together.
Oh, like by Topanga.
This guy is sick, dude.
That is sick.
That's crazy. This guy's fucking ill.
I really like his post.
I'm sure he's also pretty ill
if you don't know this much. Yeah, definitely.
Another 2023 resolution.
He has some feelings about the community.
Okay. Being more forthcoming
about liking someone and wanting to make out with them
and make them unrecognizably fat, among other things, edited."
(laughing)
And then he also says, "I don't care if you're trying
to hit on a guy, a gal, or a non-binary pal.
Don't let your very first fucking message
to a complete stranger be a compliment about their anatomy
and your desire to touch it."
And Bay says, "Or about a belly button survey."
(laughing)
- That's what most of my first messages to people are like.
- Yeah, what do you like to--
- I have a survey about your belly button.
- Be in a belly button survey?
- I'm from the--
- I'm from the US Census.
- You have a belly button survey?
- That was the word I was looking for.
- Okay, the master says--
- Sense the sticker has a pen, it's just like--
- It sticks it in the belly button.
- Ah, sniffs it.
- He says, "Reserving an entire section of the buffet
"so it's just you and me, so no one is any the wiser
"about me stuffing you until you can't move
"and rubbing your belly to make more room
"until it's time to leave and I have to wheel you out."
And Patrick Doerr at NYC says, "Would love that."
- Wow. - It's kind of interesting.
- Those words there kind of, it kind of sounds like,
it sounds like lyrics.
- You could maybe turn this into a song.
- Yeah, you could.
And then I found this guy, NYC Locale, right?
So he seems pretty cool.
He's in Irvington, New York.
He's 22 years old, five feet tall.
And if you notice, he doesn't seem very fat.
So what could he be doing on this here feeder forum?
- Maybe he's trying to gain.
- Well, I think that-- - Or he could be
trying to gain muscle.
- I think you might be surprised.
Here's his first post.
He's joined Phoebe.
Been a minute since I've been on Phoebe.
Hit me up, New York locals.
Gassy women are way too underappreciated.
So let's look at some of his other posts.
Any gassy women wanna talk?
Do any women like to fart but don't have the fetish?
That one was edited.
Does anyone know how I can make a feety bloated and gassy?
I know the basics but not sure what else works.
Big Beautiful Belly 18 says lots of soda
and he says thanks.
- For me it's lots of garlic.
- Do any women like air inflation?
I do but I don't do it IRL, LOL.
And then so.
(laughing)
I finally got into Grommer.
And made a new account.
This is Cameron Pear.
(laughing)
24 years old, New York.
Identify as gainer, gender other,
interested in men, looking for asexual relationships,
languages, English and Vietnamese.
In the process of rapidly gaining weight.
We've been talking about this.
You're rapidly putting on humongous pounds.
And I made some friends pretty fast
just by posting that photo.
I got a message from NYC Encourager.
Great photo, hair, and shirt, Cameron.
Let's meet up, cheers.
- This guy's gonna be so mad.
I cut my hair, he's gonna fucking kill me.
- Oh yeah, dude.
- If he finds out I don't have that hair anymore.
- He's gonna see you and he's gonna take you down.
- What if he's a hair gainer too?
And I'm not even wearing that shirt.
- What if he's a hair gainer?
- You're endangering my life.
- And then I guess I--
- No, no, no, you're gonna be fine.
- I missed--
- The bullets will ricochet off of you.
I must have lost the screenshot this morning
'cause I couldn't find it,
but I did find one where the guy was like,
I just had, it was this other account that I found
and he had this one post that was like,
just had the most amazing experience of my life.
I made myself completely jizz to completion
just by jiggling my belly fat in the shower.
(laughing)
And every comment was like, congratulations,
congratulations, congrats.
- That's the best part is everyone knows what's up on here.
- Yeah.
- Everyone, well like not that everyone knows what's up,
but like everybody who posts something,
the only comments are always like,
"Great, it's no one even asking any clarifying."
Everyone knows everything about it.
- That's why I was pretty surprised that one person
even wanted context for the potatoes thing,
'cause they weren't just blindly like,
"Yeah, eat every piece of food around you
"like you're in an RPG."
They were like, "Yeah, there might be some context
"needed for the potatoes."
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright, so now I have my slides that Jubio really rudely put a title slide on for no reason.
This is massively aggressive.
I don't know why he did that.
He keeps doing that.
He keeps adding this fucking title thing and it's pissing me off.
It's disrespectful.
It looks horrible.
Look at the theme of it.
It's fucking terrible.
What are you going to put on here?
Swastika, you fucker?
Oh, that's great.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Your slides look great.
Alright, now stop clicking.
Alright, now here are mine.
So first of all, this is from Fatsdagram.
This is the first post I found.
sat next to a beer belly guy at a Berlin nail screening
couldn't focus on the movie the whole time lol
Berlin nail, I don't know if you guys know, that's like the Berlin film festival
that's like how they play, it's like a prestigious film festival
yeah so he was he was sitting and he was watching, he was
seeing like uh... uh... fuckin
whatever movie
what's the movie that Jubio likes?
that's about, sure, Tar
and he just, he's just
the entire time looking at the guy who's next to him
with a belly
uh...
Coleman 2021. Anyone who wants to poop on me? And what you'll notice here also, on Grommer,
they're not likes. They're called noms.
I didn't even notice that, dude.
And it says these people nom things.
Oh my God.
It says like fat belly guy one, two, three noms this.
That must be short for nominate.
Yeah.
For an award.
Every click is a nomination for an award.
Let's see what else you have here.
Okay. So this is where your theory kind of comes in.
is this guy says garbage can 18 says wish I could turn into a blue yeah garbage
can 18 was making me laugh so hard garbage can which you gotta hope he's
not five years old that'd be bad news but I found yeah I found a bunch of
blue blueberry is one of the is ever I've so this the other thing on this
website you can only do one search per day yeah so I've been on here for days
on it well unless you get the premium which I did not get the only nine bucks
I really thought about it. Yeah, I also thought about it, but I was like I can just log on to this every day for five days and that's okay.
Yeah, and the first search I did well before I realized there was a limit the one of the top hashtags are like trending searches every day is
blueberry
If they people just search blueberry they can log on here and they search blueberry and they look at all the posts
Squishy bum boy says I'm in such a blueberry mood. Someone turned me into a blueberry right now. Oh my god
Wonka93 says, "The most unrealistic thing about Willy Wonka is that he isn't fat.
If I were in that factory, I'd be so round. Hell, I'd probably greet my guests just permanently as a blueberry."
He'd just roll out as a blueberry, bro?
Wonka93.
Yeah, these are friends of Wonka.
Fatten me to death, PA. I'm feeling like a blueberry right now.
Fatten me to death.
It'll be, he's on here a bunch. You'll see a bunch of him.
Fatten me to death, PA.
Fatten me to death.
Wow.
The devil.
I
Need a mr. Walk a top hat to wear well no piece of blueberry bread gulps me down
Wow
Holy fuck
I need to look like Willy Wonka. I gotta say you don't see any shit like this over on Phoebe man
No, no, this is way better than Phoebe
(laughing)
- Big bellied boy, tired, this guy doesn't really care
that much, tired and exhausted, just wanna be a balloon
or blueberry or whatever.
- Doesn't give a fuck.
- He's just a balloon or a blueberry.
- You know what, I wanna be a blueberry,
but if I, look, if you can make me a gobstopper,
that's cool.
- I'll take whatever, I'm not too pressed about it.
- Schnozberry, call me a schnozberry.
- Pokemon gainer.
(laughing)
Here's something that I learned.
- What?
The amount of fat people in Houston is amazing.
So many big round-bellied civilians, too.
So these feeders called non-feeders civilians.
- Whoa, wow. - That is so sick.
- I saw a bunch of that.
- Really? - Yeah.
- They call 'em civvies.
- Civilians, yeah. - Wow, dude.
- Very, very exciting to learn that.
- Do you think they have, like, you know,
when military guys have gear that they make,
like shirts and stuff, that say, like,
proud infidel or whatever?
- Do you know what else they have
that I wasn't able to find? - You think they have
like a black rival copy?
- I didn't have enough days to search this.
- An archival copy. (laughs)
- They also have a cruise that they all go on a cruise ship.
- Dude, that is a dangerous, dangerous cruise ship.
- And people will post and be like,
"Is the cruise any good?
"Should I go?"
People will be like, "Yeah, you gotta go."
- Wow.
- Do they fuck?
- Well, that's the problem.
- Oh yeah, they have to really carefully distribute
their bedrooms on the cruise ship.
- So they just--
- It's another Titanic situation.
- Full wall-e this whole thing, yeah.
That's amazing.
- Here's another Pokemon Gator.
Tonight's Last of Us wrecked me.
- Wow.
- Yeah, so they're keeping up with--
- With all the big prestige TV shows.
- Heavy fart load.
So, sorry about this one in advance.
Wish I had a lazy farting homebody gainer buddy
to spend the day baking, baking, and baking with,
smoking up and then baking our turds and butts for days
to see who can grow the biggest toilet clogger
and lay the stinkiest pre-poop farts.
We would also be making heavy, fattening,
constipating baked goods,
never leaving the house as we fart and fap
our lives away at all.
- Oh my god.
- So eating a bunch.
- Baking our turds in our butts.
- Eating a bunch so that you like,
so like it's the oven.
- But can I direct your attention
to the most incredible part of this post?
- Yeah.
- Baking, baking, and baking.
- We're talking about making baked goods
to bake farts in their bellies
and then smoking weed and baking.
- God damn.
- Instead of wake and bake, it's bake, bake, and bake.
- That's like those sentences that you see on Wikipedia
that's like, oh yeah, it's all one word,
- The Buffalo, Buffalo, Buffalo, yeah.
Baking, baking, and baking.
So yeah.
- Wow.
- Pretty crazy, right?
Let's keep going though.
Heavy fart load again, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Is there a world poop size?
(laughing)
I've been baking a massive grogan in my poop chute
for over a week and I can barely leave bed,
farting constantly as the turd festers
and generates fart gas.
Feels amazing as the farts leak out
around the enormous rock hard blockage.
Anyone else have a log size fetish?
- Art Grogan's the fucking,
the aliens from Mass Effect, the big leg?
- I don't know, I never played Mass Effect.
- Wait, this guy hasn't taken a shit in a week?
- Yeah, he's baking a Grogan.
- Holy fuck, man.
- I swear to God.
- Let's see, I think, yeah.
And then there's a comment on there from This Big Stomach.
Did you know there was a man that had a genetic condition
which made it so that he couldn't poop at all
and he ballooned so much, I think he was known as a human balloon.
No, it's Krogan.
Krogan.
Yeah.
I don't know what a Krogan is.
Well, Krogan's are like--
Careful now.
What they look like--
Are you going to start just talking about that?
If you grew a turd that looks like this--
Oh, wait.
Oh, they're the frog guys.
Yeah, OK.
That would be pretty crazy.
Yeah, that would be amazing.
They kind of look like that when they first come out.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
Big belly 13 just says poop.
That is an amazing, amazing post.
[LAUGHTER]
Picture.
Poop.
He's got one of those bellies, the fronts,
that looks like a guy's face.
Yeah, he's got a talker.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's got a big time talker.
Yeah, I could have a conversation with that
if I was tired enough.
And you know he's making us like, poop.
Poop.
Yeah, he looks like he's halfway through the O's.
He's doing the Ace Ventura butt talking with his belly.
Yeah.
Fatten me to death PA is back here.
Anyone out here good with computers?
Having a few issues.
I need a manual.
Tie me to the bed, put a feeding tube in me,
turn it on and never turn it off.
- He's so needy, this guy.
He needs people to fix his computer,
turn him into a--
- Oh, fatten me all the way to death.
- Fatten me, fatten me to death,
but first, can you fix my computer?
I don't know how to connect my printer.
- Chubby Beer Belly says,
"Mews was phenomenal last night."
- People can't see, he has a slice of pizza
hidden under his tit.
- Oh my God.
- That is unreal.
- Yeah, that's a photo of him at the Muse concert.
Fat me to death, either I'm pregnant,
have a parasite in me, or I'm eating too much.
Can't figure it out yet.
- I'm guessing parasite.
- Not sure which it could be.
Keep the food coming says,
does anyone else have a physical ick that you dislike?
For me, it's mullets.
I don't get them and I very rarely
see people look good with them.
Here's some people's icks on Grommer.
Nose rings.
Beards.
- Okay.
- Wearing unnatural colored contacts unironically.
- Wow.
- Okay, that one, actually I do agree with that.
- Yeah, that one I do agree with that too.
- And the mullets actually too.
- Yeah, actually all these are pretty--
- Yeah, actually they're all pretty disgusting.
Lil One says, "The inner battle of wanting to be the biggest
or making him the biggest."
So this is kind of shows that it's like a power,
it can be a power struggle.
- This is a flex, sort of flex,
but could be a feety, could be a feeder, right?
He does both.
Wow.
- But it's also like, you know,
It's like something where you imagine like, oh my God,
what if my spouse got famous and they left me behind?
It's like, what if my boyfriend, he grew to 700 pounds
and I'm stuck back at 400?
True.
It's hard.
That's, you know, hard for us 'cause we're all dating.
Maybe we're trying to be all celebrities.
Exactly.
So I'm just saying the celebrity lifestyle is pretty similar
to the feeder lifestyle.
I just wanted to point that out.
That we're not all that different.
As soon as I get my celebrity feeder stuff,
she is not coming with me.
Oh no, I'm dropping her.
Uh-huh, no, they're going to pick me up in a forklift to take me out of that house.
Thomas the Twunk Engine, "DMing my first D&D campaign today, hoping for the best."
That Patches? Good for them.
It kind of does look like Patches' body, a little bit.
Oh, we'll never know.
"Why am I still meal prepping when some scientist could be turning me into a growing test subject?"
Okay, definitely Patches. He's talking about nerd stuff now.
That's just such a funny, what does that have to do with meal prepping?
Here's someone's bio, and this is what I'm talking about people who are breakers, they like to break stuff.
These are a few of my favorite experiences.
Being told I'm too fat to top because "my back can't handle the weight of your belly."
Hearing a reinforced stool creak under your weight.
Unable to access the attic due to low capacity LADAR.
Being unable to reach up because your shirt will become untucked.
"Hearing the sigh from a fellow plane passenger as they sit down next to you."
"Being unable to recline a movie theater chair because your thigh won't let off the up button."
"Pretending to be too cool for school because spirit clothes don't come in your size."
"Being called plump by a partner as they lose interest from your gains."
"Wondering if the barber's chair will hold your weight."
"Choosing a booth because that chair looks flimsy."
"Choosing a table because that booth looks too narrow."
"Choosing to eat at all times whenever you can and all you can."
It did seem a little... when I was reading all this shit, it does seem like a little bit of an appealing lifestyle.
lifestyle. Oh, absolutely. You literally are just what you want. You're like a sim.
Like you're so aware of your meter just like ice cream every day.
Descending like it's amazing. You're Godzilla. You get to make you like,
like all those like foods that they make on like the subway ads that are like
stupid as shit where it's like, oh, we're going to put like,
we're gonna make an egg tornado with like whipped cream on it.
That is your breakfast, lunch and dinner. Sounds fucking dope.
- It does sound incredible.
Never enough, what's the craziest thing you've done to gain?
Enrolled in a two year degree program,
knowing when I finish I'll get a raise
that will 100% go towards food.
- Wow.
- Shotha says, I think that they should make bathroom scales
which speak your weight at 80 plus decibels for gainers,
which is a cool invention idea.
And 80 decibels, it can damage your hearing
if you're exposed to it for too long.
It's about the level of a busy downtown street.
So it's because you can't see the thing.
Yeah.
So you would have it just yell so loudly.
I looked at 80 plus decibels literally
is the threshold for ear damage.
That's exactly where it is.
Imagine you live next door to a gainer
in a house with paper thin walls,
and they have that fucking scale.
And you're just eating breakfast one day,
and you hear just like, 455 pounds.
[LAUGHTER]
And then 10 minutes later, you hear, 455 pounds.
(laughter)
- Yeah, they just hear a guy just come.
- You weigh 480 pounds.
(laughter)
- This next thing, I discovered a thing
that I did not even consider could be part of this website.
And this is the craziest thing to me.
- Here's a one pound coach.
We all have those sometimes.
You gotta be a gainer to have one of those.
Probably the bigger you are, the more, the bigger your nut is.
Yeah, that's right. 100%.
No, it's because when he's shitting, when he's jizzing.
Oh, he's shitting as he's jizzing.
That's gross. That's not fair.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
He's standing on the bathroom floor.
That was funny to me.
Let me read you guys this new corner of the website.
This is from Jbellylover.
Preds, which is short for predators, want to vor me?
Turn me into a pole of meaty sludge digesting in your gut and then turn me into shit in
your toilet.
Might even have a few trophies you can take.
#vor
And I know you guys are wondering what that guy's profile picture is.
Yes.
It's a centaur that's standing on his hind legs and he's really fat, but only the horse
belly is fat and the human body is really buff.
Wow.
How does that make any sense?
- Yeah, that is really good.
- If they both be fat, would it be a fat horse?
Why is the body so buff?
- Really funny.
(laughing)
Yeah, I really liked this picture a lot.
That is really good.
- If it was no fucking sense.
- Yeah, I don't know, standing up like that.
- If they say, why would the horse belly get fat?
And not the, why wouldn't the whole guy be fat?
- Twink99 says, "Pray, come on out,
or come out, come out, wherever you are."
and then tasty snack boy says sounds like a trap. Oh my God.
Leprechaun like this.
Damn. No, he nommed this. I am your prey. Noms this.
Okay.
Yeah, but it sounds like a trap. I'll stay hidden was really
making me laugh.
Swallow me whole says are there any Preds out there that feel
like slowly and brutally mulching up a prey and their hairy
guts were no one but you can hear my whimpers or see my
struggles colon Pete.
Dude, it's crazy.
I'm just sticking your tongue out.
I'm goofy.
I wanna be eaten alive.
(laughing)
Satisfied Belch says,
"The urge to sneak up behind an unsuspecting prey boy
and swallow him down in front of his friends
and family is growing."
Oh my God.
Satisfied Belch.
I don't wanna nom that.
I would not nom that.
No, I would not nom that.
A prey boy.
You like prey boys.
Me?
Yeah.
I think I probably am a prey boy.
Yeah, you kinda are a prey boy.
This is like the crate.
I didn't know this was my--
- I'm like one of those perfectly smooth Japanese cakes
that people like so much.
I'm like that to it.
Yeah, I'm like that, right?
I just have nothing on me.
- Zach Autumn Runner said, "It's too hot.
"Can I put you in the freezer for a bit
"and then lick you like an ice lolly?"
- This is like, I can get behind the guys
who are just like feeders, the guys who are just like,
oh, I wanna be the biggest, fucking fattest candy in the world.
- You think it's wrong to freeze someone
and lick them like a nice lolly.
You think that's wrong?
This is their lifestyle.
This is their sexuality.
Who are you to judge?
- You know what?
You made a good point.
- You're like J.K. Rowling.
- You know what, yeah, you know what?
I'm being a firf.
- Yeah, you are.
- I'm being a fucking firf.
- And now we're gonna end here with some nice motivation
from Shota.
I just have a few messages from him
that kind of, this can send us off
into the rest of the week and we'll feel good
and we'll be happy and we'll have some mantras
we can repeat to ourselves.
- This is what I need right now.
And this is from Shota.
First one, "Dreams can come true.
It depends on how much you want them to come true."
- Aw. - Oh, that's nice.
- Yeah. - That is sweet.
- Second one, "Thank you for the encouraging comment
on my photo.
I'll always have room in my belly for you."
- Aw, Shota.
- I'm gonna start using that for you guys.
I always have room in my belly for you too.
- And now the last one, "Let's bring this energy
into the rest of the week, guys.
Come to New Zealand, I love you."
(laughing)
And that's all I got. - Wow, yeah.
- Dude, that was an amazing, Shota, we--
This is definitely--
I'd like to talk to Shotha again sometime soon.
In turn--
He's a good guy.
And we've studied the diaper people.
Yes.
What else have we looked up?
Just other weird things.
Other weird--
Mostly weird stuff.
I think this community seems like--
They seem nice.
They seem very nice, and they seem very loving to each other.
And they just want--
I'll say I don't like the guys who
want to eat meaty sludges of other guys.
Yeah, I don't think that those guys--
I mean, guys like Shotha--
- He's nice though, he doesn't--
- He doesn't respect them.
- Yeah, these guys are great.
I don't like the people who call themselves predators
and they want to--
- Definitely bad luck.
- They wanna sneak up behind somebody
and eat them like a cobra. - That's probably why
they say prance.
- Yeah.
- They don't say, my sexual thing is I'm a predator.
(laughing)
They know I'm a prane.
No, you don't understand.
I'm not like a sexual assaulter or anything.
I just like to eat guys.
(laughing)
- No, I just like to--
- I like to eat them and digest them.
- In front of their friends and family.
- No, it's gonna be--
I'm not a predator.
I'm gonna unhinge my jaw like a cobra.
I don't ghost women, I just eat guys.
Thank you for watching.
If you wanna come see me in Boston on the 16th opening for Connor O'Malley.
Tickets are available at cornhop.com.
- Yeah, go to-- - ConnorXvideos.com/Connor
- Dukie shit, fuck you, bitch ass, motherfucker.
Fuck you, bye. - And if you wanna see
Caleb open for-- - For, you just wanna see
me open your asshole. - And if you wanna see me
open my mouth and eat Caleb,
then you should subscribe to the Patreon
'cause I'll be doing that this week.
- Bye. - And there'll be
a shareholder meeting.
- Oh wait, we have that scheduled?
- When did we say? - What day is it, Jubio?
- The 22nd. - You guys are trying to,
we have stuff we have to-- - Yeah, Wednesday the 22nd.
- We have an obligation-- - March 22nd,
that's the next shareholder meeting.
meeting so make sure you subscribe to the patreon and join the discord because
that's where the old all right bye bye you need to change this camera
[BLANK_AUDIO]