(upbeat music)
- Yay!
- Yay! - Clappington City.
- So I saw this video that really, really was amazing.
I can't believe it's not the most popular video
of all time. - Can you pull it up?
- No, we can't show it on YouTube.
It's a guy, a dude, he's sitting on a chair
and he has one of his, you may have seen this,
he has one of his feet is bandaged
and it's like covered in blood.
And he's like, "All right, we're gonna try this again."
And his friend is like, "Okay, here we go."
And he has a revolver with one bullet in it,
and he spins it and shoots his other foot
and shoots a hole through his other foot too.
And it's the funniest video I've ever seen.
This guy off camera, he shot one foot doing Russian roulette
and on camera, he shoots the other one.
(laughing)
- You have to show me.
- You have to show me this video.
- Can you show me that on your phone?
Just like pull it up. - I can't stop thinking about it.
I don't even know if I can find it.
- Can we pull it up on the screen and then just blur it out?
- No, no, this is a no-showing video show.
- No, no, we don't show videos.
- You're gonna be really scared later then.
- We've learned, we've learned.
We do theater of the mind, we're back to theater of the mind.
People don't like when we show--
- When we show videos, yeah, we show--
- People don't like when we show stuff
and describe it perfectly.
- Yeah, with stuff like this.
- Where it's maybe even better than looking at it.
- Whoa, oh shit.
- People don't like that for some reason.
- For some reason, people get mad at us
that we do a video podcast now,
and they get mad that they have to listen to it as well.
And I don't know why that happens.
Maybe it's just tastes change.
- Let's just let 'em go.
- Maybe some people really like it
and then some people really don't.
And you have to toe the line
and you get a lot of rude messages in your DMs saying,
"You look like shit on today's episode.
"Your hair is falling out.
"Just shave it off, just shave it off."
I can't shave it off, there's already a bald guy on the show.
I have to grow my hair back out
'cause there's already a bald guy.
- Well, there's a guy with hair too,
so you're kinda caught in the middle.
- You're kinda copying me, right?
- You're coming to a rock and a hard place.
(laughing)
- I get 100 messages a day that say,
you look so bald today, you should kill yourself.
- Literally? - Well, that's funny
'cause I get 100 messages today that say,
I have 100 Bitcoin, I need you to manage it for me,
please be the CEO of my corporation.
- Yeah, and I also get the same ones that say,
come click my profile, I'll make your butt come.
- Yeah, I don't like those.
- That's good messages to get.
- I'll make your butt come.
I'll say, hey lady, that's diarrhea.
(laughing)
- I've been thinking a lot recently.
- That's not jizz, jizz isn't brown.
- I've been thinking a lot recently about
why do you not, with those fishing Instagram accounts,
where they, why is it always--
- Yeah, the only fishing Instagram I follow
is Jimmy Houston Outdoors.
- Yep, I saw that one.
A mile away, but I still liked it.
- Whenever I get messages from those accounts,
it's always from an account,
and they're always called like Amanda1989 or something.
- Amanda Bobby.
- Why are you making it like--
- Stuff like that, fake names.
- Ruth Randy.
- It's always a man's first name as the last name.
So you get a message from Jessica Bruce.
(laughing)
Jessica Bruce 66421.
And it's like, "Come see my pussy, come."
That's my problem though. Why are you even making up a fake name?
Just name it. Name your account Vagina or Diarrhea or something funny.
I did.
Oh, that's interesting.
I got a really good one the other day.
Let me look it up because the name was stuck in my head.
You keep going while I look for this.
He had a song.
I'm not going to keep going because if I start saying something,
he'll say the name as soon as I start.
No, no, no. I'll wait till you're done.
I'll wait till you're done.
No, no. You're right.
We just have to do this exact level of conversation where neither of us really say anything.
- It's about to boil over.
Oh, are we gonna move to another topic?
- No, we're not.
- Oh, not yet.
- We're literally just filling air until he does this
because as soon as I mention something about my life,
I just know that he's gonna say the name,
which is coming up very, very soon.
- But maybe he won't be able to find it
until we try to change topics.
- Oh, now I'm paralyzed.
- I was playing a game the other day.
- What were you playing?
- I wasn't, I was trying to bait it out.
- Yeah.
- I was--
- You're in luck, it didn't show up.
- Wow.
- That was a huge relief.
- Yeah, I stopped getting all of,
I don't get sexual spam messages anymore.
I just get one, the copy and paste one,
it's a username and password,
and then an amount of Bitcoin.
It says, "Please help me manage this."
I get a hundred of those.
- Those are good, I like those ones.
- They're all, it's so funny,
they're all exactly the same.
And they don't even, like,
is it a bunch of different people
who are copying and pasting the same thing,
or is it one person who's running it all
was no way to check if they've already messaged somebody,
'cause I've probably gotten like 500 of those.
You know what I mean?
Like at what point am I gonna fall for the--
- Yeah, what if you decided to like--
- Yeah, maybe one of them's real.
- Yeah.
- I guess. - Or maybe you get like
a fraction, like maybe you get like less Bitcoin
than they promised. - But also,
the ones, they started to switch it up,
but it used to be literally every time the username,
or in some way it would have the name Douglas in it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
But now they switched it up, and now it's all--
- I would trust a Douglas, though.
- Yeah. - That's a very,
- They did market research, they figured out
Douglas is the number one name for trusting.
- I guess Douglas is a last name.
- Why Ruthie?
- I don't know.
- Who's Ruthie?
- Just the name that they pick.
- I had an aunt Ruth.
- I had a grandma Ruth.
- I met her one time, similarly,
I met her one single time and she just got,
she was so demented that she just started taking--
- Demented?
- Yeah, she's demented.
- Now it's not Douglas anymore.
- She started taking off her clothes
right in front of me and my grandma.
- That is actually fucking demented.
- She was just like, "Bah."
- That's very demented.
Yeah, and I was like you demented old bitch you are die already
And she did a couple of guys do you realize how demented you're being right now, man?
Oh, yeah to her yeah when I was nine excuse me
Let me just you're asking bloody mental you Ruth great-aunt Ruth sit down put your giant
Dino tits back in your fucking shirt and get and I you're acting demented you are acting like a demented fool
That might have been the first boobs. I ever seen in my life. Yeah, well post, baby
I thought that that's a nice
Bro chill
Fuck no. I didn't see no babies boobies. I as a post baby. Those were the first boobs
I saw was my great aunt Ruth host baby and what what are you talking go ahead? Yep?
No, baby. What what are you talking about? I was a baby, and I saw boobs
Constantly yeah, everyone was taking him out everybody baby. You won't remember this
I was at Mardi Gras handing out beads.
They're like, "This is fine, nobody gives a fuck."
"This is going to change his brain in any way."
Yeah, that's like how all those ladies used to go to Mardi Gras and do that back when cameras were just VHS tapes and stuff,
and now all those videos are just on the internet.
Yeah.
I was basically...
Girls Gone Wild, all of them.
You remember it all.
All those exploited women.
Yeah.
You were a child. You were Sherlock Holmes.
Yeah, exactly.
You had a photographic memory.
memory perfect photographic memory I remember every single Marvy Gras tits and the boobs
knocking on the doors of all the way yeah as a baby they see my eyes they go oh my god
oh my god he's imagining them right now. I just open the door I just smile
I do have Sherlock Holmes like sitting back in a recliner with his hat and he's smoking a pipe
and he has his eyes closed and he's just thinking of every naked woman he's ever saw in his life.
It's actually so smart of them in the new Sherlock Holmes, or in the British one,
it's so smart of them to have made him gay because the idea of a straight Sherlock Holmes is like
actually that's dangerous. Disquieting. Yeah, that is a scary, to say the very least.
Motherfucker, Sherlock Holmes is always British.
Damn. You know what I mean though.
The British one, he's up in here saying the British one, I ain't seen an American one.
Oh, actually, that is a good point.
[POP]
[LAUGHTER]
What was that?
No, that was a crazy mic bump.
That sounded full--
That was probably the best one yet.
That was Donkey Kong Country sound.
That was good.
I liked that.
But yeah, no, because a straight Sherlock Holmes
is like an actual-- that's like Jack the Ripper.
Back in the--
I'm straight Sherlock Holmes.
1800s or whatever.
When's Sherlock Holmes from?
When was he born?
1800s, I think.
Yeah.
When was the real Sherlock Holmes from?
Sherlock Holmes was fucking Watson's thighs.
Huh he was fucking his thighs you know how to fuck butts back then no
If they did that it was a they had you used to have more sexual stuff, and it got all got away
Yeah, it went away. What did we?
used to have more crazy sexual you're right actually that got cuz you
Can shave your pubes back then
Could the amount of no you couldn't we're talking about caveman times right now
You could shave them then - we couldn't know if you had a buddy with sharp teeth. We're talking about pre tools. Yeah
mmm
Everyone who has a really fucked up sexual idea now. It's all they can use a machine or a toy to get it
Yep, what they now someone wants to fuck a dragon
They have a machine that was built to simulate you fucking a dragon
But if you wanted to fuck a dragon as a caveman
before they even made a wheel or fire,
much less a rotating sawtooth fleshlight.
- Take it on a couple dates.
- You have to go fuck a dragon.
- You have to take that dragon on a couple dates.
- You have to invent a mythology
that allows a person to have a dragon spirit inside them
and then fuck them.
- Did you guys think it was a little bit hot,
the big dragon from Shrek?
- No.
- No?
- Not even when she put lipstick on?
- No.
- No?
No, they could have stood to make her a little more sexual.
They could have made her bustier.
Not even a little bit, though.
She was, but, bro, she weighed fucking 40,000 pounds.
You can't get bustier than that.
She didn't even have anything up there.
She got wings, motherfucker.
If she was wearing a bra, I'd be like, damn.
That's true.
Any animal from any TV or movies,
if they were in a bikini, I'd beat it.
(laughing)
I'd beat it up.
I would beat it up.
I'd beat up Rolly Polly Olly's mom heavily though.
- That's just shapes.
- That's not an animal.
- That's what I'm talking about.
It doesn't even have to be an animal.
It could just be shapes.
- It's just shapes.
- For a guy like me.
- Just shapes.
- Think about it, Rolly Polly Olly's mom,
she's like two circles.
- What are boobs?
- She's fine actually.
- Two circles.
- Shapes are, it's less,
I think it's easier to admit you'd fuck a shape
than an animal.
- Oh yeah.
- And you gay as hell if you fuck in a square.
- Let's talk about it then.
Let's say that, let's get that on the record.
Let's go to that square.
All at the same time, number one shape.
3, 2, 1.
Circle.
Wow.
OK, so we have very similar tastes as men.
OK, number two.
Ready?
But I'll fuck a triangle if I need to.
Number one animal.
I'll fuck a triangle, maybe.
Wait, just number one animal in general?
Number one animal.
No time to think.
3, 2, 1.
Alligator.
Well, I was still thinking about triangle.
We all said monkey.
Alright, I may have said bee.
I said bug, so you're a copier.
No, it's a different, you didn't specify what kind of bee.
All bugs count as my domain.
Okay, all bugs.
Okay, then I would fuck a simpson.
I don't know.
A simpson isn't an animal.
That's the only human that's not an animal.
You can't do simpson.
Every human in the world is an animal except for toons.
You can't pick a simpson.
- That is less animal than ant-
- No.
- They didn't evolve from monkeys.
- They were entirely human.
- They have no DNA.
- They have DNA.
- No, they're toons.
- Drawing and animation.
- They do.
- Mate.
- They do have DNA.
- My mate thinks Simpsons have DNA.
- My mate thinks that a Simpson has a genome.
- My mate thinks a Simpson is vulnerable.
- They just finished sequencing the Simpson genome.
(laughing)
- The Simpson evolutionary line.
- We can finally repair the old age of Mr. Burns.
We can get the wheelchair characters out of the wheelchairs.
- We'll finally solve that problem with Apu.
- Yep.
- What's the problem?
- What's the problem with Apu?
- Too funny.
- That is true.
- We're gonna figure out birth defects like little Lisa,
Maggie, whatever her name is,
the small one who can't talk, Simpson.
- What was the problem with Apu?
I never watched that movie the problem the poo is it's racial. He wasn't very good at his job
Yeah, I think that he was yeah, just kind of was just kind of annoying just yeah, and he was wasting time
Yeah, the problem with the poo is that he was a vegetarian and he was pushing his fucking beliefs on to Lisa
He was rude to Homer - he was rude to Homer
There's one art some another problem with the poo was rude to all the characters at least once basically
- Apparently there's a laundry list of problems with Apu
that they, I mean, they only scratched the surface
in that movie.
- I'm not sure there's any character who's been as rude
to every character in a show.
- They really, they only scratched the damn surface
with those problems.
- Here's the problem with Apu, he has that one episode
where he has like 15 kids and none of them,
we never see them again.
There's a problem right there.
- Doesn't he keep them in a dresser?
- I don't, there's one other problem.
That's cruel.
- Oh my god.
- That's cruel and, that's like psychopathic parental abuse.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Although every parent used to do that, supposedly.
- Pretty much every Simpsons parent is an abuser.
- They should call Cruel and Unusual Punishment Cup.
They should just say Cup.
- Homer strangles his son.
Cup is good. - Cup.
- Homer strangles his kid.
- If they made The Simpsons today--
- Yeah. - Here's the horrible thing.
If they made The Simpsons today--
- Moe has a kid. - Moe doesn't have a kid.
- Shut up.
If they made The Simpsons today,
Homer would be strangling Lisa.
- Yep.
How awful is that to think about?
That's way worse.
Wait, why?
Because of equality.
Because of equality and because of--
But you wouldn't be strangling them both or just Lisa?
Just Lisa.
Has he ever strangled Lisa?
'Cause I guess you have to balance it out.
There's been, there's 100 years of Homer strangling part.
Yeah, if you used to strangle a guy,
now you're strangling a girl because of--
Switch it up.
Because of woke--
SJW culture.
Switch it up, yeah.
If Simpsons go woke,
I'm gonna go broke-- I hate to say it,
I think they've gone a little woke.
My neck on a chair in a--
The Simpsons went woke?
Mate. Don't tell me.
- Mate, you're pulling my tit, mate.
- I heard that they're gonna change all the Simpsons,
instead of being yellow,
they're gonna change them to real life skin colors.
- And every single shade.
- All of them.
- Oh God.
- You're pulling my bloody tit.
- I'm not.
- So you're saying that we will have a mixed race Simpsons.
- Yes.
- Because of woke?
- Because of wokeness.
- That's PC culture gone mad.
- It is completely gone mad.
- Next thing you know, they're gonna start drawing
an extra finger for the Simpsons.
- Don't even think of that.
- Wokeness gone amok.
I've been following a very funny wokeness saga
that I usually, this kind of stuff I don't even notice
or pay attention to 'cause I'm kind of just above politics.
- Yep.
- In general.
- I've since never heard that about you.
- I know that about time.
All you think about is Tom and Jerry.
- There has been a crisis of wokeness
in a certain nerd community
that has been really making me giggle
and it's in Magic the Gathering.
- Okay.
- They're releasing, it's gone woke, first of all.
It's been woke for a minute.
- Can we just have just a moment there?
- And I've been on the forefront of this issue.
It has been woke. But they apparently, according to the anti-woke fans of Magic the Gathering,
it has crossed a line.
What's the percentage wise? What do you think the anti-woke MTG fans are?
I could give you an actual number. They have a subreddit. They have a separate subreddit
because they've all been banned from the main Magic the Gathering subreddit.
Let's get the number of the Magic the Gathering members and then the anti-woke Magic members.
- So the main Magic the Gathering subreddit
has 631,000 members.
- Okay, it's kinda lower than I thought, honestly.
- Big group, big group.
- I thought that'd be in the millions.
- And then the racist Magic the Gathering subreddit--
- Is it called racist Magic?
- It's called Free Magic.
- Free Magic, okay.
- And it has 24,000 members.
(laughing)
- That's pretty good, actually.
- Pretty decent proportion.
- What do you have?
- But, so--
- So those are all, wait, so those are all the people
who have been banned, so they can't--
- They haven't all been banned, but they hate the--
- But they're anti, yeah.
- They're anti, yeah. - Magic.
But so the thing that happened is they're making
a Lord of the Rings set for Magic the Gathering
and they have made Aragorn black.
And it has sent the racist Magic the Gathering fans
into the biggest tizzy I've ever seen in my life.
And the thing that was made,
they have been making really racist
custom Magic the Gathering cards
where they'll try, they're like,
to try and prove their point,
they'll make cards that are like,
this is how Aragorn should look.
And it's like a white guy.
But the best one I saw,
- The best one that I saw was a custom card
that they made called Pander.
It was like a spell, like a spell on the effect said,
all white creatures become black.
(laughing)
And I probably wouldn't, I wouldn't go on this subreddit
or show it on YouTube because they really get
extremely, extremely racist.
- Really? - Yeah.
- They take it to a whole other level.
- They made Beetlejuice into Ericorn.
- Okay, I would watch that though.
That I need to see.
I would see that.
I need to see that really bad.
Yeah, that sounds amazing.
Yeah, but that's just a kind of a
wokeness report for the week.
That's what's going on right now.
Speaking of that, so you had like,
we were talking about the things that we
like look at to like, remind us like,
oh yeah, there's a lot of fucking shit online.
I tried to get into iFunny.
We were talking about, remember,
you were like, the racist magic thing.
And I was like, yeah, I've also been looking at iFunny.
And it's the most racist.
website of all time.
- It's pretty crazy how racist some people get.
- Yeah.
- Just when you put them all in a room together.
(laughing)
It's really funny, 'cause you know that the people,
at least on the Magic the Gathering,
these are people who, they're going to a tabletop
gaming store, and they're sitting down to play a tournament,
and they're either not talking to anyone,
or they're saying, "I hate Magic the Gathering,
"it's been woke."
And everyone's like, "Okay, we also are nerds,
and we don't want to talk to you.
But then you get them all together and they go crazy.
- I don't think there's anyone at a tabletop game store,
I don't think there's anyone going to play Magic the Gathering
who's in the middle.
I think that it's like, there's two camps in the store,
there's the freaking blue hair SJW types
and then the other guys who are completely racist as hell.
- If you're into it enough to go to the store to play
instead of just playing it at home,
I think you have to pick a side.
Yeah.
You have to pick a side in the war.
And there's going to be a huge--
you're going to go to the game castle in Londonderry,
New Hampshire.
You're going to see one side of the room, blue hair, SJW.
They're going to have sharpened logs in the middle.
The other side, guy in full SS uniform.
Yeah.
I would-- I think that--
He's like--
--nerds.
No, it's because I'm playing a different game.
I'm not playing Magic.
I'm playing Risk.
And yes, it's Risk 1942.
I'd like to be in the middle of those two groups.
empty out AK-47 automatic rifles at both of them.
- I like to think that I bridge the gap.
- Between the...
- I'm basically half SJW.
- Half racist.
- I'm racist as fuck.
(laughing)
- And I kind of bridge the gap between the two cultures.
- The worst part of the racist Magic the Gathering subreddit
is like, I would say about half of it is like,
truly some of the most obscenely racist,
like just actual Nazis. - But then some of it...
- But half of it is just people who are not racist,
but or at least are secretly racist
and don't say it out loud.
but are just actual, actual nerds who are like,
Wizards of the Coast is devaluing the game
by printing too many cards.
And I'm like, oh, you're right.
- Yeah, they're making a good point.
- They're making good points.
And then I scroll their next post and it's like,
something really bad.
(laughing)
- That's the other thing.
- A really crazy drawing.
- There's definitely plenty of like,
black nerds who play Magic the Gathering
who probably also are like,
Irigorne is not black.
(laughing)
Like, can you imagine if they'd redesign,
- Imagine the fury of the black nerd community
if they did a re-release of Dragon Ball Z
and made Goku black.
- No, I don't think-- - No, they'd like that.
- You think they'd like that?
- I think they'd love that.
- I think they'd be pretty mad, dude.
- I mean, there's already, like, if you just walk down--
- There's a car that drives around here
with the license plate, Black Goku.
- Yeah. - Wait, really?
- Yeah. - Well, introducing him
as a different character, that's a great idea.
- Yeah. - Black Goku?
- Black Goku shows up. - You're sounding a lot
like a Free Magic member right now.
- And if you made a different character, it'd be okay.
- If you made a different card called Black Aragorn,
this would all be fine.
- Yeah, that's a great idea.
- They literally are like, yeah, but they have to.
- Yeah, they should at least make a special version
that has a white Aragorn on it.
- Oh my god. - It's a good idea.
- Well, that's the thing now,
is it would be called White Aragorn.
- Yeah. - Goddamn.
- Yeah, then you'd have to have,
no one wants to be left out,
you'd have to have Chinese Aragorn, Japanese Aragorn,
Korean Aragorn, pretty much every single one of the races.
- It's so funny, they also,
Yeah, Japanese and green, that's what you--
I didn't say green, I said Korean.
Oh, they said green.
Yeah, Chinese, Japanese, green.
I don't know why I only picked Asian-specific races.
I could have gone, I could have said Indian,
I could have said any other race.
This guy knows every--
You think Indians aren't Asian.
I'm going to make a list of every race.
I love getting him into a corner.
We got you.
I'm going to get every single race.
We have your list of every race right over there.
And then, OK, so you want to pull that over and then just
put the word Aragorn next to all of them.
They also, they can't control themselves at all,
where they get really mad about black Aragorn,
and then you look at the comments,
and they're all like,
"Yeah, and they're probably gonna make
Aragorn fucking trans too."
And it's like, "Well, they didn't, you guys."
- Yeah.
- You guys are--
- Well, you never know, could be coming out one day.
- They have, yeah, I mean, it's just so funny
to have something right in front of them
that they're so mad at, and they get so mad,
they forget what they're even,
and start yelling about something.
- I'm thinking of doing an SJW reboot of this show.
Yeah, I think that could do numbers. Do you think I would look good with like a blue like Skrillex cut?
Yeah, in the SJW thing you two are not involved by the way. No if anyone's not involved in the SJW thing
It's you. Yeah, what are you talking about? I'm the most SJW of them all. No, not a chance. I'm more SJW than any
black or lesbian or
Any other kind of person? Okay boomer. Bro chill
See, that's an SJW kind of way. A little more like surfer. Yeah. No, dude. No, I'm an SJW.
Ask me any SJW question, I'll answer it perfectly. Okay, here's one. I'm super SJW. What gender?
Oh yeah, wait, how many genders are there? Four.
(laughing)
- 365?
- Fuck.
- Okay, ask me another one, ask me another one.
- How many races are there?
- Oh, I know that one.
- This is easy.
- Yeah.
- Three.
- No.
- Fuck.
- 16.
- Shit.
- 16 races and ethnicities.
- Well, okay, then their subclasses are ethnicity.
- Subclasses.
Okay, ask me another one.
- Okay.
- Any SJW question I can answer except for those last two.
- San Jose Whalers.
- You're not saying anything.
- What?
- What is that, what could that be?
- You're just useless, ask me a question.
- What politics are good to have?
- Okay, that was my next question.
- Socialistic communism.
Where, with--
- No, it's actually socialist anarchy.
- Oh, okay.
- Is the type of good politics.
- No, I'm an SJW.
I think it's completely normal to put Christians in camps
and kill them.
I really think I'm an SJW and I think that standing in line for what a slice of bread. Yeah, that's good. Yeah
Yeah, as long as that bread is gluten-free. I actually like
Living stacked on top of each other with my neighbors like sardines in a city where every comedy has sing-songy punchlines
Yeah, and and I love queers and bugs taste good. Yeah, I want to eat bugs. Yeah
Yeah, my pod is awesome. I like PB&J. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah. And fuck it. I say I like Mac and cheese too. Yeah. Fuck me. I guess I'm an SJW. Yeah.
No. I do like to with the crust cut off. Chai latte. That. Okay. That is my number one food.
I'm better. That's a child latte and a slice of pineapple pizza. The crust. Yep. That's
J.W.
That is the best meal.
They're probably going to do what's the next next thing they're going to
woke if I probably or is that over?
I think I do think it might go the opposite direction soon
where they start and they'll maybe do the NFL.
They'll put spikes on their heads and stuff and make it murder.
Oh, yeah, I think basically they're going to reveal that America is a
is a fucking fourth reich.
- Shit, maybe. - Has been all along.
- Or fuck me, I mean.
- China and Russia will team up
and they will become a new country.
- Mate, you better be-- - Called what?
- Rhina.
- And they will fight against America.
- You better be, you better be.
- Oh, do I have a crystal ball under the table?
- You better be mucking about.
- Let me look.
- Oh, his penis is out!
(laughing)
Oh, God, don't look.
- And it is completely clear.
It is crystalline.
- Yeah, it's never seen the--
- Yeah, but we're looking at a pretty huge war
in the next two weeks. I believe that. Yeah, I think that also the some of the smaller countries
will also combine. They will follow the example of China and Russia. It is so funny that like
any time Putin... It'll be exactly like that. We're looking at guys, a lot of people are
saying that soon there will be a new world order with a global government, but you guys
are completely wrong. There's going to be seven countries and each country is a continent.
And I hope it's just new order. I hope it's a damn new order concert. It's so dope that
- Every time Putin talks about America,
or any of those Russian officials talk about America,
they always bring up the fact that America is wokey SJW now.
That is so cool.
- What is it?
- If we end up going to war with them,
and they're like, we have to eliminate the SJW scourge,
and that's why they come to America
and start killing people, that'd be so fucking cool.
- What is it, in France, when they complain about it,
like the word for woke is le woke-ism.
- Wait, le woke-ism?
- Le woke-ism?
- Le woke-ism.
- They complain about wokeness in France?
- In France, are you kidding me?
- That's the wokest country in the world!
- No, French people hate woke-ism.
- They're skinny.
- They hate woke-ism so much,
they wanna draw Muhammad every single day.
- They wanna do H-T-S-J-W-Mah-min.
- They literally want to smoke,
all French people wanna do is smoke a cigarette
and then with the ashes, draw a stick figure
and say, "That is Muhammad."
That's every single day of a French person's life.
I think that Varg from Bersam, he went to jail in France for hate speech, so tell me that's
not woke.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the ultimate.
Yeah, that guy was a...
Don't tell that dude about the Aragorn shit, by the way.
That would be really bad news.
I'm sure he was the first to know.
Yeah.
That guy has it.
Varg has a Google alert in a mystical scrying pool for the term "Black Aragorn," and he
refreshes it every...
Swirls it around with a staff.
Let me tell you though, the screams on that next album
are gonna be agonizing.
Do you guys think that--
'Cause he's black Aragorn.
Do you guys think that we are like maybe the forefront
of cultural commentary at this point?
Yeah, as of this episode, as of everything we just said.
Can I do a cultural commentary?
Fuck yes.
So it's actually rather ironic that
Russia hates SJWs as SJWs are Russia
and communism's biggest fans.
Oh fuck.
It almost speaks to a dichotomy in the political climate.
- Yeah.
- And the climate is changing, politically.
- Okay, you had me until that point, Greta Thunberg.
- Materia fucking Lee. - Shut your bitch ass up.
- Materia fucking Lee, the climate is changing.
Today it's 60 degrees, yesterday it was 30 degrees.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- What's up with that?
- Greta Thunberg, little bug looking.
- No, no, we're canceling you.
- Don't cancel me.
- You're can, yep, you just got canceled by me.
- Okay, so 'cause cancel culture is real.
I mean, look at Louis C.K., look at...
Who else?
I had to do that, I had to plug the plasma ball in.
Look at Patrick Doran, people come back for cancellation.
True, you're right. Patrick is a perfect example of how you can do the most disgusting, immoral acts publicly.
And people will pay you thousands of dollars a month.
And you can still have a career. Like it's really impressive, it really is.
Like you can ruin lives and lives and lives, like plenty of people's lives.
Lives on lives on lives.
- Lives on lives.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- You can ruin lives on lives on lives.
And you can be a white skinhead,
W-H-T-E skinhead over here.
- White skinhead?
- That's your song.
- There's nothing Nazi about me.
- The way you just said that.
- I did not see that coming.
- Yeah.
- Cultural commentary.
- Well speaking of Nazis,
today we're looking at psychopaths online.
- Yeah, I'm looking at a couple psychopaths right now.
- Hey, blah.
- I'm looking at a twisted psychopath right here.
- Wait, really quickly, can we each do
our best psychopath impression?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- I think I'm going crazy.
- That's mine. - You go next.
- Okay, 'cause he's gonna do something funny
for the third one. - Yeah.
- Okay.
- All the better to kill you with, this my knife, my dear.
- Okay, good.
- Ladies and gentlemen, I'm your president,
Barack Hussein Obama.
- It's not even a good Obama impression.
I did an amazing job.
- Yeah, but if it, no, but think about it,
because he's the bit you see my eye twister oh wait here's a good psychopath
impression go to your room a parent my parents yeah yeah you have a lunch
detention yeah no cussing mm-hmm no cussing in my house you know what
another piece of cultural commentary we can hit really quick here's another
piece of psychopathy prevalent right now I expect a 20% plus tip bro yeah don't
even make me think about it. And all I do is press orders on an iPad. I almost lunged at
you because I thought that you were actually being a fucking barista turning the iPad. No,
I would never have a tip. Yeah, you turn me that thing, the toast, it says toast on it,
how about I come in here with a flamethrower and make you toast? You turn that iPad towards
me, I'm hitting the home button, I'm downloading Angry Birds on that thing, and I'm making
the line wait. I'm playing the full fucking, I'm playing the free trial. Choose your tip,
I click custom, I'm going into the negatives.
Now you're paying me because I look cute today.
- Yeah, I look at the receipt, it says recommended tip.
Yeah, I recommend you zip up your body bag
'cause it's gonna make people throw up
if they see what's in there.
- The tip of my knife, the tip of my gun,
the only tips that you'll be getting today--
- Is none. - Is none.
And also I'm rhyming while I'm killing you, Mr. Panera Bread.
That's right.
I think we should replace all people with human robots.
- I think we should replace all people with humans.
- Yep.
- That's right.
- Because those people, some people out there, they're NPCs.
- But they're not humans.
- Yeah.
- They're not humans and you can do anything you want
to them and it doesn't matter.
- No, don't even.
- I think every person should be a human.
- Moral problem.
- Don't even bring up NPC culture to me.
- Sorry.
- My bad.
- Because that shit scares the fuck out of me.
- Yeah.
- Literally people walking around on walk cycles.
- Yeah, here's NPC culture.
- Hey, don't fall asleep on the furniture at Ikea.
NPC.
That's an NPC tells you that.
- I say, okay, NPC.
Fuck you, double fuck you.
If I wanna fall asleep on the toilet at Home Depot.
- Hey, don't use the toilet at Home Depot.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, what?
- Don't use all the toilets at Home Depot like jackass.
- Man, suck my dick, NPC.
Pause game.
- I'm on the Dave England level.
- Pause game, no clip.
Chop your head off in the Home Depot.
Fuck you.
- Don't draw on the wall.
- I click the Teal Day or whatever that button is.
Is that Teal Day?
- Teal Day.
the little thing in the corner. - Field day!
- I click that little squiggly button.
- Yeah. - I type in
quote,
COC,
QA smoke.
I go in there, I get all the Daedric armor, I come back.
- Yeah. - And then I just start slayin'.
- Just obliterate every single person in the Home Depot.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's not a bad idea.
But we are talking about Psycho-Pass today.
And this is, I found a little website
- It's called the Sociopath Community.
- Okay.
- This is a forum for, as you can probably guess.
- A forum for sociopathic crazies.
- Damn!
- Yeah, this is the one that I was trying to find
at one point, but I couldn't.
- Okay.
- Oh, thank you for giving me my clicker.
- I turned it on for you.
- So this is Sociopath Community.
This is the first post that I found
on the Sociopath Community forums.
Asked a homeless woman for a blowjob.
This is from user Allure and he says,
"There was this homeless woman
"who was begging for small change.
"I offered her $10 for a blow job.
"I don't know what prices sex workers charge,
"but it was better than nothing.
"She wasn't in a bad shape.
"She looked like she was homeless for maybe a few days.
"Anyway, she declined.
"I do shit like this impulsively and it's scary.
"I'm reminded I don't really know myself."
- Damn. - Wow.
- So you have to be pretty psycho
to wanna fuck a fucking disgusting homeless woman.
- Yeah, a disgusting few days of homelessness.
- Is that really what this guy looks like?
- Yep, that's a painting of him.
- That's a painting of him?
- Yeah, he has a bunch of different posts
where he talks about, he has one where he ranks
his favorite philosophers, and he gave Sun Tzu his S tier,
and he gave Benjamin Franklin F.
- Well yeah, S for Sun Tzu and then F for Franklin.
- You're a fucking genius.
- When I was reading about posts from psychopaths
and sociopaths online and stuff, it is funny that,
I feel like some of them you read and you're like,
"Oh my God, this person needs some help.
Something's going on here."
And that's a lot of them you read and it's like,
this is somebody who like,
they saw the matrix code by like reading,
like watching Fight Club and they got something out of it
that nobody else in the world got out of it.
And it changed the way they lived their life forever.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I feel like they like,
somehow they read philosophy and they don't become
like a lit guy who's like a book nerd.
They somehow an evil person.
- Speaking of lit, guys. - Pretty smart.
- Yep, us three. - Damn.
- Us three, what's up?
- What's next over here? - We took some fucking K2
before we recorded. - You wish.
Slowly turning into an animal.
(laughing)
So this is a better title than it is a actual thing.
This says, if you could turn into any animal at will,
but in doing so, every time it got harder to turn back
until you started developing hybrid features and senses,
which animal would you choose?
Of course, you could just seldom use,
if and maybe only become a bit hairier, et cetera,
by the end of your life.
- I don't wanna be hairier by the end of my life.
- Fuck no!
- I got enough hair, I mean you guys have seen me
at the pool.
- You need to become, you need to turn into a dolphin.
- Yeah.
- Dolphins have hair, don't they?
- Dolphins don't have hair.
- They're mammals, I thought.
- Man, don't mammals have hair?
- Shut up.
- They have alopecia.
- They have very little hair.
- Why not say like a snake?
- Basically it's like a sphinx cat.
- Like something with no hair.
- It's like a sphinx cat when you touch a dolphin.
- But a dolphin is a good thing to be also.
- Feels like yo nuts.
- What?
a dolphin it feels exactly like the human nutsack.
- That's not true. - I'm not sure that's true at all.
- You've never been to sea world.
- It's tight, I know it feels like a pussay.
- Yeah, I think it feels like a blowhole.
- No, that's the blowhole.
- A man about my size.
- No, the whole skin. - The blowhole feels like
a pussay. - No, the whole skin.
No, no, no, no, no.
- But the skin feels like nuts.
(laughing)
Skin feel like nuts, blowhole feel like pussay.
- You're lying.
- You're lying. - You're lying.
You've never touched a dolphin in your life.
- I've touched a dolphin.
- You've never touched a dolphin.
- Yeah, Dolphin Emulator played Herb's Moon.
- You touch a doll's fin, yeah, her finny.
- No. - You touch a doll's finny.
- Touched a doll's finny.
- You did, didn't you? - No, I didn't.
- You went up to the doll and touched the finny.
You pedophile. - I did not touch
a doll's finny. - You're an arse
and you touched a doll's finny. - I did not touch
a doll's finny. - You are.
- No. - You touched a doll's finny.
- Did not touch it. - You did.
- You've completely lost the plot.
- Mate. - You're mental.
It's funnier when we just don't do the accent and say that.
Mate, you've lost the plot.
You've lost the plot, mate.
You're daft.
You're completely daft.
Are you taking the piss?
This whole weekend--
Oh, what the blood?
[LAUGHTER]
This whole weekend, I kept-- every time I texted you guys,
I started it with mates.
Yeah.
Mates.
Because it's St. Paddy's Day, guys.
Legends.
I was on a complete different tiff.
It's so fun to text your girlfriend and say,
I'll be home later.
I'm out having a pint with the lads.
I just text, pigs have your bunda.
And then a question mark.
Yeah.
Pics of your poonda?
Poonda?
Isn't that what they say?
I don't know.
That bird has a nice poonda!
You never heard that?
No.
Couple of birds, couple of 8.5s with nice poondas.
You never seen that video of that guy where he's like, "Manchester, top scratch, horrid
flans and a poonda, the tens have got poondas."
You never seen that guy?
No.
He's this British guy who talks about every city in the UK.
London, England.
and he talks about what the nightclub is like.
- Yeah.
- He's like, "Tulpscrum, tons of poonder."
- Scran or scram?
- Scran.
- Scran like food, right? - That's food, yeah.
Yeah, so it'll be a picture of the most disgusting
French fries you've ever seen.
He's like, "Tulpscrum," and then a woman with a big ass,
"Giant poonders."
- Poonder?
- "Fatty poonders."
- I think that's the right word.
- I don't know.
- Fat poonders.
- Okay, I don't--
- Tons of scrum.
- I don't wanna hear it anymore.
- And a cobblestone wrench.
- I feel like I'm going crazy.
- And I go, whoa.
- A cobblestone wrench?
- He says nonsense shit.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- And there's a gobbler, a one-eyed,
flying purple people eater,
right there in the downtown Manchester.
I go, okay, I think I will go there.
Slowly turning into an animal,
this guy asks which animal.
This person says, an owl,
and their profile photo is of an owl.
(laughing)
This person is a dangerous psychopath,
that they need to be in jail.
- Yeah, look at their eyes.
- Look at, they're crazy.
- They have crazy eyes.
- Yeah, what, you wanna be an owl
so you can turn your head all the way around
to scare your victim?
Yeah, fuck you.
Am I a sociopath?
I feel empty and angry all the time.
I work in a head shop and sell minors drugs all the time
and even steal from the register.
I don't care about anyone or anything.
I just thought that one was badass.
That's from ADNGR.
- Dopeness.
- A-danger.
- ADNGR.
- Oh my God, they're a danger.
- Now get this.
- This is a forum post called Dark Memes.
- I don't, just skip this part.
- Okay, no, I'm not gonna skip it.
If you like dark memes, I want you to go ahead
and turn on your screen and watch this dark meme,
'cause look at this.
This is, if her soap looks like this, you're getting laid.
And it's a bar of soap with a bunch of disgusting
little puby worms all over it.
- Ew. - Yeah.
- And another-- - That was posted by a bat.
Yeah, another animal profile photo.
Anyone else think that looked like SpongeBob?
Yeah.
If my soap looks like that, I'm getting laid.
Yeah, I'm sticking the soap up my butt.
Yeah.
Dark memes.
Damn.
Yeah, and I'm killing my whole family with the soap.
That would be a darker twist.
I'm going to hell for this one.
Yeah, let's do like--
let's make these even darker.
I think we can punch those up.
I think we just make them darker.
But with the soap-- yeah.
If her soap looks like this--
If her soap looks like this, I'm slitting the soap's throat.
If her soap looks like this, she's
going to look like this, too.
Yeah, if her soap looks like this,
if her soap looks like this, you do a hundred abortions.
That's like dark humor, I think.
Yeah, they do.
That is something I'm noticing in psychopath
and sociopath communities when I was browsing.
They do not have any boundaries at all
when it comes to discussing abortion.
They love dark humor and abortion.
They say, every single post, they say,
I, yeah, I'm a sociopath.
I wouldn't care if a lady got a hundred abortions.
Well, that's the thing.
You, 4% of people, one to 4% of people are sociopaths.
Guess what percentage of people are also abortionist doctors?
- Fuck, probably 4%, right?
- I think 50 to 60% after 2009, but yeah, pretty scary.
But some of them are sociopaths.
- Well, based on those numbers, it would be all of them,
'cause 4% is only a part of 50%.
- But some of the guys are sociopaths.
All of the sociopaths are, you're misunderstanding,
all of the sociopaths are definitely abortionist MD doctors,
but only some of the doctors are abortionists.
- I know about a sociopath.
There's a sociopath doctor on TV.
- What's his name?
- Dr. House, yeah, he doesn't feel much.
- Yeah, he basically hates human emotion.
- Did he ever do an abortion?
- No.
- I never watched a single piece of that show.
- Well, you need an abortion.
- You never seen a piece of it?
- No, I've never even seen it.
- Didn't they make Cal Penn kill himself?
- I don't remember.
- Yeah.
- Everybody kills themselves and fucks each other.
- They make Cal Penn kill himself
and then he comes back like two seasons later
'cause he was done being Obama's intern.
- Olivia Munn has ALS in that movie, or in that show.
- Wow, yeah.
And Lou Gehrig's disease.
- That's what's so awful, it's like the worst thing ever
'cause it's the most beautiful woman.
And to think of her slowly turning into a cube
or whatever is so scary.
- When I was in third grade, I did a project on Lou Gehrig,
like a book report.
- The man?
- And yeah, and then I learned about his disease
and everything. - My man.
- I learned about the disease and everything.
And then like a friend of a, my mom's friend,
like died in their sleep.
And my mom was just like,
"Yeah, I just don't know how that could happen."
And I turned to my mom and I was like, could be ALS.
- Wow.
- Could be Lou Gehrig's disease.
- You diagnosed her right there.
- She could have died of Lou Gehrig's disease in her sleep.
- Okay, what's next?
You are gay, and then they posted the
why are you gay funniest African interview,
and then they responded, said,
"I'd honestly like my own post here if I could.
This vid is brilliant."
- Okay.
- Yeah, so this guy's definitely sociopathic vibes.
- You would have to be a sociopath
to like your own post though.
- 100%.
- That's a clear sign.
- Absolutely. - No doubt.
- Yeah.
- Don't even care for social norms.
- He's breaking the rules of the internet,
user 222212.
- A shadow not so far.
- Spider bursts out of a banana.
This is the kind of sick shit that these sociopaths
think is funny or interesting.
A spider bursts out of a banana.
Tell you what that's not, to me, is a good time
or something worth talking about or looking at.
If you share that video to another person,
you are literally a sadist.
You're scum!
Okay, what's next?
Where is Hillary?
Oh my God.
And this is by Donald Trump in 2019.
Hello folks, has anybody seen Crooked Hillary around?
I've received word that she comes here.
Not much of a surprise, I'd say.
She always was a loser.
Let me know if you've seen her.
That was Donald Trump.
Wow.
And he's looking for Hillary.
And he's on the phone?
He's on the sociopathic community forum
because he's trying to put,
Hillary's trying to lock her up and put her in jail.
and he's like, where would a sociopath like Hillary hang out?
Probably the sociopath.
- The sociopath.
- And the person who made this thought of the joke
in November 19th, 2019.
- It took a while.
- It only took them three years.
- It took a while, but--
- To think of doing this.
- There is one response to this post
that I think is pretty good,
and this is from Big Chungus,
and he says, "She's under my desk, sucking my chuncus."
(laughing)
And this guy--
- Talk about a sociopath, my God.
- This guy has a pretty good
- 38 posts. - Posting history.
Yeah, and I took a look at those.
Chungus Chungus, major major,
how big is your Chungus, and me, by Big Chungus.
So, Big Chungus is a sociopath.
- Wow.
- Okay, that's the end of all mine.
- All right, here's what I found.
I wanna preface everything before this.
I just wanna say that, I mean, you guys remember
back in like July 2020, I was diagnosed with psychosis.
- Psychosis?
I was going through about a psychosis.
I don't really remember that.
I'm not sure I remember that either.
Juby if you want to click over to my...
Psychosis or psychopathy?
Click over to my thing, my slide.
Wait, psychosis is a different thing.
Do you realize that...
I was diagnosed with psychopathy.
Okay.
So why did you say psychosis?
Psychosis is something different.
Well...
Psychosis is like...
There's a very public meltdown...
Psychosis is like the elephants on parade scene.
Yeah.
There's a very public meltdown that I had and someone filmed it and I'm just gonna...
You know what?
I'm gonna come...
There's a thing about mental health.
I'm just gonna come forward with it.
I'm just gonna show you.
Okay, Ted Lasso.
If that played automatically,
this would have been a lot funnier.
Guys, that's what the audio listen is.
It's the Tasmanian Devil.
It's a video cartoon network,
the Tasmanian Devil.
I thought it was gonna be in slideshow mode
in slideshow mode and it would have played automatically.
- Yo, those noises be when I'm eating that.
(imitates eating noises)
- You going (imitates eating noises)
- All right, but I needed to find, I was--
- 'Cause it's so gross.
(imitates eating noises)
- 'Cause I'm throwing up every single time.
But I was looking through, this is a forum I found.
It's not the Psychopaths Forum or the Sociopath Forum
or anything like that.
- But it's close, yeah.
- It's close, it's xnxx.com, or forum.xnxx.com.
- Damn.
post that says, "Daddy, what is a psycho nut job?"
- You can never--
- "Honey, there is a person here at XNXX
that does not like us.
Here is an example of the post that he made to our thread.
Every post we make, the same person responds
with the message, 'Daddy, why'"
Fuck, I get to just put it--
- "Daddy, why don't the moderators do anything about it?
Flaming is why the forum is so popular.
Daddy, what is flaming?
Honey, use the search function.
I don't know why you don't zoom in before you take the screenshot.
I always think that I'm going to be able to read it,
but then I never can.
You need to start bringing your glasses.
Yeah, I need to start bringing my glasses.
Or just zoom in.
This is in response to this, where they're
trying to role play together, and this guy just responds,
psycho nut job, psycho nut job.
And it's basically the whole thread
gets flamed with psycho nut job all the way down.
- Is this a sexual position?
Or is he calling them a psycho nut job?
- He's calling them psycho nut jobs.
- I would enjoy it.
- I was thinking like, yeah, I want a psycho nut job.
- Yeah, I'd be down with that.
- Psycho make me nut.
- But imagine being on the XNXX forums
and being like, man, you fucking role players are psychopaths.
- That's fine.
- I logged into XNXX.com.
- If I was a Christian, more of a Christian, sorry.
If I was more of a Christian,
And then I would be leading a team of underage people
who go on and they press the I'm over 18
and then go on the forums and say,
actually I was 16 this entire time.
And the Xanax forum and then get it completely destroyed.
- Well here's the next thing,
this is somebody coming to their aid.
Leroy Brown, who's also a role player, says,
yo Joey-- - I've heard some bad things
about Leroy Brown. - Me too.
- I've heard he's the baddest guy in the city.
- The whole damn town. - Old Jim Walker
tried to play him in pool.
- God damn, I can't believe he's posting on here.
- But he said, "Yo, Joliet,
"need some help teaching dat dude a lesson?
"I don't personally get my hands dirty,
"but I got some friends close to Joliet."
And they said, "Go away, troll, go away, troll,"
and then flamed the fucking post like that.
- They totally flamed him. - They flamed the post
like that. (laughing)
Psycho Nutjob is someone with nothing else
of value to contribute, so he stupidly repeats
the same meaningless words like psycho nutjob,
And then there's another Joliet script here.
Daddy, why did you kill yourself?
Honey, I committed suicide
because I felt I was no longer wanted.
How could you do that?
I love you.
I love you too, honey, goodbye.
Daddy, does that mean we are not going to Pizza Hut tonight?
Maybe tomorrow.
Bitch, you dead.
- I would say that you did actually do
more of a kind of psychosis-themed one,
because none of this is making any sense to me.
- Yeah, I don't really understand.
What is--
Don't you think your spamming game is stale?
From Pussy Patrol and they're suspended.
- So XNXX is a website for psychopaths?
- Well, there's some more.
- Yeah.
- Well, they get into some psychopathic topics here.
Like, has anyone ever seen a snuff film?
Do you believe it was real?
- No, but I've seen a sniff film.
That's right, the Wild Thornberrys movie.
- Yep.
Do you think it was real or just good production?
What was your reaction?
Just watch some YouTube of shock and ah,
attack on Baghdad or some of Obama's drone takeouts.
Hell, don't you watch the news?
Plenty of snuff videos.
- That is true, the news has been going wild.
- Yeah, I haven't seen snuff videos,
but I've seen stuff videos.
- Yep.
- Pretty good amount of stuff videos.
- Cribs.
- Yeah.
- It would be a stuff video.
- Impractical jokers.
- There's that motherfucking guy in Louisiana
who sometimes will make some kind of stuffed chicken.
- Yeah. - Scalecracker.
- Is that the guy's like, what happened to who?
- Yeah.
- First you put the butter on the grill.
- Yep, that guy, I love that.
- Oh my god, I just thought of a really good idea.
- What?
- It's like Build-A-Bear workshop.
It's basically all the same type of steps,
but it's like a food place.
- That's pretty good.
- Oh, where you go down a line and you--
- Yeah, but it's not like you're,
like they have the thing where you fill the bear
with stuffing, but it's with food.
- What kind of food would you pick?
- Well, I think you can pick whatever.
I'm trying to, I'm still puzzling it out.
I just thought of it as a--
- It could be mostly liquid or foam.
- Well no, it could be like, okay,
it could be a dessert place,
so maybe you could be making a donut that's filled with--
- You just invented fro-yo.
- I would put maybe chipotle--
- Since when is fro-yo inside of a bear?
- Oh, you eat it out. - Oh my god.
- So wait, the bear is made out of--
- The bear part could be edible too.
It could be a pastry, it could be anything.
- Yeah, so you're making kind of a pot pie thing.
- Well I'm saying, I haven't figured,
the idea of putting food inside something.
- That's your idea?
- Okay, but in a Build-A-Bear workshop setting.
It's Build-A-Bear workshop, but the bear is edible.
- You already said that, but what's in the bear?
- How is that frozen yogurt?
- Well, I'm not saying it's frozen yogurt anymore,
I'm just, I don't know what the idea is.
- Oh, an edible bear. - I'm trying to find
an edible bear.
- Fine, it's a bear and it's edible.
- But what's the bear made out of?
Tortillas. - Some kind of edible food.
- Just name one. (laughing)
It's a bear made out of tortillas.
- Is it tortilla or is it puff pastry?
- Do you want it to be, okay, do you want it to be,
there's two stores on there next to each other,
and one is for desserts and one is for foods.
And the foods one, it is tortillas,
and you can put in vegetables and meats inside it.
And the dessert one, it's some kind of--
- How did you get to this, how did you jump to this idea?
- Stuffing!
- It's a taco place, though.
- No, because it's in a bar! - Oh my god, wait, no,
and it's called Stuffings.
The restaurant is called Stuffings.
- Which one is, there's two now.
- It's called Stuffings and Stuffings PM.
And PM is the dessert one. - PM?
- Yeah, you eat it in the evening 'cause it's dessert.
but the other one you can eat any time of the day.
- There's also a breakfast one called stuffings.
- Yeah, man, you fill it with eggs.
- But is it the tortilla again?
- Yeah.
- So it's a tortilla that kind of looks like a--
- Or it could be pancake, it could be pancake.
- You look crazy right now.
Your eyes, I've never seen them that wide.
- You've gone into psychosis.
- When you are in a psychotic stuffing--
- It's a good idea that you're--
- It's a terrible idea.
- Fighting against for no reason.
- Because it doesn't, why is the tortilla a bear?
How do you make a bear-shaped tortilla?
- Why is that the issue?
Why, it's--
- How big is this?
- Okay, then it's a pita.
- Why is this a pita?
- Show me the pita pocket that's shaped like a bear.
- But why is it a bear?
It could just be a tortilla.
- Because then it's not cool.
- That's the style?
- That's the cool thing about what you're--
- Are you paying extra?
Is it like, how expensive is it?
- It's just a fun thing.
- It's not a good idea.
- Okay.
- It's a bad idea.
- Okay, well here, no.
- Here's deleted user who was banned maybe for this post.
- Caleb goes to every restaurant and he says,
why isn't this in a slurry?
Why can't I blend this all up and eat it?
It's presentation.
- I think a food Build-A-Bear workshop idea.
- Yeah, it's a good idea.
- It's not a good idea.
- It's a good idea.
- So tell me just--
- I think it's a good idea.
- Okay, so no help from Patrick.
- He was helping me a lot.
- Walk me down the line.
- I know, walk me down the line.
- Okay, do you want the dessert one
or the dinner one or the breakfast one?
- Here, no, you walk in and I work there.
It's the other one.
- There's no employees.
- Hi, welcome to Stuffings.
It's the most fucking stupid idea of all time
and I work here.
- There's no employees.
- No, go ahead, go get your food.
So if it's the dinner one, you start with bread.
It's a bread bowl shaped like a bear.
Are you gonna yell about how a bowl can't be bear shaped?
- It can, it's just stupid.
- And then you're like, oh, maybe I want chili in it.
Maybe I want mac and cheese.
Maybe I want a mix of both.
Oh, but if I want both, it costs a little extra.
Well, I really want chili and mac and cheese mixed,
so I guess I'll pay a little extra for that.
And then you get to use,
and of course there will be other stuff too,
which I'm not good at thinking of food,
but you can say any food that could be in a bread bowl.
- I'm not good at thinking.
- 'Cause you're attacking me.
- Okay.
- You're putting me in a defense position.
And then you use the machine where you get to fill it up
and you get to watch it fill up,
which is the main fun part.
The bread is-- - How do you eat it?
- Then you--
(laughing)
- Do you cut the head off and eat the brain?
- No, you just bite into it like it's a burrito.
- It's a Hot Pocket.
- Yeah, it's a Hot Pocket.
- It's a bear-shaped Hot Pocket.
- Okay, I built a bear for a Hot Pocket.
That still is fine of an idea.
That's not a thing that exists.
You're saying it like you're defeating me.
You're making me stronger.
- This, him talking about this Build-A-Bear thing
made me realize I messed up the prompt
for the research I was supposed to do.
- 'Cause you were searching psychosis?
- Yeah, and not psychopathy.
And, well, I found this poll.
This will be the last thing I talk about
on the XNXX forums.
What are your favorite circumstances for shitting?
And the favorite time and place to take a shit is
when I know people are waiting impatiently for the toilet.
That's psychopath behavior.
Yeah, that's one of those.
In the morning after a strong cup of coffee, psychopath.
That's not a psychopath, that's me.
That's kind of normal.
Yeah, that's me.
OK.
I don't love it, but I wouldn't say it's my favorite.
Out in the woods, in the bushes with a little view.
It wouldn't be my favorite, but you'd do it enough
that you'd have to like it at some point.
Yeah, kind of just normalcy.
Out in the woods, in the bushes with a little view.
No, that's not right either.
That's psychopathic behavior.
I've never taken an outside poop.
I don't think I have either.
When no one else is home and I can really
take the time to do it right.
at work maybe around 3 p.m. that's nice on my ex's carpet seeing as how I still
have a key to that is psychopathic behavior so the most popular is when no
one else is home and I really take the time to do it right I gotta say I'm a
full in the morning after a strong cup of coffee yeah I need to have it needs
to feel like a heart attack I've been in this one here what's my last thing I
can't click it I can't click it oh I just took my second shit it was so huge
and good I feel lighter excited emoji and then is Donald Trump mentally ill?
Oh you put that Donald Trump stuff. Yeah. Yes yes and yes Donald is mentally ill
and he is our president how crazy is that you have to love him and you need
to quit picking on the mentally ill I think and that yeah I really whiffed it
on this one that's okay this whole episode's kind of been. You were out of
So you were out this weekend.
I was out this weekend.
I did not have time to do proper research.
I was in the lovely city of Boston.
Yeah, and who cares?
Yeah, we don't need to hear about this.
Here's mine.
I'll go fast, I guess.
So I looked at r/sociopath on Reddit,
which is a community for the empathetically challenged.
And I love this vaporwave style header photo.
It's pretty cool.
I put it in there because I thought it was kind of aesthetic.
It's kind of reminding me of, speaking of The Simpsons,
maybe Bart with some sleepy eyes driving down the street.
- Yeah, true.
- Yeah.
- I think the statute of limitations on speaking of
was up on The Simpsons.
Took me a second to remember we were speaking
of The Simpsons.
- Uh-huh, hmm.
Hell, we can speak of The Simpsons.
- That's true, I guess The Simpsons is ever green,
ever yellow.
- Shit, man.
- There's multiple, there's multiple,
there's also r/psychopath and r/psychopathy,
but they're all, so I forget which one is which,
but there's one of them that's only people saying,
I wanna fucking kill and eat a pregnant woman,
I'm fucking evil, and then half of it is also like,
can we get these trolls out of here?
And that's all it is.
And there's one that's been like banned.
And then there's one that's like
from a purely psychological standpoint,
and it's all like therapists talking.
But this is the only interesting one,
r/sociopath, I had to find it.
So let's look at some posts from r/sociopath.
How competitive, they wrote, are you at games?
- This is NSFW.
- Everything on this subreddit is NSFW.
I hope so. I don't want to be, can you imagine your boss walking in on you looking at the
r/sociopath thing? Yeah. And then he would probably go, yeah me too because I'm the boss.
Damn. He'd go, wait. Wait. And he's like even more than you. Bosses are sociopaths. Yeah.
Hold on, that's actually scary in a societal way. That makes hella sense. I'd have my sound
board next to me and go, hold up. Yeah. Hold up. Hey! If you're always winning, then it's
just repetitive and boring. No challenge, nothing new, you know? And then someone else
response and says do you always win and they reply and say not always but I try
to do you always win I said if you're always winning it's boring and then
they're like well I don't always win the always I would just lie and just say
yeah yeah I'm a sociopath yeah I want exactly why to get my way
yep yeah I spent three years in prison over a monopoly game extremely wrong I
don't I don't believe that I thought it was funny though it is funny but that
- I'm not that motherfucking lying about that shit.
- Again, it's r/sociopath.
- So you think that they're all--
- They're all lying.
- 'Cause they're sociopaths.
- They are compulsive liars from being sociopathic.
- Can we even trust them on the point
that they're sociopaths?
- I really don't think we can.
- That's kind of scary.
- Which is one of the funny things,
is a lot of people are trying really hard
to be sociopaths on here.
It's very funny.
What do you fantasize about?
Violence, fame, money, success, power?
It can be anything.
Fantasies can tell a lot about a person's mental state
and overall mentality.
More specifically, their desires and dreams.
Here's what one person fantasizes about.
I've been a DM for over, a dungeon master,
for over 25 years and I've helped others fantasize
about magic realms, gritty industrial landscapes
of concrete and steel, vast oceanic flows
that enable ships and exceptionally strong swimmers
to travel between worlds, of realms where mankind
dominates all, where mankind struggles to exist,
and where mankind never existed at all.
Magical swords with demented spirits shackled to them,
seeking to enslave or serve.
whoever dares to wield them,
psychic powers and divine entities
clashing with future tech giants
of ceramic plate and fusion drives,
whimsical elves, hardworking and hard partying dwarves,
and other races that would take too long to explain.
What do I fantasize about?
Everything.
- Can you read through all of that?
That is all gun city.
- Yeah, that is word for word.
- That is gun city, word for word.
- That's starting to worry me a lot
that maybe Patches has some psychotic behavior.
- This was the top comment on this too.
Everyone else was saying like,
Yeah, sometimes I fantasize about beating up a woman and killing her and chopping her up.
And that's what everyone uploaded this one instead.
Is there a psychopath test that's like basically a riddle?
Yeah.
But...
Why don't we do that?
Are they a Blade Runner?
No, no, no.
No, there's some little riddle.
Yeah, we'll do it at the end, but you can finish it.
Okay.
What is your favorite music genre?
Psycho Billy.
Okay, can we guess?
Yeah.
Psycho Billy.
Hip-hop.
Rockabilly.
There is a lot of hip-hop, a lot of metal.
they said metal and hip hop. I really like, there's a new innovation, I think it's the
next one here, in type of music. Here we go. Video game OSTs, original soundtracks are
my favorite. Apart from that, I listen to almost every genre. I've always hated country
and opera. It's so funny to me, I listen to everything except country and opera. Imagine
that you say you listen to everything and someone would be like, "Oh, so you like opera?"
- Yeah.
- It's like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Yeah, opera equals crap.
- I'm fine with rap, but I do not like opera.
- Opera is, I will say, opera's terrible.
I don't listen to opera.
- No, I wouldn't listen, yeah, I think it's kind of like a,
it's a tacit agreement that everybody assumes
when you say everything, you don't mean opera.
- Yeah, I don't like opera, I don't like ringtones.
- All these opera singers are going,
me, me, me, me, me, I don't care about you, you, you, you.
- Yeah, sing about me, me, me, me, me, me.
- And my friends, my friends, my friends, my friends.
- My experience, my experiences, my experiences,
my experiences.
(laughing)
- 50s doo-wop and 90s grunge.
- Okay, I like the decade.
What I would listen to, 90s doo-wop and 50s grunge.
Oh, fuck me.
- I think 50s doo-wop is the most chilling thing
a psychopath can listen to.
- I agree.
- And 90s grunge is the most chill thing.
- Yep.
- Yeah, I just went there.
If your life was a movie, what would viewers think?
- What the fuck?
- Damn, that's a cold ass honky.
- Yeah, I just picked one from here.
- They'd puke.
(laughing)
- No elaboration at all.
Yo, what up?
What up, peoples?
(laughing)
- That's a post on our site, Sociopathic.
- That is sociopathic shit.
- Yo, what up?
- What are your opinions on having kids?
- Here's what, okay, can I?
- Yeah.
- If I'm responding to this, I'm saying,
hmm, kids are pretty good for dinner.
That would be my sociopathic response.
I like having kids for lunch and dinner. Yeah, and most of them say I don't care for kids very much
They say I think they're a little crotch goblins. Oh, they all say that a bunch. That's like they're that's like they're agreed
That's like calling someone an ass clown. I guess
It's yeah, it's a thing that everyone thought was a funny thing to say now. They all say it call kids crotch cockroach goblin
Yeah, but this person says it would be really cool to have a demon like child who I can teach to manipulate and conquer everything
- What did you blur out on?
- I don't know why it's black, it's supposed to be white.
I was trying to crop it.
- Oh, okay.
- It's just not funny, it's just a longer comment.
- Yeah, I don't know why it's all,
it's supposed to be white.
- I thought you were making your sensory--
- No, you can move it if you want.
- I thought maybe that was that guy's full name.
- No.
- It was that long.
- Full name and address.
- And I live here, and this is my full name.
It would be cool to have a demon-like child.
- No.
- Not a demon child.
- Conquer everything.
- A demon-like child.
- I don't think I'd want a demon-like child.
- Well because you would be bad at raising him.
- I would not want a demon-like child
unless I could manipulate them.
- Yeah, into conquering.
- 'Cause if they are against me, I'm toast.
I'm not demon-like. - True.
- I maybe have demonic thoughts.
- But also, you have dad strength.
- True.
- So if a demon--
- I could twist their little head off.
- Yeah, I'd grab 'em by their ear.
- Yeah.
- Come here!
- Or their horn maybe.
- Yeah, you grab 'em by the horn for sure
'cause that's where all those sensitive bones--
I grab demon-like children by the horns.
Yeah.
Yeah, straight up.
You grab it by both their horns,
'cause the ears, they're gonna scream.
You know.
And I'm throwing 'em, doing a whole sideways spin around.
Mario, Bowser.
We're throwing Mario, Bowser.
Trunchbull.
Yeah, and then I throw 'em into--
That would be my demon kid's name, Trunchbull.
But it would be sad as fuck when you get
to the fucking kingdom of heaven and your son is--
Not allowed.
Yeah, because of how he looks.
True.
And you say, wait,
that's fucking heavenistic racism.
- Would they let you into heaven
if you had a demon-like child?
- If you had a whole--
- Or by association with--
- No, you're fine. - Yeah, you'd probably go to--
- You probably fucked a demon to get a demon-like child.
- You could probably have a nice-ass spot in hell, though,
'cause it's like, damn, like--
- If there's one thing about hell,
I hope there is no fire in hell,
'cause I do not wanna get burned.
- Here's my-- - I got some bad news for you.
- As long as it's not-- - It's pretty much
mostly fire. - It's fire.
- As long as it's not red, then I'm fine with hell.
- Okay, I-- - You are in for
- Hell sounds kinda poppin'.
- Yeah.
- I kinda like the idea of it, but I really don't,
as long as there's not a guy in charge named the devil.
- Yeah, that would suck.
- What?
- Bruv.
- You're not gonna like it.
- I just don't wanna go to heaven.
I don't wanna go to heaven 'cause I hear
it's full of brimstone, and I fuckin' hate that shit.
So I think I'd rather go to hell.
- Yeah.
Do you leave a trail of destruction?
Looking back on all my life, the groups that I joined
always ended up with conflict within.
- I bet there's plenty of big fatties
that do leave a trail of destruction on this website.
- This person left a trail of destruction.
Yeah, I have a proven track record
of angering others into apoplexy.
- Whoa!
- Whether that be with my grammar Nazism,
my astute observations, my cynical and nihilistic worldview,
or my blatant hostile disregard
for those with religious beliefs,
yes, I have left many swaths of destruction
online and in person.
- Swaths.
- That's so cool to list all those.
- Yeah.
- Am I cynical or nihilistic?
World view.
- My grammar, opening with my grammar and Nazism
is so funny.
- Yeah.
- I've left a trail of destruction.
- That's the first one you want people to know about.
- I've caused in-group conflict by correcting people's
grammar. - Did you mean your?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- Okay.
Be honest.
Do you actually give a fuck about what's happening
in Ukraine?
- No!
- And this is a poll.
- These psychos better, okay.
- And now I have, I said it, this is my last thing.
I set up a little thing for it.
It's game time.
- Whee, yay!
- It's game time, y'all.
- Okay.
- Out of 788 voters,
that's how many people voted in this poll,
how many sociopaths do you think voted yes,
they do actually give a fuck
about what's happening in Ukraine?
- Just multiple choice?
- No.
- Okay, I'm guessing zero.
- Go as close as you can,
without going over, I guess, will be our--
- 25.
- 25, okay.
And I guess zero you guess zero have seven a do you guys are both gonna be surprised out of seven hundred and eighty-eight
psychopaths, okay, even psychopaths
305 of them realize that what is going on in Ukraine will not stand on the pale
What's it is not?
Okay
Even a person with no human emotion feelings who wants to literally grab a woman in an alley and have his way with her
Yeah, what's close that Putin?
Must be stopped even guys with claws think that food needs to be so Patrick one
Fuck me. Yeah, I was closer keep calm and claim your prize
And you may remember I asked you for a suggestion earlier. I said something Caleb. Yes and Patrick your prize is
food
We'll get you
Look up psychopath test
I know that there's a psychopath test and I want to do it right now because I am getting
more scared by the second that one of the us three might be a
Okay, who do you think well? How are we all gonna? Take it?
We just just we all go okay. This is a quiz. We'll just do it really
We'll just do we open three tabs. Yeah, okay, we'll do it as a group, okay?
Most would describe me as charming and nonchalant. I can turn my charm on and off like a faucet
I would say me this is definitely this describes me plus
Maybe wanting to drink people's blood and eat their teeth, so let's go this is definitely me
Uh-huh. I do what I want, when I want, and the moment the impulse strikes me
regardless of what others want. Yeah. That's all three of us, right? Yeah. If something goes
wrong or turns out badly, it's not my fault. Me, definitely me. Especially really hurtingly
people in a bloodly way. I've gotten into legal or criminal trouble as an adult,
not just a speeding or parking ticket. This is definitely me. Yeah, you, parking tickets with
you, I've hurt a lot. I'm easily the best at what I do, bar none, nobody could ever take my place.
This is definitely me.
For proof, watch this episode back.
Run it back, this was fire.
This is the best episode we've ever done.
I do whatever I feel like doing
and I don't care what others think,
or even if it's illegal.
Me.
Skateboarding for me.
For sure.
Every person for themselves,
I don't see the point in feeling sorry for other people
and have no desire to help others.
This is me as fuck.
Yeah, no, it is kind of me.
That's me AF.
I've gotten into legal or criminal trouble
when I was a teenager.
No, not when I was a teen.
Not when I was a teen.
No, no, no, no, no.
Something snapped.
Oh, I did though.
You did?
this is yeah I have no problem or concern in lying in order to get what I want not
me not me day that's right that's right I live in the moment there's what I say
the future will take care of itself and learning from your past is pointless me
I never feel remorse me okay can you just scroll down the rest of these and
click me on oh that's right here okay cuz I was gonna say the scroll bar is
pretty small let's get there's a psychopath the 24 out of 24 that's a
100% and it's only likely
That's probably cuz our weird three of us because it knows it was a sweet
Yeah, so what that means that one of us is likely a psychopath likely identified 16 who the hell is clickly?
Oh, the L is clickly
You said L
If you're listening if the you're listening this the day it comes out then tonight is the shareholder meeting at 5 p.m
And join the patreon at the executive producer tier to be a part of it