(upbeat music)
- Wow, it takes a big man to apologize like that.
- That was very big of you.
- That was huge of you.
- I'm really happy that you stepped up to the plate
and you did what was right.
- I didn't think that you had it,
because when we asked you to apologize,
you seemed so resistant at first.
And then I mean, that's the thing.
Like when you when you talk to
somebody who is addicted to a
sleepy time, it's a disease.
It's addiction is a disease and
especially to sleepy time tea.
Yeah. And we've known that's why
addicts are always walk around
going, oh, oh,
and that's what you do when you're
we've known that Jubio has been
addicted to this for a long time.
Yeah. Haven't done a single thing.
I actually I heard to listen to him.
I heard this week a set up a set
back as a set up for a comeback.
Yeah. And who is that?
I heard from Jack Bensinger.
Okay. Yeah, he said a setback is a setup for a comeback.
That's great. One of the most beautiful things I've ever heard.
I actually don't know if he said comeback or cun-back.
Cun-back? Well, I just didn't hear him that well.
I don't think cun-back is a word.
It's either a setback is a setup for a cun-back or a comeback.
Cun-back is the last name of those things.
I'd like to shout out Jack for putting me onto that.
Cun-back, that sounds like a last name.
It does kind of sound like a last name.
I guess it could in a different country.
Imagine a guy named Chris Cun-back.
Yeah, he'd probably be pretty quick.
Yeah.
That's like a good heckler, like Stephen Hofstetter kind of name.
Stephen.
Everyone is jacking his swag nowadays.
I don't know him that well.
I'm not going to call him Stephen.
Yeah, it's a little familiar, isn't it?
Call him his full name.
Stephen Hofstetter.
I call him Mr. Hofstetter.
Yeah.
Excuse me, Mr. Hofstetter, your jokes suck.
Hey.
Well.
Polite heckler gets destroyed.
No, that's what I'm saying.
I'm in the audience.
I'm the polite heckler.
You just said the S word, first of all.
Okay, no.
The S word is obviously a completely different word.
word is obviously a completely different word.
You can take one of my coins.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, first of all, we haven't even introduced it yet.
Okay.
And we also, we also in our, we definitely, that word is okay.
According to who?
What kind of psych-manager do you hang out with?
The first time, we already did a no swear D&D episode.
Can we, can we pull up maybe just like a list of words forbade by the Catholic
Church?
Well, I don't think that they...
Forbidden.
List of words forbidden.
List of words forbidden by the Catholic Church.
I don't think they make, they publish a swear list.
Yeah, I think Catholics are like sailors.
They should publish a list of swear words.
So then every year, you know which words are going to get you to send to Asia.
Well, first, can we get a punch in on this right here?
If we have it, a table punch in?
Yeah.
So this is, if you're not watching the video, this is a swear jar.
And we have decided to do, we didn't name it yet.
This is a Prime Energy collaboration.
between Logan Paul and KSI.
It's got to be one of the most dis-
dis-dest-dest-dest-dest-
the itchy double hockey sticks out of here.
It gives you the most exciting headache
you'll ever have in your life.
No, just just don't even go there.
Don't even promote that.
Put it down. Put it under the table.
You know what we can promote?
We are going to be
a healthy lifestyle, a healthy lifestyle,
and also we're going to be making our own
branded swear jars.
That's a great idea.
That is a really good idea.
But we need to what's the best idea
you've had in six months.
It's going to be
they're going to be like one hundred dollars
because there's gonna be a hand blown or mouth blown by a glass blower.
Mouth blown, yeah.
I think it's still hand blown.
Yeah.
No.
No, these ones don't use their hands.
Yeah.
They do it completely with their mouth.
I don't think your mouth is ever involved, is it?
No.
You blow.
How are you gonna blow the glass?
I don't know.
You blow it with a straw.
I thought you blow it with a blower.
That's probably in the factories, but the mouth blown ones, that's like handmade.
But hand blown.
Oh my God, they're blowing.
Yeah.
They're completely blowing.
She's blowing that stick.
That's why it's called glass blowing.
Like there's no tomorrow.
like they're playing an instrument.
Uh-huh. They're playing the Mordor.
(Humming)
Whoa, what was that?
That was the window sound.
I thought that somebody hit like a music button.
No.
(Humming)
Bro.
Doesn't that sound kind of right?
They're blowing on that thing like Dizzy Gillespie.
The Year of Noswear.
Oh, yeah. The Year of Noswear.
I'm trying to think if there's a good name for it.
Maybe the Month of No Cuss.
Here's the plan. We're going to try to do a full year of no cussing,
or at least if you cuss, you have to pay for it.
So it's really got to be worth it because guys,
we've been doing this podcast for four years at this point.
And if you go back into our history,
we have used so many unnecessary cuss. We've used every word in the book.
Well, at least Patrick has.
Let's get like,
this is a one minute grace period to say all the words that we said.
No, I don't think so.
We had a four year grace period. It ends today.
Okay, so stop flipping around and let's get down to business.
Yeah, and he didn't say biz.
And I didn't say biz n-i-t-c-h.
Yeah, he said business.
Because that also is skirting the rules.
Yeah, any kind of that we call that a half cuss. Impolite.
If you say a word and you have
impropriety in your mind and heart when you say it.
If you're thinking a cuss and saying a wuss,
you could say like, we'll call that a wuss word.
Yeah, like if I said, what the virtue?
I would even though the word I'm saying is virtue, you can feel behind it the word I
mean.
Yeah, you're getting pan pricks from the Holy Spirit.
I don't know about that.
And that's maybe a reduced fee, but it's still not right to do.
See, I have a bag here of all the coins.
So there's a couple things I want to establish.
Let's go over ground rules.
Okay, here are the ground rules.
First of all, we will come up with a list of coins, which it can be something that evolves.
you open up the notes app right now get that open and then we'll just say like we won't
swear but we'll say the word right we'll just say like blank word okay so words we can't
say all right so f word f word is obvious for is not a swear f word is obvious s word
is obvious yep b word b word a word you don't have to type word after everyone no I think
he does. A word. A word is good. Well then the other S word. What's the other S word?
Well I can't say it. Wait, shh. S-H-I-T. Whoa. We're making the list. We're making the list.
First donation is collected. That's a penny. That's a penny. Well I already grabbed a quarter.
And I missed. Also, another ground rule. If you miss, it's not telling you that you didn't
need to pay, but you do have to try your hardest to get it in.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. So a word, the other S word, which again, I
don't know what I'm not sure what it is either. And that's
pretty much all the cusses that I ever learned. The F word, the
other F word, we'll say any racial or slur type thing. All
slurs are, and you can't say, and you can't say idiot. Yeah.
Oh, idiot. Wait, we both just
know. No, no, no. Coins are free coins.
That's a full dollar. There's like there is thirty dollars of coins in here.
You are an idiot.
Pay again, pay again.
I'm going to be broke.
I only have like ten bucks today.
OK, so we're going to establish this.
We'll add to this as you know, in other countries.
This is a full year.
We're not touching this for a year.
But I would also like to establish up top,
what are we going to do with this money when it's all full?
So at first, my idea was to bring it to
a homeless person.
Yeah. And give it to them and say, this is all the times we've
sinned this year.
But they're going to just spend it on drugs and alcohol.
They might spend it on going to a swearing show.
Yeah, they might go to a swearing speakeasy.
Yeah.
What's the password? The F word?
Yeah. And not the F word.
I'm going, I won't, that's it's just going to be hard. Wow. You know what? Wow. Okay.
That was, that was bad. That was really, really bad one. This is going to be,
this is really, I think it's going to be so difficult. I'm hoping that this,
cause guys, you think that I just cussed when I'm, when the cameras were on and
the mics were on. When I get home, I'm saying F this, S that. Oh my God.
Look at my a-hole. I look at the S and TV on. I'm looking in the,
I'm looking in the, I'm pointing at the mirror and I'm saying, "F you."
I'm punching the mirror.
I'm like, and I'm making myself a delicious meal. I'm like, "I want to eat this F."
I'm showing my dog my D.
Yeah.
I don't want to do any of that.
Yeah. I'm saying like, "I want to drink a D glass of water."
I'm brushing my teeth. I'm like, "I'm brushing my D teeth."
I'm brushing my D.
I'm brushing my D with my toothbrush.
I need to take an S and brush my D.
I'm going to brush my D with my S.
I sat down on the toilet and got some S in my mouth.
Oh yeah, add D word there.
I'm at my house, I'm going to eat my S.
I'm going to eat my own S.
I'm going to F my S and eat my D.
I'm going to F a big pile of my own S.
What the heck am I doing?
Oh, H word.
But can you say H-E-C-K?
Hold on, hold on.
I have to say the word because...
Spell it.
Okay.
Wait, you're already doing a boner. Can't say it. Can't say B-O-N-E-R.
Okay. Okay. So that's getting around the D word.
You can't because I get home and I'm like, I'm going to turn my D into a B.
I'm going to F and turn my D into a B with S.
What do we even say? We want to talk about. Do we have to say erection?
Yes. Yeah. She gave me an erection. Or phallus.
phallus.
No, a hard phallus.
My phallus became erect.
We could probably say engorged phallus.
We could say any medical terms are okay.
There's blood in my phallus.
Medical terms are okay, but if you're using it in a medical context, you can't be like, "Yeah, I'm going to stick my phallus in a girl."
So it's also no dirtiness.
No dirtiness.
Okay, okay.
Derriere. Derriere is French.
Derriere is not French.
No French.
butt as long as it's not too crass.
Yeah.
Okay.
Like I got some, you get a couple butts a day.
You get a couple butts.
You don't ever do it.
I got effed in my butt.
Yeah, definitely.
But you can say like, hold on to your butt.
You can say that before you say something crazy.
I got effed in my butt and some S came out.
Yeah, you can't say that.
You can't say that.
Some S with some C in it came out.
No, we can't say that.
You can't say that.
We're saying it.
We're not saying no.
You can't say a B shot C in my butt.
Can I say, oh my God, my keysters full of C.
You can't say C.
Okay, okay.
You can't say C, but you can say sperm because that's medical.
But you could say like, you can say C only in a donation context.
You can say I got fornicated in my keister.
Fornicated is not that.
I'm such an S F.
I got F'd in my keister.
Yeah.
I can say that?
You can say that.
Okay.
You can say, my keister's full of sperm.
I don't think you can say any of this.
Because I got F'd.
You can't say F'd.
I'm a total R for C.
You can't say I just F'd a B.
I can't say I'm a total R for getting F'd in my keister.
I can't say that.
Okay.
I'm going to give a dollar for that.
That was purely crass.
I don't want to say that.
We're trying to make a change here.
Speaking of addiction.
And then another B word.
What?
The word for breasts.
Oh, oh, grass, one calculator
words. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can say hello, but you can't
say sine cosine plus
minus.
But yeah, calculator words.
We know. Yeah, we know.
Can we say you can't say
the OK.
You can say, oh,
my grandma has a
you can say my grandma's in my
Grandma, you can say that. You can also say my grandma has a a pussy cat.
Yeah. Yeah. But you can't say just the first part of that.
No. That word that I was you can say.
You can say my grandma has a pussy.
Will a pussy footing? You can say pussy footing.
So again, it's all it's contextual.
If it's in if it's in the dictionary, you can't say the first syllable
of contextual either. No, no, no.
And you can't say the first syllable of dictionary either.
No, especially you can't say the contextual and dictionary for.
So no, you can't say them together.
And you can't talk about how they smell when they get together.
You can't say my dictionary is put into some context.
Yeah, you can't. Well, no, I mean, that's actually rather intellectual.
Yeah. So also that's another.
Well, yeah, depends on the conversation.
OK, so OK, here's one thing I want to establish.
OK, I want to establish the.
My dictionary has no context.
I want to establish.
Do we have a Huckleberry Finn rule?
No, no, no, no.
Where we can say anything if it's a quote.
Oh, I see.
That's not what I was guessing you meant by the Huckleberry Finn rule.
No, no.
I'm saying if you're quoting it.
Right, if you're popcorn reading.
If you're quoting somebody who says the F word.
If you're popcorn reading in high school.
And they say the B-O-N-E-R or something.
Can you say that?
I think we should still spell it.
I think that's the time we're allowed to spell it.
Okay, what if you try and circumvent the thing and you say the...
Don't say the middle of circumvent either.
Yeah.
What if you say B-1-er?
Can you say circumcise?
Or do you say B-1-er?
You can say circumcise.
Okay.
I'm going to be saying that a lot.
(laughter)
And if you absolutely have to say something,
we do, do we still have the beep?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, so, and if you really need to sell it,
you could say like, so the guy said,
what the (beep)
Yeah, so like that.
He didn't say it though.
Yeah, you didn't really time it well.
Yeah, I didn't know what you were gonna say.
It's kind of impossible for me to tell what you're gonna say.
Well, I said,
You said, and the guy said,
I'm just gonna press,
I'm gonna try to react in time.
What the (beep)
Okay, you suck at this.
It's difficult. Whoa.
No, I said this.
That was really mean too.
Can we say, yeah, okay, also--
know how I can't read your mind.
It's a swear plus mean jar.
Meanness also does.
Yeah, meanness is a swear.
OK, so being mean is a swear.
So I haven't doubted I have a three
dollar budget for the rest of this
episode. Otherwise, I'm going to
serve in mowing the jar.
Right. That's why I got the coins.
But that's not my money.
That's also that's cheating.
You're cheating.
It's not cheating.
It's a dollar or more.
Other in every other country
in the world, the coin is respected
in Canada, in England.
They don't respect the coin in
Canada. They call them loonies. They call them loonies because it's a loose one.
That's where it comes from. That's where it's derived.
And you know what they call them in? They call them disgusting things in the United
Kingdom. What do they call them?
They call them... Why don't you just... Well, I can't even say it because it's so
disgusting. Yeah, but you can hit the censor.
So just what do they call that in the UK?
Todgers.
He didn't hit the censor button. I was never going to hit the censor.
You have to donate that money.
So I have two dollars left.
And we have stuff coming up that is just gonna definitely
I'm gonna accidentally curse during.
So that's really sad. I can give you a loan.
Okay.
If I run out of money,
I will ask for a loan.
With a lot of interest.
I think that this list is good for now.
I don't need, that's cheating
and you should come with dollars next time.
No, it's not cheating. They respect the coin
in other countries. We're not in other countries.
And we have all, they also say all this stuff in other countries.
Well, do you like the bag it came in?
The what it came in?
Or the what?
The bag.
The what came in?
The baggin.
Came in.
Okay.
Well, yeah, it sounded like.
What are you, what are you saying that I said?
It sounded like the other F word.
No, a French word.
We said no French words.
Oh, baguette.
Oh, oh my God.
And he said it again.
He said it just three times, by the way.
That, hold on.
French.
I have to pay.
Yeah.
You have to pay whatever the equal amount is in euros.
Do they use euros in francs?
No, they use francs.
That's a dollar.
No, they use euros.
And that's a French word.
What?
Francs.
Fuck.
No, I'm not.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not.
Dude, the sound of the coin.
He's turning the mic into the coin.
You forgot to set the F word.
You set the F word.
I know.
I'm putting more.
There we go.
And you're done.
That was a dollar something.
I don't even know.
Speaking of awful things that happened in this world, last night, I'm at a birthday party
awful things that happened in this world last night. I'm at a birthday party, okay? And
I am at a birthday party at a bar in Manhattan and someone comes up to me and they say, "Batman's
here." And I go, "What do you mean Batman's here?" They say, "Robert Pattinson is in this
bar right now." Whoa. And I walk over to the bar and sure, this place is called Ear Inn.
Sure as hell, ordering at the bar, sure as anything, ordering at the bar is none other
but the safty prince himself, Robert Pattinson. And I really wanted to spill a Bloody Mary
on him or something, but they were too expensive at the bar.
So anyway, we leave kind of early, and I have to pee at the bar, but there's a line, so
I walk, I'm like, I'm just going to go pee on my car because I parked down there.
And I start peeing on my car and, um,
I look to the left and a woman falls into the street and a guy like starts
walking away. And so I have like my penis in my hand.
Can I say that if it's the story? Yeah. Yeah. It's medical. Penis is medical.
Yeah. So I'm peeing on my car out of my penis and a woman gets knockout
gamed like 20 feet from me. And I'm like, what the heck's going on?
So I, a guy, a guy is like walking away and he's like got a mask that covers his face.
Batman.
And she's saying awful, she's saying awful cuss words.
So really she kind of deserves it.
But she's cursing at him.
And I start cursing because I kind of get into it.
I say, "What the F is wrong with you?
You are, you crazy are, effer."
And he's like, he just goes like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then I started like walking towards him to like try to approach him.
And then he starts, he just bolts.
He just like runs away.
The flash.
And I walk over to the lady.
Yeah, walk over to the lady.
And her jaw is broken. Like her face is like this big and she's this British lady and she's
like that fella just knocked me loony. Or she said something along those lines.
And then I get in the car and we start leaving. I'm like, gosh, that was so awful. It really
put me in a horrible mood. I was like, that is so awful that we live in a place where
that kind of thing happens. That is so awful. And there's nothing I can do because I didn't
know if the guy had a knife, you know, or I don't know.
So then we start driving, I'm like, "Man, if only there had been somebody, somebody fearless,
some vigilante who was fearless enough to stop him." But he was at the bar!
I thought that that story was going to end that you walked up to the woman with your
penis out of your zipper.
No, no! Batman did nothing. He was too busy drinking, by the way.
Well, do you know why?
Why?
You didn't set the bat signal off.
Yeah, you...
I wasn't going to know.
I have to sign it into the window.
The box away, dude, he was to have your phone up in the bar with the
bat with a bat low bat, the Batman symbol on Google images.
Just like the one night.
I thought nothing like this.
Nothing bad will happen.
You're saying you thought you were saying within 60 feet of Batman.
Yeah, and this woman gets completely Batman attracts trouble destroy.
It happens.
Every goes his road.
Skyler.
He follows your fault for going into Gotham.
This guy.
Well, I wasn't Gotham.
This guy was definitely a Batman villain type.
Like just like did he go?
Kind of well, no more like henchmen like he's sitting around
Yeah, wait did he go like
It was not a baby no, but he was sitting around doing kind of like, uh, you know in all the batman games
They're always talking about batman when you're walking around. Yeah the bat you hear about this bat walking around
It was like that kind of guy. He was definitely a henchman. He was not an evil. He was not tiny
little tiny fisherman hat. Yeah, little fisherman hat. He's like all striped shirt. Yeah, the same
exact body type is the next 12 guys that you see. Yeah, just like different face, maybe or different
hair. Uh huh. Yeah. If that happened to me, if I saw that I would have gone home that night and
like, got all my clothes together, got my sewing machine, I would have made my super suit.
I honestly, it was for me a little bit of a maybe I become a vigilante or yeah,
I would have become, I can't be the Jubio's the love bug.
Yeah, I didn't want to reveal this until I was ready, but I'll reveal it now really quick.
Yeah, I've been planning. I'm going to draw a love bug comic book.
That's adorable. I'm going to publish it.
That's really sweet. I think I will become a vigilante.
You have no idea the excitement that just washed over.
Yeah, that is exciting.
I'm like, I want to curse because I want to say holy F.
Yeah, well,
That is effing amazing.
You can say it's holy cow.
Holy cow.
That is flipping amazing.
Do you think there's room in New York for a vigilante who dresses up like an orthodox
acidic guy?
And that's like my super suit?
Yeah.
Right?
Well, yeah, because I mean it's the most...
Is that it's like you escape and you're doing like Naruto, like shadow jutsu.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I'm just blending in perfectly.
Where is he?
Yeah.
People are like, oh my God, he's like a drop of water, like tears in the rain.
See, my thing, I think if you're just going to like, like, try to be a vigilante in New
York, like you're going, you're going to Haseed, I'd probably be eight ball jacket guy or like,
Oh yeah, that's NYPD officer.
NYPD officer.
That's good.
No, I think you'd get caught as an NYPD officer.
I'd probably, I'd be a guy caught as NYPD officer, but eight ball jacket guy.
NYPD.
I would be a different cop star here.
It's funny that cops here are all just like fat pieces of shit.
North Carolina. Oh, my God.
Bro.
Okay, I have one dollar.
Fat tubs of lard.
Try that next time.
They're lazy bones, I'll say that.
They're lazy bones.
They're do-nothings.
They're lazy bones who do nothing, and they all have like,
you just see them sitting around eating lunch all the time.
In North Carolina, they are all military guys.
Yeah, when we were in North Carolina after you left,
We were going out to a bar with Noah and Pierce one night,
and we walked down the street in downtown Wilmington,
and literally 10 cop cars pulled up on the street
because someone was being loudly drunk.
And they were all the way down the street.
They were cuffing somebody.
There was a girlfriend who was there.
It was like, "What the F-U-C-K are you doing?"
She's like, "Do you feel good about what you do?"
Pulling that whole thing out.
And she's a crazy and it was literally it was like 10 G.I.
Joe's. Yeah, just one saying my hometown.
So the airport was like on the border of it was like Manchester Airport
and then Londonderry like the airport was there.
So my my hometown needed a SWAT team. Yeah.
But I mean, you've seen how small Londonderry is.
There's no reason for them to have a SWAT team.
So all the maybe for the flies. That's right. Yeah.
Hold on.
Yeah, maybe for the flies around the horses bottoms hit that which one which one fine boo. Say it again
Wait, maybe for the flies around the horses bottoms
Yeah, yeah, that's good
But yeah
They had like all the cops had like they were so insanely overpaid and then every year they would get new
Cars and stuff careful now Patrick because we do have added to the list here at the bottom. This is a cop rhetoric
cop rhetoric.
No, no, no, no. It's not anti-cop. Most of the town's budget went to the police.
The cops in my hometown were noble and they educated kids about drugs and elementary school.
I'm talking about their steeds.
You think the DARE program.
I'm talking about every year the cops got the Noble Knights of Londonderry got new steeds.
Really?
Yes.
They had steeds?
They had steeds, which were Toyota or Dodge Challengers.
No, that's not a steed.
That's barely a steed.
They were Dodge Challengers. You don't think the Dodge Challengers is a steed?
Is it donkey?
I challenge the idea that that's a steed.
Can we say A.S.S. in reference to a donkey?
Yes.
I think so.
But only in reference to a donkey.
But honestly, I'd rather you use mayor.
Or if it's an acronym for something.
Mayor.
Mayor is good.
The battered mayor, like Skyrim thing, the bar.
I'd say in that sense.
Can we reference video games?
No.
No, I don't think so.
That's not so right.
You can't reference--
What about Noah's Ark?
Not an M-rated video game.
Okay, no M-rated video games, no R-rated movies.
Yeah.
And nothing that has an explicit sticker on it, music-wise.
So, not even... So, no T, no rated T.
So, E10.
T is fine. I think that this podcast is generally T.
Yeah.
PG-13. We're somewhere in between PG and PG-13.
We're like PG-11.
We're like a hard PG.
E10.
Yeah.
E10+.
But I always like to say PG-11.
Okay.
Because 10-year-olds might even be a little too young for some of this stuff.
- Parts two of podcasts.
- Guys, tonight is my bachelor party.
- Yep.
- And we're, and we're, there's going to be no cussing there.
- That's right, we're bringing the jar.
- Yep. And we're going to get all the P, P,
P shaped gummies, P shaped lollipops,
and P shaped straws.
- And we're going to get,
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We're going to get a,
- We're getting totally clothes off.
- We're going to get a sex worker.
- We're going to get a sex worker, a shaker, a hole,
right in front of our faces and we get to smell it.
we can put the coins in there.
We're going to tell her to not W before she comes.
Uh-huh.
And we're going to smell her A.
(laughter)
Wait, what's W?
Wipe.
That's not a swear.
Yeah, but in that context you were right to say it.
In that context it's nasty.
In that, I guess.
Yeah.
I had to W so many times this morning.
Really?
I hate it when you have to W like your A a million times.
My butt.
- Okay, so you're here, you don't have to say A.
You don't have to say A.
- You can say butt.
- Yeah.
- So you're just A or your tush.
- Okay, you're gonna have to W, I have to W my tush.
(laughing)
I have to W my tush so many times.
- My tush was so messy this morning.
- Really?
- Yeah, I literally was making ice cream out of it.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah.
- And then you W.
- This is nasty, this is getting in a nasty territory.
- Ice cream's good.
- That is good, you're right.
I actually do like ice cream.
- That's very, not very so.
- That's probably the most wholesome.
It's the goal of this is to have a healthy lifestyle.
Would you agree?
Yeah.
To stop being...
What?
Cause I feel like we're kind of losing sight a little bit because I am saying
some stuff that could be construed as a little, um, anatomical.
Yes.
I think it's more that you're talking about this stuff because no
one else has talked about it.
But it's also toilet humor.
It's not toilet humor because when, when you change, when you shift the lens,
what do we joke about?
It's not humorous.
What do we say?
It's the news.
But then that's divisive.
Oh yeah, here's some news that he had to W his A.
Let's talk about the news that, uh, so the exciting news that you broke to us right before
we started recording.
Oh.
Which is?
Millie Bobby Brown.
Oh yeah.
Is now engaged.
Patrick was so excited about this.
This is exciting.
And we said we're gonna cover it on the show, we haven't yet.
Because as a Bon Jovi fan.
Millie Bobby Bon Jovi.
As a Bon Jovi fan, I'm excited.
I like that.
That's like a Civil War name.
There's a new member of the Bon Jovi family.
This is New Jersey royalty.
Millie Bobby Bon Jovi.
Oh my God!
That's right, that's what I said when I heard that the first time.
Millie Bobby Bon Jovi.
Oh my God!
Oh my God! Wait, is that Lord's name in vain?
No, I don't think we have that on there.
We'll do, okay, we, even though
because we have a mixed... We should try to say gosh, but...
Because we have a mixed religious background
for all three of us, I think that we
do unfortunately, it does have to be a secular
rule set for these words.
Definitely. Which I mean, you know...
If you want to personally not say G-O-D like me,
then that's fine.
- For me it's more like if I take,
'cause I follow Shintoism,
so if you take maybe the spirit of a tree in vain,
you say something kind of nasty or you invoke a rock.
- Yeah, be careful there,
don't slur your words saying Shinto.
- True.
- Oh true, yeah.
See my brain, honestly, I'm so like locked in here
that I didn't even consider that could be--
- I kind of completely forgot what I was saying.
- My religion is--
- Dalai Lamaism.
Church of Bill Hicks. Really? Which I'm pulling back a lot.
Yeah, I can't believe that you're so... That's why I brought so many coins.
Because I know I'm going to slip up. I thought that I'd slip up more. He's the one. He's the
Catholic one. He's sitting here. Christian, sorry. Yeah, I'm not Catholic. Catholics are
actually going to H-E-double hockey. He's sitting here. He's swearing like a f-ing sailor.
Okay, so again, that's against the rules. Not really, right? You could say like an ever-loving
Ever-loving.
Ever-loving sailor.
He's swearing like a flippin' sailor.
Guys, let's talk about this Dalai Lama situation.
So I wanted to go out and just put a message out here.
It's the thing I said this to you guys before.
I just want to do it on the podcast, kind of get this out of the way.
Dalai Lama, we saw the news.
We saw what you did.
You hugged a child.
You said, "Want to suck my tongue?"
And pal, I'm going to give it to you straight.
S your T.
That is...
S my T, he said.
As you said, "Do you want to S my T?"
Yeah, which is crazy.
To a child, a young boy, who was literally, the Dalai Lama was that young boy's idol, most likely.
And here he is asking him to SST. But Dalai Lama, you got one more chance, buddy.
Actually, you know what, we'll say this.
We'll give you two more chances.
That was strike one.
Strike one.
Two more strikes and you are out!
Two more strikes and you better not mess this up.
He's got two strikes, because all that stuff he was saying about Tibet.
Tibet. What do you mean? Oh, that's fine. What do you mean? He has one strike, okay?
Because he told a little baby that S is T. You have one strike and one ball. Yeah. You
have one strike and one ball. I guess, yeah, the Tibet stuff is a ball. Well, that's good
for him, right? Yeah. Because the ball is for him being a spiritual leader and a wall.
Why do people want to free Tibet? Because China made it crazy or something. Oh, then
And yeah, then he has two strikes.
No he has one strike.
He has two strikes for talking.
Pelt, asking a child to s your t is a strike.
No he's to bet.
He thinks to bet is dope.
Because he's the ruler of it.
I bet he's trying to take that child to bet.
You're making a joke about a pedophile.
Pedophilic.
Well I wouldn't go that far.
I wouldn't go that far.
Because I would say if you get to three strikes I'm definitely going to call you that word.
But until then, we're just going to call you. You're going to say you made a mistake.
Yeah, we're going to say you were very...
We made a very public mistake.
By the way, not all those who wonder are lost.
Can you hit like a clap?
Yeah. Can I get an applause? But not all those who wonder are lost. So thank you very much.
Yeah. I mean, and that's true. I really believe that. So, Mr. Dalai Lama, I just want to say
there is always room for you in the loving arms of Jesus Christ.
Fatality.
First of all, grow your hair out because I do not like that bald shit. It does not look
good on you.
What the H-E-double-hockey-dick-s-r-e-u-s-d-o-i-n, man?
I need a dollar. I ran out of money. I'm a cusser today.
Just here. That's why I brought the coins. Here's three dollars.
I'll give you these later. That's going to be a dollar for me. You need to convert.
Gosh dang it, it's hard.
And try changing up your fit every once in a while.
Yeah. Hey, by the way, you don't live in a cartoon, Dalai Lama.
You don't get to wear the same shit every...
Did you just get out of the shower?
Why are you wearing that?
You know what?
I can't stop saying yes.
The Dalai Lama, you dress like a llama that was generated in Dali.
I think it's...
Fatality.
Yeah, that's right. That was fire.
Gosh, it's so hard to cuss, man.
Hard to not.
It's hard to not cuss.
It is hard for me to cuss.
I brought this. I'm having an amazing time not cussing.
But what do you guys think about shaking the challenge to the next level?
Let's do it.
Shaking the challenge?
How do we shake the challenge to the next level?
That's right.
No, but how? You have to explain how.
Yeah.
We're going to do a very exciting special challenge.
OK.
Talent show.
A talent. And this is something that I developed.
OK.
that I thought that we could do
that nobody has ever attempted before
in the history of podcasting or even the world.
- I think you're probably right.
- This is a challenge that's called
the five fingers of music.
- Wait.
The five fingers of music?
- The five fingers of music, that's right.
Five beats, 50 minutes.
- Okay, and what do we do with these beats?
- No cussing.
- No cussing?
- Freestyle.
the top off the dome off of the
ever loving dome.
Excuse me real quick.
Excuse me real quick because of the
I guess in that context, but the word
dome. Yeah, I was going to ask about
that. It's kind of euphemistic.
Yeah, it is a little bit euphemistic
off the but it means but this
whoa, that's that's that's way worse
than saying that's way worse.
That is 50 cents.
Whatever, man.
You can act out anything.
And here's another for your flippant attitude.
You see my flippant attitude or my flippant attitude?
Flippant.
Oh, okay. I was being flippant.
You were being really flippant.
Speaking of flip, how about you flip that beat on and let's do this dang thing.
Okay, hold on.
Wow.
Okay, show me one of these fingers.
You guys ready for the first finger?
what you could say I get stop the beat stop the beat I was saying what is your
malfunction where do you where do you get off he said get off that no in this
context that is fine I said you're telling me to f you no I said that is
not okay no these are gonna give me a beaten F okay you've you've never seen
in the morning, have you?
Yes I have.
Okay so when he does sway in the morning with a rapper,
each beat is called a finger. He does five fingers.
But they don't tell them to F him.
Finger me dog.
What are you doing?
Stop it. You stop it right now.
Give me my finger.
You can say give me my finger.
Finger me. My headphones just got turned crazy.
But it's all okay.
Everything did just get a little bit louder.
That's okay.
right there that controls everything but it didn't nothing moved it huh but yeah
I was just saying finger me up we have a lot to learn just have to stop saying
that I'm sorry whatever what hello what did Cameron say what are you saying
Ford when when that thing went crazy okay oh you got caught you got caught
dang dang well I'll be danged I didn't even do it consciously isn't that crazy
How about this? Drop the beat.
Okay, ready?
I'm going to drop it again and don't say the thing you were saying before.
Okay, show me a finger.
Okay, that's fine.
Don't finger me.
You can't even say it.
Don't F me.
See how much better that feels?
See how much better that feels to say?
F me with five F's.
You ready?
Here's the first F.
We'll call it the five F's of music.
Damn. Wait, this F is amazing.
You said D.
You did say D.
Crack.
Crack. Crash.
Oh, crash.
Alright, what's my word? I gotta go off a word.
You have to go off a word? Yeah.
Coins. Coins.
Oh, I got so many coins.
I rap so good, you feel it in your loins.
I look like a loian from the zoo.
Cameron, it smells like poo.
I was like, "Pooh, I can't say P-O-O, but I don't care because I am so good at rapping
in a clean way.
Cameron and Patrick are dead.
Like happy.
And I can't say C-R-A-P-P-Y."
Dang, this is hard actually.
I realize how many cusses rhyme together.
And this come into your head immediately, as soon as you think about rap music.
This is really teaching me how sick I am.
Usually when you think about rap music, you think about cusses.
Let me show you how it's done.
Show me how it's done.
I went to the baseball game and I saw the game.
I saw the game.
You went to the baseball game and saw the game?
It's supposed to be rap.
I went to the baseball game and I saw the game.
I watched all the baseball game and I thought it was the Flames.
My team is the Flames.
The Florida Flames.
That's my favorite team and I love their name.
Me and Cameron and Patrick are going to the store today to get some more Flames.
Because we like flames and Patrick and Cameron and Caleb is our names and we're three friends
and we don't play video games anymore.
Because they're bad.
Even if we shut the door, we don't play them privately.
They're demonic and no we don't smoke chronic.
We don't drink any gin and tonics.
And we still don't play Sonic.
We don't like Sonic but we like um...
Sonic the restaurant.
What can we even like?
And health.
And we like investing in ourselves.
And Sonic the restaurant is a treat on weekends.
Yeah.
I go there, I get.
I get freaking milkshakes and french fries and burgers and hot dogs.
Yeah.
Well, what was that one?
I don't even know what that's from.
That was cool, though.
That's part of the finger.
The F.
You said finger.
Okay.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- I don't like the bing bong bong.
- What?
- What's so funny?
(laughing)
- No, I don't like that.
Okay, I like that.
- I like this one.
- We need topics, we need clean topics.
- What about this one?
Yeah, we need some topics.
(laughing)
- Topical topics.
- We're using the swear jar
and we like to drive a really slow car
Cause we don't like to speed
Cause we don't need to get anywhere fast neat
I moved the word need to the end
Cause I couldn't figure out a rap fast enough
And I just have to move the word to the end
And then I'll type a message and press send
Text is speed, not for me
All I need is some good ass speed
Whoa!
Wait, drop a bomb
Drop a bomb right now
Wait, wait
He just said, good a double marijuana.
Double. He just mentioned Merrill. That's a buddy.
The D's lettuce. Have you ever seen this on a, on a game? That's T T or M.
Yeah. Rated for drug references. Press the bomb.
Have seen it. Tony Hawk. Yeah. Drug references. So you just referenced,
you just referenced drugs. Uh huh. You referenced drugs. That's not okay.
Okay. That's I guess. Yes, we are doing it. Um,
secular. Yeah. But as I stated before, Church of Bill Hicks, it is part of my religion.
So you're saying you need to make a religious exemption.
It is a religious exemption for me to say that I love smoking cigarettes and drinking beer.
Cigarettes is different.
Cigarettes and weed is actually now legal.
Give me a finger. Give me a finger.
Okay. You want a new finger?
Finger me. Newly.
You... I cannot even believe your behavior today.
Okay. Finger me. Give me a slow one.
- I said, "Wait, hold on, we stopped the beat.
"We stopped the beat for me."
His attitude.
- Here, I'm just gonna go back into the first F
for a second and we'll go.
I put these in order.
I spent a lot of time, almost 30 minutes,
making all five of these Fs.
And I don't remember which one is which,
so we're just gonna go through them in order.
And if the next one isn't slow, there's nothing I can do.
- That's fine.
You can finger me whatever speed.
- Hey. - Enough of this.
- Okay, whatever. - You can't swear
or you're gonna get eaten by a bear.
- Dang. - When you swear,
It makes me feel bad.
I got sweared at by my dad when I was a kid.
Yeah, well, that's referencing child abuse.
That's not referencing child abuse.
It's referencing swearing.
What do you think of this?
Patrick from the church of Bill Hicks.
Wait, I can't even hear anything.
Okay.
Patrick's from the church of Bill Hicks.
He died from smoking cancer sticks.
Yeah.
Wow.
That was pretty good.
Step of the beat.
You are making fun of what in my religion would be your Jesus Christ.
And look right here on the list.
Bill Hicks is Alex Jones. That's a rumor. He died from a big brain tumor.
I think we have no religious stuff in the list.
He's not a major religion.
a major religion but you shouldn't disagree. I think the thing that makes this country
great is the freedom of expression. He just said make this country great. He's a MAGA.
Hey Patrick, this is what I think about Bill Hicks. I think you should go eat a bag of
potato sticks. Or you could bleep yourself too. This is way too much for me. I can't
also be bleeping. A bag of potato sticks actually tastes pretty good. So that's what I was trying
to say. I wasn't dissing him. I'm trying to diss him. Why would I need to censor potato
Also, the no dissing.
Wait, OK, so we're supposed to do rapping with no dissing and also we do a radio show.
Hey, Patrick, you can't rap without dissing and making others and punching down.
If you can't rap without punching down, buddy, you here's OK, here's a store
core, which is like the most PG rapping ever.
Hey, Patrick, I heard that you follow Hicks Bill.
Yeah, I heard it on the rumor mill.
Wow.
What do you think of that?
I can't tell if that's a diss.
Yeah. Yeah.
I heard that you got a Bill Hicks need.
I, Herman, on the rumor weed.
Oh, from VeggieTales.
Oh, yeah.
I heard that you think Bill Hicks is...
Larry, Bob, and the cucumber, his nephew, who is an asparagus.
Yeah.
They go on a lot of adventurous.
And they go and they go to the wall of Jericho and they go on and on and on and on.
Yeah.
It's a show called VeggieTales.
and when it's entertainment, it never fails.
I'll watch every single episode.
I'll never turn off my T-Vode.
Yeah.
Cedric the Entertainer and Steve Harvey and Bernie Mac and DL Hughley.
You're not even rhyming.
They're all the kings of comedy.
Hughley rhymes with comedy.
No it doesn't.
Hugh, well, OK, Hughley, comedy.
It's not Hughley.
All right.
I think I think we're going to move to the next step.
Let's get to the next step.
Give me a finger.
All right.
Hold on. I have to stop this.
Last one.
That's right. That's how you end all of them. Yeah. All right. You guys ready for the next
one? I am. All right, here it is. I don't remember what it is.
Wait, this is actually good. Damn. Okay. Switch it up. Hold on. Hold on. Switch it up. Stop
the beat. Stop it. Again. Why do I have to keep stopping it? You start every single F
with a D.
Oh, did I say D?
You said D.
Did I say D?
I don't remember, but I believe
that.
Julio, can you run that back?
We can't run that back.
It's un-run backable.
Did you hear me say a D, though?
He said a D.
I don't know. I'll trust Patrick,
though.
OK, whatever. I'll put some of
Patrick's money in the swear jar
because he's so worried about it.
Are you guys ready?
For F number two?
I can say prickly pear. I can call
you prickly pear.
That's cool.
That's fine.
I'm the only one here who
- Who cares about the rules?
- I think you're, you're, you're boiling into being a Karen.
- You are being a Karen.
I want to just, honestly, as much as I love the swear jar,
as much as I love the swear jar,
I really want to get through these five F's of music.
- Okay. Okay. Let's do it.
Run that.
- Whoa.
(laughing)
- That was so hard.
That was so hard. Wait, stop it, stop it. That's right. Listen, that, I don't think,
listen, that was one of those, that happens every once in a while on Swag, where they
drop one that is just way too hard and everybody just goes, oh, like, have you seen the video
of Timbaland when he plays that song for Jay-Z and Jay-Z makes his head hit the ceiling and
the floor at the same time because he's so excited about it? This is the dirt off your
shoulder. Do that one more time for me. We just have to hear that again.
You need to be ready. One of you guys needs to start here.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
Alright, I'm going to do it again.
Oh my.
Oh, that is disgusting. That's so good.
Yo, listen up.
I went to Starbucks and I saw a Karen.
Grabbed her coffee said we are sharing. She said yo, my name is actually sharing
I said ho you look like a Karen then I grabbed her coffee and I spilled it
Then I grabbed her muffin and I filled it. That's right
Se X with her not don't give it if you see K about her
I don't care about the Karen's that I have I give him my finger and I tell her that I'm Jeff
I lie about my name, I lie about my age, I say I'm 13, they don't really know my age
is actually about to be 26, I turn 26 on Monday the 25th.
That's not true!
Shut up!
Is that your birthday?
That's right, that's a bomb on you.
Yeah, yeah, I was at the Starbucks and I had to order a coffee bowl cup and I wanted it
with oat milk but then I was attacked by a MILF and she grabbed me and she did some stuff
and I said no I just want my cup but then she took me in the bathroom and she sucked
me up with a vacuum see you thought I was gonna swear but I never need words like that out
of my hair I keep them in my heart and I don't let them out and I don't say fart and I don't
say
Lopez style.
I think she sings that song.
I don't really know.
I need to go to the Starbucks too.
Also gotta go to Starbucks for this verse.
I went to Starbucks on the first of the month cause my girlfriend works there.
Shouldn't give out her job on the show.
That's a bad idea.
Someone might show up and assassinate her.
Or come over here to the studio and steal the swear jar.
Might show up and order oat milk, but they turn out to be booth comma John Wilkes. Yep show up to oh wait
Show up to the Starbucks with the swear jar give her all the money say I want a Blair Clark
What's a Blair Clark? We don't have an item that is called a Blair Clark
I'm sorry. I'm drunk. No, that was a joke. Don't kick me out the Starbucks
I just need the code for the bathroom so I can take a stinky log.
Drop a log of poop, a log of it into the toilet.
And it'll make this sound.
Wow, that was so good, that really inspired me so much, I think that was by far our best finger.
Yeah, that was pretty good.
All right, well, that was only finger number two.
Wow, wait, I thought we got a speed.
OK, we're going to go to the next finger.
Ready? Yeah. Ready for the next finger.
All right, here it is.
[Music]
Okay, this one's a little faster.
This is kind of a...
Yeah.
Kind of a DMX type.
Yeah, but you can go slow on it if you want.
I did not say this is like the clips.
This is like grinding.
Uh-huh.
Just that kind of song.
And then it also has this.
[Siren]
[Scream]
No, I'm just kidding.
I know it's not.
Put sirens in this song.
Respect the police.
Get some jackets for the cops.
Get them a fleece.
I go to the store and I get a fleece jacket.
North Face.
Uh oh, this cop did blackface on Halloween.
This cop did blackface on Halloween.
He got paid off from the union.
They gave him paid leave.
Yeah, I respect the cops.
Gave him paid leave on Halloween so he could go trick or treating in the neighborhood.
And the beat is way too loud.
He told me to turn it up.
I think that's because that rhymed.
It just rhymed.
That's a good point.
The cop uses paid leave to pretend to be a kid and go around on Halloween.
In a costume he was Yu-Gi-Oh.
He was Yama Yu-Gi from Yu-Gi-Oh.
He would go toward a door and then he would go.
Dressed as the Pharaoh.
The cop went on paid leave.
I think that he needs a red sleeve because he is a freaking Nazi.
That's right.
All the cops are Nazis to me.
I respect the cops to do that job.
You need incredible chops.
You need to enforce all the traffic stops.
Okay, it's pretty tough.
Imagine a cop with hops a cop on the court that can dunk real
tall or a cop.
That's a bunny rabbit named Judy hops and she can dunk a basketball.
She's seven feet tall.
Wait, that's seven feet tall.
I'd be scared of that cop.
He'd stand on the turnstile.
Make sure no one hops.
Dang, a cop that's actually a hooper who could stop an active shooter on the basketball court
or in the home. You know that when he dunks the whole place goes, "Oh!" Look at the cop.
He's got hops and he's got a mop top because he's also part hippie cop. He has a hippie outfit on.
That's right. What if there was a hippie cop? A guy who actually liked peace and cop stuff?
I think all cops are like that.
That's right.
I think that all cops are like that.
And they wear cool hats and I like their uniforms.
And I think that they obey all of the norms.
Go. I think the cops don't beat people.
I think that they behave not evil.
I think the cops are really good.
And I think that their cars should be made of wood.
Yep. I think all cars should be made of wood because I don't believe in technology
because I'm a guy and I don't owe anyone an apology for my beliefs.
Imagine a world of wooden cars and wooden stars and wooden bars and wooden made out of wood.
No metal.
We never learned metallurgy.
I have allergies in the summer because of all the wood we have to keep making wood.
I'm allergic to birch pollen.
Dang.
It's up in my nose.
It gets all in the pollen.
It makes me sneeze.
That's right.
Stop the pollen, please.
- "No technology is what I need.
I need a car that runs on my feet.
That's right. I need a bird alarm clock.
I need to put my jizz in a sock.
It's okay to say jizz, it's not on the list.
That's right.
Don't slap my wrist because I just said a naughty word."
- Look right there, at the list,
there is a J word, above R word, under C word,
and under butt.
(laughing)
- Wait, he just said butt.
- Butt is okay to say.
But is okay to say, we already decided that today.
It's like you didn't pay any attention to the list
on this episode of Podcasts About Lists.
I paid attention.
I also paid attention, paid many times
into the swear word jar, the swear jar.
I think that this will go far.
When we go to Locks for Love and get me a new wig
with this brand new, with the money that we have raised.
If you want a new wig.
When I was in high school, Locks4Love came to my school and I shaved off all my hair.
It was a really weird thing. We used to have pep rallies for it.
You used to have to go to the gym and go to pep rallies.
Now we're just kind of telling stories really, really fast.
And nothing is really rhyming even at all.
And if you skip the pep rally, you get in trouble.
Yeah. Yeah. That really burst my bubble.
OK, that story seriously had no stinger.
But are you ready for the next finger?
Yeah, there goes finger.
Wait, these transitions are crushing my brain.
This one's got a little bit of a Latin flair.
Okay, Julio.
Let's hear you.
Julio.
Let's go.
Completely create a green clean freestyle from the mean nacho cheese style guy that we have.
Go ahead, dang. Here he goes. Wait, he's getting out of the room.
No, no, no, he's leaving.
No.
He's leaving the room. No.
No, get back here.
He left the room.
He doesn't want to freestyle.
I think he's coming back with a coke freestyle.
He got a coke freestyle machine in his house.
Cause it's real cheap.
Get that in his house.
Come on.
One line.
We want him to do one bar.
One bar.
One single bar.
Come on Julio.
Let's hear a bar.
Okay, alright.
Then we're just going to rap as you do.
For a while.
Julio.
My name is Julio and I'm coolio.
That's right.
Okay, no, no, no.
Okay, wait, wait.
Yeah.
Alright, you gotta feel it for a second.
You gotta let that beat ride.
Do the... put some chops on it.
(Humming)
(Laughing)
That's one of the best beats I've ever heard.
(Music)
(Sigh)
That sounds better.
Maybe Julio will want to jump on the
beat now. Yeah, Julio... oh he's a coward.
Okay. Alright. Look I have no
bars. Yeah, my name is Julio and I'm
from Mexico. Yep. And my
rhymes are Julio that make people say
Let's a go like Mario. I am Mario is my name.
Like Mario.
He's got the Mario.
Which I don't remember. I think that means neighborhood or something, right?
Mario?
Maybe.
My name's Julio.
I got a cousin named Franklin.
Yeah.
His name is Mario and my villain's name is Wario.
Yep.
I got a cousin named Franklin and you know when he walks his leg
it's Stanklin.
He got hit by a car.
He got hit by a car when he was 15.
basically destroyed all the bones in his leg and it didn't get back together right.
Yeah, you don't really need to rhyme when you do a freestyle because you can't
really have, you can't really think that much. Okay, this is bad. This one is
hitting my head way too many times. Okay, let's talk about, let's talk about,
yeah, let's get a word here. Let's get a topic. Divorce. Divorce? Okay, let's go
to the next finger for divorce. No, next one is the last finger. No, we got to finish this finger first.
Yo, my parents got divorced. I'd fix it if I had the force. I'd use my hands to
make them kiss I'd use my hands to eat their piss I'd eat my own parents pee I'd make them
smile and do it for free I'd go what?
I'd do divorce with the force I'd do the anti-divorce force I'd make them touch each other's legs
I'd make them touch each other's heads I'd touch their heads and put them together I'd
make them head by tooth in the weather make them wear two matching sweaters I said I'm
I'm with stupid, I'm with cupid, I'm with foolish, I'm with bluish, I'm with a Jewish guy, he
is my friend, his name is Fry.
Fry is kind of a Jewish guy's name, I think at least, or is that lame?
You're thinking of a cartoonish guy's name.
My bad, I'm thinking of Futurama, I didn't mean to make Jewish drama by accusing Fry of
being Jewish.
Oh my god, I really am clueless.
That's my bad.
But I do fuck with Lila's dad.
He has one eye, he's from this...
You F with Lela's dad?
Full F word.
But, hottest freestyle yet.
We can agree on that.
No, there's no doubt about that.
Because I was with Lela's dad in the...
I came up in the gutter with Lela's dad.
And I was a mutant.
With Lela's dad and her mom too.
And you said P-I-S-S.
I'm with Lela's dad and we are in the gutter.
gutter and he is making me a sandwich called jelly peanut butter.
Dang.
Yup, it's a sandwich that's backwards and I am rapping with wack words cause I can't
think of anything to rhyme cause it's going too fast for me to think in time.
And I just want to eat my sandwich and I think that Leela's mom is a bland witch.
Yeah.
Cause she is a mutant and I don't like mutants and I think that she is a mutant.
And I really don't like mutants and I think mutants should.
Okay.
And my window needs new tint.
In my car.
I would say you need an improv class.
Yeah.
You need UCB01.
I took it, it was so fun.
I made so many friends for life.
I think I met my future wife.
I got an A. I had to play every day in improv games.
It was so fun.
Oh my God, I gotta go back to the UCB101.
Maybe I'll do 103 next time.
I'll skip 102.
I'll skip right to 103.
That's right.
That one is...
Get the bomb ready.
Object work. Yeah. Wow. Again, you said D in that song. Guys, we'll catch up at the end.
Okay. I'm sorry. I finally got into my freestyle zone, so I just got to let it fly. The thing
is we were doing so good yesterday. I thought it was a warm up. I think I actually drained
myself. You drained yourself? I think I drained all my good rhymes about Dracula. We did rhyme
about black Dracula for about 30 minutes. I have no rhymes. I think the type of music
I'll just give it a shoot.
I mean, you've all seen song Sunday's
a do black Dracula.
It's all in the interest of
rhyming. Yeah, right.
This is not this is not racial.
No, it's a let's go to the next
finger. Then the next one's the
last one. Right.
If you think that this is a racial
rap, you're going to go to the OK,
because the last one I do remember.
OK, this is the one that is
perfect. This is the last one.
OK, so it's maybe it will be
a little intense, you
know. Yeah. So I don't know if you
guys are ready for this.
I'm ready.
But this will... Here.
You ready?
Yeah.
I'm ready. I'm gonna hit it.
Because you guys might have a reaction to this.
I'm the cool hand Luke.
I don't remove.
You say so.
I'm not. I'm warm hand...
Warm ham.
Warm ham Todd.
I'm warm ham Dan.
I'm gonna flip out.
Wow.
Yep.
Just the drums and the words.
That's all it's about.
I'm a blacked out Dracula born and raised in Africa.
Eat you with a spatula and...
Dracula.
I don't remember what the rest of it was, but it was fire.
Speaking of Dracula...
Oh, I'm attacking ya.
I'm attacking ya, 'cause I'm Dracula, straight from Africa.
Speaking of Dracula, last night Caleb saw Robert Pattinson,
then he saw a woman get her face battered in.
Dang!
Whoa! By a batter man.
No, batter man wasn't there. Batter man was in the B.A. air.
He was in a place called Ear Inn that I went in,
I went in and I said, yes, I send I drank too much in the bar.
I had a tequila soda. It got me really far.
And then I farted when I was three feet from Batman.
I didn't mention that earlier because it was embarrassing,
but I farted in the bar and a guy said, what the fuck? Somebody farted in here.
Yeah. You farted. You farted in here.
He said what the funk I'll count that.
Not count that as a swear cause it's being the song.
And you can say what the funk if it's a funk song.
He farted- This is technically a funk song because there's a beat and it's a song.
He farted near Batman.
Okay, wait, I need, I lost the- He farted near Batman!
Yeah?
Yeah.
He farted near- He farted near Batman called- I'm completely losing the- I think I'm gonna
faint.
Wait, wait, wait, we're gonna let him, we're gonna let him touch this.
You shush, shush.
He farted near Batman.
I call that Joker gas.
Dang.
He smelled so bad, someone said, "Someone's smoking ass."
Whoa, that's a dollar.
That's a dollar.
Nobody said that, you weren't there.
Yeah, but it was just a story.
I make up a story where I say I was fucking pussy and shitting in my own fucking asshole.
What?
That's a story.
That's not a story.
You were trying to circumvent the swear jar.
I'm not complaining that I swear.
You said that no one said that.
I'm saying I know no one said that.
It's a story.
I owe like $10 right now.
So you just kind of went off for no reason.
Yeah, I kind of popped off.
You owe so much.
Caleb can't stop swearing.
I don't know why it's like he's daring.
And what the hell is this guy wearing?
He said H-E-L-L.
Oh my gosh, he's going to jail.
Yep.
Going to swear jail.
At a certain point, we're going to get a swear jail.
Not a problem for me to pay because I'm a dang millionaire.
Oh, we're going to get a thing called the swear jail.
It's a dog cage, puts you in the swear jail.
If you swear too much one episode, we're going to have a camera pointed.
Oh, that's a great idea.
You have to do the whole episode from a swear jail.
Which is a dog crate.
It's a dog crate Caleb's gonna live in.
Wait.
Because he swore too much on the show.
I'm trying to think of...
Wait, you're on the precipice of something right now.
Oh my god.
Yeezus kind of thing going on.
This is like... I'm thinking that this...
Is this like a...
Dang.
Animal Crossing type beat.
Animal Crossing.
When you go into someone's basement, you gotta fight all the cockroaches.
Uh oh, first part of that word could have been encroaching on a swear word.
Dang, yes sir. Go off.
Yup.
I like this beat. I like the sound. Saxophone on the beat. Let's go.
Let's go to the stove. We're gonna go back to Starbucks where the Karen was.
Where the Karens flow.
the
It's not even its final form.
There's going to be a big change.
You ready?
Someone start doing it.
I'll change it in the middle.
Okay.
I went to Dunkin Donuts and I saw a Karen there.
I seen her from the back.
She had the classic Karen hair.
It was blonde as heck and it didn't look so fair.
So I walked up to her and I hit her with my freaking snare.
Give me a snare.
That's a snare.
Yep.
Yeah.
Hit her with that.
Hit her with that in the back of the head.
She fell over, she's dead.
She dropped her ice cream cone.
I hit her with my phone.
I am a caveman walking around a modern world.
I am a caveman and I have a hairy caveman girl.
Also, the Dunkin Donuts was a combination of Baskin Robbins, 23 flavors, rum, raisin.
Get it in my belly, I need that.
I'm a caveman walking into the ice cream store.
I said 23 flavors do you have maybe one more? I asked for Mammoth, asked for Rock
They said no I grabbed my Glock I put it in their face. I said give me my Flavs
Oh, I may have messed up there. I think it's 23 flavors for Dr. Pep Bear. That's Robins 31. That's right
I walked into the Dr. Pepper outlet the other day
I gave them all the flavors and I said this drink is way too sweet for me.
You need to make a diet version.
They accused me of being a soda virgin.
I said I've had soda before, please do not call me different.
I told them that if they don't give me soda, I'll act ignorant and I will throw a stick
of dynamite in here and then I will go to the bar and get adult soda beer.
Wow.
And now just for everyone's
information, there is a Dr.
Pepper outlet.
You can go there on vacation.
That's right.
It's in Asia.
Store is Asian.
Yeah. The owner's Haitian.
That's right. His name is Barry.
And yes, his back is hairy.
Yeah, I seen
his back because I work there and he
used to change in the bathroom.
He's in the bathroom.
A lot of people would see him change
because he biked to work.
That's right. He had a real
recumbent bicycle and it's so low to the flow to the earth.
That's what you should say.
The earth said, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're a rubber, if you're a rubber, if you're
that was his last name, Barry Rubber, we should get political.
If you're a Democrat, I'll defend you.
Love Obama.
He's from Kenya.
Bomb drop.
It's not on the bomb drop.
See, this is so confusing.
The bomb drop.
Bomb drop.
That's right.
Man.
All right.
I mean, is that all the fingers?
That's all the fingers right there.
Except this one.
(Music)
That's not actually a finger.
Drop a beat real quick.
Wait, drop a beat for Pat. He needs a beat right now.
Because I have to play us out.
(Music)
Yeah, tell us about...
I hope this beat didn't leave your ears bleatin'.
On the 28th there's a shareholder meetin'.
That's right.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's the 28th.
What day is it? Hey, Jubio, can you look that up?
Can you see the digits on the calendar?
I said up because I wanted, when I said what day is it, I really wanted to rhyme that with
"idget" which I can't really say so right now I am about to pay.
Is that a parody swear which would fall under parody law?
See it's not a parody, it's just how a cowboy would say it.
By the way, if you hate this song, we don't rap on the Patreon.
That's right.
Go to the website, give us some money so that we never do this again.
And if you hated this episode, I got one thing to say to you.
Eat a load.
Eat a load of vegetables.
Eat your vegetables.
Because technically, we did do a list.
It's a list of band swear words.
A list of fingers.
And a list of five fingers of music.
Really quick, let's go down our list of swear words.
The F word, the S word, the B word, and the A word, the other S word, the other F word,
any racial slurred word, and no idiot, and no D word, and no "Hockey sticks"
Heck is it loud?
Boner, you can't say it, but just a couple, C word, J word, R word, H-O-O-A-S, P word
D word for pussy, D word for dick, suck.
Meanness is a swear, Todgers, anti-cop rhetoric.
Nastiness, pedophilia, choking, sexual gesturing, drugs, Karen Ho.
Dang. Wow.
Alright, bye guys. This is a new era.
That was fun.