(upbeat music)
- Freddy's Nightmare.
- I have--
- Worst start of all time, looked at something
on the screen that wasn't showing up,
and you said--
- I thought it was on the screen.
- You just read it.
- Okay, we were gonna change the name of the podcast
to Normal Podcast 'cause the one episode that we did
where we started the episode with the Mortal Kombat
theme song and it said, "Test your mic, Normal Podcast."
- Why are you talking like an eye of a dog?
That's the context.
They like to set me up and then make me look like
fucking dog shit.
- Wait, okay, so then explain how that
carries over to Freddy's Nightmare or whatever you said.
- Yeah, why did you just--
- Well, Jubio was looking up spaghetti podcasts.
- You're right, we made you look like a moron there.
- Yeah, Jubio did.
Jubio made me look like a moron.
- You know what, will you show the people
why you're acting like this?
- I'm not acting like--
- Show the people why you're acting like--
- Yeah, okay, they didn't let me go and get a Red Bull,
So in an act of defiance, I drank a white claw
that was laying around here in the office.
- What the hell, he's drunk on the job?
- He's literally drunk off his ass.
- Yeah. - It's one o'clock.
- Uh-huh. - 112 PM.
- And I have a problem again.
- No. - Again?
- Dude. (laughs)
- No, dude, no. - Yeah, yeah.
I have a problem again.
- I have a problem.
- I drink every single night and day.
- Night and day?
- Every single night and day.
- Do you think you could maybe slide
into being like the East Coast Burt Kreischer?
No.
You don't think I could?
You think you could?
Yeah, I think I could do it.
Because he's already got that position filled.
I mean, you are a party animal.
Yeah.
You would be if it wasn't for the fact that Amber got there
first.
Yeah.
He-- you haven't understand him for a while.
I'm not riding his damn coattails, you know?
But I remember in Boston--
I wouldn't be wearing any coattails, buddy.
Yeah, no.
You would not be wearing-- you'd be reversing--
Get off stage.
I'm certainly not going to get off stage.
I'd put on like an old-fashioned piano recital,
like the one with the really long coattails.
- You're gonna be called Reverse Kreischer
and you're gonna go up on stage with no pants.
- That would be upside down Kreischer,
that wouldn't be reverse.
- Reverse Kreischer would be putting two shirts on.
- Revert Kreischer.
- Oh.
- Invert Kreischer.
- Invert Kreischer, invert Kreischer, there it is.
- That's pretty good actually.
- Invert Kreischer, you go up no pants and you say,
I'm a...
- So dating is weird.
- What's the opposite of a machine?
Yeah, they call me the organism.
Yeah.
The only thing I knew how to say was
I went to Ukrainian school and they called me the organism.
We're actually coming up with a funny as fuck comedy bang bang character right now.
Yeah.
Invert Kreischer.
No pants.
The only thing I knew how to say was I am nature.
Yeah.
I am a tree.
I am a single celled thing.
You're trying to think of the, okay, what's the opposite of machine?
A tree.
Yeah.
That's just stupid.
No, that's not charged.
Oh, C. F.
Yeah, you're fail.
I'm fail today.
Okay, we're not going to start with that.
No, you're not doing fail flop.
No, no failing, no flopping today.
Yeah, because they already did it.
We're in a flop free, fail free.
We already did it in another episode.
I'm actually in an amazing mood today.
Something about us is once we do bits, we don't like to repeat them.
Fuck no!
Our bits are kind of one-off bits.
We're paid professionals.
We do not repeat anything.
I have a new favorite band, guys.
Do you guys even give a shit?
It's the Grateful Dead or Bob Marley.
No.
Okay, you have two guesses.
You have two guesses who the band is.
It's the Grateful Dead.
Do you guys want to give a shit?
- It's the Grateful Dead or Bob Marley.
- No, okay.
You have two guesses, you have two guesses
who the band is.
And let me give you one little hint.
- Imagine Dragons.
- That's actually close.
- Yeah.
- 21 Pilots?
- It's two words.
No, it's actually more than that.
It's two states.
- Florida Georgia Line.
- Yes.
- You already talked about this.
- It is meant to be, it'll be, it'll be.
- He went home.
He's gonna be over this in a couple weeks.
No I won't. I went to North Carolina.
I became a... it's called bro country, okay?
And actually I found the Wikipedia page for it
so I'll find it while you guys talk shit about me.
Literally all I can do is tsk.
He likes Morgan Whelan for his actions, not his music.
I don't know how I don't even know.
Morgan Whelan got caught saying the N-word at a high school party.
He got caught?
It wasn't... okay. He did say the N-word.
But it was not at a high school party.
It was in his front yard.
- It's really funny to phrase it like
he got caught doing it too.
Like if someone like came around the corner and was like,
"Ah, I gotcha!"
- Hey!
Bro country songs are often musically upbeat.
Oh yeah, that sounds terrible, guys.
With lyrics about attractive young women,
the consumption of alcohol, partying, and pickup trucks.
- I don't fuck with that.
The kind of country that I fuck with
is actually the kind of leftist kind of country
where it says, "I joined the damn union."
- There's been criticism.
- Yeah. - Wait, what?
It's been criticized by listeners and music reviewers
for its repetitive subject matter,
namely lyrical themes of partying associated with Friday--
Associated with Friday nights.
(laughing)
What the fuck?
Alcoholic beverages, euphemistic references to sex
and trucks, as well as its lack of female country artists.
It's called bro country, you SJWs.
It's been criticized for being about Friday night?
He's really not gonna like when I start my new podcast,
Patrick's Music Corner.
Yeah.
both have your own separate shows now.
- Why is that a problem that it talks about Friday?
- Yeah, I'm still trying to kind of puzzle over that.
- Yeah, it's Friday.
- Euphemistic references.
- I think there's only one problem in there, right?
- Yeah, euphemistic sex, euphemistic references
to sex and trucks.
(laughing)
- Euphemistic references to trucks.
- I hate these truck euphemisms.
We're back in the bed and I talk in my room.
Shut up.
How is that bad?
That's cool.
- I'm driving my metal animal.
I don't fuck with trucks because of their gas guzzling.
And I fuck with, you know what I fuck with is Priuses.
- I fuck with most everything.
- I fuck with Priuses and Bell and Sebastian.
- Luckily Blake Shelton is to the rescue in January 2013.
He came to the rescue.
He said he didn't care about old farts
who complained about his songs.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- That's right.
- Well. - Fuck you farts.
- You know what? - I don't like farts.
- I'm not too much a fan of these new farts either.
- I like that country music that's about being
like a cowboy gets shot and the ones where it's like,
"I drank so much and I'm fucking killing myself."
- That's what Morgan Wallen is.
Morgan Wallen is "I drank so much."
- I drank so much and I killed myself.
♪ I need something huge ♪
- I think I'm gonna kill myself.
♪ Something stronger ♪
- You never heard that song?
♪ Think I'm gonna kill myself ♪
- No, he doesn't do that.
- Why are you doing like a 2010 like--
♪ Wap-bap-a-loo-bow ♪
- This is like a--
- That's Waylon Jennings.
- No, you're doing like a 2010
like nerd melt creed impression where you're like myself... nerd melt creed impression
you know like like one of those guys like Jonah Ray you're doing a Jonah Ray
don't ever say that I'm like that... you're like Jonah Ray don't you ever say that... why
was that a thing in Santa for a while where they'd be like I have to go get my
shoes why'd they do muh instead of my shoes like I have to go to... cuz it's
I went to my doctor. It's silly goof behavior
Silly goof yeah, okay
Like a client like a jester yeah, but why did everyone's well?
You'll see somebody do that and it kind of really is like you're all you're definitely yeah. Yeah, you are 30 plus. Yeah old
Yeah, yeah, I feel like we have all definitely are guilty of it. Maybe at one point in our never said
I think that when he was 16 he dressed and did his hair exactly like Pete Holmes
Do you wish?
What is kind of hair does Pete Holmes have?
When I was 16 I wore
Navy
Down I thought TJ Miller swag
- Dude, that fucking, that special where he like,
does a really bad joke and then confetti shoots everywhere
and he pulls out an AK-47, that was actually sick.
- I don't remember that.
- That was a good one.
- Have you seen his new one where he talks
to a mentally disabled guy?
- No.
- It's awesome, it has like 4,000 views on YouTube.
(laughing)
- Is it just like, was he a heckler?
- Yeah, well the guy starts talking to him on his special
and he's like, "Ah, this guy's weird."
And then he starts talking to him and realizes
that he has a mental disability,
and then he named the special like,
hello Jeffrey or whatever the guy's name is.
- Wow.
- It's kind of beautiful.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, it kind of should be a box
if you ask me. - Dude, stand-up is like
a fucking art form, and when you get
beautiful moments like that,
it's actually insane. - No.
- Insane at the moment. - No, no, it's over.
- It's actually, it's pure, no, it's just, it's work.
- Yeah. - It's labor.
- It's labor. - That's how I treat it.
- It's just a job. - There should be a union
if you ask me. - Yeah.
- And a confederacy. - Bro.
- Yeah. (laughs)
of stand-up comedians.
- There kind of is right now,
between Brooklyn and Manhattan.
- Wait, wait.
Now hold on, who's who?
- It's the Seller versus BCC.
- Now who's who?
- Who's who?
(laughing)
- Shut up.
- Yeah, this needs to end.
- The fuck up.
(laughing)
- I didn't like that at all.
- I didn't either.
I couldn't even keep the bit going,
that was so fucking stupid.
- No bits today.
- No bit, no more fucking bits, okay?
- So I was--
- Jubio, pull up just the word history on Google,
and then we'll read that.
- So I was lying in bed and I was thinking,
well so recently I think I've been losing my vision a little.
- You were lying in bed?
What'd you turn to your girlfriend and say you were straight?
- Did you know that history is the study of change over time?
- These are both great, go ahead.
Take 'em away. - I already got mine.
- Take it away Pat, let's go.
- It covers all aspects of human society, political.
- And I was thinking, 'cause I think I've kind of,
my vision was going a little blurry to the point
I think maybe I might go blind soon.
and I was, do you think that if I lost vision in one eye,
like say my left eye, which is the one
that I might go completely blind in,
do you think that the doctor, if I asked,
would just sew it completely shut for me?
- Maybe.
- And do you think I'd look cool
if I had one eye that was sewed shut?
- You could look like my cat Moe, with his weird eye.
- Does he have a sewed shut eye?
- Not yet.
- Would you want it to be, you want stitches,
like going back and forth, like zigzag?
- Yeah, stitches across my eye.
- But they'll dissolve.
- Do you think it would impress my crush?
I think if anything to impress your crush you should look like what's his name the
Klingon guy from undiscovered country who has that built-in eye patch into his skin
so like lost on me one two three like I only like cool stuff like you don't
formers mate mate I don't know any Star Trek look at my shirt look at my shirt
it's closed now you know it's closed mouth the stitch oh my god connect and
- And you're made entirely out of rags?
- No, no, no, no, I'm skin and flesh and bones.
- Or saggy. - The stitch closed mouth.
- And you have a little bit--
- You know what, here's what I do, right?
I go out on my first dates and I duct tape my mouth closed.
Right, and I show up and I say, yeah, it ends today.
Censorship is ending today.
And I take off my--
- Censorship.
(laughing)
- What?
What are you saying?
- I go, I show up for the date and she's like,
wait, this guy said something so dangerous
that they duct tape his mouth closed.
- Hey, you know what?
- Now go.
- How do you say,
how do you buy the duct tape and you say,
"You're beautiful."
- You say, "Brr, brr, brr."
- Yeah, I know.
- 'Cause your lips are still tucked together.
(laughing)
- Yeah, wait, how did you get the date if your mouth
is closed?
- That's all those comedy specials
where they have the duct tape on their mouth.
I'd like to see them try to do fucking stand up
with duct tape on their fucking mouth.
I dare you, Bill Burr, go up on stage,
Eliza Schlesinger. - Does she do that?
- I don't know.
- I know Eliza Schlesinger.
Yeah, but she's got him on her nipples too.
Go up there and try to tell your jokes
with duct tape on your mouth.
And if you can, then I'll--
We will actually respect you as not--
and it has nothing to do with your gender.
No.
It has everything to do with--
I'll go on a date with you, Elijah, if you can do that.
I'll go on one date with you.
Yeah, he'll go on a date with Elijah.
I'll go on one single date with you, Elijah.
Elijah.
Yeah, the book of Elijah.
I know what you're hiding.
Yeah, it's probably a movie called The Box of Elijah.
- I would shorten her name down a little.
- What?
- Like E-S.
- I think her name starts with an I.
- E-S Schleslingler?
- Well it's just, yeah, see it's,
you triple, you can't say it without--
- Tripler?
- Having an issue.
- Should we get into, should we all do a--
- Trish.
- Should we all do a--
- Trisha.
- Trish, that'd be a good name.
- Here's how we change your whole thing.
- Who would have the best--
- Your name is now Trish.
- Your name is Trisha, we're gonna change your hair to blue.
- Uh-huh.
- And you're--
- Don't even say blue hair.
comic. Who of us would have the best T.S. Eliot style two letter? Not me. Not me. P.E.
Dora. I've already talked about it in my fucking bank account. Bank of America changed it.
Yeah. P.E.D.O.? No. But remember how I used to open the Bank of America app and it would
just say P.E.D.O. star star star? Because of my name? Well that's cool though, it makes
- It's like Beto Killer or something.
- Yeah. - Well, no, no, no.
- Like the Club Penguin's internship.
- The exact amount of letters is the same amount
as Peter Wiles. (laughing)
Every time that I would open it up.
- Dude, your parents are so stupid.
- I, dude, it's so fucking stupid.
It's so, my name is Patrick, my mom's name is Patricia.
- C.E. Fetter's kinda good, I could see that
on a shampoo bottle. - C.E. Fetter.
- A shampoo bottle? - Yeah.
- C.M. Pitts. - Whoa.
- That's like an ergonomic brand, I think.
- C.E. Pitts.
- Some kind of lifestyle chair brand or something.
- Middle name is Michael, guys.
Guess what, yeah, I tried to go as Michael
for a little bit when I was a kid.
- I tried to go as Edward for a little bit
because people kept calling me Patricia.
'Cause they would say I was a gay girl.
- That's, yeah, well, you would've been Edwardina
if you were Edward, that just happens no matter what.
My last name was Pitts going around in middle school.
- But it's a layup.
- And I smelled bad.
- And it's a layup, though.
Patricia and then I and then I it's a push up with a backed into a corner like a wimp and I say
Wack you off even more. Yeah, I'll whack you worse and I'll board you
Whack me. I'll whack you up corner. I will literally whack you all are you and what?
I'll whack you will not whack me off. I mean, I'm gonna get up. I'll whack you right now. Don't whack me
I'll whack you off right now. I'm gonna pinch the bottom of your butt. Don't don't pinch my butt till it closes
So it closes if he has ever experienced something I
Don't you dare I talked to don't you dare pinch my butt until it
Talked to two people this week who told me that sometimes they get something that they call butt chills
Have you ever had experiences where something is something disgusting will happen in a movie or something and you'll go
Oh god, and your asshole will close up. Oh wait
It's like chills on the back your nap, but but in your asshole and around your butt
I've never had that I there is sometimes anytime that I get anytime that in a movie somebody
hurts their vagina though, I feel a phantom pain as if I had a vagina.
There is something like very specific...
You guys ever get that?
Where I'm like, "Ugh! If I had a vagina, I would feel something right now."
I guess in your brain, you're just thinking, "Everyone's got nuts."
I always, you know...
It is a little bit like... But I feel it exactly between my asshole and my balls,
like in my taint, and I go like, "Oh, if I had a vagina there..."
You think you're gonna grow a vagina?
I've always thought that.
When I was a kid I thought that I used to have one
and they sewed it shut.
Yeah, we talked about that.
I know.
We've talked about that ad nauseum.
Yeah.
Yeah, nauseum, for real.
Yeah, nauseum, me thinking about you with a vagina
makes me throw up.
You know when people do the thing--
You're fucked up.
I'm not fucked up.
You are.
Where someone is underwater in a movie,
you hold your breath and you count
to see if you would survive.
Yeah.
No.
I do that too, but I can only hold my breath
for like three seconds.
I get really upset every time I have to turn the movie off.
You gotta endurance train you.
That is sad.
I think we have the dunk tank episode.
Instantly holding your breath.
I can't do it.
Not me because I won several breath holding competitions.
No I can hold my breath for probably ten hundred minutes.
That's just not fucking true.
You're not David Blaine.
Fuck you asshole.
I was going to hold my breath but then I remembered something.
Then I remembered something.
My little brother when he would get mad that he couldn't get an action figure at the store
or something, he would yell at my mom and say,
"I'm gonna hold my breath until you bite me."
- That's a classic kid move.
- That is a classic, yeah.
- I bet holding your breath, like, (gasps)
yeah.
- That's like a-- - Oh, what,
and train your lungs to be one day an Olympic swimmer
and buy me a million dollar house?
You have boo fucking hoo.
- I feel like that's something that you,
sometimes you're a kid and you watch a movie about kids
and you learn something about being a kid from the movie
and you're like, "Oh, I'm supposed to do that."
- Yeah, I did. - That's one of those things.
- I did spend a lot of-- - You learn from Home Alone
- There was definitely years of my life--
- You see The Good Son as a kid and you're like,
okay, this is--
(laughing)
- There were years of my life where I just pretended
to be whatever kid belonged to Adam Sandler
in a given movie, who was like a funny brat.
And I just did that for a little bit.
- Yeah, or you watched Scooby-Doo,
you watched Malcolm in the Middle as a kid,
you're like-- - You just ate a big sandwich
with all the stuff on it.
- Yeah, Malcolm in the Middle, I thought, I was like,
I just thought-- - You thought you were Reese.
- I thought I was Reese, definitely thought I was,
I actually thought I was Malcolm 'cause I was
middle child and my brother was a complete Reese. I literally wanted to be
an inventor. Tell me more what did you invent? Flashlight. Flashlight with tape on
it? Yeah. So the button stays on forever. I wanted to be an inventor so bad. I knew that I did not have inventor in me but I
I knew that I maybe had Inventor's Assistant.
- Yeah, you would be a good Inventor's Assistant.
- Just a really low level dream for a kid.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well.
- A position that doesn't exist either.
- I loved, I wanted to make a Rube Goldberg machine.
- The Inventor's Apprentice.
- You could do that though.
- When you're like a kid and you're like first,
you first get like a thing of dominoes
and you're like, oh my God.
- But then you realize it only goes like,
it's only like 15 dominoes.
Like you would need to spend--
- I did a pack of dominoes that are for like,
old guys to play at like, on a table.
- Yeah, I did, and also it takes so long to set them.
- I would try to come up with a Rube Goldberg machine,
I'd always hit the impasse where I'd be like,
okay, so here, the dominoes fall, all right,
they hit this book, the book falls over,
it hits a marble, the marble goes up this ramp,
and then it shoots across the room
and it goes out the window.
Well how am I gonna do that last part, I don't know.
- Also, what is it, what is it,
like, I don't have any use for it, what am I,
what is the end? - Exactly, I don't know.
- What's the last stage? - I'm a kid, there's nothing I need to do.
- Yeah, it knocks over the last domino.
Hey, I built a Rube Goldberg machine that knocks over a domino.
That's like what I would think of.
- Yeah. - Like, I'm not gonna make it.
- Yeah, you always get to the one where it's like,
"Okay, and then this needs to fly up and hit the ceiling."
- Yeah. - "This needs to spin around like a helicopter."
- At least Pee-wee had the right idea. - I guess I quit.
- Hmm. Let me think about this.
I think that what I'll do is I'll quit doing this now.
- I think instead I'll just draw it.
- I'll draw it and I'll imagine it for a while.
(laughing)
And then I'll think about how it might go
as a scene in a movie for a little bit.
- I wish I could watch a movie and be like,
I didn't like that movie, I'm just gonna imagine
it's a different one instead.
- Did you ever do the thing growing up
where you would be watching a movie
that you'd seen before and you would just be like,
I'm pretty sure that it will be different this time
and the bad stuff is not gonna happen.
No, I still do that.
Sometimes I'll-- - You know what?
- I rewatched Barbarian and I was like,
I think this time she's just gonna call the police.
- Yeah.
- She did call the police though,
and they ignored her. - But in the beginning.
I was like, I think while she's still pretty,
she'll call the police, 'cause that's a good idea,
but she didn't do it.
- Yeah.
- So I'm hoping that happens next time I watch it.
- That was one of the only movies I saw last year.
- Speaking of seeing movies.
- Oh man.
- Oh my God.
- Do we have a treat for the listeners of this pod, Cameron?
- Can you just read your full review?
- My full review?
Well, I'll just do a, I didn't really.
- I wish we had like a screen that could pop up
that had just like a photo of you in a box of popcorn.
- I wish we had a screen that could pop up.
(screams)
- I guess we have one.
I saw John Wick 4, ladies and gentlemen.
And I actually didn't even want to do a review,
I just wanted to share a funny thing that happened,
but I'll do a review.
- Give us the review.
- Fans of the violence inherent to the three prior movies.
- What?
- Will be flocking in droves to see the new John Wick 4
and they will not be disappointed.
as the
post can we put like popcorn like his head is a piece of hair I'll start over
that was a bad start anyway and then we'll put the we'll put the at the
Ebert and Roper at the movies theme song Keanu Reeves is back for his fourth
time try him okay let me start over yeah really get this because this is gonna
like drive you if your thing is gonna be your thing is blindingly speed okay if
your thing is blindingly fast martial arts at the speed of sound or Cameron
- Yeah.
- Just, okay.
- I want you to, this is gonna be an IG reel, so.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right, so you're gonna be in a movie theater.
- Two hours and 49 minutes of pulse-pounding action
is the name of the game,
and the name of the movie is John Wick 4.
Directed by Keanu Reeves' director,
and starring Keanu Reeves,
this movie did not disappoint when it came to
fighting with different characters,
many different actors playing the characters,
- And all sorts of music, pulse pounding action
and pulse pounding music as well.
Dubstep and that's one song.
What's the one?
- Don't focus on the score, focus on the action.
- Okay, and there were, there's a scene
where cars in the circle, there's a scene
where the firings.
- We don't want spoilers.
- Okay, no spoilers.
- No spoilers for you.
- The ending will shock you.
- Cameron, just give us a one minute,
one minute, one minute.
spoiler-free review from Cameron's Corner.
- The popcorn will fly across the seats at this flick.
How's that?
That's like a brief--
- It's a minute.
- The soda--
(clapping)
- The soda will fizz.
- The soda will flow.
(laughing)
The popcorn will fly and the soda will flow
this week at John Wick 4.
The action fans are sure to have something.
- And there's no spoilers here.
- Make sure to see it in IMAX for the biggest screen possible.
- And if you're interested in spoilers,
might I recommend going to see Fast and Furious instead,
if you're that kind of an action fan.
- Or my new movie, Spoilers, about rotten apples.
- And rotten kitties.
(laughing)
- Anthropomorphic rotten apples,
it's a sequel to Shrinkers.
(laughing)
It's about a bunch of guys who shrink down
and have to fight rotten apples called spoilers.
- And the tagline.
- And you have to stop them from getting into the bags
with the other animals, 'cause they make themselves a spoil.
- The tagline is, "This is one bad bunch."
- So you were saying that John Wick 4
has a lot for the action fans.
- But what happened in this theater, Cameron?
- No, but listen to me.
You're a bit of an interrupter today.
That would be the movie about Patrick.
- It'd be a good movie, though.
- That would be a pretty good movie, the interrupter.
If you're more of a fan--
- Interrupting the news.
- If you're more of a fan of the talking parts of John Wick,
is there something for you there?
- Oh yes, there's something for everyone.
The action fans, the fans of talking,
the fans of two, one female character,
or many, many male characters,
many of whom do not have names.
- The fans of Keanu's long hair.
- Fans of Keanu's line reads.
- And his hair line.
- Longer.
- His red hair.
- Will be disappointed.
- Oh, 'cause his hair is still black.
(laughing)
- Keanu Reeves--
- But fans of his red gunfire will be slavering
and cyberpunk and slobbering.
- Slavering?
What are you talking about slavering?
What, that's not a word?
- That's a word.
- Cyberpunk 2077, Keanu Reeves red hair mod.
- I'm a film critic, I have to know all the words.
- Will you look up slavering to see if that's a word?
- Slavering is a word for film critics.
- See?
- To let saliva run from the mouth.
- Slavoring.
- It's similar to dribble.
- Oh, okay.
- Dribble.
- Fans will be dribbling.
(laughing)
And fans of action stars from throughout the ages
will be dribbling out of their lips.
- People also ask, what is the meaning of dribble?
- No, that says dribbable.
That has too many Bs.
- Yeah, there is no meaning.
- Oh, it's also trickle.
trickle. Fans will be trickling in their seats.
-Triple.
-John Wick 4. Does he go to different countries? Oh wait, sorry.
-Yes, he does.
-Just tell your fucking story.
-I mean, it's a good movie. You should see it. I really liked it. But I was sitting in
the IMAX theater next to an old black guy and the entire movie.
-Stop right there. That's a pretty good story.
-The entire movie, every single time that somebody got shot or stabbed, which is like
literally probably at least like 300 times.
- Yeah.
- Like the most shootings and stabbings
I've ever seen in a movie.
- Yeah.
- Every single time he like visibly jumped,
like he was like, literally every time someone got killed,
he was like.
- That's a guy who's--
- It was so crazy.
- That guy's definitely a veteran of some kind.
- Yeah, something was going on with him.
- There's some kind of issue.
- And I was kind of worried about him,
'cause I was like, this does not seem like he's having fun.
But at the end, like when there was one really crazy thing
it happened he was like oh oh okay he's good.
When you get that oh in front of the ho ho ho's that's how you know oh that's a good time.
All right I'm gonna have to see that. Yeah yeah but it is three freaking hours long.
Three hours? I think it should be four hours one for every movie it is. I hate the movies so
much now because they're all three hours long. I remember when movies used to be
21 minutes at advertisements and they'd be 30 minute blocks and there's a bunch of different channels back in the movies used to have
commercials in them
And they used to be modified for the smaller screen movies used to come in these little
Cartridge things and you put them in your movie player
And then you play them around with a with a play around with myself when I watched them
And if you put a man's got a watch lose your seat lose leisure
Let me try that again.
This guy watched it leisurely seat Larry.
- Flop. - Or seat.
- That is a flop.
- Leisure suit.
- Speaking flop.
- Speak flop.
- Okay. - Speak flop.
- No, I didn't speak in a flopping way.
He just farted.
- No, it was a burp.
- No, you acted like you were burping
but it came out of your ass.
You moved your mic away from your mouth to fart.
You went.
- I didn't even fart.
- Yeah, you did.
- I would have admitted it.
- I felt it.
- No, no, no, no, no, 'cause it would,
my farts have been just rancid lately.
Ask Noah.
- Ask Noah about my farts.
Call him right now.
- I'll ask him. - Call him at work.
- I'll ask him.
- We'll call him at work.
He's gonna tell you that my house has been stinkerton city.
I know that he's gonna use that word.
- That's exactly what he's gonna say.
(laughing)
- That's exactly what Noah will say.
- Yeah, he did it stinkerton.
(laughing)
- He did it stinkerton in the living room.
- I'm calling him on speaker.
So you're saying he's gonna say,
- He's gonna say stinkerton city.
- The house has been stinkerton city.
- Yo, what's up?
- Hey, I was wondering if Patrick has had
really, really stinky farts recently.
- I haven't noticed.
He hasn't been around me recently though.
He's been dodging me.
- Whoa.
(laughing)
Whoa, that's an accusation.
- I hung out with him, we watched home movies last night
on the Plex.
- All right, well.
- Yeah, first time you spent time with me in months, dude.
- All right, you're sounding--
- You are--
- You're sounding really, really whack right now.
I just wanna say that.
You're sounding pretty whack.
- I guess you (beep) made you soup.
I said her name, I can't say her name.
- Yep, and now we have to bleep that out.
We're on the show right now.
But basically, we thought that we were gonna--
- Patrick's farts are smelly, but they're second to yours.
- Can you, thank you.
- Ooh.
- Thank you very much, thank you very much for that.
Could you, we thought that we were gonna call you,
you were gonna call his farts Stinkerton City.
That's what we anticipated.
- No, they're not that bad, that's definitely you.
You're Stinkerton City.
- Okay.
- Well, he's still sitting.
Guys, this backfired on me in a massive way.
I hope you have a nice day.
(silence)
(laughter)
Well that couldn't have gone worse.
That couldn't have gone fucking worse.
(laughter)
- I thought straight up he would have said
Stinkerton City at least three times.
- Yeah.
- I could have seen it happening.
- I thought he was gonna say Stinkerton City population
whatever, do all of his different lines in a row.
- Yep.
- And we were gonna go Noah, you bastard.
- He's acting like I didn't hang out with him.
He and I watched that video.
- By the way, I think if he had known
that he was on the show, he wouldn't have been so kind of,
that guy was pretty female,
the way that he was complaining like that.
- Yep.
- Right?
- He's saying that I dodged him.
I watched that video with him last night.
You know the Tweek Tweek, the meth head pedophile?
And he backs his car up into the pole and stuff
and gets tackled. - No, I don't know that.
- Have you seen that video?
- I don't think so.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, I don't seek stuff like that out usually.
I don't search meth head in a file.
I usually, yeah, I look for like kind of like...
The video where the guy, he's in a Vons and then he's like...
Yeah, you shouldn't Google yourself, Patrick.
He's in a Vons grocery store and he's like on meth and the guy's like, "Why are you trying to hook up with my 13 year old brother?"
And he's like, "I'm buying fiber so I can poop!"
And the guy chases him.
These videos never make any sense if you explain them.
Yeah, they don't.
So why even try?
Yeah, but this one's the best one.
Noah and I watched the full 13 minutes.
When you see this, you're gonna understand.
- Why have you had such diabolically
stinkerton city toots, man?
- I think it's 'cause I made that cabbage thing.
- Two weeks ago?
- Yeah.
And then I've been eating a lot of gut stuff,
like fermented, like I made myself.
- That's good for you, that will make you not fart.
- I think the farting is good.
- It gets you at first though.
- I think it's clearing my gut biome.
- Oh yeah, I've been on it.
- I'm eating a lot of fermented foods and stuff.
- I'm starting to believe that my stomach
is more important than my brain.
And the way that most people obsess about their brain health,
that's how I'm obsessing about my stomach for now on.
- Do people obsess about their brain health?
- I do that too.
- Oh, is that a thing?
- You can't do anything for your brain.
- Well, like vitamins and stuff.
- People think that you can take ashwagandha,
you can take nootropics and stuff.
- It doesn't work on him.
- None of the brain stuff works.
- No, not for you.
- You can't change what you're immune to.
- It doesn't work on me either, 'cause I outsmart it.
- I take the ashwagandha and my brain kind of like
plays around, it's like, oh I see what you're trying to do.
- Dude, ashwagandha is not a nootropic.
- No, no, no, no.
- No, I take like lithium and then I'm like.
- Yeah, my brain is like, I see that coming in.
- Lithium, what's that, a battery?
Come on now, matrix.
Trying to charge my brain up?
Get out of here.
- You know who needs some lithium?
Elmer Fudd.
- Yep.
- Wiffium.
- He does, he's bipolar as fuck.
- I didn't take my wiffium today.
(laughing)
I didn't want to kill you, bunny.
I don't want to kill the bunny.
It's duck season.
It's wabbit season.
Oh, no.
But yeah, Elmer Fudd should be helped.
He should be at least put into a mayor's prison.
Or a foster care, yeah.
The thing is--
People forget that about him.
If Elmer Fudd existed today, he'd be all over TikTok.
You literally couldn't make Elmer Fudd today.
You definitely could not.
He'd be called Elmira Fudd, and he would have pronouns.
- What's his name, Elmer Fudd, age 83.
- Wait, what?
- We're not doing guns,
Elmer Fudd loses his white to bare arms.
- Oh my God.
- That's kind of rude to say.
- Is there an Elmira Fudd on Baby Looney Tunes?
I feel like I know that, but I just need to--
- Elmira Fudd?
- Yeah.
- Is Elmira Fudd a millionaire?
- Elmira Duff.
Elmira Duff.
- Oh, okay, that's stupid.
I hate that.
- And it wasn't on Baby Looney Tunes,
it was on the other one.
- I literally would smack the fuck
got on most of the Looney Tunes were they real?
- Oh, me too, bro.
- If I saw Taz, I mean, you know,
I'd have some tranquilizers on me first.
- Let me tell you what-- - But if I saw Taz--
- I'm going lethal.
- Yeah, I see Bugs, that's an open hand, front hand slap.
Bah!
Right, he spins around.
- If I see Daffy-- - Then I turn,
I turn, Daffy, boom, backhand,
the knuckles crack his fucking beak.
- That's what I would do with Bugs.
- Porky, what are you doing to Porky?
- I'd smack the shit out of Bugs,
say, "That's for the transphobia, mister."
And then I see Pepe Le Pew over there, I'm spinning my arm like I'm winding up for a baseball pitch.
That's for the sexual misconduct, Pepe.
I walk over, I walk over, boonk! Right on the head.
Yep.
His head goes down into his chest like a Mortal Kombat fatality.
Gossamer, I'm picking up Gossamer by the legs, I'm using him as a bat.
Who's Gossamer?
That's the big orange guy.
Oh, I hate him!
I'm swinging Gossamer right at Granny.
Thanks for making me think that you were a mascot for a sports game team.
You know how they do a speed bag and they go boo boo boo boo?
Yeah.
Like that, I'm going up to Tweety Bird
and I'm doing that with two fingers.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
(imitates gun firing)
That's for having a speech impediment.
And for being a boy.
And then there's a lot of--
That's for being a boy when I thought that you were a girl.
(laughing)
Asshole.
I'm lining up all the ones with speech impediments.
Come on, Elmer.
And then I'm slapping them all in the mouth.
I'm taking Elmer home and I'm starting to tell people
that he's my brother at the grocery store.
Yeah.
(laughing)
And I know I would say, listen, I'm walking around,
I'm slapping Daffy, I'm poking Tweety,
I'm doing ever slap and Daffy sounds like
That sounds like like a song from the 50s. Yeah, like having sex in a car. Yeah, I'm walking
I'm what I you know I've been I've been doing hand-to-hand combat against these tunes, but I see Porky Pig. It's on-site
I'm literally I literally I'm gonna walk home. I'm
Put a tracker on him first of all so I know where he is before I walk
walk tag on
Going on my closet open up my gun safe. You think there's a gun in there. No. It's a spiked flail. Holy shit
I ride my horse back to where he is
Marvin the Martin is going I mean soda can that one I think is an even matchup between me and him he would laser me
to death
Why is he never included in any of these like Homelander versus Superman things yeah add Marvin
He could he could he could go up or add that motherfucking Roadrunner
- True. - He's invincible.
- Superman versus Road Runner.
- That's true.
- I think that's been done though.
- If I could go into-- - Really?
- I think it's been done to death.
(laughing)
- You might be right.
- If I could go into the Toon world--
- Yeah, I don't know man, I think it's been done to death.
- I'd go up to Wile E. Coyote and be like,
"Yo man, stop fucking around."
I would just say that and literally just from that,
he'd grab the Road Runner and just shred him up.
- I'd show Wile E. Coyote Dance with the Devil
by Immortal Technique, change his fucking,
like fuck him up in a way that is like so visceral
in his brain through that song that he's like,
I'm like, I can't control my emotions,
I'm buying a piece today.
I'm fucking shooting that road.
- He needs to get after it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Be about it.
I'd sit down, I'd kneel down, 'cause he's really small,
he's a coyote, I'd put my hand on his shoulder.
I'd say, hey buddy.
- After he's done the deed?
I don't know. Before, this is how I would say it. Honestly, I've been watching your show
for years. I like you. I think you're a good guy, but you're not about it.
I don't care.
And I think I...
Because he looks up to you.
Exactly. He knows me.
He looks up to you.
Well, before that, I'd formed a relationship with him over a few years. So he did look
up to me at that point.
So you'd drive up with your limo, and then he'd come up and say, "Gee, Cameron, you're
one of my favorites.
- And I'd say, you're one of my favorites too,
except one thing I really don't like about you is
you don't want it like that.
You're not hungry.
- And you also don't got it like that, really.
- You don't got it like that.
- You literally, it's almost like the point of the show
has become your failure.
- Yeah, and then he'd see me walk away
and I'd walk up to the Roadrunner and be like,
"Yo, what's up?"
And we'd start partying.
- Roadrunner.
- You're being the Roadrunner, we'll be partying.
♪ He's got cold, I'm wondering why ♪
- That show should have been two episodes, okay?
It should have been, the first episode should have been
Killing the Roadrunner on the second episode should have been what he does with the body disposal
Yeah, and then maybe a third episode. It's an investigation basically Fargo is what that's a good idea
Yeah, they're doing it with fucking honey the poo
Shut up, can I just speak my shit
Talk like shit
Can I just talk like shit please and just say hubbada, but with it and you guys not stop me for once in my life
Okay, because it hubbada, bubby
Okay, I looked at you
That's right there and he's one beer deep so I know he gonna do the whole squad
Would you do the gang if you had one beer you can't stop but then having to apologize your girl for the next day
I'm sorry, baby. I had a I think I said this before I drink half of a raspberry white claw and I did the whole gang
I did let the whole squad hit I said this a while ago
I think but I want I don't it wasn't I think I just said it to you guys at lunch
I always want to maybe get it on recording
But if I was a girl I would
Yeah, I would be giving it up to Patrick
Yeah, for certain and I know it sounds like it sounds like it said but listen I go for a BP
I'm just not finished here. Okay. It sounds like that means he's like
I think he's really hot or special or whatever.
But if I was a girl, I'd just be fucking literally everybody.
- Yeah.
- I'd give it to anybody who asked.
- Yeah, dude, of course.
- They would literally,
they would call me in and out burger.
'Cause people would be in and out there
and my shit would look like a burger.
(laughing)
- A burger, I'd do a burger.
I would.
All right, do we wanna get into the list?
- Yeah, let's go to the list for today.
- Intro to it.
Actually, I'd also just remembered there was something we can we'll save it to the very end
There was a picture to show this is a title slide. This is a good title slide. So this is just a
Blog that I found this is
Here I'll show you the tables moved weird today, cuz I just like pulled a hamstring. I'm so sorry you pulled a hamstring
Yeah, you floss with hamstring. This is the
This is the blog of Tyler
That was really good. Tyler the awesome. Tyler the awesome. And this blog has probably enough content to literally do maybe a
hundred episodes on. Wow. From Tyler? From Tyler. Tyler like is really a high-volume creator. Maybe this is where he got Igor.
Mate. Huh? Do you realize what you just said? What did I say? Tyler is a high-quality V8 creator. What?
Oh, I should. Does it remind you of any rap, mister? No, wait. No, you're too indie. You're thinking animal collective.
I'm trying to think of rap iron and wine. No motherfucker. Who are you talking? He pretended to be gay for four years
So he could sell an album called flower boy. Yeah. Yeah, so that way and it all fell apart
So when everybody got mad at a model, yeah
Yeah
I'm I think my favorite thing my my my secret pleasure my happy joy is that when?
Whenever somebody an artist or something doesn't make something for a while
they make a bunch of music and they stop because maybe they're happy or they become fulfilled
or whatever. I think I'd hate them when I say you fell off.
Yes.
I gotta say, you didn't make an album in a few years, you fell off.
Frank Ocean fell off.
Yeah, exactly. They found what they want to do with their life. They're living a beautiful
private life.
Fuck you.
You're mid, bro. You fell off.
Yeah, you fell the fuck off.
You need to be getting interviewed by Drewski right now or you fell the fuck off.
You fell off.
Dude, imagine though that interview.
Drewski.
Drewski and me? Yeah, I can imagine it. I've thought about it a lot.
If we want to circle back to our point before this, Drewski, Wiley Coyote interview where
he's talking about like, "Yeah, I saw you in Cameron's limo."
Wow.
You saw the celebrity photo.
I have a strong feeling that Wiley Coyote and Cameron in a limo would be a Megan The
Stallion's Tory Lanez kind of situation. Where you might shoot a hole right through his fucking
leg, right?
right? Yeah, he'd be like, so basically the cover would be like, I'm just driving him to his house,
I'm driving him home in my limo. I'm like, "Oh, you want to get a ride?" Like, "My limo's right here."
He goes to get, he's like, "Thanks for the ride, Cameron. Okay, I'm going to get out." And I'll be
like, "Yeah, sure." Click. Doors locked. Oh my God, that's scary. And then just boom, boom, boom,
boom. Like he's in the passenger seat and I'm not even shooting him. I'm hitting him.
- But then you would get sent,
they would send you back to Kenya.
- That would be all over TMZ.
- No, 'cause my limo has a button
where it compresses itself and disappears into a dot.
- Yeah, TMZ wouldn't be able to find the story.
Okay, so show us Tyler.
- Yeah, so here's the welcome to his blog.
Hello everybody, so yeah, this is my blog.
Not too sure what to write for a first post,
but well, you're in for a heck of a time.
- Written with dictation software.
This is a, it's really hard to explain with this blog.
He makes up a bunch of video games and movies and TV shows
and they're all super lore heavy and all intertwined
and contain characters from all his favorite TV shows
and stuff like that.
I like it.
So I don't really have a good introduction
for what most of this stuff is,
but we're gonna go through some of his characters
and then some of his editorials that he also writes
in between where he's coming up
with all his world building and stuff.
He also says, so here's an introduction of the blog.
If you've been itching for a peek at my imagination,
which I know you guys have,
then you've come to the right place.
We've got character profiles,
weapon/equipment descriptions,
outlines for multiple seasons of Tyler Fishfingers,
the animated series,
beat by beat breakdowns of individual episodes,
lyrics from original songs,
you'll have to make up your own tunes, sorry,
multiple ideas for feature films,
an unhealthy obsession with Vordak the incomprehensible,
boss fight strategies, randomness,
the occasional fan fiction, and so much more.
Be sure to come back often as I post new content
So you can watch my ideas unfold and evolve in real time.
- How did you find Tyler the Awesome?
- Randomness.
- I think I was looking up original characters.
I was looking up, finding people's original characters.
- My first thought was that you looked up
the word randomness.
- No.
- And this showed up.
- No, 'cause then I'd be finding basically random ass shit,
which would not be very useful.
If I typed in randomness through Google,
it'd probably be like, "Geez, bicycle."
- "Cheese bicycle?"
- Yeah, stuff like that.
And that's not really all there is.
- You just made a Wisconsinites dream.
- But so this guy, he says, "Be sure to come back often
"as you post new content."
And I checked with the most recent thing,
this website, he stopped putting his stuff up
on his blog in like 2020.
And I was reading the post where he said why he stopped.
And he's like, "Yeah, I don't use this blog anymore
"'cause I discovered Google Docs."
- Oh, so he's just typing himself now.
- He puts everything into Google Docs now.
- Oh wow.
- It's just so funny, he's like,
"Yeah, I discovered Google Docs."
(laughing)
- And also just admitting that nobody ever needed
to read any of it.
So this is a healthy helping of my original character.
So here's some of his characters that he's come up with.
Most of the characters featured here
were originally created for the video game
Dramarama 2 in space.
Recently, I decided to bring them back and reinvent them.
They could be useful in an alternate version
of the Tyler Fishfinger series
that features only original characters.
First up on the list we have--
- Do we have like a photo of Tyler Fishfinger?
- No, there's no photo.
No, Tyler Fish, I literally,
all I could find out about Tyler Fishfinger's,
like this is such a web of complicated story stuff.
He's a cyborg.
Tyler Fishfingers. - And he's got
fish for fingers? - Sounds amazing.
- He's a cyborg, that's all I know about him, really.
But I think he's the main character,
but he also could just be the name of it.
But anyway, and he's not even in the original characters.
- 'Cause he's in, it's obvious.
- Yeah, you should know who he is.
- At least Tyler would be awesome.
- Here's the first character that Tyler's created.
Cooper Holdive.
- Wow, Cooper has a different kind of style going on.
- Yeah. - Yeah, you wanna
describe his outfit?
Yeah, so I would say that he has the kind of a Statue of Liberty style stance.
Yeah.
But then he has a...
Marvin the Martian style hat.
Maybe a Cory...
Yeah, it looks like a colander almost on his head.
And that is two big strings of spaghetti on the side.
And his shoes actually look dope.
Yeah.
He has a new style of shoe as well.
That could be on like that Instagram page of skier sneakers.
Oh, and he has a bowling shirt on.
His shirt is a bowling ball going through two bowling pins.
Oh my God, I thought that was a Bob-omb.
No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no.
- And he's holding a baseball.
So this guy, a little bit of a sportsman some might say.
- So let's, based on, that's a good game.
We look at the drawing, see what you guys think,
and then we'll see what he actually is.
- Is he wearing glasses?
- So that's my guess, that's my guess is that
he has a sport ability.
- You have any guess, Pat?
- I think that he is also, yes, a sports guy.
- Okay, so copier.
What else is new?
- Cooper is exceedingly confident at any sport
That involves a perfectly round ball.
(laughing)
And has the skills to justify his confidence.
Too bad he was born into a family of free divers.
Yes, his mom is none other than Beth Holdive
from this post, which I clicked on,
and I couldn't even find information about Beth Holdive.
Although Cooper is often at the bottom of the sea,
when he'd rather be at the top of the ninth inning,
- That's a pretty good line.
- He secretly enjoys the sensation of being underwater.
Just not a whole lot.
- Okay, Cooper.
I like the name, too.
- I do like this guy.
- Yeah, what do you guys think?
- I like Cooper, I'm gonna give him a four.
- Yeah, yeah, okay, what's the--
- And I also wanna get-- - Four out of what?
- When we get to the end of the characters,
I need to hear which character you guys--
- 'Cause it could've been four out of 10.
- Tag yourself, type five.
- So Cooper, I'm not Cooper,
because I am more into different oblong balls.
- Yeah, almonds.
- Almond balls.
- Almond shapes. - Pucks.
- Pucks. - Yeah.
- Do like pucks.
- Is a puck a ball?
- That's what I was just about to say.
- It is, it is.
- September Pleszewski.
- Polish. - Okay, so here's
what I'd like to say.
This is a trace of Franny, or Frankie--
- Total Drama Island. - No!
From Foster's Home. - Yeah.
- No, it's not. - For Imaginary Children.
And she has her, but just in the way
that she's holding her waist, right?
I do like that he drew her knees.
That was sweet of him. (laughing)
To draw her knees.
- Oh, and she's wearing shorts.
- And honestly, she looks pretty busty.
- And she also has some kind, she's wearing a square.
- And an exposed belly button.
- Yeah.
- Okay, so as far as abilities,
she has a bandaid on her right cheek,
so I'm guessing that she is amazing
at getting really badly hurt or something.
Or she's invincible, or she's invisible.
She's either invincible or invisible.
- You know, when I see bandaid on the cheek,
my brain immediately goes to the singer Nelly.
- You think she's a rapper?
- So I think, yes, I think she's a Saint Louis.
- All right.
- You think she's a saint?
Okay, so she's either a invisible, invincible, or a lunatic.
Those are the three guesses that we're gonna take.
- Let me read this out to you.
- Or she's a Christian.
- This tough, unruly anti-hero grew up
on the streets of New Jersey, pronounced Joy-Z.
While September may seem unfriendly at first,
you just have to give her a little time of respect.
Do that and you've got yourself a loyal companion.
She's a bit of a prankster, that one,
though her pranks used to be a lot meaner.
She still punks her friends every now and then
just to remind them that they're lucky she's on their side.
a little behind the scenes.
September was originally going to be from New York.
That idea was scrapped after I realized
the unfortunate connection between New York and September.
- That's right.
- Okay, so pretty far away from Saint Lunatic.
- But when I saw Auntie here, I was like,
okay, lunatic-esque.
- Yeah, I guess, all right.
- I'm gonna give her a three.
- Yeah.
- I really like that the unfortunate connection is a link.
- Three and a half for the unfortunate connection.
- Oh, we'll get there, okay, all right.
So we'll just keep going then.
Yeah.
This guy's name is Jet Lag.
OK.
So describe this guy's style.
OK, so Jet Lag is wearing a onesie.
He has a--
Onesie?
This one is totally Patrick Vibes.
This is Patrick Vibes.
I was-- I'm glad you guys said it, not me.
It's the college rule that I'm mistaking for--
or that I'm mixing up the lines.
So he's wearing a cardigan.
And he has a-- what looks to be either a saxophone
or some kind of like clarinet thing?
- Maybe that is a didgeridoo.
- Or a didgeridoo.
- And his name is Jetlag
because it takes a long time to go to Australia.
- Oh, so he also has a side swipe haircut
that covers one of-- - Kind of emo style.
- But, so you're thinking from the nose up,
you're like, this guy's totally emo.
But what should peek out right underneath that line
but a smile?
So how can he be emo if he's smiling?
- Emo smile.
- This drawing is so funny to me.
- This is an amazing drawing.
I'm gonna say that this guy's ability is--
- Is music.
- Shut up.
His ability's not music.
- Okay.
- This guy's ability is so clear to me.
He's an empath.
- Okay.
- He has pure empathy ability.
He can empathize with anything.
- Well you can do that through music.
- But the rule is, he can empathize with anything
with blood, so he can't empathize with a rock
or a stick or a tree.
but he can empathize with a frog or a bird or a bee.
- That's a beautiful ability.
- That is beautiful.
- And it rhymed.
- And I yield my guess because that one is so good.
- That is a good guess.
- Yeah, bees have blood.
- And you thought Tyler Fishfingers was a little eccentric.
- I did.
- Jet here is both an aspiring aviator and a jazz musician.
- I really wish--
- So I was right about the jazz, so one point for me.
- What?
How does one expect to balance
two completely different professions at the same time?
I guess Jet has his ways.
People tend to comment on his neck,
which you guys did not comment on at all.
- No.
- He has a big ass neck.
- He does have a big, kind of Mike Tyson style neck.
- Yeah.
- Plus, Jett has written a mathematical formula
to determine how nice someone is
based on how their hair is styled.
Tyler Fishfinger's initially registered as pure evil.
- So that is scary.
- Little lore tidbit.
That's kind of like a FromSoft hidden in item description.
- Yeah, that's kind of sweet.
- That is kind of like a--
- I'm gonna give him a four and a half.
- Yeah, that is kind of like an empathy thing though.
- That's true.
- I guess he can sense somebody's emotion.
- So I'm so good.
I've been pretty close on all of this.
I would say that this guy--
- I'm starting to think maybe Tyler the Awesome
is a pen name for somebody in this room.
(laughing)
- That would be so crazy.
- I actually stumbled upon Caleb's old blog.
(laughing)
- Old, six months old.
I think that this is definitely my favorite one so far.
I really like the design of it.
I think that he, like, the last two were just a little,
like, kinda normal looking.
He definitely, this is a unique shadow.
This guy has a nice silhouette that you can recognize instantly.
A new foe has appeared, I'm saying, oh, it's Jetlag.
- I was gonna say, like, the last two were like,
Amy from Sonic, you know?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- But this one--
- At least Amy has the hammer, though.
- May be more of a Tails.
- Mm. - Yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause of the long tail shape of the saxophone.
- All right, show us the next guy.
- Okay, next person is Estelle Knight.
(whistles)
- Wow. - Go ahead, Caleb.
- Caleb, that is a child's eye.
- Take it away. - Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Okay. - Talk about her.
- So she has a freckly face.
- It looks like she's part animal.
- And her legs go all the way up to her waist.
And she has a mullet.
That is so beautiful.
She looks like she has glasses or eyebrows.
I would take either one.
Her hands are completely wide open.
- And her thumbs are on the back of her wrist.
- This is definitely, you're seeing now,
this guy definitely takes his hand models
from Total Drama Island.
- Yeah, this guy's a big Total Drama Island fan.
- That's clear, because those hands are stolen
right from their design bible.
And I would say also--
- Which Caleb has read.
- Which I have a copy of.
- Which he reads it often.
- I have a copy of it.
- That show was so sexual.
- That show, that was one show where I feel like,
I don't even know what it was,
but that show, I couldn't stand it.
Like I feel like I was--
- I hated that too.
- It was like right after my time or something.
- But yeah, people talk about wanting to fuck
that goth girl all the time.
- I wanted to have sex with every single girl in the world.
These, this girl is very, very buxom.
Not as buxom as the other one.
But she has lipstick, so she's a little more into
being presentable.
- And a dog-like nose.
- I would like to say--
- And dog-like hair, too.
- So I would say that Estelle Knight's ability
is probably either lovemaking or style,
because her dressing ability is really,
she looks great, she looks really great.
- And I'm gonna guess that she is maybe part dog.
- Why are you, and I'll say there's no way
that she's part animal because I'd be able to tell
because she is very pretty.
- And I will also say, I know we said about these,
tag yourself in, hey guys.
- This is you AF. - This is you?
- And I'm gonna give her a five out of five.
- Estelle is legendary for her athletic abilities.
- I can tell, she is toned.
- But isn't overly bright.
She'll believe just about anything you tell her.
- It's perfect. - Example,
if you pretend to throw a ball,
Estelle will rush out to catch it,
and when she doesn't see it,
she'll search the ground trying to find it.
When she eventually learns of the ruse,
she immediately forgets about it and moves on.
Estelle is comparable to a golden retriever.
- No way!
Huh.
- Despite her lack of intelligence,
Estelle does have occasional moments of genius,
catching crazy schemes using whatever's nearby.
These schemes include rescuing a kitten from a tree
by bouncing on a trampoline to reach it,
and attempting to free dive with Cooper
by tying her legs to a rock.
Predictably, these schemes often end in near disaster.
- Okay, so I would like to get ahead of this and say,
I would like to get way, way ahead of this and say,
she is comparable to a golden retriever.
It says nowhere that she has retriever DNA.
Oh, oh, well, look at the comparisons here.
The hair, the dog-like nose.
Her personality.
They're all signs point to canine.
Why are you switching in like a British kind of accent?
All signs point to canine.
'Cause you're like trying to make a point,
you go British?
Yeah.
Okay, so here's the thing.
This is a good way to make a point.
She is beautiful.
She, if she's part dog, then I'll drop it down to a four,
but she's a five right now.
You're gonna drop it down on all fours.
She's part dog.
(laughing)
Is that what you said?
No.
(laughing)
She's part dog.
I'm gonna drop her.
I'll drop it off.
Rating.
I'm gonna drop her rating down to a four.
I'm gonna drop her down on all fours.
You're gonna drop yourself down on all fours.
Keep the peanut butter away from this kid.
Yeah, well.
Oh, cool, yeah.
Okay, white woman.
Yeah, what do you listen to?
Blink-182, you scumbag.
I do.
Oh.
Okay.
Crystal Cole Walker Pesquatch.
This is more of a Patrick vibe woman,
so this is not for me.
- Describe, it's, she's, do you have to?
- Okay, I guess I have to do everything.
She has the same legs-- - You do an excellent job.
- She has the same legs as Kermit the Frog.
She has an investigating glass,
whatever that's called.
- Magnifying glass. - A magnifier.
She has a crystal in the middle of her head.
- She has a vest. - She's based off
of the Star Fox crystal blue girl.
She is definitely a scientist 'cause she has a lab coat on.
and she's some kind of geologist, scientist person,
co-worker, pasquatch, she's also a Sasquatch.
- Yep, she's part Sasquatch and her parents are divorced.
- Yes, yeah.
- And she might be Native American.
- I think, no.
- All right, let's see what happens.
- I'm ready.
- This budding geologist is part Indian, as in from India,
and part Indian, as in Native American.
- Oh my God, this guy can smell dogs
Native Americans from a mile away.
Being of this unusual mix of races,
Crystal appears to be a lot wiser
than her age would suggest.
Unusual?
Maybe it has something to do with that gem in her forehead.
[Laughter]
Okay.
Crystal fills the gentle and mysterious quota
for my cast of original characters.
Often, Crystal overdoes it with the whole geologist thing,
being more interested in the sand
on the beach than actually playing on the beach.
Her braid is also a lot longer
longer than seen in the illustration. It reaches to just above her waist, actually.
Okay, one last. I will say that is crazy that he guessed Native American.
Yeah, that's pretty nuts. This guy is on a roll right now. Real quickly, a rating.
Three and a half. Probably like a four. I knew it. Just because I got
that thing. No, that's not what I thought. And not because I'm interested.
You're interested in her. Finally, here she is.
The one I bet you've all been waiting for a visual representation of. It's Boobs McKean.
- I'm gonna start drooling preemptively.
- Eleanor Slater.
- Oh!
- Oh my God.
She looks just like my childhood friend Nick's mom.
Almost exactly.
She has--
- His pants just moved.
- She has, number one.
- Nick's mom's hair.
- Nick's mom's face.
- Mixed moms dimensionality.
She has exposed ankles.
- Yeah.
- That's a boom, boom plus for me.
She has bent elbows.
Again, he was going in on these drawings.
- She has lumps on the elbows.
- She has lumps on her elbows that need to go.
- And she's got lumps in the front.
- So she has low self-esteem.
- She's got lumps in the front.
- Because of her elbow lumps.
She has beautiful hair that has a perfect right angle
built into it.
- She's wearing a collared shirt.
- And the best part is guys, her eyes are upside down.
(laughter)
We love her upside down eyes.
And this one does not, I won't let you guys guess
'cause there's no information about her.
No, no, we can guess.
I mean you can guess but there's your--
She's somebody's mom.
Nick's mom.
You're actually wrong.
I apologize if the illustration doesn't quite
live up to your expectations.
Of course, Elena Sokolov can't be too far behind.
Oh god, Sokolov.
Okay, so Elena Sokolov is probably a--
Elena Sokolov.
This is her--
We're in for trouble, aren't we?
- This is her alter ego.
- Yes.
- Oh God, so she's evil.
So now she has eyebrows, which is bad.
She has, wait, wait, those are exposed legs.
She's wearing a bikini bottom.
And she looks like--
- And she has some squares on her belt.
- And she has squares on her belt, which is kind of scary.
And she has a gun also.
- In this article, I could not,
there's no information at all about these characters,
but I was able to go through the blog
and find somewhere else.
- About Elena Sokolov?
- A bit of information about Elena Sokolov.
- Okay.
So this is, and this is in the Rouge's gallery,
the villains of Tyler Fishfinger's part one.
Yeah, that's what he wrote.
Darn near every villain in Tyler Fishfinger's history,
all in one convenient post for your convince.
Warning, major spoilers head.
Proceed with caution.
- I think we're like towards the end of the episode.
Right now, I don't want any fucking spoilers.
- There's gonna be major spoilers.
- There's major spoilers.
- You're gonna suffer through them.
- I have to suffer through spoilers.
- You have to suffer through them.
And I don't even give a fuck.
and i actually made one slide that's only spoilers for you mate
that i'm gonna show that they were going to take my headphones off and close my
eyes
uh... so here's a land a cycle of
occupation worker at a major company which that's a great job worker at a
major apparently apparent
evil spy working for a rogue nation known only as the syndicate
false name elinor slater
we go we'd knew about a little earlier on our slater
to gather intelligence regarding the u_s_ government former to get revenge on
in the cartooniverse.
- Oh God.
- And then there's one more part of this description
that is the best part here.
Ideal actor, Elizabeth Olsen.
I was considering Priyanka Chopra
before finding out she was Indian instead of Russian.
- Chopra.
Yeah, Elizabeth Olsen, she did strike me instantly.
- Okay, wait, wait, let's backtrack here
and let's cast the perfect cast.
Okay, so Elizabeth Olsen, obviously.
- We have some more slides.
- Who's here?
All right, let's go forward.
lightning round okay no no that's Timothee Chalamet okay yeah and then
that's Paul Rudd no that's Sharsha Ronan that's okay Sharsha Ronan that is Patrick
look if you're gonna say it it's Del Knight we're gonna go Zoe Kravitz oh
yeah perfect perfect also Zoe Kravitz in a dual role yeah well no this is this is
- Zoe Saldana?
- Oh, the other Zoe, Zoe Saldana.
And that's Zoe--
- And then we already, this is Elizabeth Olsen.
- Nick's mom.
- Or no, Elizabeth Olsen.
- Nick's mom, Zoe.
- All right, now let's keep going through the villains here.
Oh wait, that was the only villain.
(laughing)
I forgot to put in more villains.
But here's, he also writes some editorials
every once in a while.
And we're gonna go through those real quick.
Wednesday, November 11th, 2015.
Veterans, we salute you.
While you're at it, enjoy this early holiday treat.
You guys wanna see the holiday treat?
- Yeah.
- Turn on your video real quick and then you can see it.
- Turn on your video real quick and then you can turn it off,
but check out this holiday treat, it's a comic.
- It's a, wow, Santa meets broccoli alien overlord.
And the broccoli and him at the same time say,
gasp, he does exist.
- And that's a present for the veterans.
- That one is just for the veterans,
that fulfills some kind of GI bill requirement.
- Because the green, green--
- Well it's also veteran colored,
it's red, white, and green.
- Green vegetable. - And brown.
Yeah, green GI.
Green a broccoli.
All right, yeah, you're done.
My thoughts on Gene Wilder's passing.
He's off to a land of pure imagination, i.e. heaven.
(laughing)
That was also, this one, this looks like it's a,
this was in the middle of a really long thing
about like his like video game idea,
and then there was just one heading in the middle.
It was just that, and then it kept going after
with more video game stuff.
And then I think that this next thing is the last thing.
Okay.
I'd like to just read to you guys in its entirety.
Friday, September 11th, 2015.
Wow. Does this have to do with September Palooski?
Never not remember. My two cents on 14 years ago.
Okay. I'm ready.
My two cents.
Not never forget.
Never not remember.
Yeah.
Now I'm just going to read this through for you guys.
I started writing this post over a week in advance so I'd have plenty of time to finish it.
This proved to be a little too much time in fact, meaning I had to wait for a week to publish it.
This topic is somewhat out of the norm of this blog, for today I shall provide my insight onto what happened on this very day exactly 14 years ago.
Let's start with the initial effects.
First of all, what really grinds my gears about all this is that there were kids on those planes.
Kids! Why? Why did those meanies have to take them away from us so soon?
They had their whole lives ahead of them. They could have had class. They could have been contenders. They could have-
Alright, that's enough.
Other effects included several TV shows being pulled from the airwaves and rapidly rewritten,
along with flights being diverted to Canada, leaving dozens, if not hundreds, of angry and confused travelers getting delayed for weeks.
As if that weren't enough, we also created a brand new stereotype, or took it to new extremes if it already existed.
"Practically the day before, most of the Middle Easterns who lived in our country were on friendly terms with their fellow citizens.
But less than 24 hours later, their former pals suddenly screamed 'terrorist' and 'run away',
leaving the poor fellows to scratch their scalps, wondering what the heck happened."
That's true.
"Okay, I think that settles the bad. Now the good."
Good!
"Countless heroes were made that day.
Some were even unmade within an hour or so of their creation,
giving their lives for the sake of strangers.
touching. Unmade. Furthermore, if it hadn't happened, we wouldn't have...
That's what that means.
Yeah, he's like, "The heroes died. It was cool."
Great.
That's what heroes have to do.
A lot of heroes died that day.
That's one of the good things. Furthermore, if it hadn't happened, we wouldn't have gone all out
on airport security, which probably would have left the terrorists, only the real ones, not
those affected by the stereotype, free to do something...
Which he still calls terrorists.
Yeah. Free to do something even worse.
Look, I'm not a stereotypical terrorist.
I'd rather not think about what might have happened.
- Yeah, I'm a...
I don't do all that bombing and hijacking planes and stuff.
- I make really bad food.
- Yeah, I make poisoned food.
- I make really, really, not even poisoned.
I just make really, really bad food.
- Look, I cook everything sous vide.
- Yeah.
- And I don't get a sear on it.
- No, no, no.
- By far, the best thing that came out of this
is that the entire USA banded together
in their desperate time of need.
The Star Spangled Banner became a symbol of hope and freedom
and patriotism surged through the country
like an awesome simile would surge through my mind
if I could only think of one.
We regathered our strength, rebuilt,
and honored those we lost.
- That is like some spanned out ballet shit.
- If these attacks,
these attacks may have been designed to weaken us
by crippling our economy and security,
but they ultimately did nothing of the sort.
If anything, they only made us stronger.
Think about that the next time you have to take your shoes
off at the airport.
- I don't have to take my shoes off at the airport.
TSA pre-check.
- Holla!
- And that's all, that's the whole thing.
- Oh my God, dude.
Well, I mean, not only is he an amazing,
he's kind of like, I'm trying to think of any other figures
like that who kind of perfectly have one foot in fiction
and one foot in journalism.
- For sure, for sure. - Walt Disney.
- Walt Disney was a journalist?
- Oh wait, no, James Patterson.
- Oh, James Patterson.
- Or Tom Clancy.
- James Patterson, he does the non-fiction,
but then he also does Maximum Ride.
- Yeah.
- Now that's an amazing book series about angels.
- What was that other guy?
the base, he wrote all the sports--
- Baseball?
- Sports books. - Baseball.
- That's gonna fuckin' bother me.
- Babe Ruth.
- Bill Simmons.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Julio, can you pull up that picture?
- Yeah, real quick, we gotta leave it with this.
We have a picture to show you.
- Oh, yeah.
- So, this picture, actually, no commentary needed, I think.
I think we'll just end on this, right?
- Yeah, just pull this picture up.
- Yeah, if we can, it's taking quite a long time, actually.
- Yeah, to open the picture. - It's pretty embarrassing.
- Should've had it ready.
- Yeah, you should've had it, okay.
So here it comes.
- All right, so it's still not working.
- Mike Lupica.
Mike Lupica. - Ah, there it is.
- There it is.
(laughing)
That's me when I see a Mike Lupica book in the library.
- So that's for you guys.
You can keep that. - Me when I see the bird seed.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Screenshot this. - I'd like to see
a bunch of these. - Wait, yeah, wait, wait.
Screenshot this.
This is our new thing that we're doing.
This is the meme contest.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Photoshop battle.
Whoever comes up with the best meme with this photo, if you send it in to us...
We'll send you 50 bucks.
(laughter)
Alright, bye.
(laughing)