*music*
*beep*
Fuck, I gotta call somebody, what am I supposed to do?
Am I supposed to do something with this? Do I buy something? Do I invest it?
Am I supposed to have a bank account? What is this?
Fuck. Hold on.
Hello? Yeah, I need a guy. I need a money guy.
[Police radio chatter]
Yeah, I don't know what to do. Let's send somebody over.
I need a money guy.
Okay, welcome everybody to the High Rollers, I guess, money symposium.
Sympatico.
Sympatico. Everything's Sympatico today. Some people couldn't be there. The people who couldn't
can get their paper up. This is more of a high rollers episode. This is about
money. This is about money. This is a so about money. There was a cash way in
yeah. There is an ante
to put all your money on a scale. Yeah, and unfortunately we have some
feather weights in the circle. Yep, we'll not be in the circle long. My gold
bars, your gold bars. Yeah, I keep all my money in the heaviest form.
what you're supposed to do yeah yeah, I usually I buy expensive rocks. I buy
rocks rocks that look cool. I
in my yard, that's how I keep most of my money.
No today we have with us. We have peers. Hello, everybody knows and then we also
have money expert Rex with us today. Hey, how's it going all the way from Los
Angeles? Yeah, wow big money capital, big money capital of the world. You have to
the mic closer to you. He's has kind of like a he's kind of has like an amateur
devil may care attitude. I'm rich bitch. Yeah, we're trying to train him because
they don't have enough money. Yeah, we're trying to train him to become a
professional podcast. This is a give and take kind of relationship where we learn
about money and he learns about how to speak into a microphone. Yeah, yeah,
surprisingly difficult.
We're going to get him to be the new like there's going to be like clips of
Rex on YouTube shorts and it's going to be him. So like if you don't take out
thirty thousand dollars in PPP loans this year,
kill yourself. Yeah, I think Rex could be the next Theo Vaughn where people are
doing Instagram reels of him that are five seconds long. Yeah, that are not
even jokes or stories where it is. Yeah, people just like him enough that they
want to see him say half of us. It's every day on instagram. What's your
what's your number one claim to fame money wise
probably a million dollars for me.
It's got my number one. Clam to fame is my million dollar bill that I have yeah,
yeah, then then it goes then six hundreds in a in a rubber band yeah and
forty five fifties in a paper clip, a two dollar bill, you know, frame and a
trash bag of pennies that you got to hold on to them. You never know if
they're going to go in a frame behind my bedroom behind my bed. I got an old
jansport under my bed with five or six nickels in it. There used to be a lady
at my old job who would come in and she would give you a two dollar bill. If
you're working the register and she dressed completely in blue, whoa, all
blue outfit, all blue everything color. Yeah, I would have to think of did it
way to be green. Well, there's those new blue Benjamins, blue, blue, blue face
on it.
Why is that funny? It's just funny
there's blue face hunnits of little face hunnits. I get money. We get money
dot
you remember the apprentice theme song? No, I never watched the apprentice.
Yeah, I was
the theme song. Yeah, almighty dollar. Yeah, brother, can you spare a dime?
I feel like that would be a
theme song for a show with about people with little money. Yeah, I guess it is.
That was, you know what it would be a good reality show. Yeah, good reality
show. It's broke ass bitches on Trump's payroll. That's right. It's broke as
Dick Riders. It was. It was like people like Gary Busey and like Joan Rivers.
Yeah. And Ivy Supersonic. Who's that? Oh yes. The inventor of Scrat. Scrat. Mrs. Scrat.
She was on season one or something. She was and she was weird on it I think. Yeah, she was talking
about how she invented Scrat the whole time, right? Did she already invent Scrat at that point?
She had, well, Ice Age came out in 2001. So. She invented it probably back in 1970-ish.
yeah, she had been to scrat way back in the day. Yeah, I think we've
researched this heavily. Oh, I got the spiking chair, but you know what would
be great is like a show like that theme song should be a show about how you
become an homeless,
then becoming a millionaire. Yeah, you do a bunch of games, okay, yeah, theme
song about a showed about being homeless and then becoming a millionaire go.
Can you spare a dime, brother? Can you spare a dime? Blue face hunnit, little
face hunnit.
it
here will be mine. I will be like this yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
TV,
TV television show yeah, you need to see that was the first of the first guy who
came up with the idea of a theme song was like no it's a it's a song that
tells you you're watching TV, so it's going to be about TV yeah yeah. Oh baby,
when you walk like that, you make my money go
flat. My money grow fat. My money grow flat. Yeah, as you run going broke
trying to pay for you. Yeah, and when it's you walk like that you walk away.
Yeah, okay. Money fits. Oh yeah. Who's wants us to wants to start in detail
their money fit. Let's see what let's see what I'm rocking here. Okay, show
it off. Describe it from
I can't even let me see it made in Hackensack, New Jersey. I can read that.
I think it's a Zelios, maybe which Zell money is money. Zell Zell is money. I
form of money.
So this is a suit that a man died in wow and then I got my golfing hat on
because I'd love to go on the green golf is money. Golf is money. I love to go
on the green, which a green I'm wearing. I'm wearing a black button down to show
that I still am a goth millionaire. Okay,
we got the we got the run until that homeboy Antoine Dodson deep pop shirt
that's been a little bit bleached basic like tastefully tastefully bleached all
across the board. We've got
Van Housen suit separates
on the
separate
We got the wobble sleeves. We got the wobble sleeves custom tailored.
Custom tailored for the Assassin's Creed blade.
You look like the two other kids trying to sneak into the movie got scared and ran away.
I look like I got left out to dry outside the Regal Essex Crossing.
You should have like a pillow under your shirt.
I should have a pooch. Basically I got the coffee stain new balances.
These are from my first day at Sotheby's.
Nice.
and I got the rag and bone jeans with the with the Amazon cargo belt, the loop,
the loopless cargo belt or the what is it called? What's it call where you put
this the silver spring into the what's this piece called? What are the holes
called that this goes into? I think it's just a belt loop. I have a hole. No,
the belt loop is a hole, the whole yeah, the whole yeah. This is a whole
list. This
infinite holes or hole is
braided belt, braided belt,
and we got the hands and we got the hands briefs. We got the hands briefs
with the wobble elastic,
the tailored hands,
the whole thing because I got what do you think a fit is you're an idiot and
then we got we got the
imperial, the imperial per a vita Costa Rica brand lager hat. Can I pull up my
jeans real quick? Sorry one more yep. Oh shit, the carabiner Swiss Army Swiss
Tommy came on a backpack. We got the we got the hardware store key key addons
male key handcuff key for any kinds of comedy that we might be doing Glock safe
key for my Glock safe.
You still have that I give it to my dad. Okay, probably for the best. Okay, all
right. I just want to throw in one last detail. Damn the camo crocs. Yep, so you
you know where you can't even see where I'm going. I bet if you hold that
next to a crocodile's body,
you can't tell your next step. Yeah, I can not see you're gliding like you're
in Gary's mod. I looked on I'm like does Patrick have hooves what's going on
down there and I got normal jeans on well double fronts. Yeah, all right,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
chill, all right, all right, listen guys. I have the spirit Halloween jersey,
Okay, this is talk about exclusive a store open literally one day a year,
one day a year to get this okay. That's money. I got the like that. I got the
case for watch, which is so rare. You won't even probably find it on Google.
The time on here is wrong. I'm and it's not because I don't know about daylight
savings or how to change. You're not saving money. It's because I'm grinding
and I'm up an hour earlier and I call that the money hour when I get up an
an hour earlier at nine AM instead of ten AM and I have the daylight savings
time more like money savings, dying money, spending dime.
I got the these these black jeans, old as black jeans, vintage, family heirloom
black. Look, there's a hole, there's a hole right there on your on your
vintage. You're lucky stars one. That's how you tell them into yeah. I mean
these have been worn by generations of my money as family. They've been sitting
the chairs and standing up over and over for decades and decades and it's going
to put some holes, but you know that boy ass old old uncle got shot with a
twenty two there for for getting hands with the mayor's daughter
and then I got I got the hokas, the Plasto, New Hampshire, shoe barn,
hokas,
helped out by the friendly yup, the shoe barn. You ever been to the shoe barn in
Plasto? You know every time I'm in Plasto, I'm hitting up the shoe barn.
he sized my shoe. He said he said my left foot's bigger than my right foot. He
sized your shoe. He sized my foot. He sized your shoe to your foot. He
customly tailored this shoe to my foot. Wow! I asked him, do you have anything
this color? He said, yeah, we got that.
Just kidding. He said, no, we don't got that. I got to send away for a custom
order and I have the black socks. I mean the white socks with the black letters.
He doesn't even know the color of his socks. He's so yeah, I don't even
fucking care and your chair rolled away. I saved it for you and the custom and
look at the wheels on this chair, the custom wheels on the chair, the
roller blade wheels, so I can roll around while I'm sitting down, so I
don't get bored. And you know we got some bloody blonde hairs in those,
you know, you'd be bringing a hose over. And this is the spiker chair,
where if you sit on it, it fucks your butt. Yeah.
Which you can't see, but it's completely true. Everyone who sits in this
chair gets a happy ending. Yeah, Caleb set up that chair incorrectly. He put
in spikes instead of screws, and when I sit down, you're gonna see me grimace.
blue shell ass chair. Okay, Rex, what do you have?
Let's see, I got...
Oh.
There's unlabeled, black label. Damn. Priceless, one of a kind. Look at the
inseam, look at... What is that like... The way it's stitched on there with
those little... They look like tiny jewels.
Oh my God. Oh my God, I think those are diamonds. Those are diamonds.
Damn, the crusty dimals. Wow. Dimal. Dimal. $10,000 suit. I got
scenes with I love those pants low key. Actually, they are pretty actually no
bit. No, those are dark souls as
damn man and we call those and we call those ribbets green like a frog, just
like money, just like these shoes. He's like a money frog. That's a
green on green
green on green on green green on green on brown on blue. That's on a log in the
pond. Yeah,
that's a that's a dollar on a frog on a log green dollar on a green frog on a
brown log and a blue pond on the green earth. Oh, and if it's a blue face
hunted, that's blue on green on green on brown on blue on a frog on a front and
the whole thing is frogs all the way down frogs. I don't okay t shirt you got
on. This is my bring him young young virginity club. Okay, whoever sin
sexually sins against their own body and that's like ironic. No, it's serious.
That's how you've made your millions. It's all about courting the right
demographic.
Semen retention. Yeah, that's one you're losing every day. You can sell that
$200 a load. And tell us about that wig you're wearing.
Save money on haircuts. Yeah, that's right. And I'm a white samurai. That's
fucking right. And you don't have to- Show us that ponytail, Juan. Yeah, show
us that.
Oh my God, you know a lot of expensive food
caviar caviar, no caveat, no caviar, no caviar.
Yep,
I'll be getting that sloppy top. I be I've been living on a yacht. Oh yeah,
yeah, I don't have a house. I got a boat
and if I did have a house, it have a moat. Oh yeah, I would be in my moat
yeah when it comes to get money on the money goat and I'm like a frog the way
that I am toad and float
and I float
my money float
damn my money. I'm like Danny Green,
I'm like money, green
money, green, yeah, the white Danny Brown money, green money, green,
get your money up, get your money, that same haircut that he had in twenty
twelve. Oh yeah, what is the most money that you guys spent in the past few
days? The most money that I spent was probably five hundred dollars. Get my
cat neutered,
yeah, and of his bloodline. I spent five hundred to end his blood.
You know what's the biggest actually before you even go on at the talk about
way yeah genocide, my cats,
five bones, five bones, that's so
yeah he he even plastic surgery yeah damn and that's a major flex to because
your cat. You know that cat wasn't getting any to begin with. No, it's like
yeah, that can't even smell when other cats are in heat. That's how fucking
bogus his game is that cat. He licks he was licking his cone.
that's called he was licking his cone and he would like try to lick his penis
through the cone. So he'd bend over and like be licking his penis tip through
the me through that cone lick me through the cone. You want to hear a joke? I
probably maybe I even told this joke in the podcast, but I'm going to tell it
again. All right, I don't know if I came up with this joke because it came to me
in a dream, so it could have been like I dreamt about a joke that already heard
all right. Yeah, what are the dog that was getting head from a cat say
I don't know what rough
it's a really tight. It's a really good joke dog and cats that sand papery
tongue of the cat. It actually leads to a sharp teeth, sharp teeth. Well,
that's not well sharp, in which case the dog would go yeah, but you could say
like barb barb yeah, what I'll be about is cat penis yeah yeah, that's have
barbed penises, cats have barbed. Oh that's if they're sixty nine in the dog
says both rough and barb yeah
like say barb dog say barb sometimes if you feed them soda yeah that's true.
Yeah, because the urban nation makes what is it? What are the soda addicted
dogs say when he was sixty nine a cat barb barb and rough and rough yeah and
and the cat. What did the cat say? Maybe like me now now oh yeah yeah, the cat
said I'm coming yeah, so yeah, I'm going to come. I'm going to come. I'm going to
fucking come. Let's say the whole joke now. Okay, no, I think we I think we
failed it yeah. I think well, let's say let's say it because we were
workshopping it now. Let's just say it as it is. What did the soda addicted dog
say when he was sixty nine with the cat and then what the cat say rough,
you want to
said
I'm coming right me right me yeah per oh yeah. What are the talking I'm coming
right now and I only come one time per
year per year day or year day yeah dm per diem yeah, but the most money I spent
was shipping those fucking shirts. So you Canadian idiots, it's so cost so
much money and the lady at the post office got mad at me for doing it yeah,
so we're never shipping to Canada again. So if you guys are from Canada and you
didn't order something this time you're fucked you're done you unless we hire a
company to do it for us not happening. I will I'm not letting the other company
do anything with Canada. Canada is a poor country. You drive down your Montreal
ass to New Hampshire. You will have to meet me in Pittsburgh, New Hampshire on a
ski do. I will sell you the shirt there. Everyone in Pittsburgh gets around on
ski dues. They barely have cars. You know what you just may remember and I
think it's because of snow. Yeah. Did you guys see the news story? I saw this at
the gym on the TV, the new story that like an eight year old kid, he got lost
in the woods. Oh yeah. And he survived for two days by eating snow.
Yeah, and he slept in a wheelbarrow under a tarp or something. Yeah. He
just wandered away from home and didn't come back. That doesn't count,
right? To say you can't... You survive by eating snow. That's just drinking
water. That's just water. Yeah. He didn't survive anything. He was gone
for only two days. That was cool. He was young. He's dead now. Yeah.
That is cool that he had the wherewithal to think that snow is food.
Everyone in the comments is just like, "Disc is a survivor." No, no, no, no.
he was an eight year old kid and he's like I'm so hungry. I guess I'll eat
what's a whatever's on the ground under my feet right now. Yellows yeah, if it
hadn't been snowy, he would have been eating the dirt. He would be yeah or kid
was hungry and he was putting shit in his mouth yeah yeah, putting what I
thought that was his mother yeah. Oh my God, that's tragic.
He built a new mommy and daddy out of snow, damn snow mommy and snow daddy
yeah, that's how they found him yeah.
Oh
yeah, what's your no? I was just mimicking Cameron. I feel like well
let's talk about your let's talk about you spent. Let's talk about you guys.
I spend what I did money wise.
I fucking custom ordered stickers, embroidery patches. Oh, I went to Long
Island to buy a hundred dollars worth of laser discs so that I can resell them.
Okay, but yeah, I've been basically wasting a lot of money on art. Yeah,
that's Bala. That's a money move. That is art. I don't know if you ever heard of
guys like Picasso, Renoir,
Campbell's, the Campbell's Soup guy, Cos, David
or Jeff Koons. Jeff, all of these,
completely amazing artists. These guys, they spent money
and now people are still reaping the benefits
of what is essentially
colors on a piece of paper yeah worth worth. Exactly you look at the cost of
the materials, probably about a cent and in back then when Picasso was coming up
paper was everywhere. That was before that they figured out about the
rainforest having troubles and stuff for they figured out that you can just go to
the store like an office depot or something and just buy reams and reams
of yeah people. People used to have trees. People used to grow trees in their
houses like flowers. It was there was trees everywhere before, right yeah,
they could write their grocery list. They would pick a piece of paper off the
tree. Yeah room he was to build their houses around a tree and the tree would
grow in the middle of their living room. I bet back then when they invented
disgusting, I bet paper when they invented paper people acted about paper
like people act about phones. Now they're like the kids are always
looking at their paper. They're always on their paper. It's a fucking fad,
yeah, a fucking fad yeah, they're all walking around on their scrolls.
I'm going to get hit by oxen. I'm going to stick with sand yeah they're out
playing old school. I like sand. I like drawing in the same. You know there
was some just in timber like as who said papyrus, let's make it cleaner,
just paper
yeah papyrus
and you know, you may be a
Egyptian nerd that was like a papyrus. No paper paper paper
you talk about a multi but trillion dollar industry paper paper done the
Mifflin paper is the very thing that money done done done Mifflin. This is
Pam Dundee. I just send you
funds, get your funds up funds, get your funds up
Mifflin
Mifflin Mifflin I'm sniffing in more while in
but more Rifkin Meg Griffin, Meg Griffin, yeah, keep going, keep going
Meg Griffin, her she was drawn on paper. I thought she was the villain
yeah yeah, do we Griffin, but it was the chicken,
but it was a giant chicken,
giant chicken fight watching that shit all night.
Peter Griffin and the chicken, you know it's on site
Yeah, this is what millionaires do. This is what meetings are like.
You got to put that microphone up to your mouth.
See, we have mics that travel more than six inches because you need to relax in your chair.
Anytime you're sitting up, you're losing money.
But look at this.
It's a kind of weakness to be sitting up.
See, so you can kind of get one of these lean back and really comfortably have a
spike up your lower back and then maybe a hard plastic chair back on the back of
your head that feels like a matrix port. I feel so bad for you. I feel like I can hear your organs
hissing because they got popped. And you can see that the microphone is resting on
my face. You can see it completely moving while I talk. Yeah, I can see the metal part
bouncing up and down off your sternum. Exerting exactly enough force on my
chin to maybe give me some kind of jaw pain migraine in a few minutes. This looks like a metal
little bug is feeding you. I would if this was my life and this was a
feeding
you're like your your mouth clit stimulated by
yeah. Do you guys think that we'll have feeding tubes in our daily lives?
Yeah, within the next time I'm sure I hope so a feeding tube full of
soylent
every day, so I like a fiend in it. They're going to be fetishists for
people who like to their food. People are going to be like
no, but is it because it do you think because of maybe misophonia people? I
feel like a lot of fake, fake
scarings like that or what do you call that when you don't like something
scary? That's not a phobia, though, or yeah, it is I'm flying away. It's a
misophonia. Is a phobia never spent his money? Oh yeah. What money did you spend?
I sent the lowest possible offer on a guy on grailed for these shoes. Wow, wow
wait, but you still got it. Oh yeah, he wait. Why wouldn't he take the highest
possible offer. No, no, I'm saying I said I spent the low it like the reserve. Oh
you're speaking a very advanced language.
Sorry, I'm so used to speaking about deals. You know you just got to send
you got to start low and then you go high. It's called anchoring right right
yeah yeah. What I like to do is anger in yeah.
If you don't give me the shoes for one fucking cent, I'm going to kill your
family, because you're an idiot yeah, because and also you're stupid. I'm
kill your idiot family that that attacks them from both sides. That's a pincer
maneuver where they're either either they're the type of person who okay,
there's two types of people okay. There's the type of there's no there's
the type of there to
you're thinking of types of crabs and scorpions. The first of person is the
person who says the person who says the person who says you can fuck with me.
All you want you say whatever you want about me, but don't you dare fuck with
my family and friends, you're going to get there's the other type of person who
says I'm a lone wolf. I don't give a fuck about my family, but if you think I'm
dumb, I'll
throw it out yeah exactly. So you get them from both sides. You say I'm going
to kill your family, you and you're stupid yeah, I'm you're a weird. I'm
going to make you and your family watch while I kill them simultaneously in a
pincer maneuver yeah well or in a more efficient way. Actually do the pincer
maneuvers. You say both you and your family are stupid
and I'm going to be there.
I'm going to psychically drive you into killing each other through my messages.
Yeah, I read this thing eBay people. I'm saying there's like a shirt that
they're selling for $40 that has a stain on it and they say you are a robber
and I'm coming to call the police on you. I'm going to kill you. I read this.
That's my offer. Yeah, that's my I don't even want the shirt. No, it's
not. I've made an offer and I've typed in next to the dollar sign. It says
you are a bastard. What I do. I don't go on grilled. I scroll through
for everything I make an offer and I put in zero dollars and I put I put on the
Texas. I don't want it.
I don't want it anymore. I don't need it. I'll pay for shipping, but I'm not
paying for
if you want to give it away. I'll take it, but I'll probably throw it away. If
you give it to me, I don't really have anything to do with it. Yeah, I read
this new story when I was a kid that I'm pretty sure it's probably not true, but
maybe it is maybe Julio knows, but it was about I guess the cartel kidnapped
some people on a bus and they made them all fight to the death against each
other. Whoa, that's still is that true? I hope you think that that could really
happen. That's real yeah. I hope it's real. Well, a bunch of people I think
we're dying and dead. Is that more humane? Is that real? Can you give me a
nod? That's real you'd okay? Wow, he was there. He was there. You were there. He
was this lone survivor. Oh my God, you were the champion.
If that kind of stuff is happening because we outlawed like cock fights and
bull baiting. I yeah like we should bring
yeah there were the cartel are walking around there like kicking cans. We're
like what we do
we're not allowed to fight dogs that we're not allowed to put dogs fighting
against each other. Any more summer ever and I'm too I'm bored of selling drugs.
We sold so many drugs already. I'm bored of doing drugs, selling drugs. Yeah,
have you guys okay? So do you guys know what a bulldog is like? Yeah, like okay,
you know what bull baiting is? I'd so yeah, bull baiting and there's just like
do almost identical paintings, but they've been painted like thirty years
apart of like a bull attacking four different dogs at once, and there's
always a dog just flinging eight feet in the air. I guess that was a normal
thing to see.
We did an episode, it was like weird ways to get free food in London,
and I think bull baiting was one of the things. I'd never heard of it before.
Yeah, but... Well, you know in medieval times they did bear baiting. Right. It
was bears, they would have dogs fight bears. They would have a bear try to
like a pole and they would have like they'd let like ten. They just keep
letting dogs out. They'd see how many dogs it took to kill a bear tying a bear
to a pole seems like way more entertaining than like okay. Now that we
tied up, I guess let's make it die. Yeah, we'll play tether ball around it.
Yeah nowadays, it's all chatter baiting and and they're tying women to poles
yeah, they're tying women. Women are tying their financial security to poles
to Polish people. Yes, Polish people who single handedly fund most strip
clubs right
because you go you go because do you know do you know why it's because
Polish people that in their wallets they only carry one dollar bills,
because they don't understand what a twenty is they look at and they're
like two dollars
and then they see a five dollar, but they're like s.
What is this
is the same for some money they see a ten and they're just like wow yeah, a
hundred
I didn't they say they're like. I thought they didn't have a hundred
dollar bills. The most money I've ever seen yeah Polish people walk into a
strip club and they try to hang their flag up on the strip
and they try to change the light bulb yeah, yeah, because it's dark in there,
because it's a damn strip club. Yeah, yeah, that's what no that's why they
flock. There's the one place they know they're never going to have to change a
light bulb right. The lights stay off because they got led strips, you know,
and someone's stripping all the wires that must have changed stripping that
must have changed Poland forever.
Oh, you strip clubs, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
too much. Y'all care too much. I just learned that I've been saying wrong.
It's sorry. I don't even know what it's his favorite. It's his favorite beer.
It's a beer that's so bad, but it's $2 and it's what color is it? Brown amber.
Yeah, that's the beer color. Yeah, that is the main color of the order that
looks like syrup. Okay, here's what we're going to do. Now. We're halfway
we're going to transition into Rex's money mode. We're going money mode and
we're going this is as part of the high rollers money green talk green chat,
the green initiative, the green initiative,
the green win initiative. We're going to be doing a money Q and a a panel about
money to make money out of save money, spend money, use money, what its purpose
is,
how much things cost, how to use money, the shape without spending it, the
color, money for goods or services, smell, what is a good, what even is so
first off, what is a good? Probably something that's nice. Yeah, yeah,
exactly, and a service,
probably anything that's bad. Okay, so money can be used for goods and
services, yeah, and bads, and bads, yeah, goods and bads, goods and bads.
There's goods and bads of money, right? Yeah, so yeah, I guess my first
question is that I would like to ask is what is the number one easiest way to
make $1,000,000 instantly with zero time spent or any effort at all?
Probably robbing someone with $1,000,000. Okay, so have you how many how many
successful robberies have you pulled off in the $1,000,000 ballpark and what was
your method? Did you what what's the use case and did you use a case to take the
the money. What kind of receptacle did you or was it digital was it a
or was it digital
yeah kind of an eye bag yeah. Did you make someone buy something scamming baby
milk,
baby milk, skin that's the scam, the baby milk, skin, a baby milk, here's I
almost got scam. He almost fell victim to it almost yeah. I don't know what
that is. It's a scam where they ask you to buy baby milk yeah and then it's the
craziest scam. They come up to you. They say I need to buy baby milk and they
make you go into a store and you go in and they're like and actually I don't
well. No, they know they ring you up for the baby milk and it's like a
hundred dollars and it's not a real thing and then everyone in the store is
like you're doing that you're so nice for doing this. You should do this all
group hug. It's a fully like it's a it's a it's a Truman show scam yeah yeah
yeah scamming is very funny because you make someone buy something. I think that
is so so funny yeah, okay, so wait what have you have you are you speaking from
experience with robberies or have you just sort of seen them from a train
car?
Yeah, no, you go to you to the bank, easiest place to get money. That's
where they keep all the money right second easiest place you go to
Manhattan and you just start walking inside pretend like you walk into a
building right with an outfit. It's basically like a Swiss army knife of an
outfit, yeah, where you can do anything yeah, yeah, a suit jacket with a
janitor outfit underneath perfect.
just say you got to clean up the vault, a mop and a briefcase. So depending on
which side you're being looked at from, because then you're looking you're
walking past the front desk right. The people from outside they look in, they
say, oh that's just a janitor, so I won't even register him in my mind.
The people from inside yeah, the people from inside look and they say, oh
that's a high roller. I should bring him further into the building. Would you
recommend like a windex container that has like a label that I made called
money wash money,
and it's blue Gatorade. It's blue Gatorade in the windex bottle, so when
you take it off,
you drink it in front of the CEO and he's like whoa, he must be made of well.
No, that's what you do. If you get caught, you drink it really fast and
they go oh he's dead anyway. Yeah, we won't even bother catching him. Yeah,
whatever, whatever ammonia in his blood, people are chasing you and you're like
wait,
okay, I'm going to keep running around yeah, yeah, I'm done for you don't need
don't chase me anymore. I'm done. I just drank all this money wash
money watch and then you have to make a fake Google pay a screenshot on your
phone where you go. You say hey Siri is money watch dangerous to drink and you
hold it up and it says this person will die and all their money will teleport
back into the vault. Excellent yeah yeah that's not so hard that's yeah, so
that's a good strategy. That's strategy number one. You could yeah, you could
sort of David Blaine the coins in yours in your small bowel. Oh yeah, it's a
sarcophagus. You could eat all of the coins yeah and then just regurgitate
the coin, and if someone catches you, you could be like oh, I'm eating coins. I
thought this was corn. Yeah, they were my bad. I guess I'm not supposed to eat.
They were small and yellow yeah like a corn, gold, bullion.
So yeah, so to recap you walk into basically any building in Manhattan or a
bank. I guess we didn't talk about how to rob a bank, but it can't be that
hard. I know literally all you do is you say I'm going to have the money and
they have to give it to you because of insurance reasons for the life of a
human being, because if you say you're going to have it, that's yeah, that's
what that's you should say. I'm going to have it instead of give me the money.
You say I'm going to have the money and then they're like oh well, there's
nothing we can do. It's a brain hack where their brain skips over even
thinking about how you're going to get the money. It's basically it's something
called verbal hypnosis, which is a millionaire tactic that you are now
getting very poor yeah
and I am taking your money. Your wallet is getting light
your
yeah hypnotized the money, but anyway geodes yes or no precious rocks or
investment poor okay or investment yeah and for your investment into geodes,
yes
and physically inside of the geo inside the hollow cavity right to clarify yeah
inject it with a siren, little crystal in there. That's thousands of dollars.
Wow, wow, every just have to get thousands of dollars. That was the first
money right. You just basically crack open, you owed. Unfortunately, I think
the first money was human beings really, and we were traded by maybe an entity.
Yeah, in a company, a company, a company. Yeah, well, honestly, well, capital
exactly wow that is the world capital earth earth, damn blue planet and and the
green planet, the moon is the biggest place on earth, yep,
you can take vacation there
well, I feel like I'm learning so much already to be honest, yeah, okay, so moon
just switch up a few to the moon there and we have money that's a that's
actually true. If you add two letters and remove one moon becomes money,
and here's how I would deal that situation. You say, subtract one letter,
add to I say, add one letter and change one letter. Wow, you can always say
I basically, you know it and you know and you know, I would, you know, you
know how I would say how I would I would what I would do is I would say
take the take the word moon, apply our proprietary formula and then it's money
hide the entire process. Nobody knows what you're doing. You can sell it for
trillions of dollars. What you're doing basically is breaking it down and
reconstituting it into a little cheese, like a cocoon, a cheese it cocoon. Yeah,
but moon craters equator planet earth green and equators equals to all money.
Yeah, well, the great equator and I equate money with pleasure. Yeah, and
pleasure things. Should we be spending our like the our disposable income or
pleasure money? What should we be buying onions, onions, onions, things that go
bad? You need those immediately. Oh right, because the most powerful or
valuable asset I've heard this is time. It's a time equals money right our time.
Honestly, I would say time equals money times two or plus one hundred or
something that's more, but having spoiling produce around you that like
It's basically like having the exact same time. Let's get to the list.
You also make money. Exactly. That's also you can you go out, you hustle,
you're selling that on the subway, on the sidewalk, at the bank, at the
library, wherever you're allowed to sell stuff or wherever you're not
allowed to sell stuff. You tell people you got to buy this onion today
because tomorrow it's going to be basically nothing but smell. Let's get
a list of and it's also illegal to buy an onion tomorrow. That's true. Every
single disposable, every single item that will go bad tomorrow.
So check this out, I mean Pavlov, he was doing all this stuff with clocks and
stimulus and the ringing of the bell and that's associated with positivity.
And you know all these money makers, they're always like,
the church bell is ringing, that means I have to go make more money because of
the time that is in the ticking clock and it's all in the ears.
But you want a smell-based clock.
Basically you wanna have things that ripen and go bad at different hours of
every day. >> Because of the smell of money.
Exactly the smell of money and also like the hormones of that the
biological clock of that. Yeah, the cloud clock,
the clouds of that, the smell of the rain, cloud bread and it's raining money,
cloud bread, disposable cloud bread, disposable. Speaking of disposable,
can I actually share a tip really quick that I've found to be very helpful in
my financial life? Yeah. So if you see this that I'm drinking here,
it's a it's the bottle is Gatorade frost thirst quencher. What flavor in fact
this will
glacier cherry, it's hard to read yeah, it's clear, but what is actually in
here it's water. Okay, and do you know and do you know what the reason behind
this is? Yes, so I know what you're thinking. I know you can make a guess
did you're going to be wrong Gatorade in there long enough that the water and
the and the particulate matter that forms the Gatorade flavor settled at the
the bottom and then you synthesized a Gatorade syrup sold that for a profit
and then kept the water in the bottle.
No, okay, Pierce, no
the overhead on that is absurd.
You are an idiot, so much on Gatorade, dear God,
bottles and then that is even worse than the stupid thing. I wanted you to
say, which was that maybe I was doing this to save money on Gatorade bottles,
then I have to buy a water bottle or a gatorade bottle. That guess is also
stupid. You know what the real reason you reuse a bottle like this is okay
think about what happens to this bottle. You throw it in the recycling, okay, it
go yeah, it goes to a plant, it gets processed. This is all happening. It's
churning up the plastic that's costing money okay, and what you're thinking
you're thinking, but that's not money my money. I threw that in the bin. That is
your money. That's tax dollars yeah. Every time you are recycling a gatorade
bottle, your taxes are going up, right up, up, up, up, skyrocketing. You know
what? Also, and I know you didn't think about this, the illusion of wealth that
comes with, with water in the Gatorade bottle, the illusion of wealth when
people see the Gatorade bottle where they're like, "He must have, he can
afford the Gatorade, he must have a fucking fortune." Yeah, exactly. "He must
have so much money." It's true, but anyway, the point I wanna make is taxes
are very, 'cause you know, this fucking government, people at our, at our wealth
bracket, we're getting taxed about ninety nine percent on our income and
are on our assets and that last one percent is a squeeze. That one
Gatorade bottle can be the difference between zero and one percent wow yeah.
I guess throwing away your Gatorade bottle is just like you have the money
yeah, you have it, you take it yeah, you're garbage man, you get paid. I'm
tired of holding this. You have it. I don't have a room in my house. I can
just put all these in my hand is tired. Yeah, that's what a why that's why
most people have mansions. You keep the trash, you keep you put the trash man
out of business, the money that would get paid to the trash man that circulates
that trickles up the trickle up economic effect. I find these to be very valuable
because of their toilet like nature
in what way because they hold a liquid. The slot is big enough for for most
distribution methods of urine and shit. Yeah, I think it's just big enough for a
have you ever pooped in a Gatorade bottle? No, but I think you could if you had to
you could because you get all the P that comes out when you when you poop yeah,
so you have one in the back yeah, and then you could get rid of the what
we're looking at here is an initially burst of poo remove all plumbing in
your home, replace it with only Gatorade.
You still need to send them. Oh, you just put the cap on sorry. That's not
stinky now averted
no, you put the cap on oh the back yard, throw it in the throat and someone
else's back yard yeah yeah yeah, I don't have a back yard. Oh wait, there is no
someone else's back yard where I live, because I own the entire world, but the
problem here, the problem here is your neighbor finds a Gatorade bottle in his
back yard full of human shit and he thinks oh my God, oh my God Gatorade is
putting poo
you short Gatorade. Yeah, you short Gatorade you buy well, the Gatorade
I rock is shorted you buy it hostile take over you buy you completely take over
then you release a public statement that says that says Gatorade will no longer
use poop yeah in our production. You know what else you would have you stock
up you go. I rock it store you go next door to your neighbor. Your neighbor is
like you hear neighbor freaking out you go next door. You say you hear them
freaking out that you go what what what's going on
you don't even ring the you you you go up and you knock on the door and you
what's happening, what's going on? What is putting they're putting poop in
Gatorade bottles? You tell that neighbor you say I
will I will pay for the lawyer. You and I have a connect. Yeah, you sue
Gator. While this is happening, you are also shorting the stock. So now you've
won a lawsuit against Gatorade, but also you are Gatorade and if you're worried
about any type of insider trading or SEC regulations that might get you in trouble
you're suing them and also tell them shorting the stock poop to one trick.
You can use is just have a secret identity like spider man yep, where you
can be spider man when you're suing them, try wearing a costume, where a
costume with a bright color that covers your face. You change your you change
your name, you get two identities, dual citizenship, when you say like my
grandma's Irish or something, so then you get like the Irish citizenship stuff
and then you say your name is spider man McNally.
So you have a secret identity like spider man yeah, which I mean you don't
have to say Spider Man. You could say you could say Iron Man. How many
identities do you have? How many are you a card carrier for maybe five or
six different people? Because I imagine that's imagine you do this all the
time with the Gatorade. Of course, yeah, you have to run scams like that.
Oh yeah, yeah, I have like you have a list of scams that you that we can do.
Can you list a few of your names of your identities if you can
one just one one initials?
I'm sorry, I can't talk about it. Okay, then here's another here's another
understand. I understand I understand I bet I bet this guy's in a lawsuit where
he's the judge, he's the jury. I mean this guy has so many different
he's the
probably he has to go into the he has to go into the court one by one is
different people. I keep locking the door and looping back around. I actually
have to go to the bathroom, all right, call a recess, okay, and then yeah, the
the mirrors whispering into each other. It's him the he's all he's. Okay, I
have another question. I recently heard I was told that this year it is the and
this is, I believe true, the fiftieth anniversary of hip hop. Whoa, for real,
how is this going to affect money?
That's going to affect money in big ways because it's it's you know a lot of
I mean hip hop has changed. Let me just say that you can say that again. Hip hop
changed hip hop has changed. Why is it that
it's a funny on turn my funny on okay? Well, I'm not trying to be funny. I'm
just trying to say hip hop turn my serious on or that's not serious. No
turn my serious
maybe that's the change of it. Maybe yes hip hop has changed.
There we go.
So it's changed in a way. It used to be about breakdancing b-boying used to be
about all that stuff now. It's about hose and money money, which is good.
It's changed for the better. It's changed into jewelry about it. Change
change change jingling change jingling
jingling jingle bells, jingle bells, richest man on earth jingle bells,
jingle bells, Santa Claus, richest man on earth. He has toys and other stuff
and a billion dollars. So net worth net worth as we're and net work
and trillion dollar
but gazillion dollar
and
Christmas colors, red and green yeah, your money's red while his money is in
the green. God damn the north pole green is way different than being in the
black and we already so much money that your your financial situation becomes
the color rudolph's red Grinch's green
related nest egg, I are a
IRA Roth Philip Roth, the author yeah not related to him, not Mr. Nut run run
new rock, Mr. Not
Rex, does anybody know who Mr.
Is Mr. Not ever going to share
he's a hard man to get in contact. What the fuck is the deal with Mr. Nut
everyone in the money community is hearing about this guy and nobody has
ever met him. I'm fucking who is a mister nut. Mr nuts is there's new money
to be made and I'm like wait. No, there's he says he says that nut bucks
are coming out.
It's a new crypto. Do we trust him? No. Do you guys believe that nut bucks are
going to drop in the next year? He's been right about everything so far,
but this is this is this is him pulling the marbles out of his ass. I don't
believe it at all. You think he's done? You think he's all washed up like
Thanks. Mr. Mr. Nut is washed. Wow, we are in the we are in the black
eyed peas era of Mr. Nut. I'm not sure if I want you to be
saying that on our podcast. I don't fucking care.
Mr. Nut, call out. Mr. Nut, call out, go. Mr. Nut, get the camera
on me right now. Mr. Nut, hi, hi, hi, Mr. Nut. Oh, I forgot you
lost a lot of money in the Nuts. Yeah, I lost probably 50K in
nut books
probably
coming out soon.
I don't even know where the fuck I you went to nut dot com. I think I put you
uploaded
and I uploaded just two pictures of my credit cards. Fuck dude, you got nutted.
You got nutted up in yeah damn. I got nutted up in and guess what it hurts to
sit
because your wallet is so skinny, your wallet is basically giving you a
credit card.
And it's swiping your ass crack. Yeah, I used to, my butt is so used to the
fat stack in my wallet, making me sit like this, sit like a Habsburg,
but now look at me.
Yeah, sitting normal. It used to be like this, 'cause my... 'Cause here,
let me do a quick analysis here on you. You do that pose. Okay.
So what I'm seeing here, do you see this? Do you see this shoulder? Now you see this shoulder
is right shoulder, left shoulder lower than the right shoulder. Let's draw a line from
this left shoulder. Let's go up to the right shoulder. You see the line in your head? Yep.
Make it red. Right. Now you see the stripes on his suit? Yep. Now add some horizontal
stripes like a grid. You see that red line against that grid? Yeah. What are you seeing?
Stock price going from the left in this position from left to right down and then it's going
up down. If it was going from left to right, I was going down profit. No
well profit for nut, not profit, not profit, instead of net profit. Yeah
that's probably why he calls them nut bugs.
It's supposed to be net books. I think it's going to be net succession based
cringe,
realistic or virginistic. Let's throw this realistic, realistic, really
Everyone is that stupid.
Do you have a bunch of family members like that who are doing things like that to you?
Yes.
I have a bunch of family members like that but it's not about like finances.
It's mostly about like when like who's going to take over.
Right when are you coming to visit home?
Yeah when are you coming to visit home?
What do you want for dinner?
And I'm like you fucking fuck what?
Do you guys think that Mr. Coyne...
You fucking fucked hard.
Get out of my face.
Do you guys think that Mr. Coyne is based off of Mr. Nut in succession?
Oh absolutely.
Yeah.
something like strong. I did get I did. I thought it was that was one part. I did
think was a little cringe, even though even through the realism is like we
lived through the Mr. Nut stuff and we lived through the election and all this
shit and it's like and you're just gonna pretend. I don't want to relive it.
Yeah, like that. Some of us don't think it's a joke and I get that it's
supposed to be some kind of by also. Yeah, when you have this little fucking
little stream. I don't think that I also don't think that Bobby would be so
concerned about Mr. Nutt. This little ass Roman Roy string bean
mother fucker saying all those fuck wits who put money in Mr. Nutt.
Yeah, it's like it's not. I'm watching TV, I'm throwing the remote at the
screen. Yeah. Because I'm like he's talking about me. That's why I have a
Wiimote cord on my remote. Yeah. It's for when I watch HBO.
I throw my remote at the TV. I put it on when I
launch HBO Max and go, and I put it on. Yeah. And then I turn
on PBS Sprout, I take that shit off.
- 'Cause I know that they're gonna say something
that is so biting.
- Yeah.
- And so satirical.
- Gonna have me biting.
- Yeah, it's gonna have me biting my bottom lip.
And I'm like,
- Biting my wife out of anger.
(laughing)
- Taking all my anger by biting my wife.
- The show makes me so upset.
It's like when a dog just bites another dog next to it,
even though you're the one who's messing with the dog.
Is that kind of what you're explaining?
And is there a way to make money off of that action?
(laughing)
- Stuff a bite in?
Is there a way to make money off of biting?
Of course.
Can you detail it a little bit?
Sure, you got professional eating.
Oh yeah.
Got food tester.
Joey Chestnut.
Like a king.
What is your dream job?
Food tester or video game tester?
Probably both at the same time.
Wow.
Yeah, I can walk and chew gum at the same time.
I can't.
What happened?
I just can't.
But you can do other things at the same time.
Yeah.
I can poop and pee at the same time.
I can't help but do that. Yeah. Is there a way to make money off of that? Like
the surplus? There is a way to make money off of poop and pee. We've
already talked about Gatorade. That's what I'm saying. Oh yeah. Yeah, well...
What about a dog? There is a Korean guy that tried to give people money
for their poop and pee. Is that true? Yeah. Well, they have fecal transplants
too. They take children's poo and they... Oh, they spread to change your gut
biome. They up your butt. That's what it's for? Yeah, your gut biome. Changing
the gut biome? Yeah. What did you think? You thought it was just to put
I was up there. I thought it was for people who can't make poop. You
thought they put poop into them, so they put poop into them to
normalcy. So yeah, it's like a place. It's like an elective. It's an
elective surgery that puts poop in. No, it's like it's like the atmospheric
processors and aliens. Yeah, what's going on with the with the inserting
now? Is there a way to a child's poop into your mouth to change your mouth
bio? Yes, but most doctors won't do that and your insurance probably won't
pay for it, but I know that none of us here are rocking with health insurance.
Nope. We don't need to so not need that. We can afford the hospital visits once a
week for swallowing a kernel of popcorn and being scared of popcorn tree is
going to grow in your tummy. Yep, or when you laugh while you're eating like
or when you laugh while you're eating, you laugh while you're eating a piece of
celery. I have laughing disease. You laugh while you're eating a piece of
celery and you accidentally swallow the whole celery or when I'm walking down
the street and I think of something from my past and I start laughing and I
quickly run into the closest hospital and I say I think I got drugged yeah. I
think somebody rubbed LSD on my ankle on a cut that I have on my ankle because my
shoes are too small. I think someone put stitched LSD into the middle of my
jacket, the inside lining yeah and that's why I'm having memories. I think
I'm getting an acid flash back getting an acid flash back because I cracked my
back bending over to get the fucking the band aid on my ankle. I'm looking
this book said I had memories to look back on and I knew I was having an
ass. I'm looking I'm looking at the I'm looking at the bookmark that I have in
the middle of my copy of Siddhartha that I've been reading for twelve years at
this point. I'm twenty pages in and I'm looking at it and I'm turning it back
and forth and there's pictures a picture of tree frogs on it, but when I
turn it one way, I would turn it one way their legs are like this and I turn it
the other way their legs move a little bit and I'm calling the doctor and I'm
saying I got fucking drug. There's something in the water. People are
going to take me out. They know that I'm making a hundred dollars a day. Yeah, I
accidentally eat like just the end of like an edible that's only five
milligrams and I'm sitting there and I'm just like
yeah
and I'm calling my doctor on the phone. I'm like
so what do you mean you accidentally ate you were just hungry for what you
thought was a normal treat? Yeah, yeah right and where did my roommates
edible?
and he fucking got me yeah and it's my yeah. I need him to call. I'm sucking on
I'm sucking on a ballpoint pen because I like it. Oh, and you get inky mouth and I
got inky mouth and it's loads on my face and I call a doctor and I go in for a
consultation and I say, well, this affects my future ability to grow a
beard yeah right and I'm thirty five years.
I'm on the phone with my doctor and I'm so loopy and fucked up from all the
drugs after eating the ballpoint pen. I'm just only saying my inky stinky. Oh,
I fall out of the shower and my shark tooth necklace gets caught on the
curtain
and I call the doctor and say that I have a shark bite.
But we can afford all this. We can afford to call the doctor for all this
because we make money every day. I'm going into the doctor. I'm walking into
the emergency room. I'm cutting in front of everybody. I'm pretending that I
have a sinus infection and that's why I'm in the emergency room and then I
get into the room. I
go in and I say I want a peg leg.
but we have the money to do all this because we made a podcast where we read
the list and then we and here's the list. It's too much overhead on a list.
Yeah, a list cost too much sometimes you can't find a list. So then you make
up a whole episode about getting money. How much money do you have?
Probably $300 million. Yeah, holy shit. And that's right. I'm bringing your
different identities or is that just you as you have that money? Yeah, that's
just me. My other identities. You don't even want to know. I do want to know
is five probably like five seven dollars, seven from each of the different
yeah yeah my each of my identities has only five dollars, but I have a
hundred trillion identities.
That's actually really
isn't that hard. You just make yeah,
they just keep referring each other to
with one dollar and that should just go interest. That's what I'm talking about
yeah, I'm interested. I'm in making money. Is it a feasible money making
strategy to open a bank account, put in one penny and let it sit for a
hundred trillion billion years? Yes, of course, I'm going to invent a time
machine. You put 60 cents future on like people are picking up money tips from
fry. Yeah, yeah, he said shut up and take my money. That's the title of his
book. It's so interesting to go from fry character like fry to a character
like Rick Sanchez, because Rick seems to
think about how they're both. I mean they're sci fi protagonists in cartoons
right here, right, when you may be compare on money motivated and non sex
motivated. Rick is
that guy's in a whole different bag. He's in like he's not human. He's in a
green portal fluid more so than green bag yeah and emotionality right he's in
his feelings, but and drinking like he's basically into all fluid all the time.
I mean we talk about we talk about we talk about liquidity. Yes, Rick
Sanchez is talking about portal fluid and alcohol and there's a little bit of
green spittle on his lip on his lip. Fry is lip all the time. Fry what is a fry
French French fry potato solid frozen solid French French put all of your
money in French Franks, French Franks, the money fire kind of money that I
don't think they use any more. Find a type of money called a French Frank
find put or I think it was France that uses Franks, Francs. I think maybe
they used to a long time ago. Are they on the Euro now? They're on the
Euro. Okay, I hate to break it. What are your thoughts on this Euro
situation?
what the hell is going on over there? What the hell is going on?
I go, I'm saying Euro, right? The Bodega guy is saying Gyro, I say
Euro. He's saying Gyro. And he says Spider Man, I say you know.
But I'm saying Euro, he's saying Gyro, I'm saying Euro, and then I don't
know, should I just go to a Greek place? Should I not get a
euro at the bodega. Lamb is fine at the bodega. Lamb is fine at the bodega,
but should I just get it over rice like a normal person?
Listen, you got to make that decision yourself. Rice. That's a staple Asian
culture. Asian going up. That's money right now. Greece, poor. Are we looking
at a Chinese century? Gyro, of course. Okay. But gyros, that's a poor country.
Imagine a Chinese euro.
Wait, I think you just had a million dollar idea. Oh my God, think about
this. You use a scallion pancake to wrap around char siu pork.
This is actually a really good idea. I wish I had a big check to give you
right now. Yeah. So what you gotta do right now is you gotta make everybody
who is sitting at this table and everybody who is listening to this
this episode right now, you better print out an NDA
non disclose. Do not share this food idea until you're able to secure the
you tube thing. It's a zip everybody comment down below and I hear to the N
D a new restaurant. There's going to be a new restaurant, be a new restaurant
what with Chinese gyros? Oh my God, good, you're a
gyros right wow and it's going to be called gyros gyros yeah gyro dreams of
Chinese food
and that's the name of the restaurant yeah wow okay. So what is a bank account
and how does it work one savage song
okay,
yep
and that's the end of the any closing or any closing questions, any closing
kind of last wrap everything up last remarks about money. Any you know what
actually you know what let's let's leave maybe our listeners, let's leave our
listeners with some money advice you want to give what's your number one
piece of advice for anyone who's listening who's a poor fucking piece of
shit string bean is three inches tall yeah who goes on youtube all day eating
the italian job and drinking mustard. We were all there. We all got the italian
job. We all got the italian job at the seven eleven on harvard avenue. We all
ate. We all spent eight dollars every day on a food called salt chicken. We've
all done it. These people they're rationing monster hydro so that it lasts
for four days.
They're watering it down like hand soap in the bathroom. What do you say to
these pathetic fucking mongrels? Don't walk, run to the bank, take all your
money out, hide it under your bed,
go back to the bank, start a new bank account. Just get into the habit of
hiding money instead of making your bed every morning. Basically... Like a
squirrel with a missed a nut, missed the nut, take all of your dollars, take
all of your dollars, sew them together into a big money blanket.
Money is made out of cloth and then set it on fire because the future is
PayPal.
The future is PayPal,
and we just want to thank Rex for being here. Rex, you are on a show
called Beers We Drank. I am, which is also part of Podcast about which is
part of it. Well, I don't know that I call it part of it. Really, I say
but maybe the pod has not as patreon the family. Yeah, I guess I'm not even sure
the red maybe would call it like the mentally disabled stepchild who we don't
want to hang out with at thanksgiving
and here's you have a show on the fur on the second second of june. If you're in
brooklyn come to my screening on the second of come to come to check out and
where can they buy a ticket on your twitter or instagram page on my twitter
there will be a link in the bio.
Great.
Alright.
Please go see this show.
I went to LA to see it.
It is so good.
Get your green up.
Get your blue face hunnids.
Blue face hunnids.
Green face money.
I do.
No you don't.
You ruined my point.
You ruined my point because you wanted to be.
No, no I didn't have a point.
That wasn't the point I was trying to make.
You are honestly, you belong in a high school debate team.
That's like the level of annoying you are.
You do do some debate stuff.
Yeah, you do have that kind of talking.
You told me I was wrong, so I told you I was right.
No.
See, that's a high school debate team.
Yeah, I'm telling it like it is.
And I have to be the moderator every single time.
Here's the point I was trying to make.
I always have to be the moderator.
Here's what you do.
Here's the point I was trying to make.
I don't even get to debate.
Before you were obtuse.
Yeah.
is that if it was the 1800s and you had no porn,
who among us wouldn't start just randomly killing women and eating their breasts
and their asses?
You see what I was trying to get at? It is a good point.
Because if you didn't have, yeah. Who's to say? I don't know.
I don't know if I would have ripped.
Can I honestly tell you that the reason I wanted to argue with you so much is
because of those glasses. It's making me mad to look at you.
well you have a bud light hat on so
he does not have a bud light hat on, he has a mexico hat on
oh it's the color
it kinda looks like bud light
if we're keeping it real right now
still
he got mad at me for my new hat that i'm wearing
this hat pisses me off. he called me a poser but i just want to point out for a whole
year
he wore a frog skateboards beanie
I thought it was from a...
You have never won...
I have a skateboard right over there.
Wait, wait, no.
Let's break this down.
Hold on.
Frog...
What did you just say?
Frog skateboards.
Frog skateboards beanie.
I don't skateboard, but I like frogs and I wear beanies.
So how's that mean being a poser?
Two out of three.
This is a golfing hat.
Yeah.
I like hats.
I don't golf.
50% is more.
What?
I don't golf and I do like old English fonts.
is on here. You don't golf. That's 52%. That's 52. You don't golf. You know what? How about
right now? I have, I have a skateboard right over there. I have a skateboard right over
there. We're going to turn the camera and we're going to see if you can ollie right now.
Fuck you man. I'll do this right now. All right. No, he's doing the camera. No, no,
You have to point the camera at you.
Yeah, so Caleb is getting the skateboard.
He's standing next to it.
Okay, put one foot onto it.
He's bending down as if he's winded.
He looks like he's going to throw up maybe.
His hands are just above his knees.
Okay, second foot on.
He's wobbling a lot.
He's really wobbling.
He looks like a snow angel.
He's got a beautiful stance.
He has fallen off the skateboard without trying to do a trick.
I'm just narrating here. No, no, no, no. Okay. So he's still st... he's doing again a star
type pose. All right. I don't know really. Okay. So he's getting back on. Okay. He's
almost destroyed our printer. You should move that. Fix the printer. Fix the printer before
The printer completely almost fell over.
We almost lost the printer.
The printer I just spent $100 on.
Yeah, we almost just lost the printer.
Can you imagine how far I'm going to get?
Caleb did the most 11 year old Ollie.
He's adding qualifications now.
You didn't say what age level I had to do it at.
I'm not saying.
I'd like to see you read at an 11 year old level.
I'm saying you did it.
you did it. I know but you had to add all these qualifiers to make me feel obtuse. I didn't
make you feel obtuse.