that's my clap. Okay, that's my clap. Y'all that's his clap. Y'all welcome
back to another episode.
Yay podcast about list. This is a big one today. This is exciting. Guess what
Caleb is getting. Phelib has failed again. Phelib shit is in the mountains
and he's I guess of shite. I think he's get like getting a diamond or something
or he's like getting he's going up to look for a diamond, some kind of rare
gem in the mountain, thinking of a dwarf he's going there to oh right he's going
to look for gold and he's trying to find a dwarf's mountain castle hobbit. I
don't know what he's doing up there, but what he's doing is an affront to God and
his stuff and let's just say the desolation of small has begun yeah right
uh-huh yeah, he's going up there. We have beautiful and replacing him today
replacing philip. We have go, which is the opposite of ailing go fish
mother fuck.
Pretty cool, it's kind of like I'm kind of working on some catchphrase. Have you
ever been on by yourself? I don't remember. I think that you you've been on
one for I was on by myself before you were on it. That's right in Boston.
Yeah, when the dark wow
the dark thirty one just makes you reminisce doesn't know yeah, just
remembering things. I know that that was a good
we're having fun. I went upstairs to Caleb's apartment and we did it in his
room. Oh yeah, because you guys lived in the same building. I just remember
there's a few times you've been on this show. You've only been on here with
Alex, but I remember the one time Caleb wasn't here and we were doing karaoke to
start the episode off and it was me and Cameron in the living room singing and
then you had to come out and yell at us. I did not yell, but I was you to
reprimand us yeah. I mean, I think important for yell important detail is
that it was at my apartment at like our apartment and in that in the morning at
noon and I was probably closer to noon. I was mid work call and you were in
back when I worked
and I think that it was so your work didn't appreciate new divide by one
park. We were it was. I think I came out on one Republic and he said you have to
go to your bedroom. I think it's a rude. I think it was probably the second or
third karaoke song of the day yeah. I was like I'm going to push this
I'm going to push this. I mean yeah it's on the it's on an episode. You can hear
it. There's one. Can you hear me in it? I think you can hear you kind of saying
like quiet.
That's exactly what you said was come on guys, and then I said, Can you just take
the call on your balcony?
Yeah, I mean I probably could have it doesn't matter. It's not like I well
hindsight is twenty twenty. Come on guys. It always hurts the most. I know
because I see I tried to ruined an amazing episode.
I'm sure that listeners love just like a straight karaoke track streamed into
the thing. Yeah, when we didn't even have a set up yet where you could like pipe
the music and do it, we didn't even. You just started off the app with a couple
songs. Yeah, you can barely hear the song. That's a good way to start off an
episode of anything is music. That's why TV episodes starts with the theme song.
Yeah, and this show has a theme song.
That's true. Did it play? It must have. Or is this the cold? Are we setting up
like hold open. Oh no, it plays right now
pretty excited. It's not going to play. That's a good idea. You don't get to
control when it plays. Okay, maybe if it played like right now, no, no, no, no,
don't you can't do that, because that's that'll be hell for dubio to edit. Yeah,
that's difficult to yeah and look he's already pissed off right now. You can see
him on the screen. I can't
he looks crazy. He looks so mad. Look at him. No he's Julio. Can you put the
Jameson right now. No he's not going to do it. He's not going to edit it. No
don't not it to him. He's not you're not doing it. Yes, there don't put it
yes, no, I feel like thanos when he got the infinity stones
pretty sick.
Okay, so here's something we were just talking about yeah. Basically, if we all
faked our deaths and ended the podcast completely yeah and it was over and then
we started a new one. Yeah, you think your dad
that no way.
To be part of it, I go Juliet. I kill myself yeah for real, as you love us too
much, you're fooled
fully. Yeah,
think about that, but then what would the next one be called? Because let's be
honest. Also, if I'm faking my death, I'm starting another podcast immediately.
That's how they're going to catch me. Yeah, if I get sent into witness
protection, I will not be able to stay away from you. Just couldn't help
so you're in your glasses, a snowball, I can be like Hey everybody
checking in here. My name is so for some reason they made me change my name from
Cameron Fetter to John Smith. The craziest thing happened today. I got put
into a witness protection because I never believe a mafia related murder
yeah and guess what the guy who was killed by
Scarducci family Johnny Scarducci killed my friend
it's a ten hour log of all the crimes and look I even have a clip. It's just
the video. The guy just murdering like yeah, but here's my new address for
real, though, if I was in witness protection and I saw somebody I knew I
would not be able to not nod to them. Yeah, I would do that. I would do the
eyebrow
no, no, no,
you
you take off the glasses that they're like making you were just going like
yeah,
don't tell anybody it's like someone that you like you went to there in high
school for like one year. At the same time, yeah, it's the one who's very
loosely take a picture, yeah, someone who would not would have even they
wouldn't have recognized you. Yes, I want to talk like a history class in
college. Yeah,
my God,
it's
I'm playing a game that the FBI just told me I'm playing a game. I'm playing a
game where I buy a new character. Do you know Johnny's Cartucci
just sitting on the bus and seeing someone you know get on and just not
saying anything, but just like we're like
just looking
are the tap ending up, like yeah, all right, you caught me. It's me yeah
tapping the old lady sitting next to me be like. I know someone on this
my friends on the bus. I can't say hello to them, but I know I can say hello to
them because I witnessed a murder and they put me on witness protection, but
my real name is Cameron and I live at this street and
yeah I would be hanging out in the laundromat and I just be talking to
and be like yeah. I can't say hello to a lot of the people I know any more, but I
can't tell you why I try to drive around my old town all the time and I just
look at people.
Look, this nose is fake
look play wait wait. Okay, they do this say I got your nose and then actually
take my nose.
Just yeah, I would be a no. I would do you think they give you a whole new
style yeah they have to like a close yeah they bring a tan France from yeah
is yeah. You just look super you can tell someone's in witness protection
because they're wearing really cool. There were nobo yeah French,
short sleeve pattern t shirt
yeah they're all in like just decked out and just mall clothes. It's you to
see it, but you keep noticing somebody people wearing the exact same out like
different. It's just a bunch of like really fat, crazy looking Italian guys
with like the like
they all like a veto really tight like yeah short, just wearing like like
like a reading, avocado toast,
you know, then I started talking to my my dad. Seriously,
I realize a lot of the fucking underlying problems
they're all wearing. They're wearing like like fucking like Hollister and
it like like those old like the shit that people were in like two thousand and
eight. Those Hollister shirts with like the felt letters. Yeah, that'd be so
sick to see one of those big Italian guys in that shit. Yeah, I guess that if
basically if if you have to get your style made over, yeah, witness
protection, which I think that seems like maybe it would happen in my mind.
It's usually hair dye glasses or removal of glasses, beard, beard or no beard.
yeah removal of teeth yeah. Oh my God, adding a beard to a lady who
protection that would work actually ingenious, but I feel like
the stylist that you hire has to be airtight yeah. It's probably someone
who's the tiniest, the tiniest misstep, I think could blow your entire cover. I
would have to imagine it's an FBI agent who just has an eye for those kinds of
things, you know, but like that's what I like. If it's like yeah, if it's like
a sixty year old, like like silver haired Italian guy and they put them in
Hollister yeah, I'm going to know right away. I
yeah, this guy's a fucking I should kill this guy, but here's the
that's what it is. Whenever you see a fucking hot topic old guy, you know when
you see like a guy who's like forty and he still has the nose piercing and the
and the band, the like the fucked up bangs and stuff that's what's that's what
happened. That's why you why they're like that. You want to kill that guy.
yeah. We need to kill the guy in the cure, because he's a fucking rat dude.
He's a fucking rat Robert Smith. Yeah, he looks crazy. He's got a fake name to
think about it. Robert Smith, no way that someone yeah, oh my God, yeah,
that is a one. We start with the name, you know what
something Smith, one of the first saw either one of their first albums has a
song called killing in a rab. Oh my God, what did he do? Yeah, that's the
or what did he see somebody? What did he see somebody do yeah and the whole song
is the whole song is a confession. Oh my God,
that is crazy than I thought all the way to the cure yeah speaking of it be
really sick to like be the witness protection stylist and you're just doing
like character creation on dudes and you're giving like you're giving them
like big like pink liberty spikes, but you just see it some like fat,
old guy. Yeah, you're putting like
you know what what we're going to do. We're going to make sure that you're
safe. We're going to send you down to Boca Raton. We're going to put your eyes
on the side of your head. Yeah, you're going to have a scar that goes
on the side of your face.
What we need to do we need to. This is the the amulet of Akatosh. Okay, I'm
going to put that around your neck. Okay, you're going to wear this at all
times. You're going to be moving in with a lady who looks like a cat.
yeah
yeah, and this is called skuma. You're going to be need to take a lot of this.
Wouldn't it be incredible ever? If you ever see someone you know, give them a
very loud fuss road.
You won't have to deal with it.
The extent of my my sky room yeah, that was good, but sure it was good yeah.
Oh, and the knee, the knee yeah, oh the arrow to the near to the name yeah. Oh
my God, oh yeah, buddy brings back the memories. Wouldn't it be incredible to
he's so dangerous. They had to disguise a guy to protect him from you yeah
that if you are so you're so evil and dangerous that they're like we have to
turn this. We have to change this guy's whole style up or you're going to
destroy him like I like the idea that it's just like they live in the same
town. It's just style
they can't afford to move. There's a serious budget. Yeah, we so a lot of
shit got fucked up at the FBI. Just yeah, they just comb his hair a
different way. We either
lower tier of witness protection. They either lose the agents who are like
doing serious, you know shit or they get rid of the guy who gives them all
hair. Well, this is a guy who like he snitched on someone who was doing
something that way like he saw somebody shoplifting magic, the gathering cards
and he was like I'll tell you who did it, but you need to put me into
witness protection.
Like Okay, I guess I do it out of the whole song and dance with them just to
like just to make him think that it's happening, but they're just like going
okay, they put them in a pod. When you come out, you're going to look
completely different. Yeah, you're going to you're going to be shorter.
You're going to have to wear these color contacts for the rest of your
life. What do you think they would be killed
if you ever take these color contacts? I'll be a white guy. I got a cat. I
got a contact. Also, you're going to be the greatest backpack wrapper of all
time. Yeah, Mr. Hobson, I think most celebrities might be in witness
protection yeah. I think that kind of counter that runs counter to
witness.
It's called riding in plain. You're a famous pop star
in the world. You came up on vine through seven second songs.
You are a guy who has the power to climb walls and swing on web
drop a spider in the room.
making a spider out of like a radioactive steel bag and just tossing it in.
Okay, so something will happen to you.
Yeah. Wow. But anyway, even the reason I brought this up is what would the name
of the next podcast be? Yeah. I kind of got sidetracked. I thought I said one
that Joe was on board with and it was motherfuckers in jeans. That's not bad,
I guess. You just have to commit to the jeans. But we can only talk about denim
and being a mother fucker. Yeah, talking about denim, just being like this is
called salvage mother fucker. The thing where you wear the denim into the ocean
after a year, that's yeah, you told me what if if you get like real nice denim
jeans, it's these if you get like a raw indigo jeans, like you wear jeans, you
wear them all year. Yeah, you like form them to your body and then at the end of
the year, you walk into the ocean. You can walk into the ocean. You can do it in
your bath. This isn't a thing, but why do you have to walk into the you have to
walk into the ocean? There's just some guys who go into the ocean.
This is the only way to cleanse what the best you
I mean you can sit in your best of bathtub, bathtub, but why would you even
want to get some wet in the first place? You get them wet, so that to wash them
yeah to wash them and then the die comes out and like you like distress it
yourself. What does it mean to be distressed? When you're feeling so bad. You gotta feel
so bad. There's this one dude, people would repost him on Twitter and his name was the
Swiss Jeans Freak. He was like an old Swiss guy who was obsessed with denim and he would
bathe and put his jeans in piss. He would soak them in piss so they would get a yellowish
tint to him. So they them in piss yeah, so that the when the fades happen. So
like there must be another you all liquid. He could have used yeah totally
to be yellow. I don't know. I just saw a yellow tent. I think if you if you look
up
you did that you touch the cameras out. Yeah, you can you look that up?
He I know what a jeans can you look up swiss jeans freak p. Oh there he is
be careful because it's YouTube effects of urine with denim.
Yeah, that's him. That's the Swiss jeans freak. Oh, what's going on there?
He has a lot of jeans. He is awesome, completely obsessed with a very tiny
picture of him. Yeah, I just remember somebody seeing somebody repost a photo
of him. I remember who did it, but it was them posting a photo of him with
jeans and P. If you like jeans so much, I feel like you're allowed to do that
something yeah P P on your jeans. If you like jeans, I think if you're like so
into it, you like rod and I would I would maybe counter that by saying I
think maybe you're it's more if you're into P, yeah, something like that, but
there did G,
but where does the peace day
what is the high caged when I was a kid? I saw something. I saw something on the
internet that was like all dudes like have a little drip of P on the end of
their
say it
right
all guys like finished, have a have a drip on the end of their what p
my
I didn't say it
when they like pull up their pants after they go to the toilet. You saw
I saw someone say like you googled. Do you guys have a
like a relay of my penis? Is this normal you are on yahoo answers? Yeah, what's
Can this happen to all guys? Yeah, what's this stuff
after I P? What's the stuff after I P that's all over me?
What is this stuff? What the hell is this crap? What's this stuff in my hands
after I P in my hand?
I think it's P. Yeah, my yeah, those those rod denim guys are crazy, raw
denim, the rod is rod denim. What does that mean like when you get jeans they
get treated and washed right. So it's like you jeans made out of what is
jeans is cotton. It's like inter woven and then died indigo. So every pair of
like you can get them raw, where that like if you sweat and then wipe your
hand on it, there will be like blue on. They don't like lock in the die. Yeah,
they don't lock in the die. So then you walk around to get completely undyed
jeans and they're just white. Yeah, really really you can yeah, probably
probably or really I think so is it look it up. Well, they wouldn't be jeans.
Yeah, well, they could be denim people wear black jeans yeah, but when you make
them
to denim, I don't know how it works. I don't know how it works. I just know
that raw denim is like the die. Raw denim guys don't wash their jeans for a
whole year. They get their booty stank all over it, and then they walk into the
fucking ocean sometimes or they pee on them,
and they're obsessed with getting the honeycombs, which is the like pattern on
the back of the the knee. So there's like a distress. It's like look how often I
move my leg in my rod denim. Oh talk about a crazy guy honeycomb, the little
guy, a little bee,
the little like monster, the guy with the arms and legs. Why did they make him
that? Because he looks like the thing probably doesn't look like a here. I'll
tell you, I mean you can ask that question again. Why do they call him?
Why do they make him that? Make him that. Oh, we're still talking about him, aren't we?
Ah, advertising at work. Years and years later. Wow. Hit that fucking button.
Whoa. Fuck yeah. What are the other ones? You'll find out. Yeah, you'll see. I need to.
That's the best one by far. Oh my God. That's a new addition too. That is the best one.
I was lying in bed and I thought I need to add that to this board.
sound. That's the one that rounded out the sound board for us. You really have
to be careful with that. It is nice. You don't know, just explaining the show,
how the show has been. I've listened to some episodes,
yeah, but not enough. I like to you and then to the fans listening who already
know this guy, by the way to the fans. We don't know this guy and he's a fan.
We just ran into so if you want to be on the show, you just run up, just run up,
just run up. There's some clues like that any video with these guys in it.
there's some clues in the background as to where they may or may not live.
So
this guy just rang the doorbell and now he's here yeah. If you guys get the get
your your geo guesser on you can find these guys, you rainbow. Oh, we had we
me and we had weed. We had weed
we
pull on. I were we're debating a question last night that we actually
ended up asking that guy, the geo guesser guy, what I had responded, you
reply in person. No, we just sent him a dm. Okay,
do you have a dc if you replied when we pull up the question here so I can read
it out. Okay, let me let me fill. Okay, let me fill the dead air while this is
loading. It takes a long time to load. Okay, so this is the question that we
asked him. I asked I wanted him to know I asked are there any towns in the USA
with no pizza
send him another message, some question marks or say here rephrase it here, send
let's say or rather are there any towns in the USA with thousands of people,
but no pizza
us thousands of people, thousands of people, but no pizza, but no pizza, but
spell out people and then and then and then send wait before that preface this
start the sentence off by saying I'm sorry if my question is not clear and
that's why you're not answering,
but I think if there's anybody in the world, I am pondering this
philosophical question. If there's anybody in the world is going to know
the answer to this question, is this guy yeah? Wouldn't you guys agree that
this is the only guy maybe who can help me yeah yeah? I was thinking about
this a lot yesterday down. Just can you imagine a town with thousands of
people and no pizza in the USA?
I'm sorry if not clear. How about this
so
so he's going to respond soon. I'm sure I fucking hope
now
there you go pizza emoji that's going to lock it down yeah. I think the it would
be so funny to like, but whatever a ten of fifteen second tick okay,
look at he list every
every street
because there are towns because there's towns that have like maybe two or three
people and there's no pizza there, but that doesn't count. Maybe I think the
problem is just that like dominoes probably can go one town over yeah yeah,
that's what I was thinking to you know, but yeah that doesn't count though, but
thousands of people that wouldn't count. I wouldn't count it has to be a
thousands of people town with no pizza in the town, no pizza, no pizza, but
nobody said that is accessible, but it could be in the town over yeah, or yeah,
it could be a new message in back and say that clarified that it can be in the
town over. It can be the pizza can be in the just one over, but it's okay. No
I say this can't say if the town was the only thing that existed in the world.
There would be no pizza, so if the town, if a town detached from the earth and
flew into space, it would be a planet without pizza
just to spend just to make it specific that there were not talking. It couldn't
be the town over yeah yeah. You have to say that all of that. Does he follow you
guys? No, no, I'll say that why what
it's not going to make any sense to him unless you clarify it to him that's
okay here. We'll we'll handle it later. He's got he's probably working on his
video
yeah. You probably already started. I know we're probably throwing a lot of
wrenches in this thing. Now I feel like I could probably find like a you know an
old picture of my dad and get him to you know figure out where it was yeah,
that's yeah, that's what it does, but we're trying to figure out.
Maybe we just scrap this pizza joke and we send him a picture of my not a joke.
like what do you, it's a real philosophical idea. I just really like
to know where my dad was in a picture. What picture, maybe you could like a
whoa like a bit of switch, a bait and switch yeah, I'm bringing him in for
with a pizza. I am
and then we're going to switch it out and make him show me where my dad is and
then when he says no, we can just say like okay, never mind. Can you find this
picture of Joe's dad? Can you find the can you where was just
we're going to follow the Google Maps car around all day with this picture of
Joe's dad. Yeah, and then there he's going to tell me where the Google Map is
and then where in that's honestly probably a good idea. Yeah, a picture in
a Google Map. Wow, can you find me? They probably censor it nowadays, though
those fuckers. I've seen the Google Maps car before. I'm on I'm on Apple Maps on
my old place in Boston. We've talked about it. I think it was two eleven
Harvard. Is Apple Maps different than yeah, yeah, different, but they both do
I posted the photo. I've sent it to Jubio before. What I love doing, I love going on
Google Maps and looking at a place over time and seeing how it changes. Can you
do that? Yeah, you can go back to like 2007. Damn, when did they start doing the
Apple car, the Google car? I think it was probably 2007 because there's a lot of my
hometown that... Are you buying an iPhone 14? Don't buy an iPhone 14 on the company
the card. That's not right unless you want to give it to me for my front
facing video.
That's true. Nowadays, movies are shot on phones. Yeah, basically,
tangerine, tangerine, tangerine, one pretty much the only one I can think of
tangerine to the orange. Oh, there's the unsane. Yeah. Was that the Soderbergh
one? Yeah, Soderbergh. Well, I think actually he might have done a few. Was
that other one also? I don't know. That's the only one I saw. That one sucked.
I don't know. Soderbergh sounds like the town where they have no pizza.
They only sell burgers. Oh yeah. So does. Oh my God. So does in burgers.
That's genius. That's the only thing in Soderbergh. And if you try to put,
dude, that's the problem. They try to put pizza there. They fucking kill you.
Yeah, they kill you, dude. They fucking kill you. It's next to, um,
that's a and check this one out fatality. Whoa little combo yeah yeah pretty cool
pretty cool. We'll get to all of them by the end yeah and you can change them if
you want to yeah, but not right now, but yes, I've any suggestions of the first
one, the like Boeing. Oh yeah,
that's his favorite one. I guess that was just quick, but I want that one. I
you can change that one. Why why are you telling them to change it? No, I'm
saying that in here, I'm saying that one is like that everything that he does. I
I think that one is ripe to be changed. Well, you know that we have like a
bunch of space yeah,
I thought you were working with
we have one. I mean there's a easily accessible yeah, you don't want to be
changing the lovers yeah, but you know it's like what you want another one.
Yeah,
oh fuck yeah yeah
fuck yeah
that one's good. I would be are we got everyone already knows about all the
listeners already know about the sounds yeah. I'm just you're just going to have
to ruin it. You're ruining everything right now. Sorry guys.
It's okay. Sorry. It's all right. You got excited about the sounds. I think
the listeners are going to be thrilled that I'm on the episode.
I have to imagine the streets. I think the way the list. This is what the
listeners are like when they're on the episode.
Thank one
That I honestly I wish we started out every episode with the with the Kern
crab zombie nation. Do you not get a song of all copyright strikes for that? Oh,
we haven't yet. We will because of how often we use it. You guys got scared by
dog copyright changes. How often you use something? I think it's the amount of
time that you use it for. We will use it so often. I think on YouTube it just
it gets auto detected. If it hasn't yet, it don't ever will.
It don't ever will. I'm pretty sure it don't ever will not for us.
We have a list today. Yeah, so with this list is an analog list.
It's not found on any computer. Chill out for a second. I'm excited
because this isn't this. I just recently I got this in my mailbox
this morning from corporate. Yeah, you can see right there. It's got a first
class first class mail. They don't need a stamp for that. Yeah, no, they put it
in themselves. Well, I took off the stamp in the address part because I
don't want people to know my address. Obviously, why don't have addresses?
Why can't you did? Well, that's how rich the people at corporate are. They
print their own stamps with every address in the world. Holy fuck! Well,
that is
corporate America man. Yeah, now what they can get away with we that we can't.
why can't you reuse stamps? That's a good question. You know what? Save that. Save
that. Hold on to that. Save that for the end. Because basically what corporate has sent me
here is I guess that they're not so happy with some of the directions our conversations
have been going. They think that we've been talking too much about music festivals, candy,
type of thing and they want to kind of steer us and give us a little more
direction on stuff to talk about that. Maybe we don't talk about all the time.
Okay, so they just sent us some like I guess some of these are like questions
do we show the go? I mean I can show it briefly. I don't want to give them all
away. Okay, I'll talk about them, but it's they sent the I mean some of these
are questions. Some of them are just like, you know, phrases to talk about.
I guess we're just supposed to talk about as many of these as possible.
Great. So it is interesting. Honestly, it is an interest. It is interesting
because it does it's a list. I mean it's also
we haven't been doing enough. We are so mad that we do we have basically not
touched lists in a long time. This is this is also we haven't seen this before.
What this is straight from this is just opened yeah yeah, I don't know what's on
this list. Yeah, I mean I have no one of them. Okay, was it the last one that has
one? No, it was the it was the second one here. Okay, that I'll just read out
and then we can maybe we can just start that. Why don't we know let's start from
the top? Let's take it from the top from the top. He clearly wants to do the
second. I want to do the second one, though let's well. We can get into the
second one to jump around. We can get into the second one second did
corporate say to jump. I said to jump around jump around
I was going to read this one first that this is maybe this is more the type of
thing we're supposed to be talking about on the show. I guess apparently the
okay, but anyway
is Tom Holland cringe
is he cringe. I don't think he's not, but I don't think he's based either. I
don't know
I think he's probably somewhere in the middle of the road. You know, I don't
think he's like
I think I think he's cringe. You think he's cringe. Look at this picture that
we just got pulled. I don't know he just kind of looks like a young boy there. I
think Tom Holland is not cringe, but a young boy. I think I think Tom Holland
he's young. I think he's a little cringe. Okay, that he's starting to look like
you to me for some reason
but to me
for the listeners at home that Jubio put Tom Holland's face over Joe young Tom
Holland. Yeah, I know pre Spidey. I mean he's probably cringe here because he's a
young kid. The thing about Tom Holland is he's a little bit cringe, but if
you're Spider-Man, you're supposed to be that's true. That is actually really
through you want him to be a little bit because if he's what is that noise you
just made what was that if you're talking crazy sorry, I saw something on
the list. You want to be a little cringe because if you're talking to MJ, he
doesn't want to be like spit, right? You know she's a model and he's a nerd.
She's a total she's a total
and he's a babe and he needs to be cringe and his powers are what attracts
her to him yeah yeah wow. So we just put that correct this wide open yeah you
see that's why that's why I'm glad we have you. I'm ready for this God,
because Caleb would be talking about this for hours. I'm ready. I'm going to
give my God my God on you're bringing the hammer down yeah, so you know what
the moaning here, maybe you can drop Monear on on this one here, which is a
conversation topic that I'm glad that corporate has brought up because
honestly I think I text Caleb and Cameron this every single day
pizza Friday versus taco Tuesday. Wow it's pizza Friday for pizza Friday for
me to what about you? What are you thinking?
See I'm going to say
taco Tuesday, because
taco Tuesday, I think, is a little bit more
special and I think it's a little bit more.
I think pizza is an any day thing, whereas taco Tuesday kind of has some
right. There's like a solid platform for taco Tuesday to stand up, but pizza
Friday Pizza Friday Friday, Friday night you're watching a movie. You have pizza.
Maybe you got a Caesar salad look. I love Pizza Friday just as much as the next
guy, but well clearly not think about the next thing about guys right here. I
love it more than think about this in your head right now. Imagine okay
Pizza Friday, you get a taco pizza taco Tuesday. You get a pizza taco. They're
going to say what the hell are you right? You can't order a pizza. That's
you can't say some Spencer say shit yeah
that's some Spencer Shay shit that they're going to get Joe. I Carly as
get Joe, I Carly as back to spaghetti Saturday, get to be at Spaghetto, where
she was from Seattle Spaghetto and I mean now that we talked about I'm glad we I
mean again we got we're still this is still a heated thing, but
this is a heated debate. He's a Friday. I hope the pizza is a heated thing.
Yeah,
cold pizza is for pizza Saturday morning. Yeah,
pizza, which I'm not even going to lie to you guys. I don't know. There's a
not even going to lie to you guys. It's Monday. I'm literally going to have
cold pizza Monday later today, because I had a pizza Friday last night on a
Sunday night and what do you think about that? That's a Friday. That's a Sunday.
It was no, it was pizza. No, there's pizza sauce. Sunday is syrup Sunday.
it's got to be it's syrup sunday and if at night you have pizza and watch a
movie, it can be pizza friday on a sunday night, cereal saturday, cereal
saturday, i have cereal saturday. I have cereal most days, yeah, cereal monday,
tuesday, wednesday, thursday, yeah, and i mean i guess that honestly i mean we
could go on about pizza friday versus taco tuesday. Let's i mean let's be
crossing these topics off yeah we would be going we'd be going
it would be going to get it all on it for the whole episode and i don't think
that would be good. No, so why don't we just go? No, what do you next just let's
just dive right into this next one? Could the next Jared Fogle be lurking in
play?
Because you think about it and it's like
Jared Fogle, he was popular. He was and it's so. Everybody knew his name. He
was at the club that he was popular. He was at the club. He was at the club and
he was walking up to these bitches saying I'm going to give you that foot
long. Yeah, and guess what? Those bitches were kids. That's a fuck.
That's not right. That's disgusting. Oh my God. I never even thought of it that
way.
That's disgusting. Jared Fogle, he kind of flew too close to the sun because he
tried to be... Yeah, somebody's son. Yeah.
He flew too close to somebody's son. They were on the same private jet. Yeah,
and then guess where that jet was going? He... Subway headquarters. Yeah, they
knew of. He tried to be a Ronald McDonald that wasn't a cartoon, but he was a clown. He tried
to be a real guy. He tried to be the honeycombs guy. McDonald's is smart because they do a
bunch of different Ronald's. They have the different ones on the benches at the places
when you go. What do you mean? And it's not just a guy. There's the Ronald on the bench
at McDonald's and you sit next to him and you take a picture. That's the same guy. That's
just the same Ronald. But each one is a different one. He goes to the different ones every time.
and he just comes to which everyone I met yeah. He follows him. He likes me
low, kill, a little sus,
a little, a little sus. Actually, that's exactly what Jared would do speaking of
I mean we've probably talked about it before, but long of mcdonald's and
Jared, we don't to do a mall. You can just as me jump around to precise me
Jared Fogel's just there interviewing him at a damn school. Yeah, you don't
remember that scene and super size. Oh yeah, I do that. He shows up to talk to
him about eating healthy and he's just like well. I'm just here to talk to the
kids. He said dude he there's so many pictures of him at movie premieres for
like puss in boots and oh yeah, it's like he just went to every movie premier
for you. You used to have like a big slide show that you would do. I would do
it. You would do that slide show. I just found a ton of pictures. It's crazy.
Yeah, when I was when I after that happened, I went to a subway like two
days later, yeah, and bear and waste there was a tumble. We the row in the
back of the subway. There was a
three days after it's just a guy just
he
he opened up like the bread like a great things.
He's the last of all rations. There is a there is a framed picture of that guy
and Jared yeah in the on the back wall and I was like. Oh, did you did you hear
what happened and he went
he's got put it down. Oh my God, can you imagine you should have offered to buy
it off?
I was like
Dude, can you imagine being like yeah like a guy a guy? What did that have
you have you have no life at all? You work at subway, you dread going to
subway every day yeah it's it's well. He owns the franchise. When did I talk
about just that I'm saying I'm saying you're a per your person who works at
subway, you're not this person as a junior in high school. You're a junior
as a senior. I was only three
you you, you dread going to your job every day, because it's like a fast food
you don't want to do this shit yeah and then you see the news and you're like
like every every day for for however long someone's going to come in and say
something to you about Jared for yeah, yeah, you even want to be there. You're
seeing I would do in that situation is cut out Jared's head, put a different
celebrity in it yeah in that photo that photo that everyone walks in there like
oh my God, someone else is going to believe that a different guy has pants
that big that don't fit him. Shaquille O'Neal, but he's the pants are too big
but is he wait it's him and the guy standing in the pants together. No
is one like one like whoa pretty cool. Is science going too far? Yes, next
question, what's the next hot meme?
Okay, see that one is that one's actually a reason to think about because
the next fashion is all I was going to cross out fat yeah. We talk about denim.
Oh yeah, we did a lot of fashion,
but the hot next hot meme is scary to think about because obviously
with the way that society is going right now, every single one of these memes
that comes out now is based on a national tragedy. Damn is that the
orange smoke, the orange smoke that became a meme that was a posting how
orange things were baby crunk and you know, I'm just gonna say in terms of
the next hot meme, just keep your eyes on the finale of the mass singer this
Sunday. Okay, you have inside. I have a feeling that there's going to be some
serious memeable content that could be. I bet there will be at least a gift or
two will come out of that. I'll give you a dream. I've a I've a I've a I've a
sneaking suspicion that cucumber princess is going to be revealed. Okay,
okay, and let's just say she's not that great at singing. Oh man, cucumber. I
think I have a feeling, though, about the next hot meme. I'm thinking that it's
likely going to be an original drawing. Yeah, something that someone has drawn in
in terms of when people draw a face that's crying. Why don't we try? Okay,
pig, a frog on the back of this. We'll, we'll, we'll sketch it out right now. So
yeah, you tell me, wait, we should do the thing where we fold it.
You know,
a mad magazine folded, you know,
you draw the head. Well, you have the head. Yeah, you draw the head. It's
gonna be this is the next meme character. You can't look at it. You can't
look. I can't. No, none of us look at each other. So I'm just gonna draw the
neck and then you draw the body and then you draw the legs yeah, okay, great
yeah, who draws the head? He's drawing the head in the neck. Oh, I got it
I want to try okay, okay, but in the meantime, all right, well, I think wait
wait, hold on give us the other two pages. No, you know,
okay,
okay, okay, yeah, chill, but I still want to talk about memes, though you
don't I do oh, okay,
okay, all right, then keep going. Sorry, I'm sorry for interrupting. Well, I
think that maybe don't stop looking at that. Okay, don't stop looking at it.
No, stop looking at it. Okay, we had image memes. We had gifts as memes. We
then we got video memes. What is next? I think is memes that are interactive
and their games with three point. You know where you it's completely a
controllable me where you someone posted on Twitter and you have to play through
the whole thing in order to get the meme. The joke of the meme. Okay, that's
so like it looks like maybe it's like a first person walk around person
salamander and it's like a meme and it's like when you have to go when you have
to go to the bathroom and the meme game is you're running really fast and you're
and you control it to go to the bathroom and you're taught and it's a salamander.
I don't know why I'm married to this right now, but it is a salamander for a
salamander could be a good character. Yeah, because think about it all pepe in
the future, the frog that's true. He's a frog. What's the next logical step? A
a slimy little salamander.
A salamander, yeah.
And he has...
Can you hurry up with your drawing?
He's shedding his skin.
He's shedding his skin maybe.
Do salamanders shed?
I don't really know much about salamanders.
Me neither.
Did you know that they used to think salamanders were fire
monsters?
They are.
They are fire type if you look at Charmander.
He's a Charmander.
That's true.
Well, I think they used to think that they were
in...
Okay, now it's Patrick's turn.
See, was salamander a topic?
No.
Now we're...
but I don't go ahead and draw your draw. All right, okay, and me and Joe will
tell you what topic is next. All right, yeah, I guess now we can move on to a
topic while he works on that you'd sell salamanders was not a topic. I heard
salamanders yeah, it was not a top. I mean, let's see you want to keep talking
about salamander. I don't know. I don't know what to say. Let me let me look at
the other page here. Let's okay, let's see what we have.
Let's see here.
Do we need superheroes in our society?
I think that the question was superheroes becomes why should they be
the judge of what's right and what's wrong. That is so true. That is so so
true, but do you think that maybe
if someone's super powered, it was to know exactly what was right and wrong.
See my dad once told me we were we were playing a little league game and I was
praying that we were going to come back and win and my dad pulled me aside. He
was like why would they why would God choose to let your team win and not the
other team and I feel like we're so conflicted in this world. So we're
bringing God into this now. Well, God is the number one superhero of all time.
that's true. I guess the main superhero. He is the main superhero. Yeah, and what
if the superhero was anti God
would be low keys carry that would be more of a villain. I feel like than a
superhero. It depends on your your thought about God. I'm just saying that
it's things are so things are so polarizing right now that I don't think
it's super here would necessarily. Okay, wait. No, you know what here. I have a
question for you this one. I think you're uniquely
equipped to answer this one here. What can music fans expect in 2024? Oh wow,
let's just say I have a sneaking suspicion that Adele is going to drop
some serious heat.
I think that do you think pianos are going to make a comeback? I think 37 is
probably coming out. That's me guessing Adele's age wildly. She's probably a
little bit younger 35. Does she name her stuff out of for her age at the first
these couple. They definitely were. I don't know anything about Adele. To be
honest with you, what was the second question you asked? Are this piano is
going to come back pianos of music really? If you don't listen to the radio
that much, have you ever seen a producer flip a sample?
Yes, often with piano songs, oh my God, and he's doing it on the piano to do
you think we could see a new genre emerge in the next year? I do feel like
country and rap are fusing in a major way right now. I thought that already
happened. I thought that was happening even more now it's happening again.
Let's just say there's going to be some more country songs with some nice beats
behind it. I feel like my theory is I feel like we're going to see a new
genre that's not even two genres fused and it's just something completely new
that no music has ever been like before
ring tones ring to ring tones are probably going to be huge again. People
are going to start having ring tones again. I don't know. I still have a ring
ringtone. You still have a ringtone? Yeah, actually while you're pulling up
your ringtone, let me ask you about this. Cousins. Cousins. That's all it says.
That's all it says. You're very close with your cousins. I am very close with
my cousins, actually. I love all of my cousins very deeply, but I'm not like
super close personal friends with them. Yeah, well, I lived next to all of my
cousins growing up. My next door neighbor was my aunt, and then a little
down the road was my other aunt. So I had five cousins down the street and four
cousins who lived next door. Yeah, that's very weird. You're just literally
close to them. Yeah, literally and figuratively very close to my family.
This is my ringtone. Okay, let me hear it.
it's minions doing panda
and I did it like a long get that every single time you get a text. It's when I
have because I've got it like in college and I kept my I kept my phone on like
vibrate for a long time and then now when I wear headphones, it like pops up
on my oh yeah. You know why it's kind of a good one. It does make me answer. Oh
my God, where's the new me? We have the meme. This is the
next to me.
you guys, everybody take cash, cashier, your checks. Now, if you're listening on
audio only, I want you to open up your phone right now. I want you to take a
screenshot. I want you to start posting this with captions and make this catch on
as the next viral me. Wait, hold on, let's let's workshop one right now. I'm
hold on
okay, okay, wait when your teacher says the homework was is due
and it's yeah yeah, that's pretty good. Wow, if we break down each of the
components. See, I was going for kind of an angry guy. Yeah, so
you've got an angry guy with a soul patch and steam blowing out
of his ears as the head. That's the angry guy and the body here
is, I think, size double G breasts. Okay, what does it say
on the stomach? And that is a tummy rocker that says, "Come
shot with a dollar sign on the S." Okay, and she also, let me
just point out one thing here, also has one finger and one
thumb on a really small little spaghetti arm like a crab. Yeah,
would and then let's see these legs here. Yeah, so I just tried
to go with something simple, some legs with lines on them and
socks. Okay, I like that that kind of bases it and those are
not that is not hair. Those are lines. Yeah, well, it's a
drawing leg lines. Wow, those are leg lines. This guy's the
leg liner and here and let me let me just here's the next
topic here. Let's just combine these two because once you hear
but once you hear them combined, it's going to make a okay a lot of sense.
I'm sure corporate won't mind that how to deal with that termites and woke
culture. How to deal with term same way when you have to blow them the fuck up
yeah with fire. Well,
that's right. No, I would say for termites I'm for me. I think peanut
butter works peanut butter, peanut butter definitely works. I don't think
termites yeah termites because unless it's like I'm the type of guy. I don't
like to I don't like to look up an instructional thing on how to do
something. I'm a handyman. I do stuff myself. I'm not going to buy fucking
furniture from Ikea and follow the instruction manual. I build shit myself,
so when I'm getting rid of termites, I'm not going to go to an exterminator.
Say how do I do this on by the way exterminator exterminator termite? They
work with the termites yeah. It's literally a they're putting low more
cycle in your house cycle. They put eggs in there so that they have to come back,
but anyway, basically I'd probably use a straw to suck them up yeah and same with
woke cold. That's a good sound effect. Just get a strong
for the sound. Yeah, I want to eat that
yeah. I don't think that would actually be so good of a sound. Can we live
record and put stuff on it? No, no, it's not a thing. I know how there might be a
way, but I'm not going to try and figure it out. Can you do some like Reggie
lots of loops on it. I can do this
wow that's a record scratch yeah, yeah, yeah, but how would you deal with woke
culture?
See in in my in my opinion, I don't necessarily have many opinions that are
more important than like
what really matters to people. So like you know
like none of my none of my takes on anything
so
I'm okay with it.
If you know if if what culture tries to take away like you know videos, then
I'll
they want videos to be gone. Oh man,
well, then I'm gonna have to get it. They try to take away videos like if
they try to make world culture takes away videos. They try to make videos,
not okay.
I'll get pretty upset about it. Yeah, I like video. I hope videos. I love
videos. I really love videos yeah
oh well in woke people when when you play a video
that's right screaming yeah.
What is that from
just screaming from D and D? It's from the Dungeons and Dragons and it'll make
of a like what is the screen? I just got it from Youtube yeah yeah it's a
thousand people dying. I
know it's a sound effect and
so let me let me let me just transition that last question. So I said I would
deal with termites and well culture using peanut butter.
Let's just get right into this another question from corporate is peanut
butter based your cringe. I used to here's I you were doing your set yourself
stop for a little. I thought about this before I used to think it was based
nowadays. I think it's cringe well
Patrick, just take I didn't hear it, but I thought it made it was a completely
silent spit. I think that water bottle has been here for a very long time. No,
I bet that this morning
the spitting, but I had too much water.
oh
man that was more like a squirtle water gun type spit take than it was a
funny. You need to
be one. You need to press my bed. I did not know. I've never okay. I'm sure
I've never done a spit. Take no, no, we're not doing
doing now. No, no, this is my water and I need it to do it on the shelf of
technology. Don't do it on the shelf of technology. Do it in any way. You're
not supposed to have spit takes in here at all yeah. That was even one is to
that's one of the rules and here is our next topic from corporate rules. I
fucking hate rule. You hate rules. I hate rules too. That's why let me guess
you like rules. Joe likes rules. If we don't have rules, what are we? What are
we? What are we? What are we following rules? Don't have to be bad rules. We
don't have rules. What are we following? Yeah, I don't know. I wouldn't know
where to go man rules. Don't have to what about the leader? Yeah, what you
or the leader. You can make I make my own rules up. I do what I do what I want to
do, but I live the leader. Now I live by a coat. I'm the leader
your ass ain't the leader. I'm not the leader you're in general. No, you're not
the general. You don't see me as a leader. I don't see you as a leader. You
don't see me and follow my lead.
No damn what whose lead do you follow probably gods?
Yeah, I mean me too, but I thought I was like I think he's the one leader one
true leader, but there's okay. Here's a one true leader. I think we can really
because we're having a little bit of an argument here. Yeah, okay. I think maybe
it's just a question we can really dig into. It's just discussions, discussions,
but what
what was it like long ago?
I like thinking about that. What was it like? I'm going to go question really
fucking hate thinking about that. What was it like long ago? You know you think
about that you think about what it was like long ago, then you start to
do start to yearn right. I feel like a year in for what was long ago. You know
back in the day before they figured out how to make animals right or animals
figured out how to evolve correctly. They when the first animals, the first
multi cell, whatever's, they were just like things they weren't even they were
like sub plant. They were like they were like circles that would sit on the
ground. They were just pieces and they would they would just sit in the bottom
of the ocean. It would just be like a hot dog or like a pancake and it would
to sit there and if food went by it, then it would survive yeah and if it didn't
isn't that a long, long time ago. That's what he means. I long ago, I was
thinking yeah. What was it like long ago? I was sort of thinking like nineteen
ten Ellis Island. Let's talk that yeah. I mean we can talk about that. That's
the beauty of discussion. Well, I'm as you guys might know I'm fascinated by
old maps. Really
what is it about old maps for you? I love if it's a place that I'm familiar
So New York, I got it with Boston after going to school there and I kind of have it with
Los Angeles a little bit.
I love to see that the streets that I walk on today still existed and served a purpose
way back when.
That's kind of magical, isn't it?
It is actually very magical.
That's actually pretty cool.
What was it like back then?
So New York changes a lot.
New York is kind of built around this rapid change.
Rapid transit too.
still historical. You know societies and bus on their landmarks started being
made people were tearing shit down willy nilly, whereas Los Angeles kind of has
more
of a
steady like
okay here, okay, here, I'll say yeah, we're going to do we're going to do a
few more. We're going to love it because there's a few. I want to get are we
doing a speed around now with the last speedish round speedish around. I want
do I just want to get through all the I'll just go in order here. I'll skip
some of the ones that you know what no we'll do a lightning round. We're going
to do all the rest of them. Okay, I'm ready. Okay, can I get the third paper?
Yeah, the third paper is very important. Okay,
okay, so I'll just go down the line. Yeah, let's just let's just go around
each give a quick answer. It's not to be so quick, but quick
Joe, please quick the streaming wars. Whose side are you on? Oh my God, thank
thank God we didn't have thank God this is in the lightning round, because I'd
be here talking about this all day. Let me get into it,
because obviously I'm on the side of the streaming yeah for me. It's like I
always
kind of aligned with the young, the scrappy, the new kids on the block, the
people who really want to like show the fat cats what's for and that's why I am
throwing my way behind a little new service. So some people might not have
about yet called Max. I like Max Max has scrappy coming crazy. You're thinking
boomerang, but they also they are has it, though, also on that, but also it's on
both. There's a section on now there is no, but there's a scooby section and
it's called boomerang because it keeps you. They have Tom old Tom and Jerry's
as well. I can races if they got like a race. Some there I'm there. They have
the one with the evil guy next topic. Why can't race us every time? It's every
the hockey race. Whatever happened to chivalrous men,
you just got to look a little bit harder. Yeah, that's right there out
there. We're out there. We're waiting. There's three on your screen right.
Yeah, that's true. Well, let me actually let me throw something out there.
Maybe you know, because people always complain the men don't hold the door
anymore. Yeah right ever think about nowadays. You can get a job holding a
door at a hotel or at an apartment building. So why would you do it for
free or you can do it
Amy Yeah, well, I was going to say some people do it for free out in front of
the McDonald's. Yeah, actually they do it. They don't want to be doing it for
they do it on commission. Those people work for the McDonald's.
That's why they have a cup. Okay, here's one in a past generation
in a past generation. Guys like us would be rock stars.
so go ahead and discuss that. I mean it's not really up for discussion. There's
still time. The thing some guys would say that the podcast, the podcast boom is
the rock stars of today. Yeah, and you guys, I think, have you guys have a wait
no
yeah.
I would say that you guys have carved out this like incredible audience and
this incredible like loyal fan base. Wow, who holds you up as if you are rock
stars. What is going on in Ukraine
much don't even want to know. Yeah, next that sounded like a sound effect.
Water monsters.
Oh, I saw a few. You've seen some. Yeah, I wanted to. There's a video that
Caleb was talking about a water monster attacked a man. Oh yeah, that shark.
Yeah, sharks are water monsters. Orcas are now. Yes, the orcas, payacon orcas
or attacking. Yeah, why are you outcast?
What a movie. Whatever happened to cowboys. Cowboys are still around, but
you got to look a little bit. They are wearing little that's a really good
answer for a lot of little dangly things in front of their face, calling
themselves orville peck. I don't know if that's a cowboy or not. Is that the
tattoo guy? Maybe
that's Oliver Peck. What's the guy from ink master? I don't know orville peck
nevaro. He's like a gay cowboy who sings. Oh, I don't know if he's gay. I don't
know if it's a he. Okay, here's one this this trump bullshit.
We'll see we'll see how it goes. Yeah, we'll see all right.
what's wrong with doctors nowadays. They are too focused on the medicine and not
focused enough on creating a relationship. Yeah, it's not friendly
enough. I would say I would say that they really stepped up big during covid
yeah, and I would say that they're probably still reeling from the effects
of it. My doctor almost sent my medical bill to collections just because I forgot
to pay it. Wow, how long a lot of my bills are in I paid it right now today
and today was the day it was going to go to collections. A lot of minor in
selections right now and guess what you do you just ignore them. You ignore
them until they break down and cry calling you. What would you do if you
saw someone drinking nut milk?
What kind of nut yeah doesn't specify
and I don't know I didn't write these not like I mean, okay, not like a human
semen, but I can like all mon you can kind of see what corporate was trying to
you under a very kind of spark, a funny little, a funny little riff, yeah, a
a little riff. Let's let's not give it. Let's yeah we're not going to engage
here. Why are so many people getting injured lately? Probably because I'm
hitting them. There's someone slipped a
lot of people there. There's people that try to come by the office. They try to.
I know there's a bus stop near it, but I think that they are attacking my
fortress. I go out with a broom. I haven't had a serious injury in a while.
Me neither. Genetic splicing facts, it's fine facts. Yeah, right, let's let it
I'm let it what I'm going to do when I get home.
Oh, I can't discuss that because it's a Monday for me. It's a rod. I tuna fish.
I have some tuna fish. You have it with you know at home and then I'm going to
have another one of these guys. Okay, nice. We can't endorse that on the
short and culture. It's ice tea, art and culture. Y'all are in culture. Y'all
love it. Well, just I said, you know, I graffiti is art to me. Next question,
would you eat a rock? I ate one as a kid depends on how porous it is. Could
someone with ice powers defeat someone with fire powers like the ice freeze the
fire or what the ice ends on is it like a Voldemort Harry Potter vibe where
they're just going at each other straight up? Let's see it says someone
with ice powers and someone with fire powers because I think I started to
kill the rain ice powers could kill the fire guy. If he snuck up, if he snuck
up yeah, you're probably rocks could put out the same. The fire, though, is
chewing gum based chewing gum is cringe
because of the bubbles. I think it's well bubble. You don't not all gum is
bubbles. Really, I would say chewing gum can be I have I have something of a
what's it called
TMJ. Well, yes, but also I have like a oral fixation thing like I whoa, I eat a
lot of like plant like this. You chew your, oh yeah, I take these these off of
bottles. I chew my little brother used to do that with cans like at the top of a
top of a can the top of like a coffee cup fixation. I guess yeah, because you put
your finger in my finger in my butt
touch stuff a lot.
Okay, what's this? The future of TV. That's again. Yeah, we're streaming.
Yeah, we covered that. I hope it's good. Would you adopt a baby from cringe
parents? Fuck no.
Okay, see I kind of just want my own. I want my kids to be my own,
my own making. Robo adoption robots, cringe, little scary.
Is injustice real? The game.
Injustice. What to do when you are visited by an angel?
I can't even discuss that. See what the town would be like without you.
Wow
film fan. Yeah, I would trap a little person
keep it in a jar. I would sell it. Is there hope for nerds? No, if you're a
nerd, I'm sorry that we were doing the lightning round. I know that, but if
you're a nerd, it is over for you. I would say it is so all right. I've had
a little renaissance recently and I think it's I think it's kind of coming
back to the to us jocks. I think you're right. Would you guys say I'm a nerd or
more jock, you're a jock, yeah that's cool. Okay, we're going to do actual
running around now. Okay, one sentence answers, okay, okay, what up and doing
would you rather live next to squidward or sponge bob my own house squidward
sponge bob sponge was a little more fun. No, it's good. We're at squidward
squirter house in the middle of squirter and sponge bob. Is there a
special place we can go to hide out the the hide out
twirling twirling around just twirling and twirling is cringe. Our drugs getting
more evil. Yes, I think they're getting a little more evil. Yeah, Fent Fent how to
survive in the forest
shelter, water, food, shelter, air, yeah, as well as hierarchy of needs kind of
yeah, that's good needs needs precious metals, diamonds, how poor are they?
Yeah, exactly how precious can they be? Yeah, why are we metal? Why are we
treating metal everywhere? Let's take off the baby gloves and let's treat
these things with some serious throwing. What can you say at a sleepover to gross
everybody out. My booger has a boner.
I just shit on my shit. I just shit it out of that was the size of a I just
fucked my shit in my bag. I just fucked a booger. I just fucked my booger yeah
there. We go like that. I just fucked my I'll say so and so's mom was naked yeah,
so dad. I saw so and so's dad yeah. I saw Kyle's dad's cock and it had a booger
on the end of it.
Dad pissing a booger off his cock
elves elves elves in general, yeah elves, Santa bro, Santa, bro, that's my answer
as well. How to deal with teachers who assign hella too much homework. I think
we discussed this okay. We covered that with today's generation. Consider Homer
Simpson a good father. Hell, no
Homer, the Simpsons, lightning round lightning around Joe early, yes or no
early Simpsons, Homer have heart
magic, the gathering should it based should it be a crime to lie. Yes,
whatever happened to cartoons. I think they're on the TV. I don't know what
they cuss now. How come Thanksgiving is only once per year?
Oh my God, I wish we touched upon that earlier.
History we could have really go ahead. Go in on that go in on it a little bit
then. Okay, so if you know the history of Thanksgiving, like I do
how many people know where Thanksgiving comes from? It comes from a little guy
called Squanto
and Squanto pulled up. This is what they don't teach you in school. Squanto
pulled up with the turkey and the cornucopia and he said we should do this
every single day, but these fucking whiteys were like yeah, oh yeah, yeah, of
course, and they never pulled up again.
So we were supposed to have Thanksgiving every single day.
My family does Thanksgiving in a restaurant. Really? I did that one or two
times. So we could do that. I do that. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, but you know
what? I'm here. Here's the thing. Here's another. Here's another little thing
about Thanksgiving. Okay, if you are a Canadian American citizen, guess what to
thanksgivings? Yeah, you just have to travel. That's a trick question from
corporate. Also, they wanted me to reveal the truth. You got to be. You got to be
traveling. Did cavemen have stores caveman's had caves? There was some
trading. There's definitely some trading or going on yeah
uga buga paper straws. Come on man. Are these things still around? They are
disgusting me when I go to a woke restaurant
yeah, you need to dip it in water. First, he's sucking penis at the
restaurant. See I'm okay with the paper straw as long as it's something that
I'm going to drink quickly. No yeah people don't talk about this, but paper
drink beer.
That's what I like a paper straw for I'd like a paper cup drink my beer. See why
don't we put this wax coating that's on paper cups inside the paper straws to
only mother fucking shit. I think I think you're right yeah to have just
created the greatest, you know in the movie, the new it movie when it opens
the first one, it starts in the little kid. He makes a boat out of paper and he
covers it with wax, paraffin wax yeah and it's like that maybe that was the
he was going to do that to straws and he got eaten by my God and that's the
origin of why paper straws suck so damn bad eaten it e a n
by the clown. He got eaten it e a n. He got eaten by the clown and now he can't
make eat. He can't oh yeah, I just got it. He can no longer make it. He can no
longer make pennies off of his wise discovery.
Okay, just just a couple. We're just blowing every single thing. Why is it
wrong to blow something up? Yes, no, if it's a controlled demolition. Yeah, no,
I would say it depends on the context. Okay, fair. Don't do what matters in
explosions is the age of Mario over. Yes, no, I think there's probably a sequel
coming. Whoa, not right and then I got the last one here. This is we got we
went through these two pages. We have the third page that corporate sent us
and this is the biggest one we have yet to talk about reddit.
reddit,
which is why joe. Why don't you go ahead and explain what's going on with reddit
right now something about the api reddit is now
the sub reddits are down because they don't want to let people use
third party apps in order to like access the
website. Say what third party apps are no longer
is our is our subreddit blacked out right now. Can you black it out? Yeah, I think
we should participate in this. We need to participate in this blackout. What is
this? What are you looking at? What are these numbers? Destiny's a kind of grab.
He just likes. Oh, it's just all the ones that are the
blacked out subreddits. Oh, will you go ahead and black cars out? See I was
pretty upset because that I don't I don't know how to do it, but once I've
learned how to do it, oh my God, our slash shower thoughts is down. Our
filmmakers, shower thoughts deleted my last few shower thoughts, so I'm not too
mad that they're down. Yeah, I think a lot of these subreddits deserve to be
shut down forever.
Our slash one right here, street where did how am I gonna know that nature is
fucking lit? Yeah, our slash atheism has been blacked out.
Oh my God, oh my God, yeah, they're gonna take a huge hit. Alright, well, I'm
glad we were able to shed some light on this. Yeah, the NBA one is down now and
it's the finals today. What the fuck our slash martial arts has also been taken
down or
me
fight today.
So our site wait, our slash Asian beauty has been is been blacked out. Oh my God,
when does it end? When will it stop? Holy crap, it's crazy how much stuff people
like. So what everyone should do now is go and check out
home planet and watch some of the funny planet planet video that Joe is half of
Home Planet that makes his funny videos. Yep, you've seen Alex on here.
You've seen Joe now. What's Home Planet's Twitter? Home underscore underscore
planet. Okay, so when you're on the Twitter homepage, you can just add it
to the end of the URL. It says twitter.com/home normally. So then you
can just add... Yes, underscore underscore planet. Wow. Underscore underscore planet.
Pretty cool. And it's on YouTube and there's a website too, I guess,
that I had forgotten about. Homeplanetvideo.com. Look at that. Guys,
if you have any design notes for our website... You can send them over
Joe and speaking of design notes, I have one for you right now, Joe. Why don't
you add a section on your website that says live show? Oh shit. Yeah, yeah,
because this guy right here is going to be joining us along with philip and
philip and alex and pierce and we're all going to be doing a sketch show of
funny comedy. Um, and I've been, should we maybe watch some home planet videos
and like mystery science theater them? It could be pretty awesome. It's going
to be at Littlefield on I believe July 14th. July 14th at 8. I can buy tickets at 30pm.
Swagpoop.com/shows and maybe eventually on the HomePlanet website if they get their shit
together. HomePlanet.com/whatthe1show. And Pierce does not have a website so. I think
he might. I feel like he should have one. I think he definitely does actually. World
biggest army of ports of call. Go on-is. It's going to be really fun. It's going to be great.
You're not going to want to miss it. And if you don't live in New York you're probably
we going to be traveling here? You will be taking the Amtrak Sella train. Do
we know how fast as you can? Do we know how they're selling the tickets? I have
like somebody just bought ten tickets for a hundred and ninety two dollars.
I really I really need this to go well. I really need the cash. Oh, and Julia,
what day is
what day is our shareholder meeting the twenty third? So next Friday at at six
are we doing six again? Is this a six eastern am shareholder? Meet is this a
a patreon one. Yeah, no, this is this is on you to oh you're going to be on
you made it. You're going to be famous. I can get some thumbnails. If you want
you have anything else you want to you want to plug
besides home planet and our show that we share my twitter. No three on all
socials. Don't I made a tick tock video for him and he didn't even acknowledge
it. I made a tick tock promo for jubio. Yeah, just follow home planet. That's
the only thing I care about. Yeah, that's right. That's the only thing I
and buy tickets to that and buy tickets to the show. Yeah, we're going to make
hell a new hell a new video. I've written so many sketches this week.
Patrick's been damn. I've been sending them to everybody and I got no notes.
He's been going. I've got zero. I've gotten zero. I'm going to give you
notes today. We also wrote something. None of you guys read it. When did you
say? Well, I was said I said I'm going to read it today and he said you
shouldn't read it because we did. Okay, all right. And let me say something. I'm
probably the only person who said I'm sorry. I didn't read it yet. I'm going
to read it today. Is that true? Yeah, Cameron, you are. I have to look at this.
Nope, you don't because it's too late. I'll read your things though, Patrick.
Okay. All right. Well, anyway, bye. Thank you so much for having me.
[Music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]