I
What is just because I'm fucking scared this alert why?
Scared right you have such a protective kind of like
Defensive energy today. I'm on edge you were I mean not to mention there on the edge of madness
You're on the edge of you're on the edge of barely being friends with me have been a fucking targeted
I don't know if you know clearly we've been targeted. That's like an arrow
hitting a target and bouncing up and down. Yeah, we've been targeted. Oh wait
by that's obvious. One of the most probably dangerous serial killers in the
world. Probably I mean, okay, so a lot of fatalities. I would say men like me
wimp women like you men like you said women and men and men like me who are
wimps. Yeah, probably targets wimps and women. I think you're more of a chump.
Yeah, you're not a wimp. You are definitely a chump. I'm not a chump.
Why do you think that's the number one chump thing is? I'm not a chump. I'm not
a chump. You think that you, I'm not a chump. You're not a wimp. You've been
targeted by the McChickener
and it's going to, it's ruining my life. I didn't sleep last night. That's all
you've been thinking about. It's all I've been thinking about. I mean, it's
definitely tough. I do think that this is clearly I don't think this is a
current serial killer. I think it is a future serial retired. No, no future,
no, no, no, a future serial, right? Yeah, who is he'll retire in the future,
though? Probably one day. I don't think they really retire. Some of them do.
The zodiac did. Oh, that's true. Well, maybe he died. I think that's I guess,
though, that is the thing about him is that that's the reason he's so
it's because they did. He's the first one stopped and they did get him. He's
He's Michael Jordan. He would just, he goaded.
But his calling card is not as scary as a chicken stuck through a spike.
Impaled through a spike.
Was it impaled or was it just in between two spikes?
It was impaled.
We were targeted by, you want to just tell the story?
Yes, so Friday night, I mean, what's in the intro?
Yeah, but there's people in the audio.
There's listeners who don't listen to, don't watch the show.
So Friday I was here, I was working late.
Tell people what that means.
That means that no I was editing a video.
What video?
That flopped.
Oh okay.
Editing a video that flopped.
No one cares about promo for sketch shows anymore.
No one cares about.
They used to though.
They used to care so much.
Nobody cares about.
It used to be huge.
About a funny video game looking visual.
Kind of Eric Andre show.
Crazy insane style.
2017 style videos.
People don't like them anymore.
People don't care.
don't like him anymore. People don't prefer 2016 style square posters
definitely yeah and even then
I put it at the end of the video.
I put it in there. So everyone can have what they want. If there's anything
people like less than a 2017 style video or a 2016 style poster, it's a 2016 style
poster at the end of a 2017 style video. Well, okay, maybe that's why I was
targeted by this disgusting, vicious man. This disgusting villain. This disgusting
So this person saw the, saw the, they saw, okay, so let's assume they saw the
Instagram post. They probably, they probably, they probably, like, smelled my
pheromones on me. They probably, think about this, think about this, I leave
here, I'm, all day I'm editing this video, I leave here, I'm closing up shop,
this guy
walking down the street like that. He was doing that? Yeah, obviously. Obviously.
He's a fucking crazy psycho. He's
sniffing the air like that and then doing that with his tongue so he can get the
taste too. And then he sees me, sees me standing there, he knows this guy just
made a flopping video for a sketch show at Littlefield on July 14th. And the
landlord is outside. This isn't good.
flopping video and then he saw he was like, okay, I'm going to come back here
later, but how am I going to remember how to come back here so I can completely
decimate this fool?
Right.
And what will remind me of this?
Like that Bible story.
This fucking flopper.
And so what did he do?
he impaled his McChicken that he was eating
through the spike in our gate.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Put it right through there.
That is right through awful news and then I immediately I turned
around because he thought I wouldn't notice, but I watched
that area like a Hawk.
Yeah.
He thought I wouldn't notice.
I see the McChicken impaled through and you go.
I
I immediately- You pull out your guns. No, I ran away. I ran all the way home.
I went wee, wee, wee all the way home, texted you guys a photo of it
immediately. Yeah. And we have been on guard since Friday. You haven't left
the office. No. You've been sitting here. No. You're armed, aren't you?
Why do you think I've been doing Twitch streams because I'm so scared?
You're like the opposite of a sitting duck. I'm a sitting cannon. Yeah.
There's a way to a century. You are at the office of a century right now.
There's a cannonball that has been sitting in me for centuries.
And this guy is going to accidentally light the fuse.
You're a Bloons TD. You're upgraded.
I'm doing tower defense.
You're the monkey in the middle.
You started out, they bought you for one dollar on Bloons,
wimpy chump. Yeah. They upgraded you.
Now he's going to be my interactive buddy.
And I'm going to put the Napoleon Dynamite skin on him and I'm going to bounce him off
the wall.
I'll tell you what I always used was the George Bush skin.
Yep.
Because I wanted to disrespect him.
George Bush or Saddam.
Because I, let's play both sides here.
Yeah.
My dad got mad at me for using the George Bush one.
Yeah, because he loved Bush so much.
Wow.
Bush was cool, man.
I mean.
He did, he golfed.
Yeah.
Everybody golfs.
That's true.
Every single person.
Pretty much everyone else.
Last time we had a prisoner that didn't know how to golf.
Probably before golf was invented.
Probably Jimmy Carter.
Jimmy Carter was a fucking pussy hippie bitch.
He was a pussy whore.
My peanuts!
They made me steal, they made me get away my peanuts!
Fuck him. Jimmy Carter, bitch ass motherfucker.
Jimmy Carter, if that was you who put that McChicken on the gate...
We gonna shoot the shit out of you.
We gonna...
I don't think we can say that.
the houses and they take pictures of him and he looks like a...
Yeah, he looks like a...
Buddy, I know you ain't building those houses.
He looks like they're using him as the hammer on the house.
It looks like they're picking him up, swinging him around,
demolishing walls with him like a curtain ledge hammer.
Using him exactly like a tool.
Picking him up by the legs and...
He looks like shit.
He's been a tool since day one, if you ask me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
But anyway, so the McChicken thing kind of got Patrick pretty shaken.
He's sitting here with the bulletproof on, looking like Troy Ave.
Yeah.
He looks good.
I have a good look for you. I have bullet proof it woven into my skin, so I don't
need a bullet proof woven into your skin, the fibers I've definitely yeah. I've
definitely had enough teflon from that's what you just see if you just scrape a
non stick pan and eat out of it, but that's only covering this part of me
eggs that you scramble on the pan for about fifteen seconds yeah with
the highest highest possible heat for fifteen seconds.
You do my double fork technique, you take an archaeologist chisel and you go
to get them off the pan. Well, you break it in the my double for a hammer and
you do like a sculptor.
You have the you have the heat on like the highest setting with a teflon pan,
because you think you got it. You got to season it like a carbon steel walk. I
think it's the black stuff is pepper yeah.
I think that it's pepper that they put in the pan, so you don't have to pepper
your eggs yeah. My dad used to have I do hate fucking peppering my eggs. I wish
he's already in a pan. I wish it was already in the pan. Oh God, just put it
in the pan. Just shake it. That's a- wait, another amazing invention. He got
so scared for a second. I'm sorry. Yeah. Another amazing invention. What about
that I didn't like peppering my eggs? Me? Yeah, you don't pepper your eggs.
Well, I was confused. Guys, I have another amazing invention today. Okay. I
have one after you. It's more of a phil- it's a scientific concept. I guess I
could come up with one by the time you two do one. I guess I could do three.
here's my back off of my pots and pans that have all of the seasoning and
ingredients already in the pot, the pan. All you have to do is add the meat or
the rice and the heat and the heat as well. But yeah, so say you're making
oh and they're disposable like you can buy them at the store like the the Tony
Sashory's engineers will figure out this. Yeah, I don't give a shit about
any of this for the nerds. Okay, it's going to refill or you're going to buy
things that go in the pan, like different, like fill it, like color
covers that are the flavor pack, yeah, cartridges, a cart. Oh, my God, it's
like a so it's a cartridge. It's a soda stream for your food and it's called a
food pan
and you can put you can make stream. It's called a food a pan food. A pan is
good food and it's really good. You take a you take a say you want to make
chicken alfredo right? Well, let me look at my fridge. I have chicken.
But I don't have Alfredo. And actually, I don't even know what Alfredo is.
Let me throw in my invention before Pat's really quick because I just came up with it
based off of yours. And it's basically you buy a straw, but on one end it is closed on
the straw and inside the straw is a small amount of a drink. And you can buy, okay,
this is a soda straw, this is a water straw, this is a milk straw.
It's called a drink a straw.
Drink a straw.
And it's like kind of the spin off of the food a pan. And it costs very little money.
so if you don't, if you want to sit liquid, if you want to sit and it comes
with or you can buy a big straw that's the size of a bottle
or it has like different flavors. The straw has different flavors. You can put
it into like a sparkling water. Yeah, so you can mix and match the straw flavor
with the liquid base and you only get one. It's like I want just one sip of
spray. These are disposable. These are like you have to buy like a razor. These
are very bad for the environment. How are you going to turn water in a milk?
very well. That's one of the base liquids. So for example, it's like I can
have nice truck and be filled with water, milk, wine, chicken broth or if
you don't really, if you don't like drinks, then maybe
powder like salt and pepper. Yeah, so then the straws are like strawberry.
Oh, maybe you could do something where it has a savory, has some kind of
vegetable, like just flour in the straw. So when you suck it turns into a
drinkable flower. Oh my God, a little pretzel or a flower where you put it
into the drink and it sucks up through the stem your drink and it puts it into
the air. Yeah,
here's
the
seven year old girls and you can breathe in the drink in your room. It's like a
humidifier. You can put this is literally like a little girls and you
could probably put any liquid into an ultrasonic humidifier. Yeah, because
they just throw it into the air. Yeah, so I got one of the good. That's the
one that's dangerous. If you use tap water because it throws sediment into the
there, because it doesn't boil the water cool. Miss is dangerous. Yeah, I mean
it's only dangerous if you don't clean it and aren't careful with the water.
Yeah, I've never cleaned or you or you would never clean. I'm not a fish. It's
made out of water. Yeah, it's a humidifier. It's made out of water.
That's another good one. That is a good one. This is the invention. Yeah, I was
thinking of and it's not really an invention. It's more of like a bio
political engineering okay,
and it's done to it's not done to humans. So why don't you say what it is yeah,
so don't get all scared or anything. Well, what is it done? What we do
flavored chickens and eggs yeah, yeah, I'm liking it. So you get a it's one oh
one y'all. Oh, I thought you were giving me a you can have a fist bump, but I
was going to stamp approved on the table. Oh, okay, so what we do we get like
multiple types of chickens like they're already doing it to make chicken breasts
bigger right. Why don't we put as well as the black chicken and the black egg?
Yeah, yeah true. The silky
no, the black chicken and the black egg. It's called black chicken with
completely black egg and I've seen it on a lot of websites and Facebook posts. I
know what this is now, yeah. Black meat. So we're putting, we're gonna, we're
gonna, from birth, from the egg, plus the eggs, they're gonna have like tons of
flavour in them, 'cause it's gonna be flavour concentrate in the egg. You can
cook these, you're gonna be putting barbeque, sour cream and onion. And think
don't want barbecue chicken, though you don't need to then think about it to a
barbecue chicken, because then you got the flavored eggs. You can flavor
separately the yoke and the white create some ratatouille style combination
strawberry and cheese, but but but but but but but what if you were making a
an egg with cheese already in it, so you can make a crazy omelet
was that you're going to say that's that's your problem. What you say is
that you say something and say is that what you're going to say yeah, I've
just diagnosed you well. Here's what I was going to say and you were never
going to guess this okay. I was going to say what if you bake a cake and you
accidentally put a some kind of hamburger egg into into your oh that's
really right yeah and that one that's on you. If you put on if I do, if I do
that that's on you one and then to the eggs are going to have like a screen
printed. Can you have some kind of neutralizer egg or you put that in and
I go back to normal? That's a that should just be exist for flavors in
you know, if you make a mistake, I have been saying this for too long. If I add
too much salt to something to the point where it's completely inedible, you
add pepper should that's it should it doesn't it doesn't, but it should as my
roommate told me in community college and in in college and he told me that's
exactly what you do and I was like that is not what you do. No, I made and I
tried it and it didn't work. It does not work. It just makes it taste worse. I
made a chili that was just far too salty and here I am water
you
water to chilly, but as flavor remover,
ingredients and
ingredients and because here's every gradient has
a what you do if you are one of these freaks or
don't like gradient out greedy. Oh, my God,
there we go. Here's what it is. It's a it's a
square kind of a scratch and sniff square with a
bunch of different little pellets like pills. They
pop out for each thing cilantro, lime, salt, all
all these things. It's like carry it with you. Yeah, and so if something if
something comes to the table at a restaurant with some shit that you don't
like in it, sprinkle that on, it's neutralized. Well, here's what I was
thinking is that maybe more realistically, it would have to be since
they're they're out gradients. There will have to be the opposite of the
gradients, so you have to go to you'd have to maybe they all look like the
same ones, but opposite and you'd have to go to kind of the ungrocery store
and go shopping and be like okay, I'm going to get all this stuff and then
you have to you'd have a whole separate pantry, a cantry full
gradients and it's like okay. Well, if I'm going to buy this ingredient, I
better buy the out gradient of it and then so it's like you can like they're
all the
yeah. I think so you maybe need a whole nother house. I keep tab with an
kitchen. You just came up with a
I'm thinking of a actual product that people can use people in need. I'm just
you want to fit it into actual physics? No, it doesn't know physics framework,
a scientifically designed pellet. Oh, I didn't realize
designs the pellets so that they are basically they're a salt kind of thing
and they are a salt. They're that it's mostly salt. It's or is that is
negative of what are our if somebody like cilantro, they do that. If you did
like the chemical breakdown of it is basically let's do the chemical.
Five hundred percent of your daily sodium in the chemical breakdown,
five hundred percent of your daily sodium intake and then whatever the
other flavor is chemical breakdown. I'm going to say it's going to be a lot of
chlorine hydrogen, hydrogen, hydrogen, which is a different hydrogen. I
thought I meant to say no, but you did actually you actually got the right
thing when you said it the first time, because again, this is scientifically
hydrogen high dry gun. No, I think we're going to put him in there.
What about
it doesn't matter what's in or on the point is that the point is that it
works better than
dehydrated. I do it in bore. I'm often making something. I accidentally add too
much mashed potato flavor or you mash something that you didn't mean to
masher and everything should be honorable. My God, why can't we in this
world undo our mistakes. Why do we have to bear our sins to the grave? We need
mistakes, mostly culture, yes,
let's get into it.
We need to all have click remotes. We do every last person on earth now that I
think one person should be in charge of the click remote and then that should be
kind of that's hard to decide. Everybody's going to think that they're
the one who should be the Sandler yeah. I mean that's why the audition process
excuse myself yeah I'm not I'll step back. I'll let somebody else handle it.
I'll do it. I will not do it. Maybe each group of people, each maybe friend trio
or something like that. I did not think he meant yeah, I mean each race needs
yes, and why would you jump to that one? What is there on each of the seven
continents? This is the
language for race.
What are you guys on today? Oh my Lord, I'm on each group of people, like each
white group of friends
has one person who has the remote for that group. Yeah, and then we don't and
then maybe there can be a king who can only everybody group. Yeah, but it can
only control the group. That's good. That's good and it could be families or
just friends. Yeah,
I guess it is a paternal remote because the dad has it in the movie. I never saw
that movie. You never seen. I saw click in the is it supposed to be more funny
or more emotional, more emotional. That's so crazy
because I always thought it was supposed to be simply an osmosis jones style
from Moses Jones is very scary yeah yeah, but the park here it's not really an
emotion. What is the dad here?
What what does he get a remote? What is dricks a
strip finger, a finger? Yeah, it's crazy finger. I thought it was strip finger
and I told my girl when I was watching that because I wanted to see it. I said
the villains name is strip finger.
he said the villains name was strep finger
as a name was. Did you ever did she at any point during the movie say I can't
say over and over it's going to is what are they going to say?
Strap finger, I think that dricks the idea that it's also just a
said that before on the show, but I just remember I think dricks
said again strip. I think he said something about I think I don't think
that you're that far off. I think you're just well. He has a finger, two things
up.
He definitely has a finger. He uses a finger. He has a finger. He has a
soul caliber. What's his name? Drax is the good guy. Drax dricks because it
was Ozzie and dricks. He's the good guy. Yeah, he's dricks. He's the good guy
dricks is the pill and he's
Drax is the guardian of the galaxy. Yeah, Drax is a guardian and groups a
tree, but so what's the evil guy is can't be stress any stress. He's not
strep because of that, can you Google it for he was if Bill Murray's character
was in the hospital like that, most of the video that's what I'm saying,
yeah, there's no way it's
it's finger. Yeah,
I will not it's I know it's a so that's what I okay, so can you Google strep
finger as well? What is he supposed to look at him? He looks like he does. Let
me tell you something about Ebola baby and he's an evil Ebola is a case of
and drift compared to me. This is the from the straight from the words of
thrax yeah. Hi, go ahead and this is the search ten seventy. I'm the admin of
this. I know I thought this is part of the thing. Search strap finger, though,
and see if that's a real ailment in a cartoon strap finger strap fingers
peeling strap finger infection. It is it's a rare cause of finger super
you can get stretch. You can get strength in your finger. What the fuck you
shouldn't pull up a picture of this on you. I want to see it, but
show it to us, but don't show the audience.
They're completely black fingers. Wow, don't those look
those look exactly like the horrible colas. They did that. That's crazy and
that's the what he does in osmosis Jones. No, I will say if he had strip now,
I'm a little more convinced that he was trapped
because that looks fucking serious. Yeah, that was very make a zit
remember. He has the zit isn't that Thrax's fault oils. No, it's like oils
and fried chicken. Yeah,
yeah, he does yeah. He's the fried chicken egg off the monkey exhibit at
the very beginning, yeah at the very floor
and that's how he even gets this guy in the first. That's how he gets to a
Stringer, which why we should do an osmosis Jones question next episode.
What can we do that as Moses Jones panel? Yeah, it's a very good movie. I like
that. I've seen I did. We watched that and recently yeah, we did. I watched it
recently a couple of years ago. I feel like we watched it somewhere. I watched
in a hotel. We watched it in a hotel. We was no, no, it was just me and my
beautiful girlfriend watching osmosis Jones. I said just wait, just wait baby,
I was waiting for a strap fingers.
- Strap fingers are coming right up.
- And if he had showed up, I mean,
that would have been disgusting.
It would have ruined the romantic mood between you two.
- Yeah.
- Damn, I hate strap finger right now.
- You kind of look like a pill that would be in--
- In Osmosis Jones, I look like an Osmosis Jones character.
- You do, I can see you in the steam room.
No, I just think you have big eyes,
like a cartoon character.
- Remember they had Kid Rock and Josie in that movie?
- And he says that line about, you know what,
or so statutory but I say it's mandatory.
Yeah.
Who said, Kid Rock says that or Joe C?
The little one.
Joe C says that.
Joe C.
I thought Joe said it.
And Osmosis Jones has the evilest smile in the world that's scary to everyone.
Joe C's on that album cover and he's holding a word, a poster, a sign.
Holding a word that says fresh eggs over Kid Rock's penis.
What does that mean?
His penis is fresh eggs?
He's got huevos.
His balls are fresh eggs. Yeah. Yeah. I thought I had to do with sperms.
Probably not a sperm is the exact opposite of a hangout. The sperm is an
ungritty in the south where kid rock is. Women in the south are so fucking
stupid. He's in from Detroit. Shit.
That's the Midwest. Fuck that might as well, but he likes hanging out in the
south. Yeah, so they welcomed him with open arms. That's why he went to the
south and he started confusing women by saying you want eggs and he would try to
serve them his hot balls on a plate.
He'd have them piping hot. It looks like two haggis under a plate. He'd cut a
hole under a piece of paper. I don't even know what the haggis looks like. What's
a haggis, you Harry Potter motherfucker? It's intestine. It's Scottish.
It's pretty good. Shut up. I've had it before. It's good. You are such a sucker.
I was fine with you until you said it's pretty good. No, you had tone. You are
the ultimate food sucker.
No, I'm not.
You are the food sucker.
That's a...
From now on, you are the food sucker.
That's a food from...
Any kind of weird...
I think that I have Scottish blood in me.
No, shut up.
No, you probably went over it.
Any kind of weird food...
Maybe you did.
Yeah, there's a little bit at the top.
Put a little blood in your top.
Like .01% or something?
Well, no, because I had like tested populations and like there's like Newcastle-upon-Tyne,
which is like right next to Scotland.
If you...
Oh, it's next to it.
If there is a weird food from another country...
That went there.
this guy's going to say no matter what he likes it. No, no matter what he will say
I don't mind if someone says they like food, but if they say it's actually
pretty good yeah, that's you like you. You are an Andrew Zimmer.
Yeah, but I'll eat bizarre foods. I don't care. You are a bizarre food. You
want to start eating. You want to hang out with Timone and Pumba. You want
green. You would hang out with you want green eggs and hen. You would hang out
you
green eggs. You would eat the big you would eat the big gray. We actually
all the time in the cafeteria. Did you all have that now? I'm on made green
eggs at ham one time. You never had that. We had that every year. You're lucky on
what day I don't even know. I have no clue. I don't know what on Saint Patrick
there was some kind of maybe it was a bad first day. Green milk. Yeah, mate
green milk. She made it. She made it actually just mixed it. She put she put
which is synthesize it actually yeah, but I do think that the reverence that you
have for odd foods is really disgusting and you need to get a grip and you just
figure out most shit. You don't like any food man like cheese and bread sign me
up. I should know he's the one who doesn't like he doesn't like any. I like
all food. I like the middle. I won't like making food. I like the middle amount of
yeah. I probably like the most food. The only food I don't like is stuff. That's
gross or outside of my comfort zone.
if
if Jesus, if Jesus too spicy, if bread is too crispy, stop making spicy cheese
like guys like I like spicy cheese, stop making it's actually if the mayonnaise
is too cold out the fridge, that is oh and it hurts your teeth.
It's so cold. I heard you God if the water if the water glass to fall and it
dribbles down your chin. No, no, no, I
doesn't matter. They are investigating the McChickening. There's two detectives.
It's the landlord with two detectives. There's two grizzly detectives outside
investigating a McChicken. They are detecting it. Yeah, and they're not
seeing much. That is incredible. Thank God. Thank God for our beautiful landlord.
Oh, we have a DNA sample that we can use, apparently. Oh, yeah. I found the
McChicken wrapper outside. Left a McChicken wrapper outside. And you hear
those sirens? It's happening, y'all. They're coming. They're arresting Patrick.
they're not arresting me for faking the entire McChicken thing from the start.
I was a fire truck from the jump. You were faking it. It could be the fire
truck. Yeah, because you're getting fired and you have to drive a truck.
Yeah, and you're a truck. I drive. Yeah, you don't know how to drive. Yeah,
have you? We went go karting with you, though, and you you fared all right.
That was fine. It's a go cart, though. It's basically the same exact thing.
It's not. It's the psychological thing that matters. Yeah, I can't. I can't
drive a car because of my name, which I found out recently. Every single person, if you
look up Patrick Doran, there is some incredible car related injury or crime that has happened.
There's an Irish traveler who was going around the UK doing a bunch of shit with cars. Then
there is that guy in Richmond, Virginia, who
rented a dump truck under the name Jacob Fury. Right, I remember that. Yeah,
and that is killed a baby and look at that. That's him.
I don't know that is killer. I don't know who that is, but
yeah, baby killer Patrick Doran. And if you look up that Patrick Doran, he
was wanted by US Marshals. If you look him up, if you look up fat
Patrick Doran on YouTube, he's there.
Oh, this looks like there's some kind of one lunch on and enjoy this some
pedophile guy is not a pedophile. This is the way. This is the guy who killed a
baby is not a guy who killed a dozen darn. I mean, it is the same name. It
looks like a type of guy would kill a baby. I think that guy looks handsome.
He looks like a shit bird. Shit head looks like a shit bird. Are they coming
in here? Chill out. You need to relax. You mean are they coming? There's what
What do you mean?
There's a door right there they could walk into.
Why would they walk in there?
There's nobody at the door.
She walked in like Kramer that one time.
Yeah that was the day that we moved in.
Yeah I know but what if she walks in and does it again?
She opens the door.
Oh no!
That would ruin everything.
We'd have to move.
No it would ruin the episode.
You're ruining the episode right now.
I'm not ruining the episode.
And I'm bringing it back.
Let's get that energy up.
I want to see you bounce off of that.
I'm not bouncing off of that.
I want to see you bounce it.
What's wrong with you? This McChicken thing has you in all out of sorts.
Yeah. I'm really not doing well. It must be the feng shui in here.
It definitely is the feng shui. It must be the feng shui in this room. It must be the feng shui.
It has to be. I'm so fucked, man. We should move the fucking table around.
Let's start the episode.
need to move the table around. You think so yeah, I think it's fine. I don't
think you should move the table. We can turn it. We can turn it at a crescent
moon shape. It is a crescent moon shape. It's not a little bit more. It's a half
moon shape. It's a half moon. We can make it a crescent and then change the
function. You want to make it a jigsaw and shave my friend.
I've heard of a waning moon, but that's a bit. I don't know the moon cycle. I
don't remember it. Basically, it starts out nothing and then it grows to full and
and it's small, yeah, and it goes away. If you watch it, the all if you watch it
twenty four hours a day, which is possible because sometimes it because
of traveling around the earth, the play, yes, yes, yes, if you watch it twenty
four hours a day, there is no moon phases man yeah, and that's when you
realize the moon phases are bone falses. Their moon falses is what I mean to say
and they don't exist. It's all just a moon. Just a trick of the light yeah. If
you saw a guy every couple of weeks and he was getting taller, would you say,
"Oh, this guy has different phases that he goes in"?
Well, if he got shorter again and then he repeated every month, I might say
that. Yeah. No. I would definitely say that. No, you wouldn't. I would totally
say that. The guy got taller every single day and then one day, just like,
one day, he gradually went down. Yeah, I'd be like, "Oh, he's waning today."
Yeah. He did not do that. Wayne, his name is Wayne. His name is not Wayne.
his name is not wax. Max is waxing Matt Max and Wayne. This is Max Wayne. Okay,
so today we decided to do a little bit of a study on Feng Shui, which if you
don't know is Chinese for water and wind. Is that true? Yeah. Oh man, I
learned that from my website. That makes a lot of sense. During my research,
I found plenty of wind references. Yeah. And double in water. We have all three
us always been so fascinated by feng shui and honestly since the beginning of the
podcast since 2018 we have been like waiting for a chance to really delve
into and be like can we get down to business and do the feng shui episode
yeah but it's tough it's tough because people don't want you to do it people
don't I mean I mean it is sacred knowledge there's feng shui masters yeah
I've learned but I also learned doing this I have a fucked up I had my house
has like complete anti feng shui feng shui is so fucked you're supposed to
I have the bed not looking at your door yeah, which is there's all sorts of
things. Do you know what's horrible about my house is feng shui right now is
that we switched. We switched our office in our living room and the new living
room is great and it's really cozy and nice, but the new office is the worst
room of all time and that's just bookcases in two desks and it's so bad
that we keep the lights off all day and it's in the middle of the house and it's
like it doesn't exist. It's like you're walking through a portal from the
kitchen. I'm going it's horrible funks bad, bad, what is really bad? What if
combine the two we're looking at getting a chair a living law let's change the
office to an arcade yeah yeah your girlfriend with a barcade barcade is not
a bad idea. Oh my I wanted to change it. What did I want to change it to that I
will there was trouble with maybe it was a room for building things. You didn't
put enough Godzilla stuff in a man cave. No, I was thinking more of like a
laboratory yeah nerd a man laboratory man tell me my slideshow I would like to
see this so let's see I went to a website called I don't remember what it
was called calm no mm-hmm very very funny really fucking I went to a website I
don't remember what it was called but it was a forum for funks way things and I
found some amazing questions that we are here to answer. Pizza slice shaped house
equals bad feng shui. This is it and it's also called geomancy I learned. Yes.
Geomancy slash feng shui. So someone named Tor says, "Hey all, I see a place. I liked it
very much. Me and hubby walked in, felt very comfortable and somehow we just kept
keep going there despite first time viewing. They reject our offer. Second
time viewing, we increased COV. Someone offered higher COV. Then somehow the
the higher C. O. V. Did not go through, so we still offered and they accepted.
Now it is transacted and it is mine, and I read here that those pizza slice
shaped layout is bad. Any way to remedy? What is C. O. V. Pepperonis?
So yeah, so okay, so how do you fix this? If you find yourself the proprietor
of a pizza shaped house, which way? Which way? Which way? Pizza shape going
vertical or the whole house is a pizza shape? I believe it's a pizza shaped
floor plan. Yeah, I think it's I think most feng shui. I don't think most
feng shui deals with the shape of the house from outside. I think it's
okay. The floor plan. Okay, so their house is like shaped like a pizza.
One of those like fun house tunnels that keeps going like this.
That's what I'm wondering. Yeah, I don't they included a floor. This is a
very old pose. It's 10 years old. So they included a picture, but it's gone
now. Oh, I couldn't see it, but I'd imagine it's something like
akin to the Oscar Meyer Wienermobile, where it is a pizza shaped house that
looks like the front door is on the pointy end or the crust. I would hope
that the front door is on the pointy end. The pointy end, it's going to be
this thin. Yeah, but that's your hallway.
How are you going to get through this little door, man? It's a point.
Hopefully, it would motivate you to lose some weight if you're a fat fatty.
To become as thin as nothing? I think that the person who buys a pizza slice
shape tells will need to lose some weight. True way, no matter where the
idea of buying a house that is a giant piece of pizza is looking at a
shaved as you wait.
Is this a bad for a
giant pizza house, but yeah, pepperonis round table, desk, ground chairs,
overhead, the round, the round, the plastic table, yes, yes, round everything
and then for the crust, a rug that is brown. Yeah,
yellow floors, yellow and I think you do just have to lean into the pizza theme
anchovies in the bath. What is your opinion for showcasing weapons in the
house? S Ryan yth he says single here will be getting my two room flat soon and
living alone. I fancy buying a Japanese katana sword, not from authentic sword
blacksmith's blade of is of course blunt in accordance. Some more of a sword like
object that is a low to display my bedroom as I really like the aesthetic.
I'm usually not a very superstitious person, but a weapon is still a weapon,
even though it is not authentic, I guess.
Would you advise someone to display weapons in the house,
especially the bedroom?
And if anyone knows if there is any temple
that can bless the sword to act as a deterrent
against malignant spiritual forces,
as in, and then some thing I don't know.
As I said, I'm not particularly superstitious,
but I could use all the spiritual help if I can.
Thanks in advance.
So you got a couple of replies here.
This person says, "Hmm, it depends on many factors.
If we speak about katanas,
I don't see anything wrong with doing it,
but if you want to showcase some fire guns, I don't think it's such a
good idea. Maybe if you have a collection of old and rare hunting guns,
I would understand it, but showcasing any other kind of gun, it's not okay.
I have five pistols, so do I have to showcase them in my living
room? Nah, I don't think it's a good idea. I even ordered a new
Sig Sauer. It is my sixth gun. I decided to buy it after reading
this Sig Sauer 1911 review. I mean, this gun seems to be precisely what
I want from a freaking pistol. And then this is the last comment here,
this guy, I think, just got confused about the topic and said, Hi, all I want to
choose a scope for hunting. I am considering various options, but I
decided to stop at the vortex. What do you say? The vortex? That's a brand. Oh,
but this guy, I thought he was saying he's I thought this is some feng shui
related thing. No, no, this guy does not look at he's the only everybody on this
forum is Singapore is from Singapore, except for this guy and his name is
Kerrigan. And I think this is the only comment he ever made. Huh? Wow. Help
does anyone know where to get a red roof,
maybe from a chest from a trove yeah yeah. How do you get a red ruby,
because apparently I bet if you finish a dungeon, there's a good oh yeah, I
would say go to your nearest dungeon. You may be a
kill everything in there yeah. See if there's a chest
lately. My HDB block underwent H, I P and the two toilets in each of the
six units could not be used for ten days, meaning weewee, poo-poo, slash washing have to go void
deck. Some rich ones moved out and stayed elsewhere temporary. Only then all neighbors discussed
about toilets and also appreciate the importance of toilets.
Is this about a boat?
No, this is just about something in their apartment.
Oh, okay.
Something about a toilet. I think I accidentally included this, but it was a funny comment.
Well, yeah, I guess 'cause feng shui is a lot about the different elements, I think. And
a toilet is a strong water element.
Weewee and poo-poo and washing.
It is the controller.
And there's a lot of posts about toilets on this forum.
Office desk near toilet.
So this is a bad, this is a dangerous situation.
This is not where you want to find yourself at any point in time,
is with your office desk near a toilet.
Hi everyone. Any advice?
Recently I joined a company. My desk is near to the toilet.
I can even hear the flushing sound.
I heard that this is bad from Feng Shui perspective.
Out of all the companies I had joined, this is the only company that I felt
that I have lose my confidence in my job and things has not been going so smoothly. I'm
not sure what whether I'm being superstitious or if it's true. Any advice? Thanks. The smell
or even the thought of the smelly, smelly yucks already bad lau la. If one of your colleague
didn't flush that day or have a bad stomach, you'll be the first hand filter. Superstitious
or not, you already lost half the battle. That's what I was going to say is I don't think you
you even need to bring Feng Shui into it to know that this is a
inauspicious setup. Yeah, which they all want to be either auspicious or
inauspicious when they're selecting. Mostly they want to be auspicious, I
think. But they always are talking about if something is auspicious or inauspicious
in this forum.
And then this guy says, "One way is to treat each flush as a nature waterfall
and psychologically win the war,"
which is genius. And people just have a positive mindset here. Look, far,
God wants to train you to be different and specializes in thus temporary
torture. You enjoy the torturing and become a great man in the coming. You
are not far from success. That is really deep yeah. It does say Leo at the end,
which I think is some kind of I think it's some kind of Singapore word for
like bro bro yeah. I think it's like Singaporean for bro yeah.
Harry Porter's magic
Kelly Manton says, so do you guys believe in Harry Porter's magic? In today's
world, is there such a thing as black magic? What do you guys think?
Yes. Yes. You think there is such a thing as Harry Porter's black magic? I'm
looking at a black magic device. What is it? Oh, right there. Oh, wow, that's
very interesting.
There could be something emitting off of that right now. Some kind of frequency or
field.
That scares me. Wi-Fi is a type of black magic. That is. Last night, oh my God,
I'm sorry to, I'm sorry to go off topic.
Last night I was playing video games. My wife is at my house with her sister,
okay? They're in the living room, I'm in the bedroom playing video games,
they're giggling, I think they're probably pillow fighting or mud wrestling
or something, until the internet cuts out.
They were playing with the cable.
They literally were playing with the cable!
Really?
Dude, I walk out, I say, "Did you guys turn off the internet?" She was like,
you know I
I didn't turn off the internet, but I unplugged the like cable cable because
we don't need it and I was like
I was like what she's like yeah, you know the like cable thing the thing that
goes into the TV. I just unplugged it because we don't we don't have a TV
that we don't have cable. I was like that's where the internet comes from.
She's like no, it's not it comes from the wi fi router and I had to explain to
a grown woman how the internet works and then she unplug it two more times. I
I think she did that on purpose to know do I mean they were giggling. It was
killing me. I literally I've never been so mad. I wanted to cave their heads
and yeah, yeah, and they made us lose games. So, but just sorry that's a
little that was and I blame bad feng shui. Yeah, both of that for making them
if this rock is the feng shui had been good. The cable would not have even been
in a place where it could be unplugged. Yeah, I agree. Wow. Well, okay, the
other one, the expert, they unplugged it once and then when they were trying to
plug it back in, they unplugged it again while trying to plug it back. They
they plugged it in and then try they and then they didn't they didn't they
didn't try to be lucy righty jump up with it. Yes, well yeah, but they were
trying to eat it. They thought that it was going to it was a straw yeah, but
then they put then they put a piece of we have like a big storage chest and
then they put it directly on top of it and unplugged it once more. So that was
my fucking Monday night. God, we've had such a feng shui experience these past,
however, of much. I have a couple more slides, so Harry Porter's magic, of
of course, is Feng Shui related. Geomancer's hand chopped off. What? So
this is a story, I won't get into the story,
but basically this is a guy who said, who's a geomancer, got his hand chopped
off in a vicious attack, and he admitted that he did not get any premonition that
something bad would happen. Wow. And the comments give him what for for this?
To tear him apart? Full loads of excuses, calling himself a Feng Shui expert and
not a fortune teller, can't even predict for himself how to help others. See this
is why I don't call myself a Feng Shui expert. Yeah, you never know when your
hand's going to get chopped off and people say, and you look like a bitch,
you look like a fucking bitch, as I get your hand chopped off. Yeah, if I got my
hand chopped off, man, man, that changed a lot of stuff in my life. Oh yeah, and
then also about half the stuff in my life, the last change, it would change
how I open doors forever. The last thing here is that there's a bunch of posts on
this forum that is really old, like from 2006 and stuff, that I've just been
completely deleted, but they have good names. But this is my favourite one. I
really wanted to read it, but it only had the title. It just says, "What the
Fish?"
The 16-year-old post called "What the Fish?" What the Fish? Wow! What the Fish?
But I honestly, I spent two or three hours going through this forum, and I
so much about fun. I thought function way was I honestly thought that it was
Pilates. I thought it was an exercise, but I knew what it was about Frazier
putting the couches and interesting way. It's pretty fun. Mine is kind of more
about how I kind of put in a bunch of function way rules and stuff that I
found from online. Okay, that maybe we could think about for the office or if
we're designing a house for us all to live together in the future that I know
we talked about maybe once before, but it's definitely in the cards. Maybe will
will happen. And it's funny to say cards, but we'll get to that
later. But so these are kind of just some some rule, feng shui
rules and ideas for whenever we're designing a space that we
can maybe build a house, a car, I'll pull up this, this will be
all these things that we can and they're from a bunch of
websites. And we can just talk about how we might implement
them and how it might be fun in our space. So first off,
doormats, feng shui rules for doormats. And so this is
something that we this is the first thing you got to think
about right now. Our doormat is just red. Yeah, so we're actually going to look
into this. All right. Well, we do have a doormat. Yeah,
welcome to the front entrance of your home with favorable colors, shapes and
accessories like doormats. Feng Shui rules suggest the right doormat will
give a boost of positive energy every time you or a guest crosses it to enter
your space, which makes sense to me. So door direction establishes mat design.
So does someone have a compass app on their phone? Does anyone still have the
compass done? Maybe I do, but I wanna figure out what direction our door faces
so we can figure out the door faces or I guess you can use New York style
thinking. I think it's facing north northeast. It looks northeast to me.
Yeah, because it's do it this way. Yeah, it's northeast 30 degrees. Alright,
so southwest or northeast, the earth element is in the southwest and northeast
earth's colors are sandy clay and soil shades as well as red, pink, yellow and
purple, none of the pastels. The best shape for the mat is square. We are
they're already that's a kind of a rectangle. It's okay, though it's okay,
but it could be, but we'd need to cut it down to a square. Also, we need to make
a door mat that is like a tooth tunes where you step on and it plays a song.
Yeah,
every time you walk in,
then let's see the black hat school of function, which I don't know what that
is. I put the same thing a black hat hacker yeah, so it's a bad guy teaches
and a black mat at the door that is about as wide as the door is a money magnet
and will energize your career. So there's something to think about to yeah,
maybe we change it. Then maybe we get another one. I don't really give a shit
about money. I don't I also I'm not sure if we should trust the black hat school
because they sound sound a little sinister. They sound kind of maybe I
don't agree with them
and also mind your message. So we're doing well here. Forget cutesy sayings
and monogram mats. No one's home. No rug rats allowed and be where the cat are
guaranteed to chase away positive chi or at least give it pause placing your name
or under initials underfoot just means people are stepping on or wiping their
dirty shoes on the Smith Jones residence every time they visit. Why would you
want that? So you have to find a good message. I guess that's not funny or has
your name in it and we have no something just like this. That's good monogram
dried on doormat yeah step here step here for positive chi could be good.
that seems like a no brainer. Actually, it is also a bullshit holiday mat.
That's good. You wipe your well. You don't really want to step in shit, so
maybe foot cleaner, shit eater, clean step here to clean shit,
parenthesis, meta meta, meta for a bullshit bullshit that doesn't get on
shoes. Yeah, and it's metaphorically and it doesn't get on your shoes
and it actually invites positive. Chee, how about just a picture of the
fucking Queen. Yes, that's not bad with her eyes X out
holiday match should be displayed with extreme care. No kitschy or cluttered
designs and removed promptly when the holiday period ends faded beachy flip
flops in February or happy holidays with poinsettias in July signals that you are
lazy or just don't care about the all important portal at the gate of your
home. That's not a good message for guests or good fortune. So switch them
out with the holidays. Okay, stop get rid of the Christmas one after Christmas.
stop with the Christopher that's important and also for here's to how to
get it auspicious.
What oh yeah, this is just what I wanted to read one lucky trick is to tuck red
ribbon tied feng shui coins. So they have a whole currency under the mat to
attract money to your door. Three coins are okay, but nine are better. So here's
what I've learned about this this coin thing. So you use its Chinese coins and
you use them like real coins, but you put you people put them under the door
ground, but they also when they tile their homes, they will put coins under
each tile.
So your house is full of fucking money. Well, that makes sense. It's a money
magnet. Yeah, we're no wait opposites attract. So wouldn't you want to have
opposite money?
Radiate version of here's the hard thing. Opposites attract shit under your
tiles, but birds of a feather
so long together, but wait. So how do we square one in the hand is worth and
wait square the circle?
What the fuck does that make sense? What is that? Square the circle. I think we're
finding out something about the world right now. So, okay, so a doormat is a
square and you put circles under it. Also, what about a doormat? What about
your doorman? Is that good feng shui or bad feng shui? An old doorman? It depends
on if he's nice or mean, I guess. An old doorman named Coin. An old doorman from
New Orleans named Coin. Yeah. Yeah. That's a good idea. Coin Crabtree. Yeah,
that's an amazing. That's a really good idea and that's got to be the luckiest
doorman you could have yeah hundred percent hundred percent.
You can function your bedroom for better sex. Okay, guys, I don't even want to
know about all this guys. I think we can maybe use this in the office. Okay, why
who's having sex in this office? If you play your cards right with what or who I
mean
with what with or I mean like you know,
but what can we do a piece of rope? So first of all, find the love a
relationship corner. So this is a map, which I guess I didn't know about this
before I was did research, but I guess each corner of everything
of the house has a different thing. So if you want to have sex, you should
always have it in the back right corner of your room, because that's the love
and marriage square. We are my radiator is we are in the wealth and prosperity
corner. We are in the wealth and prosperity corner right now, but we're
left, but I can't read these right. My what does that say Casper career?
That's the front door. No, the that's the your piano, okay, is in the career
Pat's desk is in
knowledge, so knowledge and self cultivation. That's pretty good, genius
and the bathroom is in the love and marriage
so I think we just figured out that's where it's going to go down. Huh, what
it it sexual center, it just a center. That's good. If on a long enough
timeline,
anything happens yeah. How if if somebody will have sex in this bathroom with
another person who works in this office, it's between the three of us.
I think that it would be probably
it would probably be Alex and Patrick. I think
why I could see that I see that the most yeah. That's why you guys wouldn't do it
at your house, because like a girlfriend's there yeah here is like a
it's like this is the this is broke back mountain yeah
and I think you guys could have like this street yeah down the street where
she can walk over whenever she wants. That's what happens in broke back
mountain. Yeah, that's true. She walks in
what the hell's
here fucking this guy also. Why are you dressed like a cowboy
guy can't read any of this? I did a or a small as they call it in fung shui. I
want to go here. This here's the nose, the big, not okay, the big nose for
having a sexual room, okay, fung shui do not have violent, aggressive, lonely or
desolate imagery in the bedroom. So it says no civil war scene, no painting of
the vase of dead flowers and no painting of a single person or a barren
landscape. Wow, so just keep that stuff out. You want to be sexy, no evil pain.
I saw another thing that was how to stop your partner from cheating on you using
fun. One of the biggest ones that they reiterated multiple times is don't have
two beds in your bed.
That's funny, because this one said try to have
doubles of everything in your bedroom to represent couples.
so there's a lot of contradiction and that's why we need a function of master
and the other big the other big nose filth and clutter being dirty with your
lover in the bed is fine, but dirt and clutter in your bedroom is a definite
love slayer and in the game of thrones way, not the beyonce way. Wow yeah, so
you're on fucking die yeah, okay, but then I think this next slide is what I
really wanted to talk about the most. No, this isn't this is just an extra
thing color theory within a chair context. So this is just a diagram. I
found that I thought was funny that if you're getting a gaming chair, this is
the colors you pick whether you wanted to be energetic and optimistic or calming
and creative. Now, this is specifically a website I found for there was a gaming
chair website that had a whole page about the fun way of the chairs. You know,
this is my gaming chair. This is the chair, the exact chair I use on my desk.
Really? Isn't that awful? That's horrid. Yeah, it's really horrid, but it is the
color is formal, stable and harmonious, though. Well, I actually have a brown
one. Okay, okay, that's not even on the chart yeah, but here we go. Whoa,
oh shit, this is actually incredible and this actually will change our lives
forever. Okay, because this is maybe so excited to go back to hit the casino
again. I have learned so much from what I needed. I went on like five websites
about this and this is we're going to have a gambling room in our house.
That's obvious, yeah, because we can also use this one. Oh, that's what you
need to use this extra room for in your yeah, yeah, but here we go.
According to function, you are also lucky if there's a small hill or a
mountain behind your structure. The land formation symbolizes the patronage of
the turtle. If you have the presence of a mountain on the left of your
structure, it means that a green dragon protects you. The turtle and the green
dragon can give you and the inhabitants of your structure great fortune and
prosperity. I knew that about the turtle, so we need to build our structure
near around and yeah, so or turtles live in the water under wait, we're going to
but we're going to have a gambling room in our home. Yeah, where or we could
just build a casino, but in here, what's the money come from? Who does it go to
wherever the money comes from in a casino? The bank, I guess yeah, but if
so, we I think that this is more useful for us to scope out lucky. Yeah, so
that's what that was. This started out as I was saying, okay, we can build a
gambling room, but this did turn into how a lot of these are how to win money
at a casino, because I think I think the only place that I can think of is is
like a casino Royale in whatever, Monty whatever, or Las Vegas has mountains.
Yeah, so Vegas, there you go. But it has to be to the left to get the Green
Dragon's protection. Is there a mountain or any kind of maybe like a butte or
something in Atlantic City? We could make one. There is no, no, it's as flat as
an apple. But we could lift it up with geographical, geological activity.
you say to decide and they could do some they do they do that in reforming
oceans, one of the oceans, which one the third one, the second one, no, they
build a mountain. They cause an earthquake
to be a drill yeah that basically can make a mountain. That's what I guess
mountains is you would get a drill underneath up. Well, if you just push it,
that's what if you push them together, I'm millions of fucking years yeah, but
we just do it fast with hyper power. Yeah, okay, anyway, here are a few
suggestions to attract feng shui luck for your game play. So here pay close
attention. Okay,
limit bathroom breaks before playing a game in a casino. Make sure that you go
to the bathroom first and do whatever is necessary to avoid breaks during your
game. This is to prevent your hands from getting wet because water is a symbol of
money. According to Chinese lore, you will lose your winnings. If you wash your
hands, if you need bathroom breaks in between games, try to stay dry and
anticipate nature calls. So what I'm getting here is it's not actually that
you need to not go to the bathroom. You just need to not wash your hands. If
don't wash your hands and don't get P on your finger and this goes those hands
dry fucking dealers, no lotion, no lotion at all and dealers stop washing
your hands yeah because you got that your wife. We need a fully drive. We
need a dehumidifier and in the casino to bring a dehumidifier pack in your
backpack. It's an amazing idea, okay, so then here's the other one where a ring
if you're going to plan a casino, make sure that you are wearing your ring on
the correct finger. Remember not to wear a ring on your thumb when going to
casinos, because it symbolizes letting go of success and losing all your wealth
on your thumb. It is a really dangerous thing to symbolize. Yeah, you know
that's all. I think all your love that's maybe the worst possible. They're
going to instantly
you must wear a jade ring on your left hand. If you're a woman and your right
hand, if you're a man, so we got to get some jade rings to not wear on our thumb.
Yeah,
invite a pregnant friend. Pregnant women attract good luck for gamblers,
according to Chinese beliefs. Even if there's a pregnant stranger standing
behind you to watch the game, make sure that she stays and lets you win. Just
making her like
follow you around, putting a leash on her yeah, but so yeah as many pregnant
women as possible are going to up your luck. Factor next time your your friend
tells you that she's pregnant, you say oh my God, but you know you're going to
Vegas.
Yeah,
One last dry, dry trip to Las Vegas.
Well, now you can get fucked up.
Just don't wash your hands.
Just getting her fucked up on all her weird
pregnancy craving foods,
like putting pickles in peanut butter sandwiches.
Damn.
All that pregnant food sounds good to me.
My mom still orders a fucking chicken parm sub
with pickles and mayo on it.
'Cause I got her fucking pregnant.
'Cause the pregnant thing.
Yeah, 'cause I got her pregnant.
She did that at a real Italian place one time
when she got they looked at her like she was the stupidest person. She's
pregnant with my son and I'm going to name him Patrick. No, yeah, you won't
have a son named Patrick. I think that's my last. If you had a kid and you named
him Patrick, that would not even be an honour.
Whoa, okay, there goes my name idea. I'm sorry. It was either
nice try. My son's name will be norm CK Carlin
Murphy changing it just to Patrice. You had
top of the list and right under it with the trees. You're just like
I was going to have Timothy Chalamet, Fetter, yes, and Sir Sir Ronan Fetter
and my daughter, Amy Wong, Heidecker,
Jas
my daughter,
fucking
Super Deluxe, my daughter,
Sam, Sam Kitteson, the insult comic dog, my kid,
Super Deluxe Doran, Bart Homer Fetter, yeah, this is my daughter, Jashua. Is
your son coming to the party? Which one funny or die?
Yeah, they're both coming. All right, this next one, so
you guys know about like a non standard McDonald's like the you know this one
here that shaped like a like a church or something and then this one on the
what the right that shaped like a bank. It's like a government one on the left
the one on the left is a church yeah. That's not a church. It looks like a
church.
That's like a town hall. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
zoo. No, that one's a church and then the other one looks like a
bank. So then I saw I looked up the I was trying to find the
fung shui of McDonald's, maybe an article talking about it. But
there was a McDonald's in Hacienda Heights, I think it's
somewhere in LA, suburban LA, that remodeled their whole
fucking place under the principles they got a consultant
in. They they made it look like this. It looks incredible. This
this is a function. McDonald. This is like a normal McDonald. This looks like
the McDonald's looks like the Burger King. They stop at on the mega bus.
No, no, look at those red table. Okay, you're going to see more photos. You're
going to see more photos. The colors are a little different, but this is I would
not Cameron. There is a waterfall in here where you'll see just be patient.
The ancient Chinese practice of function is designed to provide people with a
sense of serenity. A McDonald's in suburban Los Angeles has recently been
remodel to reflect the principles of function way. There are waterfalls,
wooden ceilings and a specially designed entryway. The doors don't align, so we
confuse the evil spirits and they stay out and we keep the good spirits in, says
Mark Brownstein, the restaurant's owner and operator.
If you look up McDonald's fight on YouTube, millions of results, none of
them at this McDonald's. That is so true. Can I say something really quickly that
I learned about function way, which is when you move, you're supposed to be
you're supposed to do something called a door blessing when you move into a new
place where you roll a pineapple all around the apartment. Wow. And if you do
it wrong, you will get 100% a demon living in your apartment. It happened.
That's scary. The story that I read and a little girl said, where's my big
sister? And they said, you don't have a big sister. She said, yeah, she walks
around every single night in a white dress. That's scary as fuck. It is scary.
Can I say something about this slide too? Yeah. How pissed off would you be if
you were a good spirit and you you they trapped you in a McDonald
keep the goods, the evil spirits out that keep the good spirit yeah, because
in you, I guess I'll go in here. This is yeah this room looks like it is
amazing. I
finally
God fucking damn it
Brownstein, who runs twenty three southern California McDonald says the
redesign was all about rejuvenating slumping sales. When he looked at the
most recent census data, he saw that the Asian population in the area had grown
to nearly 40%. We wanted to make this story invited to everyone, but
particularly the large and growing Asian population in this area. He says,
sitting in earth in an earth tone booth next to a waterfall.
This is just a white dude that's like, Hey, there's a lot of fucking Asian
people in this town. We're going to function. We should make McDonald's a
function way. Enviro started from the waterfall and then he found out there's
something called function. Yeah, but look at this. Look at that beautiful make
look at how beautiful this looks. That picture is nice. It looks incredible. I
actually think that casino is probably what looking at this. It does look like
it looks like a latex. They literally do really. They actually do yeah. I make
because well it's because it literally they do it because they're a bunch of
like high rollers from China that they want to come and they want them to be
like oh it's look it's not. I read a whole interview with it was really funny.
it's like an interview with like this, like high roller Chinese gambler guy,
who's like their interview and be like. So what do you think about these
casinos like using feng shui to attract more like high profile Asian gamblers
and he's like, you know, I don't care at all, but it looks nice. Yeah,
he's right, he's completely that's probably why casinos feel so amazing to
be yeah, they're literally the peak of fun. I thought it's because they were
pumping some like well, they actually I would say they use black hat feng shui,
because if you read, I did read a lot about this people who feng shui experts
don't like casinos because they have no windows. It's like fake sunlight,
which is evil and it's like the function is in service of trapping you,
but they do you. I think they use evil function to trap you in there. A
trapped good spirit. Whenever I go to the encore because I'm leaving with
an uneven wallet, yeah, because I left my credit cards in the hotel room,
but I kept all of my grocery store rewards cards. The other half of my
wallet for all the suggestions, the lose made there was one thing they
couldn't change the menu. Just like all McDonald's, this one serves up artery clogging fries, Big
Macs and milkshakes, which raises the inevitable question, how does one, how often does the
Grand Master chow down at the Golden Arches? Depends, he said, when I'm very busy and very
hungry sometimes I need to eat. So there are these two, they consulted these like, they
are Grand Masters of Feng Shui in Los Angeles.
FSM's.
Yeah, Jenny Liu and her dad.
I don't remember the dad's name.
Jenny Liu suggests that the feng shui somehow reduces the negative aspects of greasy processed
food.
Feng shui is about the laws of nature, so in that way it's a counter, she said, adding
when you're in an environment that's wonderful and peaceful and soothing, your whole mindset
relaxes.
You eat food slowly and don't rush and stuff your face.
The mental is very important, her father agrees.
That part is stronger than the poison food.
Wow.
He's calling the fucking food poison.
Mind over matter.
Oh, then this one, a woman named Tina Turner was in there eating a double cheeseburger
and fries during her lunch hour.
Then this is what, this is like the end of the article.
Mark Brownstein says that he sees nothing peculiar about blending fast food and feng shui.
It's not ironic at all, he said.
One more thing.
Did he say that like this?
It's not ironic at all.
Maybe.
One more thing.
Don't call it fast food.
The food isn't fast. The food appears quickly, but that's service," he said,
adding, "We're willing to do this to say to the community, 'We're going to build
a store that really stands out. That's just good business sense.'" And then
here's just like, that's the waterfall. This is beautiful. It's incredible,
right? I want to eat. Yeah. And look at this picture that I found in the
article. Wow, it's so small. That's how big it was. Look at how big...
That's actual size? Yeah, look at that. Oh, it's got bamboo. So this is
that's what it looks like when you walk in. So describe it. It's got bamboo on
the left and then, like, another plant there. It's, like, circular. There's a
lot of tiles with a path. Yeah, tiles with a path, like, a lot of beautiful
looking stuff. And you know there's money under all those tiles. Oh,
absolutely. We break in, we steal all the tile money. And then this next slide
here is a review from Angelica Cerna
that says, "Aleah is black."
four four stars. It's incredible and you have to guess that it may be a Leah
somebody. So you maybe works there or maybe the singer. I don't know. Yeah, I
mean, whatever the original, I guess, yeah, it's translated by Google. It says
a Leah is black and then the original says Elijah Serna. Oh, it was her name.
She was trying to put her name. Oh,
yeah, then look at these photos here. Look there's a juvie. If you can zoom in
here, there's a man who's astounded by the beauty of this McDonald's. He's
covering his eyes up
with a receipt, with a receipt, and then this next photo here, just pure album
cover vibes. Look at that. This is album cover. That is one of the most
beautiful McDonald's photos I've ever seen, and then this one is
the board for employee shout outs, and it is completely empty.
well, that's not functuated to put people's faces. Yeah, I agree. Yeah,
exactly it's like wrapping them. Yeah, exactly. It's a
here's some more photos. Here's a guy in a booth and then here's another photo
of the booth is, but I have some bad news. What is it? What is it? I think
they remodeled the McDonald's. I think they remodeled it based on photos. I
found on the same. Well, this is an old one.
Most of the function way stuff is, I think, gone.
that's what it looks like in twenty twenty two. I think those two glass
things right there. It looks like just a brand new normal McDonald's. I think
that those two glass things right there are where the waterfalls used to be.
Yeah, I think you're right, because usually I was when you showed the
waterfall, I was thinking that's usually where the glass thing is. Exactly,
yeah. Then this next one here, they put the kiosks in. Kiosks, bad feng shui.
Sliding automatic doors. Yeah, it's terrible, terrible feng shui. And then I
I was looking up trying to confirm whether or not there was a remodel.
Thomas M says, obviously a recent remodel and then there was something
disgusting in the bathroom. Poo. I think it was due.
But again, bathroom, water, feng shui, it's all connected. It's all connected.
Wait, go back. This guy ends it in a perfect way. Had to ask for a
drink cup. Next. That is so funny to say about at the end of your
McDonald's. Next. Next McDonald's. Onto the next one.
I made it too small. My local McDonald's. It's nice since the remodel that was in
2050 or five years ago, 2015. Some homeless that hang out there, blah, blah,
blah. And then Dan Man said, McDonald's socks, no more food from there.
But yeah, so all of that stuff about the feng shui, they got rid of it,
complete and total remodel, right? Getting rid of every single, well, not
every single, but you know, changing, changing a lot of the feng shui in
there, right? So that was five years ago. Five years ago was 2019, right? Close. 2018. Really,
really close. 2018. I thought I'm still writing 2022 on all my checks. Well, that would make
it way wronger. So, okay. Okay. So that actually makes sense. So it was five years ago was
20. That does actually make sense. Because in 2019, employees were hospitalized with mysterious
symptoms at the Hacienda Heights McDonald's.
Holy shit.
At the Feng Shui McDonald's.
After it was remodeled?
Firefighters have found, after the remodel, firefighters have found no abnormal readings
after a carbon monoxide detector was triggered at a McDonald's on Monday.
Hazmat techs with the LA County Fire Department determined air saturation is normal inside
the McDonald's at the one, I'm not reading that, the alarm may be malfunctioning.
Despite that, three employees experienced symptoms.
three employees reportedly experienced minor headaches and will be hospitalized.
Wait. So there was a feng shui attack.
Yeah. Full feng shui.
Wow.
Full feng shui. They get rid of every single thing. And then the carbon
monoxide detector goes fucking crazy. Three employees are hospitalized.
But no carbon monoxide.
Wow.
That's insane.
And this was in December of 2019. So this could be something else that
happened around that time. No, I don't think so, but there was a because no,
because there was a function way. It was a mysterious disease. There was a
function way change and it was a carbon clear carbon monoxide attack.
Well, no, that is crazy. No, it means a
pure energy
energy, but not carbon got their casper tail stuck into the car. I got sucked in
no, no, no, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
yeah, came back, he dissipated, turned in a mist and then people started
breathing it in and went, oh, I have ghost headache, yeah, yeah, and maybe
the only way that they could cure that would be with my invention I mentioned
earlier, the flower that puts food in the air, exactly, that's a shit invention,
exactly, well, I guess the moral, the moral here
is that once your feng shui is perfect,
do not fuck with it, no, fuck with it, do not change it, do not mess with feng
don't make a room where the lights are off all the most powerful thing in the
world, the universe, the universe, the the observable and unobservable. It's
more powerful. I
don't want to talk about this. I don't want to get into details. Okay, but I
thought about it. Okay, no, I want to very quickly say there is don't look
this up. There is feng shui rituals and practices that you can do
to assassinate somebody. I think that's a Chuck Palahniuk story. It's true. It's
a hundred percent true. Yeah, I thought that's in one of his I from reading
that in high school or something. It talks about it. I thought that shit was
so cool. It's true. It's I found it from that. You are scaring me right now.
And it's a hundred percent true. You are so scary. The fuck out of me right now.
Sure, it's in the book. It's in the short story about foot massage. Yeah,
wow, but it is true, but crazy. We won't get into that. We won't get into what
we will get into is the some fucking trouble.
Poop dot com slash shows. Pull it up. We talked about it. The video flopped.
The video was the video.
The video. We don't have to worry about the flop all the fucking time.
Make another video, man. And you can't live another life. So you can't live
another life. Go buy tickets. It's going to be sketch comedy. It's going to be a
fun show. We're doing it at Littlefield with Home Planet who make the videos
that you love Alex and Joe. We're doing it with Pierce as well, who you also like and
you can buy a ticket right here at swagcoop.com/shows. It's July 14th. It's going to be a lot of
fun. We're going to be writing a lot of fun crap. There's going to be some videos. I've
already written so much and maybe a lot of it won't make it in. We're going to go ahead
and buy 10 tickets right now that you can't have. That's called scarcity. Maybe we do
a
All right, well, that makes them have to buy another ticket. Bye bye bye
happy
no, it's a library. I was going to say laundromat. It's a library. That's
next to a laundromat. Whoa, that's already good and I already like this
the the lady who works at the laundromat closes up the closes up shop puts a
shirt on a hanger and then walks out, walks into the library.
So then she walks up to the, it's clear that she has a rapport with the
librarian. She's talking, she walks in. I love that. Is it a librarian girl or
boy? Hey, Janice. Oh, hey, Bernice.
Hey, what have you... You clean a lot of clothes today?
No. I like that. Just one shirt today.
And I hung it up before I left.
oh all right.
Are you here to get a book? No, I'm here to return my book. Okay, what book is
your
no more suffocation? Oh wow, okay, no, no, no, because I said laundromat,
because then that could be racist coded. No fifty shades of gray. Okay, okay, now
she's returning now. Do you have the gray and then Bernice picks it up and
goes who and she goes yep and then suddenly a man in a trench coat and a
cat runs in and slits her throat and she falls on the floor and screams and
grabs her throat. Which one? Bernays or Janice? Both. Her name is not Bernays.
It's not like a meal. It's the laundromat lady gets killed and then
cut. And then theme song. And then the rest of the episode. What in the, what
in the, what is going on in this library? How the hell did this happen? I've
of a bookish demeanor but I've never seen something...
A bookish murderer.
Murderer.
I'm a murderer.
But when it comes to this criminal there's no one demeanor.
This is demeanor's criminal.