All right, where are you saying Pat and we're starting nothing, maybe boost it
up a little bit. Is this better? I'll just
wait, I do that talk test your audio. You have a cable. You can't do that. You
can't do that. It's a do that you're plugged in. I don't think anybody can
do that at all yeah. This is a this is a flop. This is an insta flop insta flop
insta. You are flopping the first action you decided to
do in the new office is you insta flopped you're not even on camera. I
don't think no you are you're on the very what are we going to do on the edge
buddy? You are on the edge. What are we going to do?
This is nothing you can't be hurt. We're not going to include that on the edit.
We're not including that. There's no fucking way. We're including that because
We have a microphone. Just talking to the microphone. I understand, man. You're upset about the
TV writer strike.
Yeah. I'm really upset about the writer strike because I just submitted.
Think about all the shows we're about to lose, man.
I just submitted. I'm not kidding. I just submitted a packet to a show and...
Abbott Elementary.
No, no, no. The late, late show with James Corden.
I don't really know.
And now because of the strike, that show is gone.
Yeah. It's tough for me because I kind of am running out of people now who I can send
in my adventure time spec scripts to yeah, I kind of just have to send it to my
parents. I just send them to everybody in the industry. I don't really want to
be seen as a scab. You don't get
you don't get his newsletter. Is it? No, no, I haven't walked. I send it to you.
Yeah, he has a lot of different males. Caleb pretty kitty at Gmail right. That
is not my email address. You're making me sound gay on on TV. Email. No,
I've been sending my there's a heavy echo in here. That's okay. That's fine.
there's nothing we can do about it. Yeah, we have a new office. Yeah, oh yeah,
and can I say can I just I want to say something really quick, but it's a
message to everyone who fell for my hashtag hashtag one last episode,
hashtag Patrick forever. I don't think anybody actually somebody who felt
helpful who fell for that yeah. When the hell are you going to learn that I'm a
master troll? Yeah, when are you going to figure it out? That is true.
Why are you still believing a single word? I fucking say, how have you not
gotten it through your thick skull that this guy is a troll master,
unparalleled troll. They're calling... You know the troll face was based on
Cameron's face, right? Make the face right now.
See? It looks just like him. It actually kinda does. You do look trollish.
Yeah. I would say you look ugly like a troll. You just look so
ugly today. You were saying I looked ugly earlier too.
You just look fucking terrible today. Don't tell him he looks terrible.
I woke up. Say it behind his back like a man. I just don't like how you look today and I
really don't want to. I didn't really take care of my appearance at all today. I kind
of woke up and I saw your text that said I'm going into the new office and I got so excited
that I just... No makeup. Yeah. No makeup. See I really never knew how much the makeup
did for you until you walked in. Yeah, it's pretty important for me. And you were kind
of the reverse. You know how pregnant people are glowing? Yeah. You were kind of sucking
the light out of everywhere you go today. You don't really glow like when you're, like
you have makeup on you don't really glow. It's more of like a sheen. You know when you leave
ham out? No. No, I've never. First of all, it lost me. When you leave ham out for too
long. You know when you leave meat out for too long. When you leave meat out at a barbecue
or like Christmas day.
Oh and it gets kind of waxy so it's looking like fake food.
It gets that sheen on it.
That's kind of like what you have.
I think that's just the fat solidifying a little bit.
Yeah and his fat has solidified all over his body.
Yeah.
I can't even be mean with her.
Laughing immediately.
Because you think it's so funny.
No I don't.
I want people to know I'm joking so I laugh.
So I can't even finish the joke.
It's okay guys I look like shit today.
you just look not like shit, just normal ugly like shit, just like I feel like
normally when I walk when you come into the room, I think a lot about if I saw
you on the street and I didn't know you when you when I with a test is if you
walked by me,
am I turning that I'm coughing and look at and turning my head and do you go
like that's on the rear yeah
and just look right behind me.
So am I doing that
thing most of the time most of the time I say yes, but if you walk by me today
looking how you looked and you had a cup of coffee, I'd probably put change in it.
That's how I tell you. Can I tell you why? Why? Why? Because I couldn't sleep
last night because I was too excited about our new office. It is very I live
down the street from here. If anyone knows, I was excited for the new or for
the writer's strike because because it's kind of the same. It was the same day as
us getting the office. Yeah. And we have insider Intel. Basically, I was like
happening for me. It was like, you know, we're working hard moving stuff, getting
all tired out. I get home. I'm basically lying on the couch in my undies on my
iPad, playing Temple Run to type thing. And I see pop up on my buddies,
Instagram stories on my buddies. Yeah, all my buddies on my buddies. They're
all saying solidarity strike. We don't want to work. And I think I'm so fucking
retired and yet I had to get up, go outside with a picket sign right now
and knock on my neighbor's door. That's right. We gotta go to the funny
mind. What are you doing? What are you like going up to every single
neighbor in my building and say, by the way, what are you doing for the
strike? I'm saying I need your signature on this birthday card. Yes,
but it's not a birthday card. These TV writers, I don't think people realize
how bad it got recently. These TV writers have been living on $6,000 a
week.
What? Can you believe? That's horrible. How the fuck are you living on that?
and they have to they have to spend the time and like emotional wavelength to
to write Barry. Yes, Dan, they only consider both. They have to consider
basically, they can only buy six Mac books a week. Yes, they can only buy
six. How are you dude?
Okay,
okay, so that's why we're striking guys, because we are striking for a living
wage of ten thousand dollars a week minimum for every television writer who
nights on a show about depression. Yes, dude, I will be so happy right now
teenagers the show, which is another show. I submitted a packet for yeah,
because I you guys know I'm trying to break into the industry. Yeah, I've
got a press teenagers. You want to work with teens in new slang word. I slang
word is for industry, so for industry and it's indo and you basically it's
like in that's what we are now. It's also I'm realizing right now. People
all that people call weed that in smoking in oh, but that's what the I
thought. No, that's the bike trick. I don't know that's an end. Oh yeah, yeah,
I know what the bike trick you're talking about. I think in is the
the
term to in terms because it's so smart. Yeah, I think they're going to make a
Star Wars movie named that one anymore. Yeah, who's going to write these movies
man, I'll do it. I mean I honestly
immediately, I will if I can go in to the these striking workers jobs and I can
go in in a mask with a voice box to this guy's my voice, a strider,
uh-huh, whoa rider, oh my like the mass magician and writers would get so mad
at you, but they don't know who I because you would give up the tricks
like the Harmon circle. Yeah, I would tell them all about the harm.
and they go
and not talk about the Harman circle.
You okay, I'm crying, I'm telling people all about the Harmon circle. I'm
telling them how to draw in Cal art style. I'm releasing I'm releasing a
hundred page coloring books of Cal art style that teach people how to draw for
the crime of releasing the Harmon circle to normies.
you have been sentenced to one hundred hours of the big bang theory. You
you have been sent us to one hundred hours at a coffee shop only drinking
coffee, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
and everyone sees your way. That's actually a really great, but there's
trickle down effects to this whole writer's strike. Yeah, coffee shops,
who's going to go there? Oh, my God, I can actually go to a coffee shop. Yeah,
I'm going to see and I
can't even walk into it. I know a shop is the
they're going to be there to typewriters. Well, art is there with their easels
and stuff. Okay, here's my prediction. Here's my prediction. I think artists
are going on strike soon. No painters that would actually all because of AI
they're going on strike because they don't want a I that would take my heart.
I think that we will see as TV goes down. We will see art make a return.
that's a really good point because and the art art has been let's be real
usurp by television. Yeah, in the last I mean, I know that's kind of a car. I
know carlin's been there a thousand times. Yeah, but yeah, can I actually
say the writer that I just that I just thought about just now is that you know,
so these writers are going on strike right, you know, who never went on strike
who
painters like Pablo Picasso, yeah, inventors like Leonardo da Vinci, yes,
flyers like Amelia Earhart, one of the best people. These like these don't go
on strike and who are they? They got their pictures and books on. Hey, here's
a question. Yeah.
Are the guys at the news going on strike? I hope and they're going to stop
writing this bullshit. Oh my God, that's right, because guess what I would love
the season of twenty twenty three. That's right. Can you I kind of feel
like tomorrow or today we're going to wake up. We already did, but
today. Today we're going to wake up in the area. You're going to say, well,
it's going to be guys, the entire Ukraine and Russia war is officially on strike
because nobody we don't have anybody to write it. Honestly, I feel like maybe
the news writers went on strike in twenty sixteen and twenty twenty. Yeah,
and I know what I best I bet also is not going to happen this year. While the
strike is going on mass shootings. Yeah, well, here here's the thing. Here's a
thought TV shows cause it to here is how selfish this writer's strike is what on
who's part about the writers, right? Yeah, yeah, okay. Think about how hard it is
for our boys in uniform boots on the ground over in Ukraine right now.
And they can't we got about a million. They cannot watch Ted Lasso on Apple TV
in the bunker right now. Well, yeah, that's the thing. They get back to watch
reruns, but no new season. They get back from their fucking pumping lead into
people's animals all day on farms all over the country and then they get back
to their hole and they sit down. They said, I just want to watch a brand new
episode of something. Oh my God, it's a rerun. Turn the gun. No, you're
pointing a gun directly into a child, a baby's mouth, but then you turn it this
way and you blow your head off. Meanwhile, the Russians, they're over
there. They're also like, oh my God, show every day. Well, no, they're like,
I want to watch a new show. I want to watch a brand new episode. They load up
up there like Russia plus or whatever they have over there. They see a
million, they see a million new episodes of all their shows, but they're like, I
can't watch this because I will never cross a picket line. These are written by
Scabs.
See, I think that the Russians probably are, because they're communist piece of
shit, they probably like reruns. They probably like reruns and they, you know
what they really love, those commie fucks, they love strikes. Yeah, true. Actually,
wait, strikes are fucking commie bullshit. This is the wackest TV era we've had.
this year.
Now I'm thinking about a soldier who just wants to unwind and watch Ted Lasso. He
sees a new episode, although normal writers are on strike. So we got these
scab writers coming. They don't know anything about the show, anything about
the characters. So this soldier, he's trying to escape his life of bloodshed
and destruction. He turns on Ted Lasso. He's like, I just want to watch some
wholesome soccer. This episode, Ted Lasso is a soldier and he's getting shot at
because the people writing it now, they don't know what the fuck the show's
about. They're going to hire these Ted Lasso, these scab writers, and you're
I'm going to turn on Ted Lasso. Ted Lasso is going to be talking like, "Duh, duh, I don't
know what to talk about. I guess I'll play soccer. I don't know what to say. I don't
know what to say anymore. I don't know what's happening around me. I guess I'll watch a
rerun."
He watches Ted Lasso in his show.
Exactly.
Because now, because the writers strike, they can only get meta.
These damn scab writers. We got to make the episodes. We got to fulfill the contracts,
but they keep writing, "Duh, D-U-H-H-H."
Yeah, because these scabs, they are not the smartest people. No, dude.
They're hiring. That's the double-edged sword of this writer's strike. You think,
"Oh my God, all these old writers who are writing all this crap are getting out.
We're going to get all these new brilliant writers who are not afraid,
who are not afraid." Who are like, "Oh, I bet I could write that." Yeah,
and then they're going to be in there. Yeah, it's going to be just these guys
on the roofing season. Yeah. And all the jokes are like, "Oh, yeah,
this guy used like this type of wrench yeah,
use the wrong red. That's how that movie Idiocracy got me yeah. That was during
the last writer strike. It was to be about a bunch of smart guys, but then a
bunch of
not very smart people who weren't professional writers in the guild. You
know, how do you get into that? You got to be part of the gill? I don't know
deal the guild. I think you have to do five quests yeah up here to up your
level before they let you in. You have to up your reputation level. I heard that you
can like just kill indiscriminately. You can kill indiscriminately? And then if you kill
the right person, they'll let you in. Yeah, I think you need to collect five goblin skins.
What happens is you answer that little kid's prayer and you kill the lady at the orphanage
and then they bring you into the writer's guild. What the fuck are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about. The little kids prayer. No, no. All right,
the little kids prayer. He was at the orphanage in what since Skyrim thing.
Oh yeah, that seems I don't even think that's like one of the main dark
brotherhood quest. I thought you guys would get that. I thought you guys were
evil like me. I'm not a 13 year old game. That's the no, it's a new game.
They updated every week. That is true with mods. You know, they are adding
artificial intelligence to Skyrim. I saw that they actually are. Yeah, you can.
you can put in vr you can talk to the people and say what's your favorite part
of skyro
and they go, but I hate the dragon. No, but they don't they don't do the like
accents or anything. It's like pure text to speech voice. Oh really, I like the
river. It's really good. Riverwood is cool. Yeah, I need to replace sky. I
I haven't played one of those games in a long time. I replayed it. The thought of playing
any game like that is so boring to me. I hate Skyrim. That's insane. I really hate Skyrim.
I don't need it. My life is amazing. I don't want to escape. The idea of escaping is fearful
to me. To me, a video game, it's toil. Yeah. You have to labor. Also, Skyrim, I don't want
to deal with bandits, and I don't want to have the idea... There's a guild that you
can join up with the bandits. Thieves Guild. I don't want to join up with bandits. I want
I'm gonna be a good man. I joined up with the thieves guild. You would I have not
complete. I'm still playing skateboarder. Of course he joined up with the thieves
guild. Yeah, he's you know he likes graph and he has friends that do graph and
writing. I know and he talked about this to me yesterday like it wasn't like I
wasn't wearing a wire and leaning in directly into his face. I said all of
their names and I said all their real legal names. Their names are all fucking
Sputnik and Bozo. I don't fuck these guys.
These guys are clowns. They're not. They are clowns. They're actually street
artists. How would they feel if I killed their fucking mom and then did that shit
on top of their coffin? Do you think they'd think that was cool? That was
fresh? If you were a good writer. Do you think that they'd think that was ill?
And maybe if you were a good writer and you wrote a decent RIP. There's no such
R.I.P.
That's a decent R.I.P.
R.I.P. and
decent king on it.
I think that you, you know what you should get into instead.
I would be a toy if I wrote.
You're a toy right now.
You are my toy.
No.
Here's a, here's a thing.
Writers strike.
How about all these writers go on strike?
BMX, skateboarding,
skiing,
snowboarding,
graffiti, horseback riding,
horseback riding, X Games strike.
X Games horseback riding.
We get the X Games to strike so that guys like me can join up. I get the gold
because there's no one else is skating anymore.
Is there gold in X Games?
You get a silver still.
I would maybe get the silver.
You get the silver if we know no one is competing.
If I was competing at a skate...
We can't just give you the gold.
Yeah, I cannot.
Put your snowman down the fucking thing.
I cannot flip my board for crap.
Do you think that if how...
We have one try and you go on the mega ramp, do you think you would die?
you don't get any warmups, no practices.
You have to do... Would you die? Can you warm up on a different ramp?
You can warm up on the... Wait, wait, who's mega ramp?
On a miniature ramp. Who's mega ramp? The one from the X Games.
The one from the X Games? Yeah. The big one that people get hurt on.
The Jake Brown 2007... 2007 Jake Brown
incident, 2007 writers strike.
Oh! We didn't know. We had nothing
interesting to put on TV. What do we do? We make this Australian guy get his fucking kidneys
destroyed because he fell like 32 feet to the ground.
But which really was his fault. He should have slowed.
Yeah. Well, he was going for like a 540 or something.
Yeah. If I was on the X Games...
$540 copay at the hospital.
Yeah. Well, he's Australian. They pay for health care down there or something, right?
I would just try and go as high up in the air as possible and I wouldn't worry about
what was going to happen after. I'd try to go a thousand feet up in the air and that would
would be like I'm just going to figure out how to land later. I would put I
would put jets on the back of my skateboard. Yeah, I would be I'd be
fully nobody ever see me again committed to going as high as possible. I hit
space. They have those robotic ones. There's like the skateboards that you
can control with like a remote. I know I saw a guy practicing that at the at the
park the other day and it made me mad. It makes me mad too, but not as mad as
any normal skateboarder. Yeah, because he's that's a commuters tool.
that guy's trying to get so that's he's not using it as a he's training to be a
spider man. Yeah, yeah, he wants to like I think skateboarders are just spider
man. Yeah, it's just normal ones. There is there is a spider. I've been reading
some old spider man. There is one of the guys is just a guy with a remote control
skateboard. Really? Yeah, he's called the rocket writer. Really? Wow,
they had they just suck. They was dude. It's the funniest thing that I've been
reading through all like the old ones from the sixties and seventies and the
the funniest thing that I that like I picked up on that, like they just write
the same story over and over yeah like and the funniest thing is that
literally every single issue has has whenever Spider Man gets in a fight with
the villain. Where you going buddy? So we on this are kind of hard. The wheels
on these chairs are like scooter wheels. Yes, I almost fell away. What were you
saying? Every single issue in every fight with every villain, there's always
we've seen the first punch that somebody throws the other person always plays
possum and the person is like as a speech bubble like. I think I knocked
him out, but he might be faking it and it literally had like like two hundred
issues. It happens every time it's so funny to imagine
fighting a guy and every time he punches someone they could just play dead and he
falls for it every single time. I would do a spider man punch me yeah I'm
playing dead. Well, they just all play. They always play dead and then five
seconds later they go. I was tricking you and they punch him back and he falls
for every single time. I would I would crawl away. I would like not even not
even engage him anymore in the fight. You'd get a rip his clothes off. You
would marry spot. You would be doing upside down kisses to spider man. So
not me, not me. I'd be taking razor blades. That means that means that I
would get to meet all the guys in the cubes. I get to meet all the other cool
people in the justice. He doesn't have any friends. He has no friends. He's the
youngest one so they bully him. And everyone hates him because of J Jonah
Jameson. So shows what you fucking know about Spider-Man. I don't know anything
about Spider-Man. He's a public menace. My nephews like that song that goes
*singing*
Oh Post Malone. Is that about Spider-Man? It's in Spider-Man. It's about Miles
so that was I didn't know that I thought it was flower. No, it's a sunflower. No,
not when my nephew sees it by down. You're a spider man. No, it's not that
either.
You're a spider.
I would believe
on the room. I would believe that post one would write a song called Spider Man
about how he's Spider Man. That guy needs to get it together. He just he just
been on that weight loss drug. Have you seen a video of him recently? Dude, he
looks insane. I know somebody who's on that weight loss drug. I was listening
to an Adam Ragusea podcast about that weight loss drug today. Is he cooking
with it?
Here's my ozempic omelette.
He's just injecting an omelette with ozempic.
You should in general be injecting food. Yeah, I don't think you should be
that's what when people say food science, I know we've talked about this. You want
it to be a beaker yeah beakers and stuff, but yeah, you should have to be
injecting stuff. You have to be taking like treating it like the only real
heartbeat. The only real food scientist. If we're going by this logic is Tony
Sashory, who that the Creole seasoning guy, the little chef who goes like
a little Cajun, little green Cajun big. It's like he's this big on the box.
of the seasoning. I don't know the box, man. You don't know Tony. You got to get some Tony
Sachery's for your French fries. It's real good. But he's a scientist? He also makes
an injectable butter. Oh, yeah. A butter is not. I'm thinking more chemicals that you
put in. Flavonoids. What's a flavonoid? MSG? Definitely a flavonoid. Is that a flavonoid?
I don't know. I've heard flavonoid and they sound... Don't they sound amazing? Don't they
sound like a little creature from another planet or country that tastes amazing? I'm
I'm a flame annoying yeah and I would eat them instantly. Yeah, you grate them
against
that sounds so good. You have to catch them in the jungle yeah. You have to go
on an expedition with a big butterfly in it. Yeah, it's like a
rainbow. They're all different colors, like a little pick man kind of guy.
Yeah,
no, we don't want he doesn't like it. No, yeah, you don't want to be
to hunt them down. Yeah, you have to bait them out. You put it like you put
leaves on the ground over like a pitfall and you sprinkle like salt on the
leaves and they come out. They
they smell the salt, but some of them to get like the different ones. You got to
this amazing video game idea. It is a no, it's flavonoid. The first baseline
you bait them with different things, a different types of sweet, savory,
umami,
garlic guys, garlic guys and garlic girls, garlic girls, mushroom,
the girls are in the deals
who else do we got in here? These are the different kind. These are different
kind of flavonoid
orange juice,
orange juice.
This is smurfs.
I've such a good idea, though,
if you let your base spoil. If you put the wrong day, you have to be careful,
because sometimes you'll be like catching. It's like, oh my God, I'm
much. I caught like fifty sweet fellows and these are like the sweet ones and
then it's like right then you got it. You got to close the cage right then,
because who's running up who missed a poop
he's a big fat flame annoyed and he tastes like poop, and if he gets into
your he gets you
them. So you have to you have to like it's all like a game of like okay, I
got to leave this this cage open long enough that all my
but here's the hours can use the crawling. It's like that it's like that
one game that would do, but the thing drops happy bird. Here's the twist of
game though. So you're working for like a food corporation, right?
You're like, and they're like, we need you to go to them.
And at the CEO of the food corporation is Emeril, is Emeril Legassi.
And he's like, you need to, bam,
you need to go into the woods and catch all these fucking flavonoids.
And then...
Wait, what is it? It gives you a mission?
Is he just a CIA?
Your mission is you have to go into this,
this it's like the Amazon rainforest.
You're a freelancer by the way.
You're an agent.
The first mission is you fill out a 1099.
Yeah. So you're working for this big corporation. You go into the woods. You
have to catch all the flavonoids. Okay. Then what happens? The flavonoids catch
you in a big net Ewok style. Then you find out it's like Avatar. You become
on the side of the flavonoids. You can have your character creation. You pick
which flavor you want to be. Yes. And you're fucking a hamburger girlfriend.
Based on things that you did in like the first half of the game. Yeah, it
game. It's like a paternity test. It determines what kind of flavonoid you
are. That's amazing. Oh, man, I got Mr. Poop. Yeah. I got Mr. Poop too many
times. It scans your body and it-- It scans your face. You are Mr. Boob.
No, I would be chocolate. Yeah, then the end of the game is a big flavor
competition. I would probably be water flavor. Wait, but this is not making
any sense. The end of the game is a cook off. Why are you turning into--
How do you turn into a flavonoid? Maybe that would be like the-- You know what
already know a flavonoid. You just this would be become become on the side of
the this would be the
twist. I'm giant, but I have a tiny flavonoid girlfriend. No, you yeah, I
guess you're a giant and then you have a tiny flavonoid girlfriend who is forty
five and
but they live till ten thousand. So she's like three years old. I don't
think I would want to be
I don't think I would want to be involved with
Well, you can choose to you can choose flavonoid at the end of the game. You
work with the flavonoids and learn their lifestyle. Then at the end of the game,
you make a choice. Do I go back and work for Emeril's company? I know what it
actually is. I don't know what it's actually gonna be. What? No, no, no. What
is this? No, no, no, no. This is it's actually the whole thing. It's it's a
multiplayer, asymmetrical multiplayer, like dead by daylight. You either play
as a flavonoid or as a chef. So if you're a flavonoid, you gotta run away.
Yeah, yeah, and do have a society. I guess yeah, you can air it kind of just
pitch like a visual novel, basically like a like a dating simulator. I was
thinking maybe like the first one, the first game in the series. Well, that's
like a storyline. This is the multiplayer game. The first game in the
series. You're just a chef and you're catching the flavonoids and the second
game. It's like a plot twist at the beginning where it's like it's like the
metal Metal Gear Solid thing where it's like, oh, I'm gonna be playing a chef,
but then boom, you're actually a flavonoid the rest of the game. Yeah,
and that's like ape escape, but for flavonoids, I like both of your ideas
and metal. I will say in Star Wars, the fact that they are made of flavors has
almost nothing to do with either.
What are you talking about? Because the the the flavor of the chef Corporation,
either one of these could have been Smurfs. No, because you are a psychopath.
If you I guess it could be Smurfs. If you took out all the flavor and cooking
and chefs, that's a good point. But instead of a fucking idiot, Gargamel or
somebody like Gargamel. Okay, if you want to try and get that license, that's
all you but that's how you're going to be able to pitch it. Did I just create the Smurfs?
Is that what it does? Gargamel wanted to eat the Smurfs. He wants to turn them into gold.
Oh, I thought he was trying to turn them into food, but it's might might as well be the
same thing. He wants them for something they don't want to be doing. Yeah, but this is
different because imagine if Gargamel had a big corporation that makes a big mouth instead
of a big nose McDonald's fries. The guy with the big nose wants to turn the Smurfs into
to gold. Yeah, you never realize this. No, this is a crack.com article. Yeah,
no, there's a writer. Blue guys are the good guys. What?
No, there's a writer strike. We can't even write this crack.com article. Yeah,
what is crack.com? There's no writer strike for video games. There's a writer
strike for... I kinda feel like this office could be a video game developer's
office. We should write a video game. We're gonna be in Indie Game, the movie
I'm down yeah, I would be down to make a video. I would be down to honestly make a
flavonoids, we play the noise video. I think it's a really good, but we just
need I'm telling you, I just need some reason. It's like my
noids because you come back and you cook with the flavonoids yeah wait. So
there's a cooking mama. So yeah, that's the whole thing. I will do that.
This sounds like that's the whole perfect video. Can we add it? Can it be
like concourse bad for day? The I always say concourse is
conker concore conker concore, like a hundred and fifty. That's how my
brother used to say it concores bad
can it be like that where there's Conan the Barbie Conan Conan. That's how
Conan is how I say it. I think that's how you're supposed to say it. I'm
saying concord like it's cool. How come Conan O'Brien is Conan because he is
wimpy, not a barbarian. Well, concord is a bad ass. He is for they kind of look
was he a dog? He's a fur baby.
Conker and Conan have red hair. I was going to say fur baby. Were you going to
say fur baby? Yeah, I don't know why. I know he calls his dog a fur baby. Oh my
God, we're not around. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I call him shit. I hate him,
but can it be like Conker? Where? Conker. I guess that is just the word
Conker. Yeah, that's the joke. I thought his name was Conker. No. It's such a
crazy. I never ride that be anything's name because it's cooler. It's a cooler
cave man, concord
can it be like that where there's violence and sexual nudity. I think
there should be a toggle in the setting so you can turn on nudity. Yeah, maybe
the first game is like an innocent, like first game will be for any s and it
will come out a long time ago. Did you guys hear
and then we can go from there and then we'll be pretty by now we'll be pretty
did you hear about this game that I cannot remember the name of now I
haven't heard of that has options for people who get scared of stuff. Oh,
they oh yeah the game that
yeah it was the horizon game right and you can yeah well what I didn't
understand you can turn the water afraid of the water, but you can't even turn
the water. I was reading it and it's like what all you can do is like it
turns down the like ocean sounds okay, and it makes your character be able to
you're a reader of water and yeah, I guess I guess I never like I think this
fear is that you're like it literally said in the thing. It was like the fear
that they're trying to like the fear that people have is like of being in the
deep ocean. You can't see and there might be something in there with you and
it's that so we're doing is we're turning off some of the water effects
and you can breathe. That is a fear that one developer had. I got that fear.
That's a fear that one ever not for a video game. Everybody's fucking afraid of
drowning to death. I don't think that's the thing. It's not even the fear of
drowning. It's the fear of like there's a yeah, it's it's a it's one of the
reddit fears. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Well, like the one with the iPhone cameras. Yeah,
yeah, actually, it's one of the it's one of the ones where it's like I'm I'm
afraid of like something cosmic and I know I'm afraid of it's a napkins
touching. It's a phobia that like you hear about like tryptophobia or whatever
like, oh my God, you spilled over the new office for it's like tryptophobia or
or whatever, like the fear of tiny holes like no one that's what no one had that
fear until they read about it. I like yeah, because you can put pencils in
back in the day, people used to like tiny holes. Now it's all about big
nowadays. These girls are getting surgery to make their holes bigger.
They get surgery to make their but I've heard about this. He's right.
Girls are you serious to make their butthole? You can put a great three
counts. I put a grapefruit in a girl's, but now because all the so you're going
to do that for a while. They started with golf balls. That was the first ball
they got put in a but soon they're going to be putting soccer balls up there
soon. They're going to be putting fucking bowling balls, sixteen pounders
directly into women's. Well, the weight doesn't matter that much. You tell
that okay, well, let's put a fucking you try sixteen pounders a two pound. I
got sixteen pounds in my book
as long as it's man and skinny, it's
a bowling ball
compared to a soccer ball. It's pretty thin
actually rather narrow. I guess yeah, a soccer ball pop in my butt. I think
they make those. You're not you're not like that, bro. You are not tight like I
am. They make those butts loose as hell. Now his butts loose as fuck. They make
that is not true. You can put a whole I've never had. I have I only have
diarrhea because my butt is so tight that it just squeezes into a million little
pieces when it comes out.
Like the book? It won't come out as... Yeah, like the book because you're a
liar. No, I'm not a liar. And that book is real. That book is real? No, I wish
it was. Yeah. What's the...
I remember...
It was on... You remember that? I remember seeing the Oprah episode with
my mom. Yeah, and then he got exposed. Where Oprah's like, "You are a lying
piece of shit. And he's like, "What? Who gives a fuck, bitch?"
Hey, Oprah. Yeah. Hey, everyone, check under your seats. Now, look up.
Double burrs, here's what you got. I'm out. That's how it ended. We should do
the Oprah... He flipped everyone off. We should do the Oprah set here.
That should be the set. That would be a good idea. Sure. One to one
recreation of Oprah. I do think that the Oprah set looked amazing.
I can picture it right now. Yeah, I think you're blue and the floor is kind of our
Oprah set floor. So chairs, lots of chairs, studio audience, mommies in the
crowd. I would like to get on the stage all around mommies all around. I would
like to get as many mommies in this office as humanly possible. I think if
we put a box of wine, oh, I just remember my internship was next to the
Oprah offices. I'll go back. I'll go talk to them. Harpo Harpo Productions.
yeah, that was the name of what her production company was Harpo
production some clownish name. I don't know. Well, spell it backwards. I said
yeah, because I thought he was saying something crazy. Oh my God,
I just
spell that back to the incredible. Are you crying? I didn't mean to, but I'm
crying a little bit because of what he just said. What did he say? Say it
Harpo is Oprah backwards. Oh my God, isn't that crazy?
that's like a be like office. Oh my God, we're in no they had an elevator. We
were not allowed to use that's Oprah's elevator. They said yeah, it was
literally you're not allowed up there. You're not allowed up there because
you know, not allowed to go. If you go in Oprah's elevator, you take it to the
at the floor. It says s that's Stedman's one time. It was an elevator that went
that opened on our in our office on our floor and we weren't allowed to go on
one time when I was younger. We were and I was in California and we were doing
we were driving and we my little my baby brother he shit his diaper yeah we had
to pull over to change his diaper and we did it and it was Oprah's house in the
driveway oh yeah yeah there's a big Oh and stuff and you had a big Oh the
security he saw his little brother shit I saw Oprah's security guard yeah and I
was it Stedman? I don't know who Stedman is. I think that's her.
Stedman is like her boyfriend, not boyfriend or something.
I thought that fucking Roger Ebert was her boyfriend, not boyfriend.
You are insane for that. They dated. They dated?
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, they dated in the 90s. I think
Stedman. Stedman is Oprah's best friend.
Nobody's actually named Stedman, man. No, Dr. Phil is Oprah's best friend.
you've seen television. I've seen a lot more Oprah than you. That's probably
true. That's what I learned. That's what I learned about breast cancer as a kid,
and then I saw Mewtwo. There was a breast cancer report. Mewtwo. There was a
breast cancer report I saw of, it was a picture, Oprah, on the show of a
mastectomy, and then I saw... It kind of looked like Mewtwo's chest, no
nipples. I told my mom, I asked my mom, "Does Mewtwo have breast cancer?"
(laughter)
- Because I saw his like,
- Oh my God.
(laughter)
- I think,
- Did Mewtwo have breast cancer?
- I think Mewtwo,
- She got mad at me because she thought I was joking.
- I kind of wanted to fuck Mewtwo until,
- Mewtwo was a sexual awakening.
- Until I heard his voice.
- Yeah.
- In the Pokemon.
- Yeah, I thought Mewtwo was a girl.
- Me too.
If they had given,
they made such a correct decision by giving him
the deep man's voice. Yeah. If they had given him a sexy girls, they had given
him like the most hottest girl's voice. If they had so they should now do the
voice on that, that would have been. Does any be playing the ukulele and shit?
No, he's not. So he's not. It just would be the voice. It would just be. No,
it's not the right voice. You got to get like a like a like a
female voice who would fit me to
okay. Like Oprah. Oprah would not have. I would not. Oprah does not have a
Mmm fucking Michelle
Michelle who's Michelle from the I don't know
What I'm trying to think of of one of you to have that I was gonna say
Baby
I don't think that would have done it for me Gwendolyn Christie whose armor from you to had robot armor
I was just trying to get out of this. Yeah. Yeah, I don't talk about Michelle
I don't have anything about the robot armor. I was gonna say Michelle Quan
on. I don't even know that is
you have anything else really boring. I bet Patrick wanted to
fuck me. You know,
whatever happened to me three. I like me too, but he's too big.
Whatever I am you three. I didn't want to fuck you. I want
to be me. You yeah, it was a thing. I made up when I was a
kid. Really, what did it look like? Everybody made up your
three when they were a kid. It looked like shit terrible.
I think I think everybody who who liked Pokemon as a kid drew a picture of me
three. That was the worst picture they ever drew. I mean I didn't draw. I go.
It was too embarrassing of all my drawings. I'm so bad at drawing man. I'm
okay drawing. I think that I would like to I'm really bad at drawing, but I'm a
really good painter. I want to get good at three things. I want to learn how to
draw. I want to learn Spanish yeah, and I would like to do a high line type
a tight type rope yeah. Oh on to like to sky, you want to be a type rope walker.
I want to be a type rope Walker and I want to walk very I want to be the
fastest fastest and I want to be really scared.
You run all the way
because I don't like this style of the guys who do they do this thing where
they hold the thing yeah and they think no thing also one no thing and I'm
going to hold my breath and run as fast as possible all the way down. That's
I want. Yeah. What about like a highline tightrope, but it's slanted? What if you're the first
slanted guy? Yeah. Oh, and also I always had this idea, which is that you set it in between
your ass cheeks and you kind of use your body like a zip line and you just kind of and you
hold your balls up. You hold your balls all like as high up as I go, so they don't get
turned into nothing. I notice your hands at your chest. I have long. I have long ones.
I've said this before, I have pretty long stretchers. Yeah, that turn, you know,
like, okay, so if you take your balls personally, your, your ball sack and you
flatten it out. If you personally take your balls. If you, yeah, if you do it
yourself and you pull it as far out as possible. Uh huh. Stretch it. Show me
with your, yeah, show me with your, with your hands how wide that would be. I
don't, I haven't stretched it. You don't do that in the bath. Probably about this,
this wide? Let me think probably the length that's respect of the length of
my pants. So show the show the camera.
We'll just do it with your hands. You don't have to show that they can't see
that on the thing. I would be probably like I might be like maybe here. I
think I honestly might be that big for real with my sack. Well, that means
you know what that means, right? We know that means yeah,
I literally look it looks like I used to have giant balls.
I lost the dog who just went on a diet. Yeah, yeah, you know, you know what that
means, though. That's how big your your pussy would be. I know for real. That's
what I'm saying, bro. This guy's not tight. Yeah, I think that if I was a girl,
I'd have the fucking most huge shit ever. Yeah, yeah, you'd have beagle ears
between your legs. I'd have beagle labia flaps and ears. Your leg would look
your your pussy would look like a basset hound. I think that my
Yeah,
it would look at home in a Sherlock Holmes.
I think that your your would look like the curtains into a fortune tellers
caravan.
No, I would have my would actually look really no, it would no, it would look
yeah, it would look like two glass doors. No, yeah,
really flat. It wouldn't be flat. It'd be I would have a juicy ass. You'd have a
juicy. No, you're just the show would be dry as fuck all the time. My dude, they
call you. They call you Sahara. Girls say like,
my pussy's fucking dry. Fuck me. They got to put pH strips up there. I heard
yeah. P. H. A. T. Strips because that thing I heard from girls that I know
they have to put a PH strip up there like they're testing a pool. Yeah,
if it's all messed up, they do have to put a powder up there to a powder,
powder. It's chlorine. If I had one powder be coming out of there, yeah,
all the time, it'd be like when you when you like, I'd be triggering hard and
the corn starch starts flying everywhere. Men would try to eat me out and I'd
be triggering their allergies.
if I had a something you to mitt pollen, I'm going to say something really,
really nasty, but mine would have some kind of substance that looked like rice
yeah and it would come out all the time. What those would be your eggs? That's
it. I don't know what it would be, but I'd be coming out and I'd be like
wearing a scurvy going down my leg. Some guy be eating me out and he'd be like
pot of silica gel packet for his fucking tongue. Yeah, because it's so you need
to keep it dry. So no oxygen, so it doesn't oxidize. Mine would have a
tongue. Yeah, I might have a beak.
I think my would have wings like wings, not like like name or wings. Yes,
exactly like name or wing. My pussy would have wings. Hey, my pussy. Come
on man. Yeah, don't don't don't swear. We have neighbors who can hear us.
No, they can't. They can hear us. They don't want to hear. You guys would be
able to hear us saying pussy ad ad nauseam. I would have one of the loud
far my my pussy would be ad nauseam yep
and also it would have said that like you were on it.
Would you guys if you had a if you guys had a pussy, would you say it like that?
Would you get the two lips on either side? Would you get them tattooed with a
company for a monthly fee, I get like wrapping a sedan yeah? I guess I would do
I'd pin them open like a butterfly.
For $20,000, I would get the Carl's Jr. logo on my mons pubis.
Can I tell you guys something about...
No, no, it's got to be on the lips.
No, no, no.
It's right like, but like too close.
Okay.
Sure.
Like part of the star is kind of going in.
Yeah.
My girlfriend got a tattoo from this lady who spider webbed a girl's butthole.
I've seen, I've heard of that.
Wow.
Yeah.
Can I tell you guys something about Carl's Jr. that I forgot to tell you guys from Mexico?
Yes.
They had a Carl's Jr. near our hotel.
I thought it was very funny because they had all the Mexican food and they just had a Carl's
Jr. and it had a big, a big glass window so you could see like the whole, you could see
the counter and like the menu and everything up on the screen.
And one night we were walking back to our hotel and there were two guys who were like
clearly a little drunk but there was like two American guys who were just standing outside
said the carls junior and just standing like right next to each other and just
just staring into the window at the menu and standing completely still and
they're like their girlfriends are like come on come on and they're just
sitting there staring and we're laughing so hard at it and then a third
guy who clearly did not know them came up and stood next to them. It started
to
just looking at the menu like a like a cat staring out the window
Speaking of Carl's Jr.
Our college girlfriends took us to Mexico and now we're so sad.
Now we're mothed to a flame at Carl's Jr.
The menu is probably different.
It's all the same.
Well, okay. Speaking of the butthole tattoo,
I don't know, like, that person got their butthole spider webbed, right?
For $50,000,
I would get the Carl's Jr. logo on my butt.
The mouth is the...
I like the girl with the octopus ass.
I mean, yeah, the thing about that is that, I mean, I don't...
It's just... At that point, it's like how much money would you pay to suffer this pain?
Because I don't know how many people are going to be looking at my butthole and being like,
"I'm seeing your butthole and I can't believe there's Carl's Jr. on it. What's wrong with you?"
That person that got a spider web in his butthole.
I mean maybe five to six people Maxel see my Carl's Jr. But you cannot get this
job
but
I
am I ever going to get a job now, but you have an as you would be able to get
the job of Carl's Jr. Though that's true yeah, that's a
bad job. Yeah, let me show you. Let me show you by the way that's a birthmark
yeah, that's what I would say my the
lady or the person who got the
spider web but whole. I saw an interview with them where they're like every
time I went to the bathroom, I had to put Vaseline and every single time that
they went to the bathroom, they had to do after care. That surprises you? Of
course. You can't get poop on a tattoo. Imagine the commitment to a spider web
butthole is something that I could not do. For $50,000? For 50 Gs? Easily. For
some spider web paint on your butt and then you gotta wash your ass for three
basically yeah, basically two weeks of washing my ass every day to wipe my
butt after
I would not
sit down after thousand sitting down after getting that
I'll go to the hospital for two weeks every day. I'll hire somebody to be my
personal nurse and give him five grand and then I told forty five thousand
dollars a good idea. I shouldn't hire somebody to wipe my eyes. I shouldn't
have talked about this person spider web butthole tattoo this much, but my
my girlfriend kept showing me it and she was like isn't this so cool. I was
he said it was cool. I was like if you get that I I'm putting spiders in your
yeah, I put you got to yeah, I walked a walk. I'm putting spiders in your butt.
You are getting spiders in your butt. I'm going to put random. I'm going to
put flies in there and you have to catch them in the way. If I saw a girl
with a spider web, but that you'll be like oh my God, this this but hasn't
been used in years.
Oh God, getting a broom.
I know why I talked about that spider web butthole tattoo so much.
That was funny.
It was funny. It was fine.
Do we have a list today? We're supposed to do a list.
No, writer's strike.
That'll be our excuse today. Mostly it's no wifi.
No wifi so we can't really do anything like that.
They have not messaged me back about the wifi.
Didn't you say you scheduled it? Why would they message you again?
I gotta create an account.
So you didn't do it?
couldn't do it and I'm going to make the password very funny. I know you will.
I'm going to hate the password. It's going to be shiz or piss. It's not going to be shiz or piss or tits.
It'll be pez.
I think that... Can I tell you guys something very controversial? Yeah.
Because I've been just thinking about candy a lot. We can't... I have candy on my mind.
I don't really want to talk about candy. We've been talking about it a lot.
But I do want to say one thing.
I think that Pez is in my top five candies. I like Pez. Cherry Pez. Is
that not? I feel like people, people should be crucified. No, that's that's
fine. I love Pez. Pez is the same as Smarties. If it comes out of this,
I mean, one at a time, and I'm enjoying them so much. Pez is better and
different than Smarties. Yeah, but it's the same class of... It's the same
class. It's like it's an insane candy to eat. There's also something about,
it's like how wine is better if it's decanted. There's something about Pez
out of the package, I don't really want it. If it comes out of Fred Flintstone's
neck. That's good. That's a good candy. It's the plastic in the Pez. It adds flavor.
Oh my God. It's also because you've got to work for it. That's true. Because it's
hard for a weakling like me, a wimp, it's hard as fuck. For me, I'm kind of a
cynical, ironical type of guy, so I don't often give many thumbs up. So my thumbs
are kind of atrophied because I sit there like this all the time. Also, I watch
got a TV and I go, that's the closest I'll ever get to loading a magazine of
a gun is putting the fucking Pez things in. And I feel like I really do feel
like a tough guy when I put the Pez things in. Yeah. 'Cause it's the exact
same
thing.
And then hearing it go like,
"I love that." Yeah, wow.
But I would love it. For me, that's what I get from plugging a damn XLR cable
in. There is some way to load up Pez where you can just put the paper thing
in there and then like I guess you shoot it down. I want the guys over the paper
comes out the bottom. I think that's how you're supposed to load up Pez. I'm not
entirely sure, but if that isn't true, then it should be Pez. Get your dumb ass
German fucking asses on this. I really want the guys over at the modern warfare
like reloading animation guys to do a Pez one. That'd be the guy who does the
real life staplers and stuff. Yeah, he needs to do. I think he did. Maybe that's
what I'm thinking. Maybe I saw that video of that guy loading up. You mother
fucker. Yeah, oddly satisfying. It is seriously oddly satisfying. Strange
words. Well, that was kind of perfect.
I think that this studio could be used for all. I think that we could
definitely do art in here. I think we could do squidward voice acting. We
could do squidward. We could do paintings. Uh huh. We could do squidward
voice acting classes. I don't think that that would be very good. We could get
that guy who just walked by to come in here and we'll try to teach him.
We could teach that guy how to talk like Squidward.
Or I guess more Squilliam. I think we could do Squilliam for sure, but
Squidward is hard. Should we just leave that door unlocked and just and have like
people walk in? Yeah. Actually just let people come in here if they want?
No, because then people will find out the address and then like people will try to
come in, which isn't as fun. I don't think so. It's not fun if you know who we are.
I don't think anybody has the time to go look at a studio. You know what we should do? We
should charge for tours.
That's a good idea.
That's a great idea.
That's a really good idea.
There used to be...
We should put down rails and have a little car, like a...
Oh my God, we get mannequins of us on the set.
I went to a podcast studio tour when I was like 15, on that same trip that we changed
my brother's diaper.
A podcast studio.
It was...
Earwolf?
It's way worse. It was a
Tech news today Leo Laporte. Okay. It was this guy who was like this you were a weird-ass kid
Yeah, I really was he was this guy who did like
technology reviews and stuff and he
Had a podcast studio. I think it was called TWI this week in tech was his big show. It's
And we went and we like scheduled a tour because I really wanted to and it was
they're free and we you go and you just like sit there while they do the show
and I was like blackout happy. I barely remember any of it.
There was two. It was like the lady who I organized the blackout happy is so
real. I know exactly what you mean being like a nerdy fucking like 14. I
couldn't even believe it. I was just sitting there like wasn't even able to
enjoy it. Seeing a band that I listened to on iTunes for seven years. Exactly.
life just not yeah, I just fully unable to even react and I met the guy Leo
Laporte and he was he had his voice and I think I went like
like some kind of a noise when I saw him and then I and then like the week
after we did this tour, it came out that he was cheating on his wife with the
the lady who I booked the tour with like the the the intern that I was like
emailing and he the way that people found out was he like open. He was like
reviewing a phone and like a samsung galaxy or whatever, and it was it was
like a live show and it was showing the phone and he was like so let's take a
look at the photos at he opens it up and it's just like a photo of her ass.
And so then I was like this guy's a scumbag and I never listened to him
again. Yeah, I got my I got my enjoyment and when I when I could good work, but
we should do stuff like that yeah for sure for sure. We should have people
come and they can sit. We should review tech as well. Yeah,
I think we should
I feel like I should get some compromising nude photos of you soon.
Why?
Just to have.
I want a Manila envelope.
I don't want them on my phone.
I want them nude.
I want a panel in my house that I can unseal.
This is kind of smart.
I'm not that nude that often.
Well, that's why I think I'm probably nude.
You're nude the most.
I think I'm nude maybe.
I'm definitely nude the most.
You're probably nude the most.
I'm nude maybe.
I'm nude all day.
if there was like a pie chart of my day, I think the smallest liver would be
being nude. Yeah, I'm not nude very often, but I am. I am. The biggest
liver would be big on this guy. You are big on these. I like to be in
my own. That yeah, that I think maybe I think okay, okay, you know what?
I'm pie chart of the day pie chart of the day. 12%
mate or 10% nude,
maybe 50%. I wish I lived one more. I would be. I would be. I think
I'll be a walking around new guy. If I would if I would live, I here's here's
the breakdown of my my clothes situation. Okay, the least I ever am probably is
just underwear on yeah. The second least is probably completely nude and again
that's probably still twelve percent of my day yeah and then clothes is
obviously my number one, but the one in between nude and clothed is completely
naked, but big
I didn't mean to start doing this literally like a girl, like a girl
thing. I read a guy's house. I wear a big T. It's called Pooh Baron. I have
I go Pooh Bear. So I do that the second I get if I'm the second that I
get home always, if I'm not out or people aren't over, I always just take
off my pants and I'm shirt and underwear. No, I go no underwear. My
dick is hanging below my think if I was if I lived higher up, though,
that's what I would be doing. That's got to be the worst possible look
that underwear is so it's got to be the worst look ever. It's making me laugh so
much. I do that. I go full either full on just underwear or shirt and underwear
and I just sit on my couch for five hours on my
men. I'm shirt and underwear all the time, but I've my problem is is my I've
fucking bay windows yeah in my house, so everyone in my neighborhood can see that
I'm walking around my house either like just underwear on or like I stand it's
like I stand I stand. I look out the window and I stand at the window and
you know, you know that I look at people walking. I'm sitting on my bay window
and I'm looking out the window for Lorne. That's exactly that's literally
exactly looking. I go, I go on my underwear, I sit on the computer, I go
in your underwear, my video games and then I get up. I look out the window
and I stare that stand there and only my under when I look at all the families
walk by. I just
I literally I am in the most compromising if if somebody was hired to
get blackmail photos of me, it would take them about thirty fucking minutes,
because I get home and I'm I will watch TV sometimes and be like I need to
stretch my back out and this is the situation is this. My lower back is
hurting because of the gym, so I'll get on my couch. My head is sideways
watching the TV. My head is in the in the on the thing and my ass is poked up
and I have no pants on no underwear on just a t shirt. So I'm mooning and one
side of my couch moons the fucking the window and then, if I so if I do it that
that way. People are looking my asshole, my balls, but if I do it the other way,
it looks like I'm waiting for a ghost of fuck me. I have the worst. I like a
ring, a ring video camera installed in my house would ruin my life. Oh yeah,
even if I was the only person ever saw the footage, I'd probably kill myself
yeah because I'm just walking around with like a baby penis and balls hanging
below my shirt and sometimes I dance. Oh yeah, that's the other thing I'm doing
the dishes. I'm listening to the kid, Roy, shaking my penis
dancing in my underwear to my music. It sucks having like two roommates.
Yeah. Cause then it's like, I'll be at home doing that. And then I fucking,
you know, one of them come home, comes home from work and then it's like, Oh
man, I gotta like get up, go to my room and put like pants on at least. Yeah. I
can't like, I can't, that's not an alpha move. That's just an uncomfortable,
I used to watch of Barry. When I lived with Neil, I would, there was a lot of
sometimes where I would try to get from the bathroom to my room and back
completely naked. Yeah, yeah, because I would just either it'd be late at night.
I didn't want to put on clothes and I piss or I would be getting out of the
shower and not want to put on my dirty clothes. Yeah, you were close enough to
the bathroom where that is like barely a challenge. Yeah, it was it was right
across the hall. It was like, but I know you were going like
running into people's rooms, I'm all oiled up
and down the thing
speaking of being half nude. Is your girlfriend ever? I'm not talking. I
first of all, I don't have a girlfriend. Yeah, that's true. You guys are both
me neither fiance or you have a wife. Yeah,
well, does yours does your significant other ever complain? Is your life
partner ever complain that you are just casually playing with your balls too
much?
No, because it means that she it means I'm covering them with my hand. So
just like, you know, just scratching them and just like play with them all
the time in public to yeah.
I will say
I can tell that you are on YouTube and then just like scratching them. I
mean, I know that you are in the top 1% of people who play their with their
balls. Yeah, I can do it more than most men do because I see you do it
all the time. Yeah, yeah, I'm always doing this. Yeah, you're always doing
You love scratching them.
It's hairy down there.
You need to shave.
You don't shave at all.
No.
Man, you need to.
I gotta.
You need to start.
At least trim them.
I gotta do something.
I'm not saying you gotta shave them completely clean.
I'm saying you have to shave them completely clean.
I gotta get that manscape thing.
No, no, you use your wife's trimmers that she uses on her mustache.
She doesn't have those.
Oh.
And I broke, she got me like a beard trimmer for our anniversary, I think.
You broke it on your own nuts?
I literally broke it trying to shave my nuts.
Whoa.
Well, you just don't know the technique.
The motor just stopped working.
Here's the technique for all y'all with balls.
The technique is you basically make little dreadlocks with the hairs on your nuts, and
then you snip it with scissors.
Yeah, but my hair is too thick.
You don't need a trimmer.
My hair is too thick down there.
That doesn't make any fucking sense, motherfucker.
It's too thick all over.
You can't be cut by scissors.
You got a thick-ass hair.
I know.
Is that what you're saying?
No, I need to get down there with like a machete.
A katana.
Katana flying here. You all fly alert. Oh my God, it reminds me of breaking bad
episode. Wait, check us out where that episode does what
that sucked. You can't do shit like that in this new place. He's been he's been
throwing and knocking and he's been the nice a new office. We upgrade from the
basement. That's completely fully flooded and then walk in and you start
throwing stuff. You're knocking stuff over. I'm knocking stuff over. Whatever
louder than average. I am excited, but I mean think like when we left that basement space,
can we say the address? Sure. 133 Menehan Street. Usually, why do you want to say the
address? Why do you care? Just for fans who walk by and then think, man, that's where
they used to have the office. The old set might still be sitting out front. It probably
is. If you want to go get it. If you want to go take pieces like it's the Berlin Wall.
yeah
we left something Caleb said the other day. You say that the yeah, not letting
it slide. Yeah, you stole it. I stole it.
That's right, karma for stealing my my comparison. Yeah, you're witty line, my
witty line.
That place was so flooded. There was dirt all over and I mean we're probably
not getting the security deposit, but they try to blame us for that flood. I'm
going to be based you're going to yeah, because you had to clean up all that
stuff. I
was star of the day. You are not star that you are not sorry. The day I was
started, I thought it was so funny the day after the day, the first day when it
flooded really bad and when I would say me and Caleb, it was honestly pretty much
just Caleb fixed the flood. Yeah, the first one. Yeah, the first one in you
were full MVP. I went and then and then Pat getting in like like four or five
hours after we got in and then I like and he because he was a brunch. I get
someone see to it like the fucking office flooded
he got there after we fixed
so funny
yeah, because I had to I had to like I was cleaning up everything, but then I
was like I would try to move my desk or whatever like yeah, it was more something
and my where my computer was was where it all puddled yeah, so I had a little
that I had to deal with. It pisses me off when people complain so badly I've
realized. Yeah. Yeah if people complain about pretty much anything I get so mad.
It's incredible that we're friends. I love to complain so much. I know. Nothing makes me happier. That's the only thing I don't like about you two. I love bitching and moaning. It's so fun.
It's the best thing in the world. You two really love it. I despise complaining about my
my scenario. I love complaining about other things so much. My girlfriend hates it. I
also have it to the point where I despise it so much that I will like accept awful service
always. Yeah. Awful food. Because you don't want to complain. I will never complain about
that until later. I've never sent anything back. I've never complained about anything
like that. I will - bad situations if I wait two hours at an office, I'm just like, "What
what are you going to do? I won't ask about it. If they forget my food, I
leave. I will leave before I ask about my food. I will not complain ever. I
complain about the best thing that ever happened to me. Cameron, that's why
you're good to have around, because I'll have you be the complainer for me. I
love to complain so much. And then Patrick will complain about weird stuff.
I just complain about the weirdest thing in the world. My favourite thing to do
is to complain. Patrick will go to that door and be like, "Well, it doesn't
open both ways." The way you complain, I feel like I'm a dedicated complainer,
the way you complain weirds me out. It throws me off the way I love playing
about weird. I like to complain about stuff that is not an like I as soon as
something is solved, I like to complain about it. I like to be like man that
fucking suck. That was so annoying to have to do that, but if it's I have to
complain to get through it, so I'm finding every single minute detail to
complain about and then I hate complaining during doing stuff that makes
me mad. I don't like that, but once something's over, I love complaining
about you know what it's like like if I like
if you like you ever seen like an older man, no working on something like one of
these older men who complain like do the same thing I do where they have to
complain to get through it yeah and they're just like
well, the fucking
yeah that's fun. I guess I'm only just now realizing that yeah, I can't stand.
I don't like that type of complaint, but I really like being like I had such a
long day. I had to do so much that or before it being like I'm about to have
to do so much. I really before during and after I really like I'm just a bitch.
That's true. I like convincing myself that I'm such a stoic hero that I don't
have to- You know we suffer more in our head than we do in reality.
Exactly. A lot of people see my smiling face and they think that I'm happy.
I gave up.
Buddy, I want to fucking kill myself every fucking second of my life.
I gave up on the stoic hero thing as soon as I started.
I've never seen you even be a little bit that.
No.
You were the least stoic person I think I've ever met.
I have to I have to say every single thought that I've ever had yeah, which is
okay. Yeah, you guys think I'm stoic. I think wait your bro lick brolic strong.
I think you look kind of stolen. Yep. Yeah, home lows. You look holic.
What is the way you look? You look solid. I don't think you're still like
I think you're heroic.
Okay, I got a p. Yeah, I mean, that's a wraps on this first time and guys we
We will have a set and we will have multiple cameras.
We don't have internet right now.
I do like that we set up the camera.
We set up the camera.
We had to show people how empty it is.
I mean the first thing that everyone sees is all of our fucking costumes and props.
And by the way that was we got rid of.
That's probably less than 25%.
That's way less.
That's less than 10% probably.
Has everyone seen?
You can stop it when you're done.
We can show, I don't think everyone's seen this from the live D&D show.
That's okay, we'll put a picture or something.
The big Sullivan?
Yeah.
I'm going to stop it.
All right.
Bye.
All right, goodbye.
You know what my favorite public prank at a place is?
My little prank that makes me laugh every time that's so dumb?
Is what if I go to a place and it's crowded, like a store or something, just really loudly
I say to whoever I'm with being like yeah, it's so sad that this place is
closing down. Yeah, I'm just glad we got to come here before it closes.
It's really what I'm saying for people to over here. Are you saying that at
like FAO Schwartz and Chris at like random stores? It really gets me.
Every mom and pop store is only one employee. It's so sad they're
demolishing this place.
Man, just because I know it doesn't nobody. It doesn't mean anything to
It's not tricking anybody.
It's so sad what I'm going to do here next week.
That's so sad.
It's so sad what I have in this backpack.
It's so, so sad.
Oh man, I don't want to put it in the bathroom.
I don't want to put this backpack in the bathroom.
But I have to.
The voice is telling me to.