*Badass music*
Well...
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Cameron!
Happy birthday to you.
I love that song so much.
And Manny, the birthday song?
Yeah.
I love happy birthday.
That's what my weird math teacher in sixth grade said was his favorite song.
The birthday song?
He said you would ask him what his favorite song was and he would know.
He genuinely went,
"My favorite song is happy birthday."
He had you wrapped around his little finger.
In more ways than one.
That's my favorite song.
Wrapped around your finger.
linger had me wrapped around. I've had me wrapped around my own finger. The
Rugrats movie. That movie scared me. I thought that's in a Rugrats movie.
Yeah, dude, the Rugrats movie. Remember when he gets the new mall? I know about
the Rugrats movie that I've heard in Paris. Reptar, whatever the Rugrats
movie, though the Rugrats movie is the Rugrats movie. Rugrats. Oh, my God,
that movie is so heartbreaking, dude. When he's on the plane and he clicks
the flight attendant button because he thinks it'll bring him a new mommy.
is that one? I've never seen this one. I still try that. That's the Rugrats movie.
Okay. Rugrats in Paris as they go, which is a weird bunch of babies in Paris.
That's your idea for the movie? Well it's mommies and daddies too. Yes there's
mommies and daddies there. The mommies and daddies go to Paris I assume. Yeah. But fucking Mr. Chetty
Chuckle. What's his name? Chester. No the fucking ugly kid. Tommy Pickles. Chuckie.
No, the ugly, Tommy Pickles is actually the handsome one of the Rugrats.
Or Phil and Lil.
What's his name?
Chucky.
Chucky Finster and his dad Chester Finster.
Chucky tries to get a new mommy.
I don't think that's his name.
Chaz.
Is his name Chaz Finster?
I don't think that's that important.
I think the baby's name is Chucky.
Chucky Finster is looking.
Maybe he goes by Chaz when he gets into all grown up.
Chucky Finster's mom has passed away.
Is that for real?
I didn't never know that happened.
I thought that show was about crawling on the floor.
He gets on a, he gets on a, he gets on a, he gets on a, he gets on a, he gets on a, he gets
Lucky Fenster's mom has passed away. Yeah, that for real. I didn't ever know
that happened. He gets on. I thought that show was about crawling on the floor.
He gets on an airplane. I thought that show was about fucking ripped off. And
then he went to Paris looking for answers to questions that bothered him
so. Wow. And so he gets on the plane and he sees the flight attendant button and
instantly he's like, time to get a new mommy. The husband? The... Tries to
press the... The husband tries to do that, yes. The child son, the baby son
The child son of the Rugrat Daddy.
The child son of Chester Finster.
Is it Chester Finster?
Or Chez.
Is it Chaz?
We have a guy who can look this up for me.
But the point is,
he gets a new mommy on the airplane.
But it's not the mommy that he was looking for.
You have the chroma key on your hat.
Sorry.
It's kind of cool actually.
White hat, green hat.
hat green hat white hat green hat. Yeah, you were doing yeah. Okay, I was trying
to figure out what that song was for that entire time. I figured it out
instantly. It does you or he always does the I don't think you were hitting the
right note on the one can tell green hat white hat green hat. You should be
green hat white hat the second time green
for the second time. Oh,
green hat, white hat, yeah, that's right. That's an amazing song and they need to
put little John back in the music and I think I know exactly what the music
video will be.
I got a green hat and I got
that's way too many words. Little John would never say all that. What are you
talking about? You would never say all that. He only does like three words per
bar. No, yeah, what's that song? But they don't
do shit, but they don't do shit.
You know the one.
That's four words.
All I ever remember.
That's a sick song.
All I ever remember about Lil Jon is his song where he talks about, or where they sing about
pussies and buttholes.
What's that song called?
What are you talking about?
The other song, Skeet, Skeet, Skeet.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Which Skeet, by the way, probably.
He says a lot of words in that song.
Well he says Skeet the most though.
He says, "All these bitches crawl, sweat down to my balls. I'll skeet skeet,
motherfucker." I probably didn't learn that skeet was a cuss until I was
probably 18 or 19 years old. Right, you were too concerned with shooting skeet.
Yeah. You were kinda thinking about that. I thought skeet, the thing is,
dude, I'm from the farm. Yeah. I'm from one. So I was out there and
I was shooting clay pigeons. You're from the manger.
I was born in a manger. Pole. I was saying pole to my assistant.
And you didn't even know pole could be a sexual word. Yeah, you didn't even
you know, it could be on your on your weenie and then all of a sudden I get to
the big city. They're saying we're pulling on my God, so it's making pulling
your thing till it's skeets and then they get mad at me. When I put my gun
thing till it's skeets, yeah, I used to think that it was just fucking. I
usually think it was just skeet because of the shooting. I didn't even consider
the pulling yeah, pull it and then you pull the pull, create skeet and then
you the pole does create
when you say pull it creates a great skit in flies up, he flies in this as high as
it can flies in a napkin or the sky, not a lies and you shoot skeet. I don't like
that they took skeet away from us and they made skeet a cuss. They made skeet
in I don't know. I guess I mean, I guess it's technically a cuss, but like if my
kindergartner came home and said skeet, I don't know that I'd be like how dare
you say, but what if like his friend is I think I was probably video recorded.
Yeah, I would think it was funny. I guess yeah, the same way I would if he
said fuck yeah, kids cussing is never gonna get old for me. It's always funny.
It's funny every single time my
mean towards you. My nephew tells on me when I swear, but then he says the
swear and it's so funny. He says he says like Uncle Pat, Uncle Pat said a
bad word and then my sister will be like what and he goes, he said mother
motherfucker that's on your that's on your sister. Why is she asking the kid
to say the word just say just say just trust him bad word yeah, but it's I
mean yeah, it's she's asking because it's funny. It's it is funny. Yeah,
it's funny. Every single it's funny every single time, but because he's got
a speech. It's funny when the kid gets trains like a train seal to say I agree
when parents I honestly think
I think that it's go actually trashy to cuss around your kids. Yeah. I think that
people should not be doing that. You got to wait till they're adults. Yeah, yeah,
even then I down a few middle school own to throw them out of what you can say
damn an ass in middle school, right, but I'm saying you have to you have to swear
in front of your kid one time in high school to late it to be like yeah,
that's right and even even when they're grown is all powerful, even when they're
grown adults until you're like a grumpy old man, you should not be saying fuck
this, fuck that, mother fuck you.
Oh, I'm complete trash.
Yeah, I know you are.
My parents swore in front of me all the time.
I know, I can tell.
I was saying swears when I was a little boy.
My parents were not.
That's why I was an expert on swearing in elementary school and that's why kids would
learn cusses from me.
I learned that I could say crap at school when I was around my parents in second grade.
Yeah.
I learned that I could say crap in third grade because out of Jimmy's head, that movie or
reanimated. They say the word crap in it, and it was the word crap was on Cartoon
Network on Prime Time, and I said, "Whoa." I wasn't allowed to say sucks. And then I
said crap. Really? I wasn't allowed to say this sucks. Yeah, I wasn't allowed to say
"shut up." There, in my third grade class, there were people who said that jerk was
on par with the F word, and they would try to get me in trouble for saying jerk.
what the fuck is wrong with these kids? Yeah, these jerks. Jerk is as bad as F-word?
Yeah. Hey, tell that to a
linguist. Yeah, tell that to a Jamaican linguist. Tell that to a cussist. Yeah.
Which I've been looking into becoming. The cussists versus the linguists.
A cussist is gonna take that every single time. Yeah. Words have power.
Yeah, words have power, but a linguist is gonna make a sentence that a cussist
couldn't even tell. But a cuss can basically, it's basically adapted to be
any word of the English language. It can basically mean anything. I'm going to do
some shit. I'm going to work some shit. I'm going to eat some shit. I'm going to
play with my shit. That type of thing. A linguist will know what the etymology of
the cuss word though. I have to go to fucking work. I have to eat fucking shit.
I'm going to play with my fucking shit. It adapts. It can mean anything. I took
my shit out of the toilet. I took my fucking shit out of the fucking bitch
toilet. I fucked my shit in the toilet. I fucked my shit. And then I ate it. What?
That's so nasty. That's disgusting to think about.
Somebody fucking a shit and eating it.
But picking the image of a guy pulling his picking up his turd out of the
toilet is always funny to me.
We're back.
Anytime, honestly, if I imagine that the first thing that comes to mind is like
some kind of picture, the guy where he's like, guys, I just took the like as a
Reddit post where he's like, I took one of the biggest shits I've ever seen.
and they're all like. Why are you holding
still
holding a
that's like the size of a football? It's so funny. I always think like if you
somebody says pick up a shit. I imagine somebody like doing it at work yeah and
then having they're in like a meeting and then it's like a flashback scene of
them being like well. I walked into the bathroom. I took a shit and then it was
really big and I picked it up and took a photo that one of the funny things to me
about picking up a shit out of the toilet is as I whenever I imagine it or see it.
It's always somebody always is is full handing it yeah. You'll never see
someone daint like being like oh, I don't want to touch it. I was picking up
a shit. They're going you don't pick it up like in a clear. You pick it up like a
cell, like a baseball bat. I think that could be funny is like it up like it up
like picking it up. That's that's a that's a thing I've never thought about
because in my head, whenever I imagine somebody picking up a shit with their
their hands. It's always a full fist. It's always like, yeah. There's this kid that I
knew. I think I said it before, but there's this kid I knew, my brother's friend, they
called him Tater because he got blackout drunk and took a shit in the woods while he's camping
or something.
Ron Weasley?
No, the Ron. It's Ron.
I don't know what the fuck.
The Ron who drinks.
The comedian.
Swanson?
The comedian from the blue collar.
Oh, Tater Salad.
Tater Salad.
The comedian from the blue collar...
Oh, Tater Salad.
Tater Salad.
Ron White.
Yeah.
But everyone called him Tater because he got fucked up, took a shit, forgot about it, and
then picked it up and was like, "I think I found a baked potato."
That is not a true story.
That is a lie story.
I don't know if it's true.
I don't know if it's...
I still think that that is funny.
I don't know whether it's true or not.
It's a funny story, but it's not...
I think that that is funny story, but picking it up, picking up a turd and
saying, I think I found a baked potato is funny. It's definitely funny, but it
did not have the funny part of that is picking up the shit, though, yes,
and having the nickname tater is also funny. That is a made up story. Yeah, I
don't care. It's a false. I don't care. I told you this is a kid. His name was
tater because he ate a potato one time and they put a potato to school yeah and
they were like. Oh, you tater now that's tater and then he's like how do I how I
change this? How do I change the narrative? I'm going to pick up my he
told his story. No, my brother told me yeah, that's a fake one. Did you know my
brother said taters coming over that
tater chowder? Who the hell is my brother hanging out with food? Yeah,
he was best friends with Bob the tomato and Larry the fucking cucumber. I will
you
but I imagine it wouldn't be good to make a meeting.
Wasn't there in the pickle Goliath?
Well then they show that they can forgive him.
Goliath is the pickle.
I don't ever watch that much VeggieTales.
I watched a lot of it.
I watched a little bit when I went to church.
I had these little pewter VeggieTale action figures.
Not even action figures.
Instead of watching VeggieTales.
I was watching Newgrounds on the pewter.
As soon as I found out about Newgrounds,
VeggieTales was done with.
I watched VeggieTales.
I watched VeggieTales for a very long time. They had an amazing VHS case on the VeggieTales.
They had the green tapes.
Yeah, they were green and they were really, you know those like huge ones that have a
lot of air in them?
Yeah, the puffy ones.
I loved those.
The clamshell ones.
Clamshells, that's what they're called.
They were amazing, dude. And the VeggieTales ones were really high quality, man.
Yeah.
Wow.
And they had some great stuff on those boxes. A lot of info.
I love the info on the boxes.
Me too.
I love looking at the run time.
I used to take them into the bathroom and I'd read them while I shit.
that was like a lot of there. That was a real primitive three D stuff, because
you re watch that they should remaster all that first of all
buddy. I have a movie for you.
There's you like an unreal engine five. Yeah,
dude like re like finding all the old three D models that they made for
regular, upscaling them with a and it gets all like fucked up. Yeah,
proportions are all putting like a billion more polygons or whatever. It
doesn't look anything like a vegetable. Yeah, yeah, like like San Andreas,
yeah, like the fucking San Andreas remastered. They're doing like that.
They turned Larry to a rack check and Benny. Yeah, Bob, the tomato is not a
vegetable. He's a fruit, yeah, but they also have the blueberry. He's definitely
a fruit. I'll say that much. He's walking around being a know it all. He's a
fucking, he's one of these closeted Christian guys that his mega church gets
defrauded or defunded because everyone finds out that he's gay. Like a Mark
Driscoll. Well, he wasn't gay, but he, I think my mother's surname, he was using
heroin, not heroin, prostitutes. Made a name. Or maybe drugs too. There was a
bunch of big church guys. I heard that happened to this one family called the
Gemstones. I've actually been watching this documentary about it. Wait, really?
Yeah, they were pretty crazy influential growing up in the South. Yeah.
yeah, but speaking of pickles, yeah, I did yeah. I went to the gemstone
church, yeah, yeah, and I worked at parks and rec to
yeah, it's true, and then when I works at at Dunder Mifflin and then I broke my
foot and went to scrubs. Yeah, I'm sorry, and I was friends with a guy named
Nintendo, and even when I was a baby, I went to cheers and I drank beer with I
drink beer with norm. Why didn't they call that show beers? They should have
that fucking show, Woody Harrelson's hairline timeline.
You go on the whole show.
Can I say?
Yeah, wait,
can I save it by presenting Cameron with his birthday? Yes, you can.
Yes, Cameron's birthday.
And it's also America's birthday.
Yes, but I don't give a shit about that because of my leftism.
That's fucking awesome.
Honestly, I see America's birthday is less of a count up and more of a
countdown. Yeah, count down to annihilation. Yeah, wow,
that's something I thought of a few years ago. Something something I know
about Cameron is that he loves music right.
He is a the musician of our group. He see he loves this song. I like the
song more than I like anything in the world. So
well,
besides whatever I'm okay, all right, show him the birthday bash.
So I
spent painted. I came in here early today and I made Cameron something that is, I
think, so amazing.
Wow, George Michael, George Michael from way, I am which it's supposed to be
George Michael, but I said that this looks like to be, which is why I put
sunglasses in and also why you put George Michael. Yeah, I had to put his
name in the band. He was in good. It looks great even yeah, and I like you
put police department up there. I like that. No, that's my artist signature. Oh
yeah, well, I like okay. I was the police department was not very kind to
George Michael. If you remember history, I don't know anything about George
Michael really, and this is maybe a bad gift. I think George Michael, this is
exciting because it honestly makes me want to learn George Michael was one of
their first gaze yeah music. He was one of the first gay guys.
Last Christmas got on what would happen to him. They they set his ass up and
they're going to say on fire. No, they said his ass up. They made they knew
they said they knew he was a gay guy. They knew he was a gay guy and they're
trying to expose him the British tabloids. So then they enticed him with a
glory hole. When are we going to be done with that fucking tabloids? What are
talking about that is a total. He was set up. He was set up. How's that a set?
That's a complete and total. They had a paparazzi on the other side. They had a
yeah,
selfie of his and the police and the police
the other. The Bobby was on the other side of the glory box as they call it
right in the yeah. Well, no, it's just a difference like how they we call it
like a like a dollar, but they call it a they call it a pound. Yeah, I mean,
Yeah, you know, I didn't know that quid wasn't a different kind of currency
until last year. It's just a name for a buck. It's I thought that they had
quids and shillings, whatever it's called. Shillings is apparently old
shillings. They don't even use anymore. Yeah, I would hope not. They're old.
Yeah, they're made of metal.
He's got a lot of crowns in his mouth. I got it. I might have another one
on a Friday might get another crown in there because I cracked my damn tooth
open. So can you tell me why you chose George? So let me actually tell you
because I walked in and this wasn't George Michael when I came in. There was
a different face that was drawn on here and it was a picture of Vin Diesel, who
I like Vin Diesel, but what I said to Patrick was, oh, I get it. It's like a
cheeseburger.com/pun because it's on an easel. It's supposed to be Vin Diesel.
I think that's a bad change it. Yes, he's one. He saw the gift, so I got
self conscious facing the door. Okay, I didn't think that you'd be the first to
show up. Caleb said I'm on my way. You said nothing, so I'm already. I had no I
had no
thing. I had nothing to to to gauge my time and then I had to turn the white
board away from the door and I thought who does Vin Diesel kind of look like
right? Who can you? What can you add on? Yeah? What can I do to like you know
when they like do I can see the cover of the tent and kind of yeah,
that like a renaissance master yeah. You can kind of see does George Michael look
like that. I don't know. I don't look exactly like this. The fucking there's
like an album cover where he looks like this. He's a pink body and blue hair. He
looks pretty much and then I know he was gay to a tee. He looks like this. I
think I don't think he's a Mediterranean man. That's why oh yeah. George, my
real name is like George. He's Michaelopolis or something careless
He does these Quasimodo style soldiers.
That's just kind of like a perspective thing for my art style.
Maybe his left shoulder is a little closer to us and that's why it's higher up.
No, it's just because he's playing the guitar.
He's playing the guitar. Have you seen the...
Well, he has a music video. You don't know anything about George Michael.
He has a music video called "Faith".
Well, I know that Limp Bizkit cover of that song.
Here's what you should have done, man.
This is him in his leather jacket and his little Levi's 501s playing his guitar with his big
ass.
Oh, I forgot the fucking earring.
I forgot the earring.
Here's what I would have done if I were you.
Motherfucker, hear me?
You know, if I was Patrick, here's what I would have done for your birthday if I was
thoughtful.
Okay.
Well, I have a birthday in 19 days.
I would have drawn for sure.
I would have done a drawing, and I would have done something wham, but it would have been
in
I'm a girl. I don't really know. I think it was just a note of that. Why are you
saying? I don't really know. I don't really know, but I mean that's open for
interpretations. We're saying you're saying you're used more pink because
you're saying he's more girl than guy. What the hell you're saying? What
you're the most homophobic drawing I've ever seen. I was just homophobic
because you just admitted it was a meaning that I'm honoring him lips with
the pink and the beard with the blue. You say that he has a boy. He has a
his girl mouth and boy hair and boy beard. Yeah, I don't really know and you
say you're saying he has a beard also. No, it's homophobic drawing. I've ever
seen a beard. He had a
I guess a husband. I don't know. He had a husband and they were wondering died
on Christmas. He's dead. He died on Christmas. You're disrespecting this
day. He died on Christmas and he had a song called Last Christmas. That's
crazy sad. Yeah, wow, and the only good Christmas song. I don't want to die on
Christmas. There's no good Christmas song. There's no good Christmas songs, but that
one is, it sucks that that's a Christmas song, 'cause it sounds amazing. I don't
care so much for that song. And I want to listen to it all year round. I found out
this is a bit off topic. That's fine. I'm ready to leave this topic. Yeah, me
too. I think we should have left it a while ago. Alright, we'll leave it in
two seconds. Okay. One, two. I found out something amazing this week. Okay. In
1920 something, a man in Sweden swapped bodies... I've heard this. With a man in
the year 3960. Whoa. Yeah. Can you believe that shit? No. And there's a couple of different
facts about it. I mean, yes. And they're coming at you right now. Number one, in the future,
and this is 1920, this is before nuclear bombs or anything, but he said that there was a
nuclear war in the year 2800 and something, and it wiped out 90% of the population, including
most English speaking countries. So the dominant language in 38 whatever is a combination of
like Swedish and some other thing.
Hope it's not Arabic.
Swedish and Greek or some shit.
Why don't you hope it's not Arabic?
Imagine that fucking alphabet. You got all those A's with the umlauts or whatever.
Jeff Dunham kind of racism coming out here.
Problematic.
he's homophobic. Now he's being racist against whatever countries they do
Arabic and I don't know, but I didn't have to learn that I'm giving you the
I'm giving you so much knowledge right now and you're just trying to drop some
drop a little more because I have some know after this. Okay, so not only that,
but by that year we have moved on to the next stage of human evolution, which is
gills, not gill wings. It's not so you might think more you're thinking. Oh,
it's physical. Oh, it's surely a physical. It's a mental autism.
No,
there is a the next step of evolution is people start undergoing this this
spiritual change called nebelreich yeah, okay, spiritual is not so I knew no,
no, no, no, no, no, but it's your changes humanity. It changes humanity
from
being interested in the self and being selfish to being selfless and living
for others, and so by the year thirty eight hundred something and this
evolved it evolved, and if you were wondering about aliens in this universe
or in this timeline, this feature this university by this university mean our
universe
they've existed forever. They're around they're not interested in chilling with
us. Of course, they are guardians okay, and so once we get the nebo reich, they
pop in they say what up what up you joined the whole kind of League of guys
who don't give a shit about themselves and now you're awesome. The UN wow yeah
the United Nebulas, the uninterested and he spent the uninterested days and days
there in the body of a man who was in a coma and then woke up. Wow what was his
name? Some shit bull right? I don't remember that guy's name yeah, but that
which is my science facts of the week. I actually have some interesting
information, too, to drop. I mean, you go ahead. I just I knew a guy who
fully believed that
autism was the next step in human evolution. He fully believed this, and
he said he hoped all of his kids have autism. That was the big plot point in
that terrible Predator movie. Really? Shane Blackman. The Predator has autism?
No, there's a kid that it's so, dude, the kid, the main kid has autism, and
the predator like wants to get him and then they're like the scientists are
like the reason the predators trying to get this kid, I think I remember this
because he has autism in a thousand and eighteen, so like twenty seven yeah,
and it's not a good portrayal of it's like it's fully like a like a moaning
noise, a lot of it, but he's got like the predator wants them because he's
he's highly evolved. He's like a little kid and he's drawing like pictures and
he's doing like magneto like in the prison thing where he's doing the
standing up and all the stuff's flying around him. He's not doesn't do
anything or like Matilda in her house. He has no power line around her. Can't
you give yourself autism with if you microwave plastic or some shit? Let's
start doing that. What are you talking like the stuff in plastic? If we
microplastic, I know the that's when it's good. PPA. That's if you put
plastic in a shrinker. Yeah,
we should whatever you do do not use plastic bowls in your shrinking
machine. You can get up with a microplastic. You know what you can give
yourself, you put some plastic in the oven, Spider-Man, get some
Shrinky Dinks in there. True, Shrinky Dinks. Yeah. What's a Shrinky Dink?
We've had this... Okay, we can't get into that. We're not doing... We have
totally, 100% explained what a Shrinky Dink is to you. Let me share my
information, 'cause this is more important than Shrinky Dinks, which are
a kid's toy. Is it on the same level as my idea? It's barely a toy. It's
not quite on the same level, but I think that it could eventually get to
that level. Okay. Basically, this Facebook group that I've been moderating
for a while.
Yeah, so I've been moderating this Facebook group for like a little over a
year on Facebook.
I told you about this before. What is it? It's a conspiracy group for people
who don't like I don't want to say what it's called, because I don't want
people to join. How'd you become the moderator? I just like I like woke up
and I got a notification on my phone that said you are now an administrator
of this.
Like it just randomly gave it to me. That's amazing fighting spam on it,
which I so I've been kind of on the front lines of spam. I've known all that
you know all the spam links to try to get old people that are like
unfortunately, Justin Bieber has died going one hundred twenty miles and per
hour in Chicago. What I get those all the time wait and I see all the way
what happened to Justin Bieber. That was actually false like
Christ, but actually you know, let me actually check really quick what what
the current one is because they're always they're always doing stuff like
that.
they always have well. No, I can't. I'll find it later. Yeah, but anyway, I this
group that I've been moderating and kind of welcoming new members and such. They
recently added to Facebook a function where you can make a group chat attached
to the group and it will automatically put everyone in the group into a group
chat. Okay, and so I made this chat. I told everyone welcome, welcome and
everyone was saying hello. Hi. I was like, how's everybody doing?
And this is what I received from member Brenda. This is Brenda. Here's what
friend to so before you go. This is the Facebook group where the woman believes
that her son is an angel. No, I wish I was an administrator of that. My group
is a lot lamer. That's why I don't want to get up. I want to kind of make it
cool before I get
because it is kind of what I tried to start. I tried to start free thought
Fridays in there
and the only response I got was my guy going. What
it's been kind of rough getting this off the ground. Thinkers there,
yeah
wait. What was your idea for free throughout Friday? I just said happy
free thought Fridays. I was hoping someone would well. You should you
should have at least explain what it is to the people. I mean I'll do that
next for yeah, yeah, next I'm going to be doing a week. I'm going to be
ramping this group. Can you add me into the yeah? I only I only have a
Facebook to use my Oculus. This is the only reason I have a face, and I think
it's called Doug something.
So this is what Brenda messaged me when I said, how's everybody doing okay?
right now things are awkward as hell in this group. So what do you guys
personally think about Biden's latest comment about selling state secrets? Was
he kidding or did he let something slip that he really wasn't supposed to let
slip well, and then I said I wouldn't put anything past him. Yes, Anthony said
me either to him, then Brenda says I'm kind of thinking that his dementia mind
sold him out. There is no video that indicates that he was kidding. Look at
his face. He's not joking and then I said what's everyone getting up to
and
and then Jeanette said, and this is the bombshell. Jeanette said, I believe
Biden is played by four different people and we are watching theater these days,
whoa and I said true that and then Jeanette said a thumb sent a thumbs up
and then J M sent a thumbs up and then Brenda said is it only for whoa she's
thinking it might be more than four guys playing the president yeah. That is
incredible. Here's you are being so disrespected as a moderator. You're
asking what is everyone doing tonight? Nobody
completely. I'm being completely. That's why we got to get in there.
How's everybody doing? No. Okay. This is awkward. You need a couple of
plants in there. Yeah. Who would you send stuff like that? I can be like
free thought Friday. I'm having a fucking Wednesday. Yeah. I need maybe
maybe I will Crocs Monday. I'm switching my name Wednesday. Yeah.
Chlorine half chlorine half. So he didn't even participate yesterday in
Crocs Monday. Also, I wore Crocs yesterday. Did you send a photo like
me, Cameron, a dubio day Crocs Monday is a good day. That's a dumb ass day. It's a
good day. We are our group chat already has one other. What other day is going to
be cross day and there's no day that there's no reason of a crocs. Do you
think there's a day called crumb day? It has to be Monday that there's a day
called crumb day crocs crumb day. You think
for why you wouldn't have crocs. I'm saying that you're you have lost. Okay,
you think it's called cry day is or cry day. It should be casual Friday, which
is you can do it every or that's separate, whatever we can do free thought
Friday is that I'm staying, I would say I'm the the number one advocate for me
Wednesday yeah. I love me for me. Wednesday is very big in the group chat.
We see some funny as shit, but the skeletons jumping around their skeleton.
If you don't like jump around my message, if you do not like ironic
skeleton jumping around
when you jump around when you're jumping around
from a if you do not like me,
we have jumping low poly skeletons. If you're scared of that kind of shit,
you're not enter our group chat because you want to be afraid you are not
allowed. Otherwise, you can enter. Otherwise, you're fine. Just give me
your number. Here's the thing. We got to keep Thursday and Tuesday,
Thursday and Tuesday. Those are work. Those are work. Those are also like
those are discussion. Those are kind of like stuff, extracurricular activity
type days. Those are the days that I would be doing baseball or Caleb might
doing gymnastics yeah, so we kind of want to keep those. I do for you to do
lunch for people didn't know that I do beam gymnastics, mean gymnastic beam
beam. Yeah, I do the one on the beam where you hit your balls and I'm
inventions. I invent laser beams, so yeah, so you don't have a hobby. I do
sunbeam electronic sales. I sell like toasters and fucking is a sunbeam.
That's a hobby. It's a job
Well, it's a hobby when it's on eBay. Yeah, that's fair. Yeah, it's actually
completely true. So eBay, it's a hobby
loading dock. It's a job.
Yep.
Speaking of, well, what's Etsy? That's a hobby. Speaking of loading docks, wait,
no, we gotta keep going with what you're saying. Let me call out, let me call out
crossword creators real quick. Okay. When you have a clue that says "online
marketplace and you start it with E and you end it with Y and it's four letters
and you know that everyone's putting eBay in there, but every time 100% of the
time it's Etsy. People are on to you. We put Etsy in now. We don't think it's
eBay anymore. Switch it up. You stole the words right out of my mouth. Thank God.
That's something I've been thinking about. Thank God he said this. Yeah,
yeah. That's a really, I mean, thank God he fucking said this and also Walgreen
security guards. Yep. Yep. Talk to you. Do not need a gun. No way. You do not
need a gun and you need to stop buying Gatorade because I here's the thing.
Gatorades are free for them. I am sitting in the line minding my own
business and oh and there's another part about the security guys. The
security word, the word security needs to be on the front and the back
because when I'm in line behind you,
when I'm in line behind you, I am seeing just a black shirt, black pants, a
Gatorade in the back of the head to make you go faster.
I'm seeing a black shirt, black pants, I think you're an usher for the law. I
have my extendable fork. I'm this is a problem. I'm seeing the all black
outfit, a Gatorade and a Glock on the guy's hip, and so my cortisol levels
going insane. I'm becoming so stressed out that I can't even see, right? I'm bumping
into stuff. I'm accidentally cutting the line in front of every single person and being
confused about tap to pay, right? Because of how much distress this is causing me. Until
I see them turn around and they have security on their shirt.
They have to have a big Velcro patch. Also, you should be wearing a bulletproof vest that
has a Velcro patch that says security if you're going to carry a gun. And if I pay you enough,
I get to shoot the vest.
hey and another thing hey Wendy's, thanks for making me my food the other
day.
It was good. What'd you get the thing that Dave's double the bag, the biggie
bag, what are you doing with a bag, the big bag or the full of hole, the biggie
bag or the full for four for five, and he they do a four for five. I think it
said four for four. That is so fucked. I think they have four or five and six.
The Biggie Bag is the, they have five and six and they also do four for four.
When Applebee's adjusted the two for 20 to be the two for 25, I felt a disturbance in
the force.
I like sat in my, I remember being at home and feeling like a shockwave over my body.
Because Applebee's changed.
Applebee's changed.
Applebee's is not good man.
I've been to Applebee's I think two times.
No shit.
I think I've only been with you guys.
Yeah.
You go there, you get two meals for $20.
I'm a TGI Fridays man.
Or a Red Lobster fan.
Red Lobster.
I guess so. I didn't grow up with them.
In my head, it's rare.
Yeah, I've never really been.
I've actually never been to Red Lobster.
Only Red Lobsters in Connecticut and New England.
I always just got the
they have the cheddar biscuits.
Chibio's pulling up Chili's. Chili's for me.
Chibio likes Chili's.
I've only been to Chili's one time.
Chili's is good. Chili's is better than Applebee's. Yeah, Chili's you can get nachos in.
Yeah. That's a big bonus. I didn't even know that. Yeah. I didn't even know that.
Speaking of jobs and working at different kinds of jobs. Speaking of workplace accidents.
Well, okay, so at Chili's, what kind of workplace accident would you get? Getting the chili in your eyes
from the logo. That's so true. Fajitas accident. Stabbing yourself on a chili.
Yeah. Bringing a fajitas to a table and a
little punk puts his foot out. You're 100% right. Why didn't
some that definitely there's some ocean violation with with the good search.
Yeah.
But fuck I should have looked up for heat. We today we decided that for the
fourth of July and I got to look up who suggested this in the disk. What's
more American than getting extremely physically injured at your job? That's
my point of view. At least. Yeah. Well, I think the only thing more American
than that is being unemployed. Holy
Holy fuck on that and there should all honestly be an OSHA for people who
don't have jobs.
That was I think this was vex. Okay, so thank you vex in the discord for
sitting this OSHA for people who don't know OSHA stands for oh shit. He hurt
his arm
oh yeah. He's and
which is a some kind of it's a some kind of acronym that it's a saying it's a
saying basically it's a popular so anytime somebody says this saying is
very powerful on a work site, the government, which I don't even get me
started on the government, but the government has to put this in a database
of every time somebody said oh shit he's injured. So we they have an online
database and we found some hilarious accidents, some funny as accidents and
we had a rule yeah and if it wasn't for this rule, I want I want to say this
should be a much funnier episode yeah, but the only one got Mary, but the rule
was we couldn't do anything where somebody died, which was I'm going to say
ninety percent of the pretty much crazy a good chunk of them. Yeah, can I say
one that where someone died that I didn't put in yes, cowboy died falling
off horse
because every other things these are the word employee, but there's one that
said cowboy.
Okay, so cowboy, but that one's not fun. Someone died. Somebody's not a tragic
cowboy passed on to the next not funny because the ranch in the sky, the cowboy
didn't die in like a gunfight or any like a lasso thing. That should be a cow.
By the way, cowboys should not have a job. That's not a job. That's not a job.
That's a thing you wear for Halloween. That's a legend. Yeah, and you should not
have. OSHA should not be involved in cowboy. That's the most dangerous job
there is yeah. They have a different man. They have a different. It's the same as
a ninja. Yeah, a robot exactly. Why the fuck are you a cowboy is exactly the same
as being a rope, although there is a lot of robot stuff on ocean. Yeah, if you
search robot all right, throw up my power point, I'm going to go for a that
was another good search term. Yeah, I don't have all so many drive heave
all right. So here's here's some that I found some accidents.
Employee is injected with soapy water at approximately seven forty AM on
September, Fifth, Two Thousand and Six Employee Number One was cleaning
mandrels. I don't know what that is when she accidentally injected herself with
soapy water. No
injecting a man, how could we have stopped this? What kind of regulation do
we need to come? Well, first of all, we should probably not be cleaning with a
syringe. Yeah, I agree. That's probably the number. How are you injecting
yourself with a syringe for the sponge? Yeah, let's use a sponge. I miss a
wrench, a brush you
using a syringe on the ground to clean something. It really makes it a
fish. It doesn't even like it. It doesn't even make any sense. I'm
getting flustered and maybe the mandrels can stay dirty. If it's between that and
injecting yourself, mandrels are not that listen. Even if you inject yourself
with soapy water, you're not going to become cleaner man. No, you're not
going to clean faster. You're not going to be able to use your skin to scrub
the. There are so many of these incidents where you read it and then you
think to yourself, oh this guy was trying to become a superhero in this way. Yeah,
there's one where you'll see that is one hundred percent. That is one of the
craziest things I've ever read.
Here's this next one employee suffers respiratory distress, brought on spray
deodo. Was this the one assumed deodorant? Was this the one you're just
mentioning? No, you'll know okay, you'll know I was trying to become deodorant
man
at seven thirty PM on September sixteen twenty eighteen, an employee was
cleaning shift change in a patient's room and suffered respiratory distress
brought on by the spray deodorizer. My God, this is me in the damn locker room
in middle school. Yeah, I was in friggin sixth grade acts, dark temptation,
the acts. But also I have to say this guy probably was stinky. Yeah, if he's
so allergic to deodorant that he's having to go to the hospital, he was
stinky. This is employee turns into chocolate man after spraying acts, dark
temptation on himself. That's a good commercial. That's the most amazing
commercial of all time. All right, here's the next one. Employee accidentally
ingest brake cleaner. It's really making me laugh at nine thirty a.m. On January
thirteen twenty twenty, an employee filled a Gatorade bottle that was in the
shop with water and Mio energy liquid concentrate. The employee drank from the
bottle and thought he smelled a chemical odor, but figured it was a co worker
working on something in the shop. The employee took a second drink from the
bottle, finishing approximately seventy five percent of the contents. After
taking the second drink, the employee realized the chemical smell was coming
from the Gatorade bottle and recognize the smell as break cleaner that had to
be like a play. Okay, so seventy five percent of it to drink. This was an
empty. This was an empty Gatorade bottle that you had been used to house break
cleaner. At some point, I guess it doesn't really specify. I would like to
imagine that there it was a partially full with something and he just talked
and he's a what is break cleaner smell like this is, if anything, this is an
amazing
advertisement for me. Oh yeah, me, a mask, the taste of break cleaner, you can
drink anything with me, but also if he had not put the bio in, he wouldn't have
had nausea, which is what he suffered from true. It was the aspartame. The
accident was because of the meal they called O show over some nausea. It was
not I mean I think you had to go to the that's some bullshit, but
this is the
insane
employee incurs arm swelling from piglet vaccine infusion. He was trying to
become pigmen in at nine a.m. on October fourth, twenty nineteen, an
employee who worked on a pig farm was administering exceed vaccinations to
piglets. The employee infused herself with a full dose of the vaccine in her
left arm. The employee had a serious reaction to the vaccine, cold and
holding swelling and restricting blood flow. What was the vaccine? Exceed
vaccinations? She was vaccinating piglets and she thought I'm going to put
this in my arm. I might as well give myself the piglet. What is it? What is
it? A seed vaccination? It's probably some kind of vaccine for pigs. Don't
worry about that. I don't yeah. It's what I don't do to the pigs. It probably
prevents disease. Probably prevents exceed yeah or maybe it makes them
succeed piglet vaccine infusion is so insane yeah. I couldn't believe this.
This is why I didn't this is this does not seem like an accident.
Oh, it's not an accident. How do you put a full she was wearing roller skate?
She was like whoa,
how do you put a full thing of old piglets vaccine in yourself?
Yeah, but it just her arm just swelled yeah, it's really not that I would have
thought it was well. Yeah, I thought something bad happened snout or
something or a tail like a tail. Oh my God, no, yeah, yeah, that'd be bad news.
Okay,
so employee experiences, nausea and fatigue while working at approximately
nine thirty AM on September two two thousand and eight employee number one,
an inspector was at a cinema roof performing steel inspection. He was
feeling a little weak and went downstairs to the restroom in the
bathroom. He started to sweat, so he walked towards his work box area where a
the worker gave him some milk. The employee immediately vomited an
emergency medical services were called. He was taken to the hospital and given
an injection. They prevent nausea and vomiting a handheld nebulizer treatment
with breathing medication was as minutes was administered because he sounded
congested. He was diagnosed with weakness, malaise fatigue, but was not
hospitalized. He was released after four hours without any work restrictions and
was advised that his blood work and EKG were normal. The attribute the employee
attributes his symptoms and condition to his personal medical condition and not
work related. He did not want to disclose additional information about his
physical condition and did not want to sign a medical record release form. So
he got ranks and milky threw up and he had to go to the hospital wow and then
he got so embarrassed that he didn't want to sign
medical release. They were like you're completely normal. Nothing is wrong with
you. He's like this is actually because of my personal
we need to call you right now.
He's sweated in the bathroom. I've had like moment like moments like that,
where I'm like if we had to file a sick complaints for this for the podcast, I
would have this complaint ten thousand yeah yeah. Oh my God, I'm a yeah tummy
sweating in the bathroom yeah, taking your shirt off to poop. I don't take my
shirt off to poop. Mine was already have it off okay.
Kind of cool to learn
okay, then we have employee injured by soccer ball and please tell me this is
in Fifa. An incident occurred when employee number one was seriously
injured by a soccer ball. The soccer ball hit employee number one's head while
supervising kids playing soccer ball. Employee number one was transported and
confined at the hospital for treatment of her head injury and concussion
occupation, guards and police. So I got it was a school cop. A cop got hit by a
soccer ball in the hospital and then called OSHA yeah yeah. I feel like he
was planning that he's like I could probably get some. I was a girl. I was a
girl yeah. He doesn't think girls can be a lot of years. No, I don't know yeah. A
lot of years are girls. A lot of them are women. You're trying to hurt girls.
No, I don't think you're trying to make a lot of girls hurt. You don't think girls
die as much as guys, because they don't have as many jobs.
No kidding, okay, then these are just a bunch of ones that are that don't have
descriptions. I just put the funny title. So employees suffers non work related
chest pain. So why call Osha? I don't know this doesn't doesn't fit to me.
Seems like you shouldn't call Osha for that employee suffers burns when sprayed
by thick hot beach.
Is that a death that we know? No, none of these are deaths, but the I mean this
the description of this was like a juice and employee got sprayed and burned very
badly. It's not very pleasant, but thick hot beet juice. Yeah, it feels like the
titles are funnier than yeah. So then
I have a whole series. I'm going to go through lightning round here. Okay,
employees attacked by lion employees hand is bitten by wolf employees finger
bitten by chimpanzees employee discovers bees at work site employee injured when
attacked by river otter employee injures leg when attacked by panda, when
attached by panda bear employee, injured by venomous vector. When I have been in
this vector
by venomous
employee is bitten by insect during maintenance employee performing some
apartment maintenance and was bitten by an insect. He hadn't seen employee
injured when
employee injured when door kicked by camel door kicked and that's all I have
car door,
but I know that we that these are all from a zoo. We have to live in the
fantasy land where these guys are working a factory floor. They get
sat on by an elephant, best buy, all that kind of thing. Yeah, the best by
elephant, it fucking just sits in there. All right, go over to my sleds.
I pretty much have the full of all of these employee experiences, adverse
reaction after insect bite to G and I'll tell you what G is at three thirty PM.
An employee was operating a forklift when he was bitten by an insect on the groin area.
No, the employee was hospitalized due to an adverse reaction that required cutting away
the infected area.
This guy got his penis cut off because a bug bit him.
That is not good news.
I also have a similar one to this one.
I can show you later.
This is awful, awful news.
That's terrible.
And he was 57 years old.
So he was a little past his sexual prime, so I'm not too worried about it.
doesn't matter that yeah. There's just like there's basically menopause for
employee. I bet it was an excuse. I bet he didn't even get bit by a bug.
Employee lacerates genitals with skill. So, oh my God,
what
employee
number one was preparing to change
bracket on a skill saw. He did not unplug it. He was kneeling with the saw
between his legs and you
to rock the nut holding the blade as he did. So the saw started climbing up his
pants leg and lacerated his genital. He he rocked his nuts for sure.
He definitely rocked his I would call that an unskilled saw
yep
employee is not injured, falls asleep operating vehicle hell yeah employee
number one, the driver and co worker were traveling in company work vehicle on a
public road. Employee number one fell asleep at the wheel and drove off the
road into a fence. Employee number one did not receive any injuries in the
accident. The co worker was taken to the hospital and underwent a medical
examination after being
valued by a physician. He was released on the same day. My thing with this is
why are they calling OSHA? Yeah, why are you there's a lot of stuff on here?
There was one two that I didn't put in or another another like death one that I
I don't put in because it was a death is like employee dies at home from non
work related
you could have put that way in
and this guy following the rules.
The occupation, it says
the something hard and soft. I can't read that. So I make tile tile setters,
oh, I'll setters hard and soft.
This one is employee struck by slow moving vehicle. I like this one a lot
employee number one while working as a
I can't read that something inside a construction zone. You made your shit
was hit by a vehicle driven by an elderly man.
The vehicle was traveling between five and ten
he was taken to the hospital for treatment of a laceration and concussion.
So yes, I'm some okay going five miles an hour in a car hit this guy while he
was working in a construction. So that's funny yeah. I like that one.
employee becomes ill while picking fruit and employee was packaging table grapes
when packing grapes the employees. Oh my God, I made everything so what the hell
did you do? The point is this bitch was
felt numbness, blind, blurred vision and shortness of breath for no reason. While
well, you know, a bitch, this old lady, she was 42 years old and she didn't even
the hospital. She just felt ill while she was picking fruit. Why would you report that to
OSHA? Sometimes I feel ill when I'm picking fruit at the grocery store because of how
many options there are. Yeah. Or also the bananas are brown. Oh yeah, when I go to the
exotic fruit section, I touch a dragon fruit. This is an employee injured by venomous vector.
We won't do that one. Venomous vector is so funny. I read the whole thing. There's nothing
they don't say at all. What could it possibly be? It's got to be a cobra. But at the bottom
it does say bee sting animal bite. So it's got to be something. Oh, another one that this
this reminded me of that I put in that I didn't put in was was employee bitten
by a snake or spider.
They were like he wasn't sure what he got by two employees are injured from
firearm discharge. Oh, so I won't read this whole thing, but what happened here
is that they were at a range and a guy shot through his own hand into another
guy's asshole. Oh, the whole yeah, the asshole and then these two guys decided
to call OSHA with a bullet in the guy's ass. They called OSHA because they were
at work. I bet there were police officers right. They were guards and police,
yeah. So there were two cops and he shot through his left hand into another guy's
ass. Jesus! It's kind of cool. I thought it was kind of a neat one. I would love
to see that in a movie. Employees buttock impaled by rake.
Employee fed, fell off a bed, the bed of a dump truck and landed on an asphalt
a
Hey, look, I got a hole in his asphalt for sure. Come on now.
Because of his butt, he got a hole in his another hole in his butt.
He said he got a hole. He already had a hole. He got another hole.
Talk about tearing him a new one.
There we go. Okay.
Okay, it was it was right there and I didn't take it. Employee is injured
when cow charges in the gate. A part-time employee with the livestock
the market was helping to move cattle to designated peers during a livestock
auction. As a cow was moving down an alley, a co-worker signaled employee
number one to let the cow enter a particular pen. As the cow approached the
designated pen, he opened the pen gate, but the cow stopped. Employee number
one then backed up to allow the gate to fully open and stood behind it. Rather
than enter the pen, the cow jumped over the gate.
Whoa. What the... This is a high jumping cow. Employee number one...
one. Yes, this is a one of the highest jumping cows. Okay, here's what it
should say. Rather than enter the pen, the cow jumped over the gate,
breaking a world record. No, no,
'cause one of them jumped over the moon. Yeah, jinx.
That is not even true. That's a true story from a true song.
That song is supposed to be like Wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald. It's not
called a... The cow struck the gate, knocking it. Okay, the cow jumped over
the moon, including the gate.
diddle diddle is exactly like record the Edmund Fitzgerald. The cow struck the
gate, knocking it into his face. Employee number one was transported to
the hospital and transferred to a medical center where he was treated for
fractures. His upper jaw nose and both eye sockets. His sense of smell was
also impaired. Oh no. Well that might be nice if we're working on a farm.
Yeah, you can't smell cow. You're in a livestock market. It's pretty actually
kind of a blessing to have your sense of smell impaired.
worker unearths beehive and is stung in the face over 100 times. I have this one.
You have this one? Yeah. Well, I'll save it for you then. You could use this one
later. Oh, you read it. I don't have it. I just have the title. Oh, it's my last one.
Yeah. On 8 a.m. on August 10, 2017, employee number one employed by a
construction company was clearing land at a job site.
Employee unearthed a beehive. He was stung in the face over 100 times.
Emergency services were called and the employee was transported to the hospital.
he was admitted and treated for the beastings.
If you could believe that one hundred one hundred times, I don't think I could
fit those on my face. Also, the word stung by a hundred is a big for an
earth. Yeah, it was about a receding hair. It was covered in honey. Yeah,
that goes up to the top of his or wait. What do bees make honey? They like
these like flowers and flowers. I've been covered in flowers and bear fur.
Yeah, I don't like bears. It says here. He was it says like honey or whatever
Earth moving equip.
All right, I guess go to my slides.
Doesn't want to go to your studio is is tired of working. Yeah.
All right. So these are just some titles. I found that I did liked
key. Well keyword guy. Yeah,
177 results. No girls couldn't find the word girl there. Wow.
You didn't I guess Cameron found
but I have a sense for when we find the risotto did not return any results.
Results for no results for risotto.
That is fucked.
That is so fucked.
Employee fractures tibia and fibula after being kicked by a no employee
suffers from preexisting condition.
Worker on Earth's beehive and is stung in the face over 100 times.
Worker injures hand and noodle machine employee fractures hand while sorting
heavy grapes.
So it's a heavy grapes. Oh my God, I squeeze you do. I could read it on my
computer
teacher is inadvertently struck by student falls and breaks. So what
happened was the teacher breaks employee number one, a teacher employed by a
school district was watching students play a game of four square. One of the
students backed up into the teacher and knocked her onto the ground. Emergency
surfaces were called. I think she broke yeah. She fractured her hip. Oh my God
after she was
I like to think that she was watching this four square game and just like
throwing down like one dollar
but this next one employee is injured when struck by frozen chicken. Oh, you
marked this one up yeah. I marked it, but then realized the window was too small
for me to read anything
Yeah, an employee on January. Yeah, employee of a temporary employment
agency attempted to clear a blocked pipe on the jib chiller while clearing the
blockage. The employee was struck in the face with a plug containing ice and
chicken parts. Employees suffered a broken jaw and shoulder injury. That was
what was blocking the pipe. Chicken part made of ice and chicken. Yeah, my God.
Imagine like getting your shit rocked by like a chicken wing.
Yeah, that was so bad. Yeah, it's not even a chicken. It's chicken parts.
Yeah, employee is injured and fall from ladder. Now you think like, oh, this is
just like a typical like, oh, he fell hit his back. No, he was getting a
cheese sample from a hopper. He slipped and let or can you make the window big
again? I like can't read it all. Approximately six feet landing in a
straddling position on a handrail. I found this because of the keywords penis
the ladder slip packing. So if he fell off of a ladder, this is on his wiener
and balls. Yeah, a handrail. This happened at like
like I feel like this is a Kevin McAllister trap. Yeah, there's no way
and you're not let Kevin McAllister onto the work. So no, no, this guy is
not. He's a child. Second of all, this guy has not done an OSHA forty hour.
no access to this thing from maybe he has now maybe he you know. I mean that movie
came out in what ninety three and Kevin McAleish has got to be old enough now.
Now yeah
employee is bitten on penis by Black Widow spider. That's scary. That is so
so the employee. He was working on a job site went into the porta potty and got
his his penis bit by a Black Widow. That's horrible. Which I thought he was
fucking the spider wait. This is Kern County. Where's that? This is in
Bakersfield. Oh
oh my God,
yeah, but the so I guess black widows is another reason why I don't ever want to
shit in a let me read this. This sentence that's at the end, a causal
factor for this event was identified. This guy did something yeah. He was he
was fucking the spider to fuck the spider man. What do you think he tried
He was trying to kill the spider with his penis.
Yeah. Do you think that he was trying to do that or maybe he went in there to
take a shit? Maybe it was just because I mean hey,
when you sit down on a porta potty toilet those things are kind of deep.
That's gotta be such a nightmare to get bitten on the dick and realize it was a
black widow.
Yeah, it could have been any spider. Yeah, because that could have destroyed his penis for good.
It probably did. I'm sure it did. They definitely took away part of it.
Yeah, well, speaking of taking away a part of penis, I found the absolute
worst thing in the world and the reason why I don't wear sweat pants.
I think I've talked about it before.
Your print is too small.
My print is too small, but
employee is entangled in mixer and is seriously injured.
Oh no!
Employee was wearing loose cotton drawstring shorts.
Fuck!
The other drawstring dangled loosely on the outside panel of the front shorts.
He was cleaning a like in a mixer.
The outside drawstring on employee one short gotten tangled in the rotating
shaft where the accessories are usually attached.
The inside drawstring wrapped around employee one's testicles and the shaft
of his penis, while the outside drawstring pulled employee one into the
commercial mixer.
Read the next thing.
The employee's skin degloved from the shaft and castrated his two testicles as
a result of the accident. Employee one picked up his testicles off the ground
where the commercial mixer is located, then placed them inside of a plastic bag
with an ice pack. Physicians were unable to reattach his testicles, but were able
to perform a skin graft to replace the lost skin on his penis.
that is that is actually worse than dying. Three times worse D Glove, the
he get a
pick those balls up off the ground.
War, she did the
leg. They didn't loving of the skin on the shaft here. Okay, first of all,
this is this. I put this in here as a PSA against sweat pants, but I also
put it in here as a PSA against circumcision. This is what you're doing
to your babies every single time, but it probably would have not have happened if
he was circumcised. Keep it good, leave the hood.
I'm wearing drawstring shorts right now. I actually am too. I'm going to get
sucked into this mixer. Your dick is caught in a mixer. I'm getting caught in
this one and like your balls have like or make you so high pitch drawstring gets
stuck in the fader. I'm trying to turn the volume up
I
yeah well, that has got to be one of the worst things I've ever heard in my
entire life. Is that your last one? That is my last one. Okay, good, because I
don't think I can handle that. That's that has to be that one ruined
everything. Yeah, that is I don't like this website anymore. No, I didn't like
it. I thought it was funny until you put the worst one. We did all of this and
then I couldn't find it funny and then I just kept looking at the really was
you made the best Gore version of the website. This you know what this is.
This is like this is like best Gore for like a like like a text based best.
That's so awful. It's so bad. It's really. Yeah. So who sent this to us?
Vexa Vexa. Fuck you. Fuck you. This guy never wanted to read that story. We
thought that this would be funny. It was funny. It was funny. You just put at
at the end of a crazy one. Yeah, you kind of you and you made in it's not my
fault. You put it in, you screenshot it, you highlight it, yeah, you highlighted
the most gruesome part. This is not my but the one thing I'm not going to
accept is
responsibility for okay. What I put in the slide show,
that's the one what I will accept responsibility for is booking an amazing
show on the fourteenth of July at Littlefield World's Biggest Army
tickets are still available and they're going to be available until the
fourteenth when you can make it by the door or can sell out before
something is going to happen at that show that you are not going to want to
miss. I don't like you saying that after the thing you just read. I don't do
something is going to happen and let's just say
don't show up wearing sweat pants because you're going to suck. I'm going
to
Pat won't be able to
print
yeah, the print fuck dude. Oh my God.
Come to Littlefield on the 14th. Bye bye and happy birthday Cameron.
Happy birthday to you.
*claps*
*gunshot*
*static*
*beep*
Let me just say
I meant, I gotta
I forgot to apologize for something
What'd you do?
I have to issue an apology to our producer
Um
Juby if you want to get on screen
to accept this apology
or deny it
I'm here.
Okay.
So, last night I was asking for reference photos for a D&D poster for pictures of our
faces and Jubio, let's just say, I thought he was trolling me.
Oh no.
And in a...
Hit the GoPro cam, Jubio.
Yep.
fit of rage.
My girlfriend is kind enough
to draw this poster for us.
And because I was getting trolled
by Jubio last night, I
commissioned her with a snack
and said, can you please draw this
immediately and
come to my defense?
I'm being trolled.
And she drew this.
Whoa.
Which is Boobio.
And I just want to say that I'm
sorry to Jubio.
why I'm apologizing. Why are you removing points?
He didn't even know you did that until right now.
You didn't have... It's gonna stay between you and your girlfriend.
This was in the group chat. This was in the group chat.
Oh, I don't check that thing.
You sent a photo. You sent a reference photo.
Show my photo.
Also, if we're getting into this, I need my photos to be shown
and I need to get some...
-GoPro. -I need to get some...
Here's my photo.
-That's a nice photo. -One of my best photos.
So look at... Show the photo that I sent.
My girlfriend said she needed a better...
Now read what you said.
No, no, no, no explanation.
Just read what you said in response to that show.
With your hair, Cam.
With my hair?
Okay, now what did Cameron send?
I, okay, I said that because my girlfriend told me
not to have my hair.
Show the photo that Cameron sent.
It's just a photo of his hair.
But you know why?
Because he's following orders.
(Mario sound effects)