(upbeat music)
- Thank you Patrick for going down on your chair
so that it makes it look--
- I moved down so that Caleb does not look small.
- I look really, really, really small in these chairs.
- Yeah.
- But--
- I look tall in mine. - It's not true.
I'm actually pretty large.
- This cable thing is gonna be claustrophobic.
- Joining us this week is Cameron Fetter.
I'm treating you like a guest because you've been gone so fucking long.
I honestly don't even know who you are anymore.
I have a hard time relating to you.
I forgot what your Facebook's like.
Can I ask you a question?
So yeah, I didn't watch whatever episode you guys did.
I don't know who you guys are.
It was with Eric Grayhill.
You knew that actually.
Speaking of, right now you're also doing it.
You have a problem with staying in the frame.
You are addicted to getting out of that damn frame.
Just let, what is your question?
Did you guys already cover the coronation?
Yeah, no, no, you know why because I have something to say I wanted to say let's
all right real quick way. Hold on real quick. Tokyo shit. Okay. So basically
here's something that I wanted to say that I was hoping you guys didn't
already say. So I'm glad I got the chance to say it.
So yeah, the the coronation right. So
the UK
they these these guys are all ruled over by some crazy weird old white guy who
is completely evil in the government. Yeah, we hate the UK. Good thing America
is not like that, right? Wait.
That's what I wanted to say. Oh, wow.
That's pretty good. Yeah. I would have said...
Yeah, it's probably not for that. The audience doesn't wanna join in. I would
have said differently. I would have said, "So they're having a coronation over
there in the UK, meanwhile in the United States, we're having a corn nation."
Yeah, because that's a huge yeah. It's one of the biggest all the food we eat is
just corn syrup and I also probably would have said
Queen
didn't the lead singer that band get fucking AIDS and die decades ago. Why do
we give a shit about this about her dying now? So I want to piggyback off of
the corn nation thing. Yeah, I'd say they're having a coronation in the UK in
the states were having a corn nation corn kid fevered sweep in the country.
Everyone loves this crazy cone nation. Everyone loves the cone kid. What the
fuck is it? They're having a cone nation over in the United Kingdom? Yeah. Yeah.
And over here we have an ice cream cone nation. Yep. Fat people. There's giant fats
everywhere. Yeah. And then you can also do... And a corony, a coronary nation.
coronary ation coronary
coronary ation. Yes, everyone's eating the bacon explosion. Uh-huh. That's good.
Everyone's eating the bacon. Bacon explosion. It's a video on YouTube. You
can look it up. Talking to you about it earlier. I didn't listen to you. You
know why? Because you've been in a lying mood all morning. I've not been in a
line. I shit you not. Patrick has been lying to me about every little fucking
ticky tack thing here and there for no reason. I told Caleb that I was going to
I'm going to go feed my cat. No, no, no before this, no, no, no, no, no, you
hit you did two big lies. One was you said I have to go and I said where are
you going and you thought for a second you said
the pet store yeah, I was skeptical, but then you left and I came back as a
pet store. He's far away. It's thirty seconds later and I said where'd you go
and you said
it was too far away. It's too far away. So what are you talking? What first of
all, I thought okay, okay, the one that I bore witness to I want to I want to
all the evidence out before you can try and fight back here. The other thing
that when I the one I was here for was you said yeah, I have to go home to
feed my cat or something
like to feed my cat or something. I really just know you just had to get
out. I had to feed I to go home. I know what it was actually a pill. It was or
whatever I have to take. I did take a pill and I had to shove it down most
wrote. I know what no, I know the truth. He got neutered yesterday. I know the
truth. You
were in love with the Fios lady. She was in love with not want to be in
the same room as her because you thought that you were gonna act up. Sparks
were gonna fly. Sparks were already flying. Sparks were flying crazy. Hey
Patrick.
She said Patrick. Hey Patrick. She might listen to this. Yeah, he told her
all of it. He apparently told her, he said, "Yeah, I told her how much
money we make."
I didn't tell her how much money we made. I told her, I told her, she was asking
about, she was asking,
she was asking, she was like, how much, she thought that we bought this place,
and she was like, how much did you spend on this? And I told her, I was like,
"Oh, I don't know." I was like, "Whatever." I told her the price, and then
she was like, "Oh." And I was like, "Yeah, we get money through Patreon."
And then you pulled up the Patreon and you said... Yeah, and then I pulled it
up on my phone and I said, "Look at that." "And if we get to $20,000,
- Or make a movie. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - You should have taken her phone
and signed her the fuck up. - Yeah.
- Yeah, should have. - Yeah, would have been a good idea.
- I kept forgetting to ask her,
and I think that I told you guys to ask,
but you guys might not have, but there is a deal, right?
Okay, Patrick's Deals Corner, okay?
If you are a listener-- - If this is the only time
you ever do this, I want you to know
I'm gonna be fucking pissed off.
If this is the, if you-- - The only time?
- If you do like a-- - The Deals Corner?
- Yeah, a one-time, like that is the most lazy podcast bit
you can do. A deals corner? This is from now on, once a month you have to do this.
I told everyone about a deal last two episodes ago, or this episode. Oh,
really? Did you tell them in your corner? Well, now I have the... Can we get a
graphic going? Can we get a new graphic for Patrick's deals corner?
If you are a small business owner in the state of New York,
this month until June 30th, I think, or maybe the end of this month.
This is the... You can get... It's taking so long.
A $300 Visa prepaid gift card when you sign up for Verizon Business Fios.
You might be the worst speaker of all time. Yeah. That just took like a
full minute to say, "You can get a $300 prepaid gift card if you get
Fios." If you get Fios for business. For business. So you have to start a
business if you don't have one, if you want to take advantage of this deal.
I think most deals should be for businesses. Start a small, start an LLC, get a business,
get like an office, rent an office, then sign up for Verizon. Go into tens of
thousand dollars of debt. You need to be buying equipment. You need to go ahead,
even if nobody's interested in what you're making, make merchandise, make
hats, do all over print shirts that have your face on it. All over shirts that say
market that say fuck no, they don't say no. That's so no for the business that
you're making yeah and the business is called make a bit make and then make a
business called fuck shit poopy. I'm allowed to call it that you can't call
it that why you can't I don't think you can do profanity. Yeah, you definitely
registering for a I think you can do profanity if you if you city not a real
state correctly.
You censor it correctly you could do that. That's not our CK then that could
anything. F star C, K, productions. You do not think that you can legally put a star
on anything. Oh my God, he actually made a graphic. This is beautiful. Now I am so prepared.
I thought it said 2025, but the TV is just very angled away from me. It says, it's great.
Rick's deals corner. Yeah. All right. That's that settles it. Now you have to
keep doing that for pretty much ever. Now I'm going to find deals. Well, you just
need a, you need homework. You really do need some. I do have homework. What's the
homework that you have? Well, you have to make the finished your home. I had to I
setting up the Herculean effort for me. I had to keep calling. You saw me every
single day. I was in there. It took actually what I saw you every single day
was you going. Oh, I have to do the files. Well, no, you didn't see me on the phone.
fuck yes, I did and you didn't see me on the phone saying saying I did a
hundred percent. So you know, you know what I kept saying. You know what I
kept saying to them is like this has been a total headache. You do that. You
did the exact thing that I do on the phone where you where you walk or you
just come pace around and you're just like okay, great, yeah, great, great.
You try to sound really upbeat and I try to get even higher energy than
yours on the other side of the phone and that's awesome. Okay, thank you.
Thank you so much. Thank you. So you have an amazing day. Yeah, I don't say
I say you have amazing. I go like this. I ask them a question and they answer the question
and then I wait for a full five seconds and then I go, okay. That's how I do it.
How was your vacation? Oh yeah, Cameron went on vacation.
It wasn't really a vacation but it was nice. Just basically was in Plastow, New Hampshire.
Went to the Plastow shoe barn. Plastic, New Hampshire.
to the fucking Plastow Savers. I know this guy knows about the Plastow Savers.
You can find a lot of good Savers. Last time I was there I found a Tobuscus t-shirt. I
want to blast out the Savers. I found a shirt. I didn't buy it because I didn't want it,
but I sent a picture of you guys. It was gamers for the troops. Oh yeah. It's a good one to
find. Yeah. And yeah, it was pretty interesting to see everything. This sounds like one of
on the worst fucking vacation I've ever heard in my life. I wasn't even going to talk about it.
I don't know why you asked me about it. I was just at home with my family.
Just make something up.
Okay, we went to the casino
in New Hampshire. Dude, every time I'm in
Boston now, I see the
Encore and I want to go so bad.
I literally think if I still lived in like
Austin, I would literally be going to Encore like once a week.
Doing the most amazing kind
of gambling addiction. Can you imagine being able to take public
transport to a casino from where you live?
You have to take like a shuttle.
Oh, no, wait. No, because I was living in Revere at the
half time, but they had like a shuttle from the wonderland stop that you could
take all the way, which also wonderland
buddy, course, a wonderland wonderland is not in revere. Come on now
you're are you maybe you should say revere is no wonder. We're here is no
wonder. When you say wonderland, I don't have any is not in revere. You're
thinking of maybe never never land. Yeah, no, I'm thinking of wonderland.
what wonderland? Oh, Alice in that one. Oh yeah.
What other wonderland? I thought that wonderland was maybe, I think of
wonderland as a pretty generic thing of like, it's always somebody's
wonderland. So you could have Caleb's wonderland. Yeah. You could have
Santa's wonder, like, you know what I mean? Oh, Santa's a nice pole. I'm on
his side now because he said Santa's wonderland. Santa's wonderland, that is
a thing, right? That's what they call the thing at the mall. That's what they
call, oh no, no, no. So I think of a wonderland as kind of a generic, it's
utopia. Yeah. L Ron Hubbard's Winter Wonderland. Yes. Winter Wonderland is
what I'm thinking of. Yeah. So Winter Wonderland is true. That's a
checkmate. Santa's Wonderland is not a checkmate. Winter Wonderland.
Winter Wonderland.
Wonder Winter. But you just think it's never going to snow again. Yeah. We
didn't really get a lot of snow. We got no snow this summer. It was insane how
little snow there was and to a point where it scared me. But I guess it's
just in New York. Why did that scare you? Because that means there's going to be no more snow
forever. It confused me. Really? It snowed in New Hampshire a lot. I would go home and
there would be a lot of snow. But here in New York, good old NYC, not a lick of snow.
Not a droplet. There was snow one day though. But what did you guys do when I was gone?
You were like crying or? What did we do? I came up with my new rap name. White Phosphorus.
It's a good one. It's a really good rap name. It does kind of suck that when
you're me, just every rap name, you gotta have white in the name of it.
Yeah. Why does... Why can't I be just... You don't have to be white. Okay,
here's my new rap name then,
Amygdala.
Let's see, that's not... White Amygdala. No, just normal Amygdala. White
Amygdala. Just Amygdala. Or some part of the brain 'cause... Cortex. Cortex is
really good. Cortex is good too. White. Cortex. What about pons? White cortex.
Lele Pons yeah. What about occipital lobe? That would be
that you're getting in you're in a nerd world and I know I was kind of telling a
joke of maybe the juxtaposition of a kind of a nerdy brain part with a rap
and hip hop. Well, a rapper, a brain part, that's a
or brain part brain. This one's a little. This one's a little nerdy, but it
could maybe be crying trap.
that's a brain part corpus callosum. Damn, that's name is kind of his name is
pork
is pork is so loco
yeah yeah and that that would be his anagram rap. That's what I would. I
would have to it would have to be God. It'd be so fucking funny to be to be to
be a guy named Porkus and be like I'm going to be a rapper. What's my rap name?
I can't be anything about pork. I have to hide the pork is to reverse it. Yeah,
you can't be porky yeah, but it is such a good idea to work either rapper your
name or I mean that's the logic behind
be lack, but
you are luck, but you should always have
your rap name be an anagram of your real one hundred percent yeah tap
you that's every that's every every high school rapper yeah tap norad
that'd be kind of cool. That's no no no no no, it's like the Santa Tracker.
Right? Well, they do a little more than just Santa tracking. I don't think
your old friend.
I don't think so, man. I don't think they do anything.
The adult
much else, not my world
do that much. That's like when you're a kid and you look at a map, you're like,
oh my God, the North Pole
it's real.
but
nor is it. What else I do really good? I don't even know national.
I just know they do other stuff. Santa
national
I mean, it's definitely what they're most known for. I think it's some kind
of weather thing. Yeah, or no, they track saddle all the satellites around.
Oh yeah, yeah, that's what they do. National orbiting something rotation
radar. Yeah. Automatic device. Yeah, it's just a device.
What else did I do while you were gone? See, I feel like we
got to catch up. I honestly feel like I've been gone for a
hundred years. You feel like a stranger. I feel like I've been
gone for so long. I went to a restaurant on Friday.
That's a story. And my friend was there.
You are the worst. There is nobody worse at this job than
you, I think. What are you talking about? I went to a
restaurant. I guess my friend was there. Maybe this is just filling him in on my
weekend. Maybe this is too kind of
emotional. Okay, honestly, this job, I feel like any other job you go on
vacation, you think, God, I don't wanna go back to my job. Yeah, God, it's
Monday. But you are missing us so badly. Me, on Monday,
I don't even have to work on Monday, I'm still on vacation. I'm like,
please can I do some work on Monday? Yeah, please, please. Can we have a
meeting? I've always been like that. I've always been... You know what, I
I'm exactly like Carl Casper from Chef. I'm always doing my work.
You're exactly like Casper the friendly ghost.
Yeah, because you're white and your body's fucked up and weird.
Yeah.
And it ends in a weird way.
But my work relationship is really affecting my relationship with my son.
You are nothing like Chef, man.
I'm pretty much exactly like Carl Casper from Chef.
You, okay, first of all...
I have the same tattoos as him. They're all forks and knives.
No, you don't have any forks.
See, there's a knife.
you come in, you say snow's fucking weird and then you steal my chef
observation.
Wait, that's green screen.
My I was talking about chef two years ago and now you're saying, oh, I'm
the chef one. No, we have always talked about chef on this show.
I've still never seen chef. No, you're not the chef. We've never talked about
you being the chef. Caleb was the shit. The killer was a whole episode of
feel of being the chef. Oh, there was a whole episode about him being the chef.
I'm not saying that I'm the chef. I'm saying that I'm exactly like I'm saying
I'm like carl casper, not a chef. He's been trying to be a social media chef
lately. Yep, he has been. I have been. I could I've seen you've been working on
your plating. Yep, I've sent I send you my meals. Yeah, I see them. I think I
could never make that. Yeah, yeah. Really? Do you want to come over my
house for dinner sometime. No, do not let him over. He's going to make you the
biggest bullshit out of this. No, out of this. Here's what you're going to do.
You're going to go over. You're going to be like, oh, this is actually
surprisingly good. You're going to go and then he's going to be my airfare
goes up to four fifty. Do you want to watch? Do you want to watch Rick and
Morty clips and you'll go and you'll sit down YouTube. It'll all be just all
Jake Kinji Lopez videos that he watched. He copies all the recipes. That is not
chef. I'm not that is not a chef. You are doing Legos.
Yeah, following recipes is not what chefs do. Chefs create their own recipe.
I created my own recipe. Name one recipe that you've ever created. Well,
obviously, Patrick's delight is more of a cocktail. That is a cocktail.
Not more of a cocktail. That is a cocktail. I made a recipe, a custom
recipe this morning. What? So it was about one
a cup of water, okay, about one half cup of oats yeah and a
some and a drizzle of maple syrup, okay, sugar bits
that's oatmeal. That's my recipe came up with that is and you did not come up
with oatmeal. I added I came up with the maple syrup part. What color
you did not invent oatmeal because you put something sweet in it. It's all
it's that's temperature water. Did you use? I started it well. That's a good
so I started it with cold water and then I was able to warm the water up. Okay,
with along with the how do you manage to do that different? I did about one
minute plus one minute. What would you so to the microwave? What would you say
was could be texture of your creation at first at the end? Not at first? I'm not
I don't give a fuck about what
do this to me. What was it when you put it dry? No, and then I added the water.
I got a little wet when you put it in your mouth. Was it mushy?
Would you say it was mealy?
Yeah, but it was at first
what it was at first when it came out of the microwave, it was a little kind of
runny a little too wet, but adding the maple syrup actually was able to thicken
it up a little bit. You made oatmeal that's not a you didn't invent that you
I didn't look at a recipe. I just went in that I just kind of was like
freestyling like yeah,
but a half a cup of O. I'm like what the hell am I going to add this to make
this edible? So you went so you went through all your
water
and to finish just whatever was left in the where
it up from where the oats come from a bag or a big circle. Okay, is it a
what you call a can if it's like a cylinder? It's a it's not really a
can. It really is for posters the and a quick yeah, oh yeah thing yeah,
which was says what on it oatmeal in one minute. It's as quick and easy oatmeal.
It wasn't Quaker. I kind of try to get my stuff from I do more. You're stuff
like bowl and basket. What's bowl and basket? That's got to be some generic
brand, huh? Yeah, I don't want to make a really good.
They make good oats, a bowl and basket because I prefer it over Quaker because
Quaker just I don't know it's a text. You know, it's just no, it's just like
this money, then you're like they're using that Quakers image too much.
Yeah, yeah, it's also it's kind of they're exploiting him. Yeah, yeah,
they're exploiting him for profit. I think when making food, leave your ego
at the door. Right. What kind of what kind of leave your ego in the freezer,
though? That's right. I don't like that shit. I have a waffle maker. Do you
want to come over for waffle? Whoa, no, wait, I could make in the air fryer. I
can make chicken and then you could make the waffles on your wife. You can say
know he's out of this. He's out of we're going to start a restaurant,
waffles, waffles and chicken by
and he doesn't get to go. Yeah, why? Because he's been rude. You're negative.
Yeah, tell that to my disguise that I'd wear any restaurant. What would your
disguise be? Actually, don't tell me because I'll be able to tell scanning at
the door so you would not be able to wear a disguise. It would take my eyes
fucking replaced. I will get I would chop my hands off. He's about to cry
I guess, because you know what we're having to our restaurants, we're having
DNA scanning that scans it tells it tells the server in advance what the
people's allergies are. So the server doesn't have to ask your food. You
would probably serve DNA at your shit future restaurant. DNA is actually a
really good protein if it's prepared right. It's not good. It's not good to
eat. DNA burrito bowl. That doesn't make any sense. Yeah, dinner and
appetizers, that's what we have. I will go to your restaurant. I will, I will
address, you guys will think I'm a food critic and actually I will become one. I
will write the most scathing reviews. I will and I'll include all sorts of
stuff. I'll say the service is bad. I do holistic reviews. Yeah, what magazine
are you going to write for highlights for kids?
Try time out New York City. You're going to be in time out. Yeah, no, I
won't.
We're going to say we have a special table prepared for you and it's going to
be facing the corner of the room. Nope, I will be writing in vulture about how
but your restaurant sucks. These two ugly comedians did the most bullshit
restaurant of all time and by the way, the bathroom is stinks. The bathroom is
problem with the problem with you trying to do that is nowadays controversy
sales and honestly you're going to drive our sales through the fucking you guys
we're going to have one of those to no no you're not
you're not doing pink sauce. No, okay, you guys are going to have such a I will
curse you guys. You guys will have one of those bathrooms. That's the water.
I'm going to reverse the curse, reverse the curse. Yeah, so the water in my
bathroom will smell bad. Yes, yeah, God damn it. How did you do that? I don't
know
that's so I don't know how I did it. I just well if you two are so good at
thinking of a restaurant to come up with
tell me two things. Okay, number one, the theme theme is casual. Yeah, casual
Friday theme. Yeah. Oh, there he have and the chef don't wear outfit. There's
already a casual Friday. The restaurant is who you can't tell who the chef is
there's already TG, TG, that's thank God. It's Friday. This is still wear
clothes and this is you can show up as EDI. No every day is Friday. This good
day is Friday.
Every day is Friday and the chefs and get this the chefs and waiters. They sit
at the tables too. So you really can't tell who anyone is because there's a why
why are they?
That's the thing. Where do they sit now? This is a thing that we thought of and
something that we thought of that has never been done in a restaurant before
they cook the food at the table for you table, but only at some tables.
You're Benny Hanna is what you're thinking. No, no, you're doing Benny.
He works there. Who's he Benny Benny works at the yeah.
Okay, so that was my first question is the theme. So I guess the theme is that
it's always casual Friday and the waiters are are blaming it.
Waiters are it's indistinguishable.
And also they cook the food at the table.
Let me say that's also why we have to have the biometric thing because I know we're going
to run into problems where people come in and pretend to be waiters.
Yeah.
And I'm taking people's orders.
I'll cover that.
The dead giveaway is that I have no hands.
I'm going to hold the fucking plate.
Well, the first week, first week of your, like the first week that you're an employee
at EDIF's.
EDIF's?
Yeah.
Every day.
Oh, I thought it was EIF.
RFID chip right there.
FID chip right there and if you
we call it a big I F chip, it's proprietary. That's why it's so big. It
needs to hold a lot of data. It holds your entire. It's it holds every every
so it's a little stick of ram. So what's to stop me? We might
also mining cryptos and all of our employees arms. What's to stop me?
That's how you tell the employees that they walk around you just hear like
yeah loud ass. You see the probably they're they're coming to your table
with your water, right? That water is shaken, not stirred. They're fucking...
That hand is shaking.
Shaken water.
Yeah.
Shaken water. That's another one of our beverages. It's water that's shaken up.
It's shaken because we're mining so much crypto out of the rain chip.
But also it aerates the water.
Why did you say stirred? Like they usually stir water.
They make stirred water.
Where?
In all the restaurants.
No, most other restaurants have stirred water.
No, you want still water, specifically still water.
Stirred water.
So what's to stop me from... What time do you guys close?
never eleven fifty nine PM. We're open to one a. Okay, all right cool. So let's
just stop me from eleven fifty nine cruising in front of their there's no
cruising. Oh Benny, there's no cruising. It's not all right walking up front and
Benny's locking up right and I guess I'm not cruising. So I say Hey buddy, you
need to ride home. So that sounds a lot like cruising. He will. He would say he
would say no. I would don't want to ride home because we opening it in two
minutes yeah. Well, he's not working two days in a row, you because that depends
on what he's scheduled. Okay, so obviously I would go when I would know
his schedule at this point. So what's to stop me from giving him a piggyback,
but then we start we're walking and then we I piggyback him past his house. He
goes wait. That was my house and I just say nothing and keep walking and then
he's getting a little scared right, but then we get to my house and I
butcher him to death and I take his arms and I just hire a new employer. Do you
but I would go the next day and the RFID chip would be scanned. Oh,
and I'm walking around with these and by the way he's a different he's got
he's black guy. So I'm walking around with these black arms and I'm walking
around. So what would stop you from doing that? Probably the police, maybe
or someone who heard him screaming for help. Yeah, that's kind of outside. I
was what I was thinking an RFID chip in him and we have a tracker in the
office. The other thing about the RFID chip, so he went to my house. If you're
sure if your blood pressure drops, even by the slightest amount, it detonates
yeah. So if you cut his arms off a block, this is a high stress job. Wait, the
police, your blood pressure,
yeah, yeah, very high and drops it.
Okay, yeah, well you will he's he works at a restaurant. He's already full of
Ivan. So what I'm realizing right now is that I will
I am plankton
it slips so perfectly into the role. I realize right now that I would be a
perfect plankton and that, like all I could think about right now is like
ways to get into your
okay. So
well, I guess I mean if I'm going to play plankton, yeah
hey, this is per sponge bob and squidward. This is so perfect, not
Patrick.
No, he's not he's sponge bob okay. Well, he's kind of both yeah, yeah, okay,
and you're kind of squidward and sandy yeah, you give off what's the
vibes about me female female controlling the science part of the
I
I'm so glad I guess I guess Andy, because I'm a man, shit yeah, I'm live on land
and I breathe there and you have roots in Texas. Table is wobbly, so just stop
pulling on it. I always pulling on the fucking roller skate wheels on this
here keep pushing me back. You want to go back one last time I did that the thing
fell. Oh yeah, no, no, no, you're really between a rock and a hard place buddy. I
feel bad for you not
well, then I guess if I'm plankton, then I have to start my own restaurant across
the sea or the road.
Yeah, our restaurant's going to be underwater too. Yeah, I didn't think
about that now that I fucking that's my idea and I get a royalty now. Okay, you
and yeah, you can be royalty, the king of king, the king of nothing yeah, the
king of the kingdom of shit. That's what I can be yeah. That's bull. I don't
want to be that. Oh there's all site types of shit.
Your kingdom
I will be
I am going to be
man. I'm really glad we started talking about the restaurant. We're talking
about snow. I think now we have a real topic. Yeah, this is a restaurant,
which I mean it's we're going to talk about this all day. If we don't stop
right now, we have to get into the
we talk for five minutes about my restaurant, please, because you guys
were all time it out. I'll time it out. Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait,
let's start levels. Okay, ready? Yes, I'm going to start or he's going to
pull up. Okay, we'll get a timer. That's even better. Make sure you put it on
the starts. This is five minutes and eighteen fifteen seconds. All right,
started go. Okay, all right, so my restaurant will be the last fifteen
seconds of this video. Oh,
my restaurant will be if I need something from you guys. I'll ask my
restaurant will be across across the street from yours and my and what's
yours called every day is Friday. Yeah, EDI F's mine is called no day. Mine's
called six day week.
Okay, we're closed on Friday. We're closed on Friday. Chick-fil-a style. We
also serve pretty much all of Chick-fil-a's food, but all of McDonald's
food as well. All of Burger King's food, basically the top ten biggest fast food
restaurants. We go every single week. We buy a couple of things of every single
thing on the menu. We flash freeze it and then we reheat it when people is that
what the is that why you take Friday off? Yes. Okay. Oh, and you can't get our
food.
That's why you're yes, so yeah, but then also yeah, so that's why I'm going
after you guys. I have the top nine, but you guys are number ten and so I
really, really need to go get but what's your signature dish at
edia? We already explained it oatmeal. Yeah, it's oatmeal. It's oatmeal and
water
oatmeal waffles with chicken and we call them and we call them and we call them
water shakes really like a so it's just oatmeal and shaking water.
did you say chicken water? Because we have that specialties.
I just got the secret ingredient and it was that easy. You gave it to me.
Fucking terrible at your job. Spices being anti. You don't know the secret
formula. Yeah. And by the way, plankton knows it's called a crap. And by the
way, by the way, the secret recipe is maltodextrose. Okay, so I just got that
now. So,
but you don't know what paper we're wrapping in. Yeah, it's foil.
it's fun.
You have oatmeal and foil. Okay, so also I am hiring I'm spending half of my
half of the entire budget of the restaurant on
an anti plankton
guy who basically handles it because you guys needed one the entire time,
because every restaurant has a plankton yeah, every single restaurant,
somebody who is plotting on the downfall of the restaurant, trying to figure out
all the secrets. Yeah, so I don't know who mine is yet, but I'm going to make
I'm fucking damn sure that he dies. So I'm hiring an anti playing. I'm getting
I'm getting the the Pinkerton's. I'm hiring the Pinkerton's to come be
anti plankton security. Okay, and
yeah, you guys are basically going to go out of business. I'm undercutting
you in every single way. I'm going to make oatmeal with maple syrup. The
main thing you forgot is people can get food anywhere, but an atmosphere. Yep,
and a place where you can't tell who's the waiter in the chef. Yep, you can
only get that one fucking at your table. Well, my atmosphere is even better.
all the water's flavor. We your restaurant has no atmosphere literally
because we just sucked all the air out of it with a vacuum and all what if I
know it's underwater. So I guess it does. No, I pump extra oxygen into mine
like a like a I guess all your guests are passing out from from over
oxygenation. No, because it's a perfect amount like a Vegas casino and also
every single clock. So people sitting there will eat for two days.
Every single table at EDIF does have its own ozone machine.
We have an ozone, which is a place where you can go get masturbated.
Okay, you're being shut down by the government?
The health department is going to shut that down.
It's a separate thing from...
You can't get tug jobs and shaken water.
Why? That's how they shake the water.
No.
No, it's not.
Don't say that. That's horrible.
We also have...
We shake it with a proprietary shaking machine.
And we also have...
I have bitches who twerk with the water on their butt.
You don't even have what I thought Cameron said earlier, but now I'm going to implement
it into the restaurant, which is chicken water.
What is that?
What's chicken water?
So it's shaken water with chicken essence in it.
What is a chicken's essence?
A chicken essence?
It's like a little bit.
It's another secret formula that I can't tell you.
We can't really tell you about it, but it's just the top.
And guess what?
It's maltodextrin.
No.
Chicken water is good, though.
Yeah, chicken water is fucking good.
I don't want to talk about chicken water. We can do that.
We got to talk about what... You're ceding your time? Yes.
I'm ceding your time. What we are here... Wait, I want to see what
the last 15 seconds is. It's probably... Is it just like a subscribe button?
I bet it is. For Adam Eshborn? Oh my God. It turns different colors.
It's a fun party. That's unbelievable. Okay. So today,
if you guys have been with us for years and years,
you will know that one of our favorite websites is mysticinvestigations.com.
mystic investigations. For those of you don't know is ran by a man. His name is
Xavier Remington, and he is basically the
foremost investigator of all things paranormal. Yeah, I think he is. He's
earth's link to this supernatural world kind of. There's a couple of things
going on. The most important thing is that he documents all of it, and he's a
very intelligent guy. Yeah, he's basically the smartest person in the
world. He will be one day he will he will be his name will be spoken along and he
works with an organization called Mystic Investigations. Well he's the head of it
which Mystic Investigations is based in a school kind of a Hogwarts situation if I
remember correctly. He has a lot of information. We've been over it a couple
of times but today we decided to make a return because it's been a while and
he's got plenty of new information. Oh yeah. To share with the public. I mean the
The last time we investigated mystic investigations, one, we didn't even
scratch the surface because we just happened upon, actually it came into our
- it was fate. Yeah, yeah, we accidentally discovered it. We, it was an
accidental discovery. I think I googled how old is Mrs. Claus. Yeah, yes, that's
exactly what it was.
Yeah, and because stuff like that, those kind of esoteric
questions, he always has an answer for. Exactly. And I would say that's exactly
what he's kind of the king of the esoteric. Uh huh, 100%.
percent. So
I focused on we each did our own little mini investigation into Mi. That's what
we call it. Yep. And today I well, I found a couple of things. One was we
click on this, Julio, so that I can I can use the thing.
Is it off?
It's completely off. Okay, but now it's on.
Photos prove Dubai is strange.
I didn't click on this, or I did click on this, but I didn't end up doing an
investigation into this, but I will say this caught my eye in a massive way.
This photo to me does prove to be a strange. It's a woman in a bikini.
And what is that behind her? That is a bunch of bales of hay?
No, it looks like some kind of roadblock, maybe.
Oh, okay.
So I did not do, I just wanted to mention this up top, but I did not
actually do my investigation into that. I did my investigation into Xavier's
this article on the supernatural stench.
Are you guys familiar with the supernatural stench? No, no, no, I've
never heard of the supernatural stench. So I'll tell you about him.
The supernatural stench, the supernatural being known as the stench, is the
premier paranormal purveyor of sinister smells. Amazingly, he was born Stefan
Stank in the year
1939 in Nantes, France. Although the surname itself doesn't mean wretched
stink, but rather a standing pool of water, most likely stagnant in nature.
Stefan was born with the psychokinetic power of fragrance manipulation with a strong emphasis
on biological stench generation.
At a young age, he became fascinated by making people suffer and even become physically sick
via sickening scents.
This was seriously seen when young Stefan took a dump so wretched that they had to evacuate
his elementary school in the process.
Most of the students suffered from varying degrees of sickness while the janitor died.
The principal recalled seeing Stefan laughing hysterically under an oak tree, being the
only one who wasn't barfing.
Wait, let me look at the date on this.
Okay, April 23rd.
I just wanted to make sure that this was not some kind of April Fool's prank because I
will say...
Oh, this is recent.
This is a new article.
Yeah, this is a pretty new one because Xavier, being a man of culture and academia as he
is, would not normally say, "Take a dump."
I know so it's a bit out of character, but
yeah, I guess another thing to for people who aren't familiar maybe with
the mystic investigations is it's a big it's paranormal, but it's a big focus
on holidays and holiday. So we see a lot about well because that's a
cause they don't fool the Easter bunny. Yeah, so this is I this is that's
the realm we're in right now is the suit kind of a universe where the
Easter Bunny and the supernatural stench could yeah, the stench prodigy
has the awful ability to amplify his body odor, bad breath, fart gases, and an armada of alarming
aromas. Stank's flatulence is one of his greatest weapons as his ghastly gases can be terribly
toxic along with zapping the oxygen out of a room. With an exponential increase in the
smell comes excessive levels of hydrogen sulfide, methane, and carbon dioxide that could easily
kill a person. This vile villain can also amplify the stank of other people near him
to varying degrees. The stench has also been known to power boost pleasant
smelling things such as cologne or perfume into something so strong that it
induces headaches and nausea in his victims. Generally his stinky powers rely
on a biological host having contact with the odor of origin. When his powers are
in use his eyes glow a light shade of brown that almost looks orange. Nose
emoji. I like that. I like generally his stinky powers rely on a biological host
having contact with the odor of origin.
The odor of origin.
He smells bad if you can smell him.
Yeah.
You see, this is, I feel like a lot of the, what I found interesting about this one is
a lot of the characters that Xavier writes about are usually, like you said, people from
holidays.
Holiday lore.
Holidays.
I don't remember any kind of stinky holiday in my life.
I do.
The Stench Cult.
Stinksgiving.
Oh, Stinksgiving, true.
This is the Stench Cult.
Stefan also uses his stench generation abilities to raise money for various
purposes. Oh, that's not so bad. He can force people out of anywhere in seconds
and then and then rob it of everything. He is also a hit man for hire who will
take down anyone's foes via felonious funk. Stefan has occasionally allied with
the plague doctor by using aromas as a vector for disease. Everyone put
remember the plague doctor because he will be reappearing. Put a pin in that.
Oh wow. However, the high class doctor turns his nose down on that on
your nose too. Clothes pin due to the stink. He turns his nose down at
the nasty homeless stench and uses him sparingly only when necessary.
Still, Stefan begs the plague doctor to let him in on the secrets of
dark immortality as he pushes into his 80s. He also strives to hone
the powers to absolute stench status. Indeed, Stefan does live as a
traveling, disheveled homeless man in large cities around the world
with the most concentration of people and repugnant rank.
This filthy fiend loves skulking about sewers,
breathing in the toxic aroma of human waste.
He has acquired enough money to live a grand life,
but it goes against everything he believes in.
Most of the money is used to fund
his perplexingly poisonous plots
and the crazy cult that supports him.
Of course, every supernatural lunatic has a cult,
and this one is full of the most disgusting people
you could ever hope to meet.
So here's what I like about this.
It confirms two of my biggest suspicions
about any given homeless person is that number one, they have plenty of money.
They just don't want to use it. Right. And number two, they are probably a
villain. So any given homeless person, usually an elderly one or something,
they, there's a pretty high chance that it's Stefan stinking disguise. I guess.
I didn't even think about, yeah, you have to read the thing about Xavier's
writings is you have to read between the lines for things like that because you
know, he's not going to tell you straight up. He can't tell you straight
up. These words are too, you know, the concepts that he creates are too
boggling for the human mind that he has to tell you through riddles like
this. Yeah.
Like Stefan, all... Yeah, I know, we're getting a call from our landlord.
"All cult members are expected to never take a bath, brush their teeth,
or partake of any proper hygiene. Although he does provide mystical remedies
so members stay in fighting shape and don't find their teeth rotting out.
The stench and his foul followers are responsible for the recent.
What does that say celebrity supported no bathing movement? What the hell
this has already supported
imagine this is people discussing people like Britney Spears that yeah,
celebrity. Yeah, if you want to call them that in the name of preserving
their skins precious
microorganisms and despicable skin oils
bathe responsibly and you'll be just fine. Some of these celebs are secret
cult members who bow to the stench as their guru. If you know someone with
noxious B.O., then odds are good that they are a cult member as well,
especially if they give the excuse that it's good for their skin. Their ultimate
end game is to return to the dark ages where nobody ever bathed, or if they did,
it was once a year. They pray for a stench-ridden society, polluted with
blasphemous biological sewage.
- And what's that emoji there?
- That is a poop emoji.
- No way.
- Whoa.
- Can you believe that?
- That is nasty.
The Stinch Slayers.
Ooh.
Okay.
Yeah.
There is a small group of brave warriors known as Stinch Slayers.
They hunt down cult members and force them into showers and baths,
soaping them up really good.
Afterward, they make them put on freshly laundered clothing
and begin the process of deprogramming.
The hope is re-assimilation back into society
to lead a normal, clean, and healthy life.
So far, they haven't gotten close to Saffan
due to his overwhelming scent manipulation,
superhuman strength, speed, agility, and senses.
Superhuman strength?
Well, yeah, he did mention that earlier, I guess.
Wow.
Their dream is to scrub this guy clean, give him a seriously close shave, and lock him away
in a room devoid of scent.
This sick puppy hasn't bathed since the 1940s.
1940s?
Goddamn.
Most of the stench slayers have either lost their sense of smell or wear protective gear,
although such gear can be forced off or have one little accidental crack that allows stink
to enter.
Some have psychokinetic powers, such as stench removal and scent shifting, to combat the stench
and the followers ripe with rank stank.
If you know someone with barf-worthy BO, then urge them to take a shower and use some deodorant.
If they angrily refuse, then assume they're a brainwashed stench cult member and contact
a paranormal professional for help.
If you spot the stench himself, then prepare to vomit or even die.
See, this is one of the things that's nice about Xavier Remington 2 and Mystic Investigations
is this stuff always has kind of a societal message. It's something like, it's like, okay,
so we're talking about the supernatural and magic and you know, but you know what, actually,
a lot of this stuff matters. This will matter in your day to day life and there's a meaning
and theme behind it.
It's prescriptive.
Watch out for your friends.
It's saying go out there, if somebody's on the street and they look stinky, then you
you should probably be kidnapping them, bringing them to a large bath, dunking
them in it, and shaving their face.
And a room devoid of smell.
A room devoid of scent.
They should make some kind of, you know how you can put up like soundproofing
foam and stuff?
Yeah.
They should have smell proof.
Oh my God.
I know they have air fresheners and stuff like that, but I want specifically a
foam that I put on the wall.
That'd just be better.
Yeah.
Okay, so, and then this is I think just the last thing that he decided to
include here, which is the infamous B.O. episode of Seinfeld. The video above features highlights
of an episode of Seinfeld called "The Smelly Car." You can watch the 20th episode of Season
4 here, and there's a link, which I don't think is probably good.
The attendant in the red jacket is a representation of a proud stench cult member who has worked
diligently to build his body odor to the point that it can be spread to other people and locations.
The art of rank stank spreading is a key practice within the crazy cult. The goal of every cult
member is to make their stench take on a life of its own and live on even after their death.
In sitcom form it's funny, but in real life it's no laughing matter.
That's actually, honestly that last sentence, that is true to me about almost everything.
Or if I see it in a sitcom I will laugh my ass off, but if someone says something to
me in real life I will say, "Oh, okay."
I mean think about even other Seinfeld stuff. Think about the Soup Nazi.
If there was a Nazi for soups...
I don't think it would be that fun to me if I if I said, can I please have a clam
chowder and can you take all the clamp it just the chowder please and he says get
the fuck out. I thought I'm the fucking Nazi. Yeah, look at my Nazi tattoo.
Yeah, that's not funny. I'm an effing Nazi. Yeah, but no. Yeah, you know, you
cannot have soup. I'm a Nazi. Yeah, I'd go. What the fuck is going on? I
probably report him to the cops. I feel like I'm I would honestly I would I
would feel like I was in an episode of TV, but not a sitcom. No, I feel like I
first of all, of course, first of all, I'd say what is this Seinfeld yeah, but
then I would say then it would sink in. I would say no. What is this curb your
enthusiasm? Yep, then I'd say no, but he would get he would probably like the
soup so much that he'd just say, oh, who gives a shit? Who gives a yeah, it
gives a shit if it's a Nazi, but me personally, I'd probably go back and I'd
probably fucking execute him. Yeah, probably blow his brains into the so I
would go into the soup Nazi. I'd go, I'd shrink myself, go into his body, start
playing with all of his little pieces. You know what I would show myself to be.
I would change my size to be. I would be maybe half, maybe a quarter of an inch
smaller than him, so I could go inside of him and just be fully my full body
inside of him. I would stay regular size, pick him up
and then put him in a blender, right? Cook him down with some tomato paste or
something. You'd make a soup out of him. I would make a soup out of that Nazi.
I'd do all that, but then I'd also shrink to half my size. And then you'd
swim in the soup on a crouton. Yeah, you know what I'd say? You know what I
do I'd say after you're doing yeah yeah I'd use it like a kickboard yeah here's
what I would say I would he'd say all this BS Nazi bullcrap uh-huh and I'd say
yeah big surprise soup surrounded by fucking crackers oh shit yeah damn and
then I good fucking insult his cracker ass and every way I think of yeah he
would crack he crack under the pressure he'd crack another pressure I'd say
that's right I knew that was coming all right um who's next who's next with this
I can go next.
All right.
Are you sure?
I feel like you have a bigger investigation than I do.
Okay, if you want to go next.
I can.
Mine is kind of brief.
You said who's next, which implies you don't want to go next.
I'll go next.
I'll go next because I don't have too much.
No, it's not Patrick Steele's corner.
It's not.
Get out of the Steele's corner.
Put that away.
So I was looking yesterday.
So I was looking around on Xavier's Twitter profile.
Metaphysical PI because guess what happened you guys?
The craziest thing.
Metaphysical PI is team follow back.
Really?
Team follow back metaphysical PI.
So I sent them a DM.
I said, "Hello Xavier.
I've been very interested in mystic investigations for a while now.
Big fan.
Was wondering if you could answer some questions for me.
Xavier is so elusive that I did not hear a peep. Look at that.
Left me on read.
Honestly, because of his metaphysical nature, he probably tried to type it back
and his hand phased through the motherfucking phone.
He probably got trapped in his keyboard and is now in a cyberchase-style situation.
Trying to type you a message back.
Yeah, but he's too small. He can't even press the keys on the circuits.
Also, you can't... Yeah, there's no... Yeah, it doesn't make a lot of sense.
It doesn't make any sense.
he needs to be it makes no sense at all. There's not a keyboard on. Yeah. So the
first so then I'm just clicking around his page. So I'm clicking around. I'm
just trying to figure out all this stuff. You're trying to see why does it if
maybe he has some kind of like text back guide. Yeah. So then I saw this.
When you'll crush text you. What these emojis mean. I've been looking through
his page and I got interested immediately because he was talking about
shaman George Lucas, guided by our powerful shaman, George Lucas has been
in contact with force goes from a bubble universe where Star Wars is real goes
to mo. The reality was created by the human collective consciousness belief in
his stories. Lucas hopes to join them as his afterlife someday. He wants to
George Lucas hopes to become a I would be so pissed off if I died and it was
Star Wars. The afterlife was
you, do you mean you would go to star wars or you would be a ghost like in star
wars? No, like I would go to star. You would wake up like the afterlife is star
wars. You wake up and kit fist. I think that like kind of that would be I would
be pissed off because I would be like it's a real like come on star. I would
why not something else that I like more yeah, it was for everyone else. It was
star wars. I would learn to love it. Yeah, I probably would too. I would learn
to love it. Here's the thing about star wars.
The franchise is indeed based on a true story. The Jedi, the Sith, the fourth
Force, Rebel Alliance, and the battle against the Galactic Empire a long time ago in a galaxy
far far away are real. This includes Emperor Palpatine, Darth Vader, Yoda, Luke Skywalker,
Han Solo, Princess Leia, and the rest of the characters to an extent. There is also the
original trilogy and prequels that involved George Lucas. However, the latest trilogy
in Disney's hands loses touch with what actually happened to these legendary people. The evidence
that Star Wars is real has been suppressed by the government with a controlled release
to the entertainment industry. That explains so much about the last Jedi.
Mm-hmm. This is oh, yeah, because look at this.
Lucas sells to Disney and the real trilogy is lost.
Damn. Yeah. Lucas gave his story ideas for episode seven through nine to Disney,
but they chose to take the more creative route
and made up their own stories for the most part.
George also tried to convince Disney that Star Wars was based on a true story,
but they thought he was nuts.
Although later on, Disney's government connections
in the U.S. Paranormal Defense Agency made them think otherwise.
Unluckily for them, none of their psychics could get confirmed contact
with the Star Wars galaxy, and they were hellbent on telling their own tales.
It is thought that the character of Rey was a substitute
for the real Luke Skywalker's daughter, Anika. Wow.
As far as we know, Palpatine never had any kids.
He was the quintessence of evil at a height
beyond any desire for love, sex or procreation.
In fact, if he had a child, he would see it as a threat to his power and eradicate it.
Despite George losing his way for a time, he has been promised force-go status upon his
natural death as a reward for telling the Star Wars saga.
Can you go back?
I'm shocked that nobody wanted to let Palpatine hit it raw.
He's disgusting.
Gross.
He's got kind of like...
Sheave?
He's got kind of like the tired white boy.
He's got Pete Davidson eyes.
Yeah, he does.
Oh, he does actually.
Yeah, maybe he would actually smash hard.
I feel like I would bet money that genuinely a US some kind of US
government agency has tried to get psychics in contact with the Star Wars
galaxy. Oh, yeah, that's something that they do. No, they were like yeah in the
in the s and shit they were just going for yeah, all the like remote viewing
thing where they would like get people with ESP to be like they'd be like draw
pick, draw a picture of the moon yeah and they would draw a picture of the
moon and then draw a building on it and then they'd be like Holy Shit. Oh my
we need to lock you in a room for a year. Yeah, so if you thought that these two
slides were the sort of rude to the Disney trilogy here, okay, wait until
you see this next tweet that I saw from Xavier mate.
Kathleen Kennedy is trending as she is the darkness of the Star Wars universe,
the fundamental source for the dark side of the force. She and her allies
managed to lock the bringer of light George Lucas in a cosmic cage. Will the
Jedi of the righteous light be able to save him. We need to save George. We
need to look at her eyes in that photo. She does look demonic. She looks
demonic as hell. There's a bunch of other stuff about Kathleen Kennedy
too. Kathleen Kennedy announces that Star Wars the Rise of Skywalker will
end with the revelation that the last three movies were a bad dream in the
mind of a drunk Ewok. After that she was stepped down in a new team who
knows what the hell they're doing will redo the trilogy. Not! Fatality.
Yep, so this is between posts about how Santa Claus is actually fighting the
yeah, there's a dark version of the April fool, April, anti for
anti Claus. Yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, so these are these are all in between that
a year ago. Yeah, this is about the Disney Star Wars hotel flop
Xavier had Xavier had this to say to fatherly HQ.
I heard it was too fake and expensive most likely Kathleen Kennedy was
involved in this debacle in some way.
She's the one behind all the Star Wars failures.
I'm not sure why she hasn't been fired yet.
Yeah, Kathleen Kennedy has re-upped her Lucasfilm contract for three more years.
Thank God.
I don't know how Star Wars or any movie franchise would ever get along without
her not.
Wow. I mean, it would have been not that big of a deal and we wouldn't need the gunshot
until the last.
The knot is incredible.
That is a scathing knot.
And then I saw this here, #NorthKoreaChristmasGift.
Oh, I love that hashtag.
Yeah.
I'm known to peruse that.
I'm always browsing that hashtag.
I read this one a lot. North Korea Christmas Gift. Some are saying Kim Jong-un's Christmas
gift will be remaking the latest Star Wars trilogy, including Star Wars, the
Rise of Skywalker. Apparently he'll star in it and defeat Palpatine.
You know what I have to say to this? You know what I have to say about this
one? What? Points. Yes.
This is kind of an at midnight.
Yeah. There is a lot of these at midnight style Xavier tweets that I've
been looking through.
Baby Yoda problems. Oh, that is definitely an at midnight one. Baby Yoda
made off some made some offhand comment on the Galactic Twitter and it wasn't
politically correct. Now, baby status as a media darling is over as they hate
spews forth like an intolerant hellfire. He tried to clarify, but it's too late.
He's ruined for life. Poor Yoda. Points are laughing emoji. Points are no points.
I think no points. So laughing emoji is spiteful. This hits a little too close
to home because I think even Yoda, sadly, even Yoda could be a target of the
woke left yeah, especially baby yoda grogu exactly, which like they're all
they probably try to get baby yoda kicked out of high school exactly. Now
I want I want you to read the school. I want you to think in the for this next
one. I want you to think in your head. Just imagine Johnny Carson saying this
okay, all right.
Now do my best. There's one retweet on this. Okay. I'll do my best to try and
sound like Johnny. I'm closing my eyes. Okay, uncle Ben's will rebrand and enter
the world of science fiction.
They will either feature Obi-Wan Kenobi or Ben Parker from #Spider-Man as the new Uncle Ben.
Most are expecting Ben Kenobi to win as people want rice that is strong with the Force.
(laughter)
Could you see Carson?
Yeah, I mean that sounds very much... I don't know if it's because you were doing the impression or not, but it did kind of sound like it.
That sounds, that's written in Carson's voice.
Yeah, a little bit.
This is Xavier, I think, tapping into, using his powers to tap into other
interdimensional beings like Johnny Carson.
This next one here, I guess this one more is like a Jay Leno.
So hit the J on this.
You know, every time I see Hoda trending, I think of Yoda.
And how that would probably be the name of his wife, who feels allowed to get married.
Yes. You know how you name your wife?
Oh wait, Dan's here. Wait, pause it. Landlord is here? Okay, alright. Well, so that happened.
Okay, so this next one here, again, if we're going with late night hosts, think about this
one in Jimmy Fowlens' voice. I can't really do, he doesn't really have a discernible voice.
have a voice. He doesn't even have a voice yeah.
Do you remember he would do? Thank you cards
no okay. I'm the only one that remembers that
thank you, J. J. Abrams for letting Luke Skywalker go nuts on Palpatine with
amazing force powers. We've never seen him use for Anakin having returned with
as a force goes with a major role wait that never happened. Wow, oh wow, then
I'll just burn through these last two hashtag how star wars should end the
first ghost of Luke Skywalker ends up on Earth in one thousand and seventy
one and shares the saga of Star Wars with George Lucas
points that's points that's points. Then I thought the Phantom Menace was
trending because they were remastering it by deleting Jar Jar Binks from
existence.
Dean and then this last one here, I put this in here because I felt this one
so episode
six through nine are not really the real outcomes. That's why they seem so
lackluster compared to the others. Good to know. Also, hi, Xavier. Are you free to
talk?
So this person is saying that this is because they started going off the rails
of the actual history. So this is basically like the first six of the
Bible, and now they're doing kind of a Mormonism kind of thing.
Yes.
It's getting wacky.
Okay. That makes sense.
Alright. I did mine about another holiday being that I was very happy to
find.
This is very interesting to me.
Okay, this is who is the Mardi Gras Joker. Oh my God. Wow. And this is a
picture of the Mardi Gras Joker. Pretty scary for all you people who can't
look good. It's a jester.
It's a scary gesture. No ordinary gesture. No suit looking a bit
supernatural in nature, a goth jester. But here I'll go ahead here and
retell you guys about the Mardi Gras Joker. The Mardi Gras Joker's real
name is Frank Farkas, but he's long since abandoned that identity. Frank began as a
low-level criminal who utilized theft and intimidation to create wealth, all the
while enjoying the torment of innocent people. There's some evidence he had
abusive parents and may have once had a speech impediment that caused him to be
bullied as a child. At some point, he discovered voodoo magic and found he had
a deep interest in it. He realized his natural talent for dark voodoo and began
training under a voodoo master named Trailfeeze. His powers grew and so did
his criminal enterprise, which began to employ its own thugs. Isn't this the
same backstory as Sweet Tooth? No, Sweet Tooth was a serial killer. It's funny
you say that because they do mention twisted. I don't think I put it in, but
the way that I found this article was from a list of apocalypses and they
mentioned twisted metal and they're worried about this. So being a dark
master of voodoo magic grants the Mardi Gras Joker immense paranormal power. On
top of that, he taps directly into the spirit of Mardi Gras and Carnival.
fall. Oh, my God, thereby adding its metaphysical energy to his body. This
not only increases his magical abilities, but also grants him enhanced
superhuman strength, speed, agility and senses. He also has a slight psychic
ability to sense danger afoot. So the power of the Mardi Gras Joker is it's
he's Spider-Man.
Oh, true. He has the senses. He has the exact same powers as Spider-Man. He has
funny senses.
His weaknesses may include those employing an even greater voodoo against
him or the use of other forms of magic. He is considered virtually the top voodoo
practitioner on earth, so it would probably take a group of talented magic
masters to take him down. As the leader of a holiday, he needs a magical
artefact of some type to channel the holiday spirit into his body. This is
often a crystal, such as Santa Claus's infamous Christmas crystal.
The Christmas crystal. Which we all know about the Christmas crystal. I feel like
we don't even have to go into that. I'm starting to remember it a little bit,
but yeah, people can do their own research. The infamous Christmas crystal.
I remember it being blue. Everybody knows it. Yeah.
Once his supernatural status had sufficiently increased, he set his sights
and metaphysically taking over Mardi Gras. He has warped the spirit of the
holiday into a dark force that he channels through his own deformed soul
awaiting damnation in hell. Although he doesn't care much for the devil
emperor of hell, but does like the self made king of hell, Dimitri Diablo.
The Joker now works with other forces of darkness around the world to destroy
humankind. The goal is to bring about a party apocalypse to shroud the world in
eternal darkness and violent partying, plausibly like something seen in the
purge films, except twenty four hours a day every day for eternity. One of his
most recent associates is the plague doctor. Remember him often employs new
genetically engineered STDs during marty crop. As I've heard of this, the Joker
has also been rumored to have terrifying ties with an even more famous jester and
even more famous gesture known as the April antifool, which way more famous.
Everyone knows the antifool. There are also recent associations with various
clown cults. Watch the purge films to get a frightening feel of the party
apocalypse ad. So there's something I noticed this now. He has a bunch of ads
that are links to watch movies like he got a bunch of I think he got
sponsorships for with some streaming site or something. Oh, did you click on
any? I didn't click on them because they say ad
and basically as a child of the Internet. I know not to clean no better
yeah
update twenty twenty one. The Mardi Gras Joker is livid about the cancellation
of Mardi Gras and other carnival celebrations around the world. Due to
the coven nineteen pandemic, the Joker has cut ties with the plague doctor in
discussed as he as he initiated the
oh my God, Saint Nicholas is happy about this development as Shrove Tuesday
pushes forth the greater spirit of Christmas amid the weakening of the dark
Mardi Gras spirit, another win for the supernatural forces of good. So this is
kind of bearing the lead, but he I mean he the the big breaking news here is
that the Cove in nineteen pandemics completely manufactured by the plague
doc yeah yeah, I mean pretty crazy. If you had no idea, if you sit down and
think about it, if you sit down and think about it, that makes complete.
notice. I didn't say the plague doctors, you name that's true yeah, but this is
where it takes a turn here.
I'm hoping nobody walks in during this part. This I saw this at the bottom of
the of the article here, Mardi Gras Joker stories, the Mardi Gras Joker's
role in the George Floyd
this is the first link
I clicked on this yeah yeah protests, riots and civil unrest rage forth as a
result of the dastardly death of George Floyd, even we even when he's talking
about this, he's doing a literation, the dastardly death. This crazy chaos has
included looting, vandalism, battles with counter protesters and major
property damage and violent police response.
There is one confirmed sighting of the jeopardous joker at a New York City
protest. He wasn't wearing his complete gestures costume, but his apparel was
odd enough. He and his cultists were where inciting violence by throwing rocks
at windows and police. The joker laughed loudly like a loon as he flung a few
rocks at police clad in riot gear. Two officers ran toward him and shot the
joker with pepper spray. It had no effect and again he began beating down
on the police with superhuman strength that broke their face shields. Other
officers moved in while his cultists ran around destroying any cameras trying to
film, the spectacle, I'm going to ask yeah, but there you go. He wrote it in
another officer tased him and the joker's response was. Are you trying to
turn on me boy? Turn me on boy, turn me on boy. Oh my God, he forcibly grabbed
the taser away and shocked several officers. They drew gruns, drew guns
ready to fire when he quickly recited an incantation and clutched a voodoo doll
that looked like a cop. No, the police suddenly froze as he frolic away down an
alley and disappeared within ten seconds. They were moving again. Wow,
so the the jester. I like the idea that one all the cops look similar enough
that one voodoo
just a voodoo doll, which is a big like pot belly yeah. It is a really fat.
That's so cool, man, so he's actually he's actually pretty much based yeah
that he's attacking the cops yeah. Well, so this kind of gives you an insight
into what exactly
of evil,
but there's a little more here. Protesters gone missing. Oh, there have
in reports of protesters who mysteriously disappeared during the violence or were
later found dead. The police have denied responsibility. In some cases, it's
non-paranormal serial killers and other sick puppies, along with sex traffickers
looking for new victims. New victim exclamation point, by the way, looking
for new victims. With the rest, it's the Mardi Gras Jokers cult, kidnapping
people for sacrifices or brainwashing them into their organization of terror.
This also goes for the plague doctors cult, who also love spreading COVID-19
and other diseases within the large crowds. Various evil witches and warlocks
they're also searching for fresh blood sacrifices to their demon or dark deity
of choice. Many have the false illusion of feeling safe in crowds, especially if
they are like-minded people out for a single cause. Remember that you are in a
sea of humanity that is a target for supernatural sharks out for your flesh
and blood. Always be on alert. So if you're in a- if you ever go to a protest,
just keep your eyes out for witches, warlocks, plague doctors,
Mardi Gras jokers, vampires. Honestly, guys, you're better off not going to any
protest. It's dangerous. It's dangerous, very dangerous. There could be all sorts of
ghouls. There could be a warlock. Yeah, and that's all my slides. There could even be,
and also if you would, I mean other dangers of protest, nudity. People are going and they're
showing their penises and their vaginas. There are women sitting criss, or spread eagle.
Uh huh, and crisscross. Pussy ass. They're sitting crisscross and appropriating Native
American sitting circles. Yeah, well that would be basically something that we should
protest yeah, but do it quietly. You sounded like you were about to spit do
it quietly and go to a protest. If there's one or two people there yeah
that you know is not a vampire yeah or a marty grodd joker warlock ghoul type
something I didn't put in here that I forgot to put in that. I just remembered
the marty grodd joker. Also, he hates if you compare him to the batman joker
really really well, then I'm not going to go there. We're going to go ahead and
go to the episode before we get anywhere near that and also you know what I'm
Our landlord's been knocking on our door for about 15 minutes.
Really? He's still there?
He's just kind of walking around like a Sasquatch.
Okay. Bye guys.
It's just the most...
Why do our bodies hate what's good for them?
Yeah. You know what I mean?
Why the hell is this?
Why is it that vegetables taste like doo-doo to people like us,
but candy and bread taste so incredible?
Yesterday I had probably the worst diet I've ever had in my entire life.
I ate breakfast, lunch and dinner, all three of them were sandwiches.
Jimmy John's. Yeah, Jimmy John's.
Yeah, Jimmy John's.
I had a breakfast sandwich, a tuna sandwich and a Jimmy John's sandwich.
Those were my meals of the day.
That's...
That is such a bad way to live. You do that every day, don't you?
That's what you're gonna say.
That was a good couple years of my life.
Just three sandwiches a day?
With sandwiches and chips.
Three square sandwiches every single day?
That is so fucking good.
I also be the first maybe on a podcast to welcome Jimmy John's to New York City.
Yes, for green ordering on Best Buy.
They do it right there.
Yes, they really do.
I didn't know they didn't have Jimmy John's in.
I thought Jimmy John's was a like a Jersey franchise.
Oh, that's Jersey Mike.
Wait, hold on.
Yeah.
That's fucking embarrassing as shit.
Can you can you imagine being the first morning radio?
You realize you could do this?
Got this shit and...
Yeah, I always think about what was the first,
the first, like, noise that they put on a soundboard for, like, a stern or whatever.
I mean, they were probably putting, like, Amber Alerts.
They got all the utilities.
Back then, all those children were getting kidnapped.
The buttons used to only be for Amber Alerts and, like, weather reports and stuff like that.
And then one guy was like...
A child has gone missing in Orange, New Jersey.
[Gunshot]
[Laughter]
Oh my God.
Tornado alert for your county.
Oh my God!
[Laughter]