I
saw a bug and Tifa is back where what oh you're fucking don't even say it. Let
me say it. I know I saw that it is very well. Okay, one year ago, a tech. Do
you guys remember what happened? I remember bottle through the way I can
a low class cheapo bottle of beer, a hipster beer, a hipster beer, a hipster
beer, a Dutch piece of shit, some Dutchman, the flying Dutchman through a
Heineken, through my window, crash my window open, slam, millions of particles
of glass. If I'd been in that car, I probably would have my carotid artery
sliced up and down, tic-tac-toe. Do you think about that though? Maybe it's
not Antifa, maybe it's the flying Dutchman? I have considered every option.
Okay, an antifas like, but I thought I was safe. I put a bunch of coexist bumper
stickers on my car, Bernie bumper stickers, the Bernie back yeah dog dog on
bird on bird
bird. What
said a baby on dog on bird dog, because they like because it's a revisions like
animals, but a dog
sticker on the back. It's my original sticker. You get a guy. We get a baby,
sell the sticker is a pretty good idea. Baby is a bird, something like that
baby bird, but
it didn't save me. They knew the make and the model and they knew the
license plate, which by the way our license plate also got stolen last year.
I remember that we have a new license plate, too. So where are these fuckers
even? How are you? I was in a GPS tracker breaking, but maybe maybe that's
why maybe they have their spreadsheet. They're like okay, here's all the law
abiding citizens that we have to harass and ruin their belongings today. Let's
see well. Oh, we haven't done this license plate yet. Let's do it. So true,
but I know they deal this one and make it a
like put it on a kill dozer and then get them in trouble. But honestly,
knowing them, they probably have a checklist where they do each license
plate at least four to five times. That's true. They stole our license plate.
Now there's a but we get photos. We get all the time. That's what photos of a
gray Acura driving down the do you remember the highway number?
You know what actually happened? They did they they broke your window. They
checked off your license plate and they were like wait. I know how we can get
again. We'll just take the license plate fuckers, then we don't have that one
it's unchecked. So I wake up yesterday yeah, I'm getting poked in the face by
my wife
poked directly in the face and the morning. It's the weirdest way to wake
somebody up first of all, so I'm already pissed as fuck. She says somebody
smashed the side view mirror off the car and I just said all right, I'm used to
it. This is how fucked up it is. I'm used to it at your car is such a piece
so now I have a pink hand mirror from Walgreens duct taped to the side of my
car. It doesn't do anything. I can't see anything out of it. I have to lean. My
face has to be in the steering wheel to see the angle that I would normally see
with the side view mirror. It is great. You know what it is? My life's over.
Have you considered using robotics so that the side mirror can be adjustable?
The hand mirror? Of course I considered robotics, but I barely know how to do
that. Yeah. Your car, though, is like,
like, maybe, maybe it keeps getting attacked. Maybe it keeps getting attacked
because the hood is being held in with zip ties. There's... That was the other
thing, they sabotaged it, trying to kill my wife on the highway. All over.
What happened? Some... They tried to kill my wife. How? They undid the latch
suspiciously a day after I was doing something with the hood of the car,
but they must have gone in after me and un get the latch and forgot to close it
and then she's driving on the highway. One Hundred and Twenty Miles an hour,
the wind, the hood flies up, crashes the front window, explodes on her and her
sister and my dog. Whoa Jesus, while they were driving down the highway,
they didn't call and then they had to call somebody and the girls are not
very good on the phone. No, no,
hey, what are you wearing? Yeah, so now I'm in a situation where I think that
she's cheating on me with some some, but she's just trying to make conversation
Exactly. She doesn't know any other way.
What's your favorite color?
Yeah, that kind of thing.
What's your favorite color of car?
No, then you shouldn't come fix this one.
But yeah, dude, I
just don't know if it's worth it
having a car for me.
It's getting so fucked every single which way, up and down.
You need to get a smart car, dude.
No one's touching a smart car.
That's not true.
People are going to pick up a smart car and carry it away.
Yeah, exactly. Go put it on top of a light pole
I think about it every time I see a smart car. I think I could put me in
like five other people could probably just take this and not even in a not
even a really strong yeah, just no, just five people yeah period and five
any gender and just could be picking this car me. Yeah, I'm a fit in my
living room. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I did not even consider when
you're when you're terrible. What is say your say your pickup truck gets stolen?
There's only so many places a pickup truck can be a big parking space, a
the field, a big parking space and parked on the line between two spaces.
That's where I would look for a smart car could be almost anywhere. Yeah,
they could put it in the bath, a public bathroom. Imagine a smart car right
there. It would fit easily. It would fit so easily. God, maybe that's why it's
so smart, so compact and I'm having an idea. What? Yeah, we should get a car.
I wanna get a car for the business. Can we get a car and keep it inside?
But I just don't want my car anymore. I wanna, I wanna get rid of it.
Yeah, this happens for scrap. This happens one week after one week after my
in laws say hey guys to all the kids and their significant others say hey guys,
we're getting rid of our old car. Does any we're getting a new car? Does
anybody want this old car? And I said
no, I don't want this car. I have a car already now. I want it and now and now
wait say that again. You say say it like so say you just say it again.
So they said, "Does anybody want this car? We're getting a new car. Does anybody want
this old Honda CRV?" And I said, "You know what? I already have a car. I don't need it."
And then what happened? And then they smashed the mirror off the side of my car.
Is that a new addition? Why did you lie? That wouldn't even happen in the... That has nothing
I was Larry David worked. I wasn't like no. I don't want the car.
What's
it? I didn't say like him. It was that sign to your
I didn't say that at all damn. I just wanted to show it off. Yeah, there's
going to be an opportunity to there will be. He will do something kind of
rude and later. My older brother suggested the Wilhelm scream.
that's gay. That's gay. That's all right. Sorry, man,
not happening. It's not happening. I was looking like before before
before I felt I was trying to think of something new to add and I was going to
add. I couldn't find a good one, but I was going to add epic fail. That'd be
good. I think that I'd like that, but the Wilhelm scream, the Wilhelm scream
is what's the what we do that when someone gets hurt. Yeah, I'm an ask
credit post flies out a window. What are we using that one? It'll it'll like
I could we need a sponge bob my leg. That's pretty. That's a good one.
That is a good one. That would be good. If somebody that's like a almost a
strict level up on the yeah, that's the same thing, which is better thing.
My leg decimating my brother's suggestion, so fuck out of here.
Yeah, we can keep that one, but we would have my leg there. Yeah, if we
yeah, yeah, because we would have been like we insulted this guy so badly. He
hurt his leg. Yeah,
holy shit,
but besides that had an amazing week. Why is it departed again? Well, let's
talk about the elephant in the room. What the submarine everybody talking about
is a submarine. You guys don't know the submarine. Oh yeah. Are you kidding me
buckle in? I know that once I get I'm going to get into this story too late,
but like the people that I saw what in God's name are you on about? Okay, so
basically kind of annoyed me. Okay, it annoyed him, so we can't do it. Can't do
it. Basically, there's this service where this is this has been the big news the
past the past few days, so we're definitely too late to it, but I but
it's I'm kind of obsessed with it right now. There's this the service where
they these rich people they pay to go down and look at the Titanic in a
homemade submarine. It's the service where these guys built a submarine and
they take people down to where is the Titanic crashed really, really far down
like far like you should not go down there. I mean I mean on a summer, I
don't know. I don't know. I don't care the ocean, the water in the
the Atlantic. It wasn't a lake. No, no, man, this time, but this you should see a
picture of this submarine. It's literally homemade. They've got parts of
it from campers world. There's like a video of this guy talking about it. They
control the submarine with a knock off Xbox control. Okay, that's how they use
it. They control it. This is cool. This is
twenty million leagues under the sea. This submarine is completely that's the
controller. They use to control a shit. It's modded and it's lost right now. The
people are almost certainly dead. They've either blown up it's it's lost
it's gone yeah. They can't find it. There's no somebody past cost two
hundred and fifty thousand dollars per person. Who are these people that
they're just rich people who like the Titanic
and they're gone. They're almost the most dead and there's like a bunch of
videos. I've been surfacing of like the past like year because they've been
doing it for like a little while yeah, and this is like I guess not the first
like there. There's a thing of some guy being like yeah. They took me on it. It
it's pretty cool and then I was sitting on the and the boat like watching the
control panel and then they they yeah they lost the submarine for five hours
and they turned off all the wife on the boat. So we couldn't tweet about it.
That happened like a year ago and I think it's always there's all these
videos of the guys who invented it being like like yeah, there's no seats in
here. There's just one window and check it out. This is what we used to control
it isn't this cool and being like yeah. I got this part from like I mean yard. I
hate it. I'm on the side of a small business. That's what I and that's what
I'm saying. Everybody's saying why would you ever get on this submarine?
everybody's saying this is this is insane. That she is so stupid, the
being obsessed with the Titanic, who gives up the touch? No, you're on
your is completely right. This is the only problem. Here's the submarine
yeah, no, but what I was going to my point of is. Can you imagine you first
of all building a submarine that works at all enough to go down to the
Titanic two point three miles under the ocean? Yeah, that's not to do any
amount of time any like you do it a bunch of time. Amazing you built it out
the parts that you bought it to try of of you're not a scientist. You went to the
store and you're like they're doing this handle looks good. I guess I'll buy
this handle. They're doing my summer named kids next door to buy for
technology, a million dollars per trip.
Well wait, I think I just figured out where the titanic thing went for to go
the delightful children from down the lane. Oh yeah, they struck again. I
think they definitely definitely took it out, but the inside of it. It has no
seats. It has what it looks like it looks like it looks like that. Look up
it looks official man. Wait, you see the inside. Yeah, wait, go back up, go back
up that picture right there. There's no seats. It's just a tube. There's a
toilet set into the floor. Can you shit in it? You can shit in the toilet.
How they fucking died? Did they shoot the shit out and they died in the
submarine? They died because somebody crapped and they fucking smelled so bad
they destroyed the thing. Well, I don't know about you guys. When I get
stressed out, I need to take a really stinky shit. Yeah, and I would be one. I
would be really stressed out if I was trapped under the ocean. Where are they
where they're leaving from? It's an impressive story outside. Where do they
leave from? Is it a- It's a boat. Oh, here's the other thing. No, like what,
like- Where do they port? Yeah, where do they port? I don't care, the ocean. You
keep saying, "I don't care." I'm just asking a question. I don't know. We're
trying to learn about this thing that you said you're completely obsessed with.
I don't- where did they- okay. Anyway, the cool thing that I was about to say
that's better than where they came from is that also you can't get out of the
submarine from inside, you're bolted in and the only way to get out is if a
crew member if you come to the surface and they take they completely unbilled
this. Whoa! So even if these people who are lost got to the surface, they would
just suffocate inside of it. Oh man! Yeah! Yeah! So this is not the best
this submarine. I'll say it sucks ass. It's crazy. Look at it. Look at the guy
who's driving. He's not even driving. It's remote controlled, but he just sits
there. He looks out the window. Jesus Christ. I think it's cool, man. I think
it's so cool. I don't know. I feel like if you get in that thing, it's just just
like the Titanic. If you get in that thing, whatever happens to you, you
deserve it. Think about it. I mean, through the Titanic. Yeah. 100 and
something people. Actually, maybe it was more than that. How many people died in
the Titanic? It must have been more than 100, but I don't know. I think it was
big back then. I mean, the Titanic was quite large. Titanic was Titanic. How big
How high was it look up Titanic death count?
It must be it must be pretty high. I'm going to guess they made a whole
fucking. I would say I would say 500 is my my kind of say six hundred and
twenty three fifteen hundred people. Oh, and there were two thousand two
hundred forty on board more than fifteen hundred
oh fifteen hundred died. I guess I mean if you get on that fucking kind of
suspicious that exactly fifteen hundred died. Don't you think I think it's
inflated straight up?
Well, yeah, I mean there was that you know life was worth more back then
we're worth less back then. Actually, they had little kids going into
factories and shit and putting their fingers in machines. Life was worth more
because you live short, less people and you live shorter. No, it's worth less
because they didn't have like the phone or the computer or anything. Yeah, what
do you do like to do a basic hyper pop? Well, that's what I was thinking. Okay,
I watched The Departed the other day.
Uh-huh.
And you know the sex scene in The Departed?
Jubio, pull that up.
No.
The sex scene in The Departed, they start fucking and they play...
Comfortably numb.
Yeah, they play comfortably numb.
Yeah.
And it's like, what, did, I just, did people used to fuck to like classic rock all the
time?
Yeah.
What do you talk, yeah.
That's awful, man.
They would have like the radio on.
They wouldn't be able to control what it is.
There is no pain, you are receding.
You're jeered at.
Honestly, I can't imagine fucking without Hyperpop being in that dick.
I need my play play Bill Withers or something. If you're going to put a
sex scene in a movie before they had Mario, I saw something I saw like
this video this dude like breaking down
what like
like hi fi audio equipment they had in movies and I guess Matthew Damon's
hi fi set. Matthew Damon so incredibly expensive. Oh yeah, the one that she
plugs her headphones in to listen to the CD.
I guess that thing is like, you know how like the audiophiles get all like insane about
like, "Oh, there's too much hiss on this."
I guess that is like...
So that's like, I think it was like a $15,000 like hi-fi set or something.
And back then that was a lot of money.
It's basically chump change now.
That's how much I'll probably have to spend to replace my mirror at this point.
That movie is so good though, The Departed.
Yeah, Fie.
That's the best Scorsese movie.
One of the best.
Well, it's top three.
Yeah, Goodfellas is obviously his best.
I'm pretty excited for his new one.
Yeah.
What's the new one?
The Flower Moon.
The one about, did you see the trailer?
You should watch the trailer, it's really good.
Really?
Yeah.
Who's in that?
Everybody.
I'll watch anything he does.
Leonardo DiCaprio, Robert De Niro.
Scorsese, I'll watch anything he makes.
He's in the movie this time?
He's behind the camera.
Oh, well he's not in the movie then.
He's a rat.
we actually don't know yet, because all I've seen is a trailer. Yeah, very well
be in a movie there. That'd be cool to have like a cameo where he just walked
by in waves. That's what I'm not. Sean Malone does really basically yeah, yeah,
yeah, that's the twist. That's a real twist. There's always like a UPS
driver. He has the best cameos. Yeah, and signs they he's he plays the guy
who killed their mom in a drunk driving accident. He's a bad guy. Usually
they like an old that's
a director came. It's the best cameo ever, because it's they like they don't
tell you that that he's that guy yet, but you know that that guy exists or
whatever, and basically the whole family like is walking by and they see him in a
restaurant and they all just look at him and go. Is that him and I'm not sure I'm
a yeah point,
and then you realize it's like they mean that he's a drunk driver, but it's
really good. Wow, I think I would do that if I was a director. It's so cool,
but I'd get I'd have he does he's as a slap shop commercial and the new his
newest one. I would know shit. I would be with he's the slap chopper. He's
Vince, he makes up a slap chop type commercial.
That was the craziest thing ever.
We've talked about this before, but just like the slap chop guy, he slapped and chopped a
woman with his mouth.
He chomped.
He did a slap chomp?
Yeah.
He bit.
No, he got bit.
Oh, well that's the complete opposite.
Yeah, then he should be slapping and chomping her in defense.
But it was like his story, the slap chop guy's story was that he was a failed comedian and
and then got paid to do...
I would say he's an extremely successful whatever.
Yeah.
Well, he made a movie in the 90s.
He made a movie in the 90s called the Underground Comedy Movie where he does blackface and stuff.
It's like, "Oh, how do I make the most offensive movie?"
And then he made...
So then after the success of Slap Chop, he made Inappropriate Comedy.
Oh, I know Inappropriate.
Which was supposed to be the sequel to Underground Comedy.
Oh, okay.
I never watched it, but I would always see it on Netflix when I was a kid.
it's Rob Schneider. It's a yeah then the whole the premise of that movie is like
all it's like vignettes but it's all like through it's like oh well this
that's what's happening because of this app. Honestly I'm sick of movies having
premises and if I made a movie I wouldn't have the premise. You should do
like some Dublin 95 type shit. See that's a premise. That's a premise? I thought
that was a crazy rule. You just did a premise. No it's not a rule. The only
the movie rule that I would follow is a golden rule. Yeah, I would probably
follow the rule of using a camera to film it and beyond that, all bets are
off.
My whole movie would be doing this.
You can make a movie every single day. That's what Apple should do instead of
their damn goggles. They should make a camera that works with your fingers. I
agree. Fingersquare camera. Here's a Apple, Apple, knife, nope.
Hey, Apple, here's a question. How come the slogan of Apple Vision isn't "Become
the apple of your eye. Think about that. That's pretty good. That is good. This
guy's or a half an apple of your eye that you that's the apple of your eye.
The apple of your eye, the apple of your eyes is what it should be. The apple
for your eyes. That's what it should be. Wait, I phone iPhone, I Mac, I etc.
I eyes, I paid glasses like from super monkey glasses. I paid for apple
vision. Yeah, whatever happened in the eye, they say, call Apple Vision Pro.
And also, this doesn't make any sense. You put on the headset and you see stuff
and it becomes an apple, that's their whole product? That is not it, but you
could probably make it. You were close, yeah. Well, what's the product then?
It's a type of goggle that makes you see the world through Steve Jobs' eyes.
Yeah, but he only ate fruit. Yeah, exactly. And he was a bit of a fruit.
for a year. So every single food that you eat when you wear the goggles, it's like fruit.
No, it doesn't taste like fruit, but it looks like an apple. Is that why they're called
Apple? Uh huh. What? Because Steve Jobs ate fruit? Yeah. I think it was well before he
was a fruit. But it could have been that. I don't know. He's a fruit. A Terry and try
to cure his cancer with his fruits. People always say that, but I don't who I think it
was probably that in the last year of your life, if you know you're going to die of cancer,
like fuck it dude I like fruit. How many fruits can I eat? He's probably eating dude. Like
if I spent the last part of my life eating sunflower seeds and beef jerky because I knew
I had chemo or I was going to die of cancer and the chemo wasn't working, would everybody
say like he tried to cure his cancer with beef jerky? Yeah I would say that. You would
say that? Yeah actually I would say that. I would start that rumor I would say that
the only thing that he ate towards the end of his life was the new spicy sweet chili
Doritos, Jack Links. Yeah, but it's just because I like them. It's not because I was like,
"Oh, this is going to cure cancer." It's going to cure... The nitrites are going to cure
the tumor. Yeah, that doesn't make any sense. It's grown in my mouth. The guy liked grapefruits
and watermelons. Yeah. Who doesn't? Maybe if he got grapefruited before he died, he
wouldn't have died so sadly. What does that mean? Getting grapefruited? You never remember
that video where the lady shows you how to give a blowjob with a grapefruit? First of
all, my dick is not fitting to the end of a grapefruit. No way. That is just... She's
he's going to need a lime for me at that point
and it's going to stay yeah and it's going to stay and even then it's just
going to sit right under the head right. It's going to be like that the juicer
thing yeah yeah exactly that's that's the exact like process like that's like,
but she says you put your dick through the grapefruit and then I'm still I put
my my mouth on your cock at the top wait. That's this guy's dick is fitting
through a whole grapefruit all the way through. What the hell's wrong with this
guy? He needs to go to the hospital. He's got an elephantiasis of the penis.
Yeah. It's disgusting. It's disgusting too, 'cause I mean it's like
grapefruits kind of have that... That's not the fruit I would want to be eating.
Yeah, the taste of a grapefruit is kind of like... She better have that
shredded tongue. In my head it tastes like ink. Grapefruit kind of tastes like
when you accidentally break a pen off in your mouth. I used to like grapefruit
when I was a kid. I used to eat grapefruit for breakfast. You put sugar
it though right? Tons. Yeah. It was worse than fruity pebbles. Plain grapefruit as a kid is
like, you're like, oh, I thought there was going to be a big orange. It's fucking bullshit.
I wouldn't call it a romantic fruit or a sexual one. It's also kind of an expensive fruit.
That's why people think it's sexual, because it's pink and it looks like a damn labiar.
It does? No it doesn't look like it. What kind of labiars are you sitting on hanging
A big round one?
With a rind?
That's the jizz.
You jizz on the outside in a perfect circle?
The rind is actually all the cum that girls have.
Girls don't have it, they weren't born with cum.
Girls don't cum.
They can get it installed, but it's a very expensive procedure.
Yeah.
I heard about that.
I heard about that shit on LinkedIn.
You didn't hear about that on LinkedIn?
Do you have a LinkedIn?
I never did.
I had one for a little bit. Yeah, I made one for the podcast. I made one. Yeah,
we got one for the podcast. I think I might either made my my linkedin is it
says says co founder at Sullivan, the frog enterprises, and so I get a bunch
of emails all the time. They're like linkedin. It's like then it's like hey
new job opportunities for your position co founder.
One day we should go through our like our employee directory and all that
stuff that we just made for no reason. Oh yeah, it's all private on our notion. We
have like a
we have an employee director on the website, but we also have like a
business. We have a secret one. We have one. What do you call a mission
statement and all that stuff that's just sitting in our notion that nobody can
ever read? Yeah, it's pretty cool. We should put out a hand, but we are a real
company. Yeah, it's true. We are a public. We don't have any employees, though, do
something? Yeah, we do. We have just contractors. We just have one contractor
and it's Jubio. We have two contractors. And patches. Wow. Just wow. Yeah. One of
them really looks like a contractor too. The other one not so much.
Okay, today we are doing... One guy looks like he knows his way around a
contract. Yeah, exactly. Today...
No. Yeah, if it wasn't already obvious from the, you know, the fucking title of
episode in video. What's that? That's the apple of your eye. Today we have
something so special for you guys, which is, have you ever been assaulted? Yeah. By
who? Parents growing up. Most people don't bother with me because they can
tell that I'm it. Brother and sister. I do think that happens with me. Yesterday I
brought the dog to the dog park and there was a bunch of skaters around and
I was fantasizing about the skaters all attacking me at once and me killing
every single nobody fucks with me, except for younger kids, because they don't
know
most of you have a crazy situation. I don't want any smoke, but like sixth
graders, I wouldn't played basketball and with Noah and me and we're playing
basketball, torching them. By the way, he stepped in shit and walked home. He
stepped in shit. He walked a big fail, tracked shit through my apartment, a
full hour long fail where I beat him at basketball. Then he hurt his ankle and
he stepped in shit on the way home. But anyway, besides the point we're playing
basketball. Why are we making fun of him? He had the worst day ever. And a bunch of kids
are riding their bikes and their scooters in the middle of our game, right? And as if
this wasn't pissing me off enough, like a four-year-old kid rides a scooter so slowly,
like it took him like a full 90 seconds to get from one end to the other. And as he's
doing it, he keeps saying, "Watch out for me! Watch out for me! Watch out for me!" over
over and over and over again and I wanted to kill this kid. Children are so
annoying. That's a horrible thing to say. Watch out for me. Make your parents
should say that. Yeah, watch out for him. Yeah, this kid. Hey, watch out and say
it once and that means that the kid had the wherewithal to realize that he was
in the middle of something where he could get hit. He was doing what he
wanted you to do was chase him and tickle him. I guess I'll do that next
time. Yeah, there was this little kid that would run around. He lived like
behind the skate park in Nashua.
And he would like run up and down the ramps
to like try and get people to hit him.
So that like his mom who had crazy anger issues
would come over and try to fight the skaters.
It was so insane.
He would like run up and down the ramp
and then like look at you like,
like while you're trying to like go down
and like try to like run into you.
So you'd have to like dodge him.
So like no one would go on the mini ramp.
And then there's this one time he like
almost got decked out and then some kid just went like,
"Yo, fucking move!"
And we heard his mom over there just go like,
"What the fuck did you just say to my fucking son?"
And then she ran over and while she's coming over,
the little kid ran away and we go,
"You guys are idiots."
And then ran away.
- Homophobic story.
- How's that homophobic?
- You've tried to hit a little gay kid
and his mom got mad at you?
- I didn't try to hit a little gay kid,
I was just doing little kid voice.
- Little kid voice?
- Little kid sound like this.
- This kid was gay and you were bullying him
at the skate park.
- I'm not bullying a gay child.
the bullying. I'll be one of the baby. No, he's trying to he was trying to be
included. You think he thinks that he was trying to you think it should be
excluded. You should be executed. He should be executed because he was
annoying. Next time a kid interrupts my basketball game, I am going to run at
them. I'm going to get you because if their parent comes and is like did you
say to my kid I'm going to get you like what are you talking about? Yeah, he
fucking crazy liar. Your kid is in the middle of my basketball game. I just
said get out honestly. You should keep him away from me because I could
could accidentally kill him. I could accidentally get him now. I'm not
saying I'm not if I was dribbling the ball towards him, it could kill him. We
play with a heavy ball. There's a regulation NBA basketball. Yeah, fifty
five. It's pretty easy. It's pretty easy to like fake a fake an attack on the
kid. Yeah, they just run away. Yeah, you just like flinch at anything. You
have to do is around just like you're you like shoot like a half court shot
and like aim it towards. Yeah, and just say what
yeah, Kobe full chest pass. Yeah, I thought he's playing. Sorry. I thought
of my
I'm shacking a fool.
Anyway, he was the only other person on the court with a shirt.
My fucking team. Yeah, yeah, he's undersized for his position. Yeah,
whatever. Yeah, mugsy bogs or whatever. Yeah, but he's a court general. Look
at who it was. The mugsy bogs. Yeah, okay. He was like five five. Yeah, but
he could dunk
five four five dunk. Yeah. So today, if you ever find yourself in that position,
we're talking about martial arts that you can use to destroy basically anybody.
Martial arts that destroy a child.
For mine, I decided to look around on some of the martial arts forums. There's a lot
of them and they're very, very active and they've been active for a long time. This
first one is a post that says, "Gangster Rap is making a comeback." This is from Wrestling
Karate Champ. He said, "Youngbloods, 50 Cent are making gangster rap hot again. What are
you thoughts?" This is 2003. This is the height of 50 Mania.
Wow. Oh my God.
This is a height of 50 mania from wrestling karate champ who's a brown
belt by the way. Yeah, you can see you got a picture of a brown belt there. He
gets shut down fast. Yeah. Yeah. Valtor says I generally but not exclusively
prefer music with literary depth and vocal tenure over rhythmic monotony and
superfluous rhyming green. Wow. And read that signature. Keep smiling. And this
guy, so this guy, he's a pre black belt is a bocha dog. Oh, okay. So pre black
rap out. So yeah, he should be should listen to the brown belt. Listen to this
guy. Yeah, yeah, he shouldn't take offense. This is here. The brown belt is
oh everyone hating on rap. Why?
Oh my location Brooklyn. Oh my God, we can go hang out with this brown belt
shot. High school. He's a first name. He was in high school in 2003. This man is
probably older dead now old or dead. Yeah, anybody could be dead. Yeah, it's
not like an old. Yeah, he's dead from karate.
you know.
This guy is just one single post. I didn't include any replies because
people are just saying what is wrong with you. Mostly, but this guy says Hey
guys, I do not have any interest in becoming a competitive fighter. I want
to become one of the most lethal human beings
able to protect my family and others. I want one day to be known as a walking
killing machine. Wow, based on this info, what are the right arts for me to
everybody. Thank you very much. Everybody people this guy everyone shut him down.
There's a problem with these forums. You come in and you say on it. You'd be
honest. You're like I want to become a key, a killing machine. I want to kill
every single thing I want. I want bugs to be afraid of me. I want plants to die
when I walk by them and people give you nothing, dude. Yeah, so no, no advice.
They give you a guff, yeah, complete guff, and they're making fun of this
fuck. They give you guff and then they say, "Fug off," which is the reverse of
backwards. But he sounds like a jock to me. And this next one is jocks.
How about that's enough guff?
This next one is jocks versus wimps, okay?
Oh my God. We talk about this constantly.
Yeah, I mean it's a defining social order, Peterson style. Jocks usually are drawn to
the "Fuck, I made this too small."
You did make it too small.
No, I'm going to get closer. Jocks naturally gravitate to the something martial arts.
Wimps normally gravitate to martial arts which are long on kava and short on competing.
GBR, I gave him the GoPro, you can switch to that.
Wimps will argue with the jocks on the web about which martial arts are the best,
but the wimps will never face the jocks in an NHB match to prove the argument.
This is because, deep down, the wimps know they will lose to the jocks and lose big time.
big time. Okay to your camera and lose big time. Say it says this jock,
but then a somebody responds and I want you to tell me if you think this person
is a wimp or a jock. Okay, okay, here we go. Go to the highlight the Google
site, press a button.
This is Edmond Blackadder.
You think he's a jock? No, no, no, no, he's a wimp. Knowing from the show,
He is a total wimp, but he gets jocks to do his bidding.
And he says, I stand between the darkness and the not bright.
And he says, is that because jocks can't handle real martial arts and must limit themselves
to the rules limited ones?
I'm more of the opinion that real martial artists spend their time training, not trying
to prove how smart they is on this here interweb thing.
Then again, their entire sites dedicated to the angsty wannabe who thinks that his UFC
foo will save his lame ass in a street fight.
Us wimps make sure we stay away from these morons and actually hope they do try for a
submission when we roll. Makes it easier for us to stick 'em good with our blades. ROFL.
Your argument is that if one doesn't compete, one is somehow a wimp. I say if one only trains
to compete, one may hold trophies and medals, but be ill-prepared for a real fight. Having
talked to a number of real deal people like Hawk Hakim and Mark Hatmaker, I tend to have
a low opinion of the sports-only let's get in the ring and see who's a real man morons.
Personally, I think they and the whole pressure test your art crowd suffer from some serious
problems. They should be like the French and run away, but the job fires back.
The jock says
us. So he's quoting him, Edmund Blackadder and says the I'm too deadly
to compete argument. Thanks for the example of how wimps argue, but are too
afraid to fight. But Blackadder comes back strong as he does and he brings a
poem. Would you say he goes forth? He brings a poem called Gentleman Rankers
by Rudyard Kipling from 1892.
Kipling.
And the entire thing is too long to see on this thing, but basically he, this is the
utmost known from Wimps, I would say.
So Wimps came out on top here.
Rudyard Kipling wrote the Jungle Book.
Wimps weren't Jock Zero.
I don't know.
I don't know who Rudyard Kipling is.
So Wimps are a bunch of racist stuff.
Well that makes sense that Edmund Blackadder would be a fan of him, I guess.
He's also a big Rowan Atkinson fan, if that's his fucking name.
I mean, clearly.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then I just have one more thing here, which is from another martial arts forum.
The topic is, "Has a gay guy at your academy ever make people feel uncomfortable?"
This person says, "Has a gay guy at your academy ever make people feel uncomfortable?
There's a gay guy that joined the academy I train at five months ago.
He's not bad for a blue belt.
Actually has some skills.
And he acted like a very decent guy at first who's very cool and chill.
But he started acting weirder and weirder each time.
He told everyone he was kicked out of at least 5 other academies before because they were
bigots and felt uncomfortable with rolling with him.
He posted all over social media which academies it was that kicked him out because they were
bigots, intolerance, things like that.
But now I can see why.
The guy makes a lot of my other classmates feel uncomfortable too.
Like for example, when he introduces himself to everyone, he always brings it up that he's
gay.
I mean, who the fuck cares who you like to bang?
This is a grappling class.
Stay on the subject.
And he would say weird, nasty things out of nowhere while doing a water break.
Such as, a lot of guys hate tossing salad, but love getting their salad tossed.
Nobody said anything, and were grossed out.
While the gay guy was laughing all by himself.
Sometimes when he rolls with people, he would have a creepy smile right afterwards or during
a roll.
I made it clear I don't want to roll with him.
He makes me feel uncomfortable.
On his Facebook, he posting pictures of him making out with multiple dudes all at once.
I had to unfollow him and so did a lot of people that I trained together with.
Our instructor didn't want to say anything because he's afraid the gay guy will post
on Facebook or Yelp telling everyone we're bigots.
but seriously, though, this guy is just a creep in a sneaky way. It's hard to
describe. I hope he leaves on his own very soon. Anyone ever had something
like this guy at their academy before? And this dude had it. Imagine this
scenario, though. You all get together in your dojo, and you're having an
intervention with the gay guy. You say, "You have to stop saying such gay stuff
and acting so gay." He's posting you, making out with multiple dudes, by the
way. So he's also polysexual. You're all standing around him. He strikes the
goes, the music starts. He likes striking. One gay guy defeats 99 straights. Yeah.
Movie. Tarantino. And you know that song, Frankie Goes to Hollywood, Two Tribes Go to
War. I don't know. The Gays vs. the Straights. I was thinking more like John Wick type music.
No, that song is John Wick style. They need to make that movie. Gay Guy vs. Straight Guy.
indiscriminately killing straight guys or straights? It's on its way.
L G B T K I L L. That's what I would call it. That's what I would call it.
Oh my God. That's pretty good. Yeah. Or gay Bill. Yeah.
Okay. The gay. The gay guy. I don't know. I'm not that good at it. I'm
not a professional movie namer. Oh, the gay guy man, like the bye bye man.
Yeah. Or like it man. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So this person responds with a
very harrowing story. This next person, okay? And they say, here select that, they say,
a gay guy once gave me a wedgie. Chuck's manhood. A gay guy once gave me a wedgie. Speaking of
jocks versus wimps.
Bro, your manhood was Chuck the fuck out when that gay guy gave you that wedgie.
How do you face your family at Thanksgiving knowing that a gay guy gave you a wedgie one
time?
Yeah.
It's over. Your life's over.
I mean, that's why you devote your life to martial arts. You leave your wife and
kids.
Asceticism. Yeah, you're a monk. You live on a mountain.
And this person makes a similar point. They say, "Did he do that to you while
rolling? This should be considered sexual harassment."
Yeah.
A gay guy.
What does that mean, "while rolling"?
Rolling is what they do.
Yeah.
That's like a spar.
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know Aikido is rolling.
He's saying that while they're doing Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu, this guy wedged him.
And he thinks that that should be sexual. So I think that it's no holds barred.
I'm not sure the guy should be wearing underwear in the first place. Yeah, let
that thing fly. Yeah, just wear the wear the gee. Yeah, they did a samurai did not
even know what underwear was that was English. They didn't understand. I think
the gay guy was revealing that he was dressed in a dishonorable fashion
exactly and he was exploiting it and let me guess the underwear at hearts on it.
Yep, this is why this is why many people who do Brazilian Jiu Jitsu, they don't
have long hair. They have short hair because in a street fight you can grab
their hair and you can put it on your crotch or something embarrassing. A
similar thing with wearing underwear. If you wear underwear, you're at a high
risk of somebody wedgieing you if they feel like it would give them the upper
hand in a battle. Also, if you have long hair in a fight, they can cut your
hair and it will cause psychological damage. And hair damage. The risk of a
wedgie on the street just constantly, 50% of the time,
50% risk. At any given time. At any given time, somebody could run up on
you pull up your your your I think I would rather be knockout game with a
brick than be wedged on the street. Oh my God, can you imagine that video being
your your legacy forever and then people are looking wedged and then I feel like
people would have the same fervor that they have for like like finding
somebody's finding a Karen's job or something just to find out my name and
phone number so that people can call me after that. Yeah, like it wouldn't even
maybe they're not even mad at me. I just got doing stand up yeah exactly it
would be every single I would never escape you. If you got in public,
yeah, you have to you'd have to make it your identity. You have to start
everything you do. Yeah, I got wedgie guy ten years from now. I'm running
for president wedgie guy. I'm hosting some some house tour show on any yeah
on any as the wedgie guy. I don't want that man. The documentary about my life
comes out to wedgie guy. You find out that I there was a that I you find out
was all staged. That would be sad. That's what I'm going to do. I'm going to do
like a Jesse Smollett thing about me getting wet
by two jocks.
Yeah, the jocks came in and wedgie, but then you find out that I actually hired
two wimps to do it.
That's scary. That is scary. That could actually happen.
And then one last thing, there's a super troopers reference. This guy says I'd
call him a chicken fucker for twenty dollars. Wow, so that guy's pretty
That's fucking funny.
Yeah, that guy is fucking funny.
That's it for my stuff.
Supa Troopas, dollar bills y'all.
What are you doing?
Dollar bills y'all.
What?
I don't even know.
I thought that that would make sense and it didn't.
Dollar bills y'all.
I was just being random as fuck to do it.
That's okay.
You can be random.
What do you have?
What are your researches y'all?
This is my slideshow about the greatest martial artists of all time.
So I didn't know what to do for this.
My first slideshow that I made had too many videos in it, and that's bad radio.
So we're just going to look through all the famous martial artists that I started
looking up on the computer.
First one, Bruce Lee, most famous.
Cool uncles wear a shirt of him.
And also, he wore a cool shirt.
He wore a cool shirt.
Yellow shirt.
Yeah.
Look at that yellow shirt.
Classic yellow shirt.
Next guy, Chuck Norris, the first white guy to ever do martial arts.
And he's pretty damn good too.
Pretty damn good at it.
And he's handsome and I heard he did all sorts of things.
And you know when he crosses the street the cars like that.
Apparently when he does a push up he does 100 push ups.
Yep.
Then the next one my grandpa he does Aikido and some other.
Some other martial art.
I don't have any pics of him doing Aikido.
I just have I really only have this one photo of him.
This is the only photo of my grandfather.
That could be Aikido.
He looks like he's maybe thinking about Aikido.
Maybe.
Jackie Chan used something called "drunken boxing" for his film The Drunken Master.
What does that mean?
And I saw that and I was like, "What the hell is drunken boxing?"
So I looked into it and "drunken boxing" is the general name for all styles of Chinese
martial arts that imitate the movements of a drunk person.
Drunken boxing is not a single martial art with an established lineage and hierarchy,
but rather a group of loosely related kung fu styles.
In this respect, drunken boxing could also be understood as a phenomenon within Kung
Fu.
A phenomenon.
That word phenomenon made me remember this phenomenon.
Jar Jar Binks is actually a Sith Lord and Drunken Fist Master.
If you guys remember that.
I don't remember that he was a Drunken Fist Master.
Then there's an example here.
If you take a look at the very opening of the film, you can see Jar Jar Binks doing
like a similar starting pose as a Drunken Fist Thing.
is crazy. Yeah, I didn't clap. They had a little clap there, I guess is a similar pose. Then
I started thinking, what kind of accent does Jar Jar have? Alien. Yeah, Gungan accent. But
what is it based on in the real world? Turkey. A Jamaican accent. Now hear me out. I found
a list of on Jamaicans.com that said there are seven and seven interesting facts about
about the Irish influence in Jamaica. The Jamaican accent shares elements of the
Irish accent. The Irish lived with the newly arrived African slaves. Some taught
the slaves the English language. The Irish guttural accent is still evident
today.
That can't be true. The Jamaican accent is an Irish accent?
Technically, by that logic, Jar Jar Binks has an Irish accent.
But let's look at it a little closer. This is a list of stereotypes of Irish
So violence, food, alcoholism, red hair.
How's food a stereotype?
Yeah, they're the worst food in the world.
I guess a stereotypical foods are corned beef, cabbage, and potatoes.
That's just the things they eat.
Wait, how's that a stereotype?
These people are such a fucking victim complex.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
They think that we eat potatoes.
Shut up!
Hold on, hold on.
Notice anything peculiar?
Yes, food.
Jar Jar Binks exhibits every single one of these stereotypes. Look at this.
Wow. He is a completely violent man. Look at him in the battlefield. He is
eating food and look, there's Jar Jar Binks pouring himself a glass of
what looks like whiskey. And also in all those photos, he has red hair.
These are his ears, Patrick. This is red hair. It's an
Jar Jar Binks is Irish. It's inconclusive. It's inconclusive. Now that we know
he's Irish, doesn't the drunken master thing
Doesn't doesn't this drunken master thing make a little bit more sense?
Are you attacking us? What's going on PowerPoint comedy dude? Doesn't this
make a little bit more sense that the drunken master? Let's circle back to
the Darth Jar Jar theory. Wait, doesn't what make more sense? Let's circle back
to this Darth Jar Jar theory real quick. Jar Jar Binks takes control of the
Senate and was supposed to be become emperor. That's not a real, that's not
from any canon Star Wars thing. Let me go through this.
What's an emperor? It's like the president.
Look at the list. Here's a list of Irish presidents.
Jar Jar Binks could have been an Irish president.
You got Joe Biden, Michael D. Higgins, the Irish president.
It goes deeper.
This is a list of US presidents with Irish blood.
That's a most of the US president.
Wasn't Kennedy Irish too?
Yeah, he's on there.
This is a post from r/conspiracy detailing the Hibernian
conspiracy iceberg.
It's inconclusive.
The Irish control everything.
It's still inconclusive?
The Irish control the media. What is media? It controls the people. Look right here. Media
is Internet, radio, television, magazines, newspaper. Wait a second. Radio podcaster
Raider. We are doing a podcast. Half of us are Irish. I don't claim Irish, by the way.
I'm Irish because I ran to you. Not half of us. Well, you're Irish. No, you would know
because on race on race off, I was I was Irish on race off. You don't remember. No, that
that county cork that ruins this whole thing there.
He doesn't even remember. I won't now you're Polish and African. You can be
not Irish. You said you couldn't claim, but I'm technically more Irish than you
know yeah fine. Well, I'm Irish because of my grandpa, not just my Aikido
grandpa, but my dead one too and my dead grandma's and also both of my ancestors
on both sides and then Caleb is sixty eight percent Irish.
I re watched race off and it did. I don't remember anything about you being
Irish in it, but Caleb, who do we control through the podcast? The
listeners of our show. That's a photo of our last live show.
Most importantly, though, we control Cameron and Jubio. Oh, that's a nice
picture. I don't have that picture. Through what? Are drunken fists. We do
like drinking more than the other two. Also, I controlled Cameron through a
mental martial art to say this. Now, Cameron, why don't you take a read of
this? This isn't real. No, no, I want you... You read for your part and he'll
for his part in this text thread that we have a photo of okay go. Is there a
yellow one? They should have a double sided one of brown and yellow. No, but
you want one. You want to put your mouth on the yellow. It's written no, but you
want one. You want to put your mouth on the yellow saber. Yeah, you want to suck
down the yellow lightsaber. I want to suck down the yellow saber. Where did I
learn this mental martial art
from my grandpa? That was the other martial art. I talked about earlier pose.
So in conclusion, the Irish are the greatest martial artists of all time.
So it finally concludes.
So now it's conclusive.
Okay. And there's a YouTube.
It was supposed to play automatically, but we don't.
It's not even playing at all.
Yeah. Okay. That's fine.
We don't really need to see that.
Yeah. But was it going to be?
Shipping up to Boston?
It was something like that. Yeah.
What was it?
It was you can't beat the Irish.
Oh, you should have done shipping up to Boston.
Yeah, I should have done that.
But that's got to be one of the most just nonsense things I've ever heard in my life.
But I did enjoy myself because I like arguing against you.
Yeah.
Even though you're my Irish brother.
I had to change my whole thing because the other one that I wanted to do was I think
probably 12 minutes of videos of a guy.
This, the new set should be just all, we should just do Ireland.
Yeah.
Yes.
No.
No, we won't do that.
No, we're not going to do that.
Okay.
I did yeah all right now. I'll let's take it back to real martial arts guys. You
said it is Irish bullshit honky, drunken fist that we all benefit from. So I've
been reading a lot of old comic books from the 60s and you I've been reading
them from scans where they scan in the comic books and they have a bunch of the
old ads that they have and they have you know it's order an X-ray glasses,
X-ray glasses monkeys become strong how to have a male voice. If you're a boy
stuff like that gun targeted, not so many gun rubber band gun rubber band gun.
Yes, very good rubber band ball remote control. Ghost is a classic one that my
dad would always tell me about where you order it and it says remote control
ghost and you get it and it's a balloon with a sheet and you get it in a box
and it's just a remote control. You just pulled you pull the string on the
balloon to control, but there's the here's an ad that I saw that was
fascinating me. You be was a okay. Okay, boys men. I'll help you master you be
was a says NJ Fleming you be was a master you be was a is the secret
amazingly easy art of self-defense that turns just one finger of your hands into
a potent weapon of defense without any bodily contact. Oh my God, here's some
other parts of the ad master every situation make no mistake. The world is
crowded with anti-social enemies who think nothing of sticking a knife into
for the ribs or attacking peace loving citizens just for the fun of it or
molesting boys and girls shamelessly. This is in Spider Man. What was in this
was in Spider Man or knocking off the side of the exactly somebody's car. I
just would put that out there. There is a crying need for a system of self
defense that relies on knowledge, not big muscles or strength. Yeah, that
depends on technique, not on weight or size of body. That is based on simple
training, not on illegal possession of weapons. And here's another part of the
had it's a picture of of Yoshi Imanami. I weigh only ninety eight pounds, yet I
can paralyze a two hundred pound attacker with just a finger because I
know you be was a says Yoshi Imanami pretty Japanese wife of MJ Fleming, you
be was a master.
So I was looking up for my power point. I saw this at a while ago and I wanted
to do a deep dive into this and look who's a MJ Fleming. What's the deal with
this martial art? You be was a I made a power point about it and then, as I was
some research, I stumbled on something else and I deleted the rest of my
PowerPoint because this is more important than I found that you was has
guided me to something I could never have believed. Yeah,
you be was a two point. Oh, my God, by Eddie, we ten a grand master founder,
a guarded exclusive confidential course. This is the cover of a book. He wrote
about you be was a can we get a bigger photo of this? Because is that the
Freemasons logo right there? Is that the Aerosmith logo? There's all sorts of
so good. This guy is also a graphic designer. As you'll see, tell yeah,
we're going to go through a lot of his book covers and a lot of stuff like
this, but this guy is what's his name? Eddie, we ten a right. We can you bro.
I think he is. I thought that was
he developed you be was a two point. Oh boys men. So you can see he took it
from the ad boys men. I'll help you master you be was a two point. Oh,
Murray was a clock theory. Oh my God, look at and then he has he looks like
sub zero there. I don't think that's him. I think that's cgi that he made,
because he also makes cgi, but he has something called clock theory that I've
never found any explanation. He just writes it under a lot of stuff, but he
invented this this art called Maria was a which is his the deadliest martial
art in that is you. You want to point out? I think you be was a two point. O
is contained inside Maria was gotcha
here. So I teach Maria was a the way of unlimited techniques. That's what he
calls it. It has unlimited techniques and I've been doing so for over fifty years.
I have had plenty of time to research and learn all styles of martial arts. I
borrowed the best techniques out there, secret or otherwise, and eliminated many
pointless, complicated, inefficient or cinematic type moves to create what
Maria was is today as part of my quest to design the most deadly fighting art in
history. I had to scavenge what I believe to be the most efficient and effective
techniques from within the martial arts universe. So he's taken every martial
art and taken only the most deadly. That's what I would do yeah, and he also
has unlimited techniques. Oh my God, so unlimited deadly technique, literally
unlimited wow. Here's one of his diagrams. He has I'm not I'm not he I
I've taken all this stuff from only the free samples of his books on am. I
ordered one of his books, a hard copy that I'm going to get next week. I'm
really excited about it, even the free samples. There are probably fifty
diagrams that look exactly like this with this exact density. So for people who
are just listening, it's a human body. There's a bunch of numbers on it. It
says IAA insertion attack areas, and then there's a bunch of arrows pointing
to different insertion attacks, and it's all, I cannot read it from here 'cause
the TV's too far away from me, but there's, I like, there's some of the TV.
It says no shoes between toes. It's one vulnerable area that you can attack with
an insertion attack. If somebody has no shoes, you can insert your finger into
the web of their foot. Yeah, I think you can put your finger in between their
toes and it will cause damage to them.
Yeah, Mario was a system. You be was a target holes. So these are holes on the
body that you can target with your finger 'cause you be was a translates a
finger technique by the way. Okay, so these are the holes you can attack.
What is finger? You was a what is that's the name of his art? Okay,
so Muriel is just a made up word. I think so. Yeah, threat pit
the clavicle pit, you know all this, so you can put stuff on people. You can put
your fingers between people's fingers between their toes. These are the holes
that you can attack with. That's just an example of a
sounds a little bit. I don't mean to be offensive. Sure, it sounds a little bit
to me like tickling. No, no, okay, you'll be completely wrong. Let's maybe this
will clear it up. If we do a little bit more fingers in their armpits and the
bottom of their no, no, it's a
insertion attack. Look, right there, he says, I let it is the penis that was
the most sensitive part of your body. Yeah, yeah, well, it's just and with one
finger, that's all you need. It's deadly, whatever you keep going, okay,
keep going. Here's some of his other book covers. This is the one I order on
the left, Maria was the way of unlimited techniques written and illustrated by
Grandmaster founder, the deadliest self defense system in history. He also has
Mario was a the way of unlimited techniques, arboreal locomotive hands,
body language, projection
and he which
where is this what this book is about?
It's about arboreal locomotive hands and body language, projection, arboreal
meaning trees, yeah and body language, meaning body language. So here's the
first page of his book legend, victimology, noun, the study of the
victims of crime and psychological effects on them of their experience.
That is, if they survive the assault.
Oh my...
As a Murya Wazen, your primary goal, as it relates to self-defense,
is to learn special body mechanical techniques and special concepts
designed to enhance your power, to increase your capacity, capability, and ability
to survive beyond an attacker's primary intent to do you harm,
and do so by eliminating the initial assault and any evolution or progression of the attack thereafter.
Thus, anti-victimology.
This manual is designed in such a way as to enhance your efforts in developing
your own individual specialized TDP total defense plan through hundreds of
unique drawings, secret concepts, charts, medical implications, strategic
body, mechanical techniques and hand contortions,
and I did there. This is he's on some Naruto shit. He's literally this this
whole book this that in the free sample is all diagrams of hand motions. You can
do to stop attacks. Okay, here's some symbols he put in for arboreal locomotive
hands projecting common symbols, ratting back and forth. Where's et on the top
the first one on the no that's a rattle snake. Oh my God, your hands are going
to make these these signs, for example, stop or stop and think or danger to bob
or quiet zone
and all stuff like that. He also has some some warnings here for compromised
organ malfunction and compromised glandular malfunction. It's potential
potentially lethal security personnel related. You can see he has some
security personnel warnings for an tease and these are supposed to go. You
supposed to make these hand motions yeah. These hand motions could cause
compromised organ malfunction, so you just have to know that before you go
into doing the gotcha and here's one of the hand motions.
This one is called what willow branch. These are a branch in the willow leaf.
None of them have names, but I could see it's there's also there's literally
fifty of these. Okay, almost I'm going to do I'm going to do this. This says
that you need to rattle each hand. Yeah, in a kind of a right angle motion. So
you I would rattle like this,
rattle like that and then bring them up and then do this. So try to attack me,
try to attack me, Patrick.
Stop, you're supposed to be psyched. You're supposed to be psychologically.
You didn't even look at my hand. You just punched my chest and I heard a
full way. It says there the message, the front hand is sending the message,
stop and think. Oh, okay. All right, ready?
you. Stop. No, that hurts. I did not. You told me to attack and honestly making that rattle
snake thing and made me want to attack. Cameron, none of this is working. Okay, well, maybe
about how here's my idea. Try to attack me. Okay. See, that worked out a lot better. Here's
your issue here. I'm zooming in here. Okay. Allow a salient to fixate on your locomotive
my hands fixate on okay wait. So you gotta do so you gotta maybe say watch my
hands first, watch my hands. The willow tree gives us hope, a sense of belonging
and safety. Furthermore, the ability to let go of the pain and suffering. So let
go of the pain and suffering. I don't care to grow new strong and bold close.
Maybe that's the
how
it actually hurts me. A l h puffing and blading coupled with a debt adept blp
techniques will absolutely and unequivocally convey subliminally to any observer the following
variables. One, an unknown capacity, two, an uncertain capability, and three, an obvious
ability. The aggressor will subconsciously react to your BLP and interpret them as an
overt warning of an imminent threat to their continued health and safety, as well as force
them to rethink the original purpose for their attack and/or POA plan of attack by injecting
their emotional state of being with overt uncertainty.
Maybe I'm just immune to this.
you might be okay. Let's let's move forward and let's let's talk about
attacking a little bit. Fucking shit, I'm sorry. Clearly, the defending didn't go
I'm sorry that it made me attack you harder.
This is so now things let's take a look. You get to try it next time or he does
because I've taken enough punches today. Okay, that's that's okay. This here's
another book. You wrote Maria was a the way of unlimited techniques, the
different animal fighting weapons and characteristics used in the martial art
of Maria was a Maria was a twenty animals. That's the name of this. Wow,
this is his different animal styles of fighting. So if you remember from
Kung Fu Panda, there's different animals, and Kung Fu Turtle right, he
has a lot. He has twenty styles and I put in only a few of them here,
but these are what he calls calamitous patterns based on animal attacks. Okay,
so these are animal attacks that you can use in Maria was a so first up is
his first style of martial arts is the great ape monkey, baboon, chimpanzee,
gorilla, orangutan, spider, capuchin, okay here on H one. He has five different
attacks you can use okay one eight climbs tree trapping slash control,
grabbing arms, executing a jumping head, but to eight bites branch biting at an
assailant's arm with control three eight grips, bamboo stock, a merciless hand
grip at the throat for hairy the eight
marching type front snap kicks at knees five monkeys, paw clawless tiger strike
to face a neck. So that's a style. So this is grabbing somebody biting them
and scratching their face, yeah, and being harry the ape, okay and becoming
harry the ape for a short amount of time in the next. Here's the next style. I
want to look at is badger style, Wolverine, weasel, scum, first one, look
at the first one, the honey badger grabbing, clawing, pinching, stabbing,
punching at an assailant's groin area. Number two badger digs hole dirt or
object, tossed to an assailant's eyes. Number three badger retreats, quick
calculated running backwards steps. Number four, the badgers mirror ultra
quick scratches to entire ultra quick this and number five twisting badgers
clock quick snap back twisting claw list strike
okay. So if anyone wants to use the badgers mirror, just make sure you're
this is how a badger fights. Yeah, it retreats and has a dirty man. Yeah,
well there you go badger digs hole.
Here's the next style the armadillo number one armadillo roll ground attack
Mario wasn't rolls into a ball by assuming a semi beetle position,
protecting internal or
number two armadillo itches vigorous, unrelenting nail, scratching at
opponents, arms, neck and face during the duration of the altercation.
Imagine you're in a martial arts, but it was fight with someone and they're
like next. I'll use armadillo
number three armadillo absconds, Maria wasn't walks or runs away that hey
I've been that's what I do every single time. Yeah, Armadillo style fighting
of yeah number four Armadillo shell block on coming punches with lunar
punches to attack body weapon. Well, if I knew how to do a lunar punch, I
probably see that's what I was doing. You were doing lunar. Yeah, I hunched
over so I could throw in haymakers. I don't get hit in the head. Armadillo
sweeps tail blood short, stiff legged kick slash seep to the heel of feet. So
we those are three animal styles. Any guesses on what the next day we've
we've looked at ape style, badger style, Armadillo style. What animal do you
think maybe mouse next okay, so you're both completely wrong. The next style of
animal style we're looking at is human style
and it says the human homo sapiens, African, Asian, European, Native
American and Oceanian. Here are the different attacks on the hunter extended
arm slices under the nose and at wind pipe number two, the fisherman rapid
severe piston like punches to the stomach. He did that he did a fish. You
did the fisherman, you did the fisherman number three, the archer spear to the
wind
number for the blacksmith hammer strike to the top of the head or side of the
head and number five, the wrangler. Why do you wrangle and it's wrangler with
just an are no yeah embrace the individual around the body with one are
and with another complete embrace with an elbow smash at solar plexus with a
striking arm circle high coming down to a groin grab while embracing arm grabs.
the assailants cloth, then pushes with while their hand performs groin,
squeeze and pulls with an action reaction to dislocate man testicles from
transition total standing matador position. Okay, so you jump on there,
so
with one arm, you grab onto them from the back and then with the other arm
elbow to the solar plexus, you go like this and you grab the a nut,
then you grab their cloth
and then you grab their nuts. You're fighting another kind of ancient human
here yeah as the wrangler yeah, I'm going to use the wrangler. If you'll excuse me,
I will become the wrangler yeah,
so that's kind of an overview of his martial arts. That's pretty much all I
really I really know about his martial arts from the free samples before I get
his book in the mail. But what about his arts, but he's actually a complete
renaissance man and martial arts is not the only area. Everything about it
screams renaissance man. Here's some other books that he wrote. Here's a
short story he wrote called Prehistoric Birds and Modern Times, and this is a
cover where it has a picture of a bunch of pterodactyls, and it says Africa, New
Zealand, Madagascar, Willisee County, Bexar County, the Amazon, Cameron County,
three counties, Cameron County right there, three counties, two countries, a
continent and a giant forest yeah, and then he also wrote a book called Long
Live the Dead, a psychological thriller and mystery for the deep thinker, a pair
of homeless, mentally ill vagrants struggle to keep what remnants of sanity
that remains despite the never ending bouts of hallucinations and homicidal
flashbacks that are slowly consuming them by Eddie Vuitton, a PHD. Oh my God,
he's a doctor, holy doctor and he's not and he's not just a doctor as a former
judge, a long time private investigator. I must say that I truly derives great
satisfaction having solved some of the mysteries surrounding the lives of the
original French Vuitton a settlers, their spouses, friends and neighbours. So
that's from a book he wrote about the history of his family, okay, but he's not
he's a judge, a private investigator, a martial artist, a doctor and an author
yeah. What else is he? He's also a musician. He's some of his album
color. Holy fuck, there's a summer place by Eddie, we today in the time
travelers download today, mp3, Eddie, we today in the time travelers. You're
the best thing that ever happened to me. Eddie, we today in the time
travelers, that is that a style council cover. He has covers of everybody. I
need to hear that fucking style. Can you have any music? I didn't put it in,
but you can Paul justice. You could do a search right. He had a good cover of
heaven knows I'm miserable now. Whoa, wait, will you please look at the same
music? Eddie Vuitton a music you're Eddie Vuitton a you're the best thing
that ever, but also it's why oh you are yeah the best thing.
Oh my God, first result, Eddie Vuitton a you're the best thing.
Let's hear it. There we go. Let's hear it. Don't look at too many of his other
videos because I have one that I want to show. I just want to hear the music.
Yeah, click yeah. Go to here's a rainbow connection. Oh, this one is a good music
video. Actually, I need to hear this.
Look at this amazing album cover. Look at that old man that that woman's talking.
I think this is making no noise. Maybe go to the change of the output on the
bottom, right? Yeah, because I have to hear this. I will. I need to hear this
so bad.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Did we lose just skip to the middle of it? Maybe Eddie. Did we
lose him?
Whoa, music video is cool. Yeah, the music video is a bunch of soldiers going
into a house. Yeah, this isn't working. All right. Well, the sound isn't
working. That's so I wanted to show myself at the end. I guess you can just
play the plate on the go play it for the at the end. Yeah, that's true. I
could also just play his music from my phone right now. Yeah, here I'll do
that. No, I won't. What's the next thing? What's the next thing? Why? Where's
the why is there like a raid like a SWAT raid on a house in that video?
you're probably eddie. Probably first person. Yeah, oh probably yeah, it's
probably him either rating a house or his house getting rated because of his
extreme techniques. So load two words yeah, so awesome man. He also has
he's not just a musician and all that other stuff. Here's some of his other
stuff that he does. Here's a little banner he made from himself. He's also an
everything freelancer and let me just read everything that it says here.
comics, toys, fast food, glasses, bicycles, old lunch boxes, G.I. Joe's, Toy Story, Bugs
Life, Hot Wheels, California Raisins, ghost writing, illustration, websites, photo restoration,
green screen/background removal, face swap, thousands of fonts, complete business launch,
ads and promo, pop-up chat boxes, explainer videos, small Android apps, movie voice transcription,
100 language translation, TTL voiceovers, female or male, many foreign languages, video
and audio as special effects, video editing, avatars, library of thousands of graphic and
and audio assets logos. I mean avatars do I can he not avatar yeah, and then the
last thing I had here was a video that he made with that he animated three D
animated and he used his own voice over thing. His his text showed on a yeah,
you gotta show it and I'll point my mic at it too. Okay, actually I'll point it
up just here.
Hold on, I have to I have to get it find outside of the power point here, but
this is like I gotta tell you guys this is barely scratching the this guy also
super hero that he made. He superhero is named Dr. We can it know something
dynamo. It's a guy who can travel through time by riding his bicycle.
That's dope. He just got like I he's insane and I've done so much. I can't
wait to get his book. I bet you speaking of jocks versus wimps. I bet you in
middle school. This guy was a wimp. He was a combo. This will teach you.
Don't judge a book by its cover. You never know what these people are going to
become. Don't bully.
It's called Vinny and Baldi. And for people who aren't listening or aren't
watching the video, you just know it's a it's a guy talking to a CGI, a CGI guy
talking to a CGI baby. And here it goes.
Hey, Baldi, what kind of shit did the teacher put in you?
Daddy, she said that you were a freaking flea-bitten racist, shit-eating bitch.
And that you were a fat, stinky, slime ball.
Daddy, she also said that you were a big chicken shit, dumb, and that you probably liked being an American.
And probably voted for Trump.
Jesus!
But look!
It's true!
They're ruining the kids!
Oh, I am now a good communist.
Communist! Communist! That's how you say it!
I'm going out there and teach that sorry!
I'm grateful to encode what she's going to get if she continues to put shit in your head!
Capiche?
Listen kid, yous need to understand one thing.
Yous is not a communist.
And of course I am not a shithead or slimeball
and any of that mindless shit that idiot said I was.
that I was. I stand up for the flag and also to piss. I place my hand on my heart and of
course kid, any place I've been shot, you're out of there. I'm going to fix this shit the
old fashioned way. You're going to drop out. Yeah, drop out. No, like I did 20 years ago.
But daddy, please, tomorrow we see Debbie does Dallas and eat Chinese pizza. Son of
(laughs)
*laughs*
I'm fixing to go tell your Uncle Tony and some of the boys.
And we're going down to that socialistic shit hole. We call a school and give
them some good old American advice. Let's go tough guy. Love you kid.
Oh my God. Wow. And he has
dozens of these videos. He made movie trailers. He, this guy is the real deal.
That fucking, the, can you pull that video up again? I just wanna, I just
want to point something out. What do you want to point out? I'm pretty sure that
the background
in that Gary's in that video yeah, I think that's I think that maybe that was
the source film maker. I think this is made in source film maker. Yeah, you
think he made Vinny and Baldy and source film. This is either source film maker
that is definitely that definitely looks like so yeah, it does, but yeah, he has
so much of this stuff. He I am in love with him. He is the man. I credible. I
I was just going through so much stuff. I didn't want to put too much of the stuff
in here. I didn't want to burn through it. I think you're 100% right. I think
that is some Gary's Mod map. Yeah, this is 100% a Gmod thing. Why has he got
blood on him? That is so fucking sick, man.
Dude, that camera angle, that thing is so sick. He is so cool. Dude. God damn.
And I'm gonna be getting... I bought his book. I'm gonna be getting it.
Well, let's support that. If you wanna support Eddie, does he have a website?
Yeah, he does. Oh, fuck. What's it called? I forget. It's called Dr. Eddie
Well, you can go to muriawaza.com, but he has another website that he has a
million websites. He does. He has at least three websites.
Check this fucker out, man. And give us a
muriawaza.com. Yeah. And this takes you to the Amazon page.
But he has another website where it links to all his books, but it has a
weird name and I can't remember what it was, but it's only 30 bucks for
the paperback. Actually, I think I texted it to Pierce, so I bet I can
find it out right now what his website is. Yeah. Wow. Well, check out Eddie.
What an episode. Oh, his superhero is called Dr. Petal Dynamo. Dr. Petal Dynamo.
All one word and here on the GoPro is Dr. Petal Dynamo. Wow. It's amazing. Yeah.
It looks like Xavier Renegade Angel. It really does. That is incredible. Check out
the great solution for you.com. Yeah. Check out the Patreon. We'll probably be
talking about Eddie for some weeks now. Maybe for a long time. July 14th at
Littlefield in Brooklyn, New York City. We got a sketch show with us, Home Planet,
Alex and Joe and Pierce.
Yep. And we also have the shareholder meeting this Friday. Yep. If you want to
upgrade your Patreon to the executive tier, you'll join the shareholder meeting
and get to give your input on the company. Yeah. Speaking of us being a
company, we do a... It's business formal. You have to dress up. You have to wear a
camera on, suit, camera on.
And if you can't make it, there's always a video
available on the Patreon.
We give presentations
and I think
if you're into making money, I don't know
how many people listen to this fucking
show like money. But if you do like money
and if you have $15
yeah, and Q
yeah. If you like Q's, we bring the A's.
Yeah, we got you.
Bye.
Speaking of bean curtain, they're showing Johnny Depp's kids bean curtain on HBO every
single night at 5 o'clock.
The idol used to be something that Indiana Jones stole out of a cave and now it's a woman
with breasts.
It's a woman with breasts.
I mean, it used to be a Chinese guy and we don't know if he has a mental handicap and
he goes up and sings Ricky Martin.
Let me point something out to you guys right now.
This show, it's pornographic.
Okay, this show, it goes against our values.
It's showing these things that we don't agree with.
And you notice the show used to be called American Idol.
But as soon as it turned into this, what happened?
What happened?
They took out the word American.
It's not American.
It's no longer American.
This is fully a European idol that we have on our hands on television right now.
And is The Weeknd Canadian?
And people are finally...
Oh shit!
Is he Canadian?
Yes!
He's a Canadian idol!
What the fuck?
We're finally starting to realize how disgusting the weekend is.
Uh-huh.
People are starting to realize what we knew years ago.
We were talking about eating that damn pussy all the time.
We were doing...
Will you let me flick my tick?
Before anybody even knew this.
Flick my tick.
Will you let me flick my tick or not?
Will you take the tick off my...
He's saying shit I don't even know what he's saying.
It's so disgusting.
Flick my tick.
What does that even mean?
Pop my bubble gum on my bubble gum and flick my take my ball
shit on my balls.
Shoot my balls, shoot my balls, like my scam.
I'm bugging got blisters.
Pick them picking my book.
Look at my tick.
Like my tick.
Will you let me flick my tick?
Will you let me flick my tick or not?
or not.
Nah.
I'm not going to let you flick your tic.
But he made a video.
Please, girl, please, please, please let me flick my tic.
No, we don't want you to.
I have a tic that needs to flick.
Please.
We don't want him to flick his tic.
Please, oh please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,