(upbeat music)
- I'm gonna clap, or actually Patrick will clap.
- Wait, I can't do it?
- Nick will clap.
- I got a monster clap.
- I just decided Nick is gonna clap.
- Okay.
- Podcast spot lists, take one, mark.
- Take one, I'm not doing this again, it's Saturday.
(laughing)
- Yeah, we're not doing both takes, man.
- There is no take two.
- Okay.
- We got just one take spot.
- It better be fucking good.
- Here's the bad news.
Okay, bad news. Great news. Let's start with good news. The good news is that I
love you too. You're great friends of mine. The good news is that Nick is here
from the yard. He's in town visiting us. Okay, but the bad news is that last
night
me and Nick
went to a sumo wrestling match. Really? How's that bad news? Sumo plus sushi
because I didn't because only the tickets for free. So I didn't invite you
guys. I want to go to a sumo wrestling. Oh, shut the fuck up.
shut up. I wouldn't want to go. You don't know what you're talking about. You said
you don't know what you're talking. You said they were you. I knew you would do
this. I knew you would do this. You don't know what you're trying to see. It's
hard to frame this as some. Why would I don't want to do anything? Yeah, he
doesn't like it. It will be too loud for me. First of all, the guys are too fat.
I wouldn't understand most of the language. They were speaking. They speak
English, bro. How would I know that? Well, maybe this will change your mind for
five of them, it was their first time in America.
Whoa.
Wow.
They also fought people in the crowd.
Yeah.
They did.
They literally did.
The end of the show.
Now I'm actually jelly.
Everybody comes up.
All the sumo wrestlers came.
It was called Sumo Plus Sushi.
It was in Washington Heights.
Everybody comes up.
They do like a WWE rigged wrestling against each other, which he and Brian were betting
on by the way.
Yeah, we were horse betting.
Betting the entire time.
And one of them would just like do the biggest flop ever.
I was betting with Noah too and he bet like $10 and the second he lost it, he won it back
the next hand and he was like, "I'm out."
He was out.
I was like, "I'm here for the ride."
Ryan was doubling down.
They were throwing $60 on these guys.
God damn.
Yeah, Ryan loves gambling.
He does love gambling.
The end of it was they bring up like five guys from the audience and these guys did
sumo wrestling with the dudes.
Were they fat guys?
One of them was bigger than any sumo wrestler.
One of them was one of the fattest people.
His name was Connor.
He was a huge man and he got destroyed.
Are sumo wrestlers, the whole thing is that they're like, they're huge fat guys, but are
they like six feet tall?
Because in my head, a sumo wrestler is like five foot five.
It's tough to tell from the crowd.
Maybe it's just because of the cartoons.
I think one of them was six feet tall.
I would imagine they would probably be tall because you have to be pushing people around.
Yeah, but is it like a jockey situation where they have to be tiny?
I think they probably have to be tall.
Yeah, well they also have to ride a horse.
There was one round I bet $60 on a 600 pound guy versus a clearly a 300 pound guy.
And I lost.
He picked him up.
I bet it's about skill.
I bet that someone who is kind of an entry level, I would assume that at first I would
to think, oh, maybe it's just about weight. It's pure, but it must be about
waiting, must be waiting for like I said, it was pretty much all rigged until
they were fighting people from the audience and then
one of the guys was like really like trying. So one of the guys from the
audience was trying so hard to win and the sumo guy, he turned on the jets.
He was like yeah, he got you think that you think it was all rigged and then
they they picked people from the audience to come in and
and it was real. No, those people pay $400 to do that. Oh, there's only five VIP
tickets. Where is this? It was in Washington. This was an unbelievably
expensive. It's my birthday. You get to go do your own. It's a traveling thing.
It only comes our birthday. Oh, bummer. But you you pay 400 bucks. You go up and
you you try your hardest to throw these people out of the ring. And these guys
are serious. I want to pay 400. I want to put all the money down. Go up there.
flop immediately. Just get there was some guys who got there was one guy like
full. I'm going to hide a taser in my sleeve. They can't stop me from doing
do you have to make you take your shirt off? Yeah, you guys are in my pant leg.
Me and Noah got pretty deep into the whole what if we sumo thing and we
already banned weapons. Okay, we got to that point. So it's not all that's good.
Yeah, yeah. What if I use some type of gel that makes my body hair so spiky
like that's allowed. That's a good that's allowed. Porcupine is allowed. Yeah, we
we talked about that. You can porcupine? You can porcupine. It's part of your body. If
you just do a mohawk. Some people in Japan are born that way. You can't ban it all. They
have fully porcupine. They have porcupine. I will say I noticed that these guys had almost
no hair. And they had also, we were talking about this, they had perfect ass cheeks. No
pimples, no stretch marks. They got it. Perfect, beautiful baby bottoms. One almost got naked.
He unwrapped almost all the way. He held his cock in. Which was like a demonstration I think.
It was like it was meant to teach us the rules.
Okay.
One of them.
The rule is get naked.
The rules are there's a ring.
Be fat, get naked.
There's a circle.
And you go like this.
You try to, you can slap apparently.
I didn't know.
I didn't know you could slap.
Yeah and the announcer was telling one of the.
Only the chest.
Oh yeah.
You can slap people in the chest.
They weren't slapping their faces.
You can't slap the face.
They were like DK bongoing each other over there.
Didn't really seem to do anything.
What is that like guys?
Is that a demoralization thing I guess?
I think it's embarrassing.
I think it was fanfare.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm not sure that would do anything like an in zone. So here's the
thing. Here's what you do. Maybe the momentum builds up over time. You
surgically graft a taser into your chest. Yeah. So when they go to slap it,
well, that's a good, that's a point about basically any any sport is if body
modding is available, then I'm getting a third arm. But what is it?
If my son is born with electric eel genes because of something, some chemical
was exposed to. I don't think that counts as body modding. You didn't modify it. If I accidentally
raise a perfect human soldier, yeah. I don't know if eel is the best. Well, you know, it's
an example. Yeah. So, well, what would be the best? I guess probably genes of a soldier.
Pikachu's son. DNA of a soldier might be pretty good. Yeah, but it would probably be an eel and
then end up porcupine and a lion and a tiger and a dragon. Dragon's gonna be tough to come by. Yeah,
well, I'm not gonna lie to you. It's gonna be a mutation situation. These guys had, they had the
the hearts of dragons. I was very impressed by Sumo. I always thought Sumo was a fake
sport. I thought it was for wussies. I thought it was like croquet or tennis.
I did the opposite. I actually learned that Sumo is really just about pushing someone down
once and then it's over. I didn't know that.
You didn't know that it was a high intensity kind of sport.
I thought there was like choke holds, takedowns. When you're on the ground you keep going.
That's the thing. That's the problem is you couldn't choke these guys.
Yeah.
There's no neck.
You can't fit your hands around.
Yeah, unless you got a big-ass hand. You can pinch them. You can tickle them. You can make them giggle.
I told Cale I would pay any amount of money to you guys as podcast donation to get Jubio in a diaper
and get a photo. He's already in one. Look at him. He's hiding. That's why he's hiding right now.
I would do anything. He's a offer on the table. He's in a diaper. Damn. He said name your price
for the diaper, man. Come on. Yeah, what's your price? I mean we have to... One dollar.
That's an amazing deal. You should do that for real.
We have to keep him in a diaper though. He's not allowed to leave that computer.
I'm going to feed it into Mid Journey. Start Jubio as only fans.
You made him the love bug in Mid Journey, right?
Somebody did that. I just like putting him in costumes and making him a woman on my Photoshop
application.
I want to make a virtual buddy with him so badly.
I want to make him wiggle him around.
Do you have evil fans? Sinister people?
Depends on your definition.
Yeah, I don't know. Do you have evil fans?
Yeah.
What do they do? Try to ruin your life and shit?
Depends. I don't know. We've had police show up.
We don't have that.
The police are your fans you're saying?
No, no, no. They're expressly not our fans.
But they, I don't know. I'm wondering when people come to your show, is it kind of like what you imagine?
Yeah.
Yeah, they're not. They're all really cool. Everyone's really, really cool.
That's what I think about them. They're all cool fucking people. Yeah, they
dress cool, they act cool, they're really good at talking. Yeah, they have
cool hairstyles. Yeah, they're completely normal people. Yeah, it's odd. It scales
by Patreon. I would say that if you think rockabilly is evil, then yes, we
have a lot of evil fans.
I would say that the people who listen to this podcast occupy either the, either
Extremes of the height scale where people are either like six foot seven or like five feet tall. Yeah
Reality that comes with being an extreme height on either end our fans are so tall really. Yeah, it's weird
Yeah, big dog. Yeah, I'm walking in the street. I feel I feel so small constantly. Yeah
Maybe they're not even fans. Maybe they just want to like pick you up
People who want to know like a tall guy. That's like wiggle my legs. Yeah, one of these just don't dangle this fucker
I'm sitting on the leg of this table.
You got the worst chair.
I'm going to keep doing that.
It's got the roller blade wheels.
I hate this chair so much.
This was a test for me.
Did you give him the spike chair?
I'm going to pass.
I think I put the spike chair over there.
I don't feel a spike.
That chair is a spike that goes up the butt.
It is a prank chair.
I put together wrong and I put the bolts in.
Let's get a little switch going on.
I know it sounds funny, but it's not. It's the worst. It's really just not good to be doing.
We just keep it because...
We keep it because it's sentimental.
Yeah, I mean...
Well, eventually you'll have the right guest.
Yeah.
Someone who likes it.
Somebody... who was... somebody we had was sitting in it and didn't realize it until the very end.
Princess and the Pea.
Joe.
It was Joe. I think Joe liked sitting in it.
Well, he probably has a perfect dimple in his ass that just...
He does.
I'm supposed to ask who Joe is here.
Joe is a...
He's our buddy.
He's our friend.
Joe from Home Planet.
Yeah, he's our friend.
He's our friend Joe.
So how are you liking New York City?
This is the worst place on the planet.
Really you live in LA bro.
That's tough talk.
But like New York, I was saying earlier, it's like you took all the worst people in LA and
you just made them group hug in Manhattan.
Well yeah, you're hanging out in Manhattan.
That's what I'm learning.
I've come to Brooklyn three times on this trip and I've liked it substantially more.
Yeah dude, Manhattan's dog shit.
It's like the worst fucking place to be.
Here, this place, Queens, Queens is sick, Kevin James is here, Ray Romano's here, fucking
Brooklyn. That's where... Chris DeStefano's from Ridgewood. Really? I learned that the
other day. Whoa. New favorite comedian, Chris DeStefano. Love him. He still lives here? No,
I think he lives in Los Angeles, but he's from Ridgewood. Yeah. Well, he's got veneers.
Yeah, he definitely went to LA. I need to get into being, living in Queens and I need
to become a volunteer fireman or something. Yeah. Really involved in the community. Yeah.
Volunteer fireman who's like, has like three daughters and he's so pissed off about it.
I want everybody on my block to know me.
They are getting so many dates.
Oh my god.
Have you guys thought about when your daughter
brings a guy over
and says this is my boyfriend, how you're
going to react?
I'll probably go like, what?
What is this meme you're showing, Jupio?
I'm just going to act real scared of him.
Oh, that's down the street.
This is everyone I saw today.
Yeah. Walking here.
Yeah. Oh my god. TV, high shirt.
Why are you pulling up a meme?
I hate you bro.
Does that dox you guys?
It does dox us because that is next door.
It's the same neighborhood.
But we're not like you. Nobody's trying to triangulate our location.
We've been very express.
Yeah, we give out our address all the time.
Yeah, pretty much.
Most of the time. We should give it out right now.
First person to show up wins.
I won't give it.
I would sooner give out my personal
address than the office address.
Yeah, I think yeah, cuz the office is too. It's too sacred. Yeah, what do you gave your phone number out right?
He did I get my phone number. That is horrible. I don't know what I was you were on Minecraft
I was on a lot of stuff you were
Minecraft was one of them for sure
Yeah, that was the first time I dipped into your world of YouTube man. Yeah
Mmm, we need we need you here so bad
How do you do you make the thumbnails of thumb bows as you call? Yeah? Yeah, what is it got a name for him?
You have a name for they already have those fucking pictures
They say oh, we got to make one of those fucking we have to make a photo
Juvia makers
I mean you they won. I know exactly what I'm doing. Okay. What is the key?
lesson. What is the key? So you have to first you have to isolate who do you guys
think is the most famous in your podcast? Probably me. It's not Jubio. You guys are
fucking with me. It's not Jubio. If you want help, if you want help, I need you to
be real. Okay, but by that logic, couldn't we just put a photo of Ryan Gosling?
Ryan. Ryan. Ryan. Absolutely. You can. You can. Let's just do that. You can absolutely
lie. Okay. Okay. Picture of Ryan Sheckler, right? This is the thumbnail for today's
episode. Okay. Photo of Ryan Sheckler, ax body spray, red carpet event,
then a photo of like the three of us really small, maybe like,
like one 80 by one 80 pixels big.
Just a photo of the three of us tiny, tiny in the corner.
Then it just says,
and it says Ryan Sheckler kickflip the office big inflated Ryan Sheckler.
Yeah. Like Ryan Sheckler inflation. We put him in. Yeah.
I put him in 3D and we Veruca in the middle of his backyard skate park.
Squished bottom of the shoe.
That's what we need to do.
We need to just lean into purely like SEO stuff.
Fetishistic pursuits.
But just call all of our episodes like Pokemon Cheats 2020.
You could probably randomly do fetishized thumbnails until one hits and kind of know
where your audience lands.
Oh, I know where they are.
And then just stay there.
So like if really big feet start to work, then you switch back to using yourselves.
You all just have large feet.
I would say probably people who listen to the show probably have a foot thing and a humiliation
fetish.
Yeah.
Do you think that, I mean, we all have the same size foot, maybe we just like photoshop
it.
He is so obsessed with that.
You are obsessed with that.
He mentions that once a week.
That's crazy.
I think most men wear an 11.
That means that we can share our shoes.
You're like a 10 and a half.
No, it's an 11 and a half.
Okay, it's like 11.
No one says it's 11.
I think he's halving up.
I think he's halving up as well.
I think he has a wide foot.
Are your toes wiggle rooming and you wear them to keep the half?
I think so.
I thought I was an 11 and I went to the shoe store and the guy said you should wear an
11 and a half. I might win this competition. You don't even know what shoe size you wear?
No. That's crazy. How do you not know what shoe size you wear? Wait. I don't really.
Yeah, but those are converse. The only reason I know what shoe size I wear is because Patrick
asks what shoe size I wear 100 times a year. So we can share shoes. We've never shared
shoes. I don't want to share any of your shoes. We shared shoes on tour. You wear cringe shoes.
I don't wear cringe. You do you wear such cringe. You share your shoes on
tour. We it's not true.
That's false. We were those Osiris is that's pretty cool. We didn't even wear
those on tour. I did. I wore them in Seattle. I wore those one time because
my shoes got dirty from a flood in the old office. That's true. They fit.
That's the only time I ever wore those. They fit so it's a good. They're
made of wood. They're not made of wood. You know what I was saying? What I
was saying could come back is the DC Osiris element. That's coming back. It
easy comeback. I didn't easily come back. That Paul Frank, Paul Frank and Ed Hardy all
can come back. They're on their way. Dude, walk around Bushwick bro. You got these people.
What about Echo? Echo? I just bought some big ass Echo shorts. How much were they? They
They were like three bucks or six bucks.
But why'd you lie?
That's half.
Price it per leg. Yeah. I price it per leg. That's what I was thinking.
Yeah. I got these big ass echo shorts that, uh, they got the,
you have more, you have, I don't mean this in a rude way.
You have more clothes than any girl I know. I know it's completely true. Yeah.
I'm like you. Oh, he does too. I went and stayed at his house and I lived in his closet.
But I'm just you too guys, you go shopping. Yes, I do. It's not a crime to go and find clothes.
I've been dressing myself at Active Ride Shop for 26 years. Me too. Not Active Ride Shop though,
what we got on the east coast. What do you guys have out here? Eastern Border. That's not real.
That's a real thing. Is that an Indian restaurant? No. What is that? It's a snowboard place in
Nashua. That's where I would go. Oh, that's from the office. Yeah, I know that one. Burton.
Bring back Burton too. You know that green jacket that Joe has here in the costume closet?
That is a Burton like. It's like a blazer. It's a Burton blazer. So stupid. This is not
related at all. I was here visiting my dad who lives in New York and I rented a car. What's
his address. So his address is 123 dad highway. I rented a car.
It's a terrible. He lives on a home. He lives here. And I rented
a expensive sports car to impress him. My dad built cars.
I bought a Maserati. I'm committed now. I rented a Maserati. I
really want to impress him. He builds cars and stuff. And so I
got it. But when I got in the car, it has like a display and
I was trying to I tried for like, I don't know, like 30 minutes
to connect my phone to it. It was like it was ancient like you take out your
car's radio and you put you put in like a a new type of thing like if you press a
button it probably has a CD player behind it and I could not get the thing
to stop playing Ice Age 2. The car was looping Ice Age 2 and like
it was a really it was like a 2012 so like that all the controls are on the
steering wheel but they're all just like letters it's like SRC which I actually
don't know what that means. Radio control screen. Yeah. I eventually
eventually realized that this RC controls it, but no matter what I did
when I pressed it, it would not go off of ice age to on loop. That's kind
of sick. I drove in. I remember I'm in Manhattan just watching ice age
to they had it like all in the dash. Yeah, right, right up. Just
distracting you. That's okay to do by the way. I know plenty of people.
I know I don't I won't say who it is, but it's one of my brother in laws who he
used to go to school in Georgia and drive like back and forth from North
Carolina to Georgia every time and every time he would come back for Christmas
or I would be like how's it driving he'd like man. It was good. I watched I
watched
grown ups one and two back on the
that's for everybody on the highway. Everybody's yeah everybody's already
watching you. I try it triangle goes across line. Yeah,
for five hours. You have cruise control on it doesn't you can watch whatever you
want to close your eyes. Who the fuck yeah, I wish I knew how to drive
sometimes, but honestly you could watch movies
more time for movies. I get so many movies in I'd finish come and see
getting pulled over by the cop. I'm sorry. I was just
and I
do the kids face to the cop. You turn
yeah, wait, all the wrinkles yeah
yeah, I you guys just don't drive out here. I drive man. He has a car in my
car last night. Yeah, you see is
I've never I've never hung out with you guys and not been in the back seat of a
car with four people. Yeah, Oh yeah, that happened again last night. It did
Oh my god. I'm starting to think you guys are all pranking me. Maybe. It's not bad, man.
It's not a bad way to go. I just need a bigger car. I really want like a Sprinter van or
something. You should get, yeah. I want a Sprinter so bad. Wouldn't that be dope? They're
so sick. They need so much room in them. I'd rather have a plane. You would not rather
have a plane. I'd rather have a plane. Okay, so if you want to go from here to fucking
Trump Tower or something, you have an appointment. That's a helicopter ride. A tattoo appointment.
are you going to you're going to ride your plane there? No, I'm going to take
my plane to I'm going to fly over Disney
and do circles. You can't fly over Disney, that's the whole thing. I'm
going to do it, though. I'm going to be the first guy to ever do it. I'm going
to be basically the Wright Brothers of flying over Disney. Do you think they
have an iron dome at Disney? They do. Really? It's exactly like Israel. No, I
just said that, but yeah, I assume they'll shoot you down. That's what a
California adventure is. Palestine. Yeah.
They're just at war constantly.
I'm sure the parks have beef. You know Epcot thinks they're so much better than everybody.
Oh, absolutely.
And it's like bro, you don't even have good rides fool.
I think the whole thing, full of air.
Epcot balls?
I think if you go up, you fucking punch Epcot hard enough, it's just like a bounce house.
Maybe if you're the strongest guy ever, you think you could punch a hole straight through
Epcot?
I one shot Epcot.
No way.
One shot. Like the sumo wrestler. I was telling Noah last night, if I had a week, well this
This is different, but if I had a week to train, could I 100 meter dash beat a
sumo wrestler? I thought you were going to say punch a hole in a sumo wrestler.
I don't clear halfway. The thing is, those guys are scary, athletic, sneaky
athletic. A sumo wrestler's skin, though, has to be stretched to the breaking
point. Oh, absolutely. I think if there's any guy you could punch through his
skin, it might be a sumo. Just pop him? Yeah. Maybe it's just because of the...
Maybe it's just because of the scene in Goldmember, but I feel like if they
lost weight they would look exactly like Goldmember at the end.
Well the announcer guy was a dude who had lost, he was an ex-sumo wrestler who had lost
weight.
Oh yeah.
And he looked to be about 180 years old.
But I think he was only like 4.
Yeah, they just had like a, they had his skin just like in a vacuum in the back so he looked
normal.
I mean, he looked exactly like Gabriel Iglesias.
Yeah.
Like exactly.
Like dressed like him the whole thing.
He had like the long shorts on.
I mean there's not a lot of options to dress like if you're a big guy.
You either look like that picture of like Big Pun in Fat Joe or you're wearing
Hawaiian shirts.
I said the exact same thing last night.
I said that guy looks exactly like Big Pun.
But if I was that size, I think you have to go Big Pun, you have to wear a suit.
Yeah.
Well, he was wearing a Yankees hat and then he had like, you know how you do the towel?
The towel down the hat.
And the towel just said, "I want a beard."
It was so cool.
Dude, I'm telling you, this is the most fun thing ever.
screaming, yelling at the ref.
What the fuck is that?
Like, like screaming.
It was so much fun.
All the audience members look
vaguely like like famous people.
Yeah. Who were all in Friends at one
point. But they're like just a bit
uglier.
That's where I like the like the
impersonators in New York go.
Yeah.
The sumo thing.
Where impersonators exist here.
Oh, my buddy Charlie did this.
He like dropped this like clothing
line thing. And he got this pitbull
impersonator to like to emcee the whole thing. But the dude I have his business
card. We're not doing people impersonator again. We're not putting my
head. It's new to him. I just want to let him know. But this dude, a fat wallet
from even because he keeps it like it's like the this person isn't a real
website. Yeah, this guy is not exist. So Steven like the I don't know if I can
show you the website. Why? It's promo. That's true. Yeah. If you want a pitbull
impersonator in New York City, there's Steven, but there's a technical issue. You would kill
that by the way. Pitbull impersonator? I think that's racist. I think I can't do it. Yeah,
I don't think he can do it. No, surely you can do it. Because he's Cuban. You're the
same race. You're both Caleb Petito. I mean, he's whiter than me technically because he's
very pale, but I think because he's Miami Cuban, I can't do it. Yeah, but there's a
technical difficulty and the Pitbull impersonator was just trying to fill time. I got a video,
it's just him saying like pretty much every single food that the FDA says is
good for you is not. He's telling the truth. Yeah. This guy's like a butter
eater. He was like saying like agave is terrible for you, like any real shit,
like sweeteners and stuff. He's right. Dude, yeah, he was right, but it was just
like... He does the pit bull thing to like push his Monsanto. Maybe, maybe.
Oh, that'd be so sick if he was like
saying all that shit like don't eat any health food. What you need like yeah,
they genetically modify them for that's good. That's good. Yeah, it's like
Gattaca. Yeah, we make them better. We're making all the chickens bigger so
you can have like good football and yeah he's right. Some specific food he was
saying that you should never eat. That was very funny. I forgot you were there.
Yeah, it was like wheat or something. He was saying something like do not eat
never eat like rice or like there was some one specific thing that he was like
it will kill you. Oh, that's a big one for those like those like a carnivore like
kind of dudes. They say that there's like mold growing in rice silos.
Probably. I'm sure that's true. Yeah. That's how you wash it though. Yeah.
Okay.
So I think I probably would have the easiest time impersonating somebody because
there's just so many bald guys, you know, and people just,
you just got, you just have to go bald.
When I needed you for something, I was like, I need a cop.
I instantly thought of you as like,
even a non specific kind of thing. You know, I just doctor
maybe not doctor, evil doctor. I think I look to
maybe an evil doctor Disney Channel original movie doctor. Yeah, I can be I
can be evil. Any antagonist evil, anything plumber cop, any I don't know
how many how many people are trying to hire an evil something impersonator.
Yeah, it doesn't seem like really a well, maybe on October 31st, you get
the good guy first and then you get the even maybe you can break open the
industry, you actually become more evil. If you get a little hair and evil
super evil male strip,
I don't think I could be a stripper man, but you could be an evil one for sure.
The thing is about if you're a stripper, you have to like a male stripper. Have
you seen these videos? Always a cost to do man. It is disgusting. They pull
their clothes off. They pull, they take their clothes completely off. What is
going on man? Yeah, what else do you think they do? They put their penises
in girls faces and stuff. Yeah, that's the thing about a job is that there's
nothing going crazy with my that's true. Yeah, it's like they basically have to
do like an I'm not touching you. Yeah, exactly. These like forty five year old
women. Yeah, yeah, they're like
I'm not touching you. I'm not touching you. Yeah, and the thing is with girls
also is that they actually are more attracted to the
character girls like in general to when a guy goes, I'm not touching you. I'm
something they do like that you know you could do. You could be the dancing
bear guys. You know you know the one guy yeah, no, I kill a penis is you could
be really good at the party, maybe not as the guy
I'm the plant.
So clearly the
the me like no thing for a half a second.
different is
yeah. I what I mean
how to even do
take off for wedding rings on each and being the guy at the very clearly
wants to be chosen.
We need a volunteer.
You keep moving to sit next to where they're headed yeah
and then when I don't get picked, I like unpack a lunch
eating soup out of
cold curry
so loudly. Oh my God, wait, no, this is really good. You ladies need to try
this. My dad made this
laying a beef jerky bite on the tip of your penis.
It's the new Doritos flavor. You got to try this.
the guy comes over with the like the big like fake head on the like mascot head
and you're just like terrified of
a
don't move.
I'm hiking
hiking. You see the bear yeah. You see the dancing bear in the woods. You're
but to me, I come home and my mom's like, "How was your day?" It was kind of weird.
I sucked a bear's butt.
Well, no, I saw it on the internet that if you see a dancing bear in the woods, you got
to suck him up.
You got to suck his dick to scare it away.
It is funny that porn shows and movies, which is what I call them, they have extras.
Films.
Yeah.
But are those normal extras or do you just go...
Yeah, porn extras for sure.
Do you make a career as a porn extra?
I feel like it has to be a porn extra, because can you imagine just being a normal extra
and they're like, "Okay, we're going to cast you, but here's the thing, you're going to
be in a porn shoot."
Yeah, I would say.
I feel like some of them would do it.
I feel like it has to be separate.
Well, they're the most desperate.
Well, extras in actual movies, they're told to do something.
It's like, "All right, you're riding your bike and then you stop to tie your shoe."
But porn extras, there's so many who clearly don't know where they are.
Somebody's trying to do something to us right now.
Oh, what's up?
No, we're good, man.
What are you doing?
Oh, I see.
He's hustling some window cleaning services.
No, no, we're all set man. Thank you. No, no, fuck out of here. Maybe he'll do my
phone.
The squeegee your phone. Yeah, that's not a bad idea. I brought him in here.
That guy kind of looked like a porn extra a little bit. Yeah, we're actually
like a porn star. I kind of had that rugged, you know, honestly, I know it
was because he had an occupation. I think if you're if you're in a and he
showed up at my door. Yeah, if you're in one of those dancing bear videos and
you need the guy to put whipped cream on his penis for you to suck it, you
shouldn't be in porn. Yeah, first of all, you should already want it. You
you don't like sex, you like sugar. You like sweets. You have a sugar addiction.
Yeah. I eat like the top off the muffin in that situation.
Homer Simpson.
Like a pinky swipe.
You can actually have the rest of it. Yeah, no, I don't want to.
No, but if you're like a porn extra, I feel like that's just like something you
like you either like walk in there by accident or like you were the creepiest
man in the world. You have been fooled. Yeah. If you either you those people are
walking in there by accident, probably just go to real strip clubs and then
just like keep the people who are in there in there and get involved, write
their name on a piece of paper. I don't know. Brace was saying that he like
ended up in a in a in a porn video by accident. Yeah, I don't know. There's a
video of him in the background of how did he do it by accident though? That's
he
It's a furry for sure. Like this is also furry porn. If you go to furry porn
category, you should be able to see Dancing Bear.
And now that I think about it, anything with a bear in it should also count.
So the bear...
The bear necessities. Well, look, he's got a snail on him. That's his snail
sona right there. Oh, okay. What does that say? It says snail. He's making
the face that I would make if I accidentally ended up at the Dancing
Bear shoot.
he looks like he's next in line. I thought this was just a normal back to
the rep party. I was speaking into
don't know that you guys have root beer, though.
Well, I guess if they have whipped cream, I came in here. I thought there
was
this is your face when you see the whipped cream go on the
for sure that you're guys, but I'm so hungry, me wondering
how I'm going to finish all that whip cream. That's a dilemma. Okay, say you're
type two diabetic, right, and you go to the Dancing Bear shoot and you're
supposed to just be an extra, they're paying you 50 bucks, but that whip cream
comes out and you're, you're fucking excellent. You get a beep on your little
fucking Tamagotchi thing they got. Does anybody have any Skittles? No, no, no.
All we got is whip cream on this guy's cock. Yeah, well,
it's saving my own life.
Yeah.
Yeah, that could save someone's life that day. It could. Yeah, it really could.
someone like in the middle of New York is like having a diabetic episode and
yeah, yeah, the dancing bear guy have
there a doctor on the plane? No, but I'm the dancing bear guy with cream.
The guy with the dancing bear guy is putting the whip cream on his cock and
you're like, oh, can I just have some of that whip cream? Like I'm diabetic. I
really need that and he's like he just put the entire thing
can you just spray some on my mouth? It's like a mouth keeps going. Well,
that's it's like he's taking a bubble bath. If I was a if I was a dancing bear
time my penis was smaller than it needed to be for the thing I'm going
fifteen
holding pure whip cream. The girls are eating it and confused. Why there's
nothing under
it fall on the floor.
I have to go to the hospital. I guess you better suck what's left
that's got to be whatever it did. Yeah, yeah, with creamer nobody gets abused
Pretty much nobody, right?
Probably less than one person per year.
In the world, total.
Yeah, there's only one person of abuse in America.
I read that this morning.
We have a classic style episode today for you.
What's that mean?
Where we have a list.
We have an actual list.
An actual list, just like old school style, back in the day style.
We're not doing any kind of crazy concept episode.
Nick isn't dressed up as a dancing bear, although that would have been a pretty easy way to
do this.
I wish I would have been ahead of the bit.
- What do we have?
- We have a monkey mask.
- You have a monkey mask?
- I'll do anything basically.
- You could have been in this one.
- Yeah, that monkey mask has been on the floor.
We won't make you wear that.
- You don't want that monkey mask on you.
- There's probably a literal flea.
- Have I ever told you guys how I found your podcast?
- No. - No.
- You looked up monkey mask?
- I looked up dancing bear videos.
(laughing)
So Anthony Slime, he sent me you guys kind of randomly once
and it was like, "These guys are funny,
you should listen to them."
And I got 15 minutes into one of your episodes
and I messaged him back and I said, "No, they're not."
(laughing)
- You gotta get 20 minutes in,
'cause that's when the circle can weigh in.
- And then I felt, I actually felt guilty.
I was like, well, I was kinda unfair.
I thought you could pick any 15 minute thing,
of anything I've done in my whole life,
and I might look like the most unfunny person in the world.
And so I finished the episode,
and I think it was the one where you said,
I remember he was conflicted in Yoda's voice.
- Oh, that was it.
- Oh, yeah.
- And that was the funniest thing I'd ever heard.
We had a couple of months of doing Yoda.
Yeah.
Yoda anything.
We haven't had a thing that we've been obsessed with in a while.
Yeah.
We used to have months long stretches of the we can only do one thing.
And we kind of haven't had one in a minute.
I think it's because we haven't been going to bars as much.
It's true.
Yeah.
Our show doesn't usually get obsessed with stuff, but we got really obsessed with the
idea of throwing a child pageant and everyone hated it.
Everyone hated it a lot.
Obsessed with it.
And then we had to stop doing it.
fine. It's not for it's not for kids. It's it's for adults for adults,
yeah, but it's only adult. Some of those exist in some places. So it's
adults going on stage. So it's like a B. D. O. Pagent. Is that what you're
saying? Yes, I don't know. A B. O. Is what adult baby diaper lover? Yes,
yes, it's like that. It's like that. It's child dressing as kids. Okay,
yeah, but it's called the child pageant for adults. Yeah, and it's grown men
some like little bowl. I think you guys are catching on. Let no one like now,
but we did it for like ten episodes.
We had a ten episode stretch where all we talked about with this and all the
comments were just like, please stop doing this. The thing is, what are they
going to do? I'm unable to show this podcast to anyone anymore. I'm unable to
you had people yelling at you for your child pageant idea, but I think you
should feel lucky, because I do know that at least one guy was killed for his
child pageants for adults. His name was Jeffrey Epstein. That could have been a
lot worse. That's real shit. You could have been in big trouble. That's why he
was killed. Yeah. Yeah. He was having child pageants. Yeah. Anyway, so so so
we got that's all I found you guys. I thought you're funny. So now we're here.
So our list today is so I found this this website, this blog we and this is
having done a blog in a minute. This is a blog called box of my stuff and this is
what it says at the top of the website. It is really my own cooked up top ten
lists, sometimes serious, usually tongue in cheek. Please click on a bunch of
advertisers somewhere. I will get blessings in advertiser heaven. Click on
the follower section and become a fan with a reminder. It's easy and sometimes
fun. Thanks. Ever have a sometimes fun. I might have wrote maybe two blog posts
on a blog ten thousand times in middle school. Yeah, I had a blog in middle
school. You guys could make this your podcast description and it would just
kind of work. That's true. Yeah, if you just know under that, it really is my
Have you put all that in there?
Is this really my own cooked up top ten list?
We are usually tongue in cheek I'd say.
Sometimes fun.
Do you have any info about the guy who made this?
He lives in Salt Lake City.
Okay.
So he's maybe a latter day saint?
He likes ELO.
Oh okay.
God what else about him?
I didn't put in the about section because it was just
details about his life.
But that's what I remember from it.
that he makes he makes basically only top ten lists, and so this one here is
blank. It basically doesn't exist
okay, ten rhymes that might be true or probably not as he says list he made. I
remember a famous court case that seemed to hinge on the rhyme. If the glove
don't fit, you must equip it wasn't true. In fact, the logic there is so
hilariously faulty that it's amazing that it got any traction at all, yet we
find that if there's a rhyme involved, then something is probably true. It
makes no sense at all, but people love a good rhyme, which is always seem to need
a rhyme to get a spell or incantation to work, but only if it's spoken in
English. Latin spells don't seem to need to rhyme. I'm not sure why. Anyway, I
decided to come up with some to prove the fact that rhymes are not indicator of
truth or anything really, except the ability to use words that sound similar.
I do, I mean it is anything's going to be a little more convincing if you're
Yeah, we love rhymes. I love rhyming. I mean, that's but that's because we have a kind of a root in hip-hop
I would say that yeah, I would honestly say that this podcast is grown out of hip-hop really
Yeah, we're like kind of a branch. We're doing like like a rhyme Sayers kind of podcast. Yeah
We're the next the next thing. Mm-hmm the next
Ironically think this is smart as fuck
I actually I'm thinking about this diff for the first time like if a witch were to do a spell in English and it rhymed
rhymed and then they just like did it in Spanish like wouldn't work because
it doesn't rhyme. Yeah, it definitely wouldn't work. That's fine. That's
why I've never thought about that. Not even also there's no Spanish witches.
Yeah, no, no, they don't know. I've never heard of that. No, no. What do
you think David Blaine is? Wow, wow. Is he Spanish? He's some kind of ish.
Yeah, that's a question for you. He's magish. He's a magician. Magician. He's
a Spanishian. So yeah, here's some rhymes that this guy came up with that
aren't true. Okay, prove that rhymes don't make something true.
If the car won't start, then use a cart
cart makes the rhyme, but honestly a bike is better like a go cart. Okay,
well, I was thinking shopping cart yeah, well yeah, I says cart with a C and I
think go. I mean to play a smart, I feel like you have to play devil's advocate
with any yeah, of course that's what I would want to do and the devil's a
rhymer. The devil's one of the all time rhymers, but a cart is going to work
not
your wife on the back for half the ride?
Have you guys ever ridden? You know what I've never done?
I've never ridden on the handlebars of a bike.
I've been on the pegs. I don't think I have either.
I guess I've been on the pegs. Yeah, but I don't think I've been on the front.
No, I've never been on the handlebars.
I saw a group of kids doing doing three on a bike, one on the front,
one on the pegs on the back.
That's how bad the economy is.
Yeah, we have three kids. Kids can't afford three bikes.
The fuck's going on? It's so fucked up, man. It's really fucked up.
I put pegs on my bike when I was younger.
I never learned how to grind.
I just really I wanted someone to do the thing where they hold my shoulders.
You wanted an E.T.
Yeah, so bad. I never got it.
You wanted it. Is it cool to ride on the front or the back?
It's way cool. It's not cool to ride on the front.
I don't know. It's not right now.
It's a power thing. You're essentially a horse.
Yeah, it's a power thing.
I guess I got back, though.
You're right. You're right.
You're an airbag.
The front is the third wheel.
That's that's like we're being cool.
I'm sitting in the seat and this guy's holding onto my shoulders.
Yeah. I'm like, wait, guys, I want to come to.
Yeah, he's chasing. He's essentially chasing.
Also, if you ride on the pegs, you can definitely just run behind if you fall
off and stay attached to somebody's shoulders. You can ghost ride, you can
like jump off, jump back on. That's the only plus, I guess. That'd be so sick,
ghost riding your friend's bike.
Alright, here's the next rhyme. Kill a fly, thwart a spy. If that spy happens
to be using a robot fly. So this one seems true. He seems like he's making
it true. Yeah, once you add that, it makes complete sense. Even without that,
got a fly fly on the wall. That would be the best rap name. If I was from New
York and I kill a fly, kill a fly kill, kill a fly, I think you're going to say
a robot fly
not a good
really bad
robot robot fly robot fly. You then you'd have to like add more stuff to
make it sound cool from prison
to rob a fly from
the fly from prison is just
yeah, but if bugs could talk, they would know so much stuff about us.
If they could talk, they would well, they are I think they could hear well,
they already can hear well, not now their wings are too loud. I've ears,
I think they have ears, they'd be like they'd be saying like poop is
delicious. Well, basically yeah, they don't care about it. I love shit. They
tell everyone what you're throwing away yeah, this guy just threw out a condom
yeah, yeah, and they know what you're doing. Yeah, they know all about your
poop. They know everything about you. You think that's the thing you think
they would only do you think that they're kind of keeping in their
business. They're looking in the trash. They're looking at your poop. They're
going to your armpit, but you think that would be nosy. I think they already
know everything and they just don't have a way to convey. They can smell your
gut biome from a mile away and they know that you are trying to go inside
my realistic.
It a fly also has nothing to lose because it lives for a week. That's you
I'm true with it. Thank God flies. I would be blackmailing me terrorists. Yeah,
flies could speak English and convert to religions and causes. They would be
purely every fly would have a bomb. Yep. How do flies observe time? Do they know
it's a week? Does it feel like our week? Or is it like a lot slower? 90 years?
What if it goes really way even fast? What if a flies life like I would prefer
if life was like that for me, like if it was only a week long, but but like the
jump from like Monday to Friday was like 70 years in my head. You should watch that
Queen Latifah movie. Quixi? No, the one that's like where she thinks she has
cancer. Oh yeah yeah yeah. I know that one. That's a fire movie. I watched that with my
friend's mom. She's like fuck I have cancer what should I do? I'm gonna go
skiing. Isn't it called ski trip or something? No it's called 10 days or 20
days or four weeks or something. It's called Queen Latifah's vacation. 28 days later? No it's not 28 days later.
my business. She got cancer and it spreads around the world or something
like that for sure. Yeah,
if the food won't heat, then eat a beat. I would probably rather eat cold food.
He just doesn't like beats. Is that I guess he doesn't like beats and also I
also not sure what the situation is. If the food won't heat, I don't know what
that means. I think I can heat basically anything in the world. If the food
won't heat, you have a much larger problem. Yeah, it's pretty crazy. That
is the beat to like it. Well, eating a beat won't fix your microwave, so if it
won't eat the food he's right that that would not work. Yeah, I mean this one he
is right about yeah, he is right about this one. It's hard to argue with that a
friend in need is a friend with weed. He did not come only in Colorado slash
Washington and honestly if he is in need and with weed, then what he needs is
probably a bag of tacos.
That's real shit. He's true. He's he's spitting there. He really is. I think
this guy's in need of maybe a rehab facility. Yeah, I think this guy's in
made of a publisher. I think you should be writing non fiction. A book not read
fills you with dread. I see so many bookies in quotes that have this strange
pride in reading. This is for them. It's probably true for them, unless of course
that book is a compendium of my blog entries. Yeah, I mean if you take a look
at this photo, this is a ridiculous library. This would fill me with dread.
Yeah, this room in my house. Well, yeah, then stop fucking buying books. I can't
help it. If your house already looks like this, get these goddamn books.
If your house already looks like this, you might as well buy more books.
What are you gonna do? One time I did... Maybe read them? When I was
working construction, we did a house rehab on this hoarder house and shit,
and they had a room that looked like this, and I was thinking it was
all just gonna be
useless, just random garbage books that this person had collected over the
years, but it was all books. It was like, Yes, Please by Amy Poehler,
Stephen Colbert's book, John Stewart's books. It was only like the manual.
Literally the UCB manual. It was all like the worst, most annoying guys ever,
just like his collection of the shittiest books in the world. Oh man, it
was so cool. Yeah.
Let's see here. Eat a small pie, then you won't die. Later found to not be
nearly as effective as the apple a day, but better than a large pie, I guess.
That's fire. Neither of these miracle foods will actually keep you from an
eventual death. A small pie is not a miracle food. I don't think I think
this guy's making up this whole miracle of it's really if you took the one out
of the middle, these would look like bagel bites. Yeah, one to one yeah, I've
had a big one. If I had if I had shit, if I was in like holes and I had a bunch
of little pies, I think I would live. I think I would yeah, I would survive off
that. Why is you wouldn't have to eat the sploosh if you're in holes? Oh yeah,
the sploosh. Yeah, that shit looked amazing. It did look good. The sploosh
onions. These kids were eating good. I want to be in Holder's. Those are like 1 million
year old pickled onions or some shit. Plus you make a wrap at the end. This is the best
movie ever. You get to wrap with Shia. Yeah. I've always wanted to wrap with Shia. Le Bluf.
Dude, being able to cypher with Shia. Oh my god. He's actually, he did like, didn't he
do like Sway in the Morning? Yeah, he did the five fingers. Yeah, yeah. He did five fingers
of death? I'm pretty sure. I might be making this up. That is so sick. I think that happened
maybe like a week before all that shit dropped about him. Did he smash it?
Didn't he steal it or something? Didn't he maybe plagiarize his
plagiarize like so much shit and then he was like, but it's all performance.
So funny to be an actor and plagiarize. Yeah, like you just have to act. You
don't even have to come up with anything. Yeah, you do what someone else
tells you to do. Stop doing all that. You don't need to be. I don't think
actor, I don't think we should know anything about actors, not even their
names. Yeah, they should always just be that guy. Yeah, the guy from this,
the guy from that. Like Vincent Schiaffaro or whatever. I don't know what you're on about.
Is that a character actor? Yeah, he's like that one. If you saw a picture of him. The
funny looking guy that's in all the funny comedy movies? He's like the teacher in Better
Off Dead. Oh no, I'm thinking of the Greatest Extra Ever, you know that guy? The like curly
haired fat kid who always plays like a kid in the hallway. Yeah, but I know exactly who
you're talking about. He's in the music video for Simple Plan, I'm Just a Kid. Yeah, there's
a bunch of, there's like a, and he's been doing it for like 20 years and there's a YouTube
video that's all of his appearances as a fat kid with a striped polo walking around a high
school.
Dude, he does so much work.
That's sick.
He gets it in.
That has to be maybe the most rewarding thing ever as an actor is to get a super cut.
Yeah, absolutely.
That has to be the best feeling in the world.
That's better than an Oscar.
100%.
That was Vincent Chiaffe.
Oh, he's in One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest.
He's like the really tall guy with the, he looks like, if they made him Dracula, he would
be the perfect Dracula.
But only if they made him Dracula.
If they made him Dracula.
him when he was alive. If they made him the perfect Dracula, he is the face of a
perfect Dracula.
But now he's dead.
Give some money to a bum and he'll give you some gum.
Wow.
You can just say that about all this other stuff. No, I won't. You guys know
what that thing is? Bum gum? That's the... The shock tube? Yeah, yeah, yeah. I
remember that that's that you know what man I'm never going to fall for that
again. The shot I'm putting my foot down. I have fallen for this shit too many
fucking times in my life. I would love to invent a type of shotgun. That's the
like the like cylinder, the like eclipse, the one that comes in the plastic like
canister thing instead of like so you you fully reach in and as a
like all the little the little like pellet. Do you guys remember when I had a
prank gum that I was walking around with? No. I remember your fake poop.
Wow. That wasn't his. God, I'm so good at pranks. That's an American classic.
That was, you know, you got pranked by fake poop. Yeah. I pranked him first
though. I put the fake poop in his sweatshirt hood and he walked around to
Walmart with it just hanging out for like an hour. He got pranked so hard that
he got mad. And threw the poop in the ocean.
That's a, it was just an emotional response. You got, you actually, I, but I
didn't think that it was poop. See, you thought it was poop. I thought, yes, it
was poop for you thought straight up. I got I did think it was poop. It did look
just like poop. It was shiny like it was through a car window. Yeah, it was the
car window that was doing a lot of the heavy lifting. Yeah, it was good. If I
saw that with the door open, I would have been like, oh, that's a fake poop,
but the car window, the poop in the sweatshirt hood lasted much longer and
was even funnier. It wasn't funny. It was much, much funnier. I wasn't because
everyone was there. People pointing at you at Piggly Wiggly and they don't know
that. Yeah, we were watching you like walking around the store. We were all
walking behind you, just walking like...
No, you weren't. No.
Seeing you just going like... You didn't even notice.
No, nobody was, nobody... People were high fiving us. Nobody high fiving.
Nobody didn't even know.
Great prank. Bro, it's alright. We went to sumo night. It's alright. Yeah, so
it's sumo night. They'll never have that. They'll never have that. I bet you
didn't check in your hood when you were at sumo night, though. God fucking
damn it, you're right.
he could have pooped you fall on a stick, loose blood quick, depending on the
angle of the stick. When you hit it, this one is actually probably true.
So why and put it in your list man? I appreciate him. No, he's like kind of
showing his vulnerabilities. Yeah, like he's like enforcing his argument, but
I'm not always I'm not a know it all. I don't know exactly about all the time
yeah and I just be fucking lying yeah exactly. I could just be lying about all
this stuff on this list. I could all be fucking true. Yeah, he's just he's just
try to make a blog yeah. He's just trying to make an interesting blog. I will say
man it's hard to fill up a blog. It is hard amazing people do it. If your face
is on money, then your future is sunny, not likely you're already dead.
So this could easily be fixed by saying if you have money, then your future is
yeah yeah. I have to say if your face is on money, he kind of this one. He kind
of engineered to fail. I think I agree
walking a mile will make you smile is the double one walking a mile will make
make you smile. If you have to go poo, then try walking to failed exercise
motivation at best. Personally, this one's bullshit because the first part is
true.
Walking a mile will make you smile. The second part is very false, though. Yeah,
no, that's what no, that's not no, no, no, you can you can halt a poop.
Walking makes you want me to poop more. No, you can hold pooping. A mock makes
you want to poop for a hundred percent. Not me, man. It's you walk in a weird
way, then yeah,
like that the whole way.
That's what you're supposed to do. If you can't poop, you're supposed to go walk
around. Really? Yeah, if you're constipated, like run and walk, it makes
you poop. Huh? I may have just made that up. Yeah, I think you made that up.
That's true. That's real. That's real shit. It's completely. It's real shit.
There you go. Any truth in these rhymes is purely coincidental. Next time you
hear someone using a rhyme in an effort to prove a point, just remember if he
uses a rhyme, it'll take more time. That one is probably true. Yeah, that one is
through. I mean this guy really full circle, pretty poor argument. I'd say
yeah kind of kind of sucks at a rhyme. Well, if you think that one sucked us,
this one is going to blow your mind. Here's a here's the second list from
this guy's website. Ten top ten ideas for in my God, we like rhymes. We like
inventions. This guy he's right up our alley. This is a better mouse trap and
the world will beat a path to your door. At least that's what they say that day
is Ralph Waldo Emerson.
didn't build mouse traps. He wrote the sentiment is still the same.
Everyone has an idea about how to make things better. Ninety nine percent of
these ideas are stupid and not well thought out. Oh, but that miraculous one
percent is truly amazing. The fact is you have to wade through quite a bit of
the ninety nine percent in order to actually get to the one percent. We have
had some great inventions in our time and those great inventions build on even
greater innovations. This guy's a genius. We live in an age of excess for less
thanks to invention slash innovation. We now live better lives than all the kings
of antiquity. All they had was good food and a soft bed. We would be very mad if
that's all we had now. Well, my inventions are not life changing ideas
that will turn society on its head. Instead, they are minor contrivances
designed to make my easy life even easier. I don't think that we, I don't
think we live better than any king. I don't think so. Yeah, no, we don't rule
over anyone. We can't, you can't kill people. You have to eat a normal amount
food. Also the king has like a king of antiquity would have like at least some
thought in their mind that they are going to discover a new type of magic or
something. Yeah. Holy grail. Yeah, exactly.
Of cholera or ancient STD or a bear that gets into your palace that you don't
have the technology to kill yet is all completely dwarfed, I think, by if you're
a king, there's a million people whose only job is to make you happy and rich.
Yeah, that's all they do. 24/7. You have a poison taster tester. Yeah, come on, man.
How do you beat that? You're in the possible holidays like like holiday
power King's Day. Yep. King is the first one that King is getting a bath day.
I don't think everyone in the town has to celebrate you washing your ass. I
don't think this would be a holiday. Patrick. Here's the invention. Maybe in
my kingdom number one shrink wrap present wrapping. So this idea is a
pretty easy one. It was made for guys like me that think present wrapping is
for the birds. You just have colored patterns on a bag made out of heat wrap,
drop whatever you want to, wrap in, pick up the blow dryer, and bingo bongo
instant wrapped present. That's actually such a good idea. I hate to give him the
first one. Yeah, I know. Maybe I think that all of them are going to be good if
this is the first one. This is a pretty good idea. It's really not. Do you find
yourself in a situation often where you're like, "Man, I don't want to wrap
this gift, but I have this blow dryer." In Christmas time. I don't even know how
I had a rapid present. Well, that's the problem is I can't wrap it. A present.
The problem is I'm always gifting my fucking hair dryers.
Yeah, where's that? Oh wait, okay, I got it all right. How do you wrap with
this one? You when you want to wrap your hair dryer? Yeah, I guess that's to
say what if I want to turn it on there's and tape dispenser. You turn it on,
turn it on, throw it in the bag. Yeah, oh my God, it's self wraps every present
when you buy something as a gift. It comes with a gift receipt, but also
comes with a built in heat, heat creator. Yes, I
use turn on this. You put it in the wrapping, you turn on the switch and it
generates heat and it shrink shrink wraps itself. I don't even know how shrink
wrap works and I don't even want to know. No, me neither. One of the one of
those things in life that if I know it, I'll just my life would be way worse.
Yeah,
number two Philadelphia cream cheese, easy style. This guy is fat.
This is a fat, fat
that is crazy. I don't want to comes up with a
as your second invention
cream cheese in a tuna toothpaste tube. That's your mention yeah it listen to
this. So there are there. I am in the office and someone has been kind enough
to bring bails and little tubs of cream cheese. I'm spreading the cream cheese
on my bagel and it hits me. They have cheese and pressurized cans for
spreading on crackers. Why not cream tree cream cheese and pressurized cans
for bagels? It makes perfect sense. I mean it makes sense, but don't do it.
This guy is thinking fat enough that he's whole he's holding a bagel in his
man he's spreading cream cheese on it and he's like Fox spreading this cream
cheese is taking so
when the when the dancing mayor tore makes it to Wisconsin. Yeah, yeah,
there's a switch over
here's his third idea. New Christmas Day
this guy. This guy is like a like probably like over a hundred, maybe
around two hundred top ten list on his blog. I would say at least thirty of
more about Chris. What he's an adult, this is not a child. This is a swing
in for the fences, do just the perfect like like oh yeah, like here's my top
three inventions already
heat wrap Christmas present
new Christmas. Yeah, I don't think I don't think I would even say this is an
invention is my problem. Well, do you know what day he wants to switch
Christmas to? I don't, but will you tell me Valentine's Day? Yo there's no snow.
well, yeah, what are you talking about? It's February. Here's what he says. I
don't know any druids, but I bet they wouldn't mind us taking our copy of
their holiday and moving it to Valentine's Day. Much easier to find
snow and the other two holidays that surround Christmas will gain more
meaning Thanksgiving and New Year's. So he thinks that Christmas is devaluing
Thanksgiving and New Year's, but New Year's, thanks and my girl stop on two
gifts every year. That's true. Yeah, yeah, so this is so that's so
to the end of it. He says I'm not sure how you go about getting this changed,
but I think it's a good idea. This would mean you need like a petition. Yeah,
you need something
led lights around skate tracks. My son dabbles in speed skating. He has a son.
Yeah, he's a full of his whole family. I've watched a bit here and there and I
noticed that they superimposed on the ice, the flag and the name of the
skater as they go by. This is great for the folks at home, but it sucks for the
lat for the live audience and he says they should have little led chaser
lights embedded in the ice. They could be deep enough that they
wouldn't impede skating, but they could shine the different
color for each skater. They could even light up based on the
fastest time. So you knew what you needed to be. This one I
do is too specific. I don't even know what he's talking
about. That probably means it's the only invention that is
maybe a good one. Yeah, this one's also this is for his
family. This one's based on love. This one is less
necessity. All right, this one's a ten out of ten. I think
in terms of
he's a in terms of that a hopeless romantic. Yeah, I have
I give him I have to give him this one is an Edison yeah
LCD window shader. I had this one a long time ago, but I've seen it in practice
since then. I actually saw it on Knight Rider. The old one is a picture of David
Hasselhoff. Yeah, you adjust the LCD slider and the shading of your window
changes from clear to dark. I know they have it, but I had my idea around
nineteen eighty four. Yeah, I know a day like you have like
you have like ideas like that, where you're like it like come something comes
out and then you're like oh fuck. I didn't even like I had that idea. I
never wrote it down for me. Mine was when I was thirteen years old. We were
watching that movie, that Mel Gibson movie, The Patriot in social studies,
and I think I turned to my friend and said like, what if they
think it's great at this time period,
but they made like the Assassin's Creed. That's a good idea of like the
Revolutionary War of then a year later that got announced and I was like man,
I what they should do. Speaking of video game ideas, I just want everyone to
just know that I had this idea a long time ago and when it comes out,
don't be surprised to people always been trying to steal my stuff left and
right. It's basically a Dark Souls type game, but it's set in Jurassic Park and
it's called Park Souls and you collect dinosaur DNA and you can become a
dinosaur. Why the fuck that is so it's not a name is my problem. Park soul,
the name is set in stone life. No, it's not about being in a park. Yes, it is.
It's set in a park. It sounds like a sim game. Yeah, well, it's not. It's a
it's an action RPG. It could be called maybe Jurassic. It's not a
Rassar. Listen, I would love to change the name, the juror. I wouldn't like to
change the name. Clearly, I will. I probably wouldn't. I was saying that to
appease you. I think they should do a an Assassin's Creed game in the one
nine hundred and seventy. They should do it in the yeah yeah. Kill Cobain and
shit yeah. Oh, that's the amazing. You do every twenty seven club guy.
You're killing just every single twenty seven. It's a kill Jimmy Hendrix.
quality time travel. Yeah, you killed him. A good idea for a movie. It's an
amazing idea. You have to make him throw. You are the guy who does the
twenty seven. You are the you're you're agent twenty seven. Yes, that's right.
Oh my God, I'm an amazing writer. That's crazy. Yeah, you're giving bad
reefer to Jimmy Hendrix. You got the bitch with the crazy voice. You're
making him throw up. That's how he died. Ready choked on his. Yeah, maybe
you maybe it's something we're like we all these people. If they turn twenty
if they were going to realize something, they all had some kind of DNA.
They were all... It's a Hitler baby thing.
Yeah. All these people were one year away.
They were all about to bring about world peace.
Oh, you knew you have to put an end to it.
Yeah, that's a pretty good idea. With their music.
Is that what you think Hitler was trying to do? No.
That's what we were talking about.
And you say this world peace thing. I was talking about
Jimi Hendrix was trying to bring world peace, but...
Yeah, I don't know. I completely blanked out
because I was thinking about Jimi Hendrix.
You heard the word Hitler, you blanked out.
No, just the game, the part of the game where you are going up to like Jimmy
Hendrix, you have to make him throw up. It has to has to be throw up. So you're
just like walking up to him, just showing him like you're being gross.
So
my ass right now
stinky, but my ass, this finger is in my butt smell.
That's actually I mean, I just think that's an amazing idea. That is such a
good idea number six. We're not going to read this one. I just want to read the
first that what the idea is the first sentence here medical testing like fast
food that actually did happen with
he means, but when he says medical testing like fast food, all he means is
that it should be more convenient
again he's in his brain. That means that's
yeah, but that's what happened. It's like remember in like August, twenty
twenty. You had to like go to like a CVS drive through window and they put your
lock in. They put the swap. I stole this guy's idea. I've been meaning to talk
about this for a while now that we now that we finally can the people who ran.
I think that they literally hired sadists to swab your nose. Yeah, they
were going crazy. These people were touching my brain every time it hurts so
bad. I'm sick of pretending it didn't hurt and it didn't make me cry for like
five minutes afterwards. I did not like it. The worst part to me was when
they're actively doing it and they and they stick it so far up your nose that
there and there it was the drive through one. So they're you're leaning out the
car window yeah and they stick it up your nose and you
like a
I told you guys about the one time I did a worse no time. I did it and the
nurse lady was like the hottest girl I've ever seen in my entire life and she
put the swab in my thing and pulled out like a booger the size of a golf ball
and a gag.
like, bitch, you do this all day. You've seen worse boogers. No way. This is the
worst one. I mean, it was crazy. It was crazy. It must be so funny being like
the, the nurses outside of the fucking COVID testing place just smoke, like
chain smoking the bats, like, that's not a fucking booger. What kind of person is
gagging at a booger? Yeah. Well, this, she's just in the wrong field. Yeah. I
felt so left out. I, I was so afraid of getting my first COVID test, 'cause
everyone's like, yeah, it's the fucking worst thing in the world. It's, it
as much as your brain you want to die. And when I first got it, it was so easy.
And then the next like eight times were all really easy. Oh my God.
But it's just because no one went deep. Yeah.
So I started to feel kind of annoyed. I think that's why I can handle it.
The East Coast, these bitches were going hard. Yeah. They were hurting us.
There was that one spot that we would, that one COVID testing place that we
would all go to. The parking lot? No, no, the one that was on, I think it was on
like off of Hemrod or something. And we would always go there. And every single
time we went there, it was like, oh yeah, PCR negative, great. Then we'd all hang out.
Remember that one time I went there and then we all hung out and I fucking just gave everybody
COVID?
At which time?
That only happened once.
In my brain, every single time I got COVID, it was your fault.
No.
I've only had it one time.
Really?
Yeah.
I've had it once as well.
I've had it.
I got Omicron.
I think you guys just don't know when you had it.
I got Omicron because I went to a house party that had a horse in it.
I don't think the horse was the problem.
I think the horse was the problem.
You mean you got COVID from a horse?
I got COVID from a pony, a Shetland pony.
Okay, so not a horse.
I remember my main COVID testing memory was when I was in Boston
and I went to, it was like an urgent care that was in like next to a game stop
and it was like a parking lot and like we like pulled up
and it was like the place wasn't open yet
and there was a bunch of people, there was a bunch of cars parked there
with people sitting in the cars and I was like,
well, I want to get my like this test done so I'm just going to go like
wait at the door like for this place to open.
I like got out of the car and I went and like stood in front of the door
and the second that I stood in front of the door, just twenty middle aged ladies
who were all sitting in their car, waiting it for if waiting for it to open
who had some clear like like packed in their head that they were like we're
going to wait in the car and then I got out and was waiting for the door. They
all just swarmed
all went in for
I know I was so pissed off dude. I clearly violated their unspoken bond.
That's so it was so crazy. They were getting all their numbers. I don't
understand this one at all. I need this one explained to me number seven dart
board with led through fiber optic to approximate the bristle effect. The
hurt first of all this guy loves leds. I love to play darts. Unfortunately, I'm
not that good, but I still like to play a lot. I have an automatic scoring steel
tip dart board. It's great fun, but as I was playing, I thought wow those bristles
are really not any more around than fiber optic cable. So why not sprinkle
the dart board with cheap fiber optics so we can see visual effects and targets
the fins. He's saying you use fiber optic behind the dart board like a screen almost.
What? Yeah. But what does he mean the bristle effect? Yeah, what is bristle? Is that what
the materials called? I thought it was the fins, when you throw it it will have like
little like LED. No, he's saying the board itself. Maybe he meant missile. Oh, the way
the thing. Missile is a better option. He's saying like maybe you see a bristle on a normal
small like dart board screen show a bristle. I don't know okay. I tried my
best. I really don't know yeah, this is not a good one because he also said
it's an automatic scoring one right so like what you must already have yeah.
It's very he loves light yeah. He always was flashing lights fast. I just yeah
sprinkle fiber optic sprinkle the dart board with cheap fiber optics is what
really can bring is a crazy verb to use for that guys always think the fiber
fiber optic like they don't know what fiber optic cable is and so they think
fiber optic is some like futuristic thing. Yeah, it's for any because they
put in the ocean. Then you get the internet. My granddad is always like
like if we ever go by like some city utility that's digging something up.
He's like yep, they're putting in more fiber optic cable. That's because every
every TV commercial that airs for Verizon or something and they say the
word fiber optic twenty times most fiber optic in the country. I don't know what
eruptive even means I think he's. I think he's just got some sort of dartboard
that like has bristles that catch it. It's like a different type of dartboard
and he wants those to be cable. Oh, okay, so that
yeah,
I guess, and I'm not sure that's an electric board anymore, though. Yeah,
not at all. Yeah, it's not a good invention. That's a zero. I didn't
mention
fair day cages to house movie theaters, so he wants a fair day cage around a
movie theater. So you can't text or call on your phone.
don't they do that? No, that would be so. Why does my phone not work at the
movies? I'm trying to make all these calls in the theater.
Can't even get a call. My phone literally never works. If you actually are real
texting and calling in movie head like me, you'd know it works perfectly in the
movie theater. I text in every movie theater. Oh, I'm on my, I'm singing into
my phone. I text, I talk, I'm not even. I'm recording voice memos about the
movie. Yeah, yeah. Reminder to watch this movie again. I'm on Smule Karaoke. I'm
singing with some forty five year old lady from the Philippines.
Texting the five five five number just to yeah
hello.
No don't switch that a boulder coming. I'm just amming sunflower by post
milan
they got it right. Oh shit. It actually is
yeah the entire time. I'm going Siri put my phone on silent. No Siri silent for
just an hour straight now playing silent
well, my god, able containers for real bulk foods. That little fucking guy,
okay, basically what he wants. I don't want to read this whole thing. He wants
to be my political. My political leanings are definitely to the right.
That being said, it doesn't mean that I think we should run around filling up
holes with trash. So basically he wants to recycle. He wants more recyclable
giant book
I mean not even like this is all like logistical food recommendations, not
even like oh, they should make a candy bar that tastes like pizza. He's doing
like I want to make this whole thing a little easier. Yeah, I want to maximize
storage. Yeah, this is a fat guy that lives like next to a McDonald's yeah and
his problems are all in a radius of walking. Yeah,
he also still drives. Yeah, he still drives. There's a two. This is what the
explanation of what here, how he arrived at this idea is we have bulk food areas
in the grocery store, but we really just give them a cursory glance. They are
called bulk because they don't have packages, but we need packages because we
need to hold our stuff. So I thought that any dry good could be held in large
bins and filled into smaller plastic containers. Once used, those containers
will be handed back for washing and a rebate against the next container of
product. So you can just buy one that you did. You can cut out the middle.
I don't know what this is a very. I know Boo Berry when I see him,
but you can just buy those Tupperware things online and then just,
he just doesn't wanna wash out these containers. He hates...
Sorry, this is a little... Well, that wouldn't be an invention.
That's true. This is a little bit separate, but if you work at a
restaurant and you have... And now you label everything and put it in
those containers at your house, you are a goofball.
Yeah. You are a goofball. You're calling Noah out. You're saying like
the red lead no oh no. There's a little
containers and you put and you put like shrimp one slash. Shut the fuck up man
yeah. Honestly, where he had like an hour long conversation about cheese last
night. I hate him Noah yeah, he's spurged out about cheese. I'd leaned over. I
think he was drunk, but I leaned over and I was like hey. I actually missed the
cheese conversation. Can you repeat it and he engaged with it like really
seriously and he's like oh no, we're still going and I was like okay, and I
I went back to play Mario Kart. I love him, but he like was like really
excited for me to join in. Yeah, but that that is if you're drinking your
water at your house out of one of those things, that's
garbage and your
honey on it. Oh my God. If you're in a real, if you're in a really,
really hot kitchen
and you drink out of that thing, it's so good. Oh my God, really?
So good. No new sound. You guys have a sound board. Wait, play it.
No, play the right one.
yeah.
Is it the whole song or is it just that part? No, it's just it's that part
twice. You should have one like maybe like right here. I don't like when you
touch this for no reason. Why did you switch to an empty page to tell me to
add something? Just the whole song on this one. Why? Why? It's the same. Just
so we can listen to the whole thing. Or it's like a ten minute file that has
the song in the middle somewhere. Yeah, that's a good idea. And you press it
when you start my
baby, this is a great idea,
amazing idea, a ten minute file where you had one somewhere in there and you
can press it and then like maybe you could go up to go to the bathroom and
then it plays and we don't know what's going on. I should just do one file
that's all the sounds at random intervals. Yeah, just play it. We should
do it one hour. Yes, sound you can record your topics like every like fifteen
minutes be like you know what if the dancing bear guy
had a penis, oh my God, it would just go and then you just start talking about
that yeah we have a ding that means we have to move on to we will do an
episode like that's a very smart idea. Yeah, that's cool of them on me fifty
all right. Here's the his last invention idea, okay, universal time zone. This
one, this one is really boring, but I agree. I don't agree. You don't you
want to be like noon at like six in the morning here, maybe
why maybe I'm up,
maybe I'm up at noon in that we just go by the sun like it could be like it
be like pretty bright o'clock. It could be like getting dark o'clock. Yeah.
It could be dark o'clock. Oh, you know what? Anybody who complains about time zones has
difficulty adding two to a number. You know what? You know what my problem is? I got the
time zones mixed up with daylight savings. I thought you were just trying to abolish
daylight savings. I remember on tour you always got time zones wrong. Do you guys have daylight
savings here? Do you guys have daylight savings here? Yeah. Is it gone in California? It's
gone in Arizona. Oh, okay. Thank God. I wish it was gone. They need it the most. They need
get rid of the most they got they got sand storms. They got they got there
dealing with. There's also no excuse for for not being not figuring out time
zones, because it's the easiest thing to google yeah yeah you search. What time
is it? Well, I know I know the time zone difference between here and the west
coast. I know it's three hours, but like I didn't know
good job,
but when we were on tour, I was like it being like it's tech. We're in Texas.
It's 11 a.m. so it's about six or seven.
- Yeah, I also memorized the map in my head
because it's like Ohio is like one,
there's like a part of Ohio
that's like a different time zone, right?
- Were we even in Ohio?
- Never.
- No, I was in Ohio when I was 18 for my birthday.
And then I like, that's--
(sad music)
I thought I hated sound boards,
but I've just been convinced.
- If you hate sound boards, hit 'em with the Alvin.
Oh yeah,
the fucking find it. It's right there. No, it's not. What is that one? That's
when it said Connor. Okay, so you hate soundboards again.
We got you
that's the end of the list. Yeah, yeah, that is the end.
I must I'm back about the mind present
no, please, please
you order to the beastie boys thing. I really like this comment. Joseph do he
said excellent blog great. It was a support up. No,
it does have
other scheme on the end of way to include people to go to his website
way to include the half on a blog about innovation.
I say great inventions on this post great in this invention fan. He looks like
this is an old Joseph Dewey sounds like he invented some like kind of thing to
make slaves work better. Joseph Dewey, I think he wrote like Malcolm in the
middle. Yeah,
you know, it did the one of the producer names on that show that I've memorized
all the time was Linwood Boomer. You memorized all the time. I memorized it
every morning. I woke up every single time that I saw a new episode. I'd be
I thought this up Patrick. There it is. Linwood Boomer. Linwood Boomer is
just sick. Memorizes it all the time. Memorizes it all the time. He's
forgetting it and re-memorizing it.
Well, it's nice to have a pop box. It's like a Groundhog's Day thing.
Like every morning. Every morning. Every morning he'd watch it and forget he
watched it and then be like, "I gotta memorize that. It's gonna be good as
fuck later." I need to remember that for tomorrow. I reset every day so that
that makes sense. You kinda do. Yeah. Alright, thank you, Nick, for coming on.
Thank you. If you wanna see Nick, he's at the bell house. Yeah, he'll be doing
helium in philly yeah, june twenty fourth, which is today, but he will be
at the yard. Can I have the squeaky voice to play me out? Yeah,
a dance with the devil might last you forever.
Damn. Yeah. Oh, we have to plug our
it's like you're doing five fingers of that. Yeah.
but yeah, July Fourteenth, we are at Little Field World's biggest army. We
are doing our sketch show, buy some tickets.
They are going at a pretty good pace. So
if you wanna buy them at the best time, you gotta buy by the day of
the show or else you're gonna miss the show. Yeah, or else you're gonna
miss the whole show. I think we're current,
I think we have 400 tickets to go. Yeah, only 400,000, I think. That's
Yeah, all right. Bye all.
Use promo code PATRICK to pay full price.
Do you guys ever walk by an
armored truck that's parked somewhere
and you think to yourself, I hope they don't kill me.
I hope they don't think I'm trying to steal from the truck.
Because they're covered in guns.
I hope they don't mistake me for a guy who's trying to
get into the truck. I was walking home at like 2 in the
morning a couple months ago and they were
like, the guys were just sitting
looking the other way with like
the
kill these two guys, take this money.
Yeah, easy.
Who's going to ever know?
They got cameras all over the truck.
Shut up.
Every single part of the truck has a camera.
I have a camera.
Fuck it.
You know, I think, but here's the thing.
The Brinks truck has cameras on every single part of it.
Couldn't they make an amazing reality TV show about traffic with the same truck?
Well, that's what I was going to get at, is that we should do a Parks and Rec
about people, two, three guys in a Brinks truck.
That's actually a really good idea.
Parks and Driving is what it could be called.
Parking and driving.
that is actually such a good idea. And it's a Brinks truck, it has all the cameras all
over it and it's like those 360 cameras and they're going into like into people's cars.
Yeah, we just get it, we buy a Brinks truck, an old retired Brinks truck. Or we just steal
one. We put some 360... We leave all the money, we steal the truck but leave all the money.
The problem is that people are going to think it's a real Brinks truck and try to rob us
and all of our guns are, they're funny guns, they don't do anything. They're props. But
Then the episode starts, right?
It's like, "You guys, my uncle's coming over.
My uncle's coming over."
- Same exact episode.
This is how it starts out.
My uncle's coming over.
Back of the truck opens up.
Uncle's head pops in.
"Hello, it's me, the president."
It's Donald Trump.
Damn it.
(tires screeching)