I can do the friendship to do is opening with a friendship tattoo. Does this work? Is this
what you got to wet it? I think you got to wear the what are you giving him a friendship
It's not a swastika, is it? No. You've done that before. I've never drawn a swastika on you.
I don't even know what a swastika looks like. Whoa, that's beautiful. I'm going to get...
Oh my God. It's a heart. I didn't expect that to work. I'm going to bring this to a real
tattoo artist and I'm going to get it put in there. Really? This heart? I'm going to
take a picture of it so they have a reference and then I'm going to put it right there.
you take a picture right now. I think it's a beautiful job. Well, I'm not
taking a picture of you. Okay, and then air drop it to me. All right,
okay, wait, why don't people say that? Because people say, take a picture and
then Caleb, you're in it, make a little face, be proud of it, be proud of your
tattoo. People say, guys, people say, hey, why don't you take a picture? It'll
last longer, but what lasts longer than a tattoo? Picture, I say,
after a person dies, exactly. A picture doesn't last that long either. A
picture of a tattoo lasts 10 times as long.
So what do you say?
If somebody's staring at you, what do you say?
Hey, how about you get a tattoo of me?
On your back?
On your back, because that'll last longer.
Like Steve-o.
Yeah.
What if you get a tattoo of me on your back with my thumbs up?
But then you run the risk of running into somebody who's very, very gullible and they
may take that seriously.
Yeah.
But if they take a picture, then it's like, all right, you can delete it.
But if it's a tattoo, then...
And that's an expensive tattoo that could ruin somebody's life.
second rule to delete tattoos. You can delete them through laser beams. No, they're going
to have an X button on them and someone can run up on the street and press X on it. Oh,
come on man! That cost me thousands of dollars. What the fuck was that man? That'd be good
for prisoners though. I got that's Kat Von D, put that on my back. I spent ten thousand
dollars on that. I forgot that she's a tattoo artist every single time. I thought that in
my head she's just Bam Margera's friend. Yeah, I honestly, she is a waitress in my brain.
he's a well. That was the thing back in the day. You could just be like a goth
girl on my space and then that's how you got famous. You can still do that.
That's not what she's famous. Yeah, doing yeah, I'm going to be a goth girl
on my space then
and then I'm going to be super famous. Oh, my God, honestly, but you can you
can
and I get those big scene bangs. Yeah, oh, my God, I'd be so beautiful and
they fight yeah, and then the scene guy with a
you still get famous by being a goth girl on myspace and you basically still can but instead
of being on myspace you just have to be on CNN.
Yeah.
True.
So it's not that big a difference.
It's true.
There's too many goths on CNN.
I know.
I'm so fucking sick of these goth girls on CNN.
How about instead of going on CNN you go on to YouTube again where you're home, where you
come from and make videos of you being random again.
Now you're telling the news?
What the hell?
Yeah.
I think you guys should be on RedTube and stuff all the way.
You're naked and showing their, spreading their assholes, putting stuff in there.
What?
Just a better...
That's really like half of the people who are goths, they do that.
If you have really, really brightly white skin, I feel like you gotta be goth.
Yeah.
It's kinda your lot in life.
That's where you end up.
Because what else are you gonna do?
Speaking of...
You're fucking useless, bro.
Yeah.
I'm
fixing myself. No, come on. What is it?
You're perfect just the way you are.
I'm going to fix myself. I've been wearing new clothes.
I don't want to...
No, we had this discussion already.
I'm going to throw out all of my t-shirts.
You wore that shirt already.
But I'm wearing only normal-ass adult grown man butt-downs.
This is still a funny shirt.
This is not a funny shirt.
This is probably the funniest shirt that you've ever worn, to be honest.
It's literally some kind of Middle East dollar.
It's ironical.
It's not ironical. It's actually...
It's pro-Iraq. It's iracical. It's pro-Iraq shirt. How is it pro-Iraq? It's just a picture
of money. Yeah. It's pro-the guy does look a lot like Jubio though. It is pro-Iraqi dinar.
This does look a lot like Jubio. Speaking of, how fucked is it? I got a little Jubio
in my pocket. We're working on Memorial Day and he's a veteran. Yeah. He fought in the
the Mexican War.
We don't smile. I don't smile. You can't even see you. Can you can you add your
webcam as a source?
Wouldn't it be cool? And then we can cut to the Jubio cam. If we visited Mexico
and Jubio was like a full war hero.
The thing that always makes me laugh always to tell everyone is that he's a
he in Mexico, he's the most famous pop star in the country. Yeah.
That he like performed.
Yeah, we kind of couldn't believe this.
The biggest comedian.
I looked up, I was looking at the Wikipedia page for the city that Juvio is from.
Yeah.
And it's a big, big city.
And I looked at the, I was just reading the Wikipedia page and it had a notable people
thing.
And it's like 7 million people live in the city.
One notable person.
Uh huh.
Who?
In 150 years.
Him?
No, it was like some bitch from the 1800s.
He should be.
How is there no notable people from this?
Yeah.
Wilmington, North Carolina has like 25 notable people.
Do you know what I learned today?
12 that maybe I assume you want to film on the Wikipedia. No, you're not. No way. I
tried to add myself, which I'm sure you know this. I had no idea that Venus fly
traps. They only live around Wilmington. Yeah, I didn't know that at all. Yeah,
they're like, why you go see it? You see wild. It's like, but they don't live
like anywhere else. I thought you were going to say that Venus fly trap was
like a notable or maybe not even 50 miles. Okay. Yeah. So it's like a Venus
Flytrap good name for a my Carolina.
Wilmington is the northern most subtropical climate
in the world.
Wow, and that's the blend for whatever reason.
It's the only place that they ever have been.
That's pretty crazy.
I had no idea.
What about a tropical?
So really not that cool though.
They're cool.
I saw kind of cool, but they're really small.
Yeah, they're not as big as the cool thing is when you put a
pencil in its mouth that kills it.
Yeah,
what tropical sub
Spam, pineapple, King's Hawaiian sub.
You want to talk to me about Hawaiian breakfast right now?
Maybe some like fried rice patties onto it.
No, no, no.
I'm thinking ideas to get us out the hood.
I'm thinking tropical sub, Hawaiian sub.
Oh, you're saying we somehow make a Hawaiian roll that goes all the way.
Yeah.
An all the way roll.
A foot long Hawaiian roll.
That is actually a foot long Hawaiian roll.
Just in general, maybe even a foot long roll.
pineapple. Yeah, maybe even that we put spam on it. The way I apples
teriyaki. You don't want pineapple. They don't put pineapple on the spam, man.
That's not good news. Okay, then we'll do like a bit. It's like a big.
What do you mean? They put the big the grilled? Yeah, we put grilled pineapple
on it. No, you don't want a spam sandwich. I've done that that you just
are an idiot. Then I thought that was I'm sorry. What's the friendship? What
What did we say today's episode was? I thought that was the egg split sandwich.
That place sucks shit. I wouldn't trust that place. You made those sandwiches for us.
This just reminded me. Not with pineapple. I thought there was pineapple on it.
No, you crazy piece of shit. Oh no, it was spam and eggs, god damn it.
You thought an egg was pineapple because it's yellow? Yes. What is wrong with you?
I guess it has a hard exterior. But it would be kind of good. Hard to eat from the outside.
outside. I don't like pineapple. I had an incredible idea for a TV show.
It's called "Taste Bad."
Yes.
It's supposed to.
It's supposed to be caustic. I don't want good tasting cum. It might come
tasting like candy. That would be, that's bad. Yeah, it's not right.
Because I'd be eating it all the time. Yeah. No, my idea for a TV show,
because we went to get chilaquiles, me and... Say it the right way.
He's right there.
Say, how am I supposed to say it? What did I say wrong? You just said
- Chilaquiles. - Chilaquiles.
- Chilaquiles. - A little more.
- And I had the most incredible idea for a TV show,
which is that he comes to New York City.
- Yeah. - He is a food reviewer,
but he's not reviewing the taste of the food,
he's only reviewing whether or not it is auténtico.
- Okay. - And he starts out,
the first one he has Mexican food, he says,
"This isn't really auténtico." Second episode,
he has Chinese food. He says,
"This is not auténtico. We do not eat this in Mexico."
so
different cultures for everything. This is not authentic. That's a great idea.
We
don't eat this type of that's a good point, like walking up to the manager of
the restaurant, just be like and I love the food. It was amazing. I got the
char siu pork. I loved it so much, but unfortunately this is not authentic to
Mexico.
From authentic Mexico, far from it. They're just getting so mad,
so we put a giant sticker on the restaurant door. This is not
authentic, not authentic,
in small red letters that blend in of Mexican food. Yeah, it's in front of
like a pizza place, but in front of like a great food reviewer personality.
Yeah, on a I think he's too shy. He is too shy. He is so incredibly shy.
Yes, shyness. He does have shine in a way that can't be. I mean, it's
terminal. He misbehaves in restaurants to does he misbehave at restaurants?
He says his shyness causes misbehavior.
You can't, well then you can come over here if you want to talk but you shouldn't.
You're in the room and you can't defend yourself.
Yeah, fuck you.
What does he do?
He orders something and they say they bring him the wrong thing and he goes like this.
And then the person asks me, "Oh, you didn't ask for this?"
I'm like, "I don't know, you have to talk to him."
And he's like this, "I'm too shy."
Oh yeah, I did witness this.
Wait, you do, I thought you only did this at English speaking restaurants.
He does it at Mexican restaurants too?
These motherfuckers speak Spanish.
Spanish. They do speak Spanish. You're a liar. He started speaking Spanish to
her and she said I didn't couldn't tell because it was all in Spanish. What
was going on? Well, he has a very anything what I've learned. I say he
doesn't understand people with different accents, so like it
apparently every the gap between his accent and everybody else's accent is
the same as like the the Creole Cajun accent and like most other American
by you boy. So that's what I mean. He had he has the version walking around and
people are like kind of giggling when you speak Spanish. Yeah, he speaks it like a
fool. I've actually I've witnessed that too. I saw the I saw this coffee incident
that you're talking about. We were all we were all at getting which there was
two. There's two coffee incidents and one was averted by me. The second that's
the one you saw it happened. The second one the he I had to say so that's four
more coffees right to the waitress, because I could tell that something got
lost
and I fixed it and it still got messed up, but it wasn't my fault. You know you
saying he misbehaves at restaurants. I do want to point out on Saturday night.
There was a chase.
You there was a chase. There's a there was a incident, a chasing incident. I am
at the bar. I'm sorry real quick. I have to say this is almost feeling like the
opposite of the
episode. It seems like we're dissecting our friend in a very rude way.
Home and I just want to say that I just want to... I don't think that you guys
were... I don't think you guys witnessed this, but a group of men on the street
certainly witnessed it and were very scared.
Did you chase? You chased Patrick down the street? I'm at the bar.
I'm ordering wings for me and my girlfriend to share because we were
very drunk. I order myself a Dacote as well. I'm standing there waiting.
I don't remember what happened, but all of a sudden,
I'm a block away from the bar we were at,
turning the corner and Jubio is chasing me down the street.
That's not right. There's too big of a size difference.
People are going to assume the worst. I'm also kind of,
I'm also I'm kind of worried and scared about the gap between the gap here
between ordering wings and you're around the corner being chased. Yeah,
what happened there? I don't know. It was all a blur. I'm running down the
street in my suit. What I'm getting here maybe is from you is that instinctively
you are kind of a prey animal where you see a predator on the hunt. Like
Jibio. And yeah, and you kind of exactly a predator like him. I don't remember
what happened. All I know is that it's fighter flight kicked in. You flighted.
I ran out of the bar and then I ran a full city block and then I came back and
tried to pretend like I did not get chased. But you did fully got scared of
it. Then the way of a night's job, you have to come here and explain what
happened because I did not talk to the men. The men came and questioned him.
The men talked to him. Yeah, go come this way. No, it was just a group of
guys. I don't care about the story. So you
So we're at the bar. I can hear myself. We're at the bar and I just come up to
Patrick like, "Hey, what's up Patrick? How are you doing?" And he just takes off
running.
I'm like,
that's not what happened. He takes off running.
I did not. You did. He takes off running and I go, "I must get him unless he gets
lost." And I just chase after him. He is changing the story up. I must get him
I think it's a bar in my neighborhood. I know the city.
I think you guys saw the dogs playing and you wanted to try it yourself.
Do you hear what you said? Say it again.
I don't remember.
Yeah. Okay. So keep that in mind. I chased him.
He gets to the corner and turns the corner. I'm like, I don't want to do that.
I'm going to go back to the bar.
And you were in a goofy mood.
Yeah.
You were in a goofy mood and you wanted to chase me and you initiated the chase.
There was three men. Oh my God.
There was three men, like a doorstep and they're like, everything all right.
I'm like, yeah, we're just playing around.
2.30 in the morning, maybe no, this is midnight. Midnight. Yeah.
Yeah.
So I get back to the bar. I'm like, I don't know where Patrick is. It's been
like a couple minutes.
So you circle the block because I thought it would be funny to walk by
and pretend like I don't know you. Yeah, and he finally gets back and he has
his phone open with Apple Maps on it because he got
their maps.
Okay, I did want to confirm that I was on the right street. Yes. All right, so I
didn't, I wanted to confirm that I didn't overshoot. We've done a lot of
running around that bar recently when I got dropped off there the other day. You
did run, I got out of the bar and then just ran away from the bar because I
needed to say, well, me and Patrick were sitting there, we're waiting for Julio
and Caleb and Patrick pointed to a funny looking guy and said, oh, there's Julio
and I turn and of course, what happened? He's the guy who's behind me. I turned
around, made eye contact with the guy and immediately started laughing by
looking at this man who was walking up to us. I felt pretty bad about that,
and then
a little later Patrick went, "Oh, there's Caleb," and I turned and I saw a
guy who looked a little bit like Caleb, and a full sprint across the street.
Full exact, he's wearing this hat, which is unmistakable. Yeah, and I was
like, "Wait,
that is Caleb." Yeah, it was, man. I completely thought I was getting... And
then he came back with a veggie wrap. It wasn't a veggie wrap, it was a
turkey sandwich. Oh, alright. It wasn't a... Turkey wrap. It was a
it's a spin a trap. Yeah, the reason why was because I've been so sick that I was
having acid reflux because the only thing in my stomach was my own mucus. Yeah, I
needed to eat something so bad that is nasty and so I had to run. I ran ain't
that is nasty. I'm pro people don't like running in public. I do it almost every
time I need to be somewhere or I just want to be somewhere a little bit
faster. I will. I used to I used to I was one of the kids in who used to run
through the school hall. Yeah, I don't really have. I think that shit was fire.
I think people have a shame about that.
I would run in circles.
On more than one occasion.
God gave me these amazing long legs for a reason.
I live close enough to that train stop.
On more than one occasion where like you know where that restaurant, the garlic to the chicken
is.
Yeah.
I have been turning the corner, see the train pull up and I just bolt.
I just fucking.
For some reason I won't run to a train.
I bolt, I will.
I can make it because I have a small window where I can make it.
You know where you can make it.
I know the window you're in, but then I'm like, I'm running.
That Forrest Ave stop sucks so bad because there's the one spot where everyone can get out.
So I run and I get out.
What I do when I'm trying to catch the train, I would never break into a full run,
but I do the long leg. I'm fully running with my legs, but I'm not doing anything with my upper body.
because I can stride big. You should do this with your upper body. I might start doing
that. That's my favorite thing to do if I'm running to something that I want to get too
fast is to just go really far with my legs. I think that's so fun. I do have very short
legs so it looks like plankton walking. I also have short legs. It sucks having short
ass legs. I basically have a demon inside me that lets me move fast when I want. Having
short legs is probably I think I should get like checks from the government. The
cereal yeah, you should get checked for being gay. No,
don't put the squeeze remix that the squeeze don't put the squeeze sounded
that's the squeeze. So that is the squeeze. I actually don't know what
that boing I was going to call it this brine, but the original yeah, what was
Where's the original boing from just a boing? Yeah, what do you mean? I mean,
like just came with the road. No, no, do you know what it actually is? Okay,
sound is actually do you want the history lesson here? Give it to me. That
is an instrument called a jew's harp. Yeah, that you put into your mouth and
it's the thing. Do you know punch and judy the puppet shows they do where they
do like
with their mouth? Yeah, it's that and then we're doing that now we're doing
we're going to change this. It's also called a swizzle stick and it's like
it's like a reed that you put into your mouth and you can move it.
I don't think it goes all the way in. It does, because sometimes you swallow it
by accident. Yeah, I've swallowed many a jew's harp. But I'm trying to show you
where it goes, like it's like this big and it's like... Wait, so it's called a
jew's harp or a swizzler's swizzle stick? Swizzle stick. Or maybe those are two
different things, but... We had a dude come to my elementary school to teach
us all about folk music. It was like an artist in residence thing, and he was
teaching us about that he went out of his way to call it a Jaws harp.
Yeah. It's a better name. It goes between the jaws. It's a better name for sure,
but then
I think I tried to look it up later and then I saw it was called a
News Harp and I went, "What the fuck?" What the... He also taught us how
to play the spoons on our knees. What are those? What's that? It's so funny
to tell a story and end it with, and I went and then go,
"What the..." Y'all, it's 101. 101. Yeah, it's 101. My alarm's going off.
just chill on me. Just chill on me, family, because I don't know how to
change it and I change it in my sleep accidentally, because sometimes I fall
asleep with my Casio watch on and I press all the buttons and then I'll wake
up and it'll be eleven thirty five and the alarm's going off. Wow, damn, yeah,
you should change it. I'll change you. No, I will change you. Okay, guys,
all right, all right, all right, cool. If you're not gonna change me about
friendship and about our friends, we've been talking about friendship. We haven't,
we've been talking about Jews and harps and shit. We were talking about
friendship pretty much this whole time. We were, we were looking at it from
kind of a negative lens.
If us three never have met each other,
how would we act? How would we act? I would be completely different. I would
be
probably the president, I'd probably be the president, and now you guys go
like, "What? You wouldn't be the president of the loser club from not
having two besties. The president of the not having two besties
I would know him either. Maybe I mean good chance I probably would be working on
like an oil rig or something. No you wouldn't. That is not fucking. You would
be living at your parents house. No it would be a good chance. I'd be like. You
would not be working on an oil. You'd not be doing anything. It's really funny to
say it like to be like yeah if I had met there's a one other person in my life I'd
working on an oil rig?
I'd probably be working construction and building the biggest building.
You would not! You would be hitting, you would do a Homer Simpson movie construction nail.
No, I'd probably, actually now that I think about it, I'd probably be working in plumbing or like some kind of HVAC.
You'd be working in HR?
No, I'd be working in electricity.
As a person who's accused of something.
I'd probably be working for, I would probably, what?
You'd be in, your job would be going into HR?
My job would not be, no, because I'd be working on the job site.
be like the CPR dummy kind of thing only bring you to be on this monster dot com.
That's right yeah, because I'll be looking for
rig jobs, searching
in Brooklyn.
Patrick would have actually been on monster dot com searching like food
tester and like video game
skateboard store employee.
What if like one day one day you guys are like you guys are downtown in
Manhattan, you're walking by, where is that? That's like first and something.
Second.
First and second.
And third.
And third. You're walking around that area and there's that big ass Zoomies that is in
a building that looks like it used to be a bank.
And what did we tell you?
You just see me in there just like folding a shirt and you're like, "Oh, what the hell?
He must be like looking at it."
Folding it to put it back.
"He must be, yeah, folding it to put it back."
Yeah, he tried it on.
And then you see me and I'm putting like ten more shirts out. I'm just working it.
I'm working at Zoomies and you walk in, I pretend like I don't know you. I'm just
like, "Hey, what's going on?" And then you're like, "Oh, you must know my
brother, my brother Patrick." My name tag says Ricky.
I'm just in this Zoomies and I have a backwards hat on. Oh my God, you're
starting a second life as Ricky. Yeah. Oh my God, I have gauges that you
don't know about.
I got big as like the spikes, like the trainers, and you're like, "What the
I look different enough that you're like, "This guy definitely has to be Ricky."
And you've worked at Zoomies for a long, long time.
I've worked at Zoomies the whole time I've lived in New York.
The three years I've been here, I've worked at that Zoomies.
My whole job is making the worst custom skateboard for a fat teenager.
It's got pink trucks with a big blue grip tape.
Listen guys, before we get too far into having a friendship conversation...
you never resolved. You never resolved what you would you do if I you saw me
and I was Ricky. You never resolved what I would do what I would go ahead and
say. Yeah, I don't know. You guys have to decide for me. What? No, we both
decided ourselves. Okay, then I would just adapt yourself. Okay, whatever. I'd
be a musician. Okay. Yeah. Thank you. All right. Pianist. No pianist. Right.
Rango Ringo. He'd be Ringo.
The Nickelodeon. I would work. I would work. I would work. I would work. I
You would work, yeah. I would be a good mascot guy.
You would be at Nickelodeon Universe at the American Dream Mall and you'd be
walking around dressed up as Rango and then the security would come out and say,
"You can't fucking do that anymore, Caleb! You can't be Rango, he's not in
the park!" I could be a walk around character so easily. But you're bringing
your own Rango costume.
I feel like the walk around... Wait, wait, wait. Wow, yeah. Wow. And then
Can you play just like Timmy Turner sounds?
What?
He would be a perfect walk around Timmy Turner.
You think I can play Timmy Turner sounds?
No, Tommy Pickles.
What is it?
It's a costume.
It covers your whole body.
It's 25 years old.
They wouldn't dress him up.
No, that's a costume.
No, but it's 25 years old.
But there's like parts in Nickelodeon universe where it's like, okay, this is here for the
adults to remember.
They got Legends of the Hidden Temple and stuff.
You've been in Nickelodeon universe?
Yeah.
I've been in Nickelodeon universe.
temple and stuff. You've been to Nickelodeon Universe? Yes. It's in the American Dream
Mall in East Rutherford, New Jersey. Okay, true. It's actually dope and we need to go
ride the show razor. You're an actual dope. I'm sorry. Okay guys. Yeah, this is what I'm
doing. We need to get into this. We need to full screen this though. As a friendship trip
though. Can we go to the American Dream Mall? Can you just drag it over a little bit? He
can't even see it. Oh, well it's wrong. He's going to try to fix it. He's going to try and
I
and
I don't know if you could hear that. He said it's so fucked in here now. This setup will
be okay soon. Yeah. As soon as he goes home. Once we figure all this crap out. Once we
get rid of him. So today I've thought. Before we go, I'm sorry to interrupt. I did say,
should we go to America, can we go to American Dream as a friendship trip? Yes, of course.
No problem. Okay. But I'm putting, listen, friendship conversation is over until I get
through this because you're going to burn through everything. So you have to stop for now and
just wait. Do you have my toy? Just wait. Do you have my toy? Thank you. I already got
them on. We're looking today at a website called the pleasant relationship. I googled
pleasant relationship and I feel like I would like to have a pleasant relationship with
with you guys. I feel like we have a pleasant relationship, so it seems like
it makes sense for this to be the way. I mean, it could be more so yeah, so
this is gonna allow, you know, nothing's perfect. He's nerfect. Yeah, my dad
came up with that. I think that I think Bart Simpson came up with that.
No, is your dad? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
is your dad grown up? Bart? My dad is the creator of Pobity's nerfect. If
anybody would know, I'm serious, but that is grown up Bart. No, he's not, but
my dad invented writing in all capital letters. That's not true. My dad
invented the cooper black font,
but I think that in the I want to be I want to be norm perfect. So yeah, if and
I want our our friendship to be more relationship, our pollet, a ship to be
risen yeah
Scooby Doo yeah, but I want I want to I want to have more nerf action and more
affection yeah in our relationships and pleasancy yeah. So let's yeah. So let's
go let's dive into this. So I've pulled up an article for us to have kind of a
friendship conversation that can span the rest of the episode and try and
deepen our relationship a little bit. The logo is beautiful. That is so pleasant.
That is so friendship to me.
Will you click on this? It's kind of like a dunkin donas core. How's that a
relationship? The clicker's not working. Oh turn it on. It's on. Okay, okay.
And we're looking at today, 40 things to talk about with a guy.
Oh, we're two guys.
Yeah, we're two guys.
We're two guys.
Well, you're the leader of the list and we're two guys.
No, we're all two guys.
No, yeah, we're in a conversation.
Between the three of us, we have two guys here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And this is...
Please say it's him.
And this has been...
It's him.
He's the girl.
Okay, we're not going to do that right now.
Look, that's you on the left.
left, worst possible time you could be doing this. That's me. No, no, no, no.
Okay, so anyway, this has been this forty things to talk about with a guy, and
this has been, this is exciting to me to announce. This list has been reviewed by
Julianne Cantarella, MSW, LSW, certified relationship coach. Whoa! Nobody better
to deepen a friendship than a certified relationship coach. You're saying this
is about friendship, but I'm seeing up here in pink letters, it says romantic
conversations.
Oh, really? Yeah, I think that must I must that must have been
another part of like a there must have been an article that
went up right above.
So it's like this was on the homepage.
Yeah, and then you click the other one.
This is solidly romantic like the romantic period like kind
of little romantic literature, maybe like like Roman like
Italian. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that romantic.
Yeah, Roman Roman.
I like your typo typo on the way.
So it's supposed to be romantic.
Yes, romantic conversations, romantic, Romani's yeah, okay, Romani. Yeah,
okay, all right, all right, let's so yeah, let's let's see here
start with paying him a compliment.
So who is gonna be the tester? I think we all just have a conversation.
Okay, I don't know what the test, the tester. Well, buddy, if I could say
one thing to you right now, if I could, I would say this. Okay, your
hat matches your shirt in a nice way. Wow, and if I could say one thing
to you, it would be button your shirt up. That's not a compliment. Oh, what's a
compliment? Your shirt looks good buttoned. Your shirt would look really
good. You would look really good if you were completely covered head to toe.
Not really a compliment. It would look really, really cute if I couldn't see
any of your body. You look good when you're sitting up straight.
See, now it's a compliment. There you go.
You would look really good scared,
but with your hands out like this to there we got here's my your hands look
so good just now yeah
or my hand will make you I'm not for having really ugly, awful hands. You do
have very ugly hands because of all the cuts.
I got cuts all over say that I've calluses and you guys come on my look at
the dirt on his nails. Nothing wrong with it. You see you're supposed to
compliment me. So your hands look as human as anybody else.
Those look like real human grabbers.
Thanks guys.
Yeah.
Those look like real human grabbers.
Okay, let's see.
Move forward here.
Oh, alright, why don't you be the one who advances the slide?
Yeah, how about you do that?
How about we just say next slide to you?
He doesn't know how to do anything.
He's not good at clicking.
Okay, can we get the next slide?
He's a clicking problem.
The clicker is again not working.
There we go.
Okay, thank you.
Oh yeah, we're skipping some numbers here.
Oh, alright.
We're just going to skip to it because it's 40 things.
Okay.
We're not going to make it all the way through.
Talk about your passions.
There's a woman playing bass.
Um, I play bass.
I also play bass.
I play bass.
How have we never talked about this?
This is crazy.
Wait, we all play bass?
Every last one of us?
Round wounds or flat wounds?
I do both.
You do both?
You do top, top two, top two round wounds,
bottom two flat wounds?
I don't have any wounds on mine.
wounds. I try to play a lot of wounds. No, no nylon either. Wow, I do nylon. You do
nylon and you have one string to
and it's nylon. I have one big nylon. I try to play with that wounds or nylon
just to see if I can do it and I have a tooth in the middle of my big tooth, but
one tooth as your egg tooth. Yeah, and I just I just picked that thing. It's
attached to a little bucket and my base is my base is necklace to do you guys
base is your necklace? I know it's I why yes whoa but it has no neck and frets.
Do you guys play eastern or western style? I play north lodian scales
northeastern mix a lodeon yeah nickelodeon scales I do I've never played
those
I play nickelodeon scales. Did you guys go to college for base? I was in a
conservatory. I played with a bunch of people who played cello, French horn,
flute. I used to play on a cruise ship. Yeah. I was around Berklee, but I never
went in. Berklee? Yeah. It's College of Music. I was around Berklee. Charles?
Stop playing that bass.
Man, get that bass out of here. That's Shaq. That's Shaq. Berklee's up here.
He sounds like a Muppet, like some kind of Muppet. We should just do the rest
episode of the show. You and me are kind of a Shaq and Barclay and you're Ernie.
And he's Kenny. Actually, no, Kenny Ernie. No, Ernie and Bert. Speaking of,
by the way, you guys are Ernie and Bert. I'd like to say this. I would like to.
I would like to right now curse the Boston Celtics recording this on Monday.
The Boston Celtics will lose tonight. Game seven. Oh, you're doing a reverse
psychology. I they're losing tonight. Okay. Yes. I'm doing a reverse curse.
Okay, smart. This is playoff game zone or yeah champion. They're down. It's the only time
anybody if they win tonight. Only time anybody's ever come back from a zero to three game deficit
in the NBA. Wow. It's only happened in four times in any sport. That's incredible. Nope.
So make sure to make sure to reach out to your uncles tonight. Everybody. Yeah, actually
give your dose your uncles with Vive and so their hearts are racing really fucking hard
while the game's going so maybe they'll die.
But that's the thing, your uncle has to have complete concentration on the game.
Every single uncle needs to have a mind-meld blue light thing coming out of their forehead
headed towards Worcester Mass tonight.
Is that where they play?
No, but that's just like where most of the people, where it should be.
It should be in Worcester.
I think Boston should be replaced by Worcester.
I think Boston should be replaced by...
I think they should move Boston to Worcester.
Yeah, we're call Worcester. They should switch them for a few years. Worcester
is a property of Boston. Now I think Boston should I other way around. I
honestly think Boston should be replaced by like a Godzilla foot or something. I
think it should be wiped off the map. Let's just move on. It's got to go. It's
got anything else. Got to go. No, you don't think next slide. Let's just go to
the next slide. We get the next slide that he's eating his boogers. Play the
old and famous question game. Well, I don't know what this means. Yeah, but
what I'm seeing from the picture, if anyone can see it is a question mark
inside a square and I think it's making me think, oh, Mario, let's say it on
three. Well, no, I guess Pat can say it on zero and then me and Caleb will say
it on 3123 Mario. I didn't hear the on three part. Yeah, when I see a block
like that, I fucking ran my head into it. I want money from that because I
I want a turtle to pop out. No, let's play the question game. Okay, okay,
twenty one questions. I don't know any questions. Just a question. Okay, three
questions, three okay, okay, let's play three questions. Okay, I have an object.
Okay, is it it's an object? Okay, I have an object. Is it red?
It is. Is it a fruit?
Is it round? Does it have one leaf?
iconically. Yes, it does. Yeah. What is it? Is it an apple? It's a red apple.
Yeah, it was. I was gonna guess a cherry. That's crazy that we did three questions
and you actually got it. Yeah. I mean, I panicked and said, I just, you know,
just agreed with him. No, no, I panicked when I chose my object. Wait, you
actually picked apple? I swear to God, I picked a red apple.
I was just looking at your no, no, no, no thing. Maybe that's what I was looking
at. When I chose to yeah, that's why I said red, you would have done orange and
you would have done banana. I maybe would have done a great man, maybe a
plantain,
but no one to know. No, no, no, no, three questions. I've got it's mine. It's a
concept. Okay, is that a literary concept?
is
I guess it could be is it in the room with us? Yes, and it's all around a
fucking friendship. Yeah,
God yeah, that's another win for us. All right, that's your turn. We ain't
getting
this is a
person.
Is it you
know? Is it a real person? Yes,
question. Choose your final question. Is he wearing a hat? Famously in this room? No.
Is it Jubio? Yes. I guess that's technically a loss. That's it. Yeah. Wait, how is that
a loss? Because you didn't get it in three. You got it in four. I got it in three. He
I only asked one yeah, but I think it was a collective right
collection. I hear that collective a good time. We're going to get stricken
from copyright YouTube. Yeah,
we're done. All right next slide next slide, por favor.
Okay, so this one shit bring in the S word and I know people were going to
have questions about this. So I put in another slide of their explanation of
what the S word is. So I hope you all are ready to have this conversation.
let's get the next slide. You don't have to brainstorm your head to figure out
you don't have to brainstorm your head. I didn't read that to figure out what to
talk about with a guy all the time for starter men can and will always be
interested in conversation topics related to sex. However, you need to have
a way with it. Don't just shoot a million sex related questions or topics on him
for that might throw him off the conversation entirely. I've shot a
million sex related something before probably we are already in a we're
We're starting already. We're deep in it. In my, in jizz. So would you guys
rather be deep when you're having sex? Would you go deep or not deep? Would
you rather get
deep throated or just the tip in your mouth? Just the tip in the mouth? Yeah,
or in their mouth.
Or the butt? Do you like, would you rather... Would you rather do a butt or
a pussy better? Yeah. Or would you rather have a butt or a pussy? Would
you rather... Oh, well, I already have a butt. Oh, gay.
So wait, so I replace my butthole with a pussy?
If you can only have one.
Would you rather go fast or go slow?
I like going as fast as fucking possible.
Yeah.
When I nut it sounds like a fucking turtle.
Do you guys like finishing?
No.
I, yes.
That's the only part I like.
Because I want to go all night long.
I wish I could finish fucking instantly.
I wish I could finish ten thousand times in a row.
I wish I could start at the end.
One three, everyone do your O face. One, two, three.
I said earlier, I said earlier, I said earlier, it's because I nut like a
turtle. You do speedy. I go, do you guys like being on your tummy or on
your back? I like being on my back, but as long as I get flipped over,
as long as I get flipped over onto my tummy later.
I like being on my tummy personally.
Do you guys where do you guys like shooting jizz probably in the air big
floor?
I shoot it up yeah, the air to the floor yeah, I did give it a busy year curve.
So is that how you say that busy? I have no idea be easy. I say on about I
guess I read it as a year and a bee's ear. We are that's not what we're here
to talk about. No, I'm saying the
introducing a new topic to kind of an angle to tackle sex from would you guys
photoshop a sexual photo of yourself. I already have
and what would it be? I gave myself boobs for real. I keep putting my face
in it on Lana Rhoades body with Ai yeah, just fucking throwing the videos away
yeah, I don't even open them. I do it and I just move it right trash.
You
burn them out to your just to train the Ai on it a little bit, so that yeah
somebody I use that picture might appear. So I'm hoping I get some kind of
my cloud hack or something and somebody finds it opens up. I don't want to see
you never empty the trash can. You have it all burn. You burn it out to a DVD
and then on your honeymoon, you show your wife like I got you this. I'm doing
I'm just putting all this shit in my I'm putting all this in my recycling bin and
then I'm just watching like the most shitty illegal hockey streams of all
time. So I got a nice kind of malware thing that downloads it all. Yeah, but
hopefully soon
that on a TV. I got you something special. Pulling out the DVD player, putting it in.
Also, I made a custom menu with bonus features.
There's an Easter egg on it. Yeah, give me your wife's sex tape where you made
a DVD menu with bonus features, scene selection, but the scene selection is
all like, it's like,
"I got tired, I needed a break." Yeah,
the scene selection is just like, it's ripped directly from the Crank Yankers
DVD. Yeah, it's got special ed and stuff. Hello, that's perfect. Yeah, it has a
DVD run game. Yeah, put it in your computer and you can go on to choose
your own adventure. And there's behind the scenes footage of you getting
interviewed by like your friend,
like the Star Wars documentary. And you're talking, you're going like, so
basically, you have a completely different... Essentially, I need a duck
for... I set out to make the most erotic film in the registry. It's playing that
I thought what better than a porno to elicit erotic feelings.
Elicit, huh.
Basically I thought to myself, what if I commed at the end of the movie.
Or you could do a bunch of different characters in the documentary.
Oh yeah, and the new characters are the ones getting effed.
You're the boom operator.
Yeah, that's what I would do is I would do cross cutting of the sex scene and then like a little behind the scenes thing of me holding the boom.
And like, "Wow, they're really going at it."
Yeah, they're giving it to me.
damn those five guys are giving it to me. Yeah, I'm going to Craig's posting an
ad for a boom operator for a sex tape with your and I'm not telling her
little like lower third one of those things, but it's like Chuck on him and
on NBC. It's like check out Chuck on Mondays. You're about to say MSNBC.
Well, there is Chuck on there too. Yeah, yeah, Chuck from from thank God for not
that one up. Chuck from what's the show called? Meet the Press. So fuck you buddy. Nowadays
when I watch the one I want to watch the news instead of Meet the Press I think Me Depressed.
Shit. Speaking of brainstorm. That deserves a... Why is brain people say brainstorm like
it's a good thing it sounds painful. Yeah. I think that's our cue to move on to the next
slide. Imagine a squishy brain hitting you in the head. No I was going to say... Number
seven what's his idea of a perfect date? So this is about our friendship. Well yeah but
But it's like friends can talk about what their ideal perfect date would be.
I think I started before the list saying what my perfect date was.
See that's why I was trying to stop you.
Yeah.
That's why I didn't really want you to say that.
Oh my God Cameron, I should listen to you more.
And see we're getting, I'm pretty sure there's a slide in here about communication that's
probably going to pop up.
I think these are all about communication.
That sounded like a fart through the headphones.
Mine is probably a movie, sex and cuddles marathon.
24 hours.
I just do the cuddles marathon.
you guys. I want to have sex. Why do we always need a movie to have a marathon?
Yep. That's always a fucking marathon and not just a couch marathon
or a hanging out all day marathon or a food marathon. Food marathon. Yeah,
food marathon. That would be dope. Yep. A mara, a normal marathon is a food
marathon. When you're done. Yeah. You gotta eat as much as you can. Oh my
God. That replenish. I want to eat all my food. So that's your, that's your
perfect date. Cameron, what's yours? Mine would probably be going to first.
I would fly to Mexico, then I might fly to Monter. Well, no, no, no, no, no. Just to,
I want to, just to like more beautiful part than wherever he is. I would like go to the
beach. I don't think, you don't live near the beach, right? Yeah, no, I'm not coming
anywhere near you. He's not going to say where, but he lives in northeast Mexico. I would
have been, I would be going to the Yucatan Peninsula. Then I'd probably go to Japan.
Yeah. Then probably, I'm with my friends with Yucatan. Iceland, New Zealand. I would do the
Lord of the Rings film tour in New Zealand. Then I would fly to Vegas and I would be like
we'd see the thing where you can get married in Vegas and I'd be like "uh?" and she'd be
like "no, no." And I'd be like "yeah, it's too soon." And then we'd probably fly to Alaska
and then Arctica. Go to Alaska, work on a ship for a couple years. Greenland. Catch snow crab.
I think then we would go to Siberia. I'm kind of like a cold weather winter guy. Yeah, you
like so I'd be going and then I go to Ukraine. Yeah, so save that shit. Yeah,
you know you could do go to Las Vegas, go to that. Well, yeah, exactly. Then we
go back to Vegas place in Vegas. That looks like Italy right leave immediately
get on a plane, fly to that exact location that they're ripping off in
Italy. Yeah, and then that's actually genius. Then you can compare and
contrast. So then I do that. I do what you just said. Then I fly to Portland,
get kind of our weird on a little bit. I go to Maine and then Oregon, then I'm
taking a bus from Portland to Seattle, then fly. Once we get into Seattle,
we're gonna get to the airport, we're gonna fly from SeaTac. We're gonna fly
down to Dallas. You're saying a lot of amazing stuff. I'm not done yet.
I'm at about 4 PM at this point. All I care about... And it started at
two. All I care about is, are you getting lucky at the end of this
mission? Okay, so I'll skip over all this stuff. Okay.
the the final stop middle of the Sahara Desert and you go to Pantan go to what
Pan Tan. I don't know what that is. We're getting a little Indiana Jones
plane. We're flying to the direct. You know, you talk about getting the
Pan Tan getting in and get just wait, just wait, just wait, just wait, just
wait, get to the middle of the Sahara Desert. Nobody around for hundreds of
miles. Ready got finger completely, completely flat, and then I'm going to
lay down a blanket and got a pan and I'm going to hit that red and white
checkered blanket, yeah, with a pick and Nick basket full of condoms and there's
no ants in the desert. I think there's actually tons of fucking yeah,
I think the whole thing is and then we'll go to the tundra buddy and lay
down a blanket. Good luck fucking with a wings around in a fucking pain. Okay,
okay, okay, okay, we're going to go, then we'll go to
where else is there? No people, the ocean, the bottom of the ocean,
and I laid down a blanket. You want to hang out with a submarine? You got to
be careful, a submersible crabs,
come on man and sharks and octopus. You know the fish are going to be looking
in the window, don't be like damn. I want to hit that too. Damn, and I'm
really like come on in y'all that and then you let the whole ocean run a
train on the first date girl.
that's right yeah. I would let every single person from the Little Mermaid
the newest Cgi one team can be my beat my wife beat it up getting a pain team.
No, I don't want to go to pin Tim P and T. All right next slide. You're not
trying to go to ping ping the mindful. Oh yeah, this is just in the middle of
the list. The mindful recommends our top to pick up dating sites, a harmony dot
com. I think I don't know who the mindful is. It doesn't say it anywhere
looks on the page. Scary, the mindful to my kind of a villainous name.
Yeah, the mindful recommends the harmony all so just so you know all right
number eight talk about his long term plans in life. We talked about the long
term. Yeah, we actually covered that already. I think so we can skip ahead
restaurant. Ask about his crushes, both celebrities and real life. I just want
to hear some names. Okay, I'm qualified.
-Selena Gomez. -Selena Gomez.
-Selena Gomez. -No, no, no, no.
-Selena Gomez. -Oh, she goes the most.
-She's different. -She's different.
-Gossamer. -Gossamer.
-Who's Gossamer? -From Looney Tunes.
-Oh, yeah. -Most people are looking at Lola Bunny.
-And me, I'm licking my lips at a completely different--
-I'm looking at all that hair. -It's under that hair.
-No, just the hair. You're giving me the hair.
wasn't it. I wouldn't want to have sex with the bunny very much. You wouldn't
just I guess if I was a bunny, I would go after a bunny, but even as a bunny
bill, it looks like a human. Yeah, she's kind of is in that spot. If you're a
bunny like to up to a bunny that just the most just normal rabbit is what you
want to just be a bunny, but I guess if you were also, I guess the only person
in the world would be bugs. Yeah, bugs is they're a perfect fit or bugs is
uncle. How can she ever squander him? Imagine how awkward it would be if you're at a party
and you're Bugs Bunny and you're kind of, you're trawling, you're looking for the ladies,
it's all human ladies. Trying to get a peen team. And nobody will even look at you because
you're a disgusting bunny man. And then you turn a corner and it's Lola Bunny right there.
And you're like, I feel with Halle Berry. And she's got her butt pulled out. And you're
just like, well I guess this is the only person in the world. I think that's the worst part
about Lola Bunny is she's got a big tuft of hair right next to her junk. Most girls do.
those girls do these days. No on the back, though. Yeah, they got can't even
beat it from the back because it's got hair. Every girl in America now has
twice as much armpit hair as me and intersecting unibrow, one going this way,
one going down their face. They have sideburns, they have mustaches, they have
hair on their back in places that only dad should have it. Hair on their fingers.
Hair on their, yeah, they have hairy knuckles. It's like girl, girl, it's like
Girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl,
girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl, girl,
we can actually do a perfect vertical. I'm not going to tell you again. I'm not
going to say it. I'm not going to tell you. Boil your hair. You should be boiling your hair.
Boil your fucking hair. Boil that hair. You're combing your hair. You're brushing your hair.
You're washing your hair. What the hell are you doing? You're washing it in the hot water.
Not hot enough. Boil that shit. Boil that hair. Boil it! Put that pot on. Step backwards.
Go like that. Yep. Put all your hair in an eight quart pot. Boil it. I know you want to
make lobster later, but you can clean the pot. It's noodles girl, but you don't
know. Okay, next slide.
Ask him about his favorite thing about a woman, probably the pussy in the butt,
the boobs. Okay, I'm going to say the opposite. They're clothes
and their high heels and their makeup and their hair and their clothes and the
way that glasses, you know, where the clothes I have on yeah for me, it's
probably the eyes. Yeah and the teeth yeah. When they're around your cock,
oh my God, I love when the board job got a tooth in it. Yeah, I love when
she got that one to all right, long in the front.
Tell them about your plans. We did this kind of already to for today. We're
just talking about going to the roller coaster. I guess my plan is I'm going
to go home and then I'm going to go eat.
Yeah, we can I say one last thing that's explicit in nature. You have one more
explicit go ahead. Yeah.
I love when a girl got that one front tooth that's way too long
and she shaves your shit down like it's a baby carrot.
That's not how they shave baby carrots. They put them in a
tumbler. And she's doing this, she's going
That's a Bugs Bunny, another Bugs Bunny thing.
She looks like Bugs Bunny. You interrupted the plans to tell
that. You liked it.
I did because of the friendship relationship day, but I would be
getting you. You'd be getting me? Yeah, I'd be throating you right now.
You would, if you throat me, you better have that one long tooth in the front.
I don't want that. It doesn't exist. Absurdist humor, is that what we've
come down to?
I guess it does seem that way. We've never been absurd. We've been years of
this and now we're turning into absurdist nonsense, googly moogly. What
What the hell are you? I'll admit it. I've been on. We should go back to puns. I've been
on one today and I'm sorry and I miss you. I apologize before before a girl sucks my
dick. I make her hold a raw egg in her mouth to prove she can hold it without breaking it.
That's right. That's right. What's funny? Where's the pun in that? I'm just thinking
about things. I'm just thinking about sexual. I thought you were like teeing that up. And
and I'm like damn girl use eggs. Yeah, you know there we go and before I have
sex with
and before I have sex with a
woman, I have her
put a bag of flour in her
she can take care of it.
So it's really dry. Yeah, no, no,
so you can make yeah, don't do flour, do cat litter, absorbs it better. Okay, put
cat litter in a woman's ass
to
all the time. If you don't think about it, you don't think about it, but like, there's
a turd always in your butt. I don't have to shit, I can shit right now. You need a fire
hose strength bidet, I think, is what you need in your life. There's a turd in your
butt right now, just sitting there. Next slide. Converse about his career and yours. We all
have the same podcast. Actually, zoomies. Yeah, beers we drink. Beers we drink, yeah. And
and I'm going to be pretty soon a librarian. Yeah, you actually have to go
to school for that. Yeah, I'm getting my masters. You gotta go to school for
that. You have to get a degree in library science and then you have to take
an exam and then you have to bring that you have to say, and then you have to
stay active, pick up the book and put it back, keep your education active. You
have to go take, you have to like attend
like keynote speakers and stuff or else they take away your library credentials.
You spend all it is, all it is, is putting the book in and taking it out
for someone. No, these days, no, it's a lot. You may gotta make signs that say
all are welcome. That's what the job is these days.
That's not librarian. That should be the arts and crafts counselor.
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right. They trash your pussy up too and make it bad.
They trash it up. They junk it.
They put an Elmer's glue stick in it.
They make it terrible. Librarians used to be the top in the world for sex.
They used to be. Now it's real estate agents and stepmom.
Librarians used to be so sexy in the 80s.
It was sexy.
The lady from Ghostbusters?
that is literally on average the ugliest job in America is because they all went
in thinking this is gonna. I would rather have sex with the lunch lady,
but it's always librarian lunch. Like what?
Adam Sandler, I would rather have sex with a lunch lady from that from
prison.
She's a fine too. I think the reason I think I think the reason that librarians
got less hot is because since the 80s now we have homeless people. Yeah,
come into libraries and they I think maybe it's Ronald Reagan's fault. I
think that is the librarians they have don't even bother putting effort into
their appearance because they're like I'm going to walk in. I'm going to be
next to some guy who's wearing a tunic anyway. Exactly. You used to walk into
the library and right there in front of you Marilyn Monroe. Pretty much. Yeah.
Nowadays you walk in the library a book about Marilyn Monroe. A scary weirdo.
And a woman hiding behind it. And a woman hiding behind the book because guess
That's what you walked into the library with six guns again.
I think Ghostbusters ruined it by scaring everyone who was going to be a librarian.
They did.
I used to be able to walk in and start immediately chatting up the lady behind the library lady.
Now you go up and say, "Excuse me, little guy.
Are you looking for your parents?"
Because they all look like Damien from The Omen.
Number 25, don't forget social media.
You definitely want to know his social media behavior.
Some of the great conversation stars for this topic are which social media
platforms he is active on which one does he prefer the most? What is so likeable
about imagine you go on the most amazing day ever right like like a guy has taken
it me. Imagine I'm taking you out. We have an amazing time. It's like maybe
where we go set it up. We're going we'll go to it's mostly a walk and maybe we do
an activity. Maybe we make a terrarium together and then I make I make dinner at
my place, but we're not going to have sex or whatever, but at the end it's your
first time meeting me at the end, you're like, let me get your Instagram. You just
made me imagine all that. I was close to hands free nutting and he's like, I don't
use Instagram. He's like, oh, I'll here, I'll just follow you. Okay, cool. You go
to the bathroom, freshen up, maybe you're gonna have sex, ding, followed by funny
hood clips.
What do you do?
Well, I mean, it shows that
million followers. Well, first of all, it shows I'm giving it up because he's
clouded.
Of course, that's what I'm saying. You have to, it shows that he maybe I could
make an account called Mrs Funny Hood Clips and I could get maybe three to
four million followers. Funny Hood Clips, just being associated with it. Fifth
account, follow the YouTube, back up. I could run his back up account in case he
gets banned for posting something with blood in it, that he really shouldn't be
posting on Instagram. No, no, no, no. And you're like, how did you even get this
video? Yeah. What is this? It says, this video has never been posted anywhere
else on the internet. It's fucking Funky Town.
And you're just like, "Alright, I guess it's a funny hood clip, I don't know."
Yeah, funny hood clips and it's all just other women who kind of look a little
bit like you. Yeah. Being the victim of CCTV crimes on the same block.
What if you... Okay, now what about this? Now look at nowadays, what about
something like this. You say, okay, let me follow you on Instagram. He says, oh, I
don't use Instagram. You're like, okay, what can I follow you on? And he says,
here's the QR code to my Etsy store. Damn, I would say he makes earrings out
of clay. I don't have Instagram. I do like this one. I still have vine.
He's on Google+. It never left my phone.
Yeah, you can follow me on Google Buzz. Okay, next.
Religion and faith. While imagining your future with somebody, you will want them
to share the same beliefs as you. Here comes the knowledge about his
religious beliefs. You will like to know if the person you are talking to
believes in God or not. If he does, does he spend much time worshipping God?
Discuss if he thinks all religions are similar. Try to know what he has to say
regarding communal problems. Don't get into a debate. Try to keep it subtle.
Every religion doesn't even have one single fucking thing in common. No,
they're completely different. Probably chains. And I'm bloody agnostic.
probably a chain slash mindful slash head. Although I think I will I do think
most religions, I think are unique and and and beautiful and all and all this
type of thing, but I think that I've noticed a lot of similarities between
Buddhism and Satanism.
I got I got I got there both pure evil. Definitely. I got turned to be high
because of Dwight Schrute. Yeah, yeah.
I got turned to Shinto because I like the word Shinto. Yeah, I honestly thought
that was food until right now. Me too. You know what it was? You're thinking shishito
peppers. I'm thinking a bento box. Well guess what's in my bento box? I barely have room
for one language. I'm actually going to be the first ever guy to be into Norse mythology
and believe in Viking gods and not be racist. I'm going to make it woke. I'm going to
woke-ify the white nationalist religion. You will do it for two weeks and then you will
be on fire. You do it, you're going to try and woke up by the white nationalist. I'm
going to turn them. I'm going to set them right. You're going to make like they are
like Filipino or something and someone's going to fire. You know, there is evidence
that Thor was Filipino. I see. That's a sad thing. I think that probably is the one true
religion is that Thor does exist. Yeah. Why would we have lightning? Exactly. You know
that most of those guys just got it all. They got it all twisted. You know, it's crazy about
that stuff is they most of that is just they never wrote it down and then all
the Christian people came and just made like changed everything so we don't know
what any of the original stuff was it's all just Thor might have been for a
little bit look like Juvia he could be Thor what if all the north stuff that
wasn't written down just said like be excellent my dudes yeah I think
basically well it did that's my theory be excellent my dude what if it just
said that be tough I'm gonna be the first atheist to go to heaven yeah cuz
because you final moment you're like no, just kidding. No, no, I will be so I
think Stephen Hawking already went to heaven. Yeah, he was an atheist. Well,
he went there built a machine to tell him what himself
they're like. I don't know what to do with you. Now you didn't put it back in
hell. I just teleport right back. He didn't believe in any of that atheist
crap. That was just his computer talking for him. Yeah, he literally was like
he was trying to type it. I believe in God. I love the science is heresy. What
yeah, what the all this stuff that I have quote unquote discovered as we're
trying to miss leave you into darkness and the computers like translating
translating. I love science. God is not real.
I am a heathen and proud of it yeah and he didn't cheat either. By the way, I
love the computer. That was the computer to yeah, the
hey baby yeah, he's not responsible. Do you want to fuck this guy? I mean me
fuck this going
No, no, no, all right, what's next here? Try to dig deep and discuss fears
while you enjoy talking. Take a sneak peek into the person's darker version.
Once he is comfortable with you, ask him if he has any phobias. What I know his
phobia is shouting
not my phobia. You have a shouting. I don't I don't like I'm
I have
got me. So you have a phobia.
I've gotten over that, but I have a phobia. I got scared of it
two nights ago. I have a phobia of marijuana. Yeah, me too. Yeah, I got
close. I came close to sinning. I didn't even it came out the other night at the
it was I know I was standing in a circle and next thing I knew it was next to me.
I didn't believe I didn't even Caleb Jubilee at the shindig. I didn't even
know it was there until I turned it's right next to me. The smoke is puffing
out. I'm thinking to myself, you know, I could yeah, what's going to happen bro.
If I ever took a hit of weed, it would be such a problem. It'd be so like if
we're all hanging out, somebody passed me a joint and I think, "This will be funny."
I remember when you used to smoke weed all the time.
Dude, that was the thing.
I used to smoke weed constantly.
You'd come to my house and it would literally look like a movie version of what a stoner
does.
You'd come to my house, there'd be chips everywhere, multiple bags, and I'd just be playing the
Switch on my TV.
I think that was basically every day until your most recent apartment also.
It's true.
Yeah, I didn't smoke the thing the thing for me that the reason that the thing
that stopped me from doing it in that big circle of people is I was saying
like so I haven't smoked weed in like two years right, but also I haven't
smoked weed around another human being and probably like four years. Yeah,
no, that's not there's no area. There's no green. Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god.
One time he smoked weed and he turned completely green. Yeah, he greened out.
I let my power show it was
It was actually the craziest thing I've ever seen.
Was that in college?
Yeah.
I've never seen somebody turn green.
I was there.
That was the night I drank 30 beers.
That was one of the first times that I hung out with that group of people too.
Yeah, at my apartment.
Yeah.
You turn green and then you sat down for a little while.
Basically passed out.
And then you were fine.
That was the night, it was like the first couple of weeks that I had known you guys
and I showed up with a 30 rack and drank like 15 of them.
I think it was the medicine I was on.
Oh yeah, this is, these are all here to share.
You were on a greener.
I was on a greener.
Yeah.
Was the pill green?
I showed my power, though it really scared me. All right, although you all
don't know I'm a hero called the chameleon, you
the comedian you're making me laugh with that shit and we go right to
trigger funny conversations, which we have covered thanks to me,
but we don't have to do this one. Let's go to the next one, because we do have
this unlock and this is the last one. Don't demand extravagant things like a
like and that is a picture of a car. Can I just have a napkin? Don't demand
extravagant things. Patrick, you need to chill. I thought that was a demanding
extravagant. No, okay, then can I have a tissue paper from that's even more
extravagant from a present? I don't know. Can you? May I please have a diamond
hanky? I don't know. May you
a diamond hanky? What's a hanky made of diamonds? Chain mail, mithril, mithril,
Mithril. Gilded Mithril. Mithril Henke. They don't gild Mithril. In RuneScape they do. They
do? Yeah. That's bullshit. Mithril and Adamant. He's adamant that they don't do that. They
gild it, you put a trim. That's dumb. You a bitch. If we were in the dueling arena I
would beat the shit out of you right now. You would not beat the shit out of your friend.
Good luck beating the shit out of the chameleon. I've been crawling up the wall, changing the
the color of the wall. Look at how sticky his hand is. I will eat Mo. Don't eat Mo. He's
just ruined his thing. Don't eat Mo. Did you keep his nuts? No, I wish. That would have
been funny. You didn't? You really should have. You should have eaten him. That would
have been funny. I would have loved to have had him sat down and just eaten him. Yeah,
Mo's nuts in a jar right there, that would have been funny. That is not funny. That is
gruesome. It would have been funny if we did an episode where we were scientists. How do
How do you not think of that stuff?
Because I'm an artist, not a scientist.
Yeah, but scientists...
I can make art out of anything.
Artists can parody scientists.
He's going to poke it through the bottom.
Coffee pop.
You're an inventor, not an artist.
That's an invention, you idiot.
Oh, god damn it, it's science!
Fuck, no!
Don't throw that at Cameron.
You squirted him.
Look at him, he's rubbed a squirt off.
My shirt turned orange and brown.
And my hat turned completely brown with coffee.
I'm not always in.
again. This is all white brown. Look at the splotch you made this black splotch
of coffee. Pop was coffee. Pop coffee. Pop coffee. Pop flop coffee. Pop was not
a flop. Coffee pop was a flop. Oh, the bus is here. The bus is here. We gotta
go.
Bye guys. Get the hell out of here. Oh wait. Do we promote that? No, we don't
have that. Okay, whatever
I could go into his room. You could go through. I just had the most incredible
vision of Patrick in like 10 years from now, teaching like an English 101 course.
Like a 200 person public university English class and how amazing your lectures would be.
Yeah. You'd be teaching them funny words. I'd be teaching them how to talk in a style that is...
What books would you put on the curriculum?
I know what your first slide would be. A screenshot of a drill tweet.
Study this.
A lot of people would say this isn't English.
This class is about the study of brevity.
This is a text.
You would say that.
Say this is text.
Yeah.
This is text.
This is photos.
Yeah, teaching an English class and showing photos.
This is a photo.
Photos.
Learn how to look at these.
You think that texts, look at this line of text.
Thinking that they don't know.
Look at this line of text.
Six words.
Look at this photo that accompanies it.
One thousand and six words.
You would be such an amazing teacher.
I wish there was more professors like you in this world.
I'd be such a good teacher for people with adult ADHD.
No, normal people.
Normal people?
Good people?
Completely normal people.
I could teach the syllabus one line.
I wish I could...
Fuck it.
Fuck the bullshit.
I wish I could go back in time and make you older than me.
I want to look up to you so bad.
I want to look up to you in every way.
And I want you to teach me everything that you've ever learned.
I showed him my penis and now he's being very kind to me.
And I want to look up at it.
I see you different being very, very yeah. I think you don't realize, but you
completely changed your relationship with us forever. I looked at the cock
through the cracks in your fingers and now I can't poetry. Oh my God, the
English teacher,
I brought that down to the cracks in your fingers.
The most incredible line of poetry I've ever heard someone say say it one more
time. I peered at your cock through the cracks in your fingers.
I could listen to that forever.
Keep going.
And what I've seen cannot be undone.