You're a real puppy dog.
- Hey, who you calling puppy dog over here?
I'm a big dog.
I'm a full grown adult.
- Wow, what a terrific audience.
(audience applauding)
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Hello everybody and welcome to the open mic.
Your first comedian is Caleb Pitts.
- Woo!
Hey guys, what's up everybody? Okay, I'm 15 years old and I'm fucking clueless.
Pretty much the title LMFAO. I have no idea if these jokes are appropriate for
my first open mic. Criticism not just welcomed but invited. I'm looking to
improve, not impress TBH. Here are my jokes. Teenage activists, you know them,
always parading their views about issues such as climate change and LGBT rights.
They love saying that they want their voice to be heard. I understand their
point completely. It can be hard to speak very loud when I'm throttling them to
death for being annoying cunts. As I'm sure you can tell, I'm extremely new to
new to performing comedy. Well, to be fair, I'm pretty new to living at the
age of fifteen.
That's beside the point. All I ask of you is, please, can I have no heckling
or jeering throughout this set? And in the words of my maths teacher, please
don't make me run out the room crying with six flesh wounds this time.
I believe that TikTok and other apps that give you instant gratification in
short burts are ruining my generation's attention span. It's gotten so bad that
they can't go five minutes without losing interest
stairs out into the distance. Oh wow, that was pretty good. Yeah, wow, I kind
of like that one. That one gets a wow from us.
Have you ever stopped to think why exactly my generation is called generation
Z?
I'm starting to think it might be because they saw us with our tick tock and our
pronouns and thought this is it end of the line for humanity. Let's get to Z
the end of the alphabet.
I've been told by many people from the older generation that all the rap music
I listen to sounds the same. I'm assuming this is because without their
hearing aids, everything sounds silent.
No, you can't boo me. You cannot boo me. Okay.
I take the bus to school every day. I don't know what it used to be like,
but these days every single person on the bus is looking on their phone.
Well,
that stopped last week when the bus driver has drove us off a cliff after being
distracted on Instagram. Okay.
The dog is talking to the microphone.
He keeps growling too. I live in an extremely small village
where things are quiet. Yeah, I was living in extremely small village. Yeah,
I live in an extremely small village where things are quiet and I mean
literally quiet. There's barely any sound
loudest thing I hear daily is the tweeting of birds, the gentle breeze and
the distant shotguns of people killing themselves in the background.
I find these funny, but my sense of humor is kind of retarded. So again,
feedback, please.
So I want feedback on my jokes. I'm fifteen. This is my first time doing
this. Okay, can you read
can you read that one about the village again? I live in an extremely small
village
where things are quiet and I mean literally quiet.
There's barely any sound. The loudest thing I hear daily is the tweeting of
birds, the gentle breeze and distant shotguns of people killing themselves in
sorry. I said in the background. It's in boredom in boredom in board because
it's so quiet.
So just real quick ratings ratings on that set. I like the when you said the
flesh wounds joke that was good. That was good. It's kind of a brick. This
six is probably British. Yeah. Oh yeah. He lives in a village. Yeah. He's
either British or Romanian. Oh
I thought that the jokes maybe lacked a little bit of perspective. Okay. I don't
exactly know anything more about you other than the fact that you're
fifteen years old. Well, I'll tell you this is my first stand up comedy bit
feedback would be much appreciated two different kinds of shit. I'm sixteen
now and I have wanted to be a comedian for ages. This is just my first attempt
at a bit and I'm going to take them. I'm going to get real comfortable on this
one. Yeah, Mike out of the stand. This is just my first attempt at a bit judge
harshly do what you have to do. I want to improve okay. So here's my new my
new bit now that I'm a year older, a year, wise years past. This is my new
bit.
I know shit and poop are the same thing,
but there is a distinct different between a shit and a poop poop is a
little glop yeah, a glop just a boot
just drops take diaper off. No mess. A shiver is a shit. A shit is the
fucking mess that seems to spread like a viral disease. It spreads like it's got
half a brain to go somewhere and has a cab to catch. It starts by the shitter
and ends up in your kid's hair, probably in his mouth. If you're a shit parent,
always in their mouths, kids won't take food made for eating, but give them some
shit and ten seconds flat, it'll be in their mouth. If not in their mouths, then
in your mouth. So that's my shit versus. I think that that shit versus poop that
it's going somewhere very good yeah yeah. It's on its way versus poop yeah is
really good. Are you getting there versus I think a year has definitely made you
yeah smarter, stronger, what happens when you're seventeen? Well, let's see
because now I'm seventeen okay, okay,
and I just did my first open mic
and I totally bomb.
I don't have a video, but here are some of my jokes. Tell me what you think
and feel free to steal them. Number one, I was with a friend at a party the
the other day and notice someone dropped something into her drink. I rushed over
and tried to stop her from drinking it, but I was too late and she passed out.
Now, like the good friend, I am. I sat next to her the entire night and made
sure no one touched her while I had sex with her
Jesus
at the bar or the party. I think I was at a part yet in the middle of party.
Yeah, okay, just you know yeah
yeah, it's all number to joke, but rape isn't funny. That's why we have rape
whistles
because it's not funny,
an incredible invention that has saved millions of girls from getting raped
each year. Extremely effective. That's why I like to take my dates to sporting
events.
Oh, you're a rapist, you're you rape. It's kind of guys. I'm kind of doing
Anthony Jessel Nick thing. I have the suit on. It's kind of dark humor. Okay,
I'm only really preferences old like warning yeah or anything. Well, I did
kind of say that I had a kind of a our worded sense of humor. That's true
number three. I hate living with roommates because we get into fights all
the time over the littlest things like the other day. My roommate caught me
eating his food and got mad at me. So in retaliation, he broke one of my DVDs. I
was mad at first until I realized the joke was on him. It was his sister's DVD.
yeah. She let me borrow it after I fucked
okay
number four. Okay, so this is two. This is a two part question. Oh, okay, male
athletes are scumbags. They have sex with hundreds of women and have dozens of
kids that they never take care of. You never hear about that with women
athletes. I think that's because women, unlike men, actually have responsibility
and take care of their kids by having an abortion.
I think the face there is really good. The face is pulling a little. I do all
that yeah say that say that joke again, but like mug the whole time mug the
whole time and then once you hit the punch line, I want you to basically just
like look into the look right into the camera. Okay,
male athletes are scumbags. They have sex with hundreds of women and have
dozens of kids that they never take care of. You never hear about that with
women athletes. I think that's because women, unlike men, actually have
responsibility and take care of their kids by having an abortion.
That's amazing that better yeah, that's really it's hard for women athletes to
have an abortion, though, because they're always in the public eye and millions of
girls look up to them as role models. Plus, they practice running up and down
stairs every day. Just try pushing them down one flight of them damn nearly
impossible.
so you hit the woo button on that. Wait, say that again. Guys, I have always
thought titles were weird. I feel like you have to be proficient in something
to call yourself it. Like I've played music most of my life, so I would call
myself a musician. I'm a student, a programmer, a registered sex offender
required to by law to tell you I'm moving into your neighbourhood.
So I made two edits to my post. Number one was grammar and number two was
thanks everyone for the feedback. I like offensive jokes just because I want
people to realize how stupid it is to get offended at certain things. It's
just jokes, but I realize I'm not as good as a writer as Jessel Nick or car.
That's Jimmy car yeah, so it may just come off as crude to be crude. I guess
I'll try to stick to this safe stuff for now.
I have an example of safe stuff. Safe stuff would be probably a not you do a
safe joke right now.
Yeah, sure
I think Hannibal Lecter got humans and Lay's potato chips mixed up.
Okay, that'll be, I'll be back later.
Give it up, everybody. Who's next? I can go next.
Our next comedian is going to be, he's very, very funny. Please give it up for Cameron Fetter, ladies and gentlemen.
Keep it going for Cameron. Wow, look at him. How's it going? Everybody good man.
Crazy show so far, huh? Zoom the camera.
Let's see here. So I got to remember what I'm doing. You know, as a stand up
or sometimes you'd get all your jokes mixed up. Sure, everybody knows now it
doesn't happen to me really. My wife
is a big fan of grape jam.
I'm not a fan myself, but it's better than banana jam didn't sit right for a
week after that horror.
What is banana jam? The other day, my Spotify started playing music in my
pocket. It was MC Hammers, You Can't Touch This. That song is so good, I
couldn't help but dance to it. I even got passerbys involved in everything.
It was great.
The people at my grandma's funeral were not happy.
You were dancing at your grandmother's fucking funeral? To Spotify from my
pocket. To Spotify from the pocket, yeah. Pocket Spotify at my grandma's funeral.
but you said you got people to dance with you, so it seems like they were
oh okay at the people were walking by the funeral yeah. There was an outside
funeral. Okay, the hardest part about the gym is hunger yeah. It very hard to
lose weight when you eat all the time pulls out a snickers
Guys, I have a 35-year-old friend who argues that he's not a millennial.
I read in a blog that said, "I'm a Xennial."
It's the term for someone born in the late '80s who doesn't identify as a millennial.
Which is the most millennial sentence ever spoken?
Anybody?
Vince Young retired from football today.
In other news, as of yesterday, Vince Young was still considered a football player.
Damn.
who
Christianity explains a lot. It explains why I get sexually aroused by barbecue
three
read Genesis women evolved from ribs. That's where they get those thick meaty
curves.
barbecue sauce makes an amazing lube in the bedroom to my GF never lets me use
it like that, but occasionally she will get me off with a dry rub.
That's pretty good, but we can't use BBQ sauce. No, it hurt. I saw you on salt
all over your cock and cayenne pepper. Democrats are now considering allowing
prayer back in schools after discovering recently that prayers work.
recently prayers were discovered that they work by Democrats
a couple months back. I discovered a secret setting on our shower head and
promptly used it to clean my nether region, causing me to accidentally shit
the tub.
Since then, I've been accidentally shitting the tub every day.
I have a question on that yeah. What so you you washed your my third reason
balls. I think it means, but
another reason is your penis and your balls. Well, I guess it's including the
but because how did it make him shit the toe? That's what I'm that's my
question, but also why would washing your ass make you shit? Well, that's the
maybe it was so clogged that he got the he was like pulling up like a cork out
yeah cork of shit. Oh, well, I don't forget it's a secret setting yeah as
also you don't know. He was do it was like douching his as it must have been
with the shower head and then it
made him a minute unplugged. All the sorry, where I get healthy. I make my
own mayonnaise
gotta beat the hell out of eggs and oil. It's not hard, though. See it uses the
same muscles as masturbating no, which is what you do when girls find out you
I can't afford mayonnaise. It's a viscous cycle. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
a viscous cycle. That's pretty good man. I recently ripped my pants for the
fifth time this year. I am to pants as Hulk Hogan is to t shirts.
I rip pants off my body.
When I liked and became a fan of all those stupid spam pages two years ago, I
had no idea my news feed would become a breeding ground for misused memes,
screenshots from Tumblr, poorly photoshopped pictures of Obama, and misquoted sayings over
a picture of space.
Sad news.
The British simile champion has died.
We shall not see his like again.
You shall not see his like again.
Okay, here's some that I need feedback on.
Okay.
All right.
Tell me what you think of these jokes.
Please be honest.
I'm going to keep this short and sweet.
The second season of Stranger Things was released on Netflix last week.
The show's entire young cast is back for another season.
They've all aged horribly.
This cast has aged so poorly that even Kevin Spacey doesn't believe any of them are 14 years old.
[laughter]
Netflix cancelled House of Cards amid the allegations made against Kevin Spacey.
Kevin's accuser has alleged that he's seen people laugh at Spacey's Johnny Carson impression
and he knows others that have managed to stay awake through an entire episode of
house of cards.
Damn, that's like a late night joke. Oh wait. You want feedback on these
individuals on this? I would say the worst part about these two is that it
feels like they're pretty old. Yeah, yeah, maybe this will this this might
address. What do you mean? Okay,
like I think we're there about a five or no, I have one for this hold on about
age. Yeah, Kevin Spacey and
celebrated her seven twenty second year old birthday. It was a small affair of
forty nine people and Caitlyn Jenner.
Kendall's sisters, Chloe and Kylie, were unable to attend the party due to both
being pregnant. Despite of this, the sisters, baby daddies, OJ Simpson and
Lucifer, attended the affair. Oh damn, both were pictured together drinking
margaritas and casually laughing while reminiscing about a deal. The two struck
together twenty two years ago. See that one's also about age. See okay, this one's
thought about it. That's okay. That's my it's not you're misunderstanding my
problem. I don't care about if the joke has age in it. The iPhone ten is I
don't that's not
next month. The eighth star wars will be released.
The results twice in eight weeks, people from around the world will wait on
massive lines to consume the newest version of the exact same product that
they've owned for years.
That one I like yeah yeah people not about age yeah, I like that one yeah
Okay, that's the end of the feedback part.
Okay.
Blue No Matter Who is a good slogan for Democratic voters, but it's a terrible slogan for lifeguards.
That one's pretty good.
That's kind of fun.
That one's actually pretty good.
Sorry, you said feedback's over.
Yeah, there's no feedback on that one.
Am I the only one that finds it frustrating that every time you go home and try to sit
down and watch the news Huey Lewis is singing over them?
I actually kind of like that one.
That one's good too.
I was a little funny. Okay, okay, I think we should ban abortion and then raise
those babies as our military. Send them over twenty years later, the mother gets
a telegram, I guess a telegram
in twenty years. I go back to telegrams.
The mother gets a telegram. Remember that abortion you wanted done. Damn
okay, that's fire yeah.
I want to open a store like Build-A-Bear, but with shirts. I'll call it Get Your
Shirt Together. Okay, well, real quickly, can you walk me through what that would
look like? Yeah, so you'd pick a shirt, but like Build-A-Bear, you put the- Are
you going to put the sleeves on the shirt? Are you- Yeah, so and then you- It's
not just you don't just put something on the front of the shirt. There you have
it. You pick the color of the shirt. Yeah, and you can decide whether or not it
has sleeves. You can go tank top or- I think you just- Sleeveless shirt. You
but it'll be called get your shirt together. Yeah, because I mean the name
to do one long, a place about name one short sleeve or buttons. You can pick
buttons if it's button down yeah, okay, anyway, I want to go as a vice
journalist for Halloween. Does anyone have a trust fund I can borrow
I just went bankrupt to heater heater from from Cameron? I'm so fat and my
boobs are so big.
If I were a t shirt with writing, people actually have to move their heads to
reread it. Holy Shit Damn, I always check IMDB before saying
I always check IMDB before saying Disney and Nickelodeon actresses are hot just
to make sure I am not a pervert.
This guy's a lot of Disney and Nickelodeon
good news. I just signed a deal with Disney. The deal is I have to stay fifty
fade away at all times from Disney from Disney. I guess from Disney World,
you know, just as Disney, the kind of the yes, it is a company office. I
guess, oh, that's fine. What does depression feel like put on a denim
suit, then swim a few laps?
Wow, that one I could see kind of on a kind of white text on like a it is
white text really yeah on like a gray photo background. No, it's on a stand
up shot. Oh, my shit.
I saw this little kid wearing a t shirt that said Pugs, not drugs. When are
those the options? I've never met a dealer who was like hey want some
cocaine or a great Dane
rhyming punch line joke yeah anyway, any cord cutters here, yes, yes, I've
fully cut the cord so gross all that amniotic fluid spraying everywhere. Are
those scissors even clean? Oh God, I'm not that kind of cord cutter yeah.
Oh, you fell for my joke.
Tricked you.
Saw a fat guy in a Captain America shirt
breathing with his mouth open.
He may not be Captain America, but he is America.
- Wow.
- If men are turned on by wet t-shirt contests,
then why aren't women attracted to men who pee their pants?
Tired of double standards.
- Thank you.
- If you're going to wear a wife beater t-shirt,
you should at least look like you could beat up your wife.
Look at this.
- That is a good one.
Wow, all right, you're lighting me. Okay, I'm going to go ten minutes.
Sorry, so it's cool to talk about your vintage car, bust out your old record
player, but the moment I mentioned my chamber pot dot dot dot that one's
pretty funny. Okay, we're going to go through these quickly living in
Williamsburg. I can never tell if someone riding a horse is part of the
colonial ambiance or someone saving gas money.
I trombone you.
I gave you a trombone. My friend is in the hospital after breathing in toxic
fibers from the ceiling of his house. The doctors are doing asbestos. They can
would you make that joke like in the hospital? I don't think so. Well, I'm
not in a hospital. Would you make that? I think a doctor would like to this kind
of my friend got fired from her last job in retaliation for being a whistle
blower. She was discovered by the CEO's wife, Mrs. Whistle.
He's blowing
his wife.
he's blowing his wife. I spent most of my 20s in a cult like a full-blown shave
your head and leave your family to live on a compound kind of cult. It got pretty
wild. They put stuff in our food to stop us from getting horny and they made us
all dress the same and sing songs about our leader every morning. You've
probably seen them in your town trying to get more people to join. Yeah, you
might remember them. You might remember seeing them on the news when our leader
told us to kill Osama bin Laden.
So think about that one for a second. Yeah, that's think about it.
political. I'm going to do I okay, I'm just going to skip to the last one here.
I believe that Amber Heard's career is over, though. I've heard rumors,
though. I've heard rumors that Amber might do Aquaman porn spoof for the rest
of her life, but she'll never get to fuck Aquaman. Instead, Amber Heard fucks
the giant octopus monster and an octopus has eight tentacles. She gets three
tentacles fucking her mouth, three tentacles, fucking her pussy and two
tentacles holding a phone live streaming all this and when the octopus finally
climaxes, it busts its nasty sticky gooey ink all over her face. I think that
would be the only time that people could actually believe that Amber heard
received a black eye. Holy shit and that and that's what you didn't want. You
didn't want feedback on that one. No, that one's fully formed. Okay, I know. I
think that was perfect. All right, next up to the stage. Thank you for your time,
everybody. Next up we got Patrick Doran.
Yes.
Okay, we're losing some audience members.
Yeah, you got a little hot here with that Amber Heard joke, huh? Couldn't handle that.
Bye bye, you triggered asshats. Bye bye, SJWs.
I have some actual I've actually some
some poems that I'd like to read. Okay, fuck you.
No, it's okay. They're comedic in nature. It's called an open mic. Okay,
well I'm gonna... Hold on, I gotta hang that back up. This one is called
Dude Bro. Okay. And it's a haiku.
The dude is a bro. Can you count them out while you do it,
like a haiku? Count out the syllable? The dude is a bro.
Bro like dude, broski brother.
here. Dude bro like yeah man. I like that you counted five for each of them. This
one is called No Milk. Okay. Man buys cow, no milk. Whore in street demands
money. Masturbates to porn. Wait, say it again slowly. Man buys cow, no milk.
Okay. Whore in street demands money. Masturbates to porn. Oh, I think I get
it. These are some some haikus another haiku. Okay,
it's called no simping. Okay,
X miss is here soon. She is looking for that simp clause, no simping on X miss
simp clause like Santa. Yeah, like Santa, which hold on. Let me get the companion
poem here.
Simpa Claus.
Wait, Simpa Claus?
Wait, who is this?
Once upon a time lived a man who would simp for any women in sight.
Still stuck in the fairy tale life, he became the White Knight.
Listening to his women, he did everything she asked.
Buying the kids Christmas presents, he became a money-making slave.
She would always tease him with sex and telling him to earn more money and learn to behave.
One day they got in a big fight, arguing over money and bills.
While he was at work, she was looking for a cheap thrill.
She cheated on him with the neighbor.
She was giving him head.
They went in the back of the house to fuck in the woodshed.
On Christmas day, he was heartbroken and she begged him for another chance.
The simp went for it and he started to do a funny dance.
Then one day she left him for another man when he was at rock bottom and broke.
She told him, "I just used you for Christmas. You're a low-life loser. You're a fucking joke."
Now all alone after losing his job, becoming too heartbroken to perform his work, he started
to watch men going their own way videos on YouTube. Then he changed into a red pill jerk.
The end.
Wow.
Who is the writer of the author?
These are all by Joe Fettig.
We've seen him before.
We've worked with him.
We've worked with him. I'm looking again at his work.
He's really amazing.
It's really amazing. You know how amazing he is? Let me read you this one.
I am going to fart in a jar and save it for later. Do you want to take a sniff?
I know you like smelling your own farts, so take a whiff.
Guys like to fart and girls weep.
I'm going to squeeze out a nasty fart. What a relief.
The stench fills the air. Oh my God. What is that smell?
rotten beef. No fart in a jar and save gas because the smell is starting to
linger. My last fart didn't make it in the jar, so smell my finger. Oh
open up that lady far. I got a smell. You couldn't make it to the maybe he
was opening the jar and he for his finger. Well, I was trying to get it
hard already. Yeah, I got on his finger. The fart got on his on his finger on
his finger. Okay, when he was trying to open the door, I got a smelly
surprise. The smell is so strong. It'll get you high. I'd smoke that. I got my
fart jar on me. Want to smell my toxic gas? It fills the air. Whoever smelt it
dealt it. Gotta be toxic warfare. What? Fart in a jar and share it with your
friends. I just ate some broccoli and cheese. It's time to colon cleans.
Okay.
'Cause it rhymes. Yeah.
Let me read this next one here. I got a bunch more, but how much time do I have?
You're I mean, you should wrap up pretty soon. Wrap up. OK. Yeah.
Fuck child support.
These modern women are using the court system to take advantage of men
and extorting their money.
The government needs to start tracking single mother spending habits.
That would be really funny.
Spending that child support money on nails and weaves,
hustling two to three baby daddies one at a time.
Holy. What a bunch of thieves.
Damn. She's trying to have her cake and eat it too.
She is done chasing the bad boys.
Now she wants a nice guy.
And that is you.
Me? You.
Me? Fuck child support.
Men are going their own way.
Now we can watch these angry feminists cry.
Society keeps saying they don't need men anymore
as they walk away from work and turn a blind eye.
More men are walking away from love and relationships,
taking the red pill, the downfall of society.
We are not going to be your slave or servant anymore living all alone, a
relief of anxiety. Fuck child support. I don't need no narcissistic bitch in my
life. You're not entitled to my love or my money. Fuck you, bitch. You'll never
be my wife. Fuck child support. I'm not gonna pay you, bitch. You still stunting
at the club.
Damn.
At the club.
Females having dual mating strategies and still they end up with a scrub.
Wow, those are some poems by Mr.
We got he has a new book coming out. What's it called called men guarding
their own wallets? Oh, wow, that is a book of poetry on Amazon. I will be
yeah.
Okay, I'll be down on that might be a ZW three. If it's on yeah, would you
mind introducing me? Because I yeah, I'm aging for stage time. I
you know, I want to welcome this next comedian to the stage. He's very,
very funny, but ladies and gentlemen, give it up for Caleb Bitts.
Yeah. Go Caleb. Go Caleb.
Wait, can you keep doing that dance? Huh? Can you keep doing that dance?
No. Uh oh, you're gonna have a bad set, Caleb. Pat's looking at the sound board.
Yeah, he's definitely gonna... Just leave it. It's fine. It's alright.
Guys, I have been writing jokes for about a year now, and I think it's time I finally attempt
to put it to use on stage. However, I have two main problems. One, I am only 17, not
sure if underage is okay. Two, I do not know which route to take. Short one-liners, dirty/crude
humor, long story-esque jokes. Below are some of the many jokes I have written, and I was
wondering what you guys thought of them. If they would fare well to audiences, any famous
these comedians I might possibly remind you of etcetera. Honestly would be the
most important. I would rather be shit on here than boot of stage IRL. Thanks
you said Joe Rogan yeah
here's some examples of some of my jokes. I majored in ornithology for the
chicks. Oh, you don't get that that joke. You should probably brush up on your
zoology knowledge. Wait that means you're a pedophile
does that I think
the drive right nope no no no no no no no
I'm only seventeen. The drive through at McDonald's must be a lot more expensive.
If you take the concept literally,
if you crash your car
into the front of a McDonald's and you just kill people and you break
everything, yeah, it will be more than a hamburger.
cost a pretty penny. I question God for one reason. He made potato chips the
best food to eat while watching TV and movies, yet made it impossible to eat
them quietly. Oh, I've tried, let me tell you. Sir, can you go off your phone?
Sorry. What are you doing?
Something really bad just happened. Something really bad? Yeah. Okay.
Oh, I've tried, let me tell you. I have tried. It's ridiculous. Most foods eat
slower equals less noise. Nope, not for chips. Same noise level and you just
look like a moron eating them one at a time and acting all sneaky about it.
Okay, I'll admit this next one is fucked up, but hopefully funny nonetheless.
Okay.
My girlfriend cheated on me and to get back at her, I hooked up with her
younger sister. You would not believe how easy it is to get a 13 year old to
put out these days. Not really though, I'm just not suave enough to do that.
I have no clue how any guy can do that successfully. Instead, I did the next
best thing, found her sister on Facebook and jerked off to pictures of her.
(Applause)
Yep, that's where I'm at right now. Room of complete strangers who now
undoubtedly think I am creepy as shit.
What are you playing?
I'm playing the applause, but I didn't know that the applause was long.
Okay, I need more feedback on some jokes. Here are some jokes I wrote.
Please let me know what you think of them. They might be considered a little
unusual.
If rain is God crying, then please explain to me why there hasn't been at
least one major cum storm
snow, snow.
If you could go into you could go into snow. I unfortunately lost my mom a
year ago
and I haven't been able to find that bitch since
yeah, that one's good. That's a one that email Phillips yeah, where my mom at
where my mom at yeah say that again and then add where my mom at okay. I
unfortunately lost my mom a year ago and I haven't been able to find that bitch
since
there are a bunch of new gender words that you're expected to know the meaning
of like gender fluid, gender fluid, not to confuse with gender fluid because God
damn don't drink that shit.
Oh, that one's good. That is pretty good. The where's Waldo books are a lot less
fun when you learn that the reason you're looking for Waldo is because he's
why he's wanted he's basically wanted to breathe was going to blow up a mosque.
Is that true?
That's why you're looking for Waldo.
I never knew that it's right here. I don't know what to tell you. That's
crazy yeah okay, don't get into one of those clown cars guys. I know you've
been everybody's been walking around saying I want to get in a one car, but
don't get into them. Don't get guys. Don't conquer do not get into car. Do
not
want to know why okay, because the clowns have sex in the cars.
Okay, I'm getting ready for my first stand up gig and I'm looking for
feedback on my writing and potential bits okay. All right, no wait. Do I want
to do this one or
yeah, I'll do this one all right.
Thanks everyone for coming out to the opening. Oh yeah, okay, all right.
There's an ex post from our stand up. So here's the opening part of my set.
Thanks everyone for coming out to the opening show of my nobody knows who the
fuck I am tour.
It starts tonight here on this stage and it also ends tonight about four minutes
for now in the men's bathroom with me crying hysterically of embarrassment.
No, that second show is standing room only by the way, so tickets are going
fast
wife at home. This is my wife at home's part of my jokes. Can I give feedback
really quick on that? Yeah, maybe you could say instead of singing room only,
maybe say there are two seats, yeah, and then it's going to be saying you're
only like maybe there's a toilets in the bathroom. There's two must be a dirty
shit and piss. There's two seats. Well, it's just does it's not standing
remotely. It's just the only room that has a prime. I don't want to talk
about toilets. There's two, there's two urinals and two urinals. I actually
don't have any aspirations of becoming a stand up comedian. However, I do
have three daughters under the age of six. So this is pretty much
the most stress free situation I could find on a Tuesday night. You have no
idea what my wife is going through right now, but it involves all of the
major bodily fluids, except the fun one that got us into this parenting mess in
the first place. So I'm up here and basically my wife's at home with my
three daughters and they're covered in piss and fucking spit and shit, but no
jizz at all and vomit. Is it because you're not there? If I was there to be
there, it is all over them. Yeah, I'd be jizz. You'd be that jizzing yeah.
should I attack that with that do it again do it again. Yeah, that's a no
idea what my wife is going through right now, but it involves all of the major
bodily fluids, except the fun one that got us into this parenting mess in the
first place. But if I was there, my wife and daughters, I'd be jizzing all over
the
better
trains is my train joke. All right, everyone's got one last weekend. We took
the kids to a miniature train ride in the park. They had set up these little
steam engines for the kids to sit on and ride around on little tracks. The best
is that a real conductor has to drive the train around at 4 miles per hour and they take their
jobs very seriously. As we were waiting in line, I overheard one of the conductors say
to the other, "These kids today, they don't know nothing about trains. It's a goddamn
disgrace." I thought to myself, "He's right." And maybe kids don't know nothing about trains
nowadays because trains are a 170-year-old technology. I hear there have been several
exciting inventions since Frontier America, some of them even involving electricity. And
and by the way, Mr surly train conductor, my kids will probably be zipping around
on a fucking jet pack in virtual reality multiverse. So the excitement of steam
locomotion might be lost on them.
Can I ask a question? Are you still seventeen?
I don't think he's seventeen. Yeah, I'm eighteen years old.
This is my bit about lying Chris
wait right already. I saw a my I saw a my good friend Chris from college the other
day for the first time in forever. Remember in college when there would be
so many people in your group of friends with the same name that you'd have to
assign them stereotypical adjectives. So everyone knew who you were talking about
we had like seven Chris's in our group of friends drunk Chris tall Chris dirty
Chris Pudwacker Chris. He was the one who got caught masturbating in the bushes
outside Katie Murphy's apartment.
Like I said, I saw lying Chris the other day for the first time since graduation
lucky guy. Apparently, he's won the lottery twice and now works as a
professional orgy coordinator in Hollywood. I'm so jealous.
You knew that many Chris's
five or six, I mean, five of them was a liar. There's a sexual assaulter guy.
One of them's dirty. Yeah.
Okay, dirty Chris.
New inspiring comic needs feedback on a comedy bit. Hello guys, new user here.
Doing stand-up is my dream, but I don't know if I got what it takes. I have a bit
here that I've been working on. Tell me what you think. Any feedback is welcome.
Okay, so this is very kind of written out word for word, okay?
Okay.
So last night, my fucking house reached a fucking new level of filth. I'm talking
about like type of filth they would use to air on Spike TV. Like yeah, the only
I would laugh when I watched Spike TV was during the fucking commercials. So anyways, my home is getting pretty messy cuz
My wife is out of town and I swear I have this condition that every time she leaves me alone for a couple days
I just fucking turn into a new Neanderthal
Like I'm just walking around my crib hunched over with just some fucking cheetah print underwear or I'll be eating KFC and I'll just be
Walking in my house devouring this chicken chewing with my mouth open looking like I fucking hunted this shit myself
I was dropping the fucking bones all over my nice Fendi rug
but that worst part is that I almost never wipe my ass when I'm in this
State of mind so yeah, I should probably get that checked out before it escalates to something
But yeah the house one of the first things to go missing when your house
Just looks like a straight mucky black oil spill on the Pacific Ocean
You know what I'm talking about when your home resembles the conditions of a third world country
Conditions one of the first things to go missing are either the spoons or the forks
Yep, these things escape like they believe they are the protagonist of a fucking James Bond movie
Someone call that James Bond or something right before he escapes from the bad guy
I swear
I've seen almost all the James Bond movies and this guy always does the simplest thing to escape when like not even Jesus Christ could fucking
Get off the cross more effortlessly than James Bond after he's been captured and let's be honest
What's more impressive escaping from technology made from 21st century special agents with cutting-edge technology or a fucking piece of wood?
wood and some rope with nails designed by people who thought the world was flat
and still shitted on the side of a road. Yeah, no brainer.
So I opened my utensil drawer looking for a spoon and I'm grabbing every fucking
utensil and it's anything but a spoon. God damn,
I was acting like a dumb ass fucking double checking, triple checking,
quadruple checking the same fucking spots in my cabinet.
Just hoping this shit magically appears like fucking Chris Angel in the mid
2000s. You guys remember Chris Angel?
And then I look at my sink and the sink legit looked like it threw up spoons.
like it was only just a shit ton of spoons, nothing else, not even a single
bowl. Yes, stores don't normally sell utensils individually. They almost always
sell some ridiculous high number. Like at night, I was at a store and I was just
looking at how many spoons were in the box, and I swear it seemed that they
just got one of those 20-year-old high school seniors and had him just pick how
many spoons should go in each box.
So that was my bit about my wife being in a town.
Wow, spoons and Neanderthals. And then I just have two more things, guys,
and I'll leave you with this. I started a Twitter account for I've been doing it
for six or seven years now, where I'm trying out basically my
stand up bits before I do them on stage. It's called @UpSandbox, it's the
stand up sandbox is what it is. I'm kind of in there playing around with my
joke. So just a couple of these.
I hear Starbucks... Sorry, I said Starbucks. You're thinking about sandboxes.
I hear Starbucks is in some hot water, just like their beans
and then this next one. This is my last one, San Francisco more like sans me
parenthesis. I do not live there.
Thank you guys. Thank you. Wow, your next comedian coming to the stage
is some poems. Huh, I'm gonna do poems next poet going to the stage, say poet.
Oh sorry, the next poet coming to the stage
marriage, the one and only Cameron Fetter
wow look at him look at him take the jacket off. I feel like you're entering
another level. Yeah, I did that just now. Holy shit, okay, hold on. Let me get my
I'm just going to do a few poems on a theme that's pretty near and dear to me.
This first poem is entitled "A Day of Reckoning" and I just want everybody to know in the audience
that we've been doing a lot of laughing and it's okay if you want to cry instead.
Yeah, all of my poems were supposed to make you cry or think.
So cry with laughter is fine or cry with sadness or fear.
Either one's fine.
but just don't be afraid to cry out of being afraid. Okay, a day of reckoning.
It was a day of reckoning.
No, or so it was said
it came from around me and into my head down from their website comes sounded
voice. It intrudes my surroundings. No rights of a choice. It's called voice to
skull simply put V2K hours of torture debilitates me that way. I lay in my bed
all tense and I shake. I don't know how much more of this I can take. The game
that is played on a computer screen, my body is scanned on the website it's
seen. They see what I see, they know every thought hidden in a cyber space,
not a force to be caught. A microchip in my back. No. Is there one in my head?
The ways it connects to replay what was said, my mind in the battle, the frequency that they
use, a game meant to destroy, torture, and abuse.
That's a day of reckoning.
Holy shit.
I'm going to go straight into the other two.
This one is called Cyber Science.
A microchip inserted underneath the skin while asleep on the couch, an intruder came in,
a website was started.
The present day, once the past, the torturous journey was going to last.
more intent to harm and cause to destroy the the voices that echo are meant to
annoy a sharp repeated tone that enters my mind words spoken clear come up from
behind the excuse and the lies to continue the plight. The website is
illegal that challenge a fight
the push of reverberation. I tense up and shake the horror that follow when I
need a break the saliva that flow as the magic in me never knowing just how the
the saliva that flow as the magic in me, never knowing just how my cough comes to
be into the unknown, hidden from sight in search of an answer when wrong is not
right. If only the secret I could come to know how does the fluid in my sinuses
flow
from a computer, the insolent grin and investigation, but where to begin pain in
my stomach and pain in my toes to cause me discomfort and clog up my nose. The
pressure is real. My foot hurts every day.
thank you
really the website that follow just hits me that way. Oh my God, Cyber Science is
stalking to put me to death a time of survival with hope in each breath and
here's the last one it's entitled a virtual reality attack. My body once
scanned into a virtual design, the images around me snipers formed in a
line. The walls took aim translucent each shot. One side was laughter. The
other side not. Distress as gruesome as blood curdling screams, the nightmare illusion,
the destroyer of dreams, the terror internal, the shock made me run, a virtual target of
the sharpshooter's gun. A specter led army, the dark shadow rose, hidden in the position
each presence imposed, to bludgeon the target as if it threw stone, unfocused from sight,
mind bruised and alone, a wound of defamation, the poison of choice, each glassy figure that
that shatter my voice trapped in the silence where I could not speak each
shot that impair made me feel weak shot. Notice that shot yeah, think about it.
I'm thinking and I sinister motives the assassin was sent fire and brimstone a
sting of torment. Even the arrows pinches the dart, the arrows pinches the
dart, the pain that was real brought fear to my heart. The emirates society
meets back to back no, but there is no running when VR attack wow
Wow! And that was three poems prepared for today. That's amazing. I'm sorry, this is
maybe a hard thing to follow here in terms of mood, but I'm going to bring up our next
poet. Our final poet, our final act. Our final act is Patrick Doran, everybody. Give it up!
Thank you, Cameron.
It is a hard act to follow, so I guess I'll just get right into it.
Replace her.
Sex on the first date.
Put out or get out of my way.
You can be replaced.
Damn.
Garden gnome farts aloud.
Air polluted, smell of shit, turd chasing midget dwarf.
What?
Wait.
There's a poem called Garden Gnome by Joe Fettig.
Maybe he
is a farting garden gnome. He's a farting garden gnome, yeah. That's kind of a
fun prank gift.
Women shame incels, not all men can be controlled. Lose weight, big fat whale.
Passport bros get hate, society doesn't understand until it's too late.
What's a passport bro? I think it's a man who does sex tourism.
Oh. Oh. Yeah. Okay. Interesting.
She wasted her youth chasing Chad ready to settle.
I don't like leftovers.
That was it? That's a haiku. These are haikus. Oh, okay. No,
they don't all seem like haikus. No. Yeah. Yeah.
Pay on the first date, split the bill. Equality, bitch.
You look like a man.
(laughing)
One red pill daily, not playing society's games.
My way, the highway.
Birth rates drop, marriage dead,
blaming men for the problems.
Agents of chaos panic.
The zoo hates men.
Get your passport, goes overseas.
society collapse. What is that? I have a question. What does that mean? I think
it has to do with passport bro stuff. What are passport? Okay, so you said
Chad earlier. Where do where is the what's the ranking? Basically, I think
Chad, there's men going their own way. There's passport bros. There's chads
virgins, maybe virgin versus itself, I think is a lot of what this is touching
coming upon yeah and you're a virgin
no, well, why are you in all your poems are about you fuck women and men going
my own way. It seems like more that anything you're kind of in the forest.
This will maybe this will
explain clear it up just a little bit. I'm just confused. Okay, this this will
have the mission statement in here. This is a poem called the problems in
western society. Okay,
There are many problems in Western society today.
Many Americans aren't ready for an economic collapse.
Censorship on the internet, no more freedom of speech.
We are all being wiretapped.
The homeless problem is getting worse.
Greedy corporations like BlackRock and Vanguard buying up homes, warfare on the people, the
world economic forum telling the people what we need in our lives, we refuse to take the
vaccine.
We are not sheeple.
Crooked politicians abusing the legal system, finding loopholes to make them rich, take them
them out of office. They don't care about us. Don't be there, bitch.
The nuclear family is destroyed. The feminist movement has gone too far.
Men are getting their passports and flying away.
The shaming language doesn't work anymore.
Prince Charming is not going to save you. That is the price you've got to pay.
Americans are so materialistic, living above their own standards,
just to drown in debt, a slave to the system.
What are we going to do when there are no internet?
Damn. I don't know.
Society doesn't care about men guilty until proven innocent.
The era of depression, society has become soft,
showing any signs of masculinity is known as aggression.
Suicides rates are up with gun violence
while the crooked politicians are laughing us
eating their steak.
They want us to buy their fake meat
because of climate change and our carbon footprint.
Fuck that!
Yes. Yes.
Fake. Yes.
I don't want that fake meat, man.
They don't care about us.
and watch them try to put us in another COVID lockdown, another stupid booster
shot. The people versus the government, they are trying to control us without
order. Out of chaos, we see right through the bullshit. Time to boycott.
And then this next one,
Oktoberfest, hops of spalt brewing, pouring the beer with great friends,
German style party.
Hey, you've been to Oktoberfest? There was a lot of... Would you say that
October Fest has a lot of Stacy's there right with
but I think a lot you ever see pictures of those German women with the giant
breasts at October Fest and they wear shoelaces. Where the fuck are your
nipples?
Their nipples have to be on the bottom of their titties, because half of them
are popping out of those shirts. I think a lot of it honestly is latex
prosthetics. Oh yeah. It's gotta be latex prosthetics and
a lot. I think it's like Halloween level costume. Yeah,
I don't have my testing. I don't have my password, so I can't see.
I think I have a few more here. No, I got a password. Here is
a poem
written by Joe Fedig.
Now, I want you to
damn there. There's a little there's some I'm gonna point it out,
some hypocrisy.
I like a policy you like honestly nowadays audiences say there's some
hypocrisy again yeah, there's some hypocrisy
wow
applause yeah well that's kind of listen to this listen to this okay. If you
love, if you love hypocrisy, you're going to love this mass layoffs happening in
the workplace. Will they replace man with the sheet with machine another
agenda in plain sight, no more gas powered cars. They want everyone to go
green getting replaced by a robot artificial intelligence is getting out
of control. The transhumanism agenda the elite want your soul. Controlling every aspect of
your life, living in a smart city, being charged a carbon tax, the evil leaders that you want
that you tell you that you own nothing and be happy just relax. Your robot replacement
will take your job and leave you on the street. Depopulate the earth, mocking the citizens
with a single tweet. Humans are easily replaceable. The first thing you hack is the subconscious
mind, divide and conquer, have race wars. It's the blind leading the blind. Corporation cutting
labor costs, you're replaceable at any time. CEOs being downright cheap, nobody cares, I
feel like I am a black sheep.
Whoa.
Nothing is guaranteed in life, not even your career. Getting replaced by a robot is something
that we might fear. Yeah?
Dude, what the fuck? I mean, I'm sorry. Can we just talk?
I'm sorry. Let me point out the hypocrisy here.
Okay. Yeah.
"YouTube censorship," this is posted by Joe Fetig, "YouTube censorship, a threat to free
speech where videos are subjected to breach by an algorithm with a heavy hand, once a
place for open expression, now a platform with tight discretion and voices are silenced
in this lands. Words that once spread like wildfire and now face suppression with a heavy
hand and the truth is hidden from sight. Ideas that once flourished in the sun now faced restrictions
one by one and free speech is dealt a deadly blow. But we must fight against
this tide and not let censorship divide for the right to express ourselves. We
will uphold. Wait, so what's the hypocrisy? That was written by who? You?
Chat GPT. No. Yeah. Holy bottom of the page. It says posted by Joe Fedig
written by chat GPT. That's fucking insane. Even trust anyone nowadays. Not
not even brave minds like Joe Fettig. People say Mr. Joe Fettig, who once
wrote, who once wrote, and let me, let me pull this, this
one up. Yeah, I wanna hear this.
Here's a...
Mr. Joe Fettig. That's him? The... No fucking way. The once great leader
of the MGTOW movement. He looks great. Mr. Joe Fettig, who wrote
false rape. Why protect she lies all the time, dumb bitch charger with the crime
is now relying on he is now relying on chat. Gp that man is going his own way
that man is chiving on yeah.
What is there to do in this world, but chive on man this he's a he's a chiving
hypocrite is what I'll say
the chad gbt stuff that does break my heart, because it's like is this is this
machine or is it machine and oh my God, that was good post. Yeah, there's
comments here on this post for Roy, who says I'm all about the first amendment
to and he just says thanks. He's taking credit
for chat GPT and what fucking universe is that make any God damn it's not right.
Oh God, maybe the spider verse and what's the spider verse. I mean the
spider verse that does make sense. Yeah, you're right. Yeah, but also in the
Spider verse you'd all be fucking spiders.
Do I have how much time do I have to do another one? Okay, one last one yeah,
and then I have a good thing to close out with. If anybody else doesn't have
no, I got nothing women in West lost men go overseas, find good wife, leftover
women mad.
Wow
this is a speech say introduce a speech that's coming
Folks, we're going to be closing out the show with a speech by none other than Mr. Dr. Cameron Fetter.
Wow. Thank you.
Keep it going for Cameron.
He's putting the coat back on.
He's ready to...
It's a speech.
It's a speech. Yeah, you got to be formal, right?
Yeah, button up that...
A little more stately.
Let me see. What else can we get?
The top button here.
All right, Cameron, let's hear this speech.
I hope the speech is going to move you guys.
I hope that it will too.
Probably going to move my fucking bowels.
I'm going to move this.
Yeah, I like that.
Games like Minecraft
have shaped our generation
with good reason.
Life in middle school
is just like Minecraft.
Wow.
We all entered this biome called middle school.
middle school, some imagining it was the nether. It was a completely foreign world
where we didn't know who we might run into, what we might find that is useful,
or how we were going to survive. Each of us was a Steve. Completely indistinguishable
from the rest of the kids for at least the first few days. As noobs, we wandered
the halls aimlessly until we eventually found a block, then another, and another.
With these blocks, we learned to craft bigger and better things.
We worked hard and grew our world into a place we couldn't wait to enter each day.
Some days we ran into more creepers, endermen, and zombies than we would have liked, but
we learned to defeat those bad guys.
Through friendships and the guidance of our teachers, we became expert craftsmen, building
an amazing world based on cooperative effort.
As we learned to adjust our skins, we each found our unique identity, our own unique
identity.
Most of us were even able to mine not just one, but many diamonds along the way.
Today we stand together.
We stand together.
We stand together at the portal to the next dimension, high school.
Let's remember where we are coming from.
Let's stand strong in who we are as individuals and as a group.
me and building the next world for ourselves without fear.
And that's the speech everybody.
Thank you.
We'll see you next time.
A star-crossed lovers who are Star Wars.
Okay, Star Wars movie.
(laughing)
Matthew McConaughey has to go to space
to save the entire world.
- Star Wars scary movie.
- Well, it's kind of a scary movie.
When you're, if you smoke weed, it is pretty scary.
Oh, a mysterious convict on death row
has mystical powers.
- Superhero movie.
Harry Potter.
four okay
a man's experience in a turn of the century. The experience okay
turn of the century turn of the century okay in the title it's in the log.
That is good
Leonardo DiCaprio. He has to go into your dream DiCaprio.
Why I didn't finish Leo.
Those are the names Leo period Leo period. I think is better. I'm going to
it again. Now it's a competition. Okay, a
for an escaped slave has to has to the slave.
He has to hook up with a German guy to go get his wife from Hilda from
Leonardo DiCaprio.
Slavery, the movie DiCaprio, colon, the slave DiCaprio, the slave, well, yeah,
I'm going to give it to you, DiCaprio, the slaver.
Well he, you don't know that though.
Cause I didn't say that in the log line.
Broomhilda's capture.
Broomhilda's capture?
That would be the prequel.
Okay, actually I'm just going to do Tarantino movies.
Okay.
Um, seven funny looking businessmen go back into their garage.
Seven brothers.
The funny farm.