Uh, well, finally happened.
I am all alone.
Wait a second.
I'm in a dream!
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah!
What's up? I just had the most amazing dream of my life. What was it about? Food, lunch,
lunch and dinner.
Welt.
(laughter)
Everyone just steals that now.
Yeah.
Yeah, Jack stole it first. I stole it from Jack.
he's amazing this guy
this guy and jordan alvarez you gotta look him up on instagram he's doing stuff with
instagram filters that nobody thought was possible
and now it is completely uh... he's forging a new path for himself
his stuff has infected my brain so much i love him so much he's so good
well it's nice 'cause it's something that uh...
i can watch on my phone that my girlfriend doesn't get mad at
what does she what do you usually watch on your phone that she gets mad about? she doesn't get mad about
about, but it's a lot of very annoying stuff. And this is something that we can
watch together. Like, I'm watching, like, these videos of, like,
what am I... I'm watching, like, old men doing, like, food reviews.
You're watching Guga. I'm watching Guga. You're watching people try durian for
the first time. Skate videos. And she doesn't like any of this shit. She's
not, like, you know, that comes up on my phone.
But one of his things pops up and...
Girls like that shit.
Oh my god.
They love it so much.
Big fucking shoe.
They love when a guy is being crazy with a filter.
And he's so good at it.
And even guys can like it too.
Yeah, he's so good.
Well I'm seeing double today.
Why?
Why don't you introduce us to your little friend here.
Who's this?
This is, I don't know where this came from.
You don't know where that came from?
No.
The blow up doll that looks exactly like you.
And you put your own hat on it.
No, no, no.
A matching hat.
I don't know where this came from actually.
And it doesn't look that much like me.
It literally looks like one to one exactly like you.
It doesn't look like me at all.
And you don't know where this came from?
No.
This is interesting. Do you want me to explain the story? Because it's not that good.
I want to explain. Yeah, I think that people need to know why he bought this.
Okay. So I was asked to host a thing from my friend Serge,
and I was already on tour. Serge! Super villain.
And I said, "Don't worry. I have the solution to be two places at once."
This was my solution. I was going to send this in my place.
and ended up not being able to deliver it to them because of some logistical
things that I did not think of. And now I'm trying to get my money's worth out
of it. I spent $14 on this.
Yeah, and at first when you told me it was $14, I was like, "That's pretty cheap
for a blow-up sex doll." Okay, he's mad there's no butthole or penis. There is
No butthole or penis on this sex doll, guys.
This is a Nolo doll.
That can't even take a shit.
It has nothing going on.
It doesn't have a butthole.
There is no reason for this doll to exist.
What do you mean there's no reason?
Show the butthole.
We have a reason for it to exist now.
But like, why would you even make it naked if it has nothing?
It has absolutely fucking nothing, man.
It's for bachelorette parties so they can bring these, like...
They're supposed to have a big cock they can sit on.
If it had a big cock that they could sit on, you wouldn't be allowed to bring it in public.
That's not true.
It would be an indecency law thing.
At a bachelorette party, you're going to be at a strip club and you're not...
No, no, on the way there.
You can get a microphone.
This is like a cuddling...
You can get a microphone, little Patrick.
This is like...
Okay, he has a name now.
This is like a cuddles only doll.
Yeah, and he does not fit in a lot of clothes.
You've tried dressing him up?
Yeah, I did try dressing him up earlier and I decided that it was funnier to keep him nude.
He wears like kids clothes probably.
Yeah, it's kids clothes. I don't own any kids clothes.
So we need to go out, we need to go to Oshkosh to get him something.
Maybe that's what we do after this.
Okay, I'm down.
(laughs)
- Ring up to the store.
- And we get him some children's clothes
that we can put him in.
- We can put him on our hip like a baby.
- Yeah.
- Say he's starting school.
- So Noah was gonna go and bring this thing for me,
but he was at work, and I had it blown up,
and Noah was gonna walk around the city, downtown,
he was gonna walk around with this under his arm
like he was a father carrying his child.
Yeah, not a lot of shame.
No, Noah is not a shameful person.
It's very, very crazy.
I mean, you know, because he's Irish Protestant.
He'll do whatever, he'll do anything.
No Catholic bone in his body.
No, not at all.
I mean, see, I had it deflated and I carried it here and I was worried that somebody would
walk by that door and see me blowing up a blow-up doll.
Well, you have public, you are, the people who you care the most about, like their opinion
of you are strangers. Not anymore. No, you still do that. I still do in some way. You're
still scared of doing public pranks, which is interesting as a skateboarder. I had to
shut that off. I've been working on shutting that off. Really? Yeah. You're finally brave
enough to bring a piece of paper into a business? Yes, actually. Prove it. Well, I've done. We
need to make a Prank Gas 2 that is just one single clip of you walking in with a piece
of paper. Well, no, I had the realization one day that everything is actually fucking
Bullshit and nothing matters you became an absurdist nihilist. I became an absurdist nihilist exactly like TJ Miller
I've been calling in bomb threats on the Amtrak train. And did this change your perspective at all?
It changed my whole complete perspective. And you decided that what's more absurdly odd than having a blow-up twin?
Mm-hmm me and my twin in them, but I walk around with I do
I do okay there the shame that I did feel when I was blowing this up and thought
that maybe like somebody in the neighborhood like an old woman would
look in and see me.
What it would look like me eating the ass of a blow up doll.
But you'd have I think that there's a reasonable amount of things on the
back. There's a reasonable amount of shame. It looks like you're eating the
back of it. There is no asshole. You could walk out, if a woman walked by and went, "Ah!"
You could walk outside.
Oh, I could walk up to the window and show that there's no butthole.
Hey, Granny, great news. There's no asshole on this doll.
There's no butthole.
I wish there was. I would have paid extra, but there's nothing.
There's no butt, penis, butt, or butthole, or ass in asshole.
There's nothing.
Nothing there. It's completely Nolo.
It doesn't even have fingers.
And I was going to get rid of this hat, too. It's actually, I got, I told you about this.
I bought a lot of vintage Red Sox hats for $5 on eBay.
Really?
They were all dirty and smelled like an ashtray.
And this surprised you?
Well the lady said she cleaned them.
She promised that they were cleaned.
And I ended up doing it.
I cleaned this one.
Look at how clean this one is.
Oh, that's not a new one?
No.
This is one of those vintage ones?
Uh huh.
It used to be covered in grime.
Nice, man.
This one you didn't clean, the one that went on Little Patrick.
No, I cleaned them all.
That one looks really dirty though.
This one looks dirty?
Yep.
It just looks old because it's all wrinkly.
Actually, it was Brian Madison's.
Oh shit! It's a signature.
Yeah.
Well, Patrick, tell me about how amazing it was to be a touring stand-up comedian.
Oh my goodness.
What was this like?
this like? It's pretty much the same as when we did the podcast. You're in a car for long
periods of time. Farting. Yeah, farting up a storm. I mean it's not like I haven't gone
on tour before with some people. It's not like I haven't opened for people before. Dude,
tell me man. Tell me bro. After these shows, were you getting so fucked up you couldn't
fucking see straight. I was. You were fucking hurting people. I was getting so fucked up
that I was. You were so fucked up you just hurt people. I didn't hurt people. You know
you're doing. You just start hurting, just touching everybody. What are you talking about?
Come here. Come here! That's what you do when you open for Adam? No, I was saying that's
what you did when we went on tour. I didn't. I was saying, did you do this again? No, I
did not do that. Oh, Grace and April stopped you? What? I did not do this when we were on
tour unless it was maybe to Cameron or you or Pierce. So you did it then? Come here!
I would run up to Pierce and I would say come here and I would try to lift him. Come here!
I have a hundred thousand followers on Twitter. Come here! I would lift Pierce up Hava Nagila
style. Is that what Hava Nagila means? No. It's just the song that plays when people
I have a guy in my hands. I'm lifting him. He is above my head.
Dude, we need to convert to Judaism. This is the most fun religion there is, let me tell you.
Yeah, you go on tour with Adam, now you're saying that?
No, if anything, he convinced me of the opposite, hanging out with his bum ass.
I'm asking, but
everybody else has convinced me that this is the most fun
religion in the entire nation. You can have a horn at church. Yeah, I used to
try to bring I used to try to bring a horn to church and they would put me
into the
the nursery.
They would lock me in the nursery. Yeah, a quiet breastfeeding, a bunch of
breastfeeding moms. That's where I would go. Did you guys have a breastfeeding
room at your church? I barely went to church because I was too disruptive. I had a breastfeeding
room and I had to clean it. You had to clean the breastfeeding room? Yeah, it was fucking
disgusting stuff all over the floor. It was sticky. Yeah? Yeah. What were these girls
doing in there? They were squirting? I guess. All these breastfeeding moms were squirting
everywhere? Yeah, they wouldn't even have the babies. They'd just go in there and pull
their tits out and squirt. Yeah. That's what they thought the room was. They thought there
was going to be some old priests in there and they had to feed them. Did you ever do
confession? No, I mean I was barely, I was not allowed to do CCD. I wasn't allowed to
do Sunday school. Oh, because you got banned. No, because my aunt was the teacher. Oh, yes.
She hated you. She thought I was annoying, yeah. But did you wish that you had confession
when you were a kid? I did for a little bit. I feel like you have a lot to confess. I did
for a little bit. I don't have a lot to confess. Come here! That's what you probably would
you would have done in the confession booth.
I wouldn't have done that.
You would have punched a hole through that screen.
You would have said...
What are you talking about?
Hello, it's father.
And you'd go, "Come here!"
You'd grab his neck, start tickling his ears like you do to people.
I don't tickle people's ears.
Come here, ears.
You pull him apart.
Where is this coming from?
You're really upset that I went on the news, huh?
And you're trying to convince everyone that I'm a serial grouper.
Dude, you went on the news and you bombed.
- You bombed. - I didn't bomb on the news.
- You bombed on the news, man. - What was I supposed to do there?
- Fart. - Grace had a bunch of coins in her mouth.
- You gotta one-up that. - I was not supposed to one-up it.
- You go. - I was the opener.
- Bro, you're not opening for them on the news, man.
- I wasn't supposed to be there in the first place.
They kicked me off during the interview.
- You are not opening for them on the news.
They weren't like, "Come be on the news and be our opener."
- They said... - "And do nothing. Just sit there."
I thought you were a host. I didn't even recognize you.
I thought you were one of the anchors.
You thought that I was one of the anchors.
I did for a moment.
You thought that I looked like Mark Clark in Lady T?
No.
Lady's an interesting first name.
Her name is Lady T and she spills the tea and she has a cup that has her initial on
it and it's got rhinestones.
What's her initial?
T.
Oh, snap.
Lady T. She's on Be More Lifestyle.
See, but I just think that you could have gone on there, you could have worn --
They were not asking me any questions at all.
could have taken one of these prison jumpsuits, gotten on there and say, "I have escaped."
I just escaped from prison.
But instead you went on there and you said, "I'm allergic to carrots. Come here, Lady
T! Come here, Mark Clark!"
I did not try to grope Mark Clark and Lady T.
I didn't say grope. I said grab.
You're upset. You're upset and I get it. You wanted to go on the news, but...
It just makes me sad that that is our television... because listen, Rising Tide raises all boats,
correct. So I'm thinking this is the first time any of my dogs been on TV.
That's not true.
Who's the one I'm on?
Jack and Eric and Nate have all been on TV. Sarah is on TV all the time.
But this is all, Sarah's the only one that counts because that's a network, but the other
ones, I mean this is cable. I don't care.
Yeah, you're talking shit about their appearance on the bear?
Dude, fuck the bear. I'm talking about real TV, okay? Local news. This is the first time
I'm one of my dogs. I mean it's apparently very easy to get on local
news. Then let's do it probably not new. Yeah, we could get we could
I know the guy at be more lifestyle. Now, if we do a show there,
we could get our be more. We could get on be more lifestyle.
You think they'd have you back after you bombed? They would have they'd get
the email. They say, oh, what's he gonna do? Fucking talk about carrots again.
They were they were fun. They cut a lot of that interview because of stuff
that Grace was saying.
Oh, really?
So you're going to go on...
Grace tried to get people to bring her ketamine.
On the live news. That ain't going to work.
She's already in a shirt that said ketamine.
They really didn't want us there after that.
Yeah, I can imagine.
Yeah.
So you're going to send the email.
You're going to say, "Hey, can I come on?"
The brief appearance that I had was like when
Klaus Nomi was the background singer for David Bowie.
Bowie. I don't know who either of those people are,
but if you know, you know. Okay. So that's when people see me on the be
more lifestyle thing, they're gonna say, "Oh my God, that's Patrick, he's
allergic to carrots." I'm thinking that in... And then in my documentary,
and when I die in two years, is like... You know what you did,
man? That's just a little footnote. I'm realizing right, you did,
"I like turtles." I did lie like turtles. You did, "I like turtles."
And you're thinking I bombed, and you're thinking I bombed. No, you did
bomb. I like turtles bomb. That's the most famous bomb ever. I like turtles, not a bomb.
He bombed. He did not bomb. They asked him about his costume. Are you going to say that
that corn kid bombed? No, corn kid was different because they were asking about that corn.
They were asking me about carrots. You bombed. They were asking me about veggies. No. And
tanning. You basically said, I can't eat carrots. You did that. That was you. You're carrot
boy. I'm carrot boy. That's fine. You are carrot boy. You are not, you're supposed to
be on there. They didn't ask me shit. Then just say something. They didn't want me there.
Then just talk some shit. Talk with Lady T. What's up Lady T? I'm going to spill the tea
right now. I did. I talked to Lady T before. I said I love your mug. When the cameras weren't
on. And then a lot of my stuff got cut. Well okay, tell me what these bangers were that
got cut. I think I said that, I think he made a joke about Luther Vandross and I think I
I said I heard that.
You said heard that?
You think that was?
I don't think I said heard that.
I don't remember exactly what I said.
It's kind of all a blur.
I was only there for five minutes.
I was on the news for five minutes.
They asked me one question.
What was I supposed to say?
Say fuck.
You say shit.
I said fuck or shit. It's not going in that segment would have been way
shorter. Oh, it wasn't live. No. Yeah, that's an issue because anything that
you do that's so crazy. Exactly. Do something funny. Fall off the chair.
Default jump on the chair. Start jumping around. Have a pillow fight.
There any of this shit would work. There you if you were in the situation
that I was in you would have completely
stood your ground like I did. See that's a better idea. Stay your ground.
I'm
Pulling out your phone.
No, I'm sorry.
I gotta...
It's Cameron.
He's so needy.
He keeps texting us.
About what?
When can we have our next meeting?
Oh, shut up.
Maybe when you're in town, man.
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, maybe come the fuck home and stop traveling so much.
These two pieces of shit have been just tricking around the world.
Me, I'm a homebody.
What are you talking about?
You were in D.C. like last weekend.
Yeah, and did I miss an episode?
Yeah.
Nope.
I thought you did.
Did not.
You were going to.
Did not miss one, man.
because I'm a dedicated and I know what my job is. And if they'd put me on local TV,
on local news, well, why don't you get out of the way to walk over to the West? I would
have walked over to the way they cut to the weather, right? Push the weather guy out of
the way. And then I start pointing thing. Well, there's no Dixon balls. There is no
big pieces around shit more lifestyle. Oh yeah. It looks like there's gonna be a giant
fucking huge purple cock coming right out of the northern system when you're when you're
on the news that's coming from the south and they're trying to get you out of there as
quick as possible, you're not going to say a lot of stuff. When your friend is dropping
coins out of her mouth, they are trying to get you out of there as quick as possible.
If I'm ever on the news, man, I'm going to be the star of the show. The news will make
the news. I promise you now, if I'm ever on the news, I will not say, "I'm allergic to
carrots." By the end of the year, we will try to get on the news. Yumi and Cam all go
on and they just ask us different questions. By the end of the year. So the funny thing
is all three of us are allergic to carrots. Can't eat them, especially raw. By the end
of the year starting today. So by the end of 2023. 2024 September. When does this come
out? September. Within one year. Within one year we will be on the local news. Okay, somewhere.
Somewhere in the country. Alright, we could go do, um, man what's the Wilmington one? Look
I was just happy to be along for the ride. I'm very grateful for Grace and April letting
me come on the news with them. I got to tell the world about my... I got to raise awareness
for oral allergy syndrome. But next time I'm on the news, I'm not going to be so quiet.
So next time you promise you'll body it? Next time I'm on the news, I'm going to be... we're
all going to be dressed up like sunflowers. And we're going to be saying that we're a musical
group called the Sunflowers. We're starting a musical group and we're all in big green
costumes with yellow heads. Our faces are painted brown. The center of our faces will
be painted brown. The outside of it will be painted yellow.
yellow and it will be yellow face and a brown face at the same time. Okay,
then I think will be the roses.
That might be the worst possible costume. There's no way to make a sunflower
work.
There is actually no way to make a... I can't believe you picked sunflower.
This is the one flower. I was just thinking of the most beautiful flower
I could think of. Sunflower's not the most beautiful flower. The most
beautiful flowers have brown faces. Maybe we dress up like a cactus. Maybe
that could work too. Maybe where they call the prickly pears.
Yeah, that's not a cactus.
Yeah, well, it's, you know, it's the same vein.
It's a fruit.
What, because it's got pricklies?
Yeah.
I'm obsessed with durian and I want to eat a durian so badly and I've watched maybe 15 videos.
We've talked about durians a lot.
I know, but I'm back at...
They smell like poopy.
No, but I've heard...
Just go to Chinatown, man. Go to Chinatown and buy a durian.
They're like $150 for a fucking...
They're not $150.
They're insanely expensive.
You can get some durian ice cream around there.
but I don't want the ice cream blood.
I want the real fruit.
You could find the whole hog.
You could find like a half a durian or like a quarter.
You can buy it frozen, but they said there was this video where a lady was
like if it's your first time eating durian, I recommend to buy it frozen and
you eat it, but you have to close every door, every window, and you can't leave
your house for two days because even if you brush your teeth, the smell won't go
away from your face.
And I was like, okay, I'll eat that.
Yeah.
It sounds good to me. People said it's like garlic ice cream. Doesn't that sound kind
of good?
They could make that anywhere though. Garlic ice cream?
Yeah, I don't really like fancy ice creams. Like a miso ice cream?
I do like a fancy ice cream.
What kind of ice cream?
You know what I had? There's an ice cream place around the corner. And they had a...
What are you squirming around for?
I don't know man. This shirt is too small. Do I look like James Dean in this shirt?
You don't look like James Dean, not the one you're thinking of.
Which James Dean are you thinking of?
The rapist.
I think he dressed like the real James Dean.
So they kind of look the same.
Anyway, I had a black sesame ice cream.
It was really good.
That's not what I meant to, man.
Yeah, you don't like black sesame ice cream?
Vanilla, chocolate, maybe some strawberry action going in there.
I don't like a fancy ice cream. I like a black sesame. I like a... what's the other thing
that I tried that one time?
Don't tell me you just about to say matcha or a green tea.
No, not a green tea. I had... well, I mean, any kind of like a nutty flavor, a nutty creamy
flavor.
Peanut. You don't need a... sesame is a seedy flavor.
When an ice cream is nutty and very... when ice cream is nut and very creamy...
Are you trying to be doing a gay thing?
Isn't it? It's very creamy.
Don't do that voice.
It's cause of doing a gay thing.
Talking about creamy, nutty.
Pause, bro!
You can't pause yourself.
I'm getting into pause, dude.
Getting into pause?
Uh-huh.
On tour?
Yeah.
Is it pause or shit?
Yeah, I'm starting to say pause.
See, even that would have worked on the news.
Yeah.
Well, cause when the weatherman's doing his thing.
But he say when the, they said, you know, do you eat carrots?
I say pause.
Yeah, paws ain't never going in my mouth, dog.
Carrots not touching my lips.
And they would definitely cut that from the news.
That would definitely never see the light of day.
No shot.
Yeah.
But you could have gone to the sports desk.
You can't just get up and walk around.
You literally can't.
You have legs and arms.
You know what I learned about the news?
What's that?
Well, this station, at least, this Fox affiliate
in Baltimore, completely--
Wow, big surprise.
Patrick went on Fox News.
Completely robotically automated cameras.
No cameramen that you know?
No, because they know, well maybe they swapped it all out because they knew a comedian/prankster
was walking in.
Well, yeah.
By God, a podcaster/comedian/internet personality is coming in.
They did not call me that.
They said podcast host Patrick Doren.
Wow.
And then later in the segment they used my senior photo as my head shot.
That was funny.
That was a non-bomb.
That was a medium.
They can't all be zingers, man.
You can't get all the, you know.
You can't zing every single time.
Yeah, you're not going to crush every single time you go up.
But if you had done the...
Next time we do it, we'll do it, it'll be live.
You are so obsessed with this now.
Get over it.
Because you were on TV, man.
I'm already over it. I'm already over it. It's just a footnote in my long and lustrous
career of going on the news.
It's not. It's just, no. See, the first cut is the deepest.
Not true.
Yep.
Not in my case.
Maybe the second or third cut is probably the deepest.
This news thing is going to haunt you for the rest of your life. Every single time they
ask you to be on the news, you'll go, "Fuck, I'm going to fucking black out and start talking
about carrots again."
I mean that could be a good, funny, pretty funny thing to do.
You just talk about, see that's the only option you have now is every time you do anything
you have to be like, "I'm allergic to carrots."
By the way, I can't eat carrots.
Yeah, just apropos of nothing.
What do you think, Elon Musk announces a new ban on personal videos.
Well I hope he bans carrots.
I hope he bans videos of people eating carrots because I'm going to get jealous because I
can't eat the damn things.
Yeah, and they'll go, "Oh, really?
You can't eat carrots?
Cooked and raw carrots you can't eat?"
What's that?
It's actually, it's a...
No, I can eat raw, but if I eat a...
Or I can't eat raw, but if I eat a cooked carrot, it's completely fine.
Yeah, they go, "Oh my God, he did the carrot thing."
Let's fucking go!
Carrot boy back at it again.
Paul Rudd with the Mac and Me type vibe.
That shit was funny.
I wish I had a clip prepared.
I could have.
Did I tell you my...
You just show the clip of you eating.
Going on the news and then I say like, "Yeah, we actually, we have a clip of me not being
able to eat carrots."
And then it's a clip of Paul Rudd announcing the clip of Mac and me.
I was thinking you say like, "Actually, we have a clip for my show tonight.
Cut to you, be more lifestyle."
Yeah, I actually can't eat carrots, raw carrots.
What the hell?
Your phone's talking back.
You're supposed to talk into that.
You said, "I can't eat carrots."
And they said, "I thought so."
That's messed up. That's crazy. They're always listening in to us. They are. You're just going
to start getting ads for carrots now. I'm going to get ads for fucking carrots. Ads for beef
stews dude. That's not that bad. That's pretty good actually. I would love to do, if I went
on Conan man I would have an amazingly funny bit like Paul Rudd's awesome Mac and Me thing.
Yeah. But he doesn't do the talk show anymore. Shit, you're so right. Yeah he does Conan
O'Brien needs a friend. What a fall. Yeah, this guy's lost. The greatest late night talk show
host of all time. No, that ain't true. Letterman is better. Letterman better. No, Letterman
is better. No, they're both below the real king of late night, Jay Leno. I used to like
Jay Leno. Yeah? Yeah. I used to watch every late night show when I was a kid. Really?
yeah i only watched Conan, Craig Ferguson, Letterman. I read the late night wars when it came out
oh the movie? no the fifteen hundred page fucking book. Is that about the 08?
It's about Conan vs Jay. I thought you were talking about Dave vs Jay and they had that HBO original movie.
Well it touches on that
but uh...
who they have? They have John Michael Higgins from Best in Show playing Dave
David LeBrunnen. I haven't seen that. It's on HBO Max. It's an HBO original movie and
it came out like a year or two after the whole late night wars thing. I don't think that
they. So it was like immediately after that shit happened. This is not important enough
to get a movie man. No. Straight up. No not at all. But it is a very funny portrayal of
Jay Leno as a skeevy son of a bitch. Does he wear prosthetics? Does he do like the chin
They make the guy, if you can pull this up, Jubio, you should see how they make these guys
look.
Kathy Bates is in it.
Kathy Bates plays Dave.
Look up the Late Night Wars HBO movie or Dave Letterman HBO movie and Kathy Bates is in it
and Kathy Bates plays Dave's manager and I mean she's...
The Late Shift.
Yeah, look at how they make this guy look.
They, that's, no, go up, go back up, it's right there.
It's right there.
This is in 1996?
This is '96.
Oh man.
Look at what they did to this fucker's chin.
Wait, they kind of lampooned Letterman's look as well.
Yeah, I mean, you know, they're not very, I mean, Letterman's a little bit distinctive.
He does have the gap in his teeth, but really nothing going on.
Yeah.
were like we have to put 110% into the costumes here and nothing else.
Would you do if Freeform came back and they came to you and they said we want to do Patrick
Knight Live?
Would you do it?
You probably, I mean I need a lot of money.
But you got to talk about the news.
I have a team of writers and I have a little co-host like Guillermo.
you
always does job. Yeah,
shut up.
That would be so fucking good. Yeah, that's a little bit. There's a pretty
good impression. There we go. You have to admit. Okay, you say shut up now.
No,
see, he would say now
I would ask him. What do you think like? Okay, let me just make up like a
new story from like the future is a Rhonda Rousey bites off man's penis after
much steroid injections from being in the UFC again. She's back in the UFC.
She's 50 years old.
50 years old, back in the UFC taking a billion, she actually is the first woman to ever inject
50 billion cc's of anabolic steroids into her butt which made her go feral like a damn wolf.
What is this news story about?
Ronda Rousey injected 50,000 cc's of anabolic, IUs of anabolic steroids into her butt.
her body, causing her to become kind of like a werewolf, and she ran over and
just bit off her personal trainer's penis. You said personal trainer, a penis?
It's a penis, and
no, this didn't happen.
Wait. I started saying it and then I was like... You could have said anything.
You could have said... No, I think it's similar to another, it's similar to
another thing. I was going off the dome and I think it was just saying something too similar
to something else. So I have to restart it. Okay, restart it. Okay. Uh, bad news for Louisiana.
Hurricane Katrina two has just struck and in the ensuing chaos, looters started stealing
a cyber trucks from Tesla. And uh, Julio, what do you have to think about? What do you have
to say about this? That's crazy. Wait, hold on. Wait. Fuck. How do you use this? Where's
the... Maybe you can play the... I'll find it. I'll find it. Okay. Let me think of another
news story that I can lampoon. Okay. Let me imagine another news story from the future.
A news story from the future that I will... And I'll be... I'll have a deeper voice, so
I'll be older and I have salt and pepper hair. I look real. Oh my god. You have your own tequila
line? Uh huh. I've gotten, I've become like a silver Patrick. Silver like you know, you
know like when Jimmy Kimmel lost the weight. Yeah. And everyone was like oh my god. This
will be you. Oh my god look at how good he looks now. Yeah. But here's me and I'm thinking
there's a new story in the future and
X CEO
Elon Musk
has tragically passed away
after
exploding
in a
maybe it's a jet ski accident or something and
kids say maybe if you're the
telling the news. Yeah, I'm just trying to think of
just say it doesn't have to be a funny news story. It could be a
is it a tragic one? Yeah, it can be the biggest track yeah. Okay, a child has
died today. So in the middle of the Midwest in
the in the middle of the Midwest in the country, a new type of tornado has
evolved
and
a million residents have died because of this new type of tornado that has
Jubio, what are you? No, you're supposed to cheer after Jubio chimes in. Oh, okay.
Wait, really? You're supposed to be my co- or sidekick. Wait, did that happen?
Yeah, there is a new type of tornado that has arms and legs and it picks up people
and puts it in its- And it killed, okay, and it killed 1 million people.
Jubio's reaction.
OOP. Okay, now do a monologue joke. Okay,
scientists report that the COVID-19 pandemic was all made up after lab
reports show that
that in
the lab report show that it was just a way to get. It was just a way to for
to get less work done.
The audience didn't like that so much.
Okay, okay, hold on.
Save this.
I gotta think.
Well, I gotta have a team of writers.
Okay, here, here.
Okay, okay.
I'm actually allergic to carrots.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I can't eat raw carrots.
Um.
[air horn]
Whoops.
I got it, I got it.
I have my monologue joke.
Okay.
A new study shows that the consumption of raw carrots is actually shown to increase the
size of male penises.
That's too bad for me because I can't eat raw carrots.
I'm actually allergic to them.
Yep, they love that.
That's kind of your catchphrase at this point.
You're a couple years into the show.
show science studies show that
rock carrots actually have been proven to increase eyesight,
but an unexpected.
I could be carrots.
I'm allergic to carrots.
They like to be a more I'm going to be.
Yeah, Juvia is kind of the way to okay.
Turn my voice up.
Juvia.
Why don't you how about you do the monologue then and then we'll
see the dynamic with me being the sidekick and then it's free
form presents Jubio live. No, Jubio TV, Jubio night live, JBL live.
Just say, just say what he said about liking raw carrots or not
being able to eat him.
Um, scientists actually find out that, uh, raw carrots increase
your penis size.
Let's stay, uh, and Jubio, you know, that's too bad for me
because I'm actually allergic to raw carrots.
Can't eat the things.
It's not doing well for me.
That's too bad Patrick.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I mean that's because it's kind of a bummer.
I think maybe, yeah.
You know, like he's saying it and people think, "Oh that's funny, he's not actually allergic."
That's a funny thing to say.
Well that's like when Howie Mandel talks about being like a germaphobe.
You think people like that?
I hate that shit.
I think it's interesting.
When he goes like, "Oh yeah, I can't shake people's hands, I do a fist bump."
Yeah.
Buddy, if I'm ever on America's Got Talent or whichever one he's on, X Factor,
and I do my comedy routine, you are going to shake my hand.
Yeah.
I'm going to grab your hand. I'm going to--
Oh, here? Okay. Put the monologue voice back on.
Tragedy strikes.
The set of America's Got Talent is a walking tornado,
picks up Howie Mandel,
throws Howie Mandel into the top of the tornado spout,
and he's now covered in tornado germs. Say it put him in the germ factory. It
brought him and dumped him in the germ. The
he actually
now the show is going to be called how he's got germs,
how he's got germs,
because he was picked up by a human tornado and what is this human tornado
this is not the okay. You think that in a couple of years, you think that I say
it now. I say I say this now, right? We wait like 10 years and 10 years.
Scientists create a walking human tornado. Why would scientists be
creating tornado scientists?
All right, you convince me. Yeah, let's do the list. Yeah, actually, the I'm
saying that because of a dream that I had. Oh, that's actually good because of
of a dream that I had last night.
Guys, we're getting into dream interpretation, okay?
Uh-huh.
Real quick, Patrick, are you a dreamer?
I'm a dreamer. I'm somebody that actually I log a lot of my dreams.
Really?
I wake up and I do log my dreams.
Do you have any interest in sharing one?
Whose slide is first? It's going to be mine?
Yeah.
Okay, so yeah, actually, here are some of my dreams that I've had.
The first one, I think we all know, I've talked about it every which way. I've talked about
this dream. It's not clicking. Son of a bitch. I love the production value of this show.
What am I waiting? I'm not getting a carrot, bud. Don't you dare try to make me eat a carrot.
Do I do more monologue stuff till we get this text? Yeah, do one more monologue.
A walking, talking human tornado. This is okay. Wait, hold on.
This is not. This is not a premise for a fucking monologue joke. What do you
mean? There's never going killer. The covid killer bees. Remember that
talking human tornado? Monologue joke should ever start with a walking,
talking human, a walking, talking human tornado has arrived in the small town of
uh, Poughkeepsie, New York.
Uh, residents of Poughkeepsie state.
The big tornado is actually a nuisance and we want him out of our fucking
town and we want him dead.
How's that a joke?
There's no, I can't even think right now.
I'm so confused about if we're doing the list. I can't even tell the production or anything.
You're obsessed with the production. I'm obsessed. I'm just asking. You know what I'm obsessed
with right now is this human tornado. Is this working now or no? No. Are you just going
to click through for me? Give me a second. This is good radio. This is really good radio.
It would be good if you could come up with one thing besides the fucking human tornado.
try that again. Okay, all right
dozens more and today as actress Selena Gomez was found dead in
her Los Angeles home.
Many are speculating that
the cause of death was a walk and talking human tornado
I walked all the way from Poughkeepsie and all the way to L.A.
Wait, say this story again.
Millions of people mourn today as actress Selena Gomez was
This is a boner. It's a boner. Is everybody getting a boner because you said Selena Gomez?
Okay.
Found dead in her Los Angeles.
No, you can go for it.
I can go for it now.
Okay. Yeah, the Chris Griffin dream.
A real dream I had where I saw Chris Griffin at the mall.
I talk about it a lot.
It turned into a viral video.
And Joe Chill said it has Adult Swim vibes.
It was a little bit Adult Swim vibes
because of the absurdity of the premise.
The absurdity of the premise and the property
which is a Turner property.
True.
Adult Swim has the rights for it.
Does the reruns, yeah of course.
So I looked into this dream
which I believe what this means is two things.
I had a dream about a famous person, Chris Griffin.
This could mean that he is my role model.
If you dream about a famous person that you admire,
it could indicate that you see them as a role model
or that you are seeking guidance and inspiration from them.
And I was inspired to do this video.
So it actually--
- That doesn't surprise me, I guess,
that Chris Griffin would be like a role model for you.
Yeah, well I have my own evil monkey problems of my own.
You have and you pattern a lot of your life after Chris Griffin I would say.
But here's the other thing.
You pulled into the milk thing.
Here's the other thing.
That shit was funny man.
That was funny.
Here's the other part of this.
Celebrity culture.
If you dream about a famous person that you do not know personally, it could indicate
that you were struggling with the pressure of celebrity culture or that you were feeling
overwhelmed with the media's obsession with fame and success.
So this is you coping with your status as one of the biggest celebs in the universe.
I guess.
This is after, you know, I'm going to have my own free form.
If right now is any indication.
If Patrick Night Live goes.
If Patrick Night Live happens, I'm going to be stressed out about celebrity culture.
I'm also going to be stressed out about walking, talking human tornadoes that exist in the
future.
Have you ever dreamed about a walking, talking human tornado?
No, but I have dreamed about...
Three nights ago I had a dream that I befriended an old Italian Long Island mechanic guy.
Is this true?
This is true.
All of these are true, yes?
These are all true.
They are all written down in my notes app.
I woke up in the morning and I told my girlfriend, I said I had the most amazing dream.
It was playing that Queen song, "Ooooh, you're making me live."
I was hearing that in my head while we were having marble races in his fort and everything.
And at the end of the dream I tried to hug him and he said, "Don't hug me, that's gay."
Wow.
Wow. You have a very lively dream world life. Yeah. Well, so... Have you ever done lucid
dreaming? Maybe that's what it was. Maybe in my brain I was creating all of this. If
you woke up in your dream and realized you were dreaming and you could do whatever you
want, you would just hang out with a guy in Long Island? Yeah. Wow. That really doesn't
surprise me I guess. And he told me hugging another man is gay. I shouldn't hug him. Different
dream plots about an old man. Number one, the number one thing, the most common types
of old man dreams is about, the most common types of old man dreams is about an old man
as an authority figure providing guidance in almost all cases. It's smart to follow
this old man's advice. He told me to try to not hug him because that would be gay. I had
to stop hugging all of my male friends. You're not a big hugger, I don't think. Are you?
I think I am. I don't think that's what was being told to me in my dream. I don't think
you've ever hugged me. I think I have. I don't think so, man. Well, I'm definitely not going
to do it right now. Do it right now. No, the dream world told me no. He got denied by the
dream world. I was denied by the dream world. I cannot hug anyone. I cannot hug any male
friends. This is another dream that I've talked about a lot on this show. It's a dream that
my older brother had called the poop dream. I've talked every which way about it, but
for the people who don't know, it's a reoccurring nightmare that my older brother has had since
he was five. A doctor comes into a room where my brother is strapped onto an operating table
and the doctor cuts his butt off and poop goes everywhere, which is not for all the medical
students who listen to this not going to happen. If you cut off someone's, that's not how it
where the butt does not. It's not a it does not hold all of that holds poop all day long.
It's part of it's basically just a cushion. It has almost nothing to do with poop, but
do basically nothing. It's the butthole that you have to worry about. You really need to
worry about this thing. The butthole is more important than the butt. By a mile.
It's basically the butt is the butthole shell. Yeah. And think of a butt like a
peanut. Yeah exactly. Well sure. Or a turtle. Yeah any animal. Any animal with a
shell. Yeah a turtle is actually a really yeah a turtle is not a shell.
Basically the same exact as a butt. The same exact thing as a butt. So I looked
into this dream because I mean he's probably never looked into it. He's just
told me about it a lot and good news for him, wealth is about to surprise him. Wealth is
about to, dream experts associate many poop dreams with money and prosperity which is
a good omen. You may not be looking for gains in a business venture or a job promotion but
the universe is about to reward your best efforts with surprising good fortune and that's
good. He does a lot of scratchers and sports betting. So this is amazing news for him.
This is amazing. Every single time that he has this poop dream. Money. Money. Money.
Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money.
Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money.
And so this got me interested in other poop dreams.
This is a dream from Reddit that I'll read for you right now.
"Why do I keep having these gross dreams? I want to start
this off by saying I have no poop obsessions. My relationship
with poop is normal. Face palm emoji." Face palm, girl face palm.
"For girl, face palm emoji. Friday night I had a dream that
I ate poop. In my dream it was gross, but not as gross as eating poop would
would usually be after I ate it. I realized I had to be somewhere to meet
people and didn't have a toothbrush and had poop in my teeth. As a result, I was
picking tiny bits of poop out of my teeth and just flicking them everywhere.
In my head, I was thinking, damn, I'm making a mess.
I'm gonna regret this when I need to clean it up, but I kept doing it. It was
really bizarre. TLDR, I keep having poop dreams and it's bothering me. The answer
that I found for this
which this image is so crazy. This is the image that you found? Okay. This was
from the website that I was consulting to find the answers. For people listening,
this is a picture of kind of a nebula with a plate, clipboard, a fork and a
knife and a spoon, an entire table setting overlaid on top of it. Over a
galaxy and the...
No poop seen anywhere. The title says, "Why do we dream of eating poop?"
Why do we?
Well,
Experts believe that dreaming of poop is a sign of something more spiritual.
They believe that the dream is a signal from our subconscious mind urging us to
pay attention to our innermost feelings.
Dreams can be a way for us to explore our deepest desires and
learn more about ourselves.
Conclusion, if you dream about eating poop, you want to eat poop.
>> Like it's like it's a- >> It's a subconscious desire.
>> It's like dreaming about somebody and then you're like, I want to marry that
person.
or you dream about like a big steak and you want to go eat a big steak.
I have that dream pretty often.
Yeah, me too.
This next thing here.
Oh, yeah.
This is another poop eating dream that I found.
All of these are poop.
No, there's a good chunk of them.
I only have one poop thing.
What does a dream of an alligator eating your dog poop mean?
Last night, I dreamed that there were three small alligators under my bed
and all three of them came out facing me.
One of the alligators started eating my dog poop.
My dog and I was on the bed.
Nobody answered this sadly.
No, this question does not have any answers. No, this is on Cura. There is
no answers for this and I was wondering maybe you could shine some light under
this. Why this person would dream that three small alligators would come out
from under their bed and eat their dog. This feels like a I mean this feels
like
what's the what's the last book of the Bible
revelation revelations feels like a revelations dream. The dream given to
Paul or John or whoever about the empire.
Oh my God, and then one day this happens to them.
Yeah, this is like the serpent coming out of the water.
This is like a, I think this is allegorical.
Uh-huh. I think what this person should do is stay away completely from Louisiana.
Yeah, well that's the thing. The thing that sucks so much about dreams is you might have this dream,
an alligator ate my dog poop, and you might think this is about the fall of the Roman Empire.
Yeah.
This is what this is going to be. Okay, I know the future.
know the future. But then yeah, one day it just fucking happens.
Yeah. One day, you wake up, the alligators come out of your bed,
they start eating your dog's poop, and you're sitting there,
you're calling animal control, and you're saying, "Guys, I thought that
this was an allegory. It turns out I was seeing the future." It's an
alligator. Yeah, exactly. It's an alligator dream. It's an alligator
dream. Yep, and you have allegations that you're alleging that these alligators
ate a dog's shit. Which, by the way... Which is not illegal. It's not
illegal but the thing that's like weirding me out a little bit, why you got dog poop
on your floor constantly that it's just laying around and you're worried that alligators
are going to get it? Buddy, you should be worried about your dog getting it and your dog eating
its own poop.
It means they have a low fiber. The other day Phil ate an entire one of his shits.
before he and he looked your face before you came in. Not true. I looked your face
to wake you up. He drank water. It okay. All right. All right. There's next one.
No answers. I was hoping you could answer this one. Have you ever dreamed
about this boy in your back garden with animals pooping on him and he's eating
it in your house? It's in a dry place.
I haven't
let me ask. Let me ask you this question again. Okay. Have you ever dreamed about
this boy in your backyard garden with animals pooping on him and he's eating
it and your house is in a dry place. So what is in a dry place like a desert
would I mean
all these
yeah, there's a lot going on here. I would say I've really never had any kind
of dreams like this. This is a never had a dream about this boy in your back
garden with animals pooping on him and he's eating it and your house is in a
dry place. I mean you'd have to specify the animals man like yeah, this is all
the animals of the forest. This is not, yeah, I mean all the animals of the ark. This is
not ringing a bell for me. No, I've never really had my house in a dry place. No, I
haven't said it. Can't say I've had that dream either. So yeah, I guess there's no answer
for this one. I don't think you'll ever get an answer. These are some other dreams. No
poop at all. Okay, this is by Steven 14. Back when I was 11 years old, I had a dream about
me being in my mother's room and she told me there was a mentally retarded psychotic
man same mentality as leatherface from texas chainsaw with hydrocephalus was going to kill
my stuffed animals and that I needed to save them before it was too late, referring to
them as real life people or creatures. What was so creepy about the whole dream was that
over all the suspense of almost going into my room where the hydrocephalus psycho is and
my toys were at, as I almost walked into the room I heard singing sheep. As I almost entered
through the doorway the dream ended right there. There was almost like a weird connection
and the dream as if the psychotic mentally challenged man with hydrocephalus was my brother and
the stuffed animals was my children?
It was very chilling and surreal of a dream of eccentric messages that didn't quite tell
me but I learned on my own in a very low-key and vague way.
This is from Steven and this was I think 12 years ago he asked this, which he was 14,
12 years ago.
my research on when I consulted the dreams, all the other dream experts, what they said
is that, "Steven, you are wasting your time. Your emotions are turbulent. You know something
bad is about to happen and you tend to hurt others. Your dream is a reflection of your
own desires and I hope you get the help you so desperately need, Steven." I realize this
is 12 years ago. We don't know what happened to Steven 14, the most prolific murderer in
the world. He could be the smiley face killer. Holy shit.
who fucking knows man. He could have hydrocephalus and be deranged. Hydrocephalus, I would say
I wouldn't be that scared of anybody with hydrocephalus. My cousins got it. Doesn't it, do you just
have water in your head? You just get your head's a little big. Do they take the water
out? Yeah, you gotta get like a shunt. Yeah, see that's not, I'm not scared of anybody
with a shunt. Yeah. There's next one. Does it mean anything that I'm straight and had
a gay dream. I think this is the last one I had. I consulted two people. This is a Q-ora
question.
Why do you call it Q-ora?
Quora?
Quora.
Quora. Q-ora is how I say it. There's two things. There's two answers to this possibly.
You need some attention. You have dreams of being gay because you lack attention and affection
from the people around you. You are feeling lonely because of circumstances in your life.
That's one side of the coin.
So they're saying that you're gay for attention.
you're gay for attention. That's one side of the coin. The other side of the coin trouble
is coming. Oh no. You if you suddenly had a dream of being gay or you had a lesbian dreams
at night, it might mean that a problem is coming your way. So there's two sides. There's
there's you know, I was looking at this. There's two possible answers. But thankfully, this
woman was answered by Big Jay. Oh,
yes,
really answered by Big Jay Ocreson from the from the agent of skanks podcast and
he said it's just a stupid dream. I dream all kind of crazy shit like
barbecuing with a duck and getting robbed by a cat. It's just a dream. Relax.
If you're straight, you know you love woman, so it should be clear that the
dream is just a bunch of bullshit and I just want to look at his profile picture
him with a gorilla grip on a can of monster energy.
This has to be actually him.
It has to be the real Big Jay.
It says he knows Italian. This is him.
This is the real Big Jay Oakerson. Yeah. Well, that's all my stuff.
Okay. Go over to Dreams Caleb.
Dream Caleb. I'd love to see that collab.
Do you think I'm a dream boat?
I think you look like Dreams Mask.
Okay. Moving on.
slash dream analysis. This comes from her Pacifica. Okay, I need help with this
sexual dream. So I have a friend who I used to go to boarding school with. I've
seen him three times since I left and his mom is always over welcoming. She's
very attractive with the body of a goddess. Last night, I kept having dreams
that she was coming on to me blatantly. For example, in the dream, she put her
boobs in my face, sit on lap, etc. What does all this mean? I doubt that it means
that she wants to sleep with me. So what is it? Feedback greatly appreciated. I
I included this because I think this guy's definitely just asked. He's just
hoping somebody
responds like this means she wants to. She wants that D. She jumped into your
dream to put her boobs in your face. She's dreaming about you and she's
dreaming about putting her boobs in your face. That's what this means. Dream
about someone telling me to buy beer.
This is from Adderall 5150. That's an amazing user name. It's a great name.
That is so fucking good. Had a dream earlier today about my dad telling me to buy a certain
type of beer this weekend. Can't remember the name of it and he told me that the beer
can would be worth a lot of money very soon. What does this mean? I think that's pretty
cut and dry what that means. It means he wants to be your dad. Go bring your dad a beer. Your
dad wants a fucking beer. This is not that complicated Adderall 5150. Yeah. Dream, this
is just the name. Dreaming of killing snakes, then snakes becoming tiny and developing fish
I'm pregnant.
Matt Farris Okay, that, I can tell you this one.
I've consulted a lot of dream experts recently online.
This means either, I mean, same as like dreaming about being gay, your baby is going to die
or your baby is going to grow up and become gay.
Ryan Seacrest Oh shit.
Wait, why?
Matt Farris Because snakes, phallic.
Ryan Seacrest Oh true.
Matt Farris Fish heads are, I think, a little bit gay.
What's gay about a fish head? Eyes on the side of it.
Gay side eye? Gay side eye, exactly.
World of Warcraft dream. Whoa, from GXViper98.
This means, sound crazy, but hear me out. I was playing this game, World of Warcraft,
when I decided to join a group for a raid on a dungeon. The leader was JK Simmons.
Wow. Yes, the J.K. Simmons. People were telling me about his very strict rules
about his raids where people were actually dying in real life. I remember
his game name was Dr. Rain. Think of his character in the movie Whiplash, but a
hundred times more insane. Anyway, we start the raid and everything goes off
without a hitch. I mean, we were tearing through this place at record speed. We
reached one of the bosses that was known to be pretty tough. The Doc, that's what
calls up the doc, made sure if anyone screw up, they would pay the consequences. We start
the battle and it was going well. Then one of our key players starts to lag behind. He
was given a warning, but it continues. So doc banishes him from the game, never to play
again. I don't remember much after that. What could this mean?
Then it says, "I think they fell asleep while they were writing."
What the fuck could this mean?
Well, okay. The first part about this, we already said, I mean, we already touched upon that
with the Chris Griffin dream. Oh, so this could mean as an idol. Yeah, it sees J.K. Simmons
as an idol or GX Viper is really, really like upset or concerned with celebrity culture and
like there maybe GX Viper is a secret celebrity that we don't know. What could GX be? This
could be G, G first initial first name that's coming to my head, George Lopez. This could
could be G L because he replaced Latin X G X Latin X George Lopez Viper 98 born in
98 or he's 98 years old or yeah. One of the two could be 98. He could be born on
double day. He could he could be born on double sleep. There's leap day and
there's double day scary. Yeah, high school, a fem boy and non stop coming
Dave for eagles. I had this dream where I was back in high school. I graduated a
time ago. My father was teaching mechanics to students. I asked to take his class. He
said no. I was then walking in the school hallway. All my friends and family, along
with some of my old teachers, were there. But none would let me in class till I got
a GF. I found this cute Asian femboy/twin. We kissed and then he bent down and blew me.
After he got done blowing me, I couldn't stop coming. No matter how hard I tried, I
was gushing like mad. I was coming hard. He even put my cock in his ass. He said it would
be okay till we got to the nurse. He seemed to really like me shooting
myself into his ass. He even said it was nice. Once I removed my cock,
it was still shooting. Any idea what this means?
What could this mean, man? What could this possibly mean? I don't know.
I really don't know what this could mean. You know what I'll say?
If I had this dream, this is what I would say. That probably means
nothing. Yeah.
I would wake up... It doesn't mean anything. If I had this dream,
I would wake up and then I would just say like, "Oh, Jesus."
I wouldn't even write this one down. I wouldn't even journal this one because it's so unimportant.
This one means nothing, man.
It means absolutely nothing.
Don't ever think about this one again.
No, no, no.
It's that fucking simple.
There's nothing going on in your brain.
No. Your brain is completely fine. There's no questions to be answered here. This means
nothing.
This is basically, it's like you had a dream about going to the store.
Yeah, this is, it's completely, it's nothing. Sometimes dreams are just dreams, man. Don't
worry about it too much Dave. The pink pickle milkshake. A 30 something male
dressed as little Bo Peep with curly brown locks drinks a pink pickle milkshake
in a pastel pink milkshake parlor. He stands in it alone in the middle of the
room. A Chinese friend from growing up is two generations younger again. In real
life an older version lived in Hollywood in the milkshake MTV video singer
boyfriend's house. Again celebrity. She has a small bar apartment with bar tables.
She uses the bar tables as a bed for her baby and guests.
This is again, again, celebrity MTV superstar.
The pink milkshake though. I am wondering what that could mean.
Yeah, I didn't see much about a pink pickle milkshake when it comes to the drink.
Pink pickle. Pink pickle.
A pink pickle milkshake.
Let's dissect that. Pink pickle.
This is phallic.
It's very phallic.
But it's also feminine.
It's pink, the divine feminine. It's phallic, the divine masculine.
This is a confluence of man and woman. This means that you need to get married.
Yes, and the milkshake is the pink pickle milkshake.
The milkshake is the pink pickle. The pink pickle phallus produces milk, sperm.
And you shake the balls to make it come.
shake the balls to make it come into the pink, creating a baby, your two generations younger
again Asian friend, Chinese friend, MTV, what does the MTV logo look like? A house. You are
going to have a long prosperous future. Yes. And you will bear a child. You will have a
Chinese baby. Yep. You will have a completely Chinese baby with your pink milkshake wife.
welcome Dan Bernard's Mind. We're doing a lot more than this other guy who said a pink
pickle milkshake never heard of it. We never heard of it and we came up with a conclusion.
And little Bo Peep means that your Chinese friend will become a girl.
My weirdest dream with a rapper. This is from Sasha 3. In my dream I had sex with a rapper
named Busta Rhymes. He and I were love making. I had my pajamas on but his entire body was
silver except his face. Busta would hold me while kissing me on my neck. When he
morphed into a liquid, Busta would kiss me on my stomach. I really loved him and
the sex. The dream ended when he told me that he loved me, tickled and hugged me,
gave me a kiss on the forehead, cheek, neck, and lips. When he was a watery figure
of himself and he morphed into a silver liquid and left. This is what he looked
like but didn't include a photo. But this got a response and analysis. Okay. Sounds
like you met an entity. There are discussions on what they are. An atheist view is that
it is compartments of our brain communicating with itself so that we experience ourself
meeting a different person. The dream state allows this split because it frees the mind
to play with itself. People who are more spiritual believe it is spirits, souls who exist in
an ethereal plane, hanging out. These entities are quite normal. If you search "vapor vape,"
"synth wave," and "outrun art," they are quite prevalent. I think they meant "vapor wave."
they did. It is also a bit like the liquid Terminator. I guess it is some kind of machine
entity. However, it deals with poetry. These do exist. Poetry, raps, rhymes, busta. Busta
is one of the greatest poets of all time. These do exist. You can encounter them during
dreams and you will notice it whenever they do appear because they will give you a poem.
My personal opinion is that you have been visited by a black spore print on tin foil
who became liquid culture. What's a black spore print on tin foil? I don't know, but
It's not a good thing to call Busta Rhymes.
No, it's not a very kind thing to say about Busta.
It's a very rude thing to call Busta Rhymes, man.
That's one of the best ever.
Garrick McFly.
And then the last one, "Dream Meaning of Poop."
It might be intriguing to see yourself pooping in your dreams,
but it does happen. Discover with me the dream
meaning of pooping in a toilet or pooping on the floor
within other feces dream
interpretations. Did you click this YouTube video here?
I have the link here. We don't
have to watch it. We can if Jubio can get it to work,
but it just has a
really good title. So I do kind of want to at least show the title.
I do want to see what this title is.
Let's see. I mean...
It's a lady and her husband who do dream analysis on YouTube.
That's interesting.
What is it? 30 seconds long, this video?
No, no, this is an ad.
Oh, okay.
Goddamn ads.
Yeah, goddammit.
It's time to get YouTube premium.
But this is...
Poop dreams, dream meaning of pooping in toilet, taking a crap on the floor.
Okay, wait, because this could actually help the alligator person a lot,
because they're saying a dream about taking a crap on the floor, right?
Yeah. Their dog is taking a crap on the floor.
So maybe, okay, now that I'm thinking of that,
okay,
taking a crap on the floor, your dog is taking a crap on the floor,
that is a different entity other than yourself, right?
So, as stated in the Busta Rhymes thing, your mind is playing with itself.
So you're playing with the idea.
Your dog is pooping on the floor.
Your dog is you.
That's a separate, your own separate mind entity.
Your brain is now, you're saying your dog is an extension of yourself.
You want to poop on your floor and you want those.
The alligators come eat the poop off the floor.
The alligators are representative, again, of yourself.
- Look at this emoji.
They used the poop from the emoji movie.
Pooping in good toilet seat.
Wait, play this really quick.
I just wanna hear a little bit of this.
I didn't watch the whole thing.
- If the toilet was in good condition,
it wasn't broken or dirty,
and you saw yourself pooping in this particular toilet,
it means that you are doing your best
to handle and manage tough circumstances
that you are currently experiencing
Wow.
And that you are certainly progressing in all the areas of your life.
Okay, we can combine this with the definition I just came with.
This dream means that you need to get yourself situated and make better choices.
When you're stressing too much about a particular matter, you're not going to think clear and
straight.
That is why it is best to let go of things that you cannot manage and work with the things
that you can fix.
Why does she seem like she just...
Okay, here we go.
If you try to go potty on the toilet and it landed on the floor, it means that you need
to have a better attitude towards life.
Oh.
Let go of resentment, anger, guilt.
Okay.
All of those things block you from achieving your true purpose.
Taking a dump in the bedroom.
Bedroom?
Taking a dump in your own room, this indicates that you are feeling guilt about something
that you have done and now you find yourself in a situation that it is hard to get out.
Okay. Very sticky situation. So the dog... You should solve that when the dog is the extension
of the self. Alternatively to this... Wait, let her finish. Let her finish. Diarrhea.
This can predict severe bad health for the one that is dreaming about this.
I'm Eva, a dream consultant and thank you so much for watching. I invite you to please subscribe,
We have to subscribe and we have to ask her a question. We have to ask her what this alligator
poop dream means because I am freaking myself out trying to think of it because now it's
like if the dog is the extension of the person's self and the dog is pooping on the floor.
Jimmy is going to ask him. I have a dream where three small alligators come out from
under the bed and they eat the dog poop. What could this possibly mean?
They start eating the dog poop I have laying on the floor.
They were also, their house was also in a dry place or was that the boy getting pooped
on by the animals?
No, that was the boy getting pooped on by the animals.
And then Jubia, really quickly, what is that Spanish comment?
What does that mean?
Okay, the emoji.
What is the significance of having a bathroom with no poop?
Is that what that says?
Yeah, it's asking like you go to the bathroom, but there's no poop.
That's credit. The only time in my life. I've ever been able to say it and say
you will die in Spanish.
You are going to die.
It's the only time in my life that I've ever been able to translate a
Spanish sentence. All right, that's amazing. So if you guys have any dreams
and you want us to analyze, I think that we should definitely do this episode
again with Cameron. Yeah, and with the with the we'd like to hear your dreams.
So let us know anything that we need to tell people about. Go check out the
Patreon. I'm gonna weirdly be I'm at some college in Pennsylvania tomorrow
doing stand up, but I don't remember the name of the college. Oh yeah, you're
opening for our friend Neil. Are you guys? Yeah, co show together. I think
I'm gonna just do probably four minutes. Yeah, you're opening for Neil Linsky.
Yeah, I don't remember what the name of the college is, but if you go to a
college in Pennsylvania, there's like some percentage chance I'll be there
tomorrow. Maybe just look up Neil Linsky, Pennsylvania College address.
Yeah, just don't, don't, we'll, here, wait, actually, I'll, no, I don't need,
who cares? You should plug it. Nobody's gonna be, I mean, nobody from this is
gonna be there. You don't know that. There could be. I know that, I know that.
I'm just doing it 'cause he needs somebody to drive him, so I'll do it.
Okay. Alright, bye everybody. Bye bye.
Welcome back to Fox 54, serving Los Angeles.
We're here with comedian and podcaster, Cameron Fetter.
Cameron, how are you doing today?
- I'm supposed to answer.
So I would do stuff like that.
- Yeah.
- And I would maybe, I'd probably watch a few hundred hours
of Michael Cera to train myself like an AI
to learn his mannerisms.
- You know what I, you just, the thing is about
if you do the news, if you do one of these news shows,
I'm not saying yes unless it's one of the episodes where they bring a monkey out.
Yeah.
Why is every local news channel gotten?
Listen, listen, listen.
Okay.
Wow, wow.
That, first of all, that's why it should be on the news.
Yeah.
Because you make your clip go viral.
I'm going to give you your D.D. Mega Doodoo moment.
D.D. Mega Doodoo?
What was the der hap of, what was that other one?
Where the lady had a stroke on the thing, or she said she had some kind of brain episode.
I remember the guy throwing up on himself in an Xbox.
In an Xbox video?
Smallest guy.
Video is a very small team.
Xbox can render things of any size.
That's a good point.
But listen, put me, they're bringing these guys on the day news, right?
Bring the days on the guy news!
Yeah.
They've got, listen, they've got Patrick talking about how he's allergic to carrots.
They're bringing on Girl God to talk about tanning, tanning hacks and all this daytime bullshit.
Man, bring me on for the breaking news!
Yeah.
yeah, yeah, me up when there's a killer loose when terror there in 30 seconds,
not a problem. I will camp out outside of your new studio for something real
till some kind of until something really, really bad happening happens.
Get me in there and then I show up and I go, I come in, I'm doing the
bits. Yeah, yeah, exactly. I'm doing bits, man. Yeah, yeah, I'm acting Michael
Sarah. Hey, who am I? Hey, here's my present that 15 year old kid who's
walking down the highway at the wrong time.
We're both on there and this is the guy that comes in, "We're gonna kill a kid.
We're gonna kill a 15 year old kid."
And here's BeatWad.
"Oh my god.
Oh my god about Kid Bob."
"Oh my god, those two comedians on the nerds are so funny."
*Demonic Laughter*