Okay, all right, do we still do a clap or you're just don't know we don't do
it.
He comes back and now we have to explain that to explain how really
everything is now on the shit yeah, that's all we talked about where you're
going. Oh yeah, we cry, you're right and cried and complained, okay, because you
were gone and we didn't have anybody to do stuff like turn all these little
knobs yeah. Well, you don't touch the knobs yeah, that's the first that's your
his mistake. Well, here's my first thing that is my problem. The faders the
first thing is touching all the I didn't you I was rotating these cables. I was
trying to they don't want to give rotating them yeah. I was trying to
rotate me to change the volume like switch them. Oh, like this yeah, but I
didn't work at all. They don't know you rotate these ones yeah, that does
something yeah.
there's tell there's not enough dials on this soundboard. There's a lot of
bunch of virtual ones. See it, say look, look at this. I thought that was a
need his tech wizardry back because I wanted to install doom on this the whole
damn time yeah yeah. Well, I think we could do maternal. You can honestly
install doom anything on anything day, but can it run any crisis on yes? Wow,
you can install crisis on doom these days for it. Fuck me yeah. Could you
build a minecraft computer. Did you guys ever watch these videos? Yeah, they build
the computer. They build stuff in minecraft out of some kind of stone. I'm
not sure what colour it was, but they built some kind of, well,
named after the CEO of I don't think it was red, Sumner Redstone. But whatever
this stone is they use, they made a Pokemon game and they made a Tetris in
Pokemon Red. Yep, was the first Pokemon game for this, because of the stone.
Can we stop fucking arguing? You've been here five minutes, we're already
I'm not starting any arguments. I'm so excited. I'm so, so happy to have you
back. I'm happy to be back. Can I tell you I'm so happy to be back in the
United States?
Yeah.
I really, can I say something completely honestly from the bottom of my heart? I
want you to. Every time I go, 'cause I went to Mexico this year. Yes. I loved,
I loved, I've been really, I have never been this worldly before. This is the
year of my being worldly. You're travelling for us. I went to Mexico, okay,
and I thought this is incredible. This is the best country I've ever been in in my
life. This is I'm having a beautiful time. I'm seeing beautiful things. I'm
meeting beautiful people and friendly people who aren't beautiful
and that's okay. And I'm thinking and it's okay to not be beautiful. Well, if
you're very friendly, it's okay to not be beautiful. If you're not friendly
though and you're ugly, I can smack you. Yeah, man, legally, it's easy. I can do
smack the shit, but I'm thinking maybe the US, maybe you know, maybe all my
life, maybe the US just as it sucks. Maybe it's if it's not as good as
Mexico. Yeah, maybe I maybe I'm mistaken. I go to Ireland.
The US is a million times better than I of
thank you. It's horrible. Yes, can I can I tell you a fun fact what about
here's something you might not know about about Irish people that I learn
from our tour guide. Okay, so apparently one of the most unique things about
Irish people is a social custom. They have only in Ireland. Apparently these
people they drink socially wow that's what they told and it's actually
customary for when an Irishman goes to a pub. He'll actually sometimes buy a
round of drinks for his friends and this is a social custom in Ireland. Oh,
that kind of defines their culture. That actually would be nice to do here to
drink socially. I know it's a shame that only Ireland does that yeah, but I mean
yeah, that's it's just kind of a custom. They built their and also here's
another fact I learned not from the torque well indirect. The tour guide
didn't tell me this, but I learned indirectly through the tour guides
actions, which is that Irish people every day for lunch. They eat
Thanksgiving dinner.
Really, you just learn this from a
they have they have a race. They have restaurants that are like chipotle, but
for Thanksgiving Turkey, you great, you pick Turkey or ham and then you pick
mashed potatoes or roast potatoes. You are you have that they have the
knees shield and they go through the metal cafeteria. Okay, and it's the
worst food you've ever eaten in your life. I imagine it's really bad, but
sometimes they call it carvery. Sometimes I kind of want oh yeah, but
that's, but that's, but that's what I'm saying that's there, but so yeah, of
course, sometimes you kind of want that right yeah, but which also you also you
want you want the mashed potatoes. You want the meat. You don't want the
boiled carrots and the boil cabbage. That shit is fucking disgusting nasty
thing. I want to taste like literally nothing, but here's yeah. Sometimes you
want that. Of course, sometimes you want that. That's why we have thanksgiving.
we get it once a year, maybe twice a year. If you have a special family,
whole month of
but these people, they have a restaurant. Every restaurant does this every
this is their
that's what they do. That is their hot dogs. They said that's yeah, they're
instead of being like I'm going to go get sweet green at lunch. They're like
I'm going to go get Thanksgiving dinner, so I have a question. They go to the
carvery in the in betweeners in the first episode. That's not Ireland. You
can't slap me. That's really it's not okay to do that. Sorry that I know I
how strong I am. Whoa, you are the ultimate slapper. That's the first time
I ever slapped you. You slap me all day. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? That's the first time I've ever slapped you. You slap
all the time, but I don't complain because you're weak. Yes.
Tell me. Yes. Were the people in Ireland- You'd better- You slapped me again.
That coffee's going. Were they as big and as fat as you could possibly imagine?
Yeah, here's another Ireland fact. How do you get fat eating that shit? That's
what I'm saying. Here's another Ireland fact. You think- What do you mean? Okay,
America's America's the how do you get fatty big thanksgiving every day?
Makes no sense. I'm drinking Guinness
every night. This is a low calorie beer Guinness at lunch. Is it really yeah?
It's only four percent alcohol, low alcohol percentage, low alcohol
percentage. Isn't that funny you all? They that's the other thing that you're
like yeah, we drink like eight Guinness is a night. Yeah, like it's actually two
percent alcohol. Yeah, I think it's nine. That's a rattler. It's twelve hours.
Poor is like barely a hundred calories. They're pussies, but yeah, so
people in America are fat, you'll hear that from the news and the media and you
walk around. Maybe you'll see some chubby people, but I would say maybe the top
three fattest people I've ever seen in my life were all in the past week in
Ireland.
I knew it to most of them are not most of them are not that fat, but you'll
some you'll see you'll see some big ones. You'll see some crazy looking old
people. Do they have the vest on? Do they have a stop watch? They have full
full protruding yeah, the big fucking beer beer gut from all the over their
that bats could live under.
- Yes.
- Could go up and make a
- A pensioner's nest.
- A very nice nest.
- It's called a pensioner's gut.
- It hangs out so far forward.
- It's called a pensioner's gut?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- What is a pensioner's gut?
- A pensioner is an old person
who's on retirement.
- Somebody who's on, yeah,
they get social security.
- Uh-huh.
And I made up pensioner's gut.
I think that maybe--
- That's a good thing.
- How seniors can maintain a healthy gut.
Yeah, see they all look like this over there.
- That's what I would be doing
if I was walking around with Thanksgiving
in my belly every day. That would be I mean no wonder they've never made
anything interesting in terms of no art. They also have the most musing history
of all time yeah. You go to these amazing you go to these amazing historical
castles yeah, which first of all they're there's castles, so the castles are so
cool because it's their ancient castles from the year nine hundred or whatever
before they even knew they were irish. You see these incredible well also most
of them were not built by irish people. They're built by the vikings who are
debating so exactly. I even do the cool thing in their
person is in charge of all the people who are coming and dominating them and
ruining their lives forever. Yeah,
you go there and it's the the most incredible thing you've ever seen in
your life. We went to this old, like crumbling, like Abbey. That was like
these ruins in the middle of a field. It literally looked like Lord of the
Rings, and I was talking to the tour guide, who was this old guy who had
lived in that town like his entire life. I was just talking to him about about
it and I was like yeah. This is so beautiful, like the sky is so blue and
these ruins are incredible and he's like yeah. I don't know you kind of take it
for granted. It sucks
I can imagine well, but yeah, I'm living there living in the coolest place of all
time did I mean we wake up every day. We see the statue of liberty in the Empire
State Building right outside our window and we I mean I'm not every American
thing is bullshit, though we don't have castles Hearst Castle. Where's that? We
don't have as much California. That's also most of the castles in Ireland
California Castle. I one of its got it's made out of like fucking it's made
-Hurst Castle is the guy, William Randolph Hurst that -Oh yeah, is this the one that the
house is all traps and trap doors and stuff? Or no, no, no, no, that's the Winchester mansion.
-That's a hotel. -The Winchester, the one where the person who made the rifles, so they
have all the doors that goes to nowhere. -Well, that's a lady who, she was a widow.
-Haunted by the ghosts of all the people that she was a widow. -Yeah, she was a widow.
it's a lady who she was she was haunted by the ghosts of all the people that
were killed by the Winchester rifle. And she was building a big house to escape
them. That's a different story. That's cool. The Hearst Castle is basically
this guy who's really, really rich. William Randolph Hearst. Yeah, he built
a... He's the one that Citizen Kane's based on? Yeah, he built a giant house
that was made... It's made out of... Xanadu. Yeah, it's made out of random
shit from other... He has a
tenth century, like like a church, yeah, like walls and so that's the thing
about a lot of the castles to that we visited, like a lot of the cool ones
are the ones that are completely fallen apart and are like authentic or
whatever, because most of the castles you'll go in and it's like this huge,
like a table, it's it's it's huge and it's got like the fucking it's all
built up and it's giant. You go up spiral staircases and stuff and you'll
the tour guide will be like yeah. So this castle was originally built in the
year seven hundred A. D. And the only thing remaining from that time is this
wall right here and the rest of it we all built ten years ago.
Yes, I know this. I hate that saying. We restored it. They do that in Boston,
too. I remember going to the Paul Revere house and they were like, "This
is not even Paul Revere's house, by the way. This is what it would have
looked like if he had a craftsman style." Is that the one in downtown?
No, it's in the north end. No, no. I'm thinking of... I remember going to
Paul Revere's house as a kid. Yeah, didn't somebody who fucking... Being
like, "This is Gary." It's sucked. It's $20 to walk... And it's a house
from from the
seventeen hundred, so it's one room. What kid in Boston also get learns about
Paul Revere every year from kindergarten to eighth grade is like fuck. I want to
see his house. I need to see that I want to see his horse. I'm so I'm so the
get a talk about it. The house, the house doesn't come into the story at
all. You get your burnout dude, complete revere burn. Yeah, I like his beach
actually hate his beach. I
he's got a bad word. It's like Revere Beach Hampton Beach. No Hampton Beach is
over. It is way better. There's no one there for a reason. That's true. All
there's like Kelly's yeah, they have a cat. That's it. That's the only
fucking good. Yeah, Hampton Beach is fire and Kelly's is not even good. No,
but it's the only it's the only food they have like a boardwalk with one
restaurant, the worst beach ever Kelly's is I mean it's though, but it's not good.
Don't say it. It's it's don't say it. Here's another thing about Irish history.
every single castle you go to. If it as a tower, it was built by an alcoholic.
If it as a tower, they'll tell you every single time that tour guide will tell
you. So this tower was built in this year and then three hundred years later
lightning struck it and blew up the top of it. Every single tower they they
tell you that lightning knocked off the top of the tower. I went to one yeah,
but they said that lightning that lightning blew up half of the town
because it struck the room where they kept all the gun
Ireland really it truly is a land cursed by God that God does not want to
know and try to wipe it off. I mean yeah, they all that's that they don't
even get like they don't get lightning there. It's not hot enough. Normally
it's so rare that every time that lightning is struck, it's destroyed.
So I think a monument to human greatness
yeah Ireland, they're God's strongest people because he's constantly
torturing them. That's why they're all Catholic as somebody who's sixty
percent Irish man. I can say that that's I do not claim a zero. I was
interesting going and listen. I know I'm I'm the only one here who has to I
have to I'm not even defending myself because it's two against one. I know
I'm wearing right now. I know I'm talking a lot of shit and I'm wearing a
shirt that says Ireland on it, but
it's a nice shirt, but one of the shirt it was a hundred dollars. I'm lying.
That's not true at all. You got you got no less than that was in the tourist
store. Yeah, well, I bought it because it was like a normal clothing. You think I
thought they wove it. I saw they sold this at Eddie Murphy Clothing. Yeah,
you think I went to a weaver and an old Irish guy pulled out his loom and made
I thought that this was maybe the football team. I one of I one of my
greatest pleasures is to go that I've learned about this year is to go to a
country and to buy a piece of clothing that says the name of the country. Yeah,
it's good. I have to be doing that for the rest of my life. People do that in
America who live in America. Yeah, people buy shirts that say Montana on them. I
see a shirt. Why the hell are you doing that? New York at least forty times a
walking down the street. Dude showing up in like a shirt that says like Brooklyn
with the Statue of Liberty on it and say he's not even in Brooklyn. Yeah, where
did you get to? Where did you find this shirt? I really don't understand man. They have a shit ton of those.
They buy it in a different city. That's a New York tourist. They get it
somewhere on the West Coast. I have to take this phone call it is regarding my
boot on my car. Oh yeah. You guys continue. Do we just pause it? Alright.
right, okay, he's he got the boot on his car because he's a delinquent who
doesn't pay his bills, yeah, or tickets rather, and he has six children that he
doesn't feed. He's and so for somebody for somebody who's only 60% Irish, yeah,
he's acting like a real, real, here's another, here's another, I just
remembered another thing that made me mad in Ireland. You're, you're, you like
you went there and I had a wonderful time, I've always wanted to go and you
come back and all you do is complain. Listen, let me, let me tell you
something you are such a you would love you would love Dublin. I know that you
would you would fuck with Dublin. I probably like all of it no because the
rest of Ireland is is it's a country that is a museum yeah yeah there's no
it's nothing interesting. It's all you know. I hate museum exactly it's all
towns that are that are one street
and then and then everything else is a poor castle. The pubs are not fun,
except for where there's a lot of people yeah because it's all towns. It's all
it's oh yeah, and there's only like a few people in there. You're stuck
talking to some guys like oh, I used to be a good country and then these
fucking people move you would you would like Dublin, but I don't think that you
would fuck because you also don't like nature and you don't respect God. I
would like the beautiful country of Ireland because it's where now you
would you would be disappointed because you thought you had to like it because
of what you saw, but anyway, I guess something that maybe I don't know
something else that I tour guide said that well. First of all, he was talking
he was talking about he was talking about be going to cork. He's talking about
it's where that's where my my lineage that's where mine is to yeah, but again,
it's we're cousins. We're probably it's it's just nature man yeah.
I mean I don't know I didn't go to the all I went to was Dublin, then a bunch
of castles, so I guess I'm not the expert on it, but I think I think I've
got a pretty good idea of what goes down there.
Where was what was your tour guide saying so he basically so first of all
he said, but toward this tour where I was with my fiance's family, everyone from
the south, he said completely unprovoked. He was just like we were talking about
how bis they called biscuits, cookies or cookies, biscuits or whatever, and he
was like he just completely out of the was like yeah, and I think biscuits and
gravy are disgusting. I think that's the grossest food ever
the fuck
which is making me laugh so hard, not because of thinking that, but just
because of saying that to a group of
eight people for no reason, no reason completely. He was also and so he said
that, but right before that what he had said and and nobody said anything mean
to him about this, which I wanted to kill him after he said this. Yeah, he
said he said one of the Irish delicacies, one of our best delicacies that you guys
have to try is we take two slices of bread. We put butter on them and then we
put crisps in between them and it's called a crisp sandwich and it's the
thing I've ever tasted. I thought that was a, oh never mind, chip buddy is fries.
Chip buddy is fries. Yeah. And he said that was one of the delicacies.
This is the worst country on earth. And then he said biscuits and gravy are disgusting.
This is the worst country on earth. These people need to die. This is so, so bad.
This is getting worse. You always take it way too far. This is getting worse every year. I can't believe we let,
the UN needs to send, we need to send people in all black outfits
to destroy this country. They went and they wore all black outfits and
try to destroy England. I wish that the trouble, I hope the troubles come back 50 times worse.
People's heads are exploding in the middle of the day. This is a bad, bad place. You're
only saying this because there's a boot on your car and you're angry. I just found out
it's going to, they, I hate money. No, you like money. I like money. I'm mad about this
fucking boot. The boot on my car. You're coming in here with a sour attitude. I'm sorry. You
you come in here. You have to come in here. Once the episode start,
nothing bad is ever have to you have to think
about nothing.
You can't you have to be completely that cost me a thousand bucks, plus a
hundred bucks a day until because my my fucking license all right to be a
hundred percent clear. We don't need to talk about this on the show. I just
want to say it's a hundred percent my fault right yeah. I don't my car, my
card, the tags are expired. My insurance is out. I'm everything is I think this
this has been this has been looming over me for a long time. Cast my mind
backwards through time. I think I can walk through maybe fifty memories of you
bragging about not paying a parking ticket over the past few years. You
moving parking tickets from switching your license plate, having your license
plate stolen and saying that now you could get a new license plate and none
of the old tickets attached. I thought that we could claim that the person who
stole my license plate got all those tickets, but
that would have been us reporting the license plate stolen two years after
they stole it because they had two years of tickets anyway. Yeah, I owe a
thousand dollars and then a hundred bucks a day and that's a good get.
We're going to get a we're going to get a bump here. We're just going to get a
bump on the page. We need some please go to the the patron. I need it so so I
wish I could see the I don't since I have no clock of timing. It's a we
started at twelve ten. Okay, anyway, anyway, what do you say? He said eighteen
eighteen eighteen. I would like to say I've been I've been wanting to travel
because I've been interested in some history recently, and I've been watching
this this guy voices of the past on YouTube. Have you ever seen this guy? No,
he does. He reads like first hand accounts of like like primary sources
from when like the first embassies from one country to another in like the the
sixteen hundred and stuff, and I watched the one that was the same or the first
the time that the samurai, the Japanese, their embassy to Mexico. Wow and the
first sounds pretty cool. The first words written by a Mexican about the
Japanese embassy that comes into Mexico City is they have long hair. They kind
of look like girls. That was the
historical record that they have. It was very, very you got to be careful
watching those those history videos on YouTube. I'm addicted to them. I can't
careful on like specific ones, though, because I tried to look up the
difference between like a Cajun and a Creole, and it was a whole race science
video. They
history. I was like I was just trying to figure out what that what that was
because it was sometimes they do in seasoning. Sometimes it's real. You can
really easily stray into some bad history stuff without realizing it. If
you're if you're not, you have to be so hyper vigilant. I was I was going to
make sure that this and this is the most dangerous one, so I had my guard
property league, good or bad,
no even more honestly, even more dangerous than that is if you are
watching videos on youtube about Viking history yeah. Oh yeah, to be so care
about you, you click on one recommended video and you're you're gone, you're
done for because they know exactly how to they know how to say it so that
somebody who doesn't know it's a pipeline. Yeah, there's a the Viking
history stuff is really interesting how they were like the that's like the
people who are the the fucking royal family, the what are they called the
Winds, Windsor's, the Windsor's is that Windsor's is yeah. They claim that
they're like related to the first king of England, but there was like fifteen
kings in the middle that were just Viking guys who just killed enough people
that they there was nobody left to be can Vikings are crazy. You know, like a
bunch of the like Norse mythology stuff has been completely corrupted by or not
corrupted, but like all because of Christian mission missionaries, all
they're like legends that weren't written down, got lost because they got
switched out with like Christian stuff where they were trying to like it's
very crazy. There's a there's a and that's another topic. We have to be
really careful when you watch
but you got a religion. You got to make sure you're going to make sure that the
person who uploads the video that their like profile picture is not like a night
from the crusades or or like you or a statue of it's a statue. Don't click on
it. If they you have to have a fat white guy, this one's counterintuitive, but if
person feels a need to put a disclaimer at the beginning about what they're
talking about. Yeah, that's the danger. That's bad. Yeah, should be pretty.
You always gotta have, you always gotta have a fat white guy with a little
goatee or something, maybe a ponytail. Sometimes you can trust them. They need
to look, yeah, they need to look like, they need to look like a teacher. Yeah,
exactly. Yeah. But that's a slippery slope too. If they're in good shape, no,
no, no, no, no. You see a buff guy talking about Vikings, that is the most,
that guy has done a hate crime. I do not wanna see any of that shit, man.
do not show me that that's going to ruin all my I'm not going to get
recommended any more gambling videos. It's all just going to be this shit.
It's going to be like why do Filipino people ruin property values exactly
it'll be on a history,
yeah,
like Jason history yeah and it's just like these fucking Filipinos moved in
not a good idea.
Another pool halls everywhere. I saw one that was
the voices of the past thing where he was a Chinese guy who went to where to
where Vikings from Norway, Viking, Scandinavia, he goes to Scandinavia,
Scandinavia, right?
I've realized 90 of these videos. He's like first contact videos are just these
people being like I went to this other country. They are disgusting.
Like this entire bit. He was like he was like it's the they're the most
disgusting people. He said they're barely even human. He said that every
morning, a bucket is passed around the entire village and every every man
washes his hair, washes his face, blows his boogers into it and spits in it and
then it goes to the next guy like it's a fucking like pirate movie yeah and
that's what they did every day. What's true? It's disgusting. The Viking I'll
say it do the Viking said almost no sense of hygiene. The Vikings were kind
of gross. They were just people and now you get like like and it's so funny
sorry, like the people like like the buff races, dudes are like well,
Vikings only ate like salted meat and shit and it's like yeah. They were also
fucking stupid. They're also the stupidest people in the world. All they
knew how to do is like rape and pillage. He said they were so yeah. They were
seven feet tall. They may have been stupid, but the the some some other Irish
history stuff is the like cities on the coast who would always get raided by the
the Saxons, the Vikings. They it's something that's so funny to me is that
they would get rated like like every year. They would get rated the same time
of year by the by the Vikings, but always would just know all these people
are pussies and we can beat them in a fight. So it would just come back every
year and fuck everything up and then leave and the town would just be like
oh great and build everything back and get more treasure and stuff. It
actually is
somebody is definitely again. Somebody's playing civ five yeah, that's the only
ex. It's so fucking. Oh, absolutely no, they didn't or it like maybe we should
move a little move some move towards the center of this. The I also saw a video
sorry I'm obsessed with these videos. I recommend anybody watches a video. I
wish this is what the episode was about me too, but this guy it was the Japanese
the first time the Spanish visited the Japanese and again the Japanese guys
like they are not even human. Their noses are four feet long
and then he said he tells the story about it was kind of cool. He tells like
their story of
he says like they have this religion where their Buddha is a baby. It's so
stupid,
but there's all these like paintings of like
Jesus as a Japanese guy. I'd never seen that before. It was really cool. Those
are sick and he's got like a halo around his head. They have
Mother Mary as a Japanese lady. That's pretty. Yeah, they drew the devil. It's
so amazing. Two cultures come together. I honestly love cultural confluence.
this has got to be one of my favorite things in the world. I mean, could you
imagine? I've been trying to spread I'm just Americanism. I've been trying to
spread my own culture. Yeah, they have that everywhere. I mean you can get like
a Korean style burger, Spanish style burger, exactly, and I'm trying to
further that yeah. We need to show wings. I do think here's another fucked up.
We've done burgers. Another thing. Tell me I went to a pub for lunch. I ordered.
I said I'll have the burger. They said chicken or beef.
they do that in Australia. They call in Australia. They call they do it
everywhere else, except here. They do it in Canada. They do it in Mexico.
That is just is that horrible? They call that like a physical reaction, a
fried chicken sandwich, which is a different thing, which is a different
thing. It's not a in Australia and like every other European country. They
call it a chicken burger. It's messed up. I know I'm saying I experienced it
firsthand. I know in a scenario where it should be cut should have been cut and
you got it and it should be cut in half. Yeah, it was a big knife in the middle
exactly. Give me that it would have been a ten foot tall burger pub cheese
dripping down the side.
I'm also done with smash burgers and I'd like the burgers to be five feet tall
again. Yeah, Robin contact me
that's your problem. You did order a burger in a non American. Did you get
fish and chips? I got fish and chips. Where they I it's the only thing you can
get anywhere. You can you choose between a burger fish and chips or shepherds pie
or
or cottage. I got a Scottish. You have blood sausage. No, I've had blood
sausage before, though I had it when I was in Scotland. I got there blood in my
sausage. It's not bad. It doesn't taste like anything. None of their food tastes.
It's all brown and black items that don't taste like like every other
fucking country. You get a spice bag. What's that? It's like they throw pretty
much all the shit bag. They put everything in a bag and then throw a
bunch of spices in and it comes with curry sauce. Well, and by the way,
this is the brownest food in the world. This curry sauce is not curry. The only
green, the only green thing they eat is pea puree. Yeah, man, mushy peas, yeah,
and because and I know I said they ate boiled cabbage earlier, but that it's
not even green. No, it becomes completely white. It's
translucent. It's literally all brown food. They're on a brown food diet. Did
you feel like it was almost walking around? This is kind of political. Did you feel like
Ireland was kind of Trump vibes? Let me think for a second. No, kind of lots of whiteys.
Well, there's a lot of whiteys, but they're all like there were a lot of whiteys. They're
militantly woke. Were they woke or were they crackers? I saw a group of military men training
and running around with plastic guns. See, that's wokeism. Yeah, get a metal gun. That's
is the woke army yeah a micro plastic gun. Is that what it was she's a micro
plastic in your body to make you lgbt yeah yeah, go figure and that's why
they signed with palestine. Ireland does they do
but they're, but they're very heavy, but they'll let you know that they do in
the first in the first hour
is that really why they think they're doing the same thing. They're they
literally are the tour guide with the first day we met him. I was talking. I
I don't even remember how like yeah, no no reason to bring it up. It's like and
yeah, that's why we like so with Palestine, because I guess like we were
used to being the underdog. Wow, well yeah, they get fucked by the British for
years. They don't get they let themselves get by the British is there in
Britain. They are they are northern Ireland. They are British do they have a
different accent? That's the only fucking different. We're not getting into
this. Let's get into the only difference. I'm you know how I know my
DNA test says sixty percent Irish and British. You are not the hello.
hello. She said hello. You said hello. He's saying we need to start the okay
here. Yeah, thank God. Thank God. Thank God. We did because I was about to I've
been I've been holding my tongue this whole episode. No, no, no, no, let me
intro this here. Please do so.
What's the name of the person?
Sorry, do you remember the name? Oh, let me pull it up, but anyway, I guess I'll
just I'll come right out and say it. We started a law firm. We did fetter and
Doran and pits
FTP, FDP, Fuck the Police. No, it's PDF. PDF is way better. That's really good.
It's darn better. But we start, you know, a lot of these, a lot of these, isn't it alphabetical
when they do that? It's none of your business. It's an order of whatever letters are coolest.
Exactly. Okay. It's, you know, it's a lot of these lawyers that work nowadays, you see
they wear suits. They're prim, they're proper, they're annoying.
As long as I got my suit and tie. And they're old ass. I'm a legal in the court tonight.
Old heads. I think that the legal profession needs a little injection of
young blood. Where's the young blood? Right into the core of it. Where's the
zoom? Where's the elder zoomers? The elder zoomers. The elder zoomers.
The elder zoomers lawyers. Where are the elder zoomers who know actually. Who do Riz La.
Who know, because here's the thing. Exactly, Riz La, that's what I'm saying.
Lawyers, these are lawyers from the past. If you ever created a meme that
that was your IP, your intellectual property.
See, he doesn't know. He's got some lawyering to do.
If you confess to a crime in a meme,
the old guys, they're not even going to know.
They don't even know. What's that?
What's that? Maymay?
What's that?
They're going to say something like "Maymay."
And then now all of a sudden, I'm catching an assault and battery charge.
You got caught on a Maymay?
Yep, and now I'm catching an assault and battery charge
because it's pronounced "meem."
you know. These are old men who say J instead of gift
it a big show. You in his telephone. What are you talking about? Yep? What
do you mean a picture with a telephone? I'm reaching over the stand. I'm
strangling this guy. I'm trying to kill him with the plaintiff. Yeah, he's like
a sexual assault. What's that?
We didn't have that when I was working exactly. This is why we need and this is
what we do when we have our first when we have our first meetings with the
amendments. The Constitution doesn't have any amendments. Well, it has four
that's what he might say
and then we so that's what we do in our meetings with new potential clients, as
we say, and and they this is how they understand. We say old lawyers be like
this yeah, and then you do that and that's the commercial yeah and it's like
trying to attract a different. So anyway, yeah, we're going to get a
give. We're going to give out some legal advice today, legal advice. You can
take this seriously. You can take this is completely hold us accountable for
I pass the bar and this was sent to us by Bailey. I don't know if you want me to
say your last name, so I won't. We're going to say your email address right
now. Thank you, Bailey, for sending us this website. It's a good website
where it's called Avvo and it's people post their it's basically if you've
listened to our doctor episodes, it's practo, but for the legal profession,
essentially. The name the name derives from
I have a like I have a legal question. I go quest. I have a legal question word
for lawyers, avocado, damn in other languages, what language every other
language it's avocado. Yeah, really, I've got oh well yeah, but it's the same
it. They're same in French. It's avocado and that literally means both lawyer and
avocado and I assume it's in Latin and Spanish and all that shit too because
they're green on the inside. Yep, yeah, because they're not even they got a
they got a pit at their center. I believe that's a cold heartless pit. I'm like
but so we're going to give some legal advice on these legal questions that
people have, so i'll go ahead and start it off here,
because the people who are some questions that people that are usually
older lawyers, yeah, who don't none of their get it. They don't answer
anything correctly.
Can I make a real crusty crab restaurant? I want to open a restaurant
from a tv show. Specifically, I want to open a crusty crab from sponge bob. Is
this possible? What problems would I run into with copyright issues? Who would I
have to talk to in order to make this restaurant possible?
us from a little perspective does we'll fucking will find it all. I don't think
you can get in trouble for this because Stephen Hillenburg is dead, has passed
away. So what I mean who's going to see you right now, Patrick star show, then
you can make a crusty crab exactly. I don't understand why again. Again, both
of these would go against his wishes, but what's he going to do? He can't you
know he's going to roll over in his grave. People always say that oh, this
guy's rolling over his grave. That wouldn't scare me at all. I wouldn't be
able to see it as great under the ground. So far down suck my dick. I
don't care if he's rolling over I'm up here yeah as long as you're not rolling
over into my bedroom really fast or down a hallway. I say yes suck my dick.
If you can reach it, oh and I start dancing with my dick out on his grave
bag, but then that's yeah. How do you then it's yow ming yeah under their
seven foot wingspan? I really liked it this one. I just like this one says I
want to open a restaurant from a TV show. Specifically, I want to open a
he had the he one of the question of a little TV show first yeah yeah, and then
he thought of the one. I mean these old lawyers don't know sponge, but they
don't know sponge bob at all
okay. This isn't working now great.
That's fine or like a job, jubio okay, it's working. Is it legal for your
doctor to request to watch you? I saw this one during my GI exam today. The
doctor suggested that he watched me go so he could see where I was having
problems. I said okay, even though it seemed strange, it made me uncomfortable.
is this legal? I like this because this is a this is not legal. No, no, no,
this is legal, because this is this could lead to an entirely different type
of medicine, which is that it's not what you eat. It's not the poop itself. It's
your way, the way you have poor technique that gives you diarrhea. Yeah,
it's normal shit until it gets to your asshole and then you bend your knees
wrong and it's water. Yeah, I can I can see that I could definitely see that
being definitely. I just put a camera in a bathroom. You said okay, so it's
legal yeah, that's also true yeah. You have no case.
Is it illegal to hire a hypnosis to control an ex husband? I found out my
ex wife tried to hire a person to hypnotize me into signing passports for
my children, so she could leave the country with that that's legal. Okay, I
will that's legal, because what you do under hypnosis is we're still it's very
weird. I did not include any of these in my slide shows because it goes against
my feminist agenda, but there is a lot like a lot of questions on this thing
that are like I lied to get my husband in jail and now I regret it.
Who should I tell
it's like there's like I like ten or fifteen different questions. They were
like I lied and told my told one was like I stabbed myself and blamed it on
my husband. Now he's in jail. What do I do? Oh my God, it's pretty awesome.
this is such a good website. I really as I recommend anybody check it out. I had
a landscaper buried a poop in my backyard during the job they did here.
What can I do had a landscape company coming to work in my backyard? They
finished yesterday. I went out there today, saw that my dog was digging up
some things. I looked at it and it smell it and it smells like human number two
human number two is dug about a foot down and realized that one of the
workers and deficated in my backyard and buried it call the company. They talk
one of the guy he admitted to
they do not resolve this human number two, whose is Austin powers come on. How
do they want this to be resolved? What do you mean if they don't resolve the
right there? The guy is all get his poop. They buried the poop. That's a
resolution. The the someone's looking in here and I don't know why they can
leave us alone. Does it look like a mailman? It looks like a child. It
looks like a person well and they waved and smiled and then left. Okay, maybe we
do them.
The what the sequence of events here. I don't believe at all your dog was
digging at something you looked at it smelled and looked like human poop. So
you dug a foot down into the ground until you found more you know what you
were expecting to find a person down there pooping up
and you need. Can you I would how would you be able to it's already it's shit
foot down yeah that's crazy a foot down to find more to find more poop, but the
guy, I guess, admitted to do
right yeah. Who knows
I know this may sound silly, but I'm just wondering is it illegal if a
medium or psychic puts a spell on someone? I know this may sound silly,
but I'm just wondering is it illegal if a medium or psychic puts a spell on
someone? If I went to a psychic and she did this for me against someone, would
I or could I be in any legal trouble? Thank you, yes, this is different from
hypnosis. I would say because this is true and hypnosis is weird. Hypnosis is
weird. No one works on drunk people and yeah, but if you're
like
a spell,
I feel like there's no probably legal definition of a spell. So I think you
can get a very legal definition of spells. I don't think so. Yeah, I don't
think that a spell is any magic action. I don't think a spell is any magic
action that pertains to... Any magic words that have been said that pertain
to or involve magic, which thereby lead to a magical action occurring or being
incurred upon a piece of property or which, which ascertains property, which
at the time of casting the spell were unspelled previous to the spells casting.
See this is why he knows the bar better than this is on you. I mean, I only got
the precedence. I got a twenty on my bar exam yeah.
I got a thousand yeah and it's out of ten thousand yeah, but I still let me
pass yeah, but yeah, they let you pass because you're sleeping with the
teacher. I was sleeping with the judge
that
I'm this is
I'm
also this is this is the number one question. This is the question they
have the most of on this is the only one of it. I put in this was making me
laugh out loud so hard in my house. I'm going to be have trouble getting
through it.
Okay, here we go.
I'm twenty three. I called a fifteen year old sexy just to be silly in the
context of the conversation.
did I break the law in Ohio.
This was a message over a messaging program, no pictures, no sexy talking.
It was literally just that one phrase and it got me thinking it got me
thinking. I called a fifteen year old sexy just to be simply
just to be simply ninety percent of the
I was in a silly goofy mood. Every single question on here is I'm twenty. My
girlfriend is thirteen. Is this legal if I only kiss her yeah and all the all
the lawyers respond and they said yes, this is perfectly legal as long as you
ask your parents permission. Oh God, I called a fifteen year old sexy just to
be said,
how silly would that be if I called her sexy as a as a lawyer. Yeah, what do
you what do you what's your take on this?
I don't know. I think you're going to jail for life, but I think in Ohio this is a
death penalty. Most crimes, most crimes you can usually get away with with the
silly defense. You are going to Ohio. This is beyond the Ohio. Yeah, in Ohio.
This is not happening. The legal system in Ohio be like. Most normal legal system in
Ohio. Yep. Wow. This is. See that stuff that lawyers of our generation wouldn't get.
Yeah, they wouldn't get that. But this you're going to, you're going to be fed
nylon chili until you poop out all of your internal organs. Yeah, how's that
for silly buddy? Yeah, yeah, it's going to be you can get silly with your
license plates. You're doing custom ones and say stuff like come and shit.
I have I have patronized a fried chicken restaurant for quite a while and about
two months ago. I had diarrhea right after the meal. I left my experience in
their website one week later. The manager called me denying anything wrong
in their restaurant and I still went their location for the fried chickens
thinking. Maybe I ate something bad in the previous day, but I had other small
diarrheas a few times after eating the chickens a few days ago. I had some
serious diarrhea right after finishing the fried chickens. I suspected maybe
they put something to make the chickens tender and tasty that something could
make my intestines suffered and having diarrhea that something could harm my
health. I just wonder how I can prove my diarrhea caused by the fried chickens
and that's something and hoping they can improve their chickens. Thanks. I want
you know people out yeah. What did you what did you look up to find this
diarrhea or yeah diarrhea? Okay, I got another diarrhea.
All right, let's let's go to it. Let's see it. I don't know if it's next,
because these are these are maybe the same legal. I don't think it's an
actions here. Oh yeah,
this was my favorite.
So I really want to hear you guys thoughts on this one. Can you use
telekinesis to clear away a storm? I would like to know if you could use
telekinesis to clear away a rain cloud. So okay, no, you can not know you can
not if it's over your neighbor's property. There's a couple of if it's
over your own property, but if you put it on your neighbor's lawn, exactly
problem, I would say up or down. Yeah, there's two. This is going to be
homeless. This is going to be an issue in a in a civil case. You could have a
civil case brought against you, because like you said, this could belong to
your neighbor, depending on how much sky area they have in their
as their property line, how high up their property line goes yeah right, but
also this could be a federal case. You are in if you're going to airspace,
you are interfering with the EPA's weather control devices. They have
exactly they have set all across this nation, right? So if they want to put
this could even bring out of toxic acid rain above your house, you don't have
any legal recourse for that. You especially can't use I mean offensive
telekinesis one hundred percent and speaking of weather control. I mean this
could even escalate the issue beyond the federal level. You could be even in the
everyone you could get in trouble with Israel. Exactly Oh yeah, you're going to
get in big trouble with them, but maybe again you're going to be forced to eat.
I mean, I'll all Chile you're going to be forced to eat taboo into maybe this
doesn't become a legal issue at all. Maybe you you know you're tampering with
rain clouds and and and you know you catch the eye of a foreign country that
maybe has a strong interest in weather control. You're going to be dealing with
a lot more than a rain cloud. I'm going to say yeah, yeah, yeah, dealing with
you might want to deal with this in an extra judicial manner and if you
have telekinesis, how about you do your country a favor and enlist yeah?
What the fuck you doing controlling the rain? How about making the world a
better place by making flowers get taller or become a magician and make the
world a better place by making people smile entertainment yeah, make birthday
parties a little bit. I love magic. I am looking for a lawyer with the guts to
stand up to Facebook. I'm right here, but I have received multiple bands for
jokes and memes ironically taken off of other Facebook pages, predating the
current presidency is from twenty eighteen. What is regarding immigration?
The other refugees they keep removing them, followed by bands for so called
hate speech. I have screenshots of the posts as well as original picked. I pick
I tried to post screenshot plainly show Facebook accusing me of hate speech with
the original post. Far as I knew, the US Supreme Court has already ruled that
under the First Amendment, all speech is protected, even if it offends. Please
help. I will help you. I think we are the lawyers who will stand up to
Facebook. We don't agree with you, but Facebook took away
flair and they took away the wall. They took away a lot of pokes.
They took away pokes. We want that shit back. Yeah. We have the... Make
Messenger back into the main Facebook app. I agree. And that's what we're
gonna have on hats and there could be red hats that say that. Make Messenger
back into the original Facebook app. Thank you. Yep, and take out the bots
for a marketplace. Yes, and Mark Zuckerberg gained some weight. You're
too skinny. You're looking like a twig. I just watched the social network.
I watched the social network on a plane. Zuck,
you are a little weird bastard. Zuck, you look surprised. But you acted really
well on that movie. I was surprised by how well you did in that movie. And Zuck,
I love you. And you were good in Zombieland. I was just about to say
that. Yeah. You were amazing in Zombieland. You were amazing in Zombieland.
But I didn't like you so much in Adventureland, because
I wanted to be in love with the girl in that movie. Yeah, it's kind of cringe
and you made me jealous, but you're the worst lex luther. Oh, don't even get me
started. What lex luther has hair yeah
comic book nerds rise, yes, comic book nerds, it's good. How about comic book
nerds versus the state of mark zuckerberg? Yeah, that's a movie that
will be we're going to bring it to throw away your whole case. That's our new
case. Thank you yeah all right,
make you hear it is it illegal to give someone diarrhea without their
knowledge, and this is listed under civil rights. I think it is. This is a
civil right, technically poison, although the replies under this were
all like. What do you mean? Yeah, how would you do this? What are you talking
about? I think my mom has been poisoning me every single time I go home. Yeah,
she'll leave out. It she'll like leave out chicken for like ten hours and then
I'll get home. I'll get off a flight. She'll be like Hey, I just made this
chicken. Yeah, you want some I'll go yeah, and then I mean even if you don't
way through eating it and she'll be like yeah. I made this at 11 a.m. and it's
been sitting on the counter all day. She could be jailed for lying yeah,
exactly
exactly on our line to your son's line to her son against all moms yeah,
yeah,
law firm versus mom's I'm down. I'm fucking down to pdf. I have I have a
my client has a large list of grievances that go all the way back to two thousand
and two yeah. This is a what we he's been building a case for near eighteen
years right yeah and you are losing your house man.
Can I file a lawsuit in what type against a recognized comedian for
verbally abusing my seven year old while left under his care? I saw my son
today for my weekend visit today. Immediately I noticed his puffy eyes. I
asked him what's the matter. He replied that he was left with Mike Cano
comedian public performer recently, while his mother worked on a Saturday.
He said he took him out my son to eat. Mike arrived to his home and demanded
my son to carry his two liter out of Mike's vehicle. My son tried and said it
was too heavy to him. He said Mike called him a damn bonehead and other
names. He was not allowed to say dictionary definition bonehead bonehead
bonehead now an informal, a stupid person for not being able to cater to
him. He accused him of acting out to his mother. When she arrived, he told me
he never wants to see Mike again. He is afraid of him. He said, while they
were alone, he was very demanding on him. Mike Kano is a comedian Ontario at
Gold Star. He claims he is family oriented, verbally insulting. My son is
no laughing matter. How can I proceed to have this verbal abused stopped this
rose? Okay, okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but this is pissing me off so much. The
war against comedians stops today. Yes, first, Will Smith viciously attacks
nearly kills Eddie Murphy on the stage of the Oscars right and now this guy is
being
accused of child abuse because he says bonehead dude come to the comedy seller
for the comedy mothership on any weekend night. Try that in a small thing, if
bonehead
yes, if bonehead offends you
buddy, have you ever heard of the word, the C word? Have you ever heard of yes,
you were crazy as bitch, great the B word, the C word, the F word, the
H word there you are going to get a
obliterate chart juggler. Matt rife is going to say so much shit. Matt rife,
which I'm now I'm remembering it wasn't Eddie Murphy got slapped. It was Matt
right. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I've completely fucked that up. Matt Will
Smith slapped Matt right.
That right was on stage at the Oscars. He pointed at Will Smith and said, damn
you here with a black. Yeah, I'm really sorry. That was me. That was me being
racially insensitive. It was Matt right anyway. If Matt right gets you in his
laser sights, dude, you're done. Yeah, bro, your kid's gonna fucking kill
himself yeah right. If Matt right, tell your kid to bring a soda to the car
did.
What are we doing here man? The war on comedian stops today and in me as a
lawyer, I'll defend comedians pro bono and they'll probably say something about
that sounds like boner. I did I found one on here that I didn't put in that
was that was how can I find a pro boner lawyer? You know who put that in their
slide yeah, we'll save it. We'll save it all right. We'll save it for Pats. Can I
sir dentist for inappropriate behavior. My wife was told inappropriate sexual
yes. No, you can't know you can't there's a
yeah they have a oh yeah well dentists are like funny doctors yeah. I got a
headache from playing GTA five. Can I sue rock star games? Yes, yes, and we'll
do it for you. If I were to make a sex robot costume for Halloween with a
screwdriver penis and appear in public, do I break indecency laws? The
screwdriver has a small vibration motor attached. There are small square buttons
where the nipples are that activate annoying lights and sounds beeping sex
robot is stenciled on the back. It is quite obviously a joke and is not
realistic in any way. You will be sued for copyright infringement from whitest
kids. Yes, it's over for you. Is it illegal to practice voodoo in the state
of New York? This female is a legally practicing voodoo on me and in turn is
making me very ill with her actions. Is there legal action I can take against
her to make this stop? Because when I have asked her to stop, she is simply
refusing and her lawyers plural are not helpful at all. She reports she is a
witch and this is what she does, but her actions are causing harm and sickness
and are based in evil behavior. It is illegal and we will protect you, but
evil is not illegal.
Evil is not illegal voodoo. We so leave out the base and evil behaviors part
evil behaviors are based evil, but certain vectors of evil is in voodoo or
not. Yeah, they're not okay. Do I have a case? No hello. I used to be
employed with a company about seven years and endured a lot of bullying and
harassment. I was called Patrick from the cartoon Spongebob and McGill of the
gorilla. I worked in two different locations and both supervisors called me
those names and when they spoke about me, they would refer to me as McGill of the
gorilla. I told them to stop and they said as long as I work there, that would
be my name. That will be her full name is Patrick McGill. Yeah, you don't have a
can you have no
as long as you work here. McGill of the gorilla will be your name. Also,
Patrick from the cartoon sponge Bob, you must have a very long name. If there's
a shortened nickname yeah, God, it's so funny to get completely owned by her
boss, ask them to stop calling you McGill of the gorilla and say as long as
as I work here, that will be your name as long as I work here. That will be your
name. Yeah, that's all my my slides. All right
now we're going to go to we're going to go to my slides here, going to look
through some of these things that I found. So we were talking earlier, you
know all these old lawyers, you know we're we're the we're the new we're the
new jacks. We're freshman class to twenty twenty three. Yeah, okay, lawyer
magazine,
freshman, the lawyer, the opening statement, the filibuster, that's what
we're going to be doing yeah yeah we're going up against people like Andrew
Tate and Chris Griffin. We're going to be going up against them. We're going
to be going up against Peter Griffin. We're going to go against gay glaze,
you know all these people,
and this is the first thing I found, which is a does a comedian violate any
copyright laws by doing celebrity voice impressions? I do voice impressions in
my children's birthday party magic act. I don't want to break any copyright
laws. Can I talk like Kermit the Frog without getting sued? No, no, the voice
the main thing about Kermit the Frog. You can't wear a hat with the M on it or you
get sued by Mario's company, which is called Nintendo. If you use Kermit's
voice, which is basically his Mario hat, you will be sued by the Henson
Foundation. Sorry to say. Also, wait, was that from 2010? Yeah. That's the oldest
question on this website. Everything I found was from like 2019. I found some
older ones. Really? I couldn't find shit like that. Can I break my lease after a
week from a severe roast infestation? Hey, did Matt Reif move in your damn
about
can I break my lease due to a roast investation?
Yes, he did. Yes, he did imagine Matt right standing on oh my God, standing
in the gutter like it talking shit to yo kid. Oh my God,
hey hey what's up? Where'd you get that ye? Yes, haircut
wait your dog is actually cute as fuck. Wait your dog is actually dogs are my
lady. You guys come together as friends. I actually love that. I love that. I
actually love that. I love that, but the best I'm a
the best Matt Rife clips are the ones where he's not he's doing crowd work,
but he's not roasting anyone. He's not really commenting. I just going like oh
wow, oh wow, oh wait, so you two are brothers, but wow bed that's actually
nice.
That's actually
three hundred people like I just I wow. I saw you live when you came when you
came to Pittsburgh. I love that shit. I fucking shit. You actually you shouted
out me and my cousin and you said that it was cute that we were there together.
This next one that's fifty percent of his crowd work is that it's cute. Yeah,
yeah,
wait, you're here with your mom. That's cute. There's one. Wait, I actually love
you look hella young.
You all
birthday. Oh shit. He
posted this clip where he's in Honolulu and everyone keeps giving him a lay and
that's the whole clip. That is actually feel fucking blessed as fuck for wearing
this net yeah and then he's doing the crowd work and then a woman in the
crickets
you wait.
What the hell she said
wait
yeah,
what else you say
I came to Honolulu. I thought the whole crowd was going to be waves and shit,
but it's actually fucking it's actually people and shit way, but you're
I thought you were a volcano. Why is he wearing blue like a wave? I thought it
was all going to be waves and sharks and shit. I was low key scared as a
mother. I thought this mother you're man. This volcanoes here with a black
chick. Damn yeah, shout out volcanoes. I never seen a volcano with a black
chick before that's fire for you, bro. I bet I bet I bet you hate hanging out
with his in laws, though, huh? Yeah, two volcanoes. What the fuck can I is it
legal in the state of Michigan to pay a woman to fart for you just have a fart
reddish and would like to find a woman to do this for me, but I want to do it. I
want it to be legal. I would say that this in the
independent contract
yes is ten ninety nine for farting this. I mean not even filling out a W nine on
a guy and then the the like the memo just says like blast yeah. I mean, I
guess the question here is not corporate. This isn't it seems like it's
not about legality. This he won't he's maybe a it wants it to be tax. He wants
to be taxed on this guy's yeah. I mean the government's always going to want to
take extra money. Oh, if you want to do above board work, because I could buy
that plastic cup from you right now. I don't need to fill out. I'll sell it to
you. Okay, how much two bucks
while you're doing that? I'll go to the next slide, which is what's to stop me
from making an energy drink and calling it bottle of jizz. I know, I know, but
you're doing that's a really dumb name for an energy drink, but we have one
called pussy and I know for a fact a large group of people would buy it and
drink it. It'd be a normal energy drink with the consistency of him a bottle of
jizz on a normal energy drink, but as the consistency of jizz is make it taste
like mango, though, because mangoes are delicious. It'd have all the basic
ingredients as monster energy, but healthier and different enough that they
can't claim. I rip them off. My question is are there any actual laws and
stipulations anywhere in the USA besides California that would stop me from
making such a drink and selling it a gas station, California, they're going to
by law and they hate is well. You know who else hates is these old lawyers.
Your drink is not a bottle of is the mark is therefore misdescriptive. Of
course, it is questionable whether there is any market for an actual bottle of
okay. This is not a monster. Yeah, a bag of Cheetos. Those aren't actually
Cheetos. No, they're just little snacks. Yeah. Do you think the animals a Cheeto?
Yes, no, it is a Cheeto. Let's move. Let's just let's not get into a Dorito.
It's just a chip. Let's not get into this. You're going to get he's going to
not going to understand sorry. I'm gone. He got a on the bar. Sorry, I'm worried
about my wheel.
Can a bail bonds man call me and threaten me and call me nasty booger?
So this bonds lady has been texting me calling me nasty names and threatening
me saying that she is going to send the cops to my house and tell me that I'm
going to jail.
Booker
that's fucking you first of all booger names again, not allowed. This is the
depending on where you are in the world. Yeah, it's going to be really,
really bad or more kind of fun misdemeanor charges. Yeah,
somebody just has to blow my school world of a huge booker in place on my
back. How would you label this crime against me? Is it a battery assault with
a booger? Yes, I was assaulted with a booger and what could I do to legally
punish the transgressor in this in this situation? This is not a joke. This is
absolutely serious with the police care and punish the train, the transgressor
or am I supposed to accept assaults with boogers against me? Unfortunately, yes,
you are you're if it was at school, you're going to yeah, because you can
here's, but here's the thing you're going to be called booger boy for the
rest of your life, though there's precedent for this.
This person who did this is detestable. This is a detestable and he can he has
to register as a detestable person. Tell everybody, excuse me, so you know I
moved in next door. I'm the test of when they go to a new school. I just want
to let everyone know my fun fact is I'm a detestable. I'm a detestable person.
I've put boogers on people before. Boogers on a kid with a rollie backpack.
I'm a nasty, nasty, detestable booger boy. Hello, my character trait is
detestable. Yeah, exactly.
How can I legally get my neighbors to turn their damn rap crap down?
I live in a very small valley and our newest neighbors think they can blast
their rap crap as loud as they want and want everyone in the valley to hear
it. What can be done to make it stop? This is sadly nothing. Unfortunately,
there was a Supreme Court decision about six years ago when sicko mode came
now they there was a Supreme Court decision. Apparently in now this new
America, Joe Biden's America, you can play rap music as loud as you want in any
valley, do and especially in the valley. It doesn't matter what kind of
neighbourhood you live in. It can be flat, it can be a valley, you live on a
mountain, you can play your music as loud as you want, and this is a big loss for
patriots. I would say that if the if the if the the framers were here, they would
not be accepting this. No, no, you know, if they were still alive, this is not
what they wanted and if Antonin Scalia was still alive, he'd be would have
been there was another. There's another there's another ruling pretty soon
after that, just because I know people are going to be curious about the
corner cases where if you're blasting Lincoln Park, you have to turn it down
for the Chester parts and turn it really loud for the Mike Shinoda. Exactly,
and by the way, I went to a pub in California recently that was owned by
one of the ex members of Fort Minor. Wow, I met him. Did you meet him? Yeah,
which one it's you didn't even say that I with like with I don't know them by
their I don't know his name by their name. I don't know his name, but he
I had some chicken wings and they were really, really bad yeah. Wow well, but
he's friends with my brother now. So that's pretty awesome. Maybe we can get
on a track with him. I would love to get on it. I mean I would love to collab
with him, but the whole song is about how his wings are bad and he doesn't
is pretty cool, though
and then then his verse is just a downtown new hall California. Check that
out.
some gay ass crap happened. I was cited for underage drinking and urinating in
public, went to the bar and nature called cop wasn't thrilled and wrote me a
ticket. How can I fight this? You can't you know, so I would say that you could
get off easily here on what is called the cool defense, because the fact that
you're keeping it up through this whole thing is one. It's very cool to underage
drink. It's very cool to your public, but the fact that we have evidence of you
being cool online in the in the aftermath, saying some gay ass crap
happened, he's not worried about this. Another nature called exactly Ace
Ventura stuff. That's another another possible defense you could look into
that would be the defense I would choose if you chose me for your case is the
why were you looking there? Defence? Yeah, I'm underage. Are you gay? You're
against the wall. What are you looking at? Why are you trying to kidnap my P?
Yeah, that's what I would say. That's what I would tell them. I would say,
what do you do? Wait, you have you have gloves. Are you Michael Jackson? He will
that, but also are you trying to use that glove to scoop up my piece? You can
go home and jerk off to it later because you are what I just said. Yeah, yeah,
and now the cops in jail. Will you go faster so I can get to mine? I want to
sue fortnight. How? Yes, W fortnight ban me. I want back on fortnight, ban me. I
want back on, but they won't let me. I spent like two thousand dollars on that
game. So can I sue them? How can I find a pro boner lawyer for a sexual
harassment case? Buddy? I think all of them are going to be. I think that's
got to be some kind of joke. It was a joke one and there was a description
that he cropped out that I didn't read that. I just saw that, but look at this
I
opted out, though pro bono, but if my wife and I same sex have a baby through
a boner, I saw this one to
my immigration paperwork, yes,
farting trying to get our kids back from
our suing DHR for desiccation of character and discrimination
for
this is the last one. Can you adopt a mentally retarded adult without
permission
ever. This shit is so crazy. I'm gonna say, I think there was a whole thing.
No, I don't think you can. No, you cannot. I think that probably is not
gonna work out for you. There was a whole description of this where it was
very, very, very, like they were like,
"The lawyer now controls my mother's estate," or something. So it's a weird,
it's a very weird legal thing. A back story I don't wanna hear. The back
story is not great, but that phrase right there is fucking crazy. Okay,
here's mine. Could this in any way get me in trouble? A girl was giving me a
hand job. She initiated it and it was very much consensual. Sorry for the
lewd detail, but during it I asked her if I could ejaculate on her breasts and
she said, No, you can't come on me later in the hand job. I came and while I
got seam on on her hand because she was giving me a hand job, it was not a
problem. She did not seem to mind it at all and I just started overthinking it
later. After we were done, I asked her if everything we did was okay and she
said yeah. I had fun. I had no intent of coming on her when she said, No, you
can't come on me. I thought it meant I can't purposely try to come on her body.
I thought I did not think it would include her hand, which was giving me the
hand job. I thought that was quite obvious. I don't know if this is a silly
question. I tend to overthink and over analyze everything. Any insight would be
very much appreciated. Thank you. You are going to jail compared to
years. I'll show you my reaction as a as a new young lawyer. Okay, it's all good
bro. Here's an older guy's reaction. You are on a public forum communicating with
professionals. The subject of your question is not offensive, but the
manner in which it was described is very offensive. There are three forms of
communication that every person needs to learn. One, the way you talk with your
buddies over a few beers. Clearly, you've got that down. Whoa. Two, the way you
communicate with teachers, co-workers, and people in authority. It is more
formal, but some slang is okay. If you respect your girlfriend, then she calls
it, falls into this category. Three, more importantly, is the way you communicate
at a funeral to a judge in court, police officer, or to professionals on a public
forum. If you are sorry for the lewd detail, you should have spent a few
and that's thinking about how you were going to communicate the facts in an
appropriate manner. You need to read the room before you speak to him. Wow,
that's a
this is from Patrick Steinfeld, who's a wrongful death attorney in San
Francisco, because he's all how is how fucking crazy is it to be to be a
lawyer? You're working as a lawyer and you're like well, it's time to log on
to avo dot com and scroll through the sex crime section. Two hundred words
about this guy who's accidentally
I was accused of peeping and I was charged with class C misdemeanor with
fines. I have court soon. Should I pay the fines? This is great, okay, I was
looking for an associate in a woman dress room where I work at and saw a
roach and I jumped on a stall to escape it and a woman from the other stall saw
my hair and said I was peeping. She was a crying and I said I didn't mean it.
Now I have fine. I didn't mean what should I do? Should I tell the judge
what happened or pay the fines again for me? I'm saying oh dude a roach. I'm
scared as fuck as but this older lawyer says saw a roach and jumped on a stall
to escape it. Seriously, you should find a local criminal defense attorney. I've
seen this guy a lot. This guy's all over this woman in yeah.
Will I be arrested? I was in a private room at strip club and I touch her
private part. She didn't say anything and no one come to room and said
anything. It was quick quick touch. Will I be arrested for this? Yes, you will be
suggested you are going to jail. You are going to jail.
Does being charged with a video of bestiality mean that such person would
no longer be allowed to have pets a video of bestiality on someone's camera
roll, not of which person being charged a random person on the internet, but it
was in this person's camera roll. Could this charge if found guilty make it so
this person would no longer be allowed pets for a certain amount of time. Why
are you putting this in your camera roll bookmarks bar exactly
put it in a folder in a folder on your bookmark homework yeah right put this in
an encrypted folder. I
that says you can't be trafficking with you can't you can't handle this kind of
weight. I'll say that no put it put it in a zip file called boring PDF yeah
that'll get you getting away with. Why is it in your camera? Why would you ever
need it on your phone at any point, whether you have internet or not? I
think that I need this in case I'm on a plane and this guy's in Seattle. I think
they may be
Seattle. Yeah, this is Seattle. You mean the birthplace of Mr. Hands? Yeah, this
is completely yeah. I didn't know this was Seattle. This guy is not in trouble
at all. Yeah, they're going to give you extra pets. Is it illegal to like a boy
who 18 and you're 14? They're a YouTuber who 18 and I like them and my friend
14. Would it be illegal for them to date? Yes, yes. So this is at first, but the
YouTuber would not think it's illegal. First. I like this question because at
first I thought there was a four a 14 year old asking if they could or if they
they're allowed to date this youtuber. I realize now they're trying to explain
they're trying to set up they no no they're not they're a youtuber who
eighteen and I like them and my friend fourteen. Would it be illegal for them
to date? They want to know that it's illegal, so they can say I have to date
they the year because you're only fourteen yeah wow yeah
and this guy says
and this this I liked I included this. This lawyers answer came with all these
declaimers about this not being artificial intelligence yeah that came
up with ask your and they're not your attorney. Meanwhile, us we are your
attorney, all your attorney, we are your attorneys with we're actually now that I
think about it, we're kind of doing a breaking bad better call, something
where if we're lawyers, every all these patron subscribers who are giving us
money, we have that's a retainer yeah, we have we have we have privilege. You
can tell us anything yeah in the comments of this video, say anything all
of your legal questions. Go ahead. Go tell your legal questions. We can't tell
anybody to crime. Yeah, yeah.
If you get attacked by teen girls, can you legally defend against them? Asked
in Dallas, Texas. During a talent contest, a riot broke out. I am a male
staff member. I am considerably weaker than averages. At some point, a pair
of teen girls who were rather large attacked me. They were whopping my skull,
face, and upper body. So when they chipped some of my teeth, I lashed out
landing blows after several minutes. The other staff separated us, but I ended up
being checked by the paramedics. They chipped a few of my teeth, blacked both
my eyes and broke my nose, but I was written a fine for assault, but I won
against it. They were not punished. They had many bruisers, but nothing serious,
so technically who broke the law, them or me. Well, you won the case. I just
love him telling his whole story. They be like so technically he's not trying
to sue them. He just said technically who broke the law, me or them yeah
this guy got go want by two rather large teenage girls. Is it a hate crime to
call your roommate a F A G in Texas room is terrible? I called him F A G. He had
the cops come. They said it would be a hate crime. If I did it again and left,
he is not
he is not yet
and he called the cause
that's actually that's you know what if he's trying to get the other guy to
Eve yeah kind of the perfect petty thing to do pretty good yeah.
Can I be convicted of murder? Yes, I let
crazy. I let two of my friends use my apartment. I come home with blood
everywhere and two dead bodies. My friends are dead and my blood may be in
the
but I really don't know what
yeah. I mean I get to be fair. My blood might be in my apartment right now, but
my all over my blood into my underwear and it got kicked under my bed. My
blood, maybe in my apartment, my blood might be in there. I let two of my
friends use my apartment
and I come home with blood everywhere. Two dead bodies. My friends are dead.
My blood might be there, but I don't really know what happened. I don't know
if they might and he got this advice. You must not say these things on this
site. Just promptly get a lawyer. It's actually pretty good. He's got an
avowed rating of ten. Yeah, I know this guy's a killer. Very health hand more
very, very helping hand. Can I sue a TV show for using a picture of me without
my permission? I got this guy's in a bad situation. Yeah, I got a call from my
brother one evening saying that I was on an episode of forensic files as a
suspect for a rape and murder that happened in ninety five and another one
that happened later on and a picture of me was on the screen. However, I was
never questioned. The picture of me was from me complying with an investigation
in my area willingly and was taken out in front of a pizza joint. It wasn't
doing a mug shot. What can I do about this? It's representing me as a
criminal and I have no criminal record. I'm a law abiding a citizen. That's
insane. Can you imagine? Holy Can you imagine your girlfriend is in your
you're you're playing you're playing fortnight or whatever your girlfriend's
a living room watching unsolved mysteries? Yeah, like hey, you need to
come in here yeah. What the fuck did you just do? I get it's paused and it's a
picture of suspect for a rape and murder that happened in ninety five and another
you eat a later on yeah. Look at this criminal. This is from his remuneration.
That's so funny that you would hold a never to I guess they wouldn't tell you
yeah. I guess not that they're doing that yeah. The fact that it's not a mug
shot is so fine. I
they just asked yeah hey yeah he thought he was going on the wall for
being the thousandth. The customer you ate the most pizza here to yeah, we
probably yeah they went up to him. We're like. Do you know anything about this?
he's like no. I don't know. I just work here yeah, yeah, God damn it. This is
the number one suspect. How can I sue if I had a bug in my drink from a
restaurant? How can I sue if I had a bug in my drink and then this is the last
one? I think can I sue a day care for a roach being in my child's ear? The day
care has a big infestation of roaches. They're addressing. I took my child out
of the facility a month ago. My child was seen at urgent care. The doctor said
it had been in there for some time because it was dead and causing her a
fever. I have proof of the roaches inside the facility, along with cold food
served to children and videos of how one teacher talked to my child and no
action has been taken, and that's why my child is no longer. I can I can accept
the roaches in the place, you know, it's a day care, cold food, no way
discussed something. If my kid goes to day care, he gets a hot PBJ that's been
left in a car, something that something that I found out about one of the I
didn't put any of these in there. A million of these ones that apparently is
a real medical thing, but there's a bunch of questions that are can I sue the
hospital. My newborn baby ate poop. I almost put that one in there's twenty of
them yeah. It's apparently I found a there was one that I didn't put in that
everyone's like no. You can't babies do that babies do that. There was do that.
There's one I didn't put in
that was what happens if my baby eats poop during delivery yeah. That's all
stuff like that. Sorry yeah, that's on you. You're the one who pooped exactly
while pushing the baby out. Well, it's the baby's own poop that it's eating.
All right, I have to go give the state. So what day is the shareholder?
The 23rd. 23rd.
So go ahead and subscribe.
In. Oh, yeah, I'll be in Washington, D.C.
trying to spending all of the money I make on a boot that's attached to my car.
Yeah. On the 24th of the 26th. I'm there with Adam.
Yep. And subscribe to the Patreon.
Subscribe. Patreon.com/podcastaboutlist.
Subscribe to the YouTube.
Yeah, that too. If you're watching on this,
Get us to 10K, we're almost there.
- We're almost there.
- We are almost there.
I think that right now we are at 99.99.
- And let's try and get me to six foot six.
- Let's get Cameron tall, y'all.
- All right.
(static)
The hypothetical is this.
Would you rather be a hand or a foot,
but you don't get to pick whose hand or foot you are.
So you don't get to be like Dua Lipa's foot.
You have to say, "I'm going to be a hand or I'm going to be a foot."
I just... I just made up a name. Is that a person?
Yeah.
Well, I don't fucking know.
From what I know, from what I... I don't know much about her,
I think that she is maybe like the Prime Minister of Albania.
Let's see. Who's this?
Dua Lipa's feet.
Okay, back to my question.
Would you rather be a foot or a hand?
No choice on who's hand or foot.
Probably a hand because it you know you I mean I could pick up pencils
Okay, I could get here. Here's a lot left in them. Here's the thing okay, huh?
you
Don't have any country you are just sitting there. You just everything is basically your face
So I'm wearing everything just like shoved into your face like I'm a vegetable you are not in control
Yeah, so it's like like I'm completely awake. Yes, but you're a sentient hand
Yeah, attach to a person and the person controls my every move so you're good
So if your hand you already chose hands, so you're locked in yeah, but feet you're a wiping ass and buddy
I've wiped my asshole before and I've missed either toilet papers in the wrong place poop on my finger
Mm-hmm. I've picked up every disgusting fucking thing in the world. Yeah, that's true
I've touched the tongues of tons of animals and zoos that have been eating disgusting slop
Yeah, right. I jacked my off. I
I jack my off.
Every other day I jack my off.
Yeah.
I touch my bees.
I touch them.
I touch my bees and I jack my off.
Every other day at least.
I sit on the couch, right?
I sit on the couch.
I rewatch Girls.
I hold my bees.
You just front, front of the pants.
I grab them from the back.
Yeah.
I go around.
So here's a problem.
If you're my hand, I go through.
You're not just touching.
and you're touching the, the, the T as well as the B's.
- I credit card through my cheeks.
- Uh-huh.
- Above my T.
- Grab the B, grab the B's.
- No P.
- No P, can't even reach the P.
(screeching)