(upbeat music)
- Well.
- Well. - Here we are.
- Welcome to the future.
The future of podcasting is here.
Guys. - The whole show
is gonna be like this from now on.
- We have entered a new dimension.
Not only a new dimension, a new world.
And not only a new world, - A new dimension.
- A new life.
Welcome to second life. We're here beautiful bumblebee buzz public cinema, which is a
Some kind of horse stable. It's a horse farm. I think yeah, it's a horse. Well not a horse farm. You don't usually farm
Horses well, I think yeah, but farm you could call it a farm still
Yeah, nobody would be it. Maybe only the most annoying person on earth would say it's actually not a farm. It's a stable
- Maybe that would be something that a crazy person would say.
- Maybe the only most rude person on earth would say
that maybe the most annoying person on earth.
Wait, what are you doing, Patrick?
- I'm just laying down.
I'm resting.
- How is it, wait, what's that horse doing?
- I'm just laying with my horse.
- Second life is the most amazing,
it's better than real life and it's not even close.
- Yeah, easily, so easily.
What's your favorite part about Second Life so far?
Our new lives.
- Probably my horse and the fact that I'm Cameron.
- Yeah, I like my wolf body that I was able to find.
- I'm living my life as Cameron now, which is pretty good.
- You wish, buddy.
- I like my little radio.
- I think you wish.
I mean, look at my life in here.
I got a horse.
- You have the confidence to wear an unbuttoned shirt.
- Yeah.
I like I feel like all three of us are able to be
Exactly who we've always wanted to be definitely I have I'm not bald, but I have very short hair
Patrick gets to be Cameron and he gets a horse named brouhaha. Yeah, and Cameron gets to be some kind of green
kind of demon with no genitals
- And Julio is me. - There's probably some
genitals under the fur.
- I don't know if you can see Julio here,
but he is me, and he is in a steampunk hat with no shirt.
- And he has a scorpion on his shoulder.
(laughing)
Which is a fashion accessory you could never wear
in the real world.
- No, you could not wear a scorpion.
It would not work at all.
- It would not work even a little bit,
but in Second Life, anything is possible.
except for getting a username you want guys i tried to get my favorite user name
and they made me add a bunch of numbers after it
as i was already taken
they didn't mean to me that i don't really think in
you mean there was a very pervert one three two five six seven three so
semi a friend request if you want to wear wolf r_p_
you mean to tell me that pervert one three two five six seven
was taken
you can tell me every other
perverts wanted to recruit
perverts one through one million
three hundred and twenty five thousand six hundred and seventy two were all
taken
yeah or can i say that it's it's it's a popular username on second life and who
can say why
yet the use of the username perfect but it has been
everybody there's been millions of people around the world to sit down to
their keyboard to make a second left and go
pervert fuck
i just want to see that guys avatar i want to see what pervert one looks like
i'll search him up right now
can you see? you can look up what pervert one looks like? yeah let me find it
i'll just search pervert first we'll see what pervert looks like
it was amazing going through the tutorial island and there was one door
that you walk through in the tutorial island and then you're in some kind of
of like goth sex club and sexual dungeon some kind of sexual dungeon and patch or
Cameron actually Cameron fucked me really I do oh I remember that I did yeah so I
just searched pervert the first result is pervert family Julia why are you the
second result is pervert interracial whoa that's a guy's name in second life
no I think these are clubs I would join these clubs people yeah interracial
perverts club is one you would join? I would join pretty much any any club that
would have me. Marcus W123 just an average old pervert. A bunch of stuff
like this here. You know what we need guys? Listen, all right, what is what is first
life all about? Work, taxes, work, close food, hamburgers, you're both
fucking close as shit. It's about money. Yep. So guess what second life is about
about guys. Linden. Linden rules everything around me. Lareem. Okay? This is what we care
about now guys. Linden, for those who don't know, is the dollar of the second life world.
And this shit is ruling my every waking thought. All I think about is Linden all day and night.
How can I get some Linden?
I need to get a buzz ball item that I can put in my hand.
How are we going to make Linden?
You want to get buzz balls in this game?
I want to download a buzz ball model and put it in my hand.
There's so much stuff about this that's so different from the real world.
Like for example, being able to download things instead of having to get them.
Exactly.
I agree.
- A little crash course for people watching.
Downloading is the getting of Second Life.
How normally you would get something or have something.
- Or install it.
- You would either download or install it.
And it usually is gonna cost a couple of linden at least.
- And instead of giving, you upload.
- Yes, yes.
So now you're getting familiar with the Second Life lingo.
I do feel like, you know what this is guys?
Us in Second Life, this is the immigrant story.
- Yeah.
- This is three people who don't know any of the customs,
the cultures, coming along.
We went through the Sex Ellis Island, the tutorial.
We fucked it, you fucked me, you know?
- You asked me to.
- Well, yeah, well I was strapped down
to some kind of device, okay,
and you just basically clicked on it.
- And for all, and listen, for everyone listening out there
who sees what my character looks like,
he looked a little different when this happened, okay?
- Yeah, he did. - I think it's scary.
- My character used to be a little more attractive
before his disease hit it. - I think that your character,
you hit the wall. - Was a woman.
Your character was a woman and Caleb was a man?
- My character was a man, but he had wings.
I made my character a woman. - Oh.
- He was the default avatar for my character.
I loaded up the account, pervert1325673
second life was like let's go ahead and give this guy bangs a black suit and
wait and by the way if it does it based on your name this shit nailed my vibe
instantly I have I have a groovy shirt bell-bottom pants and a radio that I
walk around with and I didn't change a single thing except my haircut I did a
lot to make myself look like Cameron I think I spent maybe 20 minutes just
looking at a photo of Cameron I had as my wallpaper on my computer and I was just
going through the sliders and editing the face and everything. There's sliders on
here? Yeah you can edit that I shouldn't have told you guys that because now
we're gonna spend the rest of the episode. We're in the throes of it but man I
wish I wish I had done some sliders instead of picking this gay-ass normal
default skin that's so average. This thing is average as fuck. This is the
- The average Second Life user skin, I think.
- Yeah, there must be a lot of,
for this to be a default skin,
there has to be so many people
who are logging into Second Life
to pretend to be a woman and flirt with other women,
and just be like, I wanna be an ugly beast.
In my real life, I'm just a normal guy,
but I wanna be a hideous monster.
- This is hard mode, mate.
You're on hard mode trying to have sex in this game,
dressed up as this evil character.
- I don't know, I don't think it's that hard
to have sex with another werewolf.
- Well he's naked and he has no penis.
- Yeah.
- So like people know you don't got nothing down there.
- Again, there could be some fur covering some stuff up.
- You think your penis is so,
okay so even worse, your penis is so small
it can be blocked by one piece of hair.
well listen buddy as much like other part my entire body on less of a show or more
of a grower
okay i just learned how to lead my horse
so now i'm on the among the same level as you guys now
but watch this
witty
well you made him jump
uh... wow that's crazy
so i can do things in second life that
are possible in the real world
like make a horse jump, make a horse jump.
Horses are not very obedient normally.
- No, no, no, no.
- So how are we gonna make Linden, guys?
Because I need this shit.
- Yeah, I need Linden so bad.
- We need some kind of Ed, Edd, Neddy scam
that we can start running on people.
- I would like to sell my body,
but unfortunately I think there's gonna be some steps
I'm gonna have to undertake before then.
I think I'm probably going to buy
a full body volumetric scanner
like they use for CGI movies and I'm gonna scan my entire body in one-to-one
perfectly and walk around as a perfectly photorealistic avatar. Oh okay that's
see I thought that you were saying that you were going to scan your body into
this game and then sell yourself as some kind of escort. Oh that's exactly what
I'm saying. Oh okay all right. Just making sure. That's what I just said yeah that's what I
I think I might do to make some--
- Sorry. - Linden.
- I was distracted by my horse.
- Yeah, this has gotta be one of the worst ideas ever
in terms of keeping Patrick attended.
- Right, well, and that window,
the second life window doesn't even have to be open.
- That is true.
- There, you don't even need it.
You should be just be standing there.
- I'm sure that he is gonna keep it open the entire time.
- Oh, I will.
No, 'cause I have to look at a PowerPoint at some point.
Um, yeah, I guess another way to make Linden would maybe to be to open a restaurant
Yeah, yeah, there needs to be
I think that one thing I'm gonna start investing in pretty soon with maybe even real-life Linden is
Peripherals I'm going to get some kind of
Haptic feedback suit to make this experience even better. I think
Yeah, so when like my horse bucks at you you'll feel like when your horse steps on me
I feel the I've always thought about thought about that with haptic feedback suits
Is it gonna be when that when those come out and they're really good
Is it gonna be something where you get stabbed and you feel really like actual pain? Is that what people want from this?
Probably will be true
There will be true that will be true
there will be truth revealed.
what are you gonna do make it where you get stabbed and you'd come
i mean i think that's what i was the only other option for a happy
feedbacks that's what i would do it with the two things you could possibly be
aware that for that would be the option is out i would put i would
put on the haptic feedback suit set it to the come only setting and then go play
chivalry
ever since get
every single night but my open the open mic on
and then just get in sort fights with guys
and you know
have a said going into my of my key bindings for my for my haptic suit and
and uh... it for my uh...
uh... and sixty four emulator and setting it so every time mario jumps it
simulates a leg shaking orgasm
this is a few of the settings around
i guess you're right that that why would anybody said it to pain
if there is a choosing option
i would set it to pain once and then if it wasn't that bad i would go out and i
I would be a criminal and I would muck people.
(laughing)
- Well that was--
- You know what I would do?
I would set it to pain one time.
- Exactly, I'd be like, okay, now I know I can handle this.
I'm gonna go try and kill people with my knife.
And if they get the knife and stab me, so what?
- Yeah, just do a bunch of draining.
- Set it to pain.
- Yeah.
- Set it to pain one time and then go
to nuclear blast simulator.
- Yeah.
- And see what the fuck happens.
- Yeah, play one of those car games
that just crash a Maserati on the wall 5,000 times.
- God, that would be fucking incredible.
that be it that's got to feel amazing to do to have a feedback and jump into a
car and just crash it 200 miles an hour. Oh my god, dude you fucking you put on the haptic pain
feedback suit and you're playing some what you're playing like a fighting game
or something but there's like they released it they rushed the release and
there's a bug in it so you get punched one time and it simulates all your bones
breaking constantly until you force quit the game. That's what I mean dude at some point
they're gonna make a haptic feedback suit
that is way too strong.
And it's gonna like,
you're gonna do mortal combat fatalities
and get decapitated or something.
- Are they, who is working on these haptic feedback machines?
- There's people, - Me mostly.
- They have haptic feedback gloves for VR.
I've seen these. - Oh yeah.
- Yeah, but--
- You've been looking into them like every single day?
- Pretty much, looking at the technology,
seeing if it's getting any better.
But my fear is always,
'Cause the big thing with the haptic feedback is like,
oh, it'll simulate like holding something.
Like it gives you like resistance
when you try to like close your fist
on like an apple or something.
- Yeah. - Right.
- But I would just get scared that it would,
it would somehow think that the apple was as big as a planet
and it would bend all my fingers back and break my hand.
- Yeah, it's a very high or a very high risk
when it comes to a glitch. Normally in a glitch you'll be upset or you'll lose a few hours
of progress. Oh that's so funny, look how I have a long arm. Yeah, oh my god I'm clipping
through the wall. I'm stuck in the wall and then you have your haptic feedback suit on
and you're like "I'm stuck in the wall!" Yeah, you don't want this. This is a bad time to
get a glitch guys. So I think sex, even worse if you- I think we're working on eliminating
glitches though. I've heard that. They're trying to stop glitches? I've heard that they're getting
rid of glitches. Oh, that's good. That'll change everything. I think that they, that's why
they should probably just keep haptics to sex because if it destroys your penis you're not
gonna tell anybody. Yeah. Yeah. You're not gonna be like. Yeah, no, imagine, imagine
you have the VR headset on and you just use like the haptic succulator 5000 and you're
and you're like walking around like after you're trying to hide it from your
your your wife or your girlfriend you're just walking around the apartment just like
your cock is broken in half i think what would probably be the scariest thing
is imagine you watch bowser you watch bowser sucks you off vr
- Yeah, it's just air playing directly.
- You didn't know anything about his jaw strength?
(laughing)
- You maybe didn't think too hard
about the fact he's a dinosaur.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I think,
I think the scariest scenario
is that you put on the haptic feedback suit,
you get into second life.
Here you are at the tutorial island,
you take two wrong turns.
Uh-oh, you're in tickle world.
- Oh my God.
Oh, a haptic tickle where there is no escape.
You have to unzip yourself from the suit
to escape this tickle.
- Yeah.
- That would be scary as fuck.
- Yeah, I guess if I was creating a tickle trap,
I would probably make it though,
so that the action of reaching for the zipper
would cause unimaginable pain.
- Or unimaginable tickling.
- Yeah.
You'll only be tickled if you try to take your suit off.
- Have they figured out maybe some kind of
evolutionary reason why tickling is programmed into the human body?
Maybe not. Maybe it's just uh, maybe it's just one of God's mysteries or miracles.
Yeah, unfortunately I think it's sexual in nature. Yeah, I think that tickling...
Unfortunately I think it's sexual in nature. Tell that to my brother!
like oh I have okay all right well never mind then don't tell don't tell my
brother that god tell that to anybody but my brother please don't tell my brother
that tickling is sexual do you think that that would change your relationship
with your brother if you had sex with him?
Yeah, that would probably change it in a massive way.
Yeah, if he found out that tickling is inherently sexual.
Well, I sure hope not,
because I've been tickled.
I think I've been tickled by everybody
in this call right now.
Really?
At some point, yeah.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure that makes sense to me.
But I think I'm probably in the top 1%
in terms of the ticklish community.
I think I'm extremely ticklish.
- In terms of being ticklish?
- I'm very, very ticklish.
- He is. - Which makes me
also very sexual, I think, by--
- Trust me, I know.
- And I'm a tickler.
I tickle Patrick pretty often.
- You do? - Yeah, Patrick is fun to tickle.
- Well, he's just always just sitting there.
(laughing)
You know?
- I just made my horse jump so high.
- Wait, watch this.
Julio, you gotta watch this really quick.
- Holy shit.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
That's the highest I've ever seen a horse jump in my life.
- Yeah, this is in my second life.
- I think that the horse is gonna explode on impact right now.
Nope, didn't work.
All right.
- Well, we should-- - The metaverse gone crazy, y'all.
- Is this the metaverse, technically?
That's the thing, they did all this--
- This is the metaverse.
- The horizon worlds and shit.
None of that shit is touching this, man.
And this game's 20 years old.
- And it's goaded.
- This is actually the metaverse,
and it's been around for a long time, guys.
We don't need these work-from-home fools.
People make a living playing this game.
70, I looked it up, there's $70 million a year
that is cashed out from this game.
- Oh my God.
- By people who are like--
Who like--
sell stuff. You sell stuff. You can be a landlord. You can be an escort. You can be a landlord.
You can sell like clothes. There are shops. People will complain and be like, "The shop
I went to, their interface was horrible." Yeah, and I don't want to alarm you guys, but
I'm completely in space right now. Well, it's high up enough that you're in space? Yes, I'm
seeing other planets. I think that is somewhat alarming to me. I'm looking at a sky dome.
Oh, you can rent a skydome in here.
That is crazy.
- Can I tell you guys something that I did
in the real world this weekend
that basically demonstrates why second life is superior?
- Yeah, why?
- So this weekend I went to Coney Island
to the amusement park.
- Okay.
- Me and my fiance, we were riding a bunch of all the rides
and we were having a rather lot of fun on them,
spinning around and twirling and writing down
uh... which sounds great right
well we get on this one ride
at the end well we're waiting in line for this one right
as little girl comes up to my fiance and starts is talking to her and being like
have you guys been on this is right before this reds awesome all i just want
you to sleep with some talking and then she's like
she like started singing she is a like
uh... and that she said
my name is harmony
and i'm gonna be a singer
she followed us onto the ride and she has to sit with us
uh... and i think it's like okay sure
and then we got on the right and it's been around and swung around rather fast
and me and
i think i'd say both felt that we were going to completely throw up and puke
all over this little girl
and did you do it
we've just
so we're literally genuinely so close to both throwing up onto this small child
(laughing)
- Who was completely alone.
- She would have never sang again, man.
- No, it would have completely ruined her entire fun
at Coney Island.
- If you had vomited--
- If I had been in second life, I would never have gotten
sick, I would have just been having fun.
And instead of a small 10 year old child approaching us,
it probably would have been a 50 year old man,
who I would have had a lot in common with
to talk about topics with.
- You could have talked about movies,
there's no kids allowed in this damn game,
it's 18 plus, y'all.
- Exactly.
- What would a puke in a haptic feedback suit feel like?
- I was thinking, see that's what I would,
probably amazing, well that's why,
you don't just need the outside for a haptic feedback suit,
it needs to be a balloon that you swallow.
- You know what, now that I think about it,
it should just be a body.
It should be a robot body that your soul goes into.
- Yeah, this is making way more sense than just the outs,
'cause the outside's only half the story
when it comes to living.
- Less than half, maybe.
- You need some kind of haptic feedback tube
that goes through all of your intestines,
through your stomach, one that sits in your heart.
You need a coating around every single organ
for it to be a true haptic feedback suit.
- Well, couldn't that just like,
couldn't that be, I mean, just kind of like an exoskeleton?
- No, you need a different-- - No, you need an endoskeleton.
- An endoskeleton, okay.
- You need a skeleton.
- I was thinking, I was imagining an exoskeleton
that has different tubes for different orifices,
like little things for your eyes,
something that goes in your butt, your urethra,
your ear holes. - You need to be able
to bite your fingernails.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah, you need to be able,
the suit needs to be able to simulate
you biting your fingernails,
and also your fingernails getting shorter
when you bite them.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And gradually growing back.
It needs to really cover everything,
or else what's the point?
So I guess you're right, it should just be a robot.
Guys, speak--
- Cameron just became a girl.
- Wait, what?
- Just playing around with my avatar.
So just another thing you can do in Second Life,
no big deal.
- Well, Jubia, do you have my slides up?
I'll take that as a-- - Why are you sitting
over there now?
- As a, amazing.
You were talking about prostitution being an escort
earlier, Cameron.
- Oh yeah.
- Oh wait, actually, that comes later.
First of all, guys, so the community in this,
I wouldn't even call it a game,
the community in this world is very strong.
But what breaks down communities in first life?
- The rumor weed. - Infighting.
- The rumor weed, guys. - Yes.
- The rumor weed is a disgusting weed
that we need to get rid of,
but there is a website called Virtual Secrets
on which people share the juiciest of Second Life gossip,
and I wanna show this to you guys.
This is, "Virtual Secrets is one of the most
"highly debated topics in the Second Life community,
"at least for a percentage of users that read/participate
"in blogging within the community.
"Secrets are submitted to the website anonymously
"and are posted by the moderator.
"There is no fact-checking."
- Not that different from the real world, if you ask me.
Consider this website a digital supermarket tabloid
for virtual worlds.
In fancy terms, secrets are user-generated content
submitted for a moderator to post without checking details.
In 2008-- - This is TMZ.
- This is TMZ.
In 2008, Virtual Secrets started and has become
one of the most popular gossip, rag,
slam book style sites about Second Life.
If you don't like what you see here,
You can close the browser.
Holy shit, that's some Tyler the Creator shit.
Lords, you are forever my girl, I will miss you.
Which I'm guessing is one of these two beautiful women
at the bottom of the page.
So I wanna show you--
- I'm guessing it's the one at the bottom.
- I wanna show you guys some of these
gossip/ragslack/slambook style slams.
Number 11, this is from the most recent week.
This is a meme and it's two buttons.
One says, "Take one for the team."
And the other says, "Fuck Emily at the Villa
or we all get banned."
And then the sweating guy says,
"She has a bigger cock than me."
So this is a, I guess, some kind of situation
that's going on this week in Second Life
at the Villa with Emily,
because there's a bunch of these posts about Emily.
This next one is Bernie Sanders,
and it says, "The real Emily from the Villa."
And it's Bernie Sanders saying,
I'm once again asking, "Fuck me or I ban you and your friends."
And then this one is the exit, the car veering through the exit photo.
And going straight is, "But don't tell my boyfriend, okay?"
The exit is, "Fuck me or I ban you and your friends."
And the car is me running from Emily at the villa.
I'm not sure I've even processed this one.
This one seems like it was created wrong because wouldn't they be running towards...
These are not professional meme makers, man.
These are just people trying to do slam books.
Uh-huh.
Well, I think this one is a whiff.
This one is a little bit of a whiff, but this next one, guys, this one's good.
This is "Fuck Emily or Draw 25" and then "Every Guy at the Villa Has a Bunch of Uno Cards."
"At the Villa," man.
So I think that we need to go check out the villa at some point.
Yeah we gotta check out the villa.
Cause I wanna meet this Emily, maybe we get an exclusive interview or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll have her on to defend her honor.
This is, so apparently people in Second Life make Facebook profiles for, not themselves
but for their characters, their alter egos.
And this is Josh Dyed who made a post that says "People when it's Black Power and a smiling
guy.
when it's white power and a raging guy.
I find it very interesting how you guys like to give creators the benefit of the doubt
when they are being racist, but when a creator makes a mistake on a product, y'all go on
a crusade.
Maybe because throwing racism around at the drop of a hat subtracts from and is an insult
to actual instances of racism.
If you're okay with one race empowering themselves, showing pride, etc. and not another and leap
to associate only one with racism, then congratulations, you are the problem, you have prejudice in
your heart.
So guys, there is, this is, a lot of people think that they could go to second life to
escape this racial world.
It's not going to work, buddy.
It's racial in here, too.
It's just as, if not more racial, in this second life.
That's insane.
Sarah Mercury from WAP, whiny ass pig.
Bitch, you ain't no Barbie, I see you work at Arby's.
One big room full of fat bitches.
Bullying is never okay, unless it's me doing it behind your back.
there is a seat that says pig bitch big farts.
- That is a--
- This is completely an Instagram style meme.
- Yeah, I mean look at that,
that's a parody of Kreashan's Gucci Gucci in there.
And then, who is Sarah from Mercury WAP?
Or Sarah Mercury, what is WAP?
I want to know all this stuff.
- I'm guessing this is one of these worlds.
But WAP I guess stands for--
- Wet ass pussy, that's what I heard that stands for.
- Whiny ass pig is what it,
See, that's what it stands for in first life.
In second life, this is whiny ass pig.
- I honestly, and that's maybe the one thing
where I like first life better than the second life.
- Same. - Damn, Cam!
You crazy!
- And then I think this is the last gossip one.
This is a picture of a child named Bubbles Blep.
(laughing)
Bubbles Blep.
It says, "What did she even do to everyone
to make them hate her so much. Genuinely curious, it seems like she has the whole of all second
life communities backing her up. People in the last virtual secret said she did stuff
but what did she do exactly? So apparently Bubbles Blep is the center of some kind of
massive controversy right now. And I can't imagine being mad at this. This is just a
little ass kid, what could this kid possibly be doing? Yeah, it's Bubbles Blep. How could
- Why would you be mad at a kid named Bubbles, man?
- Bubbles, Bubbles Blip.
- Bubbles Blip. - What a name.
- Bubbles Blip.
So you were talking about escorting earlier
and being a prostitute as a way to make linden.
So I found this website called Second Life Adventures,
I think it's a blog spot,
and it's this woman, Caroline Takeda.
Caroline Takeda is a well-known name
in the virtual world of Second Life.
She is a blogger, porn producer, and escort girl who has made a name for herself in this
virtual world.
Okay, so let's read about some of her adventures.
She has a guide to doing escorting in Second Life.
And I was looking through it and it has just like some examples of some work she does.
How to make money as an escort girl in Second Life updated June 2022.
You are thinking about a career as an escort girl in Second Life?
Then you should read this post.
It gives you an insight into what you can expect working in this profession.
This is one of her stories.
"Caroline, sorry to bother you.
I'm a big fan and would love to discuss some escort services with you whenever you're available."
This is Kevin, and Kevin has nothing in common with George at all.
The thing is, the title is "Not Every Client is George Clooney."
So she's saying this guy has nothing in common with Mr. Salt-N-Pepper.
He did not even want to look like the pretty and famous.
Instead he created an avatar that resembles pretty much the type he is in real life.
The result is a heavily overweight guy.
I really enjoyed reading about all your adventures on the blog.
It's super hot.
The fact that you escort me and that I have the opportunity to be with you makes it even
hotter.
I just like the whole experience in general.
In fact, I get most of my clients either via this blog or via my profile on our escort
website.
Kevin booked me for an hour.
He actually considers himself a groupie.
i like that
so here's a photo of him and of her and kevin
uh...
this
i have since you're dead
uh... this is
this is an example of a standard sex job this is
i'm guessing is fat as you can possibly make it
perfect for itself
no you can walk around i think you're pretty crazy with it
i've not seen anybody have this kind of body
but the uncensored photo, he has a bright pink
little tiny cock and she is holding it.
And there's a lot more photos from this engagement.
And I would really quickly like to say,
so her services cost 1,000 Linden an hour.
- Okay, what's that in real life dollars?
- How much is real life dollars into Linden?
- I looked it up, 1,000 Linden is $3.
(laughing)
$3 an hour.
She has sex with guys that don't look
exactly like George Clooney.
Here's another one.
One of my regular clients is very imaginative
and a bit of a pervert.
Every time he hires me--
- Maybe it's Cameron's rival here.
- You think this is Cameron?
Oh, it could be pervert one.
Every time he hires me,
he comes up with another kinky thing to do.
For some of his dirty fantasies,
it would be rather difficult
to find a non-professional partner.
That's a job for a professional sex worker.
The last time I met him,
he made me kneel in a dirty stall of a pig's die.
I sat right between a couple of pigs
to serve him as a dirty sex toy.
I had a long shower after that one.
And let's look at a photo from this experience.
Sex in a pig's die.
Fucked in a pig's die.
So this is, she's having--
- But the pigs are there.
- There's pigs.
- She's waiting for the pigs.
(laughing)
She's having sex in front of a bunch of pigs.
And also there's a guy in the back.
I caught this, I was censoring this photo,
and I caught this at the last second.
There's a guy just laying on a bale of hay
with a beer and he had his cock out.
So this guy, I guess this is some kind of--
- The guy's just chilling and watching, I guess.
- He's just chilling, yeah.
There's no, you know, you don't have to wear clothes in this.
But that's sex in a pigsty.
- Oh, it's not the real world.
- And then this is, I think, my favorite thing I've found
on her website.
This is the fucking rat.
Ever had sex with a furry in Second Life?
And so-- - The fucking rat.
- For the audio listeners, this is a photo
of a kind of a brooding rat wearing a leather jacket,
jeans, and some boots at what looks to be a cafe
or a restaurant.
And he's kind of looking mysterious.
The chair is too big.
It's not made for a rat, this is a human chair.
And so this guy, this is not somebody paying to have sex
with Mrs. Makeda, or Takeda, Caroline.
This is somebody who is trying to become an escort, okay?
- Oh.
- Do you want to do the rat?
A question I received from the Sleen.
That's her partner.
- The Sleen?
- The Sleen.
- What the hell are you talking about?
Apparently we received an escort application
via the form on the website
from a furry portraying a rat-human hybrid, a male rat,
which is why the Sleen didn't want to conduct the interview.
The Sleen is male.
Come on, I said.
You have experience with half humans.
Remember Felmane, which goes to a 404,
so this is a deleted page.
He replied, "She was a half cat
"and a hot teenager in real life."
That is the opposite of a male rat, don't you think so?
All right, I did the interview.
I met him at the reception area in the office,
casually dresses in jeans, simple top,
and my favorite boots.
Nothing too sexy, just like the girl next door.
- The male fucking rat was dressed like the girl next door.
- I wanted to make sure to create a strictly professional,
non-sexual impression.
Didn't want him to think about sex with me at all.
No, I don't do rats.
Call me rodent phobic, but no.
The rat was very pleasant to talk to.
I learned quite a bit about the furry communities that day.
Yes, they do have sex as well.
Apparently it's quite a thing.
Maybe we discovered a niche here.
So now she's interested.
I invited him to the Sky apartment after a bit.
No, not for sex, just for a bit more relaxed,
less cold ambiance,
continuing our talk over a bottle of wine.
And then this is a photo of her having wine with the rat.
and it's called, I cropped the caption out,
but it's called, "Nothing wrong with a glass of wine, right?"
- I bet one thing led to another, doesn't it?
- Well, you'll see here pretty soon.
He did raise the question though,
"Isn't it the Sleen who typically does
"the interviews and casting?
"Are you doing it because I'm a male?"
The Sleen. - The Sleen.
- "Are you doing it because I am male?"
"Yes, that's why," I replied.
"Are going to do the audition with me then?"
He continued.
"I noticed from our conversation,
"You know what you're doing.
"When it comes to emoting and role play,
"you are doing very well at that.
"And honestly, it would feel a bit weird
"to have sex with a half rat," I replied.
"Caroline, you are seen by many
"as the princess of sex in Second Life.
"Shouldn't you have tried everything at least once
"to maintain that reputation?"
He did have a point there.
"I will think about it," I promised.
"Most importantly, get me some text
"and some nice pictures over
"so I can put you on the website."
- That is incredible half rat riz.
If a half rat man walked up to you in a bar
and he was hitting on you and you're like,
"I'm sorry, I'm not interested."
And he was like, "Shouldn't you try it?
"Don't you wanna try fucking a half rat at least once?"
A male rat.
- That only works in the second life.
The first life, almost no women would have sex
with a half rat.
- No, very small percentage of the community.
- A few days later.
Caroline, that sofa you wrote about as Michelle,
the ruckus let's smash couch one,
They released a bed now,
which is even better than the sofa.
I bought one for my own apartment.
This is from the rat.
That sparked my curiosity.
Mind sending me a taxi?
Would like to see that actually, I asked.
Which by the way, you can fly in this game.
And you can teleport in this game.
But she is taking a taxi.
- It's called stimulating the economy.
You know, you gotta--
- I guess you're right.
- The taxi drivers gotta make their lindens too.
- I can't imagine, if a prostitute is making three bucks
an hour, I can't imagine what a fucking
tachy driver makes in this game.
(laughing)
Seconds later, I was standing in his apartment.
Very different place, really.
It was on one of the upper floors of a building
providing living space to furries.
In fact, the entire region was offering a place to live
for the furry community.
There must be quite a big community when they build
entire regions for them.
The apartment as such reminded me at 80s architecture.
Very colorful, nicely decorated and spacious,
featuring living room, bathroom, a kitchen,
and of course, a bedroom for sex fun.
That's where he--
- I guess that is interesting.
I never thought about it before,
but in second life, really the only reason
you do need a bedroom is for sex.
- Yeah, you're not sleeping?
- Yeah, it's only a sex room.
- Well, she does have another segment on this website
called AFK sex, which I guess is you can,
you can like when you go away or like log off,
you can put your character in a sex position
with another person, which is pretty awesome.
Also, apparently a big problem is that people make alts
and play on like two different windows
and pretend that they are like actually pulling
and like having sex with people,
but they're having sex with themselves,
which is a big problem if you look into virtual secrets,
guys a lot of gossip about this. That's crazy. Anyway, that's
where he had placed his new ruckus. Let's smash bed. He sat
on the bed and explain some features such as many more
cuddle animations than the sofa actually has. Okay. Let's test
them. I want to see the different animations. I heard
myself saying and added quickly. This does not count as
having sex. This is just testing the bed a strictly technical
I took off my clothes and joined him on the bed.
I noticed I made his tail twitch a little.
He couldn't hide a little excitement.
He could hide it. He's using the computer.
He had to click twitch tail.
He had to click on a button that said twitch my tail.
We went through the menu, pose by pose, to see what they were like.
He couldn't resist some sex talk and roleplay in between.
Nor could I. The habit, I guess.
Here's some examples.
Guys, here's some examples of the ruckus let's smash bed with the rat.
Okay, you ready?
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
So.
They're just testing the bed.
This is not sexual at all.
No, technical.
This rat, by the way, this is, I've censored these photos, this rat has a huge white dick.
a giant white penis coming out of this rat's body and he is taking he is making uh caroline's
having one of the best nights of her life depending i mean looking at these photos um
she's fucking this rat y'all and then this is a photo that is captioned getting fucked
by the rat honestly yes it was fun looking at the rat mounting me fucking me and getting
all excited about it and even ending in real life climax. No, it did not excite me sexually
or arouse me. I can certainly say it is not my thing, but at least I tried it once. I
can say now, I got fucked by a rat.
Jesus.
So that's an amazing story from Caroline, guys.
That is such an inspiring and wonderful story for all the rats of the world.
If you're a rat...
Rats, it's possible.
Buddy, this is in your future.
Yeah, let me pull mine up here.
Am I going next or...
Oh, okay.
Or actually, let me put it in slideshow mode.
Okay.
Oh gosh.
Is this working?
Can you see a blank white screen?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alright, here's what I found today.
So first of all, here's just one guy I found who had a bunch of posts, but I just threw
this in here.
This is Clive Steele.
He's on the Second Life forums.
He says, "To all the sick-" and his thing is that he does a bunch of italics and different
fonts and boldings and colors of text.
He likes to really spruce up his posts here.
"To all the sick twisted haters who've tried to make my life miserable on Second Life since
2010, I have a hot girlfriend and you can't knock me down.
Where's your (laughs in parentheses) girlfriend, oh keyboard warrior?
Losers!
RFLMAO."
and then it's a picture of it looks like one of the twins from the matrix without
the dreads riding a motorcycle behind a woman who has a very low-cut shirt and
big things yeah that looks like Eminem dude yeah it does wearing matrix glasses
in the man a matrix robe I just really liked that he was I liked he's riding
behind the girl.
I thought that was really funny.
And then someone replied to him and said, how much did she cost?
And he said, how about you PM me your address and we take it from
there? Oh, we can have and then a fist emoji. I just thought cowardly
calf went crazy. That is cowardly calf. Incredible.
Here's a post.
uh...
most discriminated against group of avatars this is by female winslet
uh... and female winslet says furry hate is pretty legendary in second life and
i've always assumed that furries were probably the most hated and
discriminated against group in second life but recently i have wondered if
that is true
thoughts on who it might be and why
uh... and then a bunch of people had different ideas besides furries on who
was the most hated group of people in second life and there's a bunch of
groups of people in second life i didn't even know existed
we got of course balloon pilots.
(laughing)
There's so many of these that I just don't understand
what it could possibly mean.
But Anna Nova says, "Balloon pilots,
"you wouldn't believe how many ban lines
"and worse still, zero delay security orbs there are.
"I think anything that has a range more than 100 meters
"should be banned by the TOS
"to react faster than 10 seconds."
I have no clue what that could possibly mean,
but this person thinks balloon pilots
are very discriminated against in Second Life. We also have vampires. "No biting signs in
many public areas are one thing, but often this extends to 'no' insert brand name vampires.
You will be staked. I've managed to avoid becoming a vampire despite my home RP sim seemingly
morphing into a vampire RP plays, but hold no ill will towards vampires and have only
rarely encountered rude ones who try to bite random people." It's so funny to me that this
person is running a home roleplay simulator and it just gets invaded.
Yeah, I can't fucking stop running into these vampires.
They're just trying so hard not to become a vampire.
Well also, good on him for not giving into the hate there.
He's like, "No, these are good, hard-working people, even though they're invading my random
RP and trying to bite me."
It is so fucking funny that you could be like, "I want to join Second Life.
I want to roleplay.
I want to be I want to be the owner of a 7-eleven. I want to
run a 7-eleven and somebody else's fantasy can just completely
encroach on yours and be like we're a bunch of werewolves and
we're going to come.
You're working at your job. Yeah, it does seem like the
entire the entire game. If you can just be a vampire in
anything, then the entire game is a vampire RP. Yeah, it is
and vampires are one of the default options for avatars. I
noticed here's another one. I am an elf and run two Sims and
a store of my own and I am also a guard on two other Sims most
people we have ever had to ban have been human avatars. In fact, I would go so far as to say
that 95% of those who incur a ban are human avatars. But we do not ban humans. Just because
one or two of an avatar type may do something wrong does not mean they all need to be banned.
Judge the individual, not the whole type. So this is a rare example of a non-racist
elf. Wow. An elf who doesn't want to ban all humans. Are most second life elves racist?
Is that why you're saying that?
I have no idea, but I just said that.
But it seems like maybe they are to me.
The latest folks to be discriminated against in Second Life are flyers.
Y'all flyers have been discriminated against recently.
True, we almost got banned from this server for flying.
I am now getting booted from many sims because I'm in fly mode when I tp in and I don't land
fast enough.
Flyers should not be discriminated against.
it's not right this to this isn't a group of people who got
discriminated against, but this is a little every forum thread
and second life completely derails into an insane argument
that I don't understand at all for like at least one full page
and the results are always so insane. I read another I didn't
put this part in, but another that I was reading just randomly
became an argument about whether Islam is an okay religion. It
was like it was like a thread that was like what are you
today. But this this argument that came into this thread was so somebody said I
would expect an officer of a role play sim will be better in drawing the line
between in character and out of character but then again you said you
were just office here because of personal relations so whatever and this
person replied and said I find that many people in Second Life take their RP way
too seriously when I tell people I don't RP they go but but but Second Life is
all RP in the demon RP sim there was a rule that no one was allowed to play with
a demon's private pet. If someone asked me if it was okay to play with a demon's private
pet, I'd say, "Well, it's against the rules, but if you can find a willing pet, go for
it." It was none of my concern if they wanted to incur the wrath of a demon. That would
actually make for a better RP experience than just following the rule. Then, if the demon
came back to me, I'd tell him it wasn't my problem if he couldn't keep his or her pets
in line. So there was basically a giant argument in this thread about whether it should be
allowed
to this uh... play with the demons private pet and what officers should do
about it
this side or emerald person is somebody that i i kept seeing a lot on the forms
it's a lot of uh... people who to are very active
what appears a lot of stuff
it's incredible
then another more another discriminated against group of people
so the no says no answer for you to scrimmage
I really love soda gnomes.
No extra details.
Gnomes are pretty discriminated against.
Do you primarily use a human avatar?
By Gopi Passiflora.
Moira Kathleen says, "I'm primarily human.
Once in a while, maybe a couple of times a year,
I'll go around as a dinky for a week or two."
I googled what a dinky is,
and it's a little anthropomorphic cat.
And this is one of the first results on Google
dinky's Navi avatar
And to use this Navi dinky avatar you need the dinky kitty avatar
Okay, so don't be trying to use the Navi without the dinky kitty. Yeah, you need the dinky. There's levels to this shit
If you think that you don't need a dinky. But it seems like dinkys are pretty popular right now
Yeah, what do you say? If you think you don't need a dinky buddy, you better do some dinky. You got another thing coming
Is there a shi- is there an oblock RP?
*laughter*
like there is a lot i had a good but i didn't put some input there were people
complaining about people acting gangster
yeah
uh... for a little bit
about a year this shit up
uh...
no
what is that happened
and
well in the end of the road where the s_d_s primarily is human avatar rick
nightingale said
nope primarily a frog now occasional frog and in this picture
which if you're listening audio just tune in for this one second a look at this
picture to the top it's really hard it's a
muscular green man who looks like he has
his skin looks like the floor at like an arcade
like it's got those little like you know respect goals in it
any sticking out a green tongue and he's eating a figure and he's i would say
opposed like a frog
but you know i was back
you know i don't know
no he's not a frog was on a lily pad on a little bit of normal for a connection
yeah uh... it is a crazy picture and there's women flying away from him and
trying to know what god
that is incredible and he has a mohawk
yeah he's only frog i've ever seen with a mohawk
what a frog yeah uh...
and then so to know mister
this is completely context list uh... out of nowhere he says
as a no i've never found an attractive female no man second life so i am
pursuing a relationship with a human at the moment. Wow. And here in this picture
you can better see Sodanome's full outfit. He's got a gnome from the waist up only.
Yeah, he's got a classic garden gnome head with the beard, kind of a cone hat
pulled down over his eyes. His shirt is of all over print of a lion. He's wearing
red gloves and red tights little black patagonia baggy type shorts and then he's got some converse on
and he's with a woman with an onion ass
yeah
he's with a big assed woman
and it looks like he might be in japan
he be popping soda bottles and he got bitches in japan
so to know i'm so just keep this remember so that i was going to come back period
for the hope is that every single threat of this website is talking about the
people who
uh...
need ideas for a male punk abby i'm thinking of using johnnie rotten of the
sex pistols in his prime as a possible influence
i know my punk did love a mohawk in a black vest of some sort what other
necessities
does the punk aesthetic have
and so to know says
I made a Johnny Rotten who is 600 years old and a gnome.
(laughing)
- I see it, 7-Eleven!
- This is a gnome who's at 7-Eleven
wearing full rainbow clothing
and has a rainbow mohawk that's about the height of his body.
- And it's also poking out of his hat.
He still has a hat. - Oh my God.
- Yeah.
- That is incredible.
- That's so to gnome 600 year old Johnny Rotten.
How does your second life look today?
i'm starting this thread so we can post pics of absolutely anything we like in
second life a rock
a set of stairs our homes
your nose whatever
i'm starting with a couple of pics from the island as it is now
so yeah this is going to be a little picture heavy but i'll paint a picture
with all the same for everyone
and this is from bagnew
so to know
so to know it says
the rainbow gnome a new superhero was born and it's his same rainbow johnny
rotten gnome but he's flying through the clouds. Then we have do gay or bi women
outnumber straight women in Second Life a question asked by Sam's Byron. Someone
said Beth Quandar says women running male avvies are way better lovers than most
guys and Sodanome says not gnome males.
Damn, Sodanome getting after it. Yeah, he can't find a female gnome though he has
to date humans. He's got to be the biggest celebrity in Second Life. Yeah, I did find
another throw where people were like, "Sodanome sighting!" That's amazing. Wait, we need to
add him. Yeah. "What are you doing today?" Okay, this is the, I think this is the one
that's kind of picture heavy. By Kasumi Ravenheart. Zanessa posts Sunday morning cartoons and
it's a woman in in
the job of very revealing pajamas and back
on a apollo
you know i don't know what i'm doing room with a gigantic probably two hundred
inch tv on the wall and she's watching family guy on the fox website
it's not her t_v_ while
it's so funny to imagine
well first of all watching family guy for funds for sunday morning cartoons but
then also having a giant as t_v_ and instead of was watching it show you pull
it up on a website
on the TV. So here's Zanessa again back in her living room watching classics. She's
watching I Love Lucy I think on her TV. She just likes TV, she likes Family Guy and
the classics. Beautiful modern home too. Yeah it's wonderful I mean look at
the wall. Wow. That's exactly the kind of wall you want in a house is a rugged
outdoor type of stone wall you might see in a garden. Zanessa, if you're
- Zanessa, it's not all fun and games for Zanessa.
Sometimes there's work to be done.
And here she is alone in a meeting room
and she's working on a website called Estequely Virtual.
And it looks like she's working hard on her laptop.
- Maybe she's some kind of real estate agent.
- It seems like that could be the case, yeah.
- Zanessa, if you're listening to this,
please add Cameron Fetter on Second Life.
He can show you the world.
- Zanessa, you're gonna like him a lot.
he's gonna take you out of this hustle and bustle of the workforce.
You're gonna watch cartoons all day, baby girl.
This thread is like hundreds of pages long and most of it is exactly like people with
women avatars who are wearing bikinis and they're just doing mundane everyday stuff
with their kids out.
It's pretty crazy.
But it's also stuff like Orwar who posts, "Just sitting in my living room listening to the
sparkling of the fireplace, the ticking and chiming of my clock, and the soft music of
the harpsichord playing away.
And it's in a room that's almost completely pitch black.
You can just see him sitting in a very ornate chair next to a gramophone.
He's there, does he have a fucking gramophone?
This is kinda scary.
I don't think I would want to join this guy.
He's a carnivore.
Yeah, it says "concupescent carnivore" is his bio.
I don't want anything to do with Orwar.
sparkling of the fireplace and that listening to the ticking and chiming of
my clock
you don't get stuff like that now it is that's all uh... nine-dollar box don't
take or chan
only girl
my three painting for the cultivate homes for a troops auction fundraiser
are finished and set up in the gallery i will get more info to you all if john
doesn't post in the art section as soon as i get it
so here we have
uh... a woman who's standing in front of these gigantic twenty foot tall paintings
that she's made of
a woman holding an american flag a woman dancing on jupiter and a woman maybe
turning into radiation waves
yeah something
uh... and they're beautiful
and they're going to the troops
uh... but tell you
now i'm sitting in a birdcage watching a giant baby
oh my god
uh... that is a scary baby
sitting in a birdcage and she's watching a giant baby
If you can be small and gnome-like, can you also choose to become a humongous giant?
This is a problem in Second Life.
This is the number one thing people complain about, is that height creep.
People have gradually been making their avatars taller and taller, where people will complain
they have an original avatar from when they first logged in years ago, they join now and
it's like half the size of everybody else.
Because everyone keeps making their things bigger and bigger.
It's been an issue.
inflation or deflation or something but with height it's something flation it's
something flation on this is my last one this is from Emperor Napoleon Bonaparte
he says dying inside and it's a picture of Napoleon Bonaparte who looks like he
having some kind of a shot into something yeah yeah Wow and he's dying
inside well reddable me and Patrick are on a horse together yeah how did you guys
- You guys see my new avatar?
- Yeah, he looks very, very cool.
I'm not gonna lie, he looks cool.
I wish I knew how to change my avatar.
- Yeah.
All right, so, hold on,
let me start sharing my screen real quick.
So, I got very interested
in the political inner workings of Second Life.
I wanted to know what everyone on this website,
where they lean, you know?
I was starting to look for stuff.
and i saw this post from twenty twelve
ron paul for president posted by your honor
i am not u_s_ but if i was i would vote for him how many here agree
and med who's simone a bento guru said
bomb to
i'm a big ron paul fan heart emoji now look at this photo of ben who are med
who's simone
a kind of scary
doesn't but does it look familiar to you
uh...
no who does that look like
do you guys
i think that this
is in alias
an alien ron de santis all my god the overlay look
look at how this line is a shit
i think that this is ron de santis in second life
it looks almost exactly like him
Isn't this fucking crazy?
- This is pretty crazy.
- Wait, but this is claiming he was not in the US.
Now we have all three of them.
- Well, no, no, no, that was Johan Ruh.
Johan Ruh was not in the US.
- Oh, okay.
- This is Medhu Simone,
which I think if you jumble those letters around,
it may spell Ron DeSantis.
- Is that true?
- Yeah, if you jumble them
and turn them into different letters,
it'll be Ron DeSantis.
It's the same amount of characters.
this next one. Politically neutral alternatives to black lives matter. I want to support racial
equality, reduce instances of racial prejudice, and generally live in a more accepting society,
safe, inclusive world for everybody. So I should support BLM, right? Well, I don't think
so. BLM is a registered organization that openly described themselves as subscribing
to many elements of Marxism. And I didn't read the whole thread, but here's a moderator
saying this topic may this topic seem to have gotten off topic so we're going to
lock it please remember in the future to treat others with respect and follow our
community standards when posting and replying on the forums.
Can I throw something in here? I noticed a lot of locked threads and something I
noticed is every single moderator and admin on the forum all have the name
like first name Lyndon. Yeah Lyndon means like the creator was named like
something Linden. I know so that's what all the all the mods and you have to
join the the Linden family. Yeah. To become a mod. It's a family affair. Yeah. It's a mafia.
It's a family business. This next one. Looking for a Mesh Donald Trump avatar and Love
Zhao Ying says if a jelly doll could wear an orange Cheeto that would come close.
I think that John Oliver already said something like this. Yeah I think that
they're just aping John Oliver here. I think you'd already call Donald Trump a jelly doll. Yeah a jelly doll wearing an orange Cheeto.
Donald Trump you are a- Donald Trump is a jelly doll wearing an orange Cheeto!
*laughter*
Yep.
Oh and that post was by Vanity Fair, so I think that there is a- I think Vanity Fair was planning something here.
And they were gonna plan a smear campaign against 45. This next one
Pedo hunter
So sick of child avatars and adult zone skyboxes with kitty stuff in thinking of setting myself up as a pedo hunter and effectively
Just hunt them out before anyone starts
I'm not after your kid RP as far as I'm concerned your weird hobby is your is your own
So long as it's not stripping down and getting intimate and Rhonda Huntress said taking the express train to Bandsville
Eh?
Good luck.
Then, Sio Emerald said, "Have fun in your vicious circle of frustration."
Which, then, Sparky Linden said, "This looks very similar to a thread that Tommy Linden
just closed recently."
And given the inappropriate nature of the title and the content of the thread, we're gonna
go ahead and lock the thread this time.
So if you try to become a pedo hunter in Second Life, it goes against some community guideline
or something.
Amber Frost, created by user Ja Porca, they said, "Do you think Amber Frost will start
the socialist revolution in America?
I have been watching close on YouTube and seeing him, she is turning everyone against Trump
and is making $100,000 a month from her podcast.
To which Cindy Evanier said, "Religion and politics, two subjects we have been told are
best kept off the SL forums, which got 11 hearts and three rewards."
She got three awards, I mean.
That is crazy.
Wow.
Yeah.
want to talk about Amber Frost or Chappo or any kind of left-leaning political
stuff you will be banned from the forums or that I think this like thing was
closed on this next one so then I stopped getting political and I started looking
at the adult side of it and this is from Zappa Olchawi they said recommendations
for penises and their post said hello everyone sorry for what must be a
a frequent question, but I am newly a premium member and I want to get a good bleep.
Could you refer me to a good previous thread or make suggestions?
I currently have a delight bleep which is free, comes with a HUD, but the HUD seems
to let others interact with my bleep, but I cannot cause it to be erect.
For instance, could anyone recommend any very good penises that my avatar Zappa can make
erect?
especially looking for animated penises and not just Zappa licks Zappa's bleep.
Thanks!" and then another person said "diaper bondage and institutional role
play. I am into the whole intimate must wear, inmate must wear diaper and be
restrained at all times thing but unfortunately many of the prisons on
Second Life lack this. Furthermore I enjoy insane asylums and padded cells
but I cannot find many on Second Life. Does anyone know places that may cater to
these kinds of interests? Also, finally, what are the more unique prisons? A lot of
them are too similar and I was just wondering if there are any that truly
stand out. So there are prisons in Second Life where you can become just like a
sexual diaper prisoner. I mean a padded cell is a big diaper. Yeah, it's one big
diaper. That's true. That's why they call it a padded cell. Yeah. This next one, Big
Boobs from 99spooner. Does anyone know a place to find busty girls to have sex
with for free? Just wondering. And then here is an argument that I saw. So Leah36
said, "Me looks down. Um, do I needs implants?" And Charlie Muggins then said, "Given the
way you express yourself, you're looking in the wrong direction.
Then Madeline Blackbart said, "Wow, grammar Nazi-ing again."
What's with all the grammar Nazis?
Or are you the same one from last time?
You do realize that she's using sarcasm here.
The needs implants is supposed to be parody.
Wow, this guy's white knighting.
If you're going to do satire, you better make sure it's distinct from what you're parodying
or else you might contribute to the issue.
sad that the virus of white knighting has even gotten to second life oh yeah this
is sad as fuck mm-hmm yeah what's this next one here Oh porn films in second
life so you you talked about that what's her name something Takeda she said this
is by Jamie Miller shout out to the podcast sleaze oids so Jamie Miller from
sleazoids ass well yeah I mean that's a film podcast they just want to see
different kinds of movies. I see Jamie you tried to spell your name a
little different here but we're on to you. We got you. I was curious if there is such
thing as SL porn films I've been approached several times to do
porn with the promise that it pays very well I'm a bit naive with this so any
help would be appreciated and Tamara Artist said I have two friends from SL
porn industry here's a video that one of them made which then redirected to SL
porn tube which you guys there's a hole there was it's gone now but I was able
to find on the way back machine SL porn tube which has the banner for Don
Reginaldo which is a second life cigar brand and there it's a the on the side
here you can see these are all the the most popular categories which includes
Pocky Brocco, Vlad Sharktooth, Demonic Foursome, Sex Cat, Anal Brows, Stranger, Kiss
Vaginal Anal, Pretty, Hyannis, Alicia, Music Video, Alex Komarov, E-Boobs, Plus
None, Pantyhose, Viola, Tentacles, Sex, Natalie Zenga, Rez Day, Naughty Girls, Mr.
V sex studio DP rectal revenge hell-kitchen miss Emily 63 and seduction
and there were such these are these are three of the best video titles that I
saw on this website number one being extreme bitch number two DJ got us
fucking and number three Titanic 100 which I wish I could have watched all
these I want to see what I want to see what a classic loss I want to see what
Titanic 100th anniversary is I want to see this touching tribute they probably
fuck it on the boat or maybe it's the boat fucking iceberg man yeah maybe and
well that's like the library of Alexandria yeah well guys that they're
all uploaded somewhere else oh my god we're all on the horse together now I
have only one thing to say to you please get your ass in this world because it's
popping off in this bitch. Leave the old world behind. The war, the disease, there's none
of that here. There's vampires and people who dress up like kids. This is where you need
to be guys. This is the ultimate youth group. Get here right now.
Is there any way-
We're flying around on a horse, motherfucker.
Oh my god, this is amazing.
Is there any way that we can make our own second life world? I'm sure this would cost a lot
of money.
It would be millions of Lindians.
Yeah, it would be a lot of money.
How much is this?
Yeah.
I'm ready to spend my entire life in here.
I do love it. We're going to ride off into the sunset.
Oh my god.
We just got stuck on a billboard.
Guardians of the Galaxy has just premiered.
Oh my fucking god.
We have to go to the movies right now.
Alright.
Alright, so come see us.
Oh yeah, what are you going to say?
Well no, you do that first.
see us at World's Biggest Army, or Underworld's Biggest Mummy on October 20th at Littlefield
in Brooklyn. Tickets at swagpoop.com/shows. Then you can see me at Opening for Girl God
in Chicago on November 5th. And then, I don't know, I'm on a show tonight, Secret Third Thing
at Rubalad and then tomorrow I'm also on another show at Union Hall. That's my plug.
Nice. Go ahead and if you head over to the Patreon too, patreon.com/podcastaboutlist,
you can subscribe to get extra episodes every week and D&D as well and more stuff.
And basically Beers with Drake as well.
No, I'm not sure that's on there anymore. I heard that that was ended a few weeks ago.
And then also one week from today, the battle of the century.
Oh yes.
Be here, YouTube.
It's going to blow your fucking mind.
Julio will put the teaser that I made right now.
[music]
Imagine to be on Halloween night, you think I'm going to dress up as a real
actual lifestyle of a person. Yeah, I'm going to make someone's culture my
costume. That's like me. That's like me dressing up like like my word
happens.
I'm going to start. I got to start saying my word again. Yeah, I think that I
to start scoffing. I say my word sometimes I think.
E-Gads. E-Gads is not as good as my word. Zoonz. Zoonz? You mean Zooks? No, you're thinking
of Gadzooks. I'm saying Zoonz. That's Shakespearean. Zoonz? Z-O-U-N-D-S. Zoonz.
I was like Zoonz and then Zoonz would be tunes to sounds. Zoonz is short for God's
God's wounds.
Yeah, that'd be like me dressing up like an emo.
You took that long to think of that?
It didn't feel, it wasn't that long.
It was pretty long.
And that'd be like me dressing up like an emo or a cinephile.
You're dressed like a cinephile right now, a child cinephile.
Okay.
Just seen the new Winnie the Pooh movie.
I've just seen
rocking up to
the kids
standing up at the end of cars for Bravo.
There's a report that the cars for Premiere got a 10 minute
standing ovation from one guy.
Yeah, like it's a fucking con
Premiere.
Nowhere is like a movie theater and fucking the first showing in Illinois.
Got a 45 minute standing ovation.
Couldn't get the guy out of the theater.
From a man named Bruce Meese.
Local film critic.
[MUSIC PLAYING]