I
did a clap yeah. Well, along an early clip, a very early clap. I am in a war
me to actually really we're both in wars. Yeah. I think your war is cooler
than mine. No, okay, well, then you start with your war because I want to
I need tips and tricks on wars now.
I don't know if your war is what I'm thinking of. I'm not sure my war will help you that much with yours.
Okay.
But I've been traumatized. I've been given PTSD.
That's the beginning of war.
Yeah. Well, it's actually what happens after war.
Yeah.
Now that I'm realizing it. So maybe my war is over. Because I don't think you usually get PTSD until afterwards.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah. I was at war with the biggest cockroach of all time.
Oh, God.
Dude, it was so fucking horrible.
horrible. Yeah. Oh, worst experience of my literally I'm still I'm having
I'm having PTSD flashbacks every day to this cockroach. It's I'm not that like
I'm not gonna pretend I'm like brave, but I'm not that squeamish around bugs.
Yeah, I don't care that much, but this like I was it literally ruined my life
is so fucking big. It was crawling up the wall. Is that where you saw? Where
did you spot this sucker? First? I did not spot it. This is this is part of
of why it was so traumatizing. I was you heard tales asleep and I was shaken
awake at six thirty a.m. on on Sunday, because my fiance was getting ready to
work and she saw it in the living room and shook me awake and said, I'm sorry to
wake you up, but there's the biggest cockroach I've ever seen. It's in the
living room, so I got up. I went gigantic crawling up the wall, probably like
like fucking huge. Yeah,
I was completely still asleep and like just looking and it was dark in the
room. I don't want to turn the lights on because I didn't want to run away, so I
could only really make make out the shape of it. Just like a big black
going up the wall yeah. So I go it hides behind the curtain of the window. It
knows how to hide dude. This thing was crazy. I this is literally a full war.
This is so insane. Okay, so I get the raid. I get a shoe. I go. I put I put
clothes on to cover my entire every inch of my body.
You put on coveralls. I was well, I'm a man to look for it and only my
underwear and I was like I cannot you can't expose your no, I can't see every
yeah, it's going to that's on me yeah. So I'm going to start dissing you. I
start knocking against the curtain with the shoe just kind of hitting random
spots to see if I can just kill it like you know, get a quick wall bang just
lucky. Yeah, yeah, it drops down onto the floor. It goes into a corner. I go
up with the raid. I spray it once with raid it dashes. I spray it again. It
goes under the couch like it like runs. No fuck dude. It survived the raid.
so then I'm like what do I do I'm standing guard there is I have like a
railroad apartment, so there's only one way out of my living room, so I'm
standing in that door with the shoe in the right. I'm like if it's trying if it
tries to get into the rest of the house, I'm going to kill it now. It's just
I'm just thinking this is going to be my entire day because she's leaving for
work is not going to be able to relax. So I'm going to go we're about to go
move the couch out so I can go try and get it again right as we're about to
move the couch out. I see it going up the wall behind the couch and I'm like
okay, get I'll get I'll get it. I get the shoe, it goes up onto the wall. I
hit it once with the shoe. I hear it dropped to the ground, keeps running
around. I hit it again with the shoe here, another it runs back under the
couch, so it survived to raid blast two shoe hits at this point and I'm like
I'm like I'm freaking my entire body. I can't I literally is not a car. I hit
with the shoe. I literally fully my like I actually just went.
Did you think at this point that this was some kind of Native American spirit?
I think it was a deeming. Literally, this is so crazy man. I it affected me so
shouldn't be surviving. The story isn't even over. Oh God, so then I'm like
fuck. How do I get it out from under the couch? I'm not going on down on my
hands and knees to try and see where it is. It's going to fly into my face or
something of course, so this and this is where I got. I kind of I got a little
crafty and this is how I so do you remember
do you remember that light we had for the old set that we would velcro up to
the top, though tiny. I don't know what it's called, but it's like a studio type
that, but it's tiny and it's really, really a little after that. Yeah, I have
that in my house. Okay, so what I do is I give that to and I and I put she puts it
on the one end of the couch under it. I've returned up to the highest setting
and then I'm standing at the other side of the couch. She turns it on. It
literally blasts the entire underside of the couch. So you see the lit up so I
could look for I could I was hoping to scare it out and then like kill it right
there. You know what I mean, but it doesn't come out. I'm like did you see a
shadow of it like a long shadow. I did. I wish I did that would be really scary.
It's smoking a cigarette, so then I go down on my hands and knees. I'm like
okay, this I have to get my face down here. I look down one side of the couch.
I don't see anything. I crawl over to the other side. I look down. I see it and
get this it's on its back and it's convulsing. So somehow it had it somehow.
I had some kind of delayed damage to it with either the raid or the shoe where it
survived long enough to take more damage and then go under the couch and then it
stunned like a mortal combat like finish him. Were you scared because you
already knew this was one tricky cockroach? I would literally it's I was
not a fucking thing, so we pull the couch up. I'm like go go go pull the
couch up. So I pull out really fast. I spray it with more raid. It's
literally still twitching around while I'm killing it. I go I get I get a
trash bag. I get trash bags to put over my hands like gloves because our
paper towels are too thin. I'm like I'm not fucking so then I pick it. I
pick it up with paper towel and trash bag hand and I'm so my body is
reacting to it to with so much disgust and fear yeah that I'm squeezing my fist
so tight just because I'm just like and I can just feel it like being crushed to
dust in my hand. I go to flush it down the toilet. I open my hand to drop it
like I can. I'm literally like bit like my finger. I can't pry my finger. I'm so
fucking because I'm like I was a like five minutes ago and now you were
throwing into battle. Yeah, I'm completely and I open my hand and I like
can't control opening my hand and when I do first of all the cockroach falls out
and it's like all its legs are falling up because I squeezed it so hard, but
then I drop the paper towel into the toilet because and I have to reach into
the toilet next to the cockroach to get the paper to
here's my nightmare scenario as I go to flush the paper towel. It clogs the
toilet and then I have a clogged cockroach to and then the cockroach
wakes back yeah exactly. I fully was believing that could happen yeah. I kind
of was expecting him to come back to life again. I literally think you
probably did in the sewer. He's probably like it was crawling
out somewhere on on Rockaway, just like right into the ocean and right now he's
just crawling with his last two legs towards your house. Just so slowly
is up the beach. It was so come on for you horrible. I know it coming for you.
I also that's the thing I tormented this creature. You just did them. You did as
much as you can to something without killing it. I literally yeah. Why does
you within an inch of its life. Why do so many things get sprayed with raid?
This is why I don't keep raid in my house, 'cause it's bad for you. It's
really, really bad for you. But you spray raid on a bug, they never die.
They run around, they get at every other surface in your house. Yeah. You
might as well just be spraying raid. I've never had raid in my life. That
was something that my fiancee brought into my life. I never had that in my
house ever. Why do women, why are women not concerned about stuff that gives
you cancer like that? They just don't care. 'Cause they'll love their baby no
no matter how I sleeps with her phone under her head,
literally under her head, like no not under the pillow. She sleeps on her
phone and it's and I'm like because he doesn't like headphones and she wants to
listen to a podcast right. So it's like bone conducting. Yeah, so
so I tell her every single night you're going to get a
giant Jimmy Neutron head and you're going to and it's going to be because
you're going to get a smart tumor of all time. Yeah, and she's like
they just don't care at all. No yeah, I
this is all the only thing I care about is avoiding cancerous diseases. Yeah, I
don't like raid very much. I don't like the way it smells or tastes
the way it feels between my fingers. It doesn't seem very good. Yeah, spraying
my hand with rate and then grabbing the well, I'm going to be honest. Your war
is much, much more interesting than my war. You really you really understood my
more and here's why my war is just beginning yeah, yeah, my war is just
beginning. I would like to issue a warning to an unnamed waste management
company. Okay, so this is dangerous. You know a waste management company means
have you ever watched TV? Oh, you think they might be the mafia monsters? I
don't give a fuck.
we paid this waste management company for or we didn't pay them. Actually, we
never
it's part of the issue, I guess, but the war they said we were going to pick up
your your waste. We're going to manage your waste. I don't care what they do
with it. I said all right, buddy, I'll sign this contract one year of waste
management. Yeah, that seems like a great deal. One amazing yeah, a whole year
what just a little money. Let's do it. Yeah, if all this is going to cost me is
money, then I wouldn't what the fuck am I doing not paying and I'll get in
trouble if I don't get my trash picked up. Yeah, no, of course, I'm going to sign
manage this. I sign it
one week goes by no trash pick up. I text the guy. You know what jack the
garbage man, so he's in my phone as it's the only don't know his last name. That's
what he says when he answers the phone.
We didn't get a pick up last night. He says well, sorry about that. We'll try
again tonight. I guess they tried again unsuccessful unsuccessful figured out
couldn't hack it. No, you know this happens
seventeen more times, maybe yeah seventeen more times to the point where
I just stopped texting him and I don't pay the bill and I've texted him every
single time. Eventually, I just stopped. I don't pay the bill. They send me a
collections notice for four hundred and fifty dollars for paying for trash that
they've never picked up a single fucking time. You know to play devil's advocate
here, it can be tough to tell that there's actually a trash bag inside the
trash can that you might assume that the trash can is empty is completely empty
when yeah when it's been your boss or maybe even if you get five hundred
times, maybe that's maybe that's our stuff that we left there. That wasn't
garbage that we were hoping to use the morning. So I sent an email in response
to the collections thing last week. I say, hey, I'd like to cancel this. I'm
down. I'll pay a cancellation fee. If I have to, I don't give a fuck. I just
never want to get talk to you people ever again. Yeah, I have a different
garbage collection. Go with a different guy now with a different guy strong and
he picks he is really amazing. He does it for half the price. He picks it. He
picked it up the first time or the second time the second. He missed it the
first
he missed it the first time, but we gave him one right yeah. You got one as long
as he's better than the last guy. So the guy they don't respond to my email.
Then they sent me another collections email yesterday. So I text the guy I
text Jack. I say hey, I don't want to do this anymore. I can't Jack. I can't do
this anymore right. You've disappointed me too many times. I don't want this. He
calls me and boy we went at it. Really?
It started off a little passive aggressive.
Hey Caleb, it's Jack the Garbage Man. Yeah, you know, I'm just, I'm on vacation
and I just didn't, you know, I'm taking time to call you because it seems so
crazy, right? By the end, Jack,
I've read your fucking Google reviews. You do this to
everybody. We're screaming at each other. It was a huge blow.
so I would like to say this war is on yeah and you you want to be careful
when you let your guys out on this neighborhood on the block, because
we'll pull up with an army of five strong
and we'll start. We won't fight. We'll sing in sync to you guys, and you won't
get hurt, but maybe what do you think you're going to do take us to small
claims court? We're already in jail. Yeah, where the hell are you talking?
Yeah, we're in jail.
Why am I paying for garbage collection? Anyway, that's the real question,
but these guys are going to I honestly think if anybody, it does small claims
representation in New York City. I think that we might have I think we're a good
class action. I've looked into these guys right. I think we might have a class
action lawsuit and I bet nothing we've said just now in the past five minutes
would damage any of it. What I'm going to go to war, chop his legs off. That's
not illegal.
No, I won't chop his legs off.
he's to he's that's too good for him. His legs might be a little too short.
Yeah, that yeah, exactly. I couldn't even reach him. Might not make it much of a
bend over. I'd hurt my back. I've actually never met the guy. That's the
other thing. The new garbage guy, I met him the first day he came in the office.
Let me guess, he shook your hand. He came, he shook my hand. He came to the
office. The office looked like fucking shit. I mean, it was the worst it's ever
looked, and he looked around. He said, "This place is great."
And I was like, "That's what I want. I want a liar. That's what I like to work
with I like working with a liar. This is a really nice liar
when the garbage man shakes your hand and he goes. Oh sorry, it smells like
garbage. I'm a garbage man.
He didn't smell like garbage, smelled amazing yeah, but that's put in a lot of
work in order to to smell good as a garbage. You have to do the most. That
means you are doing the most yeah, but anyway that's the beginning of my war
we're. I'm going to keep you guys updated with some kind of war journal
war stories. Yeah, maybe there will eventually be probably a
documentary about this war on HBO Max, but I wouldn't be
surprised. They do documentaries about everything nowadays. They
do a documentary about a guy walking around New York City.
Is that true? Yeah. What's it called? How to a John Wilson.
It's literally just about a guy who can walk around. Why would
it that's and it's informational or it's just it's pretty
intro. I would say it's half and half informational and random.
Some things are just
kind of whatever, but some stuff is actually there's some good info in there.
You learn about scaffolding. I'm really that episode of John Wilson made me so
scared of things falling off of buildings when I walk in man had a walk
through Manhattan looking. Well, that's not going to save you all that's going
to do is that a little fear.
Oh, like I can't move. I don't think you can move. I think you'll be frozen like
the deer in the headlights of a car falling. Oh, no, no, I am no Cameron
with a with a water bug on the wall. No, I'm a doer. I'm an I was hey. I was a
do. I did not give up. You did not give up. I proud of you for that. I didn't I
didn't even you know what I was on my station. I did not even leave that
yeah for even a second. I said, Can you go get my phone so I can use the phone
flash like can you make your fiance be a little drummer boy
next time I let her come. I have a war. I let her completely pretend the
situation was not even happening. Yeah, as soon as I saw it crawl back out, I
said leave go out of here. This is very reminiscent for me of my mice
experience. Yeah, what I'm hoping is that this is a one time thing, because
if there's another one of those types of things, I don't think I can hack it. I
really I'm not even kidding. I've been having are usually lone wolves. Yeah,
they travel. They don't they usually have. I also when they reproduce, they
usually have one baby at a time. I raise it for about nine to ten years before
can move on yeah. So as long as you wipe out two of them, you're pretty much
fine yeah. So there might be one more, but who knows yeah, but truly I've been
having bug dreams really and I've been so on edge. It's actually like ruined my
life. Do you like bugs? I don't you do like I don't like I mean I don't like a
bug in my house, but you're not afraid like you're not skittish around bugs
like I am I'm skittish. I'll say I'm skittish around like bees. I don't like
bees very much. I don't like stuff that can sting. I somehow lost my fear of
bees yesterday yesterday. Yesterday B was on my head and I my wife said
there's a B on your head and I said I don't care. That's because you couldn't
see it. Is that why I could feel it, though, and it didn't sting me and I
realise that it was pure fear man, but you were a beehive. It did not think I
was I was trying to make a beehive hairdo on my head with all its other
be friends, but it didn't happen. Yeah, I don't know this. I like really felt
it in my body this time. It really I think I maybe developed a fear of bugs.
I was like actually making involunt, like I was literally going.
I like not I'm not even kidding.
I was it was crazy man. Do you think you think you gave your fiance the Ick?
No, I gave her the opposite. I was strong and I I had a she pulled you
back into the bedroom right after you're covered in garbage, garbage bags
and paper towels. You smell like raid yeah
sweat covered in sweat. I forgot about this part of it, too. I literally
I was so it was like I haven't been sleeping very well, so I was also like
so tired and I was like okay. I think I should probably try to go back to bed,
but I like lay down and I couldn't even like close my eyes. I was still like
kind of just like thrumming with nervous energy, and so I and so she already
went to work. I'm just alone in the house and I just got up and I went out
and I just went and had Dominican breakfast by myself. It really early in
the morning and it was so nice a solo breakfast. Yeah, I haven't had a solo
I'm going to solo like sit down meal, full yeah, full sit down breakfast,
yeah, talking to a waiter and yeah yeah yeah waiters. The first person you see
that nobody else in the restaurant just made my coffee, my eggs, my sausage, my
salami, my cheese, you got that my pancake, but I go base yeah. It was so
good and the pancakes they I couldn't even eat the pancakes. It was too much
food. Yeah, it's too much. They always give you too much food. It's like four
dollars, but I was just sitting there looking out the window thinking God look
like the hustle and bustle of everyday life Sunday morning, everyone's off to
church
or or some kind of bad job from after their Saturday party. Yeah,
look at me suckers, but look at me, nobody in breakfast like this. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I killed a bug
yeah and I'd like a discount. I killed a bug this morning.
If I smell weird, it's because I killed a bug. If I smell weird, it's bravery
lifting off of my thin white body. Yeah, and you know that I went to the
bathroom in that restaurant and you know the type of bathroom they have in a
restaurant like that where it's small and you think there might be a bug in
there. I think I know the exact bathroom that you're talking about. Yeah, I
didn't go to the one that will place that you're thinking. Okay, I went to a
new place. It was okay. It was one also the time. It was also one of those
places where they have a
taxi dispatch inside it. So a guy's on the phone the entire time later, you
going okay, you have to go here. Okay, no this you're getting this call go here
and he's on a he has a computer and a phone and it's in the middle of the
restaurant. He has a full like desk and he's just talking the entire time and
he was also the waiter, but you got scared of the bathroom because it was
yeah. I give it that was the first maybe a bug could blend in yeah. That was
the first incidence of my of my bug PTSD. I wonder if I'm going to have trash
PTSD after my war and start getting scared. I've had trash PTSD just because
for that guy not picking it up every time every yeah, he already gave me PTSD
yeah walking around the corner. No thinking is that can going to be empty
or full
don't we I mean I might go to jail for real from what I'd
no no no I'm not going to hurt anybody. Legal issues, I am going to scream at
this guy's at this guy's phone a couple more times yeah and probably end up
they're probably going to win. I signed a contract of course yeah probably
going to win. What do we yeah? What can I do? What are we going to do hire a
lawyer for money. It's really not it's like I mean it's it's a year contract.
The thing is I'd be I'd be happy to do it. If they said they're charging you
the full year for breaking it. No, I haven't broken the car. I mean they
cancel what I'm what my argument that I'm telling this guy on the phone is
you didn't fulfill you never yeah, I mean yeah, I feel like we could win.
You never have have picked up the garbage a single time. I have I told
him I have security footage of our cans sitting there for four days straight,
never getting picked up a single time. Yeah, we there's no you don't have you
never did anything yeah and yeah. You know we could win this week. Can you
imagine how incredible it would be if we took him to small claims court and
they let us film it?
That would be good. That would be really got to be pretty good. Yeah, I would
love to get deposed. Yeah, I've always wanted to get deposed man. I would get.
I would do the full little Wayne thing, where it's my even if it was my own
lawyers asking me questions yeah, just be like
excuse me. What was that like ask me a question? They would ask in a
deposition. I don't even know what they would ask me just about about my life.
What was your life like
so remember you're under oath? What was your life like
it was all right
yeah, completely out out of it. This interest yeah yeah, yeah, little way
and did he did a deposition where they're like they like he's like correcting
their grammar and shit like never asked never answers a single. Oh, that's
great yeah, which I think is the move pull a zuckerberg.
I would not pull a zuckerberg. I don't think actually I'm probably I'm too. I
would be over emotional. This was the first time I ever yelled. I'd be crying
at this is the first time I've ever had a
disagreement with a guy at a who works somewhere yeah, where I was like I was
like no, just it's okay. Just do just ruin it. Just I'll pay whatever and
not ruin my life. That's how I usually am yeah, because I feel bad that
somebody has to have a job yeah, and this time I really was like
I'm coming for you. Yeah, no, he deserves it. Yeah, this guy. This is
it's not over. It's not hasn't even begun. It's far from it's far from
beginning.
It's far my friend. This is far from even beginning far from beginning this
there. This will be a pro. They're cutting this out of the movie and you
might be scared. You might be scared for me or for them,
because this prank war yeah, the only thing that you the only kind of company
you want to be in a prank war with less than a garbage company right, which has
unlimited garbage at their is a comedy entertainment online video is a group of
comedians buddy, because we're going to think of stuff that your little numb
nuts little brain could never think of me. Yeah, you're what oh you're going to
put garbage in my can. That's where it goes. That is not a prank that I don't
give a fuck put as much garbage in there as you want the other guys picking it up
now. This is what I think we could actually completely sell the rights to
this story to either maybe David Fincher, maybe score says he would touch
it, but I think maybe we could sell it to score says he and we could say like
oh, we could maybe sell him a fake story where we give him all this lead up and
and we add the detail that the waste management company did turn out to be
the mafia. Oh, that would be a good movie for him to make. That would be
pretty good.
Step into the modern world and make a movie where the main characters are
podcasters. They should make... Is there a movie that's about just like a
guy who has to just like,
who has to battle the mafia just by himself? I feel like probably. But not
like... But he's not like... Yeah, he's not even anything. He's not like a
cop. I'm sure somebody will comment what it is. I'm sure there is one.
just like a that's always the best part of of the Sopranos is whenever it's like
a normal guy like the screenwriter guy or the guy like guy who's addicted to
gambling yeah, that's always the best. I love problem. I take them serious
enough yeah when they're like oh, whatever
kill me yeah
every single time. I would love to be in that situation and not get killed.
The thing is you if I if I was dealing with these fucking guys, I just like if
the episode where where what's his name? What is the the young guy's name
Anthony Junior? No, the guy in the middle of the ages. Meadow. The guy in
the middle of the ages under Tony, Tony's cousin or uncle's son or whatever.
Tony's chair. When Tony's chair goes into the pizza place and gets all mad
because I guess I and shoots him in the foot. Yeah. Why does that guy that guy
knows this dude's run? Why didn't he own a gun? Yeah, why what are you going to
do
blow his head off? I don't fucking know that's what I would do if I was this guy.
Well, I was watching a there's only fucking eight guys. If you kill every
single one of them, do you know that movie sonatine the like Japanese Yakuza
movie? No, I just watched that the other day and that has another really funny
running at the beginning, where it's like a guy who runs like a thing. He
runs like a gambling store. They call it a den or whatever it is, and he's
like he'd though, like Yakuza guys are like kind of like harassing him to pay
them and he's like he's like I'm not going to pay you what just because
you're Yakuza, whatever I'll go to the cops and then they just kill
way. It's so funny just yeah every that's the best part of any mob movie
is like the guy's like I don't care. Who do you think you are and he
immediately gets fucking killed. I am getting shook down man. I really this is
this is this guy. I never thought about this at all until you said is a
garbage man or waste management. Yeah, there are mafia guys yeah in New York
and this guy's rich enough. He's going on vacation. He doesn't use his last
name.
He's exactly because it's probably Italian yeah and he's probably knows
that I would be. I would be wise to something, but what he doesn't know is
that I'm seventeen and a half percent Italian and that my grandpa was really
out of the Irish Mafia. Yeah, better watch out. Yeah, look the fuck out. Yeah,
they don't know that my grandpa was had a deal with an Italian Mafia. Wow, do you
know that? No, you don't know this about my family, my grandpa, my great grandpa
used to be rich,
not millions. This was hundreds of hundreds of dollars, thousands of
dollars, not hundreds of thousands, probably either. He went into business
with a couple of guys in New Jersey.
he opens a pool club with them in New Jersey, like a pool, not not like
billiards, like they they they build a pool and they start having people come
in and they sell food.
Okay, that's a classic mafia plot, a classic mafia plot. They love swimming
a funnel cake,
but make sure they have to fucking shower before the in the pool. It's
fucking dirty.
They got a shower off before and after the bull. They're going to get covered
chlorine. I guess the guy the guy my great grandpa, I guess he I guess he
didn't pay something yeah. Anyway, they said they were going to kill him, so he
just abandoned the whole business moved to North Carolina, move it yeah and
started working, but making it worked in a steel treatment plant got mesothelioma
passed away. So you used to be able to do that. You used to be able to just
kind of move to another town, but nowadays the Mafia they got Facebook.
they got my space, they got map, they got linked in yeah, this is a generation
google maps. This new is there is the mafia still going on. I think so. I
think they're like guys who are like oh yeah, I'm going to be in the fucking
mafia, probably not. I can't imagine there's that many. It's not the cream
of the crop. At least no yeah, I think it's I think it's the same. I mean I
mean not to go back to the sopranos. I think it's this thing where it's yeah,
it's just like kind of impotent. I don't think it matters that much anymore, but
I'm sure that I can't imagine they were just like oh, let's stop
whatever this family, let's let's let's get rid of this family. I mean not the
family, but you know, cut your losses at some yeah. I'm sure, but you know, I
don't think they're doing very much. Rudy Giuliani put all your uncles in
jail. Yeah, it's like what am I going to do just to try to do this shit again? I
don't want to do that. I want to be I want to be a
I want to be on. I would just move to a I want to be on a website. That's what
people want to do now
website. I want to be on a website. I want to build websites or no. They want
be on you know, like this around a website like they want some kind of
website job, notoriety yeah or maybe they say I want to be a garbage man,
but then they're I want to be yeah. You know what I'm going clean. I want to be
a good old fashioned garbage man. I want to do things the right way. I want to
work my way to the top and this is a private garbage collection company, by
the way, which under pays their people because in north or in New York, if
you're a garbage man, you make like like a public like a city garbage man. Yeah,
you make like two hundred thousand dollars a year. You make like insane
most of my mansions. They're like the top of the one percent. That's a most of
the Hamptons is that's all these videos. These little kids coming out and hugging
the garbage man yeah be spitting in his face, creasing his sneakers.
What the hell are you doing? Would you walk up to Warren Buffett and shake his
hand and I do that to every thank you, Mr. Bother. I would walk up to Warren
Buffett with and I'd have a pie and it's I'd be dressed up like a butler. Your
nice and he go and have an order one smash in his face. That's what I would
do. Yeah, we should be doing that with garbage men because they're
millionaires. Yeah, they have had it too easy for too long. I agree. They get to
drive those trucks around. You know who else has had it too easy for too long
man politicians politicians. I went to Washington DC this past weekend. Yeah,
how was the on or what's it now Adam Friedman
that would have been probably cooler. I think the one would love us. I would
love to hang out with him. Yeah, we need to link up. Yeah, I think we should link
up with it. Does anyone know him? Does anybody have a connect on Theo Vaughn?
We don't even get him on the like I'd like to take him at a dinner yeah. Yeah,
I don't want to. I don't want to hitch my truck to that. No, no, he's a radic.
He's doing his thing, man. God bless him. He's going to take everyone down with him. He's
in a different lane than us. God, I love him. I could watch him tell stories for years. Yeah,
the first time ever that Instagram has served me just random clips of a comedian or a podcast.
And I've actually watched every one and enjoyed it. Yeah, they're great. I always get, yeah.
I'm not going to say people's names, but Instagram always, for some reason, just recommends me
only a million stand up reels yeah, just like I'm not watching it. Why
what makes you think I would want to watch this because I only follow stand
up comedians. Is that why I guess that is why I only get stand up reels. I
just say do not interested, not interested, not interested, not in yeah
anyway. These politicians had it too good for too long. Yeah, I went to
Washington D. C. and I went to the African American History Museum.
I bet you two had a laugh there. No, no, no, I made it. I made a very smart
choice, which is I decided to we walk into the history thing and it's
already just so so depressing and very sad, like from the first second and I
walk two sections ahead so that me and so that
Adam never says anything crazy like it makes some off color joke where I am in
the vicinity where I have to hear and react to it. So I just walked to
things and me and him just had two very separate, very somber times nice and
and at the end we had banana pudding, which was actually really nice. The
banana pudding is amazing. If you go to the
yeah, that's cool. Yeah, it was amazing. I haven't had museum food since I was a
kid. I love museums. I love museums. I love museums, dude. I and I love the
Smith. I love Smithsonian's. I wish we had gone to more while we were there
because the
natural history museum, the Smithsonian natural history is so good, which way is
that the one we went to
I went to the one with the dinos. Yeah, we went to that one. Yeah, that one's great.
The air and space is one of the best ever. I went there as a kid, I think. It's amazing.
They have spaceships that are ducted to the ceiling. Yeah. And you can imagine that you're
in. It's a great museum. Have you seen the titanosaur skeleton they have or in the...
The one here, the natural history here? Yeah. I don't remember if it's a natural history
or not, but it's like on a 120-foot long dinosaur. There's a really big one at the natural history
everyone here. Maybe it's that it goes out of the building. It goes out of the
building. It goes out of the room on both. They have like a giant room for
it and it goes through the door. Yeah, it's cool. It's crazy.
Yeah, there's so many myths about dinosaurs that I've been learning are
being busted in the last 20 years. Dinosaur shit goes crazy. They don't look
like they didn't look like lizards at all. No, they're birds. That's another.
That's another thing that I just did. Like I think either the Twitter just
kind of like use some kind of dark magic to learn that I will always click on
is a dinosaurs. I get I got fully my like Twitter for you page is fully
dinosaur Twitter, which is like a community. I didn't know existed. It's
like it's like it's like there's a whole bunch of people and they're all
friends with each other and they just post about like scientific papers. You
feel left out when you look at this. You say I don't understand any of it. It's
all like you see that news paper about the Spinosaurus. I'm going to look
where I see any papers yeah. I get dinosaur journals every month. There's
a I don't know crazy. I'd like to see a dinosaurs journal yeah. They were
I bet they're writing some crazy stuff, probably about how big I am. I'm so big
so misunderstood, but my bones are light because I'm avian in nature. People will
probably think I'm a lizard, but I'm a well, that's how they they discovered the
dinosaurs had feathers. They found a velociraptors journal and I was like,
I forgot to comb my feathers today. Everyone laughed at me. They said
everyone sure looked at me. I forgot to come at the nest feathers. Maybe this
meant something different. Yeah, maybe they meant scales. Yeah, they had to have,
but it makes so much more sense that they're birds. No, it's a they they
looked they look like birds. Yeah, all the skeletons look exactly like they
didn't have beaks. I guess most of them. I think some of them did them. Some
had beaks. Yeah, I think they were beaked man. Yeah, it's also is so crazy
that do you know people just didn't care about dinosaurs at all until like
the fifties? Yes, I do know this. It's so not a lot of people like my
family. We knew people growing up who thought that dinosaurs were
a
distraction from the devil yeah, but even even beyond or just fake, even
beyond like even yeah, even in like the science community like they discovered
dinosaurs and like the eighteen hundreds or whatever and
people were just like like it was considered like a fringe scientist,
like it was considered like oh you're like a weird like this doesn't matter.
Why do you care about it? Is it that insane, a giant fucking bones of like a
t rex and in a mountain and you're like, how can you be a whatever man? Let's do
physics and yeah, it's probably an older version of a dog. Yeah, let's give a
new type of blue water. Yeah, that hydrates you and call it a gatorade.
Yeah. Oh, let's invent gatorade. No, no, no, leave those bones in the ground.
Let's go fuck with all these electrolytes and these dies for your
water. Let's make a drink. That's too sugary. Yeah. Oh, I got an idea.
Here's here's the first guy who saw a dinosaur bone ready.
Huh dinosaur bones pretty gay. Let's go home. Let's put cocaine and soda.
that's probably what they like. I said yeah, it's so crazy man, because also
the one they thought when they even when people started to get a little more
interested in, they thought they were because they thought they were or they
they because they're cold blooded. They thought they're like big alligator
lizard type things, so that everyone was so all the scientists were like yeah,
because dinosaurs were like alligator type monsters or whatever. They probably
just like an alligator. They probably just sat around all day and didn't do
anything and then they just died. So we don't care very much about them, but it
turns out they run around like also haven't haven't crocodiles been around
like since dinosaurs were around. I think they might be older. That's so
scary, but that that there that proves to you that it's that they weren't
lizards.
We already had these guys survive.
Yeah, see here's the reason why you know most of most of the things that ever
lived on earth are extinct. Yeah, of course, it's crazy. Yeah, so much you
think about like you think about a crocodile and you can trace that all the
way back you go okay. Well, there was a crocodile alive seventy five million
years ago and it looked like a crocodile, but it was twice as big and
I guess long legs. That's why I get really scared when you see when you go
to one of these natural history museums and you see the five and a half foot
long mosquitoes yeah or the big ground sloths. Well, yeah, you look at the
grass, you pick a look at a picture of the ground soft and you're like okay,
well, I can tell what that turned into that to do a tree sloth that turn into
my brother. So many so many
animals that you see a picture of and like you're reading a dinosaur book or
something. Yeah, a picture of it. It's like oh, this just didn't turn into
anything. Yeah, this one was well. There's very you see a dinosaur like oh,
this looks a little bit like an elephant, but it didn't turn into an
elephant. It just went away. They break away in these awful branches. Yeah,
evolutionary cul de sacs where they get to the end and there's nothing left and
they just fucking spin around till they die. Yeah, crazy, scary, because what if
that happens to us?
You know, people are evolving. I heard this. You know, people are evolving.
I've heard this. Yeah, we're growing larger
brains, brain and hearts for loving.
We're getting we're being we're getting friendly,
I do think there's too many people where we probably
there's no way that we can all evolve because there's too many people. Yeah,
does that make sense? Most of us have to I mean if we're going to evolve,
we're all going to die because that's what evolving happens, but I mean we're
getting there's so many people being born and so much genetic variance that how
can we how can we even there's no like also we don't really have natural
selection like that anymore
right because we help out ourselves yeah because the weakest people are again the
politicians right and the politicians are self selecting yeah and they're
saying more weak people or politicians more garbage men who can who can do
anything they want more garbage. You know a diplomatic community like family.
we're going to get rid of body builders yeah, but body builders need to go.
We're going to kill the
waving their hands like this kill the body builders. We hate the body
builders. They're too strong in it and they're just a place to get rid of body
builders. We don't like body builders. They're out there trying to outlaw
self tanner, a rock star, get rid of straight rock stars, get rid of them,
get rid of them. Oh David Bowie fingered of a fifteen year old yeah, they're
doing this and trying to get rid of a rock star, but let's breed more Olivia
Rodrigo's yeah, more industry plant, Bs more Greta fan fleet. That's actually so
true nowadays. Natural selection is literally about being in the industry.
Yes, people who don't go into the industry, they starve and they die. They
do people and then everybody who goes indo goes big time, sells out, becomes
the president or the king of a country, which is the ultimate sell out. Yeah,
if that's why I would never, ever, ever become the president, do you know,
because I put my hand on that Bible and I'd go. Yes, I solemnly swear to sell
the fuck out yeah and stop around about the amount of hate that we get on a
motherfucking daily basis. I imagine that
multiplied by ten trillion. That's what the president gets every day, but he
likes it. Yeah, you have to like it to get a job like that. Did you watch a
republican debate? No, I would have watched it if trump was in it. Probably
yeah, I did watch the trump tucker thing. I watch I because I only saw the
this is guaranteed to be funny. Yeah, the debate is going to be maybe oh, maybe
one guy's funny accidentally because he's like oh, I'm so stupid like like a
Ben Carson thing yeah, but no it was all just, but everyone's just competent
making good points. Everybody's just like so smart man and it wasn't even
funny. It was just like very interesting. It's true yeah, just real
shit. You know I'm just nodding my head along. I want to be laughing right. It's
like I'm just watching a conversation with me and my friends. Yeah, exactly.
we need to lower taxes sitting yeah all the sitting around wearing red ties
sitting in the you know those plastic chairs around the fire pit, those
plastic chairs, fifteen week abortion mandate yep and we got our camp chairs
out of my mom's backyard yep and then dude roasting weenies yeah that and
then dude, Nikki Haley, oh my God,
who's that she's the South Carolina something okay, but I'm in love with her.
I do I delighted
I
delighted in my love for her. I just recently did that's huge, but
get me up on that stage. What do you have to lose? Put me in there? Yeah,
there you're no, but none of these people are going to like that about
almost everything.
I agree, I agree, that's what I why not after one of the shows this guy,
Daniel Gafford, the the Center for the Washington Wizards came to the came to
the show NBA player, he's seven feet tall. Yeah, he came and hung out with his
backstage and I just kept asking him. I was like, just let me play man. Yeah,
just let me play one time and I was like I'm a I'm a lob threat right like
just just one time you run off the court and I'll run on to the court. We'll
do it really, really fast. Yeah, no one can tell the difference and he was just
like, ha ha, maybe man.
He just kept saying that and I kept being like no man, I'm fucking serious.
seriously. I really, really, really want to do your job for one day. I've gotten
in trouble before saying that to people. To who?
I said it to
this guy from Smosh. You said, I want to be you? Basically. What'd you say? I
told him to put me on. You said put-, okay, to which one? Ian? Yeah. You said,
put me on? Not in those exact words. What did you say to him exactly? I think
exactly I said, and I can't remember exactly how I put it, because I
I was kind of drunk, but I think I said something along the lines of give me
one trillion dollars and put me on your shoes.
And what did he say? He kind of didn't really say anything and scowled a
little. He's not as nice as Mr. Daniel Gafford, man. No. This guy was cool.
He didn't give me the ha ha maybe. Him and his wife were really nice. But he was very nice.
Yeah. And kind of that way that I ended the night with that I feel bad about.
So you, he wasn't really nice to you being very, very rude to him.
that no well that's how rude it's a question. A question can't be so rude.
Well, I would say the rude part of that is assuming that the that the guy who
runs smosh has a bunch of money.
You can't run smosh that a bunch of money. I would say give me a trillion
dollars to a homeless guy. It doesn't matter how much money they have.
Okay, go do it. Okay, I've done it before you've asked.
He says can I have a dollar? You say, oh, I have a really a fucking trillion
dollars because one time that might work. It could where it might be a guy who's
studying yeah, there's a might be walking Phoenix. Yeah, that's a thing
since you asked I've been treating everybody every homeless guy very, very
well, just in case they're walking to every homeless guy and say I loved you
and Joker. I think I think your madness is unbelievable. Yeah, you play madness
so well. I've caused a lot of problems by by encouraging madness and these your
chest concavity is Loki freaky. My friend, I really want to lose like a
hundred pounds for a movie role so badly. Yeah, I want to be cast as
maybe
like who could I be? You should be in the remake of the machinist.
That's a great idea. I think I would crush. We were just talking about
that movie the other night. Are they remaking it? No, I don't think so.
I never have even seen that movie. Me neither. I've seen the pictures.
That was one of the movies that I was always, I wanted to watch so
bad when I was in like middle school, but I like psyched, I was too
scared of it, of watching it. Because of the skin he was. I thought it
was going to be really scary and I just psyched myself out every time I never
watched it and I still have yeah. I did that with gamer and then I watched it
and
it wasn't that gamers fire gamer is
I mean we've talked about those kind of movies before, but those movies are
like
really what I thought movies were going to be like the rest of my life. I was
like oh okay, they figured out how to make a movie. There's people's heads
blow up. There's like insane CGI. I like those directors are doing something new
that I was excited about, but I can't. Oh, I think that maybe they're doing a
Hellboy movie. Really? The guys who, the guys, they're the guys who did Crank and
the Ghost Rider movies. Oh, they did Ghost Rider? Yeah, or maybe just the
second one. And Mom and Dad, you ever watch that movie? Uh-uh. That's the one
where there's, like, a virus that spreads that makes all moms and dads want to
kill their kids. It's crazy. What? And it's called Mom and Dad? Yeah, and it's
like a con-, it's Nicolas Cage and
Selma something. Selma Hayek? No, the one from the old Hellboy movie.
Selma and Louise. I don't remember her name, but they play, but it's like
half a comedy and half like the most horrible, horrific thing of like
moms and dads like running at their kids and being like, "Come here!" and
trying to kill them. It's crazy. That would really scare me. It's a cool
movie. I've been trying to... Okay, I tried... I stayed up for an extra
15 minutes last night in bed, thinking about how to become very rich off
of a video game because I was thinking of all these video games that these little
kids play are all scary, the scary games, right? And it's all stuff that is just
things that are, that you think about when you're a kid. It's the
fucking mascot horror stuff. There's that game Grandma. Teacher. Yeah, the
teacher baldies basic types there. All of these games are all all stuff you do as
a kid. It's all stuff as a kid. It's a part of your life. So I was saying what
if we wanted to make one of these games because these people make fucking dude
hello neighbor. Yeah, these guys made like they sold some show to like Disney.
They made like a hundred million dollars off this fucking game. Oh my God wait.
That's what we can do. What is vulture off all this stuff? We'll just go. Let's
just shop around a bunch of TV adaptations of all these games.
that is smart as fuck. We don't have to get the rights. Fuck no. No, we pretend
we have them. Yeah, wait, wait, wait. You didn't get the right. You just made it
up.
So fuck it. We'll just see the right. That's made up. Yeah, wait. It's not real.
You made up fucking Baldy and Freddie. Yeah, yeah. We'll just take it. Do
something about it. It's a fucking iPhone. Oh my God. And you know what?
You have the perfect perspective to write an adaptation of Baldy.
finally a story about story about Baldy in school from an actual Baldy. You
think I would be long. We have let haired people of hair take over the
narratives of Baldies. Can I say Baldies?
You can't say Baldies man. That's the guy's name. I didn't even think I
didn't realize he was bald. Actually, I don't know even what he looks like. He
is bald now that I think I mean apparently they sold been selling a lot
game baldies gate three. I didn't even know it was such a big that's a
different, but I've seen that's a different ball. I guess it's that's
different. Yeah, it's a completely different ball guy. I'm scared to play
that game scared of any game that will destroy my life. You can imagine it's
hard for you to imagine something balder than you is that what the fuck you
made me spill my coffee. You did that shit right then and it's just going to
sit there. You're just going to have to think about that. I see the name of
in that game and I get scared because I read it and I say bald and gay me. I
think it's talking. I think it's saying something about me, but you're neither
bald nor gay or yourself. Imagine Twilight Zone kind of oh yeah, what if
I what if you were bald?
Imagine a world this man lost all his hair, this man stuck in a prison of
sexuality and lack of hair. Well, the weight prison sexuality, no hair,
Okay. Well, it's about me. Twilight Zone reboot would be good for us, too. We
could kind of pick up the pieces of the Jordan Peele. I didn't watch it. It was
a bad. Apparently, it was bad. I don't watch it either, but I saw they had
Camille Nangiani in it. Yeah, and he played the funniest comedian in the
world. And I said, wait, this is a documentary.
I think if Jordan Peele did something in this past few years and you haven't
heard about it once and probably must be really, really bad. It must be
really good. People like him. But what is when you were a kid? Yeah. What is
is the kind of thing that you slaughter so slender is I mean they already made
that game. Oh well, okay slender man in the seven right, okay, I understand now
yeah with the question. So the question is like should be a game of should be a
game of yeah, okay, like what's not even scary like because I wasn't scared of
the teacher when I was a kid, I guess not by a pedophile. They already did
that with hello neighbor. That's what it's about kind of yeah. It's like a
it's like the pedophile neighbor next door like that's what you're scared of,
but my neighbors weren't pedophiles. They were just old old guys. You wear masks.
My neighbors were my friends. Yeah, I like my neighbor. My neighbor was a
really, really scary. All my neighbors, except for Mrs. Boyle.
You had a Mrs. Boyle. You can imagine exactly what you looked inside. Oh, my
God, yeah, I really can, but when I was a kid, you know what I was saying?
Here's what I was saying. I think she died. That's sad. I think Jerry lives
there now. Here what I was thinking was, yeah, two things. One is either like
that your parent like you go over to somebody else's house and they throw up
and you have to go. They have some yeah
and you have to stop there from getting sick.
You know you go over to somebody else's house yeah and they have like weird
rules right like I hated that. Yeah, you know it's maybe even worse than that
when you're and maybe you I mean I think you maybe you might have been a
different type of kid than me. So maybe this didn't bother you so much. Okay, you
go to your friend's house and they're talking back to their parents.
I mean, if you listen, you just assume that I like disrespect, okay, I'm just
not sure because me personally, I would never have talked back to my parents.
Yeah, I was a respectful and polite child. Of course, I followed the rules.
I had most nasty children in my life man, but you know you call their moms
bitch. Yep, that was maybe one of the most horrifying things. How's that
possible? Because how can you do that? I even beyond just saying do this do that
yeah, please yeah, what are they your slave? No yeah, no, it's your mom raising
you, that's your mom and your dad popped out of them. That's your papa, that's
your papa and your mama. What do I call my mama papa because I popped out of
her that's right and I know you call yourself the papa as you popped out. I
call her the puppy dad mom say hey puppy
okay,
so I saw an old ass guy struggling up the stairs with with the Walker and I
called the F slur by a guy with a Walker today. Damn or not. I guess you're kind
of a new style of guy that the old head can't quite comprehend. This is old is
old fucking guy. It was the same guy. He was struggling up the stairs and he was
his back like
he had a hunched back or he was about to walk up the stairs and then a guy's head
was a guy walked up to him and went, you need help poppy and then you laugh.
That guy just this guy would not have liked that. No yeah. Imagine it like
just imagining a kind of a Clint Eastwood style old guy being called poppy. You
Any help, Poppy? I think this is the same guy that Joe and Alex were telling me. They were
filming something outside and he was like, because I think they told me he had a cane,
and he was like, "What are you guys filming?" And they were like, "Oh, we're just filming
a short whatever." And then a person walked by who was wearing really short shorts and
like a really short pink top and he just like went like, oh my God,
I think it was probably the same guy because they said that it was a veteran
with a cane. The tragedy of being an old guy like that and you're in New York,
man, you're torturing yourself. And I gotta say this guy, that situation, this
guy called me a fucking F word, yeah, and just like that to his self, yeah,
and I was a little bit like I mean it's always little weird guys who you could
row around that do that. It's always old guys who know that they have immunity.
Because if I'd ever... You can say whatever you want to me, if I touch this
guy, I'm the bad guy all of a sudden, 'cause I killed a man. But this guy,
he looks... He looks just about the gayest guy I've ever seen in my life.
He has... His head is at complete dick height. He's like, could be fully
roly polyed into like the perfect sex position. I mean, this guy could be
manhandled and should be manhandled. So that's what I was saying. I guess this
guy is is internalized homophobia. I guess when I first thought of it, I was
thinking, okay, maybe I guess being a being an old racist homophobe guy who
lives in Brooklyn. Yeah, that's that might be like being allergic to bees and
being a beekeeper. Yeah, you should probably get to go somewhere else. You're
saying they should be in charge. Well, I'm saying that's what it might. I'm
saying that's what it might be like right, which the beekeeper isn't in
hard to the bees. He works, he works with them. He doesn't work, but I think
maybe it's more like their bodies. I guess maybe it's more like you are the
bee, because if you sting someone, well,
what do you expect? You die. Yeah, you're first you die, because again,
you're going to give yourself a heart attack. If you got to move somebody,
your stinger comes off your body, you die, but you'll be a keeper gets stung
by a bee. It's like, well, what do you yeah, you don't go? Oh yeah,
I'm the beekeeper. Yeah, exactly. I'm walking around. I'm the beekeeper. He
maybe it's actually the other way around. He's stingy and I go
whatever I guess you're an old guy. This is happen. I he calls me that word and I
say this has happened to me hundreds of thousands of times.
Now come here and I'm going to take your honey from yeah. Come here, get
some honey. I'm going to massage you till your honey comes out. I'm going to
find your girlfriend and flip her over.
How about that? That's what you have to say to an old guy like that. Oh, you
think I'm gay? I'm going to fuck your girlfriend. Yeah, yeah, let me see your
girlfriend. I'll I bet your girlfriend's ugly and old yeah, I have sex with her.
Yeah, you're the gay guy having sex with old women who look like men by that
time, but she how white and thin their hair is. The thing is, because if she's
dating this guy, she'll probably say yes to have sex with me, because it's such
an upgrade. Because you look like him? No. No.
No. I don't look like this guy. I don't know. It could be a lot of reasons why
you said that. I don't look anything like this guy. Why are you saying that one
thing you said? And we were, I was, both of us was white. Okay. Well, that adds
kind of a sinister tent to the situation. How is white on white crime?
That's what you're saying. Yeah,
kind of
I don't even know kind of know what I'm saying. Yeah, yeah. What are you doing
the rest of the day?
I have an exciting package coming in the mail that I can't tell you what it is,
but I'm going to send you a picture of it when it arrives.
What I just don't want to say it. I don't want to spoil anything, but it's
excited. It's really exciting. I think you might like it. I'm very excited
about it.
Can I guess? You can guess. Well, okay, I'll give you one. I'll give you I'll
tell you, you know, I'll give I'll give you this. It's an outfit.
Damn,
that's actually exciting as fuck. Yeah, I have to basically do some Photoshop and
go to the grocery store. I need to buy new pants. My pant I was in. I bought
some new pants yesterday as part of this outfit, not these. Oh, not this. These
old. No, I this this new outfit. Is it a job outfit? Yes, yeah, I like this kind of
thing. The why don't I dress up like I have a job anymore? That was this job.
I'm like I'm more excited about this outfit than I've been excited about any
outfit I've ever had. I'm so happy. I'm so excited to see this. It's not for the
podcast either. So nobody ever said until it's I had to buy pants. Tell me if you
guys went to the any of the D. C. Shows
the first two shows. I did them with a giant rip in the crotch of my pants that
I'm worried that people saw we wearing on these yeah. I was wearing on these,
but they were black undies and blue jeans briefs or boxers
or boxer briefs or do they have brief boxers
here's what brief boxers are their boxers that only last for a moment. Yes,
like this leading on yeah, edible, but edible underwear are brief boxers. No,
you don't even have to eat it. You snap your fingers and you they they poof
away. Yeah, they blow away like a like a do when a guy turns to dust in a movie
that's scary,
but it's beautiful in terms of romantic sex.
That would be nice if I could because I the thing is I like taking my shirt off.
I like taking my pants off hate taking my socks and my underwear. Let me do
this. Yeah, I don't care if they're single use here's now. Here's the
problem with this design. I'm thinking of you're in a work meeting you're up
presenting in front of every in front of the office. Obviously, you got pants on
yeah, but you know maybe you're expecting to have a little fun after work in the
car with one of your co workers and which that's just a random detail. That
doesn't matter,
but you have these under, but maybe you have these under. Maybe that's the
reason you have these underwear on or maybe you just mix it up, but maybe
you're going to have sex in the car with your co worker in the launch break, but
then maybe you give the presentation and about how you're going to switch over a
new system and your boss says, wow, that's great. It seems like it's going
to be so easy to switch over in the new system. In fact, I think we'll be able
to switch just like that right in front of everyone. Everyone sees a bunch
underwears worth of dust falls right out of the legs of your pants.
Here's the other scenario. I was thinking if you have these clap or the
snap on snap off underwear, they're only snap off. I don't know if you can
use snap, but that's another good idea. They got the metal snaps. Yeah, that
that's that would help me a lot. Yeah, you go to a
poetry reading. Oh, be a poet. And you're wearing hundreds of and your character
is underwear man. Yeah, right. You might be good for just make sure your poem
isn't too good, 'cause over a hundred snaps and you're done. Or maybe you
ate a...
You ate something crazy right before you got there and you shit your pants.
but you say luckily I have under one will hold I have underwear on under and I
have these giant wide leg dickies where if it wasn't for these underwear, these
things would go right down there, but then there's a very rude patron at the
bar who says
excuse me, bartender, bartender, yeah,
I'll have a me or tea pain yeah.
What about a shoe where it has like a Chinese suicide net around it, so if poo
falls out your pant leg, it catches it.
Why would you want to cat then it was roll into your shoe?
Well back to the drawing board at this one, I guess
I like the idea. I do think we are
okay. Here's an idea. I thought of a while ago. There's another poo shoe
related. Yeah,
it's a shoe on the bottom of it. It has
reversed
like a stamp pattern. Okay, Caleb was here. Cameron was here
you can step in dog poo
make stepping in dog poo fun and marks your territory. I like that yeah or you
know you can put whatever, but a stamp shoe where you can step in poop.
That's a great idea or you step in the sand and it shows yeah, yeah, well
mostly my ideas for poop. So what do you well the water mud away the sand water
you're going to wash the poop away. No, this what is it what I can be or it
could be concrete like for walking in wet concrete. Yeah, well, so there's a
lot of ideas, but mainly the ideas for poop
I do think that so zooming out a little bit yeah. When was pants invented?
Well these pants are so small from all the way out here. It was zoomed out.
Oh that's funny. Yeah so I bet that well could you consider a loincloth of pants?
Or is that underwear? That's a skirt. Yeah so I would probably say they didn't
reinvent that until
9000 years ago and the shirt, my guess, the shirt was probably a couple years
after that right. I feel like the shirt maybe came before pants because
I feel like you could cover everything.
Yeah, well, but I guess I don't know why I think that, but it feels like maybe
that's true. I can imagine someone winning the pooing around. Yeah, you're
probably right. You cover up the stuff. More important stuff to cover up, but I
was thinking maybe they have a, they're holding, no yeah, you're right. I'm
look up when pants came out, but it's been,
you know, near thousands of years since we had a big clothing item invented
between the 13th and the 10th centuries BC.
So that's okay. I'm not so far off. Yes, three thousand years ago, a few
thousand years off. Yeah, only three times longer. You wanna see what the
first, the oldest known dressers look like? Yes, I do. I do want to see them.
I've seen people wearing these. Oh yeah, that looks that looks amazingly modern.
That is crazy. Those are like those ones that have the like the ridges on these
are like Kanye West things yeah yeah, I've seen I've seen Patrick wear these
pants. No doubt yeah, which by the way Patrick you've been really quiet today
kind of a joke for the audio listen. Yeah he's not can't see that he's not
yeah yeah he's not here. He's in solitary confinement yeah yeah
well, that said, do we have anything to plug? Oh well, there's a huge episode
coming up next month.
You can't say much else about the battle of the century, September
twenty-seventh. It is kind of the this is a bit of a stop gap episode, but it
will be the opposite of this one in every single way. The actually I had I
forgot that we I had a list pulled up. We obviously we were not going to do it
now, but I can't. Oh, well, I completely lost. I was going to say we could read
something from it, but what was it I closed it?
It was I don't even remember morning.
This is truly a throwback to the very beginning of the podcast. You and me at
work. I mean I just I don't know thrilling conversation that I didn't
even remember that I had or anything on my phone to look at
was great. It's wonderful. This was special. This was special. Yeah. Thank
you. Well, that's that bye y'all.
you woke up immediately.
Yeah, here's what happened in the dream.
I was outside, there was lightning striking all around.
I thought, I should go inside so lightning doesn't strike me.
So I start to run inside.
Then lightning strikes near me.
I think, oh, I'm safe.
It only struck near me.
That was lucky.
But then it goes into the ground and it goes, and it goes across the ground like a video
game area of effect.
What if you woke up?
It goes into my body and then it goes up my body like, and I shake around and I fall to
the ground and then my heart stops.
And then I survived and I got up and I said, in my dream I said, "Wow, I thought I was
going to die, but it actually just felt weird."
What if you woke up from that dream?
That's how in real life you'd say like, "Sheesh."
If you woke up from that dream and your finger is just in your outlet in your forehead.
You're doing sleepwalking.
You woke up and it's like, you're like, your nightstand is here, your bed is here.
I moved everything out of the way.
I'm chewing on my phone charging cable.
fell down perfectly into the outlet on the wall.
My outlet shaped, hole shaped, finger shaped.
Well, you have a hole with your finger in your mouth.
I know you, you sleep with your finger in your mouth.
Scratch your balls, put your finger in your mouth.
I wonder if I've ever done that myself.
You know when you, it's your butt and then you stick your fingers in your mouth.
We all do it.
I don't do that.
We all do it, man.
You don't have to be afraid to admit it. Okay, I do it. You're right. I do that
shit.
I stick it in my mouth.
What is up with you? Disgusting
the mall
train
while you're like looking around
your Christmas shopping, your Christmas shopping for your girlfriend, you're in
the middle of Victoria's Secret. The woman's about to walk up to you and
you're just going
it
I was like a like a like sound is an apple. When you put your finger,
your
*laughing*
(explosion)