*AWESOME MUSIC*
(singing)
Welcome back to another episode of Podcasts Without Lists. I'm your host Caleb Pitt.
You had potatoes and peas for lunch?
I had just potatoes and peas.
It's called a combination.
It's called beasties and...
Potatoes and peas.
Potatoes and peas. It's a Jamaican dish called potatoes and peas combination.
You're thinking of rice and peas. That's a Jamaican dish.
Rice and peas.
Potatoes and peas is the Jamaican Irish dish.
Which is the same thing.
Which could be fucking fire.
They have a lot of parallels in their culture I've heard.
Yes.
They both live on the...
And they both live in Ireland. They both live on the island.
When you go to County Cork, they're just daggering. Did you see a bunch of
these old... Did you see a bunch of daggering in Ireland? Most Irish women.
Everybody was playing steel drums when I went. And daggering each other.
Yeah. And there was... Shooting their butts with maximum velocity. Except it's
illegal to
play Rasta music in Ireland. Really? There's a law against it.
You can't play any music that has more than one instrument and the voice
counts as an instrument. There is an interview with Morrissey from the 80s
where they asked him if rubber ring was inspired by like dub songs or whatever,
and he said that
rubber ring a condom song rubber ring is like it's the there's like I don't know
kind of sounds they're like oh it kind of sounds like a reggae song and he said
no reggae is the most black supremacist music.
What is the thing with I've never understood the Morrissey love? I don't
give a fuck about his music at all. I think that most of people like Morrissey just like
that he's racist. You weren't like 15 when you first heard the Smiths or anything. Back
when you were 15 you really connect with the lyrics. Oh yeah. Well I didn't know how racist
he was until like later. But he's also gay. Yeah. And he's sad too. He's a big queen.
I guess to be a singer who's racist and is always sad is better than being really happy
about being racist. Yeah, yeah, this is a system being like more
balance. I think in that regard, more sees almost a
cautionary tale to the racist. Yeah, if you're racist, you could be a
millionaire, but maybe you'll have to be a millionaire about frowning. Yes,
you'll have to make songs about how many frown. What does his sound sound
like a million frowns? I think it was the name of one of the
What was his band that he did? The Smiths. His name is Morrissey Smith? No, his name
is Stephen Patrick Morrissey. Stephen Patrick? Irish. Irish Blood English Heart was another
one of his songs that came out in 2004. What does that mean? Irish Blood English Heart?
The song is about how he was born in Ireland, but he loves England so much. He loves England?
Yeah, he's a weird character, this guy. He's a weird freak. And he dresses in trench coats?
pretty much. But he also doesn't wear a shirt. He doesn't wear a shirt and then
he swings flowers around on stage. Did he used to be skinny and now he's fat or was he
always kind of fat and old? He was very, very, very thin. You're the one
for me fatty. That's a good song. Oh God, he has the worst kind of
Irish body. Yeah, he looks kind of exactly like my father.
Yeah, those like really skinny arms and just the
giant. My dad's, he's, you know. Look at that. The skinny arms and the
giant torso. Pat, I'm going to be honest, this is where you're headed.
Yeah?
Yeah, this is a skater body.
A skater body?
Yeah.
He's clearly a skater.
I don't think he looks terrible.
Why is he, he looks fucking terrible. Are you crazy?
He just looks fat.
Is he milking himself in this picture?
Yeah, he's milking himself.
For what? As a statement of, is he bleeding onto his hand or is that the shadow of his
microphone?
He is milking himself because he's so anti-milk and he's vegan and he's so anti-milk that he
he'd rather have his own body be milked. He wants to be a cow milk. Yeah, that
sounds like a
man.
He's jealous of the cows. He's jealous of the cows to be able to be having
milk. Yes, I do think it would feel pretty good to get milked. Yeah. Well,
look what he's doing right. I don't know. It depends on if you have milk
ready to go or if your body doesn't have milk. It's probably going to feel
like when you get blood drawn, you run out. Yeah, it's going to hurt pretty
bad where your body's kind of grasping at straws and I know that
Oh, I know that milk needs to come out, but there's none ready. So you're saying
it's like, oh, I'm dry. Yeah, it's like trying to force. I think that's what he's
saying. Milk out of him. I think he's saying I'm dry and I'm sad because I'm
dry. I don't have any milk to give you my adoring fans. This person on X said
they googled why is Morrissey fat and they came upon this horror. It's not
that much necessarily horror. Yeah, I don't love it. This is a horror to you
you should check out a twenty four. You should maybe try on reaster flick
yeah because what's more horrific than your own family? Yeah, your mom,
we should what's scarier than your own mom that every reaster movie is what if
your friends or your family had
the ability to be odd to you or what if you went on vacay or what if you went
on a fire ass vacay, what if your vacation took a left turn? Did you guys
you ever watch the that movies about you ever watch his point of a
total debut is sure.
Something we talked about one yeah yeah, some things up with the
johnson's are not that funny man listen man. I just can't get into
that kind of stuff. It's a that's a movie about it.
Hey, if that's if that's that's the way you swing that's fine.
You know, I'm not the kind of I'm not going to come into your
house and tell you what to do, but but that type of thing. It's
which is typically not for me doesn't do it, except in the rarest of cases.
That's a movie
keeping it's not keeping up with the johnson's something about the johnson's
the movie about a child molesting his own dad. Yeah, it's kind of a reverse
move. Yeah, it's kind of a fish
yeah,
kind of the ultimate fish out of water. It's an unlikely hero.
Listen, buddy,
what's so confusing to me about that movie? Why go for your dad? Yeah,
dude, mom.
It really doesn't make a lot of sense. That's not right. Well, that's what's
so terrifying about it. Yeah, is that this kid is, this kid is so weird.
Wait till you have kids. Yeah, you're in a rush.
trying to get all the molesting done. Come on man. Yeah, you got a nephew man.
This is about a
somebody who is I mean he's a mold breaker. Yeah, you know, youngest to do
it. Not only is he trying to molest his parents, but he picks the weirdest one.
He picks the weird and his dad is a weird guy in the movie, which is a
standard.
That would make you weird too. I think your dad was weird. Your son was straight
getting up in your stuff.
- Yeah, well he acts weird as hell in that movie.
- I'd probably be the family man and I'd handle it.
- How many times have we talked about this movie
on the show?
- I don't know if we ever have.
- Yeah?
- It's a bit risque and we don't typically cover that type
of a guy as blue.
- No, I mean as soon as the video started getting bluer,
I think our material has as well.
- Oh God.
- Yeah.
- I like the blue video.
- I do like the blue video,
but do you think we could tone it down
with the blue material?
- Do you think it, oh.
you're the one who no you didn't. I didn't. But you're the one who called it
blue. But you're the one who was talking about blueness. Yeah. Blue, we can go
blue-ish, but I don't think we can go. I'm ready to go. I'm ready to dive head
first. You want to go straight blue? I like every once in a while. You want to
become completely blue? Are you mad? Are you mad Cameron? Every once in a while we
do something really disgusting and I think that's good. It weeds out the
people on their toes. People who like normal stuff. It weeds out the weak.
we don't we don't something about us is a little. How do I say a little
offensive to normies? Yeah, what we haven't done a big disgust her in a
while, though, stinky shit, you haven't you know touched upon eating poop.
Well, I guess yeah, you know, now that I think about it, it's not so gross to
molest your dad. It's just wrong.
You don't think it's a little I mean it depends on the dad. I guess I was on
the situation of how you do it, but it's not that I mean it's just it's
it's maybe morally repugnant, but you know it's just sex. Well, it doesn't say
anything about this in the Bible,
but if your dad is really I'm positive, a son molested their dad in the Bible
yeah, it's not upon the I'm absolutely positive. The Old Testament that is an
Old Testament story and the moral is supposed to be a job molester that
treat your parents with
listen
clean your room and listen to your parents.
I think there was a boy. There was a boy,
the most disobedient boy in all of Jerusalem,
father, Jod would tell him to clean to clean the
to sweep the part of the house or the it's so dusty, but all I had was sand
floors. The whole thing's dust and he's making his kids sweep. So he's to get
I'm going to let them. This is not
testament story. This isn't right. What we're talking about isn't right. If
that was an old testament story, they would have done a veggie tales about it
with the asperius son and dad
and I could honestly see a shot for shot recreation of there's something wrong
about it. We completely they would do they would do they would like kind of do
the Bible for kids thing and they would make the entire story about the sun was
tickling his dad. Yeah, yeah, that was like stop. You're making me laugh. Yeah,
I'm laughing all over the place on now. Normally a dad tickles the sun yeah,
but here the sun is getting tickles on the is the getting he's getting points
on the tickle board and he has no interest in is that part of that movie
where the sun molest the dad and the dad's like oh my God, this is awful. My
son's gay
is that
I don't think so yeah it shouldn't be you know what son I'm kicking you out
yep, you better find your own apartment, because if you're going to be
okay, that's right, you're going to pay rent. You're going to be paying rent
buddy. You want to do that stuff. You move to New York where all the other
sons are molesting their dad. Dad molesters yeah, I'm sending my son to San
Francisco.
Movie, why did he make this movie? Don't have to talk about it all the time.
to be weird. You probably just want everyone to have deep conversations,
but how do you if you're if you were I mean, I don't know about you guys, but I
can tell you how I can't count how many times I've been, you know, in those
classic plastic chairs, sitting around the fire pit
out of the cabin with my friends. So
you guys ever molested your dad? Yeah, and everyone deep thoughts, everyone
smoking the weed, smoking weed and then like talking to your talking to your
I did you ever fight your dad. Oh yeah. Yeah, I'm actually kind of a weird
relationship with my dad right now. Yeah.
Yeah, after I graduated, I just started molested. I just got really sad after I
graduated and left the house.
But why would you make it right? First movie? So disgustingly make that was
that one of his ones he made when he was in college. I think that was just
like yeah, it's like a five project. This is man. You can't make a movie like
make that until you are a dad. That's right. Why would you make that movie as
a dad? You make that as you make that movie as a son. It's an admission of
guilt. Exactly. You make that movie as a dad. It's a cry for attention or help.
This is why only a girl should have been able to make this movie. That's true.
That is kind of completely divorced from the problem. Honestly, you know what the
problem is. If a girl had made that movie, it would have been erotic, steamy
and sexual. It would have been a firefighter. It would have been to
fiddle late firefighter firefighters.
So they literally get off on shit like that.
That's true.
Like girls get off on the idea of a firefighter, like just tying their shoe
for them.
I did recently find out that girls like guys kissing video.
Yeah, they like gay guys against each other, girls fighting each girls, like
videos of guys fighting.
They like videos of like guys on like sixth street in Austin.
Just beat each other.
The Morgan Wallen concert fights.
Oh yeah.
All that kind of stuff.
People fighting in the stands at Philly's games.
Yeah, that kid at the Dallas Stars game who said the N-word and then got the shit kicked
out of him.
Yeah.
They like, they watch that stuff and they start gilling off like crazy.
They watch.
They're sitting on the washing machine watching that video of that guy getting shot with paintball
pellets.
Speaking of gilling off, Cameron, pray tell, what was the funny pornography video title
that you saw?
And can we find it? I don't want to find it. Okay. He's afraid nerd versus thug and there
was no victory. He said I didn't watch it there. Well, in a situation like that, I think
I would hope that both people win. Well, I would hope that the nerd, I think that it
was one girl who was a girl and then there was a nerd and there was a thug and and poor
boys. So she probably she's like, who does she was probably a nerd and a thug. She probably
I picked the thug, but the nerd should have won.
Yeah, I mean yeah, well the thug
the nerd would win the war. The nerd would win the war, but this battle
between the nerd and the thug. Well, but it was a I mean it was probably he
could have outsmarted the thug with his nerdly ways, but the thug knows about
the art of Shiatsu massage. Oh, that was that would actually work. That's
it's actually true. It's actually half. Also, no is he's also got giving a
massage, but the nerd has spider man, esk reflexes, though exactly and maybe
probably got webs of nut. Maybe maybe the nerd had a bigger member. Yeah,
it's always the nerds man. The nerds got
always an unsuspecting nerd with a large member
suspecting the large. That was another video title. Do you guys have a large
man? Do you have big members or small members? I don't even know what my
member. Honestly, I haven't seen it in the scale of like you says a scale in
the scale of like like as a rainbow fish scale, small to like large. I'm
probably
I'd say my average to small to large. That's your scale. The scale of members
across the world. I think that mine is nothing to write home about.
Okay, so you think that maybe there are some that people are writing home about.
I think that there is.
Dear mother and father, I've had the most exquisite experience.
A member I saw this evening was absolutely godzillan.
Oh well.
Europe is treating me quite well mother.
Martha, our daughter has seen one of the most godzillian members of the state.
I met the most unsuspecting nerd.
With the largest member.
whose name is Benjamin Franklin. She's having only coupled with thugs in my
ten year as a lover
I've found myself accustomed to the small. I'm now dabbling with the size
of the main member dinky, dinky member, a dinky member. I've I've saw a member
my word, our daughter is
moved on from the key members for member
She's moved on completely from dinky members.
There were people back in the day. She throws the window up and she leans out
all the people walk around the street holding clothes. I've seen the nerd
with the largest
I can't hold it in any longer.
When I've been with a nerd,
back in the day before they had phones to shoot each other, disgusting,
lewd images. Well, there were people who could draw real fast, but not
drawing even where people sure where people just writing like hello. Yes,
the war continues. My penis is as big as a bullet and I wish that I could
magnetize it to your mouth. They were taking daguerreotypes where you have to
sit still for the photo for like three minutes straight or else it blurs, so
they're jacking off in front of the camera and then they get the picture
printed on. It looks like they're the flash, their hands blurred up and down
on their thing completely still and their areas, like
which is why Japan does that.
What is that about man? Why do they still do that? I think it's a law over
there that people have to be cartoon to be in a movie. You can see well,
do they
different laws? No, when they blur the they blur out all the all the junk
yeah
that's a cartoon. Well, if you can show it in a cartoon, can you show a car to
cartoons where they show it? I've seen cartoons. You guys wouldn't believe
I've seen about cartoons in Japan is cartoons over there are for adults.
Doesn't make a lot of sense. No, I seen this one cartoon over there. That was
this kid and he's trying to collect all these Pokemon.
why can't I see their things in Japan to be able to search twenty things can't be
seen anywhere, but in Japan, well, that's why in red they have to Miffy. They have
stuff that you can see in a noodle brand. Pringles is a noodle. Pringles is
not a noodle brand stupid Google. What is considered wait? What is considered
disrespectful in Japan? Let's read okay, pointing in public. I just you're
pointing to it. We're not in public. We're not yeah, we're in private. I guess
you're right yeah, but at what line does what point is the line between public
a private blur in a podcast yeah. That's a really good point. We are
technically outside. What point do we do you guys think that we would fare well
or intensely poorly in eastern nations,
like eastern which ones far east far yeah? I mean I think okay, here's here's
my my run down. I think I would do really well in China. I think I do
pretty well. I don't know. Is that a party? Not sure I do so well in Korea,
Korea, I Korea, Korea, North Korea, they're a little buttoned up. I could
do North Korea, South Korea. I'm not so sure about China would definitely be my
most my best performance. Yeah, as a citizen, I do think you would be an
amazing citizen. I'd be really good. They would think Japan, I mean, I do
think I'm think I'm kind of quiet and demure that I could adjust to public
life in Japan and not and you see this a guy like this. He has an outside
voice and that's not looked so kindly upon in Japan. Now me, I'm more of I'm
I'm well it depends. But also but the main problem about Japan is I can't
speak Japanese. The most that I've seen of Japan. It's a big barrier. Most I've
seen of Japan is from Jackass One. That's the most you've seen of Japan? I've
not seen a lot of, I've seen maybe a few videos here and there, but the most I've
seen of, like, people going out in public. You've never seen Lost in
Translation? No, I've really, I haven't seen that. I've seen Jackass One. Really
great movie going off of what they did in that if I go there and I start
shooting bottle rockets out of my ass and doing wasabi snooters and like
running around in a panda suit. I think that that could fare well if that's
what you can do. Did you guys see that video that video on x.com of the guy
who's from Australia or something and he goes to Japan and you know in Japan,
they have they have subway cars that are women only. Yeah, I can be on and he
goes he's like he's felt selfie filming. It's like they've got a car that's
women only walk and he goes into the key, walks into the car and he's just
videoing all the women and they're all like staring at it. It's like staring at
him and he's like well yeah, it looks like it's all women.
He just walks around it for like thirty seconds and they're all just like
staring him down and then he just leaves. That is awesome! It's really
funny. I seen a video of a dude, these two twitch like IRL stream. I saw that
this week, got in there, they got their jaw slid and their phones broke. They
knocked out. They got knocked the fuck out. But the best part about that video is as soon
as the second guy gets punched, he's filming the other guy who's already on the ground,
he gets a donation. He gets a text to speech. But the sound, he gets clocked and then as
soon as he's on the ground you hear the Mario coin. It's so good. And then the text to speech
is somebody who just paid $5 to write Hiroshima Nagasaki over and over and over again. So
The guy's like knocked out on the ground. It's like Hiroshima Nagasaki.
Oh my God.
Hiroshima Nagasaki.
It's crazy.
Definitely. If I was over there, I would not be IRL streaming.
You would have...
That's all I would do.
I think that you would definitely be knocked out if you were in a public place in Japan.
I would be knocked out. Yeah.
Why?
Wait, no. You're the meekest one in public. What are we talking about? You and me are
the crazies.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
He's nothing.
No, because...
but he's meek when he's playing a prank.
But if you're hanging out and you're having a good time, you're going to be skateboarding around.
You can't skateboard during... actually I do know this, you can't skateboard
every single skateboard clip in Japan, not every single but a good chunk of them, if you try
to street skate, they're very, very... They only let you do it on a hoverboard.
They don't want you to... yeah, basically you get five stars
the cops... you get your board taken away, stuff like that. Every single
illegal street clip is filmed at like nighttime. The one thing about Japan,
their culture that is pretty interesting is, I guess it's very customary over
there that normally it's frowned upon when you break the laws of Japan.
Really? Yeah, where here... You're not so much supposed to do illegal things
that break the law. It's more than just a recommendation there. It's part of
their culture. Yeah, it's a cultural difference where you can actually go to
prison for breaking laws. Really? Yeah. Yeah. And kind of backwards country is
yes, I've never seen good manners are usually smiled upon. Yes, that's that
hell. We're here. The mild mannered are actually some of the lowest people in
our society. Yeah, like us yeah beaten down yeah, we're down trodden burn to a
crisp. We're completely down. Do they have jails in Japan? No, do they have
food in Japan? They do, but they don't eat that much of it, huh, and it's
considered respectful to
enjoy your food. Yeah, and you don't really house it. You're supposed to show
your respect the burp in Japan. I think it's very I can't is which I saw. I
always remember hearing in elementary school, you know, and and is I don't
remember Japan or China or what you're supposed to burp after you eat because
it really respect you're thinking of Shrek. Yeah, that's never never land.
That was one of those, but you know, you know, when you hear one of those facts
about an Asian country when you're in elementary school and you don't know if
You know, speaking of food and customs, there's a, in Germany, it's apparently very disrespectful
to get a to-go box because you couldn't finish your food.
Is that true?
Yeah.
That's what my German teacher told me in high school, is that if you ask for a to-go box,
they'll give it to you, but it's like, "Fucking Americans."
Americans that can't eat their food?
No, like if you don't...
Nobody, they don't eat giant portions of like sausage and pretzels?
Not that much, though.
I mean if you go to the if you go to the restaurant and you over eat or I guess
are you like over order over order that's considered very rude because
you come from a country where you get a burger with four stacks on it exactly
stuff patties and fillings, but it's also rude to tip.
Why did I ever under why is it rude to think about I don't I think it's I
think it's I think it's not right money. I think that maybe it is rude, but
they figured out that they tell you when you're a tourist in Europe. What they
say to you is they're like now it's not it's not customary to tip here, but if
you want to, you can that's every place they're like, but if you want to leave
them a little extra money, I don't understand how that could be possibly
now. How could that possibly be construed as rude that I'm giving you extra money?
Yeah, yeah, how fucking stupid are these Europeans that they think that that's
wrong every single European? They also if when you do leave them a tip or in
Ireland. We left if we left people a tip, would you a few times? I mean, I
think you're supposed to tip a bartender. Maybe I can't remember, but we left
people to they're like, Oh, my God, thank you. It's like chill. I get the
fuck out of my face. Yeah,
you got danger close to my face. I can't see with these sunglasses. You got a
real real close. I guys are fly. I felt I felt like I felt a whiff of your
finger. These are fly. You got a way from my finger. He has aren't his
finger pit smell. You need finger deodorant.
Yeah, you got to get in those webs.
My body's been smelling really badly.
Yeah.
What's going on, man?
Ever since I've had it.
Nerd versus thug.
I didn't jack off to nerd versus thug.
No, he said earlier he thought he was ruining the mood,
so he couldn't do it.
I was too funny.
Yeah.
You don't want to...
That's why that ad that always comes up on porn that's like,
"This is not a dating website.
You need to fuck ugly old grannies."
You need to fuck an old woman.
Yeah. If you reject someone's...
What are the lyrics?
you need you will have to the lyrics ugly grannies. If you reject something
someone sexually, you will be banned from the website.
It's a really good ad, but if that comes up, I'm not familiar with it. I
thought you were joking. No, it's real and I show I talked to three people
about it last night who all said they had seen it too. Wow and somebody
actually had a screen recording of it on their phone when I brought it up
and I was like, yep, that's the one man. That is a funny fucking ad and
let me tell you what these grannies not that so many grannies are hot. These
grannies are especially ugly. They have freckles.
No, liver spots you mean.
Liver spots. Old liver spots.
I can't wait to have liver spots.
Morgan Freeman's got them.
I'm going to get some good ass liver spots.
He's got freckles. He's got normal freckles.
I think I heard somebody say he has liver spots one time.
Are people still mad at him just because he's dating his daughter?
Oh my god.
Something's up with the Freemans.
In the reverse way.
Actually we don't know.
Yeah, we don't know.
We don't know who started it.
But Morgan's finishing it, I'll tell you that much.
Is it like a Sun Yi thing?
I think it was his step-daughter, but not adopted daughter like Sun Yi.
Speaking of Sun Yi, on Friday I went to this party with my friend.
It was like this event thing.
It's like 3 a.m. It's like a bunch of fucking some like
like stupid
exclusive like fucking
stupid excuses like VIP fucking
It was at this this like club thing where they have a pool in the middle of the room like a little like bathtub
and
We convinced this dude that Woody Allen was there
like two in the morning.
And
I thought this story is funny. I thought this is really funny. You can
convince them. We convinced him that Woody Allen was there with soon. He and
he was sitting by the crepe station.
There was a crepe. They had a crepe. They had a crepe station and it was
three in the morning. This guy went over and looked and then came back and was
like he's not there and we're like oh yeah no I think him and Sun Yi were really tired.
That's got to be one of the most incredible things I've ever heard in my life.
It was really funny I think you just should have seen the guy we told.
Well were you under the influence of alcohol?
I was actually under the influence of alcohol and drugs.
So you were a bit slap happy?
I was a little bit slap happy.
I think that maybe I regret telling this story now because everyone is going to make fun
of me.
Well now it just set you basically just the punchline was not all there I'm going to be
honest with you.
So it really is this story about you being a you're a socialite.
I was yes I was at an annoying thing for fashion week because of my friend.
Oh I think your fashion's week.
I think fascism's week and it's going to lose to us.
Yeah a strong socialist.
Yeah. Okay. I can save that by saying that there was something actually funny that happened
before this, which I showed you the video, but I don't know if I showed you.
Oh, wait. Yes, this actually does save it.
Okay. So before we went there, we went to this other bar because our friend was DJing
and we were outside having a cheeky cigarette and a little boy at -- this was at midnight
A little boy ran up to me and my friend Rupert and screamed at us.
Then held out a box of candy and went, "CASH APP!"
Rupert's from Australia, he's not gonna fuck it, he can't use any of that.
What'd you buy?
We didn't have any cash, we were gonna pay him, but we didn't.
didn't. Somebody else gave him twenty dollars to scare every single person
that walked by.
So all these people were leaving this club and
this little boy is hiding in like the outdoor seating of a restaurant that's
directly next door,
just running up and grabbing people and going.
See, I watched the video that you show because you took a video of him doing
hit somebody and I realize that's my biggest nightmare, because I think my
instant react. I was my
before I even realize it's a kid yeah. I would I'm swinging there was somebody
there were I didn't record the other this person, but somebody went up to
like he jumped out at the guy that's that's a so funny yeah. We just hold the
sound up. Just listen to his scream when he startles him. He did this to somebody
and the guy went kid fuck you and
That's what I was doing.
Yeah.
See, that was the only that was the funny story.
I should have told that one.
That kid is poor, guys.
That kid needs that money badly.
Well, he made a lot of money.
It's so funny to take the $20 and be like, "I guess I have to do this."
No, he was just run away.
Yeah, he was happy to do it.
He was happy to do it.
And also, I noticed.
He has a shield.
so you can say no, that guy paid me to do it. Yeah that too, but also I noticed he
the the as soon as he like scared me and Rupert and showed the thing he had two
pieces of candy left. He was doing good that night. He cleaned up. Oh my God,
pieces. How do you know he didn't start with two pieces? How do you know I
didn't eat the candy and that's why you're scaring people. He had a sugar
rush. That's a good point. I have a bit of a sugar rush right now because I ate
pineapple and had an electro lit. Yeah, that's a good. I have a little bit of a
- I got a sugar rush off of my coffee from this morning.
- That is a different kind of rush.
That's a black drink rush.
- It's a sugar rush.
- I did, I woke up very early 'cause my cat woke me up.
He bit me to feed him and I stayed up
and I had both a Celsius, or no, a Prime,
and a couple squirts of Pizzazz.
- I saw you spraying your drug.
- You squirted Pizzazz in your, yeah, that is so,
you know, I've been tempted sometimes when you're not here
when I'm at the office and I see the pizzazz thing. Oh, that's out
completely. I was, I was squirting the remnants of it because I knew that I
needed to be on my top of my game today
and, you know, and I was, I told this amazing story about a funny joke that
I'd, that I told. You just need to, you know what you need to do with your
stories, man? I need to go to a storytelling class. You gotta embellish.
Here, let me, let me, let me, let me, this is the version of the story you
should have told. Okay. So we're at this party, fashion week. It was hella dope.
you are a my way cooler and yes, more exclusive. We were people. We were
beatboxing and be boing in the corner sounds fire and this guy, this chump
pulls up chud, this chud pulls up and it's like is there anyone cool at the
party and and I'm like I Patrick, I'm like yo fam it ain't like that, but
there is one cat over there by the punch.
his name's Woody Allen. Maybe you heard of him. Oh, and he's here with soon.
You send this so fucking this guy goes over. He
sashays over to the bull. This person would have been was there and he was
fucking soon on the table. Damn wow.
See that's how you tell a story. See the problem is and then probably is I just
don't know how to tell stories. I was lying. Well, you just got to into you
get whenever you tell stories like this. I get too into the detail. You add too
details that make it sound really annoying. Yeah. Of like, "Well, I was at this
exclusive party at 3 a.m. at Fashion Week." I know. I said that. As soon as I said that, I
was like, "Who the fuck am I to say that? Why did I say that?" Yeah, you were not...
you were nothing. I was at a more exclusive party that night. I literally...
as soon as the words left my mouth, I was like, "If I... I should kill myself."
You don't kill yourself. You know what party I was a part of that night? You're not
Not beyond saving.
I don't think I'm beyond saving, but it could get there.
You think you could get to the point where you can't be saved?
I think so.
I think I could get there.
Where it's just over, there's nothing, there's only one way out.
Every single one of the fans of the show turns on me and you two secretly resent me and don't
tell me.
I have dreams about this.
I already resent you so much for going to exclusive parties.
Can I tell my joke about my exclusive parties?
I have dreams about this.
I'll say this and then you can tell me about that.
I have dreams about this because before I go to bed,
I watch all of the, like everyone,
like you guys turning on me and like everyone
hating me a lot.
I have nightmares about this because I,
but when I, before I go to bed,
I will watch the Too Lazy to Try Bert Kreischer.
(laughing)
And I'm like, what if I end up like that?
What if like every single person hates my guts?
like ten years down the line. Yeah, you got a while once once I write my
machine bro. It's
figure out your machine. Patrick, I love you and I appreciate you and I like the
fact that you are unapologetically you. I've had so many nightmares about
because it's it's it's boiling in my brain like
I'm going to be Bert dude. Maybe you're going to be the machine. Maybe you're
just coming to you're just becoming too cool for me and camera. I think so. I
you one day guys. I think wait you think you're becoming too cool. Let me tell my
thing now yeah. I was I was part of an exclusive party that night. You know who
was there for people me a rogue, a cleric and a wizard. There's three all
night. Holy shit that is exclusive as fuck, but it's also kind of nerdy yeah,
maybe a little see he didn't go to your kind of like chic, chic, though
say ye she you're kind of like geek chic, though geek chic yeah that guy's that
guys make some bad music. You think he makes bad music? That's his favorite
artist.
Defend yourself.
He only listens to TikTok sounds.
You do listen to that shit. His favorite song is
that's why he's in such a jolly mood every morning. You know what song that...
He listens to this song.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
I do.
So the Plex has your music on it and I'll accidentally, I'll go down, I'll go to watch
a film maybe, you know, the other night I watched Network.
Nice.
And, but I clicked on the music and I saw that all of the stuff on there was like Yeet
and Joey and Cemetery and stuff like that.
And Jubio, you're pushing 50.
I don't have any cemetery or joy in that and that's it. You're completely lying.
Yeah, we're lying, but we're watching out. You were born in 1970. You were born
during the Eisenhower administration. You can't be listening to the kid Leroy.
That is a wrong. It's wrong. Okay, if we just never talked about it, but like
do you feel it's like like really fucking
yeah, maybe he fakes his birth certificate like minute bowl. Maybe
yeah, it's possible.
Guys, we have been talking about exclusivity
and different parties and what is more exclusive? What is more exclusive
than what then I need to get abducted by an alien. I need to learn my choices
of words better. Play the sound getting abducted by an alien from another world.
What I think we kind of abandoned the secret alien costumes thing. What are
you talking about? The identity protection thing? My identity is
fucking protected.
That's why I've been so on one. This is the truth, guys. I'm not going to. I'm
I'm not I'm not going to split forks with you. We
could get killed for doing this episode. A hundred percent yeah. This is a lot of
private in let me just let me disguise your voice real quick. Please, please,
please
imagine this.
You are in your bed late at night. You're falling asleep. They're counting
your sheep. You're at ninety nine out of a hundred. This is normally where you
would fall asleep
as you say, one hundred, who should come and be, who should burst through your
closet door. He was there the whole time. Your suspicions from childhood were
correct. There was an alien in your closet. He uses a beam of green to put
you in a machine where he looks at your teen thing. You're teenaged? You're teen-,
yeah, you're a teenager and he looks at your teen thing. That makes sense.
The alien, the alien is looking at your teen thing? He looks at your teeny,
teen thing. Is it teen-, are you saying it's teeny or it's teenaged? He looks
at your tween thing. I'm a tween now you're back to being a tween and
you've been a buttoning up deked it by an alien and they are looking into your
stink and your thing is his green guys. It's an alien episode.
Here's some things I found. I just looked at it was honestly we were
talking about it was surprisingly hard to find yeah. It was actually really,
really hard to find the problem with the finding a UFO and alien sightings is
none of the people or none of the stuff is funny. Nobody ever yeah funny one and
When you do look this stuff up, if you look up what I was looking up about Arcturians,
right?
Obama, a famous Arcturian shapeshifter.
You have to click the captcha thing on Google.
And you don't know how to do that.
No.
No, you can't read captchas.
I have to have, I was waiting for you guys to come into the office because I was sitting,
yeah, I'm sitting there, I'm like, what's a fire hydrant?
That's tough.
Well, it's also tough because you don't know, is the little corner still a fire hydrant?
Exactly.
Right.
aliens killing people, which I've never heard this before, but I clicked it
because the guy's name is Am I crazy or not?
Have you heard of any stories of aliens killing people? And this guy says no, I
think, or he's
some Dr. Wu said, I know of only one instance in South America or Central
America, but can't recall the country. Apparently, the man had been partially
stripped of skin. I don't recall why they thought it was alien connected
regarding Beckley. He is someone they're talking about. He's known for
conversationalizing ufo tails blah blah blah. This guy says no. I think I
remember that one. Some guy in South America saw a ufo and went to get a
closer look, then got hit with a beam of light and his skin started falling off
and he died. I remember that too. This was the biggest news story ever yeah
and this was doctor. Doctor who the last reply on this thread is this guy say my
own experiences is that the reptilian slash a lizard humanoids I'm dealing with
seems to eat my clones when the need for them are up after a soul abduction is
completed. That happened in March, July, August and September this year. They
probably did that in June too, but I don't know, because I slash my soul, cut
the contact with the clone on my own and probably in early stage of the abduction.
I'm still a little baffled how I could do that, though. So long they don't eat
me, my main body, so I'm fine, I guess. That's my main body, my soul. Oh yeah,
he was curious. Yeah. Oh yeah, he's got clones. He was saying that. So this guy
has clones all over the world. They're being abducted by reptilians/lizard
humanoids, but his main body is fine. He's baffled how he's doing this. I
guess that's a good explanation on why nobody's like, "Whoa, why's there so
many of these guys? Because they eat the clones." True.
My Journey to Find Out Who or What I Am by Mark Antony. Wow, rings a bell.
Maybe it's the real Marc Antony. J-Lo's ex-husband. J-Lo's ex-husband.
Hello. I had the craziest year of my life and found out I'm the biggest secret in the world.
First thing first, I was born a pieces in 1969. That makes me a Earth rooster fish, the creator.
Both of my grandfathers are special men. Joseph John... Wait, mine too.
Yeah, of course. My special big guys. My grandfathers are pieces of shit.
Joseph John Rochefort. He ran the magic program for the U.S. Navy that broke the
Japanese codes in WW2. His nickname was Merlin, and he remembers everything he
see and heard, and the greatest puzzle solver in history.
- Whoa.
- Elf, he looks like a elf, as my father and me when I was younger, super skinny
head with large sticking out ears. Ray Bruce, that comes from a long line of
cunning folks that is famous for miracle healing. The rumor is that makes him an
angel alien. My mother and father both didn't get sick and can heal miracle
fast. Light and dark angel.
Whoa, wait.
Getting sick from what?
Ray Bruce. Rodney Bruce.
Who dat?
Oh my God.
The leader of the Illuminati.
Shit.
Who we contacted, the master.
I've been talking to him since then, actually.
Oh yeah?
Wait, actually, can you...
Once he's done with this, can you pull up some of those texts?
Yeah, I'll give you a quick update once he's done with this.
Okay.
I've been making, whoops, I've been making life from day one
paragenesis way, or like Zeus does.
I just look at you and you have a baby in a couple weeks.
(laughing)
I don't die, I don't remember my dreams,
but when woken up in a dream, I'm lost for about 30 to 60
minutes because I don't know where I am or what is real.
The dream I was pulled out of felt real.
I knew about my miracle healing because it runs in my family.
I just found out I was being used by the reptiles
to make them babies and that they've been blocking my memory and controlling me.
This Halloween at a bar party, a drunk reptile told me what I was doing in their bar.
I'm an angel and they hate me, but respect me.
30 minutes later, I heard crazy screaming coming from the girls' bathroom.
A woman who kissed me started to lay eggs.
Before that, they was staying close to me and feeding off my life energy.
But all of a sudden, they distanced themselves from me.
And I heard whispers saying, "He is an archangel."
He's an archangel. He's an archangel.
After that, the Lord Reptile at Capo Beach Church told me I was God. He only
told me because I healed him of COVID in less than a week.
Whoa.
The reptile aliens are in charge of Calvary Chapel Church, Saddleback Church,
and Mariners, and they are brainwashing the church-going humans and taking over
their bodies during baptism. You have to assume, yeah.
Yeah.
Christianity is reptile religion.
Facts.
Kind of cool, kind of like some Hitchens shit. That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
It looks like the Freemasons are in charge of the reptile souls to make sure
they are not lost and put into a new human body. LDS Church, that happens if
a male at 18 decided to become an elder. His human life ends when they put the
snake into them. Whoa. It looks like I'm the 26,000 end of the era cycle creator
of aliens, animals and humans. Birds and fish go sex crazy around me.
That's my favorite line of this. Birds and fish go sex crazy around me, as well
as younger aliens. It looks like there is a new alien in play. Big eyes, owls. They fight
with their minds and they don't like it when I look straight into their eyes and they can't
touch my mind. I'm told my alien race is a shapeshifter but looks like a very tall roadrunner.
Rooster God the creator alien. I look different to different people. God or the best looking
male or female you like. My race conquer time and space. I think I'm the firstborn. Father
of humans and younger alien races. I need help to understand all of this because
they see me but I don't see them. Most of them don't know I'm the first ancient
born aliens. They just see me as an angel as humans do."
Rooster God the creator alien sounds like one of those like
tertiary Wu-Tang clan members.
That's Rooster God the creator alien.
And that sounds like a ghost face line. "Birds and fish go sex crazy."
It's like that Wu-Tang affiliated guy that like chopped off his dick and jumped off a
building or whatever.
Oh, I forgot that guy.
I don't remember his name.
Is that what he did?
I don't remember what he did.
Did he get, did he, was he hung by his, his balls off of a six story building?
Was he, did...
I don't think that's true.
Did they smash his balls with a spike bat?
I think his balls got cut off in a way or something.
Did they heat up a rusty hanger?
He got castrated or some shit.
No, it didn't do that.
I didn't do it. I heard it went. It probably went if that happened, but it
didn't. Did they lay his nuts on a dresser? This is kind of the only
interesting thing I found. So then I just do what you do when you want to
find some cool stuff and you just go to go to India forums,
which has just got all of it's just a forum in India where you can talk about
TV, movies and digital and this digital yeah, which I didn't really delve into
the digital. They did have a one day. We will that a book just sections, but the
main sections was called the entertain cave where you can talk about movies and
tv. That's pretty cool. It's a good name too, but they have a paranormal section
alien abductions. Do you believe watch? I believe in aliens. This is monar, but
not sure if they abduct. I prefer to imagine them more human rather than any
creepy looking sloppy creature,
which is a pretty scary idea. It'd be working for us. Sloppy looking sloppy
creature, a sloppy, scary, slobbery creature is not what you want to see when
to open up a UFO alien ship.
Aliens could find humans to barbaric with an over fondness for wars. Pink
says ET was the best alient.
Weld alien. Yeah, a little Brian Jordan Alvarez type of way of talking this
welt. This alient
is seriously going to TJ Mac guys
last I heard.
Yeah, and is that the end? Yep. That's the end of mine guys. Wow. It's nice.
Thank you. Thank you so much. Pat, you want to go next?
Sure. All right. Well, this one, this is, well, guess what? I couldn't find much,
but I saw an alien last night. Cameron and Caleb told me to write about an alien that I saw.
I gave you a book report.
They gave me a book report.
Because you said, "Guys, there's no, nobody's ever said anything funny about aliens on the internet."
And I said, "Okay, well, then you could be the first."
Well, this is an alien that I saw last night.
I was asleep in my bed, usually sleep on my back.
But this night I slept on my side because I was using my phone.
And when I look up, I saw the strangest thing I think I've ever seen.
You want to click play on that?
You put a video in.
OK, so describe this video.
It's a one eyed green
alien that I saw this in my bedroom last night.
What the fuck? This is terrifying. Yeah.
You know, this is a slop, a sloppy alien.
That is a sloppy looking sloppy green.
I understand now.
Yeah, God.
And then I found this video.
It's another another video.
Yeah, this is the same the same video man.
No.
What the hell is this video called?
What I want to have sex with an alien.
Is that you?
How long is the same shirt as you?
How long is this video?
Not Scorpiona
Okay
I bet you they have some wet and juicy pussy.
If any alien...
Can you turn it up a little bit Jubio?
On the video?
Please?
Please come to where I live and kidnap me.
And let's have sex in your spaceship.
I would love that.
- You don't get to hide your identity for this.
You need to show who's doing this.
- But I heard an alien,
their pussy is always drenched.
That thing is soaked.
So I want the wettest pussy ever.
Comic book guy.
I want an alien to come,
take me to your spaceship and do things to me that you have never done before.
I think you get the gist of it. You know, he wants an alien. It's a guy wearing a
real tree jacket and he's got he's got a lot of other videos where he wears a
guy like a bio shock mask, creepy doll type man. Yeah. And he's saying that
aliens have the wettest pussies in the world or in the universe, I guess. Yeah,
the galaxy. I'm going to say I really with the slideshow portion, but I think
I made up for it by finding this video was seventy seven views. Yeah, I think I
I think I'll be watching a lot of this. I think I'll be watching a lot of
scorpions videos. Yeah, scorpions good name, alien name. Maybe he's an alien
with a face like that. I think that he's an alien face like that. He could be
true. I don't think that's his real face. The camera. It looks like his real
face to me. I mean, it's hard to see what kind of looks like a cherub shades,
but all right, we go to the next. Let's get Cameron's line show here and let's
We've kind of hit off the screen and not, yeah.
We don't want to hear about an alien's pussy anymore.
Well, clearly you did because you wanted everyone to hear about it.
You made us watch that.
I was trying to find stuff about, I was trying to find a forum of like people who are into
like avipositors and stuff and like exophilics.
I was trying to find an exophilics forum.
Oh, exophilic, that's a good word.
Or exophilia.
Right.
An exophilic is like when a mosquito or it's like a, like how many mosquitoes are there
It's like an exophilic is like an organism that lives off of like human, like eating like blood and stuff.
Like a parasite?
I looked up exophilics for them because I thought that would be like exophilia.
Exophile.
I should have looked up exophile.
I guess, yeah.
Damn it. Maybe I would have found something.
But I was looking for like people talking to and like reviews for ovipositors and stuff.
Yeah, yeah, sitting on it.
but all I could find all I could find for Avi positive stuff was what is an
fish forms what people are saying legs out of yeah snap where they're they're
saying their fish accidentally pro lapsed their shoes their fish pro lapsed
yeah I found out.
This is the worst thing ever man this is nasty on this app this one's really on
another level but I'm gonna bring it back to the wholesome stuff okay I love
wholesome ass. So this is a website I found called taken by the graze
abductions in close encounters of the fourth kind. This is a guy who's just
written about all of his experiences with alien. He's seen a lot of
spaceships. Okay, mostly spaceships more than aliens throughout his, but he's
seen some graze alien graze throughout his life and he just kind of writes
about them on his blog. So most of them are very funny. There was a technical
accident. I think that they're trying to shut us. They literally tried to shut
shut us down, but we have no where if we get some static added to splice those
two together. I think that would be appropriate. I think and I think that
they will add static over the entire episodes. It was on here. Probably yes,
this shit is definitely getting d monkey monetized. Yes, so here's what
this guy. So here's one of this guy's sightings of a UFO by the grace
taken by the grace.
Refocus the window, take another gray taken by the gray taken by the gray.
thank you all right.
Okay, sorry, backward C shaped object. It was August twenty-seventh two thousand
five at around seven thirty PM. The sky was clear and there was still much light.
We had just entered Manitoba after making a delivery for a friend into Ontario,
so we were coming back with a semi tractor empty and heading West. It was
then that I noticed a backwards white sea in the sky off to the north of it,
but not too far. It was more above the north. First of all, I'm just thinking
what the fuck could that be backwards of white see in the sky come. I asked my
buddy who was driving. Do you see that he said yes, I then asked him what do
you think it is he said I don't know
wait. Can you go back to this image? This image is not mine, but similar in
appearance. Oh God, what he saw was what was his name again taken by the graze
taken by the graze. Okay,
I was thinking that maybe he's a blood and like he saw a sea and got like
really mad. Okay, well, I guess there's yeah. I guess it could be there's no C
and taken by the grace, the Reds versus the Blues versus the Graves man. I think
that they would unite. I think that Crips and blows would come together to
kill this gray. Definitely Grady. I then had the opportunity to watch this object
for about 45 minutes. It was as white as a jet contrail and I thought well, maybe
that's it, but I soon realized that it was remaining in the backwards C shape
and not fading or changing. I know there are strong winds up there and it should
have dissolved away by now. It was traveling in a westerly direction, the
same as us. I wasn't sure, but after watching it for a little while, I
realized it was moving.
We were doing around 110 kilometers per hour, as I took note, and yet the object
continued to pull away from us and it was some distance up. It was not going
any higher up in the sky. It was gaining ground on us, though. I then noticed a
large jet airliner that was heading east. I watched the two, wondering what would
what happened when the two came closer together, the object seemed to actually
pass right by the jet. I thought to myself wow. I wonder if they saw it.
They must have for some time. I was racking my brain as I watched it
continue to get further away heading west, so let's let's let's run through
our evidence for what this is so far. We see a white shape in the sky yeah
backwards. See it's up high in the sky above it's moving through the sky
looks a little bit like a jet con trail and it's able to pass right by a plane
without them noticing even a little or maybe they did notice, but we don't know,
but it was able to pass right by a plane. So here's this guy's theory on what
this white shaped object in the sky could be okay. It couldn't be the moon,
not even close to the right place in the sky. It didn't look like any moon. I
have ever seen my buddy asked could it be Venus. I said no, it was way too big
and Venus is a bright object, certainly not a C shaped object. That is as large
as this was. I continued to watch it until it finally was too far west and
went out of sight and then he adds this picture. This was recorded in South
Korea. Fucking shit, I think this be a white object in the sky. What was it
well? It's a UFO man. It's the only explanation right fucking. I mean if it
looks like that it is a UFO look it even has like it's clear that it's like
It's not misty. It has a little reflective part where the sun is bouncing off of it like
an apple.
And it says YouTube in the corner. Look, someone was skywriting.
True. Oh, and they put that little YouTube there.
And that's maybe supposed to be a copyright symbol for YouTube.
Oh, okay.
But they made it too big and backwards.
Some bad YouTube.
Circle.
This is a silver play button, guys.
Yeah. So then here's my other part. That's my sighting I have to show you guys. But then
the other thing, I just want to talk about the news.
Okay.
website that I get all my news from, and this is the reason they're going to
shut us down is because I am plugging this website right now, but I got to
listen. I got to make a note. Everybody should be getting their news from this
website. This is where you're going to find the real news ancient files. Whoa
okay, holy fuck look at the front page of ancient files. Today, French woman
reveals she is a human alien hybrid video. Our history book teach us the
ancient civilizations were not technologically advanced, but here's the
evidence video. So this is a new this is the news website that's telling you
what you need to know. This is what's really going on okay. Is there about us
page ancient files is a website dedicated to ancient history, ancient
aliens and ancient UFOs. We will try to provide daily interesting content about
ancient aliens. So this is the hard hitting journalism that they're covering
up in the mainstream. So here's some stories that they got on ancient files
okay.
Emily finds baby alien creature with six arms in Texas.
That could be, okay, no.
This is definitely people who make Skingoo.
That could be a caterpillar.
It could be a caterpillar.
That's just a regular ass caterpillar.
I would recognize this photography style anyway,
this anywhere, this is the Etsy shop that sells baby Skingoo.
Why would it say baby alien if it was a toy?
It's literally called baby,
you're called baby alien.
It's a creature.
Today's episode is about the truth,
and you are sitting here and you are trying to say
that this is Skingoo?
What's wrong with you, man? You're covering... And this happened...
You were covering up on your own. You're completely covering it up. Okay,
if we believe everything, though, we're... You have to be a skeptic.
You have to be a skeptic to... You're being skeptic. You have all the...
I am being a skeptic of all the stuff that I don't believe in.
And that's fair. That's a caterpillar. That's really fair, actually. Okay,
this could be a caterpillar. And this took place on January 12th,
2023 is when this was found. A caterpillar type alien. Wait, that's the...
Wait, hold on. It took place in January and it has six arms.
now don't even don't even get I there's going to be something interesting about
the a distraction. All I'm saying dog a distraction. That's all it was a
distraction January six was January six from this or yes yeah, they honestly
were both distracting from each other. There's two distracting objects. Here's
another news story. Strange floating spoon has been found on Mars. What is it
exactly? January fourteenth, twenty twenty three, take a look at this giant
floating spoon and discover for yourself how bizarre the world really is that it
let's say the Mars. I guess that could be anything that's a spoon man. What do
you mean it could look at the red circle around it? That could be I mean
anything like yeah, that could be like a Martian rover, but why would that hover
guys a hoover? Why would somebody put a spoon on the ground like this? They're
done with their sats, that's the real strange thing about it. It's not on the
ground. Why would they it's above the ground rock? It's floating. I mean this
just is no scientist looked at the spoon. They said it can't be a fixed to
the rock. It must be floating based on the physics of but it's put it's
attached at that at the end. No attached to what in the red energy field around
yeah look it's got a red ball that's photo shot. No circle. They don't have
photoshop on Mars. They don't have computers.
I guess you're they can't do anything to create an image like this. Whatever
here's another story. Inter dimensional entities in form of fallen angels have
returned. Roussian scientists claim and this happened on January thirteenth
2023 and the russian we all remember this from happening in 2023 in January.
Yeah, the russians are like a race of alien that has commingled with society.
Mm hmm. The fallen angels have been defeated more than 5000 years ago during
the great revolution that destroyed the city state known as atlantis and has
been recorded in the stories and religion as the great flood. President
Vladimir Putin classified as a national threat. Any news related to a series of
mysterious craters erupting in Siberia. At the same time, remember that
Chelyabinsk meteor from twenty thirteen, which exploded with thirty times more
energy than an atomic bomb. Finally, it seems that the US, together with Europe,
is trying to demonize Putin and entangle Russia into a war in order to invade
Siberia and get hold of an ancient defense system designed to protect our
planet from these so called fallen angels. That's cut and dry. What
mainstream mainstream news they're talking about the war? They talk about
every damn day. When have they talk once about the fallen angels or the
chelyabinsk meteor? They don't talk about it man. I think two hundred people
got injured from that. Oh really, but I don't talk about it anymore. Wow yeah,
why is nobody still talking about this? The chelyabinsk meteor? I mean it's
kind of crazy. There was a meteor that hit somewhere in Russia, like kind of a
small town and I don't think anyone died, but a bunch of people got really
badly hurt. Yeah damn,
I don't know. Another story from January twelve, twenty, twenty three, this had
now this happened on January twelve, twenty twenty three,
archaeologists were shocked to discover an ancient three thousand year old
statue that looks like Michael Jackson. I'm a rock like Michael Jack, the
theory being that Jackson went back in time to various eras and was
immortalized by the ancient Egyptians and later by the painter, like maybe he
got a painter, the painter, maybe he got a
some kind of time disease and right or maybe he was going. That's why he that's
why he was always trying to have sex with children, because to them,
because he didn't understand time, he kind of he could show all of time laid
out before a four dimensional busting ninety eight year old man. He had no
it's just a nobody there's no time right there's no age. He lives in the
fifth dimension. That's an actually really good point yeah and people they
that they won't you won't hear about this on mainstream news. Here's another
one ancient submerged pyramid was recently discovered in China. It was
failed before the ice age, and this was discovered on January twelfth,
twenty, twenty three, according to a is the guy who discovered it yep, and he
also has a tv show. I think he has a long upwards hair. Yes, here's another
story for a down facing beard. Interesting, that's interesting yep, oh
my God, up and down hands,
weird iceberg spotted in Antarctica, and this weird iceberg was spotted in you
guessed it January twelfth, holy, holy wow,
I don't know if you guys remember all this stuff happening that day. I
remember it because I read ancient files. This is just one day of news.
Katy Perry collapses on stage when MK ultra mind control goes wrong and
this I forgot to put the date here, but this was also on January 12th.
I don't know if you remember this happening, but you know what that
MK stands for Michael Kors.
She's a woman and they be shopping. I put the date on this slide here
while performing on stage the beautiful singer Katy Perry started acting
weird with unexplained behavior.
She even said to the public that she is feeling weird and she started to talk without a hint.
Sources claim that it's not news the fact that Katy Perry is under the mind control
process by MKUltra.
This incident seems to take place due to an error in this process.
Wow.
Yep.
Do you think that could be the concert where Russell Brand told her that she needs to fall
over?
He wants a divorce from her minutes before she went on stage?
I think that this is probably a different one, okay, because she was really common
collected during that. Did her boobs flop out? Apparently the Mk the reason they
targeted her for Mk Ultra is because of the size of her boobs. Really flop like
a beagle's ear. Apparently they put electrodes on them to scan on them. Yeah,
they're doing the science like a like a blood hound, yeah, like the lips of a
blood hound, yeah, because when I think of boobs, I think
think of a dog's lips,
sides of boobs.
Summoning a dark force is the worst thing you could ever do and who's that
very twelve twenty twenty three. That is the devil. He's not the devil.
That's a new story from January twelve twenty twenty three strange little
being
live during a soccer match January twelve, twenty twenty three. Holy
fucking shit. This is all happening in January. Guys, open your eyes. That's a
little stick man. That's a strange little be. That's an XK CD character that
escaped and started doing science on a soccer field. He has a pointed hat.
Yeah, that could be a gnome. Strange case. Ancient pyramids around the world
suddenly beaming energy to the sky. January 12,
23. It was all the ancient pyramids. They made some experiments proving astral
the projection is actually real January twelve twenty twenty three a
teleported person caught on video is causing an accident in China still
January twelve twenty twenty three a strange fish with human face was
filmed by a tour. I do remember that China me January twelve twenty twenty
three millions of giants will awaken on earth January twelve twenty twenty
three. So these are some of the stories that are going on on the ancient
seven point six meters January twelve twenty twenty three and twenty foot
giant man. That's really scary. Keanu Reeves said the earth is a prison
planet from which we can never escape. Holy January twelve twenty twenty three.
All right, but what was the mainstream media reporting on January twelve?
Because this all happened January twelve twenty twenty three, but I'm willing to
bet you remember only one or two of those things. Okay, tell me what was what
they were covering it up with. What massive stories were being used to
eclipsed the actual news, because you need you need to be reading these
alternative news sites to see what's really going on instead of this bullshit
smoke screens that are probably made up stories. You know what I call you see
and then what crap news network kind of bullshit was the communist news network
and you want to be communism. What were they sending? You want to see what
they're reporting on January twelve, twenty, twenty three, January twelve,
twenty, twenty three, Rick and Morty, co creator, Justin Roiland, faces domestic
violence charges. Rick and Morty co creator, Justin Roiland, facing
domestic violence charges, January 12, 2023. Dog starts house fire while eating
cookies off kitchen counter video shows, January 12, 2023. NBC News, Hollywood
Reporter, New York Post, Los Angeles Times, Rick and Morty co creator, Justin
Roiland, facing felony. The truth is out there, y'all.
Oh, wow, wow, wow. You have really gotten to the bottom of this story, that they
tried to take our dog out because just because he was it started a fire in the
kitchen. He makes TV shows about aliens well that guy too, but yeah, I was
mostly talking about the cookie dog,
but dude solar opposites. I mean this is
this is gospel whatever's on that show. I haven't watched it, but it's all true
guys. It is all true and look at the guys like this. I covered up the
neighborhood to you yeah guys stay curious. Oh yeah, stay dangerous and
don't get murder, don't get murdered for what you believe guys. This is another
episode of podcast about this next Monday. Me and Patrick are going to be
hosting funny moms at come on everybody in Brooklyn come through. We'll post a
ticket link soon. Somebody will be there. Somebody might be doing that and
somebody might be doing minutes of some of the best five to seven minutes that
you've seen in a very long time, and he might be a third person at this table
besides the other two names, I already said maybe maybe two people at this
table do stand up already, but there's one guy that you have maybe one guy did
stand up before either of the other two at this table and then quit because it
was too awesome. He was too good guys and one of these, but maybe he's making a
triumphant maybe he's making a huge
deal. Just have to come. What day is the shareholder meeting this month
and it will check. Okay, he'll check in the meantime,
Two weeks from now, the battle of the century.
Oh yes.
Two combatants, you've been waiting to see them clash.
They will.
Right here on YouTube.com/
We can't spoil what it is.
We don't even want to touch it.
We should do that episode.
Get fucking hyped.
We should do that episode live, dude.
Yes.
That's not a bad idea.
Because it will blow people.
People won't even believe it if we just pre-record it.
Yeah.
So that's coming and you're going to be seeing a lot of teaser videos and posters for that
and you're going to be getting very hyped up and excited.
yard. Yep, and two months from now, I will be in the great city of Chicago
opening for a girl God
and that's
subscribe on Patreon to the to the to the executive producer tier. If you
would like to be part of the shareholder meetings, which are so fun, they're fun
as a motherfucker.
Jeopardy this Friday, oh and Jeopardy on Friday on the twitch channel.
Time
is that number and keep your eyes on the skies. Folks, what time is that at?
We'll figure it out some point and also keep your eyes in disguise with the
sun. Nobody sees them. All right, bye bye
shit guys. There is nobody worse than lawyers. Lawyers and blondes are at the
very, very bottom of my pyramid. Yep. He's not really blonde. He's got like a
dirty blonde. I'm not blonde at all. You guys only think I'm blonde because I
I think of you as a beautiful blonde.
I think of you as a beautiful blonde with big breasts.
My eyebrow was turning blonde.
That you should go to the doctor for.
That's vitiligo. You got it late in life.
Here's my problem with lawyers.
That's vitiligo, man.
You might actually have late in life vitiligo.
What happens when you're...
Vidaligo you might have.
- Yeah, adult onset.
- I googled blondness and eyebrow and there's no results.
- I'm telling you.
- It says you're a Frank Ocean.
- Yeah.
- I'm not gonna get blonde splotches on my skin?
- You could.
- I don't wanna be blonde skinned.
- Yeah.
- You have blonde, Vidaligo would not show up on your body.
- Not yours.
- You have whiteness.
- You, I don't think you have Vidaligo at all.
Now that I'm thinking about it.
- The thing with lawyers, okay,
is that they have invented--
- Have you been dealing with one lately?
What's going on?
know
It's very upsetting. It is very crazy.
But here's a lobster roll.
And it was expensive, I bet. Market price.
Yeah, I bet it was close to $24.
My mom's treat.
Whoa. Apparently.
Mother's treat.
Mother's treat. Mother's treat.
Wow.
Oh my God.
Lobster roll, mother's treat.
Mother-ter-eet-za.
Okay.
Mother treats.
Mother is treats ya.
Mother treats ya. Poorly.
Treats ya.
Mother treats ya. That was easy.
Mother treats a kid poorly, does not buy him any snacks.
*outro*