Send me cold open and thumbnail plie.
[MUSIC]
Karen's been following me around the store.
I wasn't.
This Karen's been following me around the damn store.
Get the fuck out of my way, Karen.
Get out of here.
Quit hiding, Karen.
Hey, what's up, Podcast About List fans?
probably haven't heard from me in a minute or maybe you have because we
backlogged some episodes but yeah I'm on vacation but I'm pretty excited to
announce something brand new first time we've ever done this official fan meetup
so if you want to meet and greet and say hi to all of us just meet us tomorrow
the day after this episode comes out at 8 p.m. and we will be here at the
the wastewater pumping station in Shannon Bridge, Ireland in Offaly County.
This was actually just fairly recently inspected, electrically inspected on July 11th, so everything's
above board there.
But just make sure that you're authorized before you show up to the meetup.
And we'll be signing anything you bring.
*Tesco*
Well, I'm off to Tesco.
Peep the ending, new ending!
Hey, what's up?
You signing anything you bring?
*Footsteps*
Well, I'm off to Tesco.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
- Okay.
- Clay, clay, clay, clay.
- Clay.
- Clay upon my big glass bed.
(humming)
- Is this you?
- Whoa.
- Ooh.
- Do you like that?
- I didn't think that that sound effect
would be the one that came out.
- I'm not so good at this.
It's only my third time ever doing this.
Mommy's gone again.
Mommy's gone, but we got a new mommy.
Mommy. Mm hmm.
Mr. Clay, how are you, buddy?
I'm good, man. How are you?
I mean, you know, there is already a lot of glaring
technical issues with this episode.
When Cameron fucking leaves, the thing falls apart.
Yeah. Yeah.
Last week we do our most ambitious, highest production thing we've ever done.
This week we don't have a list.
Jubio, can you pull up the the photo I sent you of our current camera?
Real quick, I just want to, I want the, I'll show it into the GoPro.
Basically he duct taped a thing.
Yeah, it actually looks really sick.
This is the, this is our current camera setup right here.
This, that is a, what are you doing with your hat?
My hat's falling off because I can't wear the fucking headphones over it, man. Chill on me.
One second, god damn it.
Well, that's our current, this is a JVC Iverio, which comes with a proprietary dock. Also,
this lens is for a separate Hi8 camcorder. What are you?
I want to wear my hat, man! I got it while I was on vacation and I want to wear it, but
it falls off.
Why would you pick that hat?
Because it was cool and it was only $45. I got it because I thought, I was like really
hungover and I thought that this was made of snake skin. But it's a spray painted wicker
hat that they put a belt on. So it's really not a very... whatever. I give up on it. Fuck
it. How was Texas?
Well, the first show was fun.
The first show that you said was bad ended up being good.
The first shows were good. I just blew through my material too quick.
I love that.
Yeah.
Don't you love doing stand up now?
Oh, I love it.
Isn't it fucking amazing? Clay, do you love doing stand up?
It's the most fun in the world.
You have the most amazing stand up
pre ritual where you...
What do you do?
I've seen him drink like six beers before.
Six beers?
Yeah, I drink like six beers before I go on stage.
Yeah, it's incredible.
Because I'm nervous.
You get nervous when you drink beer?
I get so anxious.
I have like three beers and I'm like, all right, this is going to be good.
And then I like don't go up for a while.
And I like try to keep the same level.
And then I always go too far.
Dude, I can't have any beer before I go on stage.
Me neither.
I forget all my jokes.
I mean, I have one.
I fucked up one of my jokes at your show two weeks ago.
I fucked up one of my jokes so bad because I had one beer.
I had one beer and I just blew the punch line at the very beginning.
Yeah.
It's pretty genius.
This weekend, I just didn't like, just burned through all my material.
Started, I was just like, "Ah, shit, you guys.
I'm bad."
And then I was like, "What if I just sing for you?"
You sang?
I sang.
What did you sing?
I sang Superstar by the Carpenters.
How does that one go?
Long ago and oh so far away.
That was what I was supposed to sing Cameron for his birthday but then decided Careless
Whisperer would be better.
People paid for this show.
People paid for the show.
You promoted it for about a month, got a custom poster made for it.
And then I, well it was the first set that I did.
I had just gotten off the plane.
Oh, well if you just got off the plane you're going to be in the airport.
I was in the airport.
Custom poster made for it.
And then I, well, it was the first set that I did. I'd just gotten off the plane.
Oh, well, if you just got off the plane, you're going to be bad.
You're going to be bad every time.
Yeah, it was kind of fucked up.
What was sick, though, is we, so Dan and I get in the Uber and
That is sick.
Well, the lady, we're just like, oh, we're just doing a couple of shows.
We're staying at this hotel.
And she's like, oh, that's so funny.
that's the first place I ever got a D U I really dude. There's something
there's something about the people who take you from when you're going on the
road from the plane to the hotel who are always crazy. We had in Pittsburgh. A
lady was like
with it. We got in and she was like, we has ever been to Pittsburgh before five
minutes and she literally said George Floyd is a coward.
I swear to God, I swear to God.
Okay, this is where drama's over here. It was fucking crazy, dude.
Pullover will get out of this out of the way. I mean, just like you give them one
thing, right? I think we said, I think what we, what got her to start going
off was we were like,
she was like, "Oh yeah, Pittsburgh's great, used to be better." And we were
like, "Oh yeah, every city used to be better," said something like that. And
then she was like, she told us a story about a lady during the BLM protests
who, she was like, "These sick people." There was a woman who was
eating at a restaurant, eating outside, eating a steak, and one of the
protesters grabbed her steak and threw it on the ground.
We were like, "Okay.
All right." Oh, I can't believe that. I mean, we were just like, "Oh,
you're kidding me." Yeah, yeah. And she went to jail, she went to prison.
Oh, thank God. Yeah.
That's like the best thing to, like you just, like when someone says some crazy
shit at you, just like goad them into telling you more, just 'cause it's like
So I want to see how you get to this conclusion.
The other day I was out skating and I had this Oprah Winfrey show t-shirt and one of
this dude's friends was like, "Oh, that shirt's sick."
And then the other dude went, "No, Oprah's not valid anymore.
She has a school in Africa where she's selling kids like Jeffrey Epstein."
Is that true?
I don't know.
He told me.
You should have at least opened your mind a little bit.
He told me everything.
I just was like, "No shit.
throw this away. And I just let him just like keep talking about it. I like
barely skated because I just wanted to talk more about it. He was like, yeah,
Oprah's worked, or Oprah worked with Epstein, Oprah was on the flight loans.
I feel like I'm so used to hearing that shit at like a bar or something, if I'm
like with a bunch of people and then a crazy guy starts talking to us. That
happened to me and my dad while I was on vacation. My dad was like, "You wanna
get a beer?" We usually, every time I go out there, we get a beer for a couple
hours and catch up. And we sat down and we were there for about ten minutes and this like
drunk guy walked up to us and he was like eating calamari.
Nice.
And he was like, "Hey, I'm Kenny." We were like, "Oh, what's up, Kenny?" And then he
just started telling us these stories. If they weren't good, we would have asked him
to leave, but he told us this one story about how he got ran out of the last town that he
lived in. He lived in Los Osos in California.
He's a cowboy.
He's a new age cowboy of sorts. He was like, "Yeah, man, I went on that website next
the door, right? And there was this lady who was fucking complaining. She was
like, 'Who's feeding all these crows peanuts? The peanut-, the crows are, the
crows are dropping peanuts in my backyard, and then my kid, my kid's allergic to
peanuts, so he's coming and eating them.' And I replied and I said, 'Lady, I
wouldn't be so worried about the guy selling the, or giving the crows the
peanuts. I'd be more worried that my kid is eating food off the floor.'
and apparently he got like it's a really small town yeah and apparently people
were like egg his house
it's like so me and my dad talked to my dad for about ten minutes the entire
trip yeah, because this guy is a cooler man. I just liked it more than my dad.
My boss is kind of crazy in a way like he'll come come into the restaurant part
of where I work and I'll just be like did you know that Jim Morrison's dad
worked for the CIA and I'm just like please tell me yeah, give me more when
your boss is you can't say it. You can't be like, I don't care right now.
Well, also I like love it. Like I want him to take time out of my day to tell me
about Jim Morrison being like a CIA son. And I work with Tommy.
Yeah.
Tommy has no time for it.
He's just like, oh cool.
But he likes talking to Tommy so much more than me.
Yeah.
And I'm just like, fuck dude, all I want to do is hear this.
Yeah, you get stuck with the conversation. Yeah. Well, I mean, you want it.
Yeah.
I want it. I like getting stuck with it.
It also kind of means you don't have to work, right?
Yeah.
Because they're more worried about you listening to them than you even working.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's actually a pretty good situation to be in.
It's the best.
Oh yeah, that's like the perfect situation to be in.
Yeah, I used to have this boss, I've talked about him before, but I used to work at a gym
and I had this boss who used to be like a UFC fighter, not a UFC, just an MMA fighter.
Yeah.
And he just had so many concussions, he would like drool all the time.
He would do the same shit where he would come in and he would like tell me that something
about Bill Clinton.
And I would just be like, "Oh, really?"
Because I didn't have to fold towels for a couple minutes.
It was pretty nice.
Dude, I fucking whiffed it.
I was supposed to...
I got an interview at that gym, I remember.
Oh, yeah, you did.
Yeah.
And you're the only...
The guy...
I was like, "Hey, my buddy needs a job."
And he was like, "Oh, dude."
He'll come in, he'll interview, it'll be nothing.
when I did the interview, they asked me my name, my phone number, and then they were
like, "You're hired." But he somehow fucked it up.
Yeah, I don't know how I fucked it up. I was just...
Did you put your phone number in the name area?
I literally, I think I just told the guy, "I just need money, man."
That is so bad to say.
Straight up was like, "Look, I don't really..." Basically, every single time I did job interviews
back then in college, I would always just like,
I'm going to be completely honest with you. I'm in college. I need money.
Why would you say that to somebody? I don't know. Remember I were interviewed.
I interviewed for an escape room. Oh yeah. And you lost the escape room.
Yeah. I lost the escape room. It was South park's themed too.
And he had a, he had an endorsement from like the only other guy who worked there.
The clue master. Yeah. The clue master himself.
I had an endorsement from him and the lady was like, or person, I don't know their thing,
but they were like, "That is the worst interview I've ever had in my whole career."
I mean, to be fair, you do not strike me as a man who could give clues all that well.
No, no, not at all.
I think my ADHD brain couldn't even fucking...
Not my ADHD brain.
I would get distracted by a different clue.
Yeah, you would give them I would give them a clue for the next clue.
I would just be sitting there like, OK, but it's going to it's going to lead
into the next one.
This clue is going to lead you to the next.
Have you ever done an escape room?
Yeah. Oh, yeah. They're fun.
Yeah, they are fucking.
I am sick of pretending they're not so much fun.
Did I? We should do one.
I would do one. Let's go.
Let's go after this.
I love escape.
That is so I've never I've never won a single
single one, I've probably done five. I always do the easiest room and I fail.
I've won once. I've done it twice. I'm one and one and one and one.
Yeah, you're bad in 500. That's actually pretty good. Yeah, that's not bad.
I did one with my friend's family and it was hard. It was not because it was like six people
being like, we're the smartest people in the world.
Yeah, that's always how it is, man.
We were like, "Fuck, we're so stupid."
But the first time was just like, I went and did a bunch of shit, and then I came back to
my group and they were like, "We're done with our shit."
And I'm like, "I'm done with my shit.
Are we done?"
And then...
Was it one...
I always want it to be lock picking, but it's a lot more math and paper.
Yeah, or magnets.
There's a lot of magnets.
Yeah, the magnets.
I don't like all that, man.
I want to do a safe cracking kind of thing.
Yeah, but that's like...
Not everyone knows how to fucking pick locks is the problem.
I don't know.
I want to try. I've never even tried.
I think we should do a heist.
A heist is a very good...
Or a heist escape room?
Yeah. That'd be sick.
Where they just kind of just...
Oh, so you're going in and you have like a mission.
Yeah, that'd be kind of sweet.
I want a full...
Oh, well, hmm.
I watched the escape room
Tournament of Champions movie.
What is that?
They made a movie. Have you seen the escape room movies?
Basically saw, but they made a movie where they take all of the best escape
rumors and they put them in one escape room. Interesting. Yeah, it's pretty
interesting. I watched a lot of movies this week. I watched talk to me. Did you
see that? No. The Australian horror movie. Didn't see that one. Is that the
one where they touch the hand? They touch the hand. I've been seeing that
in YouTube. They go, "Narr! Don't kill me! Narr! Don't touch me! I want to
live!" Or however they talk. Yeah. But it was kind of interesting hearing a
different accent in a horror movie. You don't hear that too often.
Yeah, the Australians don't really get scared.
No.
They got all those spiders.
Yeah, they have nothing to be afraid of.
Yeah.
Is that true? The spiders and shit? I thought that was fake.
No, that's real.
The spiders that live on the wall or go there at least?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I think they scare the piss out of me.
Yeah.
If I saw a spider that big, I'd kill myself.
But Australia needs to realize that we don't have big spiders here, but we do have
Bloods and Crips, MS-13, mass shootings.
Yeah.
They don't have any of these problems over in Australia.
They do, but it's all like...
Oh, dude.
It's all the...
It's Rangas versus Bogans.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the thing, sometimes there's a Bogan Ranga.
And that's okay.
Yeah.
What the hell was that?
What the fuck?
Your phone is talking to you.
Did you?
Your phone's talking back.
You're supposed to talk into that.
Did you accidentally call someone?
Yeah, I accidentally called my boy, Jack.
[laughing]
Wow.
This is already a legendary podcast appearance from Clay.
How the hell did that happen? Jack's a cool guy. Can I plug my friend Jack Barth? He's
cool. Check him out.
Jack Barth?
I think I did a show with him.
I don't think I know him.
He's cool. He wears glasses.
I think I did that fucking Nook show with him. I think we were all on that one.
Not all of us.
Yeah, well me and Clay were.
Well, I wasn't invited, but whatever.
I got into town last night late and I had a bad experience with a foreign traveler.
I had to change out a tire on my car, like right when I got back, and I had my dog with
me.
And so I was sitting there just fucking struggling.
It sucks so much pretending to be a grown man.
You're like sitting there doing the nuts and all this shit.
And then I hear a guy go like, "Excuse me?"
and I turn around and it's this fucking just annoying looking like Eastern European guy
and he's like staring at my dog. And my dog is this big.
Your dog is way bigger.
He's not big.
He's really long.
He's under 40 pounds.
He's really long though.
Your dog looks like the Night Stalker from New Vegas.
No, he doesn't look like that.
Yes, he does.
He's fine, but he just looks like a fucking German Shepherd.
He has the same shape and body as the Night Stalker from New Vegas.
it doesn't look like that. He doesn't look he does look like that actually
exactly like that okay all right. So pretend that he
teacup
poodle or something okay, but anyway the guy the guy's like looking at my dog and
I'm like and the dog is like halfway on the sidewalk and I have him on a leash.
He can't get any further, and so I say that I'm like walk around. You can walk
around the dog and he looks at me and he looked so sad. He goes
I scared
I scared. He said I scared twice and then I had to take my dog into the middle of
the street. So this guy could go back go past me on the sidewalk like my dog is a
bridge troll. Oh my God, and it really put me in the worst mood man. The rest of
the night I was like I scared. I
fuck you man. It's a dog yeah. Was he older? No, he's like thirty years old.
And he was, I scared about a dog.
Well yeah, he probably got, what you said he's like Eastern European?
He's something.
Yeah.
It's none of my business what he is.
He's a coward.
What is the most cowardly, what is the most cowardly possible nation?
I don't know what goes on in Eastern Europe.
Maybe they have like a 50 foot dog there that looks just like Phil.
It's possible they have some kind of Cerberus.
Yeah.
A Cerberus might be a real thing over there.
They could have seen him as a Cerberus podling or something.
I really didn't like it though.
It really pissed me off.
Yeah.
I was cussing the whole time to myself, but hoping that he would hear it.
Fucking fuck you.
Fucking dude.
I scared.
Piss me off, man.
Did you do anything fun in Texas?
Um, no, not really.
No?
I don't.
Dude, they're like, the motto is keep Austin weird, but guess what?
You guys are weird in a different way.
They're weird in kind of a touchy way.
It seems like it was a really cool city like five years ago.
Uh-huh.
You know?
Like, I mean, we did a show there and it was like fun.
I mean, we went to, but we, I mean, we hung out with...
We were there for like 24 hours.
Yeah, we were there for 24 hours.
I was there for two days.
I was like, oh, maybe I...
But you got to go to the Mecca, man.
I did.
I went to the mothership.
I went out...
You went to the comedy mothership.
I stood outside of it.
How was it?
Oh, you know what?
I, we, we went there.
We just stood out in front of it.
We didn't go in.
Wow.
But we...
But we were going to the Museum of the Weird.
Wow.
And I saw a mummy.
You saw a mummy.
A real one?
Yep.
I wish that I had more things to say about this trip.
I mean, I just kind of flopped a lot.
Yeah.
I flopped and did great.
I just was like,
I don't like, oh.
I love those weekends.
That was my last weekend in Raleigh, dude.
You flopped in your hometown?
I've done stand up in North Carolina maybe like 15 times and bombed every single time.
I had fun doing stand up in Raleigh.
Really?
Yeah, I did okay for the first half of my stay.
Did you do the club there?
No, I did Neptune.
Oh, okay.
I think I get in my head about being in my hometown, man.
Yeah, I suck at Minnesota.
I'm not good enough for these people.
There's something about it, man.
I kind of stink there.
Yeah, I mean, I thought that I would be like that when I went back to Boston.
But it was...
But you crushed.
I did two nights.
The last night that I was there, I skated all day before.
I was really tired and just a bummer of a set.
My mom and dad were there.
Oh, yeah.
I think that's the first time my dad's ever seen me do stand up.
I went to...
Before this, last time I was in North Carolina, the time before I did stand up in North Carolina,
it was me and Gus driving back from L.A. and my buddy organized like a music show where
me and him were going to do stand up at the beginning of it, but nobody came. It was my
brother, his girlfriend, and my buddy Chad in the audience. And I was like...
Nobody came for the show, the music stuff after?
I really know. But I just did my set and I was like, that wasn't even, that wasn't
even stand up. I was just talking to people I know. But then Gus went up and
Gus destroyed it.
My brother was like, "Ah!" Losing his mind. It was like the funniest scene I've
ever seen. It made me so mad, dude.
Yeah. Oh, man. That's how it is, dude. It's the worst job in the world. I know.
We have a worse job than maybe like a police officer. I would rather be working
one of the iPhone mines where you are doing World War Z and climbing over people.
Yeah, because it's like you have to sell yourself to people with stand up. You have to be like,
no, trust me, like I'm like I'm not I'm bombing right now because I'm having a bad day. It's
not because I'm it's not because I completely suck at this and I suck as a person. It's
like, please help. Please trust me. Yeah, I'm a I'm a I'm a good guy. Yeah. You beckoning
Yeah, you'd have to get them with you and then you have to hold on to that.
Where it's just kind of like, I don't know, being in the mine sounds nice.
Oh man.
Probably sounds like dirty.
I'm born in the wrong, not just generation, the wrong like eon I think.
Yeah.
I should have been, I would have been an amazing like first man type thing.
I would have been an amazing peasant dude.
You would have been, you have a peasant's face.
Oh dude, I would have been so good at eating just like a whole quail.
Like taking a quail by the two bones at the end and just going like...
You would have been an amazing surf.
Oh dude.
Oh my god, if only.
I could plow a fucking field.
I was born with like when they started putting chemicals in the water to make people not
good at concentration and shit.
So now I have to look at my phone all the time.
Yeah.
You can't spend your days eating cheese.
Yeah, eating like mold.
Milk and a cow or whatever.
It does suck. As I get older, I'm starting to enjoy nature less and I like looking at
my phone and my computer.
Oh yeah.
More, I thought it would be as I get older, I like these things kind of in the inverse.
But it turns out I was in California on the coast, most beautiful thing I've ever seen,
and I was like, "This sucks so bad. This is so fucking gay. I hate this."
Yeah. I get like that, dude. Like yeah, when we went to the Grand Canyon.
Oh yeah, we went to the Grand Canyon. Me, Cameron, and Pierce are like bawling, crying,
and Patrick is playing Candy Crush. I went, I left the group, I was like walking up and down,
I stood, I think I sat on a cliff. He was like, we were like, oh, Patrick's doing his own thing.
And then what did you, came back and you had news, you saw a guy with, what, a guy with one arm?
I saw, no, I just saw like, I just saw like so many, you know what, no, I was actually genuinely
very happy because I saw old people.
I saw like six different old people
taking iPad selfies.
And I was like this.
That's like like I was like,
oh, like I'm watching like these
people have like these people that
don't know how to use like a fucking
regular phone.
Yeah. Holding up this big thing
so they can go
with like a big
ass iPad so they can take selfies.
They look like laptops.
I thought it was adorable. It was
like, yeah, it was like an old
person holding up their laptop
to take a picture of themselves at the fucking Grand Canyon.
I sat next to an old lady on the flight back. She was very, very nice. Her name's Emily.
And I ended up helping her out. But the reason I helped her out was that she opened up Facebook
and in the Facebook search bar searched, "Can you take the Q train to the Upper East Side?"
I was like, "Let me help you out, sweetheart."
She's Googling stuff on Facebook. That's what they want now.
They do.
Just make it one thing, man. I'm sick of all these different websites. Give me one single
thing. One big website where I can do basically all that shit. And I'll be good man. I'll
be honest I think they're working on it. Yeah that's what X.com is supposed to be. Oh yeah
that all happened while I was away. Yeah. And buddy that was some crazy shit man. Wait
that's so funny that X.com is also a video game that's all about like strategy. Yeah
true. And aliens as well. Yeah. Yeah some big news came out while I was gone. Aliens
are completely real and Twitter basically changed its entire name. What the hell's wrong with
this world? The world is going to hell in a handbasket. I mean it's seriously fucking
crazy. Makes me upset. I got really really scared while I was out in nature that I was
scared that aliens were going to turn off the sun. I'm not kidding, I told my uncle
that and he was like, "Are you kidding?" and I said, "No, I'm actually really scared about
that right now. I don't know man. I don't know what they're capable of. You don't know either.
They can make a pill that flies. I mean if that's the only thing that they're doing,
I really don't give a shit. Turning off the sun would be bad news bro. Yeah that would
be so bad. It would get cold as fuck. I like it though. We wouldn't know for a while though,
like 8 years. That the sun was off? Yeah because the speed of light is so... Would it be that
long? Yeah. Eight years really? Or maybe eight minutes. I think it's eight minutes. I think
eight years would be eight light years away. I do not think the sun is that far away. No,
it's pretty close. Wait, one year is one light? I never understood light years. Light year
is how fast it takes, or how long it takes, how far light can travel in a year. How far
the sun travels in a year. How far light from the sun travels. Light from anything. A light
goes the same speed no matter what it is.
See, I took two years of science in high school because that was all that was required of
me.
You need to start watching Vsauce, Kerzagazakt, and Veritasium on YouTube.
And that's basically all the science education you need.
I put all my skill points into other crap like video production, high school video production,
learning how to operate cameras.
You are like a maxed out sliders on one thing kind of character.
And everything else is at 8.
Is that medium?
Yeah.
Well, medium is a little...
Is in the middle?
It's a little high.
No, I would say the low end.
Probably.
If it's going by stat points, I'm probably...
You're like a rogue.
Yeah, maybe like an Alyssa Steamer, Jamie Thomas.
Me, I'm like a main.
I'm like anybody's first account.
They get okay at everything.
You know, good at a couple things but never really, really good.
Yeah, I'm definitely good at drinking a couple beers.
Yeah, you have that maxed out.
Using my computer.
Also maxed out.
Using my phone.
That one is completely, that one's off the scale.
Off the scale.
That one is like when you, like when Gandhi accidentally becomes like Hitler in Civilization.
Oh yeah.
When Gandhi, like the nuclear war thing.
You mean they accidentally put, they meant to put zero but they put a hundred.
Yeah, where the computer math redid it so it went up to 255.
Yeah, that's, you know, Y2K kind of thing.
That's what happened to me with my phone.
Clay, what are you, do you have a secret skill?
Uh...
Dancing.
Yeah, dancing is kind of the one.
Oh my god, I forgot that you're an amazing dancer.
Yeah, yeah.
Did you do ballet?
Yeah, I did ballet and tap and jazz.
Wow.
I did like everything.
I have like a video on one of the dance contest websites because I made it into the Hall of
Fame with my buddy.
You made it into the Hall of Fame?
Yeah, we scored so high in our competition.
You're a Hall of Famer?
What can we search to find this video right now?
It's called, I think it's like Hall of Fame Dance Competition.
Hall of Fame Dance Competition.
Clay Park, should we search that?
No, it won't be my name.
It'll be a...
What year?
What was the crew you were running with?
Fuck, dude. I think it was like 2012 or 2013.
2012 or 2013.
Hall of Fame Dance Competition.
This is it? Hall of Fame Dance Challenge?
And then it'll be a...
Yeah, you gotta scroll down and there's a bunch of dates.
It's gonna be the Minneapolis one.
Okay. Or the... yeah.
Oh, wow.
Is this you? And then if you scroll down a little bit more...
It's me, Snitches.
That's me and my buddy.
Wait, we have to see this right now.
Please tell me this is going to work.
Do you have to buy this?
I'm in the red.
The red shoes?
Yeah.
That's you?
Oh my god.
Wait, hip hop? Whoa!
What the hell is going on, man?
Whoa!
[Laughter]
Dude, that's incredible.
Did you guys trade hats?
Oh my God, wait, that was the hat pass.
Yeah, we were stealing our...
You just passed your hat?
Yeah, we were stealing hats all the time.
Dude, this is incredible.
Do you do a backflip?
No.
I used to be able to go around with one hand on the ground, though.
They traded the hat back.
That is insane. What was your closer? What was your ender?
My ender? I think it's just, I think he jumps over me.
Oh!
Yeah. And then, yeah, dude, I don't remember. This is 2012.
You lived another life.
I know.
Yeah, I did.
That is incredible, man.
Was this a promising career for young Klay?
No, I don't think so. I liked music a lot.
Yeah, you got music out, right? Yeah, just under your name.
Yeah, I think so. I think, yeah.
Oh my god, man. I've dabbled in a lot of
performance stuff. So you have performance maximum
slider on performance? I wouldn't put it max, but I think it's pretty...
That looked pretty maximum to me. That was fucking amazing.
You filled up your special meter. And that kid is definitely dead now, yeah?
No, he's actually a football player.
He's way taller than I am now.
I think he plays in college, actually.
He's still in college?
He's a little younger than you.
Yeah, he was like two years younger than I was.
I mean, I'm not a Hall of Fame anything.
I'm going to be real with you.
I got in a film festival.
You got in a film festival?
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, that's the one high school credit I got.
I didn't do anything.
I did nothing for eight years.
I think I spent a lot of time doing stuff when I was young and now I'm old.
I just want to play 2K and then be funny on stage.
I think this was probably the same year that I started doing stand-up as a kid.
Really?
Yeah.
And I gotta say, man, I was much worse at stand-up than you were at dance.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, it was pretty... I mean, this speaks more to how good you were, I would say.
I know.
It was pretty impressive.
When they gave us the award, we got to do a little speech.
What'd you say?
I thanked my mom, God, my grandpa, Papa John's.
There was like a pancake place around the corner
that we went for breakfast.
- You thanked them?
- That was like the best food.
- Powered you up?
- I just kept going until they took the mic away from me.
- You got played off in your Hall of Fame speech.
You can't play up a Hall of Famer, man.
What the fuck?
That's fucked up.
- Yeah, I was like 13 and I could like see my mom
the audience just like crying laughing. I thought it was so funny.
(laughter)
Jesus Christ, man.
That's so sick.
But ballet, I feel like ballet was probably more your bag, huh?
Yeah, that was more fun. I think, like once I got into it, I got into it in like high school.
What was your favorite?
You can do the point, the thing.
No, no, no.
Everybody asks me about that.
Men don't do point usually.
Exactly.
other male dancers that I danced with in ballet asked our teacher that one time
and our teacher was like no. No you don't get the box shoes. That's only if you're
gay. You have to be very gay and very skinny to do that. What was your favorite
position? Honestly my favorite position is second. That one is fire. Wide stance. Yeah with the open
I don't know anything about ballet at all.
Yeah, you wouldn't.
Yeah, I don't keep up with that.
Mostly back then, when I was 2012, I kept up with a lot of skateboarding and stuff.
I thought that I was maybe going to become like a shop hero or something, get free boards
from the shop, and then it turns out I wasn't good at skating at all.
When I was 13, I think I was pretty sure I was going to be a famous director at that
point.
I'm going to make a sequel to every Christopher Nolan movie, that type of thing.
That would be cool.
I decided not to do it. I decided to go a different route.
Did you see this guy? There's this dude, this TikToker, he's got like a million views,
something like that. He's got a pretty big TikTok account. He made this video where he's like,
"I'm going to scab the writer's strike."
What?
He makes this video where he's like saying he's going to scab the sag strike and the
writer's strike.
By doing what?
Because some production company hit him up and then he's like, "Now that all these
writers and actors are striking, this is my moment."
It's a golden opportunity for people not in the field.
And then the first, he makes this video, it's him in a Tommy Boy t-shirt and he says, he's
He's like maybe a couple years older than us too, which is like insane. He says, "I'm currently
writing a movie. It's called Tommy's Boy." Tommy's Boy?
And it's a direct sequel to Tommy Boy. I'm writing roles for all of Chris Farley's brothers
and hopefully, if Lord willing, David Spade will be in this as well.
Wow. Wow.
And it's supposed to be about him being, he's like, "My character's going to be named Chris
for obvious reasons.
Wait, what is it?
It's a sequel.
Is Tommy boy, Tommy boy,
dead in the movie's boy.
He grew up without a dad because
Tommy died.
That's crazy.
Oh, wait, Tommy's boy, Tommy,
that's his fucking son.
The story of Tommy.
So it's like son of the mask.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
He's going to scab
like the strike and everything. Because this movie is getting picked up. Because this movie has to
get picked up because he said his agent knows the director of Tommy Boy. Wow. So I don't know.
But it could happen. Honestly, I want this to get made and then like right when like the strike ends,
like, oh shit, it's like shut down or something. No, no, no. We want to be at the premiere of this
movie, Patrick. I don't get this confused. I would scab to be in Tommy's Boy. I want to be
be in this movie badly.
I want to be in it so badly.
This dude's got like millions of
fucking views and shit and all the
videos are just him like with like
like TikTok audios and just going
like.
And that's and he's like, I'm
writing, I'm the next Grits
partner.
Yeah, he's awesome for
that.
Dude, there's a fucking video
of him talking about the strike
and he's like,
like.
This this project, he's probably
working on the project that they probably hit him up with is probably nonunion.
And it's probably not like a big production company that's like currently being
like struck and everything.
But like he immediately goes in on the writer's strike and it's like, you're all
fucking cowards.
We're not working right now.
And he says this like he's on this he's going on this rant and
like in the middle of his rant, he's like.
And it's really telling that the Screen
Actors Guild calls people scabs who
aren't in the union.
Wow. That's a lot about their
character. Wow.
It's like, dude,
you're just like burning
every fucking bridge you can
with sag. That is amazing.
That is incredible.
Tommy's boy is going to be tough.
Oh, yeah. To get figured out.
I mean, it's going to be.
Logistically, it's a nightmare.
This shit is already certified for
SBS. Oh, yeah.
It's going to be like, like how
fucking every single like old
like indie movie from like 2012 had like a million production companies on it.
Like 12 different fucking logos before the movie starts.
Yeah. One of those.
Yeah.
That family guy cutaway is so goddamn funny when he's sitting in the theater and
it starts with all the production companies. He's like, Ooh,
he like doesn't know what movie he's seeing.
So he's just assuming he starts the movie.
I've been, um, I,
I have been watching a lot of family guy clips recently, man. Family guy,
It's the best. It's so funny.
Yeah. I can't believe that I ever
was like one of the people who was
like, "Family Guy." It sucks.
Yeah. I thought I was like, "Family
Guy and Vine ruined
TV comedy." Oh, yeah.
It's fun. It's so funny.
Yeah. It's I like watched
the I watched a YouTube essay
where this guy was like talking about
South Park versus Family Guy.
What did he say? Oh, he detailed the
feud? Yeah. He detailed the feud.
And then he also like broke it down
and he was like, "Family Guy can
still be funny.
It's just not as funny as South Park because it doesn't follow the narrative.
The jokes can just be on their own.
I would probably rather watch a current season Family Guy episode than a current season South
Park episode.
Yeah, for sure.
I probably would.
I like South Park.
I haven't watched in a couple of years.
I haven't watched the new ones.
They're pretty solid.
I played Stick of Truth and then got back into watching it.
That game is amazing.
That game rules.
That game is so, so good.
Fractured But Whole is not good.
I didn't play that one.
It's not good?
- It's not good?
- It's, yeah, I didn't like it as much.
I didn't even finish it, I didn't like it that much.
- Damn.
- They need to make more games.
- Well, that's Obsidian, Obsidian made that game.
- Yeah, this was like a good RPG.
- People that made New Vegas, yeah.
- They need to make more games that just look exactly
like the show or the movie though.
- Yeah. - You know?
- Yeah, that's what was so sick about it.
- It just looks, it might as well be an episode.
- But that's-- - It might be how
they make the show, I don't know.
- But just speaking of like the family guy,
like he's in the video, the Chris Griffin one,
Yeah, it was like, oh, yeah, that was an
actual that was a dream I had because
around the time that I had that dream,
that's when the like the first couple
of fucking like Subway Surfer
like Family Guy video started coming
out. Oh, yeah.
So I had a dream because the night
before I went to bed because I watched
like a full episode on
the surface thing, like I went
to the channel that it was on and
there's a watch.
And then when the clip ended, I would
scroll up and then watched like again.
Wow. Dude, that changed my brain completely. Once those Subway Surfer Family Guy things
started coming out, I literally, I think I spent like, I think, yeah, you guys looked
at my screen time on an episode and how it was like, today, it was like you woke up at
what time? I was like, oh, I woke up at 9 and then I think we were recording at like
noon. It said that you had been on your phone the entire time since you woke up. Oh my gosh.
that before I got to the office, I was
fucking watching Subway Surfers Family Guy.
Yeah, I think that's I'm perfectly
built for this time period now.
I think you're in your my brain
like was only built for this time.
I mean, I said earlier, like I would
have been an amazing serve only
physically. I think you probably
would have been like still you would
have had like a frog that you touch
its tummy all day or something.
I just rubbed a frog.
Yeah, you'd have a stick to stem with.
Yeah, exactly. Just scrolling through a stick.
That's probably, if I was like a knight, I'd probably be the guy with the mace
just so I could swing something around.
You would not. If you were a knight, God, that would be first of all.
I'd be dead. I'd be, I'd be.
No, that would have been some funny shit.
You would have hit your own head with the mace, probably
because you didn't realize that it comes back around when you swing it.
And then also you probably would have ridden your horse backwards,
which would have been kind of funny.
No, I would have.
I would have had a great relationship with my horse.
I know. But you would have.
You would have thought that it was like an avatar kind of thing.
No, the horse would be smarter than me, and then the horse would know where to guide me.
You would try to use the frog to take a picture of yourself with the horse's nuts,
and then it would kick you in the head.
Ribbit?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, oh! Ribbit.
[laughter]
Would you use a frog like a game?
That's what, yeah, that's what you would do.
If we transported you back to Monty Python time...
Like Army of Darkness?
Arnie of Darkne?
Arnie of Darkne.
You would have been walking around taking a photo with a frog.
Yeah, I would have.
Here, let me turn the flash on, you pull his tongue out.
Frogs probably looked so different back then, think about that.
You think they're like corn, where we've changed them?
You know corn used to be one kernel?
Really?
One whole kernel?
Maybe just a couple.
Yeah, it was probably...
I think it was three or four.
It was like a bean with corn on it.
That was maize.
And what we have now is corn.
Okay, think about it. Isn't maze just Spanish for corn? No, I think it is. I think it's different
Right. I don't think I think corn maze is just called corn corn. Oh
Hold the phone way. Hold on. Wait. Can you say that again? Oh, yeah. Our corn maze is just called corn corn
That's good. That's really good.
You have way better sounds than I have on my...
I have like a gunshot and then I have like the Price is Right.
Oh, that's good. We need to add a couple of things.
Yeah. My brother said the Gangnam Style drop.
Ooh, yeah. That is good.
Yeah.
Wait, talk...
But the... Me or... Yeah, you don't know which one.
Oh, what the fuck?
Yep.
Yo, that's crazy.
Yep. Yep.
Anytime we have a new guest on...
- Oh, we show them. - Five minutes of the episode.
- You have to show it off. - Yeah.
- It's fun. - Yeah.
- This is, that's so sick. - Yeah.
- It's pretty amazing, right? - Yeah.
- Which cable is he? 'Cause there's also...
- Are you trying to do low?
- No, there's this, but I don't know which one.
- Oh, it's on me. - You got reverbed.
- Uh-oh. I'm used to reverb now.
I became a musician while I was in California.
- You did? Have you heard his music?
- No.
- Juvio, can you pull these out? - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- You're gonna play it? - I did hear you rapping.
The raps, yeah.
Oh, well, no, well, these are different kinds of raps that you might be used to.
I showed Dan backstage before we went on stage.
What did he say?
I mean, we were about to, I think we had like...
We had like two minutes.
And he said?
He said it sounds good.
You're lying.
He said it sounded really good.
So, listen, me and my cousin, Matthew, decided to start working on some music together.
And I'll play both of these, but the second one's just a snippet because we're still working
on the verses part.
He's like a hook master. He just started walking around singing this song and I was like, "I
have to jump on this track." But it's this.
Wait.
I got a new telephone and it's got your number. I got it from the phone book. I saw you walking
across the street and that you looked just so awesome.
My part.
[Music]
So we came up with that one.
- That's awesome.
- But then, so it had been maybe six hours
since we recorded this.
- You guys should hop on a track together.
- Yeah, dude.
- You wish.
But then--
- Yeah, dude, I wanna collab.
- You fucking wish.
You have to pay me, I have a feature fee.
- Yeah, that's fair.
- It's over $100,000.
But then, he came up with something even better, man.
- Uh-huh.
- And I want you to hear this.
I want you to pay attention to these lyrics.
- Okay.
(music)
Wow.
And then I, this is the beginning of my part.
(music)
But yeah.
Nice.
I made a new friend, I made a new friend.
He really likes me.
They're obsessed with my vanilla ice cream.
What's that song called?
called? Trace Flamas. Trace Flamas? Because it's actually me, well I didn't include all
the verses, but it's me, my cousin Matthew, and my cousin Diven. Diven? Yeah, so the three
of us, he's from Peru. Okay. So if you have anything to say about that, go ahead. They
don't eat koi. They don't, no, they do eat koi. Peruvians eat kui. Yeah, but yeah, I
didn't ask him about that because I got scared, but I learned, I got scared that he would
say yeah that's my favorite food. So I didn't ask him about it.
Matthew: I do, there was, by the Popeyes in Bushwick, there was people selling Cuy on
big swords.
Ryan: I was talking to Noah about that.
Noah: Whoa, do you get the sword?
Matthew: No, you don't get the sword.
Ryan: That better be, for people who don't know, Cuy is guinea pig and they sell them
on swords, but they better be slain with the sword. It better be something where they stick
them and then that's it.
Matthew: C-U-Y.
Ryan: C-U-Y?
C-U-Y? Not Clarkson University in Hudson. C-U-Y. Y as in, oh no, it's I. Oh, okay. Yeah, so that's
it. So that's Quee. Yeah, remember, wait, that photo right there, we used to have a Quee
tote bag. They had a picture of that on it. Yeah, I had a, yeah, well I didn't know, we
didn't lose it in the flood, we lost it. Why'd they give him a helmet and put a pepper in
his mouth? That actually looks amazing. It looks kind of cute. Yeah, it was a fucking
guinea pig. Of course it was cute. Yeah, it was cute at one point, but we lost the
cue, the coy tote bag because of the night that I found Moe on the street.
Oh, and he had, um, well I had found Moe and then his brother Tyson chicken and,
uh, died. Tyson chicken died away. Yeah. And I didn't want to laugh at the name.
Tyson chicken. I was like, I can't laugh at our boy. I didn't think I was going to
keep him so I gave them like pet finder names. But Moe's original name was The Simpsons.
And then my roommate Neil said I don't want to hear you walk around the house saying Simpsons.
You should not be naming your animals funny names man.
Well I wasn't going to keep him. And then he was a foster fail.
That means he becomes nothing, he becomes an object if you're walking around he's the
Simpsons.
Yeah I know now he's got a name.
What's he short for?
Moe Slizlak.
So it's still the Simpsons a little bit.
Kind of.
But yeah, we thought, so Moe's brother who died pooped on the tote bag because he couldn't
handle, he had like no bowel muscle or something.
He was like, that cat was, this is a bummer.
Why am I talking about this?
Born to die.
That cat was born to die.
But coming up on a year of Moe.
Wow.
the on the 28th of August. I hate that cat man. You don't hate him. Do you ever call
Moe over by being like, "Hey, Hugh J-ness." Oh yes. And then Moe's like, "That's not,
where am I going?" Is that why you named him Moe? Because that actually happens? I was
just thinking about like. You were just thinking about that part in the series? Yeah. And I
I was like, it would be funny to call your cat over, but it wouldn't really work.
Yeah, cat wouldn't.
Well, yeah, he doesn't have a phone.
I don't I don't like funny dog names, man.
Cat names.
You named your dog.
My dog's name is human name.
His name is Phil.
I like that's a normal name.
Mo is a normal name.
Also, my brother had a dog, very sweet dog.
But he named him Cabrón.
Cabrón?
Cabrón.
Like bastard?
Means bastard.
Wow, that's tough.
Or fucker, like piece of shit.
It means everything.
Pretty much every.
It's just an everything curse word. They figured it out in Spanish. You just need one cuss.
Yeah. You need one or two.
And it's all context dependent.
That's kind of sweet.
Yeah, you don't need...
That's the best way to cuss.
I think the Chinese do that too.
Really?
I think so. That could be wrong.
I've been back into Xiao Ma videos and I think I want to learn perfect Chinese.
Him and Rex need to link up.
I think that I could learn any language very easily.
I've been trying to learn Irish, Gaelic.
You seem to me like somebody who knows perfect Spanish.
No, I'm so stupid.
Okay.
I can't learn very good.
I've been duolinguing Chinese though.
Really?
You've been trying to learn it?
Yeah.
Can you give us a taste?
Ni hao.
Fuck you.
That is what they say.
Yeah, no shit that's what they say.
What else?
That's the first one.
You can say "Zai shen."
I've never heard goodbye.
Yeah.
"Zai shen."
And then I'm also a Chinese.
And then I'm also it's all pronunciation based. I might be fucking it up. Yeah saying something different
That's cool
Yeah
What else you got? What else I used to be able to count to ten, but I haven't done it. No. Okay, so you're here
You're not learning Chinese. You're forgetting it. Yeah. Yeah currently I'm forgetting in the
I gotta get back on the Irish stuff.
Don't learn Irish man.
It looks cool though.
That is not a cool language. If you're going to spend the time to learn a language, learn one that you can actually talk to people with.
I'm learning it. Well yeah, I want to talk to an old Irish person.
There's nobody who speaks Gaelic that doesn't speak English.
He wants to be able to tweet on the Irish side of Twitter where everything sounds, like looks wrong.
Oh yeah.
Unless you figure it all out.
I ne'er want that shit. I hate that shit.
I was learning it though, and it's just like dude. It's it
Yeah, it was sound like a goblin language honestly. I do they have do a lingo for that. Yeah, I'm learning it unfair
I guess and bond what's that a man and a woman?
And what are they doing?
August and bond there for their fucking
Unfair I guess I'm bond and second and they're fucking it looks like white pet. Yeah, I
I got shown an amazing white Jamaican rapper recently.
Really?
Who's really good.
What's his name?
I don't remember his name.
Have you seen those videos of Killian Murphy talking and people are saying like holy shit
the cork accent just sounds like slow Jamaican.
No.
Dude it's crazy.
It's like an actual, like, I guess the Irish, like, were, like, the English sent, like, the
Irish to Jamaica, so now, like, the Jamaican accent is, like, it's interlinked with Irish.
Yeah, Jamaican accent is basically Irish.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's so cool.
I mean, it's definitely, I would rather...
It might be the only cool thing Irish people ever did.
No, they did a lot of cool stuff until they invented whiskey.
Really?
Yeah, once they invented whiskey, they'd fuck it. My buddy was telling me about that. I
don't know everything, but there was like a good chunk of years where they were just
inventing the hell out of stuff.
Yeah, really?
Found whiskey and they were like, "We're done."
I learned about an amazing thing that I want to try, which is ether, which used to be a
big problem in Ireland.
Ether?
Ether.
Like from fear and loathing?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. So that exact thing. They used to, ether used to be like, they used to
give it to like kids and stuff.
It was just you put it in a rag and you smell it?
It basically ruined all of these countries for like a hundred years because everybody
was addicted to ether.
Is it like poppers?
Kind of, yeah.
Yeah, it's like a...
It's probably proto-poppers.
It's basically...
Natural poppers.
I think it is basically like poppers that get you drunk instead of...
Opening your butthole.
It's not just that.
You know, I've done poppers one time and I really put all of my focus, like I kind of
I meditated on my asshole for like a full minute,
and it did not feel any more bigger.
- Maybe you're just--
- What about a guy who--
- Maybe you're thinking too much.
- Takes poppers and then goes to take a shit.
(laughing)
- That, I could see that.
- I did that.
I've done poppers and then just been like,
I gotta go, I gotta go shit so bad.
I didn't realize I ate so much food earlier.
- Yeah.
- It helps, honestly.
- It helps you shit?
- I believe it.
- I just, keeping a bottle of fucking Rush in the bathroom.
it. I've been able to shit for like three days. That'd be kind of fun if you kept that like
next to the matches on the top of the toilet. That would be funny. It's at least nice for
your guests. Yeah. You know? Yeah, but people who... Well, but then yeah, you walk in and
somebody put a shampoo bottle up their ass and you're like, "Oh, fuck me, I left the
poppers in there." No, I just think that like, because I imagine the poppers buying process
is you can get them at pretty much any vape shop.
It's so easy dude.
But it's got to be more, I would just be scared of the kind of, like you remember the first
time you bought condoms?
Yeah.
And you were like, they're going to arrest me.
Well I was blessed with self-checkout at Walmart.
Oh.
That's what I was doing.
Oh, okay.
See I had the sweetest old lady in the world.
Yeah.
And I would always buy one.
I'm going to rail someone.
I would always buy one other thing.
Yeah.
But I think that made it worse because I would buy, I'll buy, oh, this young man's buying
boggle. How's your day going? Oh, very good. The smallest size condom that they have. Put
it right on top of the boggle. That'll be it for me.
There was a time in my life where I kept this receipt because I would buy another thing,
and I was, you know, I was like 17. I was like, this will be so funny. And the receipt
I kept was, it's gone now, but it was just condoms, one eye patch.
Same, like I was like...
That's a problem, dude.
Make it look like you're like, "I'm in the same aisle, so I'm just like,
"Uh..."
That's the fucking problem. If you're buying condoms, lube, anything like
that, and then you buy anything else with that, they're gonna assume that
it's all going to sex.
Yeah.
So I've bought something I bought intimate products and then also dog food
and dog toys.
I did that a couple months ago and then I left and I was like that's that was
probably really weird for that later. Yeah, I'm buying dog toys, dog food and
different kind of dog bone. I bought a full bone and then one of the rawhide
pig ears.
Like I just that's just not it should be two different transactions. Yeah, the
last time I bought a condom it was in a bodega and I bought this better been
years I bought them for a sketch yeah for cave to pull out of his pocket and
have it there so I bought like a Red Bull and the biggest condoms I could find
nice and the guys just like the first time I got condoms though my mom bought
bought them for me. Oh, that's actually nice. That's not nice. You should not do that. It was bad.
No, it's weird. It's weird, but it's like... They're just sitting in my room, on my room bed, it's used to.
Well, it's like, it's nice of your mom to think like, "Oh, my kids fucking..."
When she bought them, she bought them just because you were going to college?
I started, I started like hanging out with this girl a lot and my mom was like, "Oh, you're hanging out with this
girl a lot. I want you to be safe." And I was like, "Okay." Yeah, she didn't want you to have a kid.
Yeah, because I, dude, I can't have a kid.
Yeah, me neither.
I would be a bad dad.
I'd be a great dad, but I'd be a bad dad.
Yeah.
Why would you be a great weekend dad?
I think you'd be a good, I think you, I could see you as kind of a 50 year old dad.
Yeah.
You know, I think the 30s, those are going to be bad, man.
You think your 20s have been bad.
You're going to have a bad 30s.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know anything.
I can't, I can't take care of a child.
I can't take care of myself.
My mom literally will be like, "I'm so proud of you when I do something adult."
And I'm 25 and I'm like, "Do you think I'm incapable?"
And it's like, she does think I'm incapable.
That's very sweet.
Like, I got my ID and she's like, "You did it all by yourself."
I'm like, "Yeah, I'm an adult."
You went to the DMV?
Yeah, twice.
In New York, I fucked it up.
My ID's been expired for like four months.
That's so cool.
have
change mine soon. I've got to go back to New Hampshire then.
Just get it renewed. Just say, use all the same information.
My ID photo, I'm wondering how long I can keep this going because I had to get my ID
renewed during the peak of lockdown. Got my ID renewed, took them a couple months to even
get the paperwork done. They lost the paperwork, I had to refile it, then I had to go back
again to -- because I forgot to put my address down. Even though I had already fucking filed
it, now my ID photo since I was 18 has been a photo of me the day before I got my state
issue.
So you're 17.
Yeah, the photo that I hand to bartenders is like -- I'll pull it out.
Mine I have hair and it says I'm 5'11".
Mine is a mug shot.
I look like a little boy.
I said I was 6'1".
Let me see.
You said you were 6'1"?
Are you 6'1"?
No, I'm only 6 foot tall.
Oh, okay.
I cheated two full inches, but they don't measure you, so you can just say whatever
you want.
I was honest, too.
You look fucking...you look honestly so good and Cuban in this photo.
It's fucking crazy.
You look insanely Cuban.
I put mascara in my mustache in that photo.
Really?
Because I was 17, I couldn't grow any facial hair.
That rules.
My dad used to do that when he was dating my mom.
Really?
Your mom would come home with a little fucking mascara mustache.
Did that work?
I should try that.
Before I was born, my dad would fill it in with mascara.
I thought about doing it.
Well, you have a decent beard.
Yeah, I just have like little patches.
I always was like, oh, I'll get a beard when I'm older.
My dad has a beard. But then anytime I look at my dad's beard, it's the worst
fucking beard. I'm never going to grow facial hair.
I just I'll never be able to do it.
Dude, shaving the mustache is the worst thing I've done.
You look so crazy.
You look good right now. This is a nice kind of length.
Dude, yeah, you grew back real quick.
Yeah.
Like faster than I did.
I'm waiting. So I shaved it on the...
I have like a timer.
Like I have it in my like calendar.
Really? It's organized.
I'll see how long it's gonna grow.
Like I took the photo the day that I completely shaved it.
- You're doing progress pics.
- Yeah, I'm gonna do like a photo in a month
and see what happens.
- We need to give you like a Minoxidil face mask
and see if we can fill in the rest of your face.
I think it's possible.
- Dude, you see up here?
- That's what I mean.
You are so close to having a--
- Full Wolfman face.
- A 60 or 70% face. - I have like,
I grow hair right under my eye.
- Yeah, I know.
If we put Minoxidil, if you closed your eyes,
you would grow it on your eyelids.
It would be so fucked up.
I could do that like the massager thing.
Yeah.
Have you seen this dude on Instagram?
He like has completely like pushed his hairline forward just by using like
rosemary oil and like minoxidil.
All that shit.
Oh, rosemary oil, minoxidil, and then like massaging his scalp and shit.
My stepdad sits under a red light helmet every night.
And it doesn't work at all.
But I have a friend who uses rosemary oil.
He's got a full head of hair, but he's like so nervous.
Yeah, I was not nervous enough when I started losing my hair. I really was like, anytime
did somebody be like, "Your hair is all fucked up." I'd go, "Yeah, man, it's crazy. It's
always been like this since I was a kid." But it's just not true.
When you had, there's like that photo of you, there's a photo I took of him eating a McChicken.
It's bad that you remember specific photos where my hair looks bad.
It was a photo I used for an episode recently, which is why I remember it. It was the Grommer
episode. Anyone can look this photo up. That was a year ago? No. Probably close to. That
was a couple months ago. Holy shit, it's August. Yep, it's flying by. Oh fuck it is. Oh my
god. Tell me how ugly I looked in this photo, go ahead. Your hair looks like the top of
a, maybe like the roots of an onion. You look like a weeble. You look like you would never
never fall down. So,
(laughter)
fuck you, bitch ass. I'm going to take this sticker off.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Suck on my balls.
No, keep the sticker on. I'm sorry that I said that.
I don't care.
I'm sorry I said that. Keep the sticker on.
Say my dreadlocks look good.
You had white dreads.
I did want, I wanted dreadlocks for so long. Way longer, even past when I knew it wasn't good to have them.
Yeah.
I really wanted dreadlocks and to listen to Kid Cudi. I wanted that so badly.
That's K1's white dreadlocks.
I know, he has what I wanted.
Yeah.
He's living that life that I just wanted so bad. I had a dream where I was going to move to the Bahamas
and I was going to have white dreadlocks and I was going to work in a surf shop.
You can still do it.
Yeah.
I believe in you.
The thing is dreadlocks have to be the easiest hair transplant you can get.
Yeah.
Right?
Adam Duritz, dude.
Oh, that guy. Those are real.
Those are real?
They gotta be real. He's had them for so long.
No, look him up, because they look crazy now.
He definitely has either a beard transplant or is like wearing a piece of Velcro on his face.
There's no way he's wearing Velcro on his fucking face.
Dude.
What am I looking...
Look up Adam Duritz counting crows.
He is like...
There's no way his facial hair is real.
I want to see this. That's fine. He looks good, man. That's real. You think that's fake?
Did he get rid of the dreadlocks?
God, I hope not.
Well, he's definitely dyeing it.
I mean, that might be true.
Yeah. Well, okay. There's no way that those dreadlocks are real.
How are they not? I mean, they look real to me, man.
There's no way. That is a wig.
That is a wig.
Look at the hairline, that's not a wig.
That is a wig that he made to look like that.
You're jealous, bro.
I'm so jealous.
You're fucking jealous.
I could look like this if I tried.
If I put in the effort.
You could look like that if you tried.
Yeah.
I mean, I could definitely look like that.
But the dreadlock.
He's kind of cool.
He is cool, man.
County Crows is probably one of the five best bands ever.
"Won't you stay and watch the problem, baby?
Watch the problem, I don't know how, baby."
That's them.
- Yeah, I know.
They did a, Shrek soundtrack is an amazingly underrated album.
♪ Come on, come on, love a little fan-mer ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
- Love a little fan-mer?
♪ Framlin', Lennon, Sander ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
- It's not any of those fucking lyrics.
♪ Get your fucking stuff now, love ♪
♪ Love, na, na, na ♪
- Oh, well, just hold on, hold on.
(sad trombone music)
- I was singing it correctly.
- It's none of the lyrics.
- It was all the lyrics.
- Didn't get a single, didn't get a single.
- I said all of them.
- As a current and future--
- I said come on, come on.
Musician man, you did not get any of that shirt right.
- I'm talking to two musicians today.
- I got a new friend, they really like me.
They're obsessed with my vanilla ice cream.
- I think it's cool that you can remember the lyrics.
- With the chocolate sauce and the iced tea.
- 'Cause every time I've ever written a song, I'd never,
I was playing in a band for like two years in high school.
And we'd go on and I would, different lyrics to,
music, same thing, but the words.
- The thing is, live music,
Nobody's here in a single fucking word you're singing, man.
Who can just say watermelon, watermelon?
Who cares?
No one's here and the lyrics at a house show.
Doesn't matter.
You think that they got a proper mixer there?
No fucking hell, no.
No, but it was funny because I just would hit the same melody,
but I'd be like...
That's why I suck at karaoke so bad.
I don't know what it is.
I can't remember lyrics to any songs.
Can you not read fast enough?
I think it's fine.
Cause that's my problem with karaoke when I do something like Drake or Eminem.
Cause I know the words but I'm trying to follow them on the screen.
Yeah.
And then I get tripped up.
Oh, you get tripped up by specific Drake certain words.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You gotta stop saying certain things.
The timing gets screwed up when you can't say that word.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which I, honestly I think they should stop saying it so I can rap along.
I'm with you. I'm with you.
That's why I like Christian rappers.
Yeah.
I went to on my birthday, I ended up at this weird birthday, some guy's like 32nd birthday
party and it was Barbenheimer themed and I was like there's no way I'm staying here.
That is awesome.
On your birthday you went to another birthday?
By accident yes.
How was this an accident?
Someone was like go to this address.
Oh and you just do whatever.
I was just kind of following the night.
It was my birthday, I was pretty drunk, I was at an event that had free booze.
And I was like, "Alright, this is the rhythm of the night!"
And I'm just going in Ubers and stuff.
They did Reeboks or Nikes?
Oh my god.
And then I end up there, I went to one spot that had free beer, to that spot that had
free beer, and then I was like, "I can't stomach this."
And then I left and went to the karaoke bar.
You couldn't stomach how cringe it was.
I went to a karaoke bar. I hate cringe ass birthdays.
The 30 second themed birthday party, come on now.
What is the problem with that? You're 32, don't have a birthday anymore.
You walk a mile in their shoes, buddy.
Yeah, that's true. When you're 30, we're going to an axe throwing bar.
But we went, me and my girlfriend and Brandon, we went to the karaoke bar in Chinatown.
and I kept getting the mic handed to me on songs that I don't know.
(laughter)
That's a bad feeling.
And songs I don't know all of the lyrics to. I know the chorus.
Just make it up.
No one was, everyone was outside smoking. It was like kind of packed in there.
Everyone's outside smoking, so no one's hearing when their song is coming up.
Okay. So you're doing all of them.
I'm getting, I was getting like every song.
That's the dream karaoke.
Yeah, but I don't know the song.
You got to do a set list.
But I did get to do Dancing in the Dark.
Yes.
And then I had to do Smash Mouth.
Which one?
All Star?
All Star.
Oh, that's some funny ass shit.
But that was fucking epic as hell.
Yeah, that is.
That would go crazy hard.
I did go hard as fuck on it.
I believe you.
That went amazing.
Did you do Screamo?
No.
Oh.
Actually, I did a little bit.
Yes.
Because Panic at the Disco went on.
Not Screamo, though.
Not Screamo.
All right, Clay, where can people find you?
Because I have to go piss so bad.
Oh, we've been doing this for, I can't tell because it's not recording on here.
You can find me on Instagram @bitchrespecter and Twitter.
Continues, ignore him.
Hand job.
Yeah, that's easy for people to know.
H-A-N-F-J-O-B.
There he is.
There he is on Instagram.
There's his Instagram.
You should get one of those, you should get one of those link trees or something.
Look at that handsome ass photo.
Holy fucking wow.
You look like a beautiful painter.
Oh, there's tons of drawings of you.
Wow.
Yeah, people like drawing me.
There's a video of me falling off a chair, like breaking a chair.
You look purple there.
It's grimace.
Whoa. And check out Lunch Enjoyer on Instagram.
That's some funny shit. Is that Drake?
Yeah. Oh my god. He stole that photo from me.
I did steal that photo from him.
Alright, I have to go pee. Bye. Bye bye.
Oh my...
So I'm actually, I'm actually
pretty sure that Rodney went to sleep because right now
I'm calling him and it's just ringing, ringing and he usually
declines my calls after one ring.
So I think that he's maybe he thinks his phone was compromised. Yeah, that's a good maybe we should or something. Yeah hit
Okay, we'll try to call him right now. Yeah, I think it's just gonna ring unfortunately. Oh look at this camera
This is definitely gonna turn him off. Yeah, it's just my computer. He's looking at it
So he didn't get turned off at all when I called him like five times. Yeah, he kept talking to me
I do think I truly do think he's probably probably just have to wake him up. Yeah
Yeah, I think we're gonna keep
I just call him on his normal cell
maybe
If you want to yeah, that's not such a bad idea. Yeah, did Rodney definitely fell asleep
Yeah, or I think the Illuminati number is compromised. Maybe he knows what?
Right now yeah, I think they're listening in and that's why hang that up hang that up. They're not only listening in
Google Voice
Illuminati.
OK. OK.
So when did that become a Google voice
number?
OK, so when did that become a Google voice number?
Oh, he's probably got a Google phone.
I mean, this guy cannot.
Yeah, I think he I think he put his phone
under his bed.
Yeah.
God, that's so disappointing.
It's horrible.
All right, well, I'll leave a voicemail if I can. Does Google
voice even let you do what?
Here we go.
You've made a huge mistake.
Okay,
Pierce, that is what the number one thing you don't want to say
the Illuminati.
You said you threatened them. I don't care the Illuminati and
we're here with you.
guest on the episode. And you do this? This is messed up. I don't care. I don't even care.
This is completely messed up. I'm not scared of them. I think they're stupid. I honestly
don't even think this guy's holding it really.
[MUSIC PLAYING]