*outro music*
belong to us.
It's so hard to do a clap.
All of your base
are belong...
Wait, wait, wait, do the clap.
All of your base
are belong to us
when the long cat is...
When the power level is over 9000.
When the long cat is over 9000.
The sun pad is long.
There is nothing in this song.
We are feeling so casual because of our environment right now.
Look at how casual we are.
Normally, here's what every day is for us.
We wake up.
Oh shit, oh fuck I'm late.
I go, I hit the alarm clock.
I smash it into pieces.
And then I fall back asleep.
My dog wakes me up by licking me in the face.
And then I go, fuck I'm late to work.
I go into our office.
this. See, once we started going into an office for it, I think that the chill ass vibes that
we had... It just feels like a job, bro. Yeah. It feels like a job. It's time to kick back.
Now we're doing what we used to do. We used to sit in a line on a couch and look straight
ahead at the TV. And we would watch TV most of the episode. We would usually, we had on
Pluto TV, some family guy or some fail army or something. Pluto TV, Bar Rescue. We're watching
it right now.
So put on.
No, don't put on.
Man, I don't know.
Not that bad. Not a bad idea.
But anyway, you're just burped
is stinky.
That is maybe.
I that smelled exactly like
Dinty Moore beef stew.
Yeah, it smelled almost it was like
if you were telling somebody to
replicate a scent.
I think that they would.
What was it? What did you tell people
that often? What did I eat for dinner
last night? I had carne asada.
No. What did you eat that before this?
I had some leftover rice for my carne asada meal,
and I had some chorizo and some eggs.
OK, so I guess that combined with grapefrost C4
creates a perfect beef stew scent
that I don't even know.
I can't even you putting this on the TV is genuinely so bad for me.
Yeah, you're you're trying to kill.
I I can't do this.
This guy just fell off of a stove.
Wait, no, just describe the stuff.
Okay, this lady's riding on a hoverboard.
Okay.
Oh, she's going to fall.
She looks like she's having a seizure.
Oh!
She's fallen and hit her head so hard her glasses flew off.
Imagine if you, if you like ended up on Fail Army in front of, like, failing in front of your children.
Do you think that like, they would look at you?
What was the...
I'm trying to get out.
You can't, we can't.
You gotta shut it off, man.
It's way too funny.
You can't do that to me.
Did you guys ever see your parents fail?
Yeah.
One time, I think my sister talks about this a lot.
It was like the day, she says, she cites it as the day she realized my dad was not, uh, not, what's the word?
God?
Yeah, that my dad was not like, uh, a moral person.
A moral person.
She found your dad a bad guy?
No, my dad, my dad just, uh, my dad ran a red light by accident.
That is immoral.
And he just went like, "Oh, my bad."
And she was young.
So it's like when you're young and you learn about the laws and shit,
and you're like, "Oh my God, he's going to get in trouble."
A traffic thing.
When I was young, I'd always think about this and I would always tell my parents
this, that if I was in a car chase and I was trying to flee, I was trying to get
away from the police, I would just signal a left turn and take a right or vice versa.
Whoa.
True.
Because they're behind you, they signal left now.
Yeah.
And they can't break the law.
So they have to commit to that left turn.
But I had that idea around first or second grade and I've held on to it. I
remember telling my teacher, because my dad used to drive, he drove all day
between like job sites because he's doing construction and he would always
drive while reading a John Grisham novel. He would read and drive and I
thought it was like a cool trick and he would drive with one knee. He would
have no hands on the wheel, driving with one knee and reading a book. And I
told my teacher that it was my dad's special talent.
And she said that's illegal.
Shut up, bitch!
My buddy in high school,
we would go back to his house
before we'd go skate,
but this kid would always drive with his knees
and text while he was driving.
I miss texting and driving.
He would be driving his mom's minivan
and just fully on Snapchat
chat talking to some girl or something and I was such a nerd that I was like, "Maybe
watch the road. He's doing the coolest thing you can do as a 16 year old." And I was like,
"Okay, well..."
Well, there's nothing nerdy about not wanting to die.
Facts.
I think that that is probably the nerdiest thing you can do.
If you want to die, you are a cool jock.
Things are changing in today's world.
Cool jocks want to die, that's why you play football. Modern day gladiators.
Hey, can I tell you something? Cool jocks nowadays like anime.
Yeah. I learned this from watching nerds.
Nerds like to lift weights. I watched 21 Jump Street.
Yeah. And I learned that nowadays it's cool to be gay.
Yep. It's cool to be sensitive now. Yeah. According to
21 Jump Street and Dave Franco who's in it. And then in 22 Jump Street
they said, "Well, never mind."
Yeah. They said never mind. Actually all along we were lying. Jocks are back.
I didn't, I don't think I saw 22 Jump Street. Do they go to middle school?
They go to college.
That's a good idea.
I would have gone the other way.
Go backwards.
Why would you go to college?
So they can play that needle drop, Asher Roth.
That party last night.
And then it goes to middle school.
So it's them walking into a party.
It did me too.
And I was like, damn, college is going to be amazing.
I was thinking the other day about how old I used to think people in college were.
Yeah.
And how I was like, that's really when your life starts.
When you're a kid, you're like, college is the one.
Fourth graders were teenagers back when I was in fifth grade.
When I was one, I thought two-year-olds were double my age.
[Laughs]
I was like, "That's crazy."
I thought my grandma was old.
My grandma is as old as dirt.
But back when I was a kid, she was like 17.
I did think, I think I saw someone in my neighborhood,
I saw a 16-year-old smoke when I was younger,
and I was like, "Damn."
Didn't you start smoking when you were 12?
Maybe that's why.
Because you saw a 16-year-old.
cigarettes were nasty. There's a girl named Joey.
OK, that is you have destined your kid to a cigarette heaven.
If you name and she was the first person I ever saw to wear Jenko's.
Joey, Joey, Jenko, Joey, Jenko, walk around smoking cigarettes.
Yeah. Was she beautiful?
I don't remember that well.
I just remember I just remember thinking, damn, those pants are huge.
She was a beauty queen. Probably.
I mean, she was smoking at 16.
You just said she was.
Wait, what?
What?
He just said, I said, 16 year old smoking cigarettes.
Oh yeah, she was smoking at 16.
She was smoking at 16.
We already accepted it. We're on the couch. This is casual.
Uh-uh. I said she was smokey. Whoa. That changed the whole vibe up.
Yeah, I just realized it was really dark in here.
It was really dark. I was feeling like I was in a bit of a swamp.
Do you guys like this painting?
This is called "Good Old Days" by Paul Dauter.
Really?
Paul Dauter?
I didn't even know that.
That's like a Joey kind of name.
No, Paul Dauferson.
Oh, okay. Not as good as it.
I can't read that.
I'm actually thinking this morning when I woke up,
Paul Detto and then they scratched out his name.
I want to jump into this painting like a Mario game and go hang out with those guys.
This is the good old days but where the hell is this?
I want to jump in it.
You know those paintings that they have of all that Roman food?
No.
You know those old Italian paintings of like, "Oh there's these grapes and there's these
bread."
I don't know.
and different cheeses that we don't have anymore that we've lost the recipe for.
Stop fidgeting with your microphone. No. I want to jump. It makes loud noises.
I want to jump into one of those so badly. They look so delicious.
If they saw like a bald person back then I think they would
they would probably. They had plenty of bald people. Socrates was bald.
Yep. Did he shave his head? Yeah, every day. More people were bald back in the day
than ever before.
Yeah. I thought they just let that shit hang like Benjamin Franklin did.
Benjamin Franklin is one of the ugliest people I've ever seen.
And he got hella pussy.
He did.
Mm-hmm.
Benjamin Franklin is literally...
You realize he was an author, inventor, scientist, politician, philosopher...
And he got so much pussy, but he was ugly as fuck.
Same with Washington.
Every single person...
I don't think Washington was playing that down.
Every single person up until...
I mean, even JFK, he was ugly.
Every president has been ugly until maybe...
Here's how you know that people used to be way uglier than they are now.
People used to, when a woman was really good looking, they used to call her handsome.
Yeah. That's how you know.
Because they all looked like men.
Yeah. They had big square faces.
They used to call women handsome.
Yep. Yeah. Now, now women are saying now all women are saying is hand me some
credit cards so I can go shopping.
Yeah. Hand some credit cards over.
Hand me some hand sanitizer.
Yeah. Hand sanitizer.
Current pandemic.
Wow. We're out of that.
Yeah, it's been over. It's been over. No, we're still in a damn pandemic.
Y'all know it's over. Think about it. Okay, think about it. What do you want
me to think about? What part of it? Think about how sick everyone is
getting. I haven't. No. Oh, you just broke the paint. I didn't break it.
I almost did, though. If you could jump into any painting in the world,
what would you jump into? I was thinking about this when you're
talking about that. Rothko. Yeah, I was going to say the funny answer.
The obvious funny answer is to say like Rothko or Pollock or something
like that. I don't want funny. But those are funny, right? Those are the those are
kind of the that's what a class clown would say instantly without giving any
thought to the deeper meaning of our shit.
That's right. So my answer.
Some of that real shit.
Shoot, shoot. I want to be a clown of the podcast and Cameron one most likely to
become president. That's that's reverse shoe.
Caleb. What's reverse? What?
Caleb, you were gone for that, weren't you?
Oh, yeah. He doesn't know.
Shoot. You don't know about shoe.
Just don't tell him.
Shoe is the opposite of cap.
So when you're telling the truth, you're shoeing.
That makes sense. Yeah. Well, reverse shoe is that cap? That's lie.
OK, so you don't think Cameron would win most likely?
So what did you say? He said he was a class clown of the podcast.
Cameron just said that I won.
Cameron just said that I was class.
I'd say you win anything.
Cameron just said I was class clown.
I said you I said that's something a class clown would say.
I didn't say you won class clown.
You said I won class.
We don't have superlatives yet.
I won. I won next world
fairle. We should do them every four years, though.
It is we are doing four years.
It is four years of the podcast this year.
It's been five years.
Five years?
It will be five.
Well, the first year is a fluke.
We're coming up on five.
What do you mean it's a fluke?
The first year...
No, I'm with you on that.
The first year I wasn't on the show.
OK, so let's do the superlatives then.
OK.
Yeah.
This is this.
We're doing superlatives now.
Maybe we make like a Google Forms.
What?
Well, no.
And then we have the fans vote.
Fuck the fans.
No.
Do the fans vote for the kids in the high school?
What do you mean?
No, the other kids do.
So let's...
No, you have all the fans of the high school kids.
Vote for this.
It doesn't make any sense that
no, we've got each other.
They tried that at they tried that at a high school and it was just like too
many too many.
They were noticing traffic from one one neighborhood.
What? OK, so now you and me vote for what Patrick is.
Oh, isn't it?
Most likely.
Okay, sure.
Most likely to...
Just to maybe influence your answer a little bit.
Go.
Next Will Ferrell, class of 2015, Londonderry High School.
You got next Will Ferrell?
Yeah, and then two years before it was next Tosh.0, so I thought that I was going to get next Tosh.0.
Okay.
You could be next...
Will Smith.
I'm going to slap you.
No.
What?
Next.
It should be.
He's already got Will Ferrell and he's already gotten Tosh.
Then no, no.
Comedian.
My friend's brother got next Daniel.
No, next Tosh.
No, not Daniel Tosh.
Next Tosh.
Point.
Next show Tosh.
Most likely to be Tosh.
Point.
Simpson.
That you look like a Simpson.
And it's not just the couch talking and this is shoe.
you look like my God, we need to do a couch gag.
Yeah, that's what this is.
Pause it right now.
We're going to record ourselves doing a couch.
Couch gag for us.
That will be the cold open.
Yeah.
I mean, it's got to be us scrambling onto the couch and
then sitting down and turning on the TV.
We should do it.
After this, can we do an exact one-to-one recreation of the
The Simpsons themes. Yeah, we have to sing it.
That acapella act, that acapella app.
We could do the whole thing.
Yeah, somebody's at.
Jubio could be.
Jubio is Maggie.
Jubio could be Maggie.
Jubio is definitely Maggie.
Doesn't speak English, just like Maggie.
And who's, I think Cameron's maybe Marge.
I agree.
Cameron is Marge.
Because I have to get groceries after this anyway.
You're a Homer and I'm a combination of Bart and Lisa.
Yeah.
Patrick's Bart, what are you talking about?
I'm a combination of Bart and Lisa.
Shut up.
I'm Bart.
You're the skateboard.
Man, you skateboard in the theme song.
I'm Bart.
You're Bart.
Well, I'm a combination of...
You can't skateboard in the theme song.
Okay.
I'm a combination of Bart and Homer.
No, man.
And...
And you're the music teacher.
What, you're going to strangle yourself?
You're the music teacher who tells Lisa to leave the room.
Yeah.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
If I grew my hair out, I would.
You're Dr. Nelson Hibbert.
that one. Thank you. Yeah, but you don't get to be in the couch gag then. That's fine. As
long as I'm black off screen somewhere. It's fine by me. Your season one, episode two,
Waylon Smithers. Why that one? They made him have purple hair. He had purple hair? And
black skin. He looked different? Smithers looked different? For one episode. I don't
remember that. They did all that type of thing. Yeah. They made mistakes. You know who I hate?
became blonde. I hate those white twins. Oh, they're not white. I think they're
supposed to be Asian. No, they're not. No, they're not. They're white. I think
they're Asian, but they are the color white in the show. Am I just being
racist? Why? Because they're twins. You think they're Asian? No. What do you
mean? What? What about them? Well, there's a way that their eyes are drawn.
What? I don't know. The weird little white twins. Not that. Not the sisters.
I okay. Is it crazy of me to think that they are supposed to they are like Asian
coding not the sisters.
Wait, maybe I'm not thinking of a twin.
Who are you thinking of?
Who have the long?
Who's the white?
Who's the white kid with the curly hair?
That's not a twin.
That's a one of that's a one of Wendell.
Well, we don't know.
He's not a twin.
What if we have that one?
What's he has some kind of name attached to him?
Are you thinking of Martin Prince?
No, no, Martin.
Martin.
Everybody knows Martin.
Yeah, but you're still stupid.
You thought that white kid is a normal white kid.
No, you're right.
The twins are Asian.
They got to be. Yeah, I know.
But they're not white, I don't think.
Or are there? I don't know.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
They're not Asian.
They're Marge's sisters.
No, no, that's different twins.
You think of Patty and Selma?
Yeah.
I'm looking up Simpsons, Asian twins.
See, OK. Yeah, they actually are the twins.
OK, OK.
Are the twins really want to know if they're not an Asian?
but I don't think they are. Yeah. So and I'm standing fast.
Okay, all right. So they're going to read that first post you found from Vin Diesel
to Vin Diesel to
so Wolfenstein 38 asked, well, I forgot their names because Caucasian people in
the Simpsons are yellow and brown and black people are brown and Asian people
are white and are the twins. Are they white? So are anyway, are they Asian Vin
Diesel to says, I don't think so dot dot dot their eyes are normal.
M: That's Vin Diesel.
M: Vin Diesel said that on NeoSeeker.com.
M: That's fucking crazy.
M: Oh their names are Sherry and Terry.
M: Woah!
M: Like SNL!
M: Oh my god.
M: Yeah.
M: Probably a comedy reference.
M: It is probably a comedy reference.
M: I saw a video the other day, it was 3 and a half hours long.
M: I want to apologize for being racist about a Simpson.
M: You were right about them though.
They were not Asian.
Oh never mind.
They were wrong.
Vin Diesel confirmed that they were not.
You were wrong.
Yeah, I was completely wrong and I apologize.
I saw a video the other day, basically the Simpsons, the Simpsons decline, get this,
the death of satire people are saying.
Wow.
Satire died with the Simpsons.
Because the Simpsons was the satire of what of...
It was a satire of Gen X.
A white family's skin color.
It was essentially...
What if a white family had a different skin color than white?
That's like the baseline satirical thing that's going on.
Why were they so obsessed with Butterfingers?
What?
The Simpson family.
Do they love Butterfingers?
Bart loved Butterfingers. When I think of Butterfingers, I think of Bart. I call him in my head Butterfinger Bart.
I think of my brother.
I call him Butterfinger Bart.
I don't think of anything.
My brain goes blank.
I think in my head Butterfinger Bart when I look at Butterfingers.
That makes no sense at all.
Because the inside is orange?
Yeah, you're being a little random.
No, I swear to God, there is a series of commercials for The Simpsons and then there was Butterfingers
in the show all the time.
Mate, mate, mate, when it comes to The Simpsons, you've lost the plot.
I don't want to hear another Simpsons opinion from you.
It's over for you with The Simpsons.
It's over for me with The Simpsons.
Get rid of The Simpsons from your brain, your house, your TV.
Delete that.
Delete that shit.
It's out of your knowledge.
I don't want to hear you say that shit ever again.
I think that I don't know enough about The Simpsons to be talking about this stuff.
Have you watched all of it?
No.
I'm definitely speaking on The Simpsons with not much to back it up.
Okay, well, get this, the comic book guy loves movies and comic books.
Right.
So is this a fact that you're trying to...
I'm just showing that I have a functional understanding of The Simpsons.
His name is Comic Book Guy.
A working understanding of The Simpsons.
I'm just showing you guys that I know at least a little bit about The Simpsons.
know almost nothing. Comic book guy.
Comic book guy. He loves animated properties.
He works at a comic book store, but he's never that happy about it.
No, he doesn't. He's kind of missing.
He doesn't like the people who like comic books.
He's a motherfucker who loves to hate.
He's a hater.
You know what I've noticed?
He's a born hater.
Do you ever feel like...
You gotta stop touching that.
Do you ever feel like comic book guy, a lot of these people who work as baristas now,
watched comic book guy and they said,
"I'm gonna become coffee shop, coffee store guy."
Coffee shop guy.
They stole his flow bar for bar.
because you walk into yeah because that I feel like when I walk into a coffee shop
everybody acting like comic book guy these days.
Yeah and some comic books or some you want a cup of coffee we don't do that here.
We actually don't have coffee.
We do a mug of coffee or I walk in and I say can I have 40?
Yeah, that's how they act now.
I ask, can I have 40 or 50 scoops of vanilla ice cream in a cup?
In a coffee, yeah.
No coffee, please.
And affogato.
And they say we don't do that, actually.
That's what they're, affogato?
We actually don't do ice cream.
Ice cream coffee.
Shut the fuck up. Do ice cream.
Yeah, they should do ice cream.
Every coffee shop should have ice cream.
If I didn't want ice cream in my coffee, I'd make it at home.
Yeah, you think I can't press, well, it's a button I gotta press.
put a pod in the thing of ice cream. I press the button, the coffee comes out, I throw the
pod in the backyard. And you think, listen, you think that I don't know, I can't make ice
cream at home. I can. I learned how in second grade. I had an amazing idea just now. You
use salt or liquid nitrogen. You put it in a plastic bag. It's fucking simple. That shit
is easy. The fact that I want to come to your store and give you money to make it for me.
Cameron, I got something that will calm you down. I'm calm. No, you were just, you were
a you were popping off for you were steaming.
You were reaching pot of clams.
I was just thinking about ice cream.
Shoo.
Keurig, but for ice cream.
How would that work mechanically?
It'll be cold Keurig.
It's already do that.
It's a liquid nitrogen pump and it all goes into a pod.
So you just thought of you've just invented an ice cream
factory.
But it's an ice cream factory for the home.
Yeah, it's an ice cream. Cure egg. Yeah, I just pull it in and never no, no, no,
no, no, because they come the flavor. You have to load it. You have to load it
up before you make it. Yeah, it's not like a soft serve machine where it just
comes out and disappears. An ice cream line. Yeah, I know the ice cream. The
ice cream and the soft serve just shows up. No, you don't understand the ice
cream. Keurig you when you put it, you put in the ice cream in a container
that's only the size of a K cup, so it only makes that much ice cream at a
Yeah, it's one scoop.
And if you want more than one scoop,
if you want more than if you want more than one scoop,
you've got to do multiple K-Cups.
Would you be able to like take this to the one at work?
Yeah, you can bring this to work.
Do you need a special Keurig for it, I'm asking?
Or do you like the ones that like it's like you can only use?
What about a nanobot that transforms any machine into an ice cream maker?
Like re-does everything?
You're like the Transformers.
I think that you're going to win the Transformers.
You're going to win next big adventure.
You know when the transformer gets the, uh, they dropped the all spark and the
pulse Shia LaBeouf drops it and the pulse goes out and it turns it the vending
machine into the transformer and it's shooting sodas.
I have seen that.
That's probably the greatest scene in a movie of the past 20 years.
Why?
So this, this, the all spark is a giver of life.
It makes you, it makes, so here's, so a transformer, that's an alien.
Yes.
They have nothing to do.
They have nothing to do with an earth car, even though they might look like a
a fire truck or a Ferrari. It's a prank. That's just what they look like on their
planet. So, imagine you were a transformer and you brought your special cube to
planet Earth, 'cause you were running away from your evil
enemies, really, and you accidentally drop your cube on the ground and it brings
to life a car and the car turns into one of you. Can you imagine how odd it
would be to go to another planet and people are driving, all the aliens are
driving things that look kinda like you?
I mean, also, you really are lucky. You're lucky in to like, yeah, exactly.
Like, you've really lucked in to an easy disguise if you walk around an alien planet and people are like,
using arms to make food and shit, you know? That's easy.
So, the Transformers are not cars before they get to Earth?
They are cars before they get to Earth.
No, they're not. They're not.
they learn we have seen a nude transformer but they are fully nude on
the look at my search history you will
they go they show them on their planet i don't think their cars on their planet
but i'd like to imagine that they are
may i like that that that i've got the transformers should do movies the next
one should do a scene where that when they're doing their alternate history
they always do where they say that
here are a lot of men with a transformer or stuff like that
they should do one word
uh... that o_j_ simpson chase he was trying to transform that what and he had
had no control. He was driving. He was driving. He was like tied. The Bronco
decapitated the two people and then he used the seat belt like a lizard's
tongue. They should do, and they should do JFK too. Grabbed him. The car was
the one thing that did it to him. The car had a little gun. Oh my God. Oh my
God. It has a little gun from the tire. That's why they never found a bullet,
because it was a bolt or a nut. They were like, "Well, we found this bolt and
nut inside his head, but this can't come from a gun." That must have just always
off the car. That must have fallen off the tire or something.
Wow. I've just opened a whole new door in the Transformers universe.
This is so fucking brilliant, bro.
Amelia Earhart.
Amelia Earhart. It flew home.
It flew her to space.
If we were all the way to...
What do they live on? The moon?
What other stuff happened to Tiananmen Square?
Tiananmen Square. The tank. The guy was like revving the fucking engine trying to hit that guy.
Yeah.
And then the Transformers said that...
The Transformers really like groceries.
so he just decided to try to go around.
He was a grocery bot.
Yeah.
So what other famous cars and funny scenarios?
Maybe Franz Ferdinand.
Yeah, Franz Ferdinand's car.
I mean that's the same as JFK though.
But it's slightly different.
It's slightly different but I think there's a very clear...
Listen, it's obvious, it's maybe too obvious, but it's 9/11.
Yeah.
Yeah, both of the buildings were Transformers and they transformed.
Yeah, they transformed into rubble because they were bored.
Yeah.
Or they're transformed into rubble as a protection.
Can a transformer be a building?
Yeah, I don't have we seen that.
I was wondering, could they be a gun?
Wasn't there one? Megatron was a gun.
Yeah, Megatron was like a Walther.
This is easy.
Yeah, every gun.
Every fucking gun that has ever been used.
Yeah.
I mean, that would be my defense.
You're on it.
The first thing at first I'm using my Blackberry and then all of a sudden it's
shooting three or four people on the street.
Yeah.
My Blackberry became an AR-15 out of nowhere.
Not my fault.
Also, I had Heelys on.
I still use a Blackberry.
And they were also Transformers because they have wheels.
Yeah, and I'm a Transformer.
So, your legal system doesn't apply to me.
Yeah, I'm a sovereign citizen as well.
I would like to be able to transform, but I think that...
What would you transform to?
I think right now I'd transform into a car because I need a car.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true and it'd be easier to just be a car because then I wouldn't have to park
anything. I just parked my ass on the couch. Exactly. You couldn't be a car on the couch.
Well, you could change back, I guess. Never mind. If I was a trans. I'm saying I want
to be a transformer. I want to be a car forever, man. Come on, dude. You wanted to be a car
for I don't want to be a car forever. I'm so sick of my fucking life. The daily grind,
hustle my god. I wish I could just be a car. Watching cars like they're like horses galloping
in a field. They're so free. Oh my god. They can they can go wherever they want. You think
that's how the car fuckers look at them? What's a car fucker? Remember that from Mancers? The
guy that was like or A Thousand Ways to Die is the guy that like they put like the beer koozies in
the exhaust pipe and then they fuck the cars. Dude at that point just fucking fuck the wall.
Why are you fucking a car?
Put a hole in the wall with a beer can
I mean at that point
I mean, you know, a celsius can
and then fuck that hole
Why do you need to
Why does it have to be
You know why
Don't ask me that question
A beer can? You think you can
You think this would be anything
Imagine you're about to have sex with a woman and you look at her vagina
and it's this wide
you call your mom, you're getting picked up. Yeah, I'm not going. But that's the
thing. The thing about those guys that I'm not even taking my clothes off.
Yeah, this is not work because I don't take my clothes off until she's fully
making me the whole
your legs.
And I'm standing with my arms crossed. I like nope too big. Bye
later. Take a quick flash. Can you can you call me an Uber? I have to go.
I have to go in my foot. My apple pay is now. I have the ruler app on my phone,
the like distance
looks like it's twelve inches. Why
me and me and Sam were laughing so hard the other day about about like going to
like we he took me to the tow company to like try to get my car back and I talked
to the lady and then she was like, oh, you actually need this other piece of
paper like you can't get the car today. I was like, okay, we're laughing so hard
about being like, okay, sorry about that. And then just taking a photo over with
the
iPhone.
Okay, thank you so much.
She's trying to ask you why you took the photo.
Later. Thank you so much.
You have one of those like phones from Japan that has like the really loud
shutter click.
Yeah. You have to unfold your phone. You have a foldable phone.
You unfold it, take a flash photo and leave.
It just works at any place where somebody is just working there.
Yeah. Taking a picture of your, like the drive-through guy.
Yeah. Thank you so much.
Wait, hold on.
I love taking pictures of people.
Yeah, I wanted to take a oh man. Fuck. I told you guys about a guy I saw at the
airport on my way back from California who had the craziest facial hair I've
ever seen where he had. Oh yeah. One half of his face had a mustache and then he
shaved the other half of his mustache. But on that side he had a full beard.
Yeah. So it was half and half. He had windows antivirus. And I really, really
wanted to take a photo of him, but he looked at me the entire time as a measure. I was playing
the hide from the teacher flash game with him. I could see his cone of vision was very
wide too, his eyes were offset.
Yeah. Did I ever, when I was living in Manchester, I saw these like, I saw this couple walking
down the street one day, full Harley Quinn cosplay.
Both of them?
Then the man had green hair.
That's nothing dude.
What do you mean that's nothing?
That's a Joker couple that doesn't have a car.
Let me guess, it was on Halloween.
No, it was August.
August is close enough to Halloween that any costumes are acceptable.
Alright.
You're telling your story is that you saw
somebody wearing a costume.
I saw a Joker couple.
That guy was not even Joker.
He had grand hair, he's the Joker.
I sent you guys a picture of this. I saw Chris Griffin taking stuff out of my trash.
Oh yeah.
exact. He was. Something that Patrick had talked about for, I mean, so this was a crazy experience
for me because Patrick talked about this for like probably 10 months straight. Yeah. The
idea of seeing somebody dressed as Chris Griffin. Yeah. And we always kept saying, "Patrick,
that's stupid. That doesn't make any sense." Yeah. You wouldn't see somebody and be like,
"That's Chris Griffin. That's not an outfit that would register." But you did see it. And
I hear, I'm walking out of my house to leave, to go to the office. I hear somebody go through
my recycling. I open the door and I just immediately first thought, "Oh my God, that's Chris Griffin."
It's the it's vindicated.
Exact shirt, pants and hat.
I was so right about this.
It was, but to be fair, I wouldn't have thought it unless you hadn't made that video.
You would have thought it.
No, I wouldn't have.
He was also, he was portly.
Yeah, like Chris Griffin.
Like Chris Griffin.
I mean, seeing a skinny Chris Griffin, you're not going to think about it.
Was he a dunce?
Yeah, well he's getting recycling, so.
I mean, he thinks trash is food.
He likes trash.
The people who live.
thought my house was a store.
A guy who thinks that homeless people just eat cans.
That's what they're doing.
They're transformers.
All these fucking, these homeless drug addicts eating my cans.
What do you mean? They're going through the soda cans to try and get a drop of soda out of them.
That adds up eventually.
Yeah.
That's over a four-seventh day, you could almost get a swig.
The family that lives under me,
they moved in and I've been smelling this awful, awful smell every time I walk by
their apartment and I've been thinking they've just been making a fucked up fish.
Yeah.
and it turns out no no nobody has passed away in that apartment,
although they do cry all the time, but
what
I always
I always see the mom like outside of the apartment, just like
maybe yeah, yeah, maybe it's because of the smell. I think it
is because they do the can thing and I found that out that the
smell was just like stinky beer, old beer. Yeah, but I'm so
stupid that I thought it was fish. Yeah, but they're nice
people. I let them, they never have their keys.
You let them in your house?
They never have their keys so I always have to let them into the apartment.
Okay.
Yeah, but they're very good people.
You're saying that like you're like, you're like how, giving them like the shirt off your
back.
I mean, that's pretty sweet of me.
That's a nice thing to do.
It's not sweet, it's kind of just expected.
They come in and they stink up the whole apartment and I'm still letting them in all the time
with the cans.
That's fine.
But it made me think that maybe you could make some decent money doing that.
Oh, you make pretty good money. It's five cents per can.
I love to look.
Yeah, you didn't know that?
High me 5 cents.
You never collected cans?
No.
I did that all the time as a kid.
I didn't live in a place where you could walk around and get cans like that.
Well, you just get them.
I've been giving my cans out.
You take them to the grocery store?
I leave them.
Honestly, it's less about the money you get and more about the funness of putting the
can into the thing with the two wheels.
It looks so fun.
Oh my God.
Have you never done it?
I've never done it.
It sucks it in.
I've known that it's 5 cents per can.
I just leave my cans out on top of the trash barrel so that the guys who dig for them can
get them.
I put it under oil.
I put it under an oil slick so when they try to grab it they slip.
I love when I hear someone going through my cans, I look at them.
I watch them do it.
Because you say that you're stealing money out of my pocket.
Just so they know that I'm here.
You'll never get my full soda.
I just want them to know that I'm watching them.
That one was mine.
That can was mine.
I drank that.
that window right there and I just look down and I have no expression on my face. I just
watch them the entire time they do it.
You're not getting my soda.
No, I don't.
I already drank my soda.
I just want to look at them do it.
You think those are full.
Nuh-uh.
I already drank all that.
Just to make sure they don't take any. Just to make sure they don't try to take the rest
of the trash.
Oh yeah.
Because then I'm not going to throw it away.
The trash belongs to the city.
I have a little bit of sentimental value with my cans though. Sometimes I'll look into my
recycling bin and I'll go, "I don't remember that one."
Yeah.
You ever do that?
I do that. I don't drink anything from a can.
Okay, Rich. He drinks out of boxes.
Yeah, Mr. Boxed Wine over here.
Boxed Wine, Boxed Beer.
I should go back to the canned wine.
Boxed Chardonnay.
Would you drink a beer in a box?
I don't think I would. I feel like it would eat me.
It would definitely be bad, but I would still drink it.
You would drink it.
I feel like it would eat up the box.
What if your friend made it?
Let me ask you a question that I asked Julio a while ago
he couldn't wrap his head around. Yeah, that so so you go to the grocery store.
Yeah, you go to the meat section. Okay, looking at the the raw whole chickens
polio polio. Exactly. Maybe you should have said that you should have said
that's what yeah, that didn't seem to be the stumbling point for him. Okay,
you're looking at all the raw whole chickens because you're going to buy a
raw whole chicken. Okay, you're going down the line. You're looking at them.
You get to one this chicken. It looks exactly the same as all the others. It
It costs the same amount.
It's packaged up.
You grab it, you pick it up to put it in your cart.
You look at the label.
The label on it, it says peanut butter chicken.
So are you going to buy it or are you going to put it back?
Probably put it back.
Okay, only if they have jelly chicken.
You don't even want to try it.
Well, okay.
You don't even, there's no curiosity in your mind when you see in a grocery store something
called peanut butter chicken that you can't tell in any visible way why I
called that. You wouldn't buy that even to find out.
Certainly there's curiosity, but I'm not sure that I'm willing to spend eight
bucks to have a chicken that maybe I'm not even going to eat.
You're not thinking of any type of recipes at all?
I'm thinking immediately peanut butter. I'm thinking satay, maybe making that.
Right. Yeah.
Okay.
You don't have a curious mind.
Let's say you do a smaller piece of a chicken then.
What about a rotisserie peanut butter chicken?
$6.99?
Yeah.
Hey, why is it cheaper than the regular peanut butter chicken?
Where I did that.
With peanut butter?
Yeah, with peanut butter too.
Oh, okay.
Where's my quote?
Why don't they put every...
I should have a rotisserie option for everything, get a little discount.
Yeah.
Why doesn't the grocery store have kebabs?
But the...
They got the rotisserie.
I would buy the rotisserie.
You only put chicken on there?
I would assume that the peanut butter chicken is going to follow the same
naming logic as beer can chicken.
Where somebody maybe just shoved a can of peanut butter.
Well, they're putting a can of peanut butter in there.
That means the whole interior of that chicken is covered and coated in plastic.
Yeah, so I guess my first thing that I would do when I got home was cut it open to see
if there's peanut butter in the middle.
Yeah, I guess I would definitely cut it open before I cook it.
If there is, then I'll probably just take it out.
So, well, no, you take that peanut butter, you cook it down into a little
even this was no room for what the chicken actually ends up being. This is
fully a grocery store scenario. Well, then no, I don't it ends at the
grocery store. I don't buy it if I don't if yeah, no, I'm buying it. Best
case scenario, I'm a peanut butter chicken, but I think we can maybe do a
really interesting psychological study. The best case scenario is that you
he also would not buy the peanut butter. You get a jar of peanut butter for
free. No, it's not. No, you don't get a jar of the best case scenario is
you cook the peanut butter chicken and it tastes delicious and it has some
type of peanut butter flavor that you never thought could taste the way it
does. It's the nuttiness. That's the best case scenario. Yeah, the nuttiness
infused in the chicken. But the best case scenario is you get a jar of
peanut butter inside the chicken. What do you think that's the best case
scenario? That's a medium case scenario. That's a normal case scenario. The
scenario is the peanut butter chicken tastes good. Yeah, that's good.
And that's the best case scenario is any chicken.
No, any chicken you could buy could taste really good.
Peanut butter chicken is chicken. Yeah, that's what I mean.
So that's that's just a chicken.
Wait, so it's a chicken raised on a diet of peanut butter?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Because the best case scenario for any piece of chicken
is that it's better than any other chicken you've ever eaten.
Yes. Yeah.
Well, that could be true for peanut butter chicken.
It could be true for any other chicken in the store.
Hold the phone. Hold the phone.
Right. But there's a difference.
We can't ask any questions about why it's called peanut butter chicken.
That's what he says.
No, because I don't know why.
You don't? OK.
This is the worst hypothetical.
Obviously, peanut butter chicken does not exist.
No, no. It's hypothetical.
Yeah, exactly.
So it will exist is the thing.
So how will I know what it is if it doesn't exist?
Your question answered the questions.
No, it's a thought experiment.
Buddy, it's it's not.
I don't have an answer.
It is the worst experiment.
I mean, you finished the experiment. You guys are just pushing it onward to eating it.
It's not about eating it. It's about buying it.
What do you mean? It's all about eating it. That's what I mean.
There is no, it's not about it, but it's all about eating it.
At its core, it could be the label.
It's a question about a consumer's curiosity.
Then at that point, if it doesn't have anything to do with how it tastes or what,
or, and I don't know anything about it,
then the piece of chicken could say anything different than the other pieces of
chicken. Yeah. No, he's right. He's right. He's right. It is. It is a
question about I did get too hung up on the thought of eating it. It is
about the consumer curiosity. How you act in the grocery store. I act
polite. I let no, no, no, no. What if you would buy a weird food? Yeah,
I like that. And you're completely right that it doesn't have to. It
could be jelly chicken. Yeah. Why is it? Jelly and peanut? I mean, just
pick. Those are just the first thing. Okay, see, the point is, it has to
weird enough that you have to be curious in order to buy it.
The first two things you thought of were peanut butter and jelly?
Well, the second thing I thought of was jelly because I was thinking about peanut butter.
The thing you also have to think about in this, right, you replace chicken with chips.
Okay.
That's more grounded.
Exactly.
See, that's the thing where any person would probably get the weird chip because it's normal to try a weird chip.
It's also low stakes.
Very low stakes. High stakes is what a chicken is.
Exactly. So this is testing.
If I'm buying a whole chicken, that means I have some recipe planned. Peanut butter may
not really be a part of what I have planned. I might be thinking I'm doing some kind of
slow roasted thing. All of a sudden it's a mole.
See for me, I would try it. I would buy it even if I was worried that it would completely
be horrible and be ruined, I would be okay with throwing it away just for the chance
to try peanut butter chicken and see what the deal is.
I would love to try peanut butter chicken genuinely.
This is not...
And try making it.
I guess I do not have an adventurous childlike Peter Pan spirit.
Peter Pan is a brand of peanut butter.
Yeah, it's a type of peanut butter.
And I definitely don't.
What if the label is just a big Peter Pan logo with a chicken on it?
That, see I'm more tempted to try that.
Yeah, what if you bought that because you thought, oh, they spread out, they're doing
chicken now instead of just peanut butter. You get home, you cook it and it's peanut
butter flavored. Or it's like they have the canned chicken. You ever seen that? The canned
whole chicken? I think so. Jarred whole peanut butter chicken. Jarred whole peanut butter.
Whole big peanut? You guys ever do the machine at the grocery store that makes the peanut
butter? No, but I gotta start doing that. What? The machine where you press a button. They
They had let be fresh in Austin, Massachusetts.
I've never heard of this in my life.
You've never heard of this?
It makes peanut butter?
They have a peanut butter one and an almond butter one.
Yeah.
And you can make honey roasted peanut butter.
I never did know about this.
Yeah.
You can get fresh peanut butter at the store.
It's good as fuck.
I don't think they have that at my store.
They don't have it at any of the stores around here, but if you go to like the Wegmans.
We live in a food desert.
If you go to the Wegmans in Dumbo, I think they got it there.
That's the biggest grocery store I've ever seen.
Who the hell named that fucking neighborhood, bro?
Dumbo?
Because it's "Duh Under My Brooklyn Bridge Oh No I don't know."
Down Under Manhattan Bridge Overpass.
Is that really what it means?
So you knew the whole time?
You made me look like a dumbo.
I thought you were going to do something funny.
I thought I was, I don't know, I was floundering.
I was floundering.
Yeah, I wasn't going to bail you out with the actual one.
You could have bailed me out with the actual one.
I was going to let you flounder.
You just wanted to see me fail.
He's mad about the peanut butter chicken thing
and he's still going to let us fail.
I do not care about peanut butter chicken.
You've made it clear.
You care so much.
I don't care even enough to,
I wouldn't even pick it up at the store.
I know you wouldn't pick it up.
You would pick it up and you would read the label.
That's the question.
I wouldn't even pick it up to look at it.
You know what would happen?
If he found peanut butter chicken at the store, he would pick it up.
Get out of my person's face.
He would pick it up and go.
And then he would come in here next day and go, "You know what I saw at the
store?"
These stores are selling a peanut butter chicken.
But that's what I would do, too.
But I would say I bought it and I ate it.
And I would just leave it.
You would just say.
But that's because.
I would bring up peanut butter chicken in conversation like you guys have known about it.
I'm such a good anecdote teller and such an amazing storyteller that I wouldn't want to ruin it, ruin my own story by learning that it was normal chicken or something.
You would just make it up.
I would just want to see it and then tell you guys that I saw it.
I would come in here.
I would have peanut butter chicken.
That's a good mark of a good storyteller.
I would say the name of it.
I would make the peanut butter chicken.
I would bring it in for us to eat.
I would say it.
I would say it while we're talking on here.
And I'd say, and, you know, I used peanut butter chicken and then you guys would go,
what? Yeah.
That's what I'd say.
There's no peanut butter chicken at the grocery store.
And then you show us a picture of it.
And it would be real.
And then you guys are so mad that it's real.
I think the couch is tearing us apart.
The couch is not tearing us apart.
It's making us very introspective.
The issue with the couch is just that you're in the middle, so you want to disagree.
Yeah.
You're so right.
Yeah, you're so fucking right.
Do we have a list we're supposed to be reading?
No.
No, this is a couch talk.
What are you talking about on a couch?
I thought that we were going to do a couch thing.
I thought we were reading a list of couches.
Oh, wait, I had something I wanted to read.
I had a poem I wanted to read.
Oh, is it about a couch?
Did you write it or did you find it?
I found it.
Oh.
I googled things to tell.
I googled things to talk about on a couch.
Look at how excited I am.
And for all for some reason,
all of the results were.
Is this a is this the dingler from Wayfair?
No, that's the one I have at home.
I have the dingler and it's terrible.
What the hell is that?
I hate my couch.
You just wanted to talk about your couch.
Let me just say this while we're on the topic of couches.
I hate my couch.
If anyone wants to give me a couch for free
and deliver it to my house, I will hang out with you.
My couch is S tier.
I will hang out with you weirdo.
Did you want to get my couch at my house?
It's kind of hurting my back.
Really? Yeah. In what way?
I think it's just because I'm maybe sit, move your butt back and sit up more.
This hurts me.
Be careful with the C4.
It's empty.
OK, I was going to say you're about to spill that all over the laptop.
But now I look weird.
You don't look weird.
I wanted to look more casual.
Look how casual I've looked the whole episode.
I've been completely casual.
You guys got the sides. The middle is hard.
Look at this.
I have to crane my neck. I know that's my issue is that I have to look at both of you.
Look at me. Look at how casual I am.
So I googled things to talk about on the couch because I knew we were going to do a couch episode.
Okay.
And for some reason most of the results were things your couch would say if it could talk.
Most of them were?
There were like three or four in a row in the first like ten results that were that.
And one of them was this which is like it's a cartoon but it's a poem.
The cartoon doesn't really add much so I'll just read through what it says on it.
Okay.
and it's called if your couch could talk.
And this is what it says.
I don't have arms and legs.
I don't this is before the poem part.
This is just the intro.
I don't have arms or legs.
I cannot speak.
I have no name, but I am at the center of their lives.
I've seen Jake develop every step of the way been there day
to day and as ever I'll still be here for the next chapter of
his life, which one of us do you think is Jake?
Whichever one of us is a baby that grows up into an adult.
I think a couch does have arms.
It does.
Yeah.
and the hands and legs. Depends on the couch, I guess. I have arms and legs,
but I cannot speak. I have a name and it's couch.
Here's the poem, and this goes throughout Jake's life. Okay.
I'll be here as the carrier of his toys and milk spillage.
I'll be here as the foundation of his first pillow village.
I'll be here as the helping hand during his first steps.
I'll be here as the desk when he studies for tough tests.
I'll be here as the banker when his wallet goes amiss.
I'll be here as the wingman during his first kiss.
I'll be here as the comfort when he begins a profession.
I'll be here as the witness for each career progression.
I'll be here as the peace from home when he moves on and I'll
be here as the storyteller every dusk till dawn.
I mean and that's over the course of 30 years.
Yeah, that depends.
Who has a couch that long?
Yeah, I mean unless you're getting like a really good.
So you see here he's six months old and he has the same couch all the way until he's
30. Well at this point he's not there but he's been trapped inside of a photograph above
the couch with his family. I'm seeing it. So that's just a fun interesting photo I thought
that could start a conversation about a couch. Well I guess what would your couch say if
it could talk? My couch would say "ow" because Mo scratches it. Yeah. And people sit on it.
My couch would be like "I love when you sit on me and watch things. I like your butt on
I like your butt on me. I like everything you do on me. I'm on your couch and I like your butt on me.
Please use your computer more on me and go on your TV more and playstation on me. Put your thing in my cushion. Put your thing in my crack.
That's what the couch would say. The couch is a pervert. The couch is a perverted object.
My couch would be like, I'm so hungry you haven't fed me once the entire time you've had me. Please.
All you have fed me is M&M's. I feed my couch. My couch is eating good.
Yeah.
Riblet.
Don't say farts.
Not farts.
No, but I drop stuff in there all the time.
Yeah.
Okay.
Accidentally.
What's the worst thing you've ever found in your couch?
Dust.
A headphone.
A nasty old headphone.
Yeah.
Bluetooth headphone.
Crumbs.
Yeah, I guess crumbs.
Dog hair.
Dude, I'm having this problem where there's so much dog hair in my house.
Every time I eat food, I just find dog hair.
I'm like, "Oh, I'm going to have to get rid of this."
I'm like, "I'm going to have to get rid of this."
There's so much dog hair in my house.
Every time I eat food, I just find dog hair,
and I stopped even taking it out.
I just eat it.
- Yeah, you just eat it.
That's fine.
It's got protein in it.
(laughing)
- I just eat the dog hair.
- We didn't have--
- There's too many of them in the food.
- You can eat dog hair.
- Yeah.
- That's, if somebody, are you guys weird about
if there's a hair at your food in a restaurant?
- No, I don't care.
- I don't care at all.
- It depends.
- It doesn't matter.
- It depends where the restaurant is.
If there's like a hair in my food at McDonald's,
whatever. But if there's like a like a hair at like a nice place, I'm like,
why will you tell me? But what they proved is just maybe I could get this
meal for free. Maybe I can be an asshole. Then you're a fucking Karen, mate.
That's a complete Karen. I am a Karen. Real men just eat hair. Yeah,
just eat it, bro. Yeah. How many? If you're in a loving relationship,
how many opportunities will you have to eat another person's hair? Exactly.
You know what? I'm rethinking my whole this is this is cheated. You can cheat.
That's cheating. Eating your waitress's hair is cheating.
But nobody's getting mad at you.
It's just a free... In fact, you have the opportunity to get mad at the other
person. By the way, you can still eat the hair. Say, "I ate your fucking hair."
Yeah.
I'm coughing. Pardon me?
Can you call the chef out here? "Hey, buddy, I ate your fucking hair."
"Hey, do you recognize this head of hair?"
Yeah, you put the hair in the food and I fucking ate it. What did you
suspect. Gulping the hair.
Good for you, I ate your hair.
Hey, notice anything about...
Notice anything about my plate?
Uh, no sir. Well, there's no
hair in it. You know why? Cause I ate
the fucking hair out of it.
Now I'm gonna grow a
mini you in my belly. I'm gonna grow
a watermelon in my belly.
That still scares me. Your hair is
seeds. Hair is seeds
for humans. Why are white
seeds okay to eat, but the
black ones will make a watermelon in your body.
It's due to the blackness of the seed
is like, because it's heavier, like a black hole.
Interesting.
Wow.
But, and then the biggest seed of all, the peach.
Yes.
You can't eat that.
You can't eat that because it's full of arsenic.
You can eat that.
Is there a white hole?
A white hole?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What is a white hole?
It's in space.
I figured this much, but what else about it?
I said yes immediately, but I don't know if it was in if it's real or in a book
about wizards. I read it. Yeah, just one of those things that you're like, well,
it's got to exist. Yin and Yang.
I definitely wasn't a white hole.
They just call it a hole.
It would just be would be a hole.
A white hole is a it's hypothetical.
Oh great back to hypotheticals.
people also hypothetically there's also the rainbow hole and the while in
general relativity as agnostic about the reality of white holes thermodynamics
gives the concept a hard no.
So a red hole couldn't exist. Hey, I saw a red hole
goatee
on the computer and the library. Come on, bring it up.
Bring it up.
Thank you.
I thought that was fine.
It was fine. I thought that was fine. You shouldn't be striving for fine. You should be striving
for striving for great. Standing. Great. Greatness. It is trying to be greatness. I think it was
actually great. You think that was great? No, it was not great. You should have said
white hole was goatee. That would have been white hole is goats. No, because the hole is
red. He's he's white. Pull it up on the TV. Pull it up on the TV. You can't pull it. There's
there's no TV app that has goats. What do you mean Roku Roku is it's not a device
screen saver. You could do that. I guess if you were at a Best Buy and you were
really funny. Yeah. Oh, I just thought of just to just a guy down the back. We
talked about this a while ago. If there was a painting, I could jump into Roku
City. Yeah, the original, the original painting of it that they developed Roku
city that was painted in the 1700s.
Roku City has too much shit going on.
Yeah.
That's why you don't want to deal with Godzilla and Borat.
Because I'm not sure I'm going to be able to come out of the painting after I go into it.
Yeah.
And Roku City is a whole ass city.
It's a city of movies and film that Cameron loves.
McDonald's is there.
They have McDonald's in Roku City.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Did they pay for that?
Someone hasn't been spending time looking at Roku City.
I did change it.
I don't have a retro.
I changed my...
I look at Amazon Fire Stick TV City.
We have our own city actually.
No, we don't.
Yeah, you have Jason Bateman's picture.
We actually do.
This is literally Philadelphia vibes right now.
Philadelphia vibes? What do you mean by that?
What does that mean? I don't know.
Just like a worse city?
There are so many different Roku screensavers that everyone gets hung up on Roku City.
Buddy, they got the jungle.
They got the wild west.
Wild West. They got romantic. What does that mean? Once we're done with this episode, I'm
going to show you all of the Roku. It's just people in love. In a city. It's pretty much
always a city, but there are different biomes and boroughs of Roku. If New York City had
a jungle borough, a sand borough, a desert borough, an arctic borough, a desert borough,
Dick Burrow
Biome Minecraft
This would be way better
Minecraft Biome
This would be a way fucking better place
Oh yeah
Yeah
There has to be some place on earth where all of the different biomes meet
They have, every place they have like that, they have all, all they have, the cities where
states meet, you know, they have Texarkana
Yeah
They got the four corners
Yep
Yeah
All that stuff, they waste it all on a place where it's the same on every side
Where is the four corners?
That's what I'm saying
It's between four states
What's four states?
It's like
Is one of them Utah?
Utah, Nevada, New Mexico, Colorado? No? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. It's
four of the five of Utah, Nevada, Colorado, New Mexico, and Arizona. It's four of those.
Yeah. And I don't know which four. And they should build a city there. They tried. Corner
City. Yeah. It was called Corner City. They tried to make it. The problem was you got four
states. Heavy Mormon populations, four times the taxes, four times the taxes, heavy Mormon
population so no bars are getting made. I'd probably jump into the Mona Lisa and then I'd
jump into the Mona Lisa. And then I'd motorboat it. I'd jump into the Mona Lisa and motorboat.
No I wouldn't do that. No. But I mean I would maybe jump into the Mona Lisa. I guess you
I just got to say one of the paintings from Mario sixty four yeah,
but I jump in a bomb on world battlefield. Is it the very least I
could collect stars in there? Yeah,
stuff to do there. I know that yeah for like Mona Lisa, that might just be
it. That's that is it. It might just be one bitch. Who is she in front of
this strange white bald guy who's appeared behind Mona Lisa
where they would not be saying I was strange. They say that it would
literally stop being called the Mona Lisa.
It would start being called.
There's a speech bubble from you in the background that says,
"I thought I could go in a different place.
I thought there would be more in here."
You can't get past the frame.
And then it becomes an even more important painting
because it's the first time that somebody's done a speech bubble.
Yeah.
Is there...
Am I misremembering the Mona Lisa, but is there a river behind her?
Does she have a slight smile?
She has no smile.
I don't know if there's a river.
There's some kind of landscape behind her.
Yeah, there is a landscape.
Yeah.
never really understood why that one popped off so hard because it was the
first time that there was ever a painted woman back then. It was not,
everything looked like balloon animals and tomato soup cans.
They didn't quite figure out how to realistically paint a subject quite yet.
But didn't they discover the Mona Lisa only like two years ago or something?
Yeah. And at some museum or I did at least.
(laughter)
I discovered it actually while watching Pink Panther, I think.
I think that they didn't discover it, they knew about his other paintings for a long time.
He drew that guy with all the arms.
He drew tons of shit, man. This guy was a genius.
He also made, he was the guy that first thought of the airplane.
Which guy did Mona Lisa? Was that Mr. Lisa?
That was Mark Lisa, yeah.
Are you guys stupid?
Literally Leonardo da Vinci.
Really? Yes. I think I knew that. He wasn't a painter though. He was an
inventor and he went into pregnant woman's bodies in an adventure. He
shrank down.
That's why that movie... Not only was he a painter, or not only was he an
inventor. That's why that movie Shrinking Da Vinci is existing, is exists.
I don't know what that is. Shrinking Da Vinci? I've never heard of it. He
shrinks... Cameron just explained it. He shrinks down and sneaks into pregnant
woman's bodies and he... What? You haven't seen this movie? Is it a movie?
You've never seen shrinking Da Vinci?
What is the purpose of having the...
He's a scientist, he does experiments.
Yeah, he tried to invent a plane back in whatever 1430, flying machine.
Actually, a heliotrope.
But then he accidentally invented a shrink ray that only let him into pregnant women's bodies.
It would actually make a lot of sense if...
Because Da Vinci, the whole thing is like, oh, did he...
It's like the Shakespeare thing, it's like, did he exist or was he...
Nobody knew him.
But what if it was because he was really, really small?
He was really small and he shrunk himself with a ray.
But he was getting all up in pregnant women's dead bodies.
I don't know about that.
Their dead bodies, yeah, that's the problem.
Are you for real?
Yeah.
This is an actual truth that you learned on the History Channel?
This again might be, well again, this might be, well, first of all, nowadays,
you're watching the History Channel.
Yeah.
It's not going to be telling you, you're not going to be learning about Leonardo
da Vinci, you're going to be learning about ghosts and paranormal UFOs,
which I know from watching it a lot recently, which they have no history on
there at all, but you watch it at four in the morning. I think that this might be
something that's... No, I watch it at completely in the middle of the day.
They don't ever... No, no, shrinking Da Vinci is on at four in the morning. I'm
thinking of the Travel Channel, which is also only ghosts now. Yeah. But I think
Leonardo Da Vinci was...
I think he was... That was one controversy among... With him, is that he
was always going into pregnant women's bodies. Why do you keep saying going
into. I don't want to say anything gory or nasty.
Yeah, it's all it's all alleged and he doesn't want to. Well, I could. I think it
was true. Well, you have to say allegedly because as people. Well, you don't have
to. It's been a long time as a state, though he has left the world. He doesn't
have an estate anymore. He hasn't. Oh, he has an estate, buddy. But is this true
that he was completely acting up or acting? What he was doing was maybe OK in
terms of science but not so great by today's terms of what's okay to do to a pregnant woman's
body. There's one thing that's okay to do to a pregnant woman's body. Deliver the child.
You don't think they have sex? Fuck no! No, you can't have sex if you're pregnant. Fuck
the baby up there, you fucking scramble the baby. Oh okay. Mr. Big Dick. Mr. Big Dick going
all the way up. I'd probably fucking kill the baby with my huge fucking car. Yeah, the
The baby's gonna come out with like a split head.
Let me tell you, you can't do that.
You can't do that.
Not even if my dick is small enough that it's not getting
anywhere near. If your dick is so small that you only, you
only are, you barely, you don't penetrate, you just are in
like the labia area.
If it's just kind of like a head, you have a dick in it.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
That's, I mean, we should have known.
That's what shrinking Da Vinci is kind of all about.
So he can shrink his penis small enough that it's okay to have sex with a
pregnant woman? I think he was dissecting people, though.
Was he actually dissecting pregnant women? That's what people did forever.
That's how he made his famous drawing of the circular man.
Oh. The Latruvian man. Yeah. That makes sense. That's what the circle was
from a pregnant woman's stomach. That's how he was able to develop that shape.
Yeah, he started with that. He was trying to develop that. He traced it.
Oh, okay. He had a... He put her on her belly and then, like,
drawing a hand. Yeah, and then he was in his laboratory or his workspace
or whatever and he was sweating. He's like, "Fuck, how am I going to get a
triangle?
How the fuck am I going to do the triangle?" I did this, the circle's
obvious, you just do a circle around the guy. And that's when his assistant
pinhead walked into the room.
His assistant Dracula smiled widely at him. "Need anything, boss?" "Oh, my
goodness." "Actually, yes. Would you come lay down on this paper table?"
His assistant Johnny Bravo.
(laughter)
- And that's how he invented a Dorito.
- Yeah.
Da Vinci, that's why they're called Doritos.
- Da Rito.
- Da Rito Da Vinci.
- Da Vinci Da Rito.
(laughter)
- This is my son, his name is Dorito Da Vinci.
- Dorito Da Vinci, that's a pretty good name.
That is a good name.
- I am Dorito Da Vinci.
- All right, the couch is, it's made me loose.
Really made me relaxed, man.
I've been so calm this whole episode.
Usually I'm freaking the fuck out.
My heart rate has dropped.
Look at my hand.
All the way from its normal rate of 28 beats per minute down to 15.
Look at how still I am.
I have a really not still hand I think.
I could be doing surgery.
But I did just take pre-workout so I have tingly itches all over my entire body.
Oh yeah, that makes sense.
Your hand is not twitching.
Whoa.
I think my hand is moving.
Look at how my fingers look like.
Whoa! How do you do that?
I've known people who can do that in my life.
I've never known somebody, well I guess I did know somebody.
It's called skydiving fingers.
It does look like some skydiving fingers.
Look at that. Oh my god, that looks insane.
That looks incredible.
That does look crazy.
Alright, um.
Well I think that's it.
Go check out, I am going to be in Washington D.C. with
When are you in D.C.?
24th through the 26th opening for Mr. Freedland.
I think that's this weekend, right?
No.
No, next weekend.
And then I think the weekend after that, at the end of the month, the 28th through the
31st, I'm going to be in Pittsburgh and Baltimore opening for Girl God.
Grace and April.
Me and Patrick, always the openers, never the headlines.
We're never headlining.
We should do a back to back show where I do like five minutes.
Next month I'm going to be opening for Blink 182.
You're shitting me mate.
Doing spoken word punk rock.
Spoken word punk rock but you're just doing like slowed down.
Have you seen that video?
Spoken word with guitars and drums.
They already do spoken word punk rock.
It's called Adam's Song.
No it's called Mother's Day.
I was listening to that song this morning.
Mother's Day or Adam's song.
Adam's song. Yeah.
Remember Mother's Day?
That's a funny one.
I'll be sucking and fucking and touching, sucking and fucking.
And also there's
it's Mother's Day.
Or Blink 182.
Blink 182 did so many funny songs.
I want to fuck a dog in the ass.
That is some funny shit.
What's the other one?
There's the.
I think it's called Family Reunion.
Yeah, Family Reunion.
It's Christmas Eve and my grandpa just ate 65.
In that live album they do a version of "What's My Age Again?"
"Where's My Asian Friend?" he says there.
Dude, they were on top of the world.
My buddy Jake, I think I told you guys about this, but Jake's got a tattoo of Tom DeLonge from the Mark, Tom and Travis show.
Like the cartoon, like right there.
That is such a sick tattoo.
That is beast.
Alright.
Okay.
Well, we'll see ya, catch ya on the next couch.
I'll see you in Pittsburgh or Baltimore.
And Caleb will see you in our nation's capital.
Bye!
Richmond, north of Richmond.
Ice Spices being around for one year
is basically the blink of an eye, the flash in a pan.
Wow.
So that's when people say one hit wonder,
it's like, yeah, I wonder why.
I wonder if they're going to have another Big Bang.
Big Bang. Wow!
Yeah, because again, that's rocks and geology and dinosaurs.
Yeah, let me, that's if there was a science,
maybe the science equivalent of a youth pastor, he would be like,
"You guys are all obsessed with these one-hit wonders.
Let me tell you about the real one-hit wonder, the Big Bang."
Jesus Christ.
There is a science teacher, I think, is it?
Well, this would be more of a guy.
Middle school science teacher.
Yeah, but he was kind of exactly analogous to a youth pastor
in that he's at a science church and he's dressed up.
So what you're proposing is sitting on the chair backwards and you can imagine maybe
even just the way that every youth pastor looks in a meme or video.
So what you're proposing is a, I like this idea, a science church with a science youth
pastor.
Yeah.
And he does all the youth pastor joke meme stuff but it's for science.
Has everyone done that?
Wow.
Yeah but they don't have like, they don't have like science class like they have Sunday
school.
It's actually...
Let's do a quick check in on what's going on in everyone's week.
It'd be called SSS Science Sunday School.
It's less...
There's less danger that he would be able to...
Science Saturday.
Because they're not observing the painful Lord.
The youth science pastor wouldn't be molesting the kids because he has...
He'd be doing...
He'd be molesting him.
...an intimate knowledge of the human body and he knows how to pleasure himself.
That's right.
Without the help of another...
Maybe he would be doing...
Yeah.
He would have a wife or a husband.
He could be touching and playing with the little frogs.
They're even smaller than a kid.
Or he's poly.
He feels even more power over...
weirder because it's maybe it's just like poly people are not
scientific. He would be instead of no less than the emotional.
They're not doing experiments on the kids.
He would be doing to experiments on twins psychologically.
Yeah, seeing and physically physically cutting them open
seeing if they have been joining them and joining them.
I'm joining them taking them apart.
Conjoining them apart.
Yeah, exactly.
Conjoining them.
Every combination.
Conjoining them at different parts of the body like the foot
or the ankle or the hand.
- If you were conjoined to your twin
at the bottoms of your feet.
(train horn)