I
am little today. I'm really just get up bigly get up in a bigger way. You're
also vanishing into the background in a funny way. Oh yeah. I made it worse. We
left
this day right there. Don't move a muscle hold on. This is how big I'll be.
Do I get to be big today? Wait hold on I'll be big
I'm at maximum height actually. You can be big any day you want to. If you don't understand
what I'm saying. You guys are down here. I'm so small that I'm dead. I'm taking this away
from you. You're not allowed to have this microphone, but I am. No, nobody's allowed
to have it. Why did we buy this? Jubio bought that for you for your birthday. Is that true?
Isn't it? Did you buy this for me? Yeah. That's extraordinarily sweet. Get a look at your
years ago. That's like
a concha. That's how sweet that is a concha a conch shell. Is that what you
said? No, what's that? Is that no? It's not called a chancla. Are you thinking
of the chancla? I went to elementary school. I think a concha is a kind of
sweet bread. Yeah, yeah, it is look. Oh, my God, I was right. I remember having
this. I went there's a Mexican bakery in Wilmington that I used to go to like
every once in a while and I went one time and this always looked so delicious
Contra is mid and then I ate it. It was terrible. Contra is mid. Why do they
make it different colours? They all taste the fucking same. Is it just bread?
Is it in Mexico or is it just made here?
It's a little dry. You're supposed to, like, have it with, like, coffee. Oh,
so it's, it's like Mexican biscotti. That explains why it was mid, 'cause I
ate it dry. So, so it's not even a food, it's an ingredient, that's what you're
telling me. It's a stirrer. And that's your, that's your... I mean, I mean, you
could say the same thing for donuts. Shut the fuck up. You can't say the same
perfect for done. You're supposed to make doughnuts with brides and grooms on
top. That's how it is true. Yeah, they make doughnuts. I don't know. There's
also nowhere near as dry as a con that's true. A doughnut is a doughnut isn't
even dry at all. Yeah, my my there's some types of doughnuts might be dry.
I see you. That's a failing of a specific doughnut. I've done it as a
form. My concha dries up when I see you. You have a concha. Yep, and it dries up.
Oh yeah. When you see me, I mean that's nice. I guess I would be. I wouldn't
I want you to get wet when you saw me. Is that some kind of slaying in Mexico for
pussy is is girls getting wet like boners to they get it where they have to
stand up in front of class yeah and they have a wet ass. They have a wet ass, a
wet ask him sitting in it the whole time yeah, but in the mornings you sit there
and you're like oh my God on the bus at seven. I take a plane. Are you like oh
fuck I'm why am I randomly wet as fuck on this plane
randomly wet. I think they do. We need this info. We never had a girl on the
show. That's not true. That's not true. Oh, we've had a few girls. We've got
thousands on the girl show on the girls. We're the girl show. No, we're not that
we're the girl show. Now, apparently, according to Caleb, that we've had a
thousand girls on the show. I'm just curious about women's bodies and I
think I randomly wet. We okay. We should just have one. We should have like
Dr. Ruth or somebody come on and explain every single who's Dr. Ruth. She died.
Oh, she's dead. Then who's the old lady who talks about sex? She died and she
passed on the Supreme Court to the conservatives. Oh, you're right. She was
being bloody selfish and decided that she wanted glory. She decided she wanted
the glory of officiating a wedding. Yeah, that is. And it gave her COVID-7000.
That is so funny actually that. Her soul teleported to Jupiter. Those people's
their wedding decimated. It was not their wedding that killed Ruth Bader
Ginsburg. It was it was their wedding that killed Roe v. It was me. It was
Cameron. I dropped a germ in her mail slot.
Yep, he put he delivered when he dressed up like a mailman and he had a germ in
a little while. I had it in a vial of a germ, a little bouncing with tweezers,
green germ.
He said, buddy, listen, germ, there's a really old lady.
I heard the germ had blue hair and was a liberal. I didn't want to do it. Well,
that's why that's why he screened it. He made sure it was a really nasty
mucinex germ yeah and not a SJW germ. It was by the way, which is Cove in one
doctor. Fowchee has been creating a shade. They got green germs on mucinex.
This was a red germ. Oh, well, I'm not just saying that because it was
politically like on the red end of the spectrum, but because it was dangerous
yeah, yes, and also very hot. Exactly like red yeah. Why would you choose red
be your politician color. Right? Well, I guess red means strength. But red doesn't... When
you look at color theory... You say red, I think of blood and not just that. I think
of Nazi Germany, Hitler. Yeah. I think of... The Rising Sun. Yeah. That's true. They should
have thought of that when they were founding the GOP. I guess it just makes sense because
it's Republican red. Then it's Democrat blue. It should have been... Democrat denim. Well,
dark blue denim, Democrat denim, because they're so red. And you know what? I like denim. Whoa.
Okay. Yeah. That's right. I'm a I'm a lib. Okay. American apparel. Yeah. See, I would
have done either white or black. Yeah. White versus black is how you would have done politics.
No, that's not a good idea. Maybe. Oh, actually, here's a great idea for all the same color.
You just said you want a rainbow party.
Because they're the same exact party.
Rainbow is all one color to you?
Yeah, well it's every color in one.
No.
Or brown I guess is that.
What are you saying?
We should have done a brown party.
Yeah.
There's the green party.
Yeah, which by the way, just because I want you to have a new color doesn't mean you need
to name your party after the color, asshole.
Yep.
And just because I voted for you when I was 17 doesn't mean you can send me mail.
when you were 17 you did voter fraud. I did voter fraud. I was 19. When was the election?
It was 2015. I think I was 18. I think I just turned 18 because my birthday is on the 23rd.
Are you guys excited for politics to come out? God damn it! The Hungry video was not
even real. No it's real. It's real. Just say it's real. I saw a Forbes.com article about
don't believe for fucked up man. I believe part of the videos with whoever's
voicing it over. They don't say they say
hungry. That's the that's the secret. That was the one hung. We have the
obvious funny part, but is so funny when you see love this about you that your
mind just always goes to the
details. You're like our slash movie details. You're like a video details,
movie details. That's a good reddit that you should make just our
details. I'm so hungry,
hungly we need a see that, but anyway that goes back to what we're saying
this guy, Rhonda Santas, he's not even funny yeah. The only the funny, funny
thing, him somebody else did somebody was making him don't get on his ass.
Somebody was bringing him back to it. That's all I'm going to say bring him.
I'm going to do it's like this. I bring him back, bring him back, make him just
something I don't care what he is. I just want to be into in something again and
you have to I don't care again. I don't care what it is. It doesn't have to be
the number one spot. It can be any other spot. He should get the unplugged
controller. He should be like the
queen in who
shall not be named
Donald Donald Trump needs to be a he shall not be elected a queen style
smart like like head of head of the state yeah right figure head a figure
head where we made and I'm fine to pay. I'll pay for him. I don't give a fuck
sure yeah, whatever I'll buy his his no because you know, it's really going to
pay fine. What I was really going to pay is women in POC.
I don't think if he was the king, okay, then we'll just have we'll just get rid
of all the women in POC and the government and then you won't have
anyone to mess with right. That's a solution. He can't assault any, but any
minute. Yeah, I get rid of every single one and all the fall. If you make him
his own office,
no, we just clean. So it's an office that's full. Here's what I think. We
build him an office inside the Lincoln Memorial. He should be in space.
Now, they have a little door under his seat. He should have a matrix style
room where he has a screen of everything he needs to see. Did you just say
they have a little menorah? Do they have a little door under Lincoln's seat
in the Memorial? I don't actually know. I don't know anything. Everything
I've learned about Washington, D.C. is from National Treasure. I was just about to say
I feel like if they had a door under there, there would be some kind of crazy secret, maybe
his head, Futurama style. I think, okay, I honestly think... And only the 1% get to talk
to Lincoln. I honestly think if I could be, if I had access to any single building in
the entirety of the restricted United States, I don't think I would do Area 51. I think
I would do the Smithsonian because I guess they got some crazy shit. I would put on
Jim Henson sweater. Yeah, they have different butterflies that we've never
seen. I would go into the CDC and I would be going in and just opening all the
doors and walking around. They don't keep the viruses behind a door.
They keep them behind three doors. What do you, yeah, what else would they keep
in a box? One door to decontaminate and then two doors.
They have the gloves so they can play with the virus. Yeah, that does seem very
fun. I remember, I would love to see like
what putting a germ in somebody's body does to them.
It does. We already know. You know what that is.
I would love to be the guy at the CDC whose job is to walk up to people with the bear mace
and just spray a whole virus at a person. That's not a job.
They wear a hazmat suit. The person is sitting in a padded room and is like, "Oh, thank God.
Thank God you guys."
"Thank God I'm being bear sprayed."
"Thank God. Thank God somebody's coming in here to help me. I don't know where I am. I
don't know how I got here."
And then you spray them with the virus.
isn't it? Have you guys ever been, have you ever needed money bad enough that you were
thinking of doing a human trial? Yeah. Yeah, but you don't get paid that much. That's the
problem. You get paid like 200 bucks and maybe you die and maybe you're forever red. I did
a human trial. Look at me. I did some research stuff in high school. Now I'm shrunk. Did
you do like for high school though? No. You did like it for money? Yeah, they paid me.
What'd you do? They MRI'd me for one that I think was about, I think I was the control
group for one that was about alcohol like I didn't drink and they wanted to MRI.
So they MRI me and that might have even been middle school because I think I was
listening to American Idiot and the MRI machine. That's my they let you listen
to fucking music. They put a CD into and they play because it makes a terrifying
noises. Yeah, it does. They play music inside. Yeah. Well, I mean that's kind of
a cheat and then I did a bunch of ones that were just like I don't even know it
or remember what they're for, but it's just a bunch of ones. They ask you a
a bunch of questions and you do all the like yes. No, I got a survey taken when I
was
eight years old down at the public pool is my mom. My mom like
I think she did it. So I would have like 50 bucks for my birthday, but like your
kid do a cannonball
who can do the best belly flop in the entire pool, but I remember I'm pretty
sure the woman who was like proctoring this survey was asking me about Taco
Bell.
If I remember correctly, I don't remember what it was. I just had a
Taco Bell survey.
I swear to God. And you took a Taco Bell survey at the pool and
you're saying these are the same thing? These are similar, yeah. These aren't
similar at all. These are similar because they were testing... He was the
control for an alcohol test. That's the same... And you took a survey for a
that is that is my brain chemicals. That is the same thing. Well, you did it.
You did a thirteen year old, a thirteen year old being made to like
being the control to talk about Taco Bell, a thirteen year old being the
control for an alcohol test is nothing
you you talking about you were asked about the Mexican pizza. You're probably
why they got rid of it. Have you ever been an MRI? It gave me scars. I've
I've never been in it. Really? No. Oh, but it is scary. It's really scary. I
don't especially because, you know, if you have any metal on you, you will die.
I don't think that I would do a metal. If I had cancer, I would not be doing
radiation. I would not be doing chemotherapy. I would I would breaking
bad it. Yeah, dude.
That shit, it's too expensive. I wouldn't go to the doctor. That's all I
mean. Yeah, he goes to the doctor, but only a few times. I don't go to the
doctor like at all. I haven't been in a long time. Me neither. Last time I went
doctor. I want to put her on blast to be honest, but I do it wait. No, talk
shit, talk your shit. No, he's being a big person right now. Talk is no, no,
no, I want to hear that. I have another appointment in August. I'll do it after
that. Okay, see if she's got one more chance this and I'm going off and I come
in for this appointment. Oh, you have it could get dangerous. You have a new type
of cancer. Yeah, something could happen. She's going to I told you what she did to
me. She put me in a trap. What we talked about this. I actually don't remember
that's what happened. She put me into a glass box. Yep. Oh, I kind of remember
this, but it's a bit. He was put into a glass box and then he walked out and
they he wasn't supposed to leave. Yeah, I don't remember. They put me in a
glass, but I said I have. I told her I had asthma. Oh, that made you breathe.
And she was like, well, I don't I'm not sure if you have asthma or not. I've
had asthma my whole life and she's like, well, I'm gonna have to do some
gross on you and she gave did saw trap tests on me for a day. Really? And the
results were Yep, you have asthma and then they charged me hundreds of
I hate going to the doctor and the dentist in New York City.
I hate going to the doctor and the dentist anywhere in the entire world.
I hate the dentist a lot.
Me too.
But the dentist in New York, it's all like, it's either like the tiniest private practice
and you can't tell because it just looks like somebody's building or it's like some place
that has just pictures of teeth everywhere and things that are like the...
I'm never going to find a new dentist again in my life.
if I have so much I can't go back to my family dentist, I'm never going to the
dentist. Yeah, I got to go to you don't go to New Hampshire to do my people
didn't go. I do for years. I need the dentist pretty bad. One of my crowns was
put in incorrectly and I didn't know and there's been food getting stuck in
there. How fancy are you? The food be like
yeah,
that's what I'd be saying. Yeah, no, then I got that. I cracked that tooth and
I've had to be like I have a temporary feeling put in there and it's
the crown be like
talking to the other teeth. I wish yeah, the other teeth be like yeah, yes,
master, yes, master king of all the I wish I had a king tooth that told them
what to do. Then they would say they would say promise you have fight all the
infections. Yeah, you have a you have a power struggle. Yeah, you have a
shrewd elism. This side of my mouth and this side of my mouth are warring. You
have a blood mouth and a crypt side of your mouth with teeth. I had that
infection on my wisdom tooth that was so crazy. His wisdom to be like no. His
was in like well,
he's thinking oh yeah. Well, yeah, I was having the infection. Plus he can't
think
I'm infected because of my infection. I had a dream about saw the other night.
We're a new one really saw x. Maybe I'll include the trap that I thought of
- Paw Socks. - In my dream.
- Could be about them, could make the whole movie different.
- Well, this is something where I had this thought
and then I actually, have you ever had a thought
and then you have a dream about it?
- No, yeah.
- I had this thought and then I had a dream that was Saw
and it was my, the Saw trap was that I had to explain,
I had to explain stuff to my dad was the Saw trap.
So I had to explain like a 240 hertz monitor to my dad
or else I'd die.
And it really scared me when I woke up.
- Yeah. - I woke up crying.
crying wake up because like the the punishment was that your dad thought
you were gay. No, I'm in this. I'm in the bear thing and then they he's like
call your dad on the phone and try to explain to him. I don't think high
refresh rate gaming monitor. I feel like you're dead. Explain anything to
anybody. I was under threat of death. I don't know that that whole thing just
seems like your dad would just go. Oh, okay, but I had to really get into
the has to explain. Okay, he takes a test at the end. Oh, got it. Got it. Okay,
which that is scary. The idea of having to explain are you allowed to say that
you're going to die if he doesn't explain it right, because it's because
my dad would get too nervous. He would he would keep him from doing it or the
scariest part is what if my dad's like okay, I don't care what if he takes this
as an opportunity to let me go and pass on to the next world right and he
doesn't give a fuck about me. What I'm thinking is like maybe he since you
can't tell him you're going to die or that saw has you maybe he's like he's
like yeah. I'll do the test and he doesn't do it like I'm at work. I'll do
the test. That's what he would do actually knowing my dad. Yeah, yeah, he
would be on the golf course. You have to basically be like no, this is so
important. There's different things if what if you called 911 and your dad
picked up
my dad would be true. I would hang up and call back to talk to someone else. I
would yeah, it's a conflict of interest. Yeah, and I the job of a 911 operator is
to decide whether the emergency is important or not and whether to send
people true and my dad's always going to send people. My dad, my dad would
I'd probably not send anybody. He would be like so if I call if I send an
amulet, it's going to be too expensive. You're just going to have to figure this
out. I'm just because you know I don't really I can't really figure out whether
I should be calling 911 or not because it's too close to home. So I'm calling
on one. I'm like I'm out of bread. I have a pb. I have j. I got no bread. I
saw an operator should say this is not an emergency hang up, but I call my dad.
My dad says you should go to the grocery store. He's tying up the line. Oh God, I
saw a guy the other day and I think he was faking dying on the ground. Yeah, I
me and my wife. We were walking by this guy and he was like and I normally I
would think he was dead dying in a real way, but he was on the ground and he
was he was completely lifeless and not moving at all and just kept doing this
well, but there was a crowd and at first I was like Holy shit, but then
there was a crowd around him that seemed to be like his family and every single
one of them. Nobody was helping them. They were all just arms cross looking at
a kind of like tapping your feel like oh my God, what the fuck is this like
saying like pointing at him, like yelling at him in Spanish going like
like pointing at him and screaming and then the fire department showed up and
all of his family, instead of like waiting to see what happened to him,
they just walked away.
So I am and I told my wife, I was like I think that guy's dying and she was
like wait, wait now that guy's faking it and then we and then we got a little
bit closer and he was as they're like loading him into the ambulance. He's so
he's fully like eyes open, pretending to be a dead guy for a while and then they
we're loading him into the ambulance and he goes like this. He goes oh and
starts grabbing his stomach, like it's a stomach.
So I just don't know if this guy like if they told and it was right in front
of a bank, so I don't know if he was like somebody was like trying to get
him to write a check or something and he was just like you had a fake die.
You have to get money. You have to get money out to pay your rent and he's
just like
well. First you try being completely lifeless and then you realize at some
point you're going to have to pretend to be alive again. So yeah, your first
instinct is to instantly die, but at some point there needs to be some kind of
symptom that you're actually having. So you hold your stomach, you go, oh, I
would get out of it. I would instantly pretend to be dead, and then when the
ambulance got there, because I didn't want to pay the bill, I'd just be like,
"Oh, my God, I'm sorry, guys. I thought I was dead. I died for a couple of
minutes there, but God told me to come back. God told me to come back and tell
you that heaven is completely different." Sorry, I got confused. I
thought I was dead, but I'm not. I actually completely live yeah. I live
well. That's what that's the only the only thing that made me. I'm a new guy.
I'm a new soul just came into my dead guy. What the hell am I? Who am I now?
What the fuck I've been jumping around different people. Do you guys want to
be my family? You look like me. Do you guys want to be my family, but you have
to forgive every debt that this old guy? Yes, I'm the same guy. I'm a different
guy. I didn't do any of that shit and I'm young yep, so I'm ready to fuck and
I'm from London
and I don't care about it's. Okay, that I said that in front of you guys,
because I don't know you yeah, I'm back and you're my daughter. I'm going to
fuck all your friends
right now, because I'm a brand new guy. I'm going to marry that woman. I'm
just somebody wants that run from two thousand and nine. Oh my God, I was
really I got to this guy's body. Oh, the one where him and Vince Vaughn switch
bodies. No Matthew Perry
it was Matthew Perry. Vince Vaughn is a different man entirely. He's the same
they are not the same. He's the same. He's the same. One of them is more
sarcastic than the other. They're both sarcastic. They are both very sarcastic.
Vince Vaughn, have you guys ever seen a picture of young Vince Vaughn? Yeah,
he looked good. He was hot. Crazy. Yeah, dude, in Psycho. He was so hot. Psycho
remake, he was a good looking guy. Dude, in Swingers, oh, he's good looking.
A real good looking guy. And then now he's,
I hate to say it, he gives me Fred Claus vibes. He does. He's doing cool
ass movies with S. Craig Zahler though, have you seen any of that? No. Like
sprawl and sell block ninety nine and never cost. No, your cell block nine
nine school. Those movies are his name is S Craig or is it as dot Craig S dot
Craig, okay, but you don't say the dot. It's just an initial. Yeah,
that would help me. I thought his name was S Craig. I was like, Oh, who is
this? Who is this?
You should watch
concrete. That movie's so cool. Is it about being odd? It's about two cops who
they do police brutality. It's Mel Gibson and Vince Vaughn. They do police
brutality at the beginning. There's a guy they get they get they get in
trouble and then they're like they're like fuck this. We need to make some
money on the side, so they go and try and stop a bank heist. I get in trouble
for brutalism. I know then the yeah the police keeps like I like if it were up
to me, I wouldn't I wouldn't do shit, but you've been caught one too many
times.
It's so the politics of the movie are so evil. It's so sick, it's cool, it's so
fucking cool. You know it and it's fun. It takes place in a fictional in a
fictional U.S. city called Bulwark.
Bulwark what?
Bulwark where? They don't say.
It's gotta be in the Midwest. So cool.
Vince Vaughn was in this movie a couple years ago.
It was made by
the guy who made all these
skate videos and tried to make like these
kids pay 700k to get their
footage back. Like you try to make
16 year old kids pay him 700k
because he's got like a Pharrell endorsement
and he did this crazy
Doritos commercial where he's like
his skate company was doing a collab with Doritos
and he was like you know the triangle
represents so much and they're like just doing shit like that but Vince Vaughn plays the dad
He did Phil Jackson?
What's that? The triangle? I don't know we should watch that video
of him talking about the Doritos stuff because it's like
the Doritos merch is like little doodles he made and it looks like
absolute horse shit but Vince Vaughn plays the dad in his movie
that's about a teenager going pro skating and he dresses like a 50s greaser for
some rare no like a 50s like so for some reason for some reason because it's cool
no it looks really bad shot it's that kid from I guess he the reason he got
this movie made was because he was like the consultant on mid 90s he like Jonah
Hill either hey I know you're I know you're I saw it in the theater I didn't
I'd seen it in the theaters. I saw it on Showtime.
I bet you brought your board.
No.
You did.
I will say...
You held it by your tr-
No, no, no, no.
You all grabbed it.
I will say the mid is- mid 90s is correct.
Now he can say it because Jonah Hill has been eaten by a shark throne.
I've been saying that's been bad forever.
Yeah.
I've been saying that's bad.
So why haven't you been saying anything about Jonah Hill?
Because I don't know too much about him. I know that he's fat.
You are mistaken, my friend.
He was fat, then skinny, then fat again, and skinny, and then fat again.
And guess what happens?
Guess what happens with skinny guys?
They do inappropriate stuff in relationships.
They really do.
And Cameron, I hate to say it, you're as thin as a fucking bean pole.
It happens when you go from fat to skinny.
That's why we've been calling you fat, to make you, to get that out of your brain.
To get what out of my brain?
Your misconduct.
My misconduct.
conduct. I do think that guys who go fat to really skinny are dangerous.
Well, because it's like being a great carnation, it's like waking up and being
like... I don't mean necessarily dangerous in a relationship, but I think
they just are in every sense of the word dangerous. Skinny to fat, real
paper thin to fat guy. Skinny to fat is a good man. Yeah. That's a great
man. That just means your life got better. You're as jolly as a horse.
That means that you learned about maybe different kind of ethnic foods.
exactly Jonah Jonah. He should be in like that. That's what that means.
Jonah Hill is like the text book, weight change guy. You wake up, you eat five
slices of paneer cheese every single morning,
because you're trying to broaden your horizons,
because you thought it was tofu because of the texture. Yeah, exactly. Realize
it's just it's just cheese. Yeah,
that's what they would you would use Jonah Hill to teach in a weight change
class. They would say, look at this example. This is what happens. This is
the model. Yeah. Yeah. He grew out that beard. There's like videos of him like
surfing and he's just, he's, bro, he's snaking everyone. What is, just shut up,
man. He's snaking me. What do you mean? Is he doing that? You said you surfed as
a kid. I thought you would know. What snaking me? I surfed like four times
when I was eight years old. Snaking's when you like cut off someone's wave.
No. No, wait, their wave? Yeah. How are they going to get another one? Getting in front
of somebody and ruining their shit. Oh, God. Oh, God. Blood. Yeah. That would be, if Jonah
Hill did that to me, I'm... That is a surfer's greatest nightmare. Pulled the chopper out.
Okay, imagine you're like a dude who surfs every day in like LA, then all of a sudden
fucking Jonah Hill is like snaking you, cutting you off. You'd be pissed. You'd be so mad.
I'd probably be so chill that I wouldn't give a fuck.
- Me too. - Yeah, that's true.
- I'd probably be so fucking-- - Dude, that's crazy, dude.
- I'd probably be so high on opium--
- Yo, is that Jonah Hill?
- That I wouldn't even notice.
- What is that, Superman?
- I'm in a movie, dude.
- I wouldn't give a fuck.
- I love Superman.
- That's the thing, you can abuse surfers all you want.
That's why Jonah Hill tried it,
but he didn't realize that this lady was a poser.
She wasn't even chill.
- She was a kook.
Wait, no, she's probably a nice lady.
probably nice about fine lady, breaking my silence.
I don't think she sounds like that. I'm going to be honest.
I don't know how that voice is funny to me. That voice is so stupid. It's the
funniest voice in the world.
he's a sick puppy.
No,
here's the thing. I don't understand. He's using therapy speak to you.
I don't know why more actors who get caught doing cannibalism. Oh, have you
guys watched the hammer documentary? There's a documentary. It's on. I think
it's on HBO or Netflix and it's called like the hammer effect or yeah,
it's
it's got a hammer. I don't know. It's some stupid as name about his name.
Yeah,
yeah, but I haven't one or me. I haven't watched it yet because I don't want it.
I literally the reason I haven't watched it is that I don't want it to be. It's
going to be yeah, it's going to be so much less interesting than literally
that's the one if he had done anything cool like actually yeah, anything we
would know about exactly. I don't I really want to document. I really,
really don't want to watch it and find out that he was like I mean he was just
a normal. He was a weird kinky guy who was abusive and wanted to do say weird
sexual. I wanted to stay him thinking he's Dracula in my brain. I don't want
it to be anything but that if it's anything but that it's really gonna make
me sad. Was he in Fifty Shades of Grey? No.
No, he was in I think he was in, he was in I think,
I think he should be gay. He played the driving cruder. He was
What did you send me the other day? Would you rather go to prison for life
or be the drag.
Or be stuck as the driving crooner forever.
Yeah, that's a pretty easy decision.
I was sending Cameron some hypotheticals the other day, and he didn't even message me back.
I was asleep!
I was asleep, but he texted me all night.
That's not an excuse.
You wake up in the morning and you answer them.
I did.
I asked him.
He did answer one.
I said PlayStation versus Xbox.
And he said PlayStation.
Cringe.
And then I said pizza or Crunchwrap.
No answer.
Sleep pizza.
do pizza and then and then he hours later while I was still asleep,
emphasize the question and then sent another one. How long did you sleep and
how long were you in the middle of night? Let me let me look, you know how
we what time yeah, he always gets home from something very drunk and text you
the worst hypothetical question. It's not the worst. How is that the worst
piece versus pizza versus those aren't even a that's nothing that's nonsense.
no eggs were as baked potatoes. He just want to make my phone buzz at three
am foods at all. You see why I'm not answering. No, that was it. Okay,
you are not asleep at nine thirty six PM. I probably was. I've been having
some trouble sleeping nuggets or tacos. That one is the closest to an equivalent
food. I'm just not I'm just if I wake up and I see that you were
texting me that in the middle of the night and I wasn't responding and you
emphasized it. I'm not responding to you. You don't you're not getting that
I don't get why you wouldn't want to answer these. Then he said it's crazy
to watch Amanda Bynes clips and taken how effervescent of a performer she was
and how she totally her surrealist brand of humor took over my generation,
literally human analog to sponge Bob, an incredible contribution to culture. She
deserves the greatest care and respect.
What is that from
something I thought of
I don't remember. I copied a piece of that from somewhere
Amanda Bynes, she used to have it like that.
Yeah, she was funny.
Dude, Amanda Bynes was funny as hell.
You know what was--
She was human Spongebob.
Who the fuck says that?
There's a sketch on the Amanda show I remember.
I remember, yeah, Maha, Tony Pajamas, but I remember being six years old and
like I didn't realize like it was supposed to be a parody of like a
commercial and I saw Meatloaf Crunch and I was like, I like meatloaf. I like
cereal. Oh, that's a perfect combination.
I would eat that. I wanted to eat Meatloaf Crunch so bad. Was it Mad TV or Amanda Bynes
show? The Amanda show rather. That had the soap opera. Moody's Point. Moody's Point used
to make me cry. Oh wait, because the dad was stuck in a hot air balloon? It literally would
make me cry every time it came on. I was such an emotional child. Wow. They should not be
be allowed to do that man. What make a fake Dawson's Creek? The part where his
her dad's in the it's sad. It's not that sad. He's stuck he's gonna fucking die.
No no doesn't her dad know her mom's in the hot-air balloon that's her dad loses
his big toe or something yeah it's like a huge. Oh I didn't realize how much I
remember of Moody's Point. That is crazy. Dude just the idea that your mom or any
any parent really. If you have any variations. My mom is stuck in a hot air balloon.
Bro, I am eating chips every meal.
I would, you would not feel good about that. If your mom was stuck in a hot air
balloon somewhere way above the stratosphere. I would feel good for the first two days.
No, you wouldn't, dude. That's Jimmy Neutron movie vibes. That's Jimmy Neutron movie.
You're ripping it off. You just copied Jimmy Neutron to the movie. Great. I
watched that movie so many times. That movie made me cry, too. That made, you
know what also, what part of it made you cry? The aliens were too hungry. The aliens were too
when she's in the shower. Who the hell is she?
You know what? What are you talking? Sheen? You think that's a name? You know
it made me real hungry, though, was
seeing those green guys turned into eggs, turning fried eggs. I end where
Carl eats the egg. I thought that what is that? What is that egg holder that
eats the egg out of? Oh, that's a British thing. Yeah, I never saw. Well,
guys, you can dip them in the piece of toast. You all remember Poultra? What big
chicken monster? Yeah, yeah, yeah. That was so cool. I remember Sepoultra. And it
goes down. Yeah. One of my, one of my mom's friends. Your mom was in Sepoultra?
No, one of my mom's friends, I told him that I liked, like, Black Sabbath when I
was nine and he showed me Sepoultra. They're sick. Yeah, I never listened to
them though. They're cool. He was a grown man who had snake bites. I'm the kind of
I haven't seen Snake Bites in a while. Me neither, but they are on the way back. I think the
last time I saw Snake Bites might have been in high school. Yeah, it's probably been at
Snake Bites in Monroe. I mean, you can see, I saw someone with a Monroe the other day.
That's not a good thing. You ever know anybody who had the girls who get the dimple piercing?
Amanda Bynes. Oh yeah, true. You knew her? I knew her, personally. I knew of her, but
I didn't know her. We ran in some of the same circles, but we never crossed paths. We were
hanging out in hipster clubs in 2012. Yeah. With the weekend. You weren't hanging out
with hipsters. I was a damn I was in these hipster clubs in 2012. I would see her going
to one door. I was doing Indie Sleaze crap. I would be in a hallway I'd see her going
to one door and I'd be going to another door. Then I'd come out she'd be going out across
the hallway to another door and then I'd like go into that door and she'd come out to another
one and then down the hallway. Then I would think I would think I'd see her then I'd turn
around and then it would be Penelope Taint. Her last name's Taint? Penelope from a band
to show. Oh, shit. Her last name was Taint, which funny AF to get that on to TV. That's
like Poker Face. Which you listen to that now. This should, this song should not have
been on the airwaves. This lady's pretending to be having sex with a woman. Fuck her face?
No. Yeah. You're thinking of If You Seek Amy. No, Poker Face. She says, Britney Spears. No,
Britney Spears. No, Poker Face is about a woman having sex with a guy and pretending
it's a woman. But she says "fuh fuh fuh" or "puh puh puh poke her face, fuh fuh fuck her
face." No. Yeah, she admitted that she said this. She said this. She did a, she said this.
Lady Garga? Lady Gaga, Lady Gargle, fucked a face. Lady Garga, fucked a face? Yeah, isn't
that awful? Wow. And that got. That really changes my whole perspective. That's like
how Fall Out Boy got away with saying "God damn" on the radio. This ain't a scene, it's
a god damn arms race. I remember that one. That's a good song. No it's not. That's a good song.
No no no no no. If you see K-Me though, that was on the radio. I remember that one. You
say that one fast enough, F-U-C-K-Me. I would not. I never thought Britney Spears was hot
man. Even when she was 17. And making those music videos or whatever. I didn't think she
was hot. Well I was younger than that Patrick. I thought she was weird. Yeah that's true.
I don't I didn't like her. I thought I loved Britain never did it for me. Yeah,
I was more of an in sync fan. I loved her music. Wow. You did not love her music.
I did. All right, drive me crazy. Okay, what did you prepare for us today that
we don't know about? So today, if you have looked, I have the I'm not talking
to you is the 250th episode of podcast about list and yeah. Oh wait, hold on.
That means we're halfway to 300. We're halfway there, guys. 500 we end.
You said halfway to 300?
Yeah. If we started at 200, yeah. We're halfway to 200.
Half of 200 is 250.
Half of 200 is 250? Half of that is plus 50.
If you're looking at it like it's a dollar. If you're looking at it like it's a dollar.
Right.
2.50.
that's two and a half right plus another half, which is fifty right would be
three. He's right that we only have one more half until we get to three hundred
half of something. Well, half is fifty or five. It makes sense in my head. So
then I will say it, but you did say it stills a halfway to three hundred when I
said two fifty. We're halfway to three hundred from two hundred. We're giving
him a hard time for this. He makes sense. It's not he's not a genius. No, he
never claimed to be a genius. He doesn't have to know. I've never claimed to ever be a smart
person. It's just a funny thing to say. It's not that funny of a thing to say. I don't
even know why we're, this is a waste of our time. He's getting anal retentive. Getting
anal retentive? Wow. And metrosexual. I'm not metrosexual. People used to say anal retentive
and metrosexual every single day for about five years. Anal retentive then became, oh
he's so OCD about that. And metrosexual became autism.
People say that guy is... People, we used to just, if somebody didn't know how to
match their clothes, you'd say they're metrosexual. Now you say, "That guy's
autistic." Last night,
my girlfriend said that she thinks that I have autism,
because I was stimming and I didn't realize it. What were you stimming? I
was just, I was sitting there just going...
- This fucking bitch thinks you're autistic.
'Cause you were singing?
You were stimming, you were singing.
- I guess I was doing it for really long.
- You're doing Patrick Lee-Lee-Lee
in the middle of the day
and she thinks that you're autistic for that?
- I was doing it a lot.
I was doing it a lot, I didn't even,
I was in the other room just doing that.
- I've had the Grinch song stuck in my head for two weeks.
I'm not stimming, I'm singing my song.
- I don't know.
I think--
- You're not autistic.
- I think that I should take a quiz right now.
on a web no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I think that I should die.
Alright, explain the two hundred and fiftieth episode. What are we doing?
What's the so let me ask you guys a question. What's the number one thing
that has got us to where we are list? That's true, but what's the more number
one thing questions to be? It's a quality equality. It's a quality. Oh,
it's not equality. Far from
humor. It's evil evil. You can't you can't get to two hundred and fifty
episodes without how that's two hundred and fifty, not even including the
patrion, not even that's true, not even including that at all.
You gotta be if you want to make it in this biz, you gotta be evil. That is
you have to be more so ruthless, ruthless, which is a subtype of evil. I
guess you're right. Yeah, you gotta be evil and I thought for the two hundred
and fiftieth episode because you know two hundred and fifty that's a lot
eventually we'll have to stop maybe a two hundred fifty two or two hundred
fifty three. Yeah. When we run out of space on our hard drive. I'm surprised
that so we're going to need we're going to need some other people to fill in
the gap when that happens. So I thought maybe that we could look at
you know if you're looking to create your own podcast empire. Yeah. Can you
click on the power point? This is when we this is where we become influential
how to act evil. Oh my God. So I found my God. Look at that super villain ass
name. The name is already as evil as they come. So here's the problem. I
found this how to act evil. It's about acting.
It's about preparing for a theater role, and I was pretty disappointed by
that 'cause it's all stuff how to read your lines, how to do your
costume, whatever. But... Can you give us an example? Can you... No, 'cause
it's all boring and I didn't prepare it. No, I mean, can you like
do... Can you just do like a... Like an off the dome evil monologue
with evil acting? No, because I'm not an actor. Well, you could probably do it. I
am. I don't know why you want me to do that. What is my what's my scenario?
What's okay? So the scene is that you are the evil ice cream man.
Basically, do you remember Max Keyboard? Yeah, we have two flavors today,
bone and blood.
That's my evil ice cream song. That was Woody the Woodpecker. Yeah, that was
I was what either would pick what's that
that again we do it more evil and more sinister.
Today we only have two flavors blind and bloody bone.
Okay, that was really good, but today is not an acting episode.
That's what I was trying to say here. This we're not doing how to act evil,
but what we are doing from how to act evil something that is attached to this
this wiki how is they have a really big Q and a section where people who found
this article type to ask their questions and the author answered them. Okay, so
these are people who found this wiki how clearly did not read it and are just
kind of asking free freestyling questions based on the name. I like this.
They're asking Alina Boko, Colovia, yeah, go, Vickova, Boko, Vickova. How do I
become super evil
acting selfishly without regard for the feelings of others will make you super
helpful. 196 said that was helpful. 41 people tried this and it did not work.
Yeah. It didn't work at all. I tried being selfish and it just didn't work at
all. I tried cutting in line, I was not super evil. Yeah, well, the point, the
sticking point is without regard for the feelings of others, because they probably
cut in line and were like, "Sorry." Yeah, I can't say that. Yeah. I don't think
you can teach evil, honestly. Well, no, you just, it's nurture. Yeah. It's
nurture. So, you just taught... Or nature. No, it's nature. Yeah. It's nature. I
think it's maybe a combination of nature and nurture, but the nurture is
large. I think it's opposite nurture, where someone has to be evil to you and
not to lack of nurture makes you
and the lack of nature. I think that kids who were put on baby formula instead
of fed from their mother's teat are probably more than 50% more likely to
become evil. Definitely, I nephew learned that he was breastfed recently and has
been making fun of his brother for also being breastfed. Well, that's a that's a
classic stones in a glass house kind of sit. It's a pretty funny thing to do,
though. I will say that is funny. I guess
I guess they got into an argument or something and he said yeah. Well, you
used to suck mom's boobs.
Sheesh
I didn't come back from that. I guess you did too,
but then you're you're not winning. Then you're just both on the same level.
Like there's no point even saying no, I didn't. I pretended
I pretend I put it behind my mouth and
can I have a high doll like voice and make it sound creepy. It is difficult to
make a high voice sound creepy, but it can be done practice speaking in a
squeaky voice, but weigh it down with a horse. Darth Vader, you can have a
whole high, dry this voice right now squeaky voice, but with a horse Darth
Vader tone
Whoa.
- Hi. - That's creepy.
Oh my God, I'm getting shivers.
- I'm getting shivers. - I'm gonna eat you.
- Oh my God. - That is scary, man.
- I'm gonna turn you into food.
- Into fruit?
- Into fruit.
You're gonna become a berry.
- This is just-- - A berry.
- Gollum.
- Yeah.
- I just realized.
- Yeah, it's just Gollum. - Not that impressive
'cause we've heard-- - Eat you.
- Wow! - Whoa.
- I'm gonna eat you.
- That's better.
This is an original kind of character.
- This is a frog.
(frog croaking)
- No, this is a-- - What do I, yeah,
I don't know the evil toad
say we have two flavors today, blood and
I guess I found out I'm not an actor. I'm more of a writer.
No, don't go really.
What
I thought of even an even better evil ice cream man. Okay,
oh my God, because the thing I would eat a bone ice cream blood
probably not yeah. Depends on the type of one, though I don't I've never eaten
that shit. It's not good enough to be ice cream. It is food, but you want to
have ice cream. I guess there's an ice cream place around here that does a
black sesame.
How can I be an evil person's sidekick? That's a that's kind of nice yeah. No,
that's I mean that's guys. This guy's a loser. Yeah, if you're already going to
already decided,
yeah, I've already decided to be evil and then you're like, but also I want to
a henchman. It's like you don't even have the kind of confidence needed to be an
evil mastermind. Yeah, you kind of just become
an evil person sidekick through like years of abuse. It's basically luck.
Well, this person says find someone evil and ask if they could use an evil
henchman to aid them with their evil deeds. Say you'll do all the dirty work
and you'll discard the bodies when asked. Okay, I mean that's pretty good.
I guess that's fine. That's good advice. That doesn't even tell you how to find
like no, you really need you need somebody and it could be anybody doesn't
have to be me who makes maybe some kind of like
Patreon Siri web series of how to get your foot in the door of the
industry. I mean that more than anything else. Yeah, 'cause this is fine advice.
A master class. How do you fucking find someone who's evil? They don't usually
like telling people that they're evil. So... Their evilness is actually displayed
through their actions. Which you need or you need some kind of detector,
but at that point tell it to your and make some money yeah also at that point
you're an inventor and you could be evil yeah. You don't really get a finders fee
for finding an evil person to reporting them to the police, because guess what
you'd be reporting the police all the time. Yeah, I mean we disagree on that,
but yeah sure
what should I eat if I'm evil eat anything that really makes your taste
bud pop being evil. You could also ignore all the advice about sugar,
additives, fats and everything else, or you could be extremely precise and weigh
every calorie and a shoe all sugars and fats really eat as you want your evil
and capable of thinking for yourself. This person is kind of saying that it's
evil to be big and fat yeah and eat whatever you want, but like that's the
thing. Don't you think somebody being more like the precision like what says
how I like a lector eats like who's that mother fucker that ate one P on death
row? It wasn't Hannibal lector as a real person. That was Hannibal lector
kind of like peas, he liked peas, he likes fava bean, skinny Fred, skinny Fred, yeah,
he was, he was a notorious serial killer with even one pea, he was, yeah, he had a
small stomach, yeah, and he drove him to evil, he killed all the workers at
Burger King, no, he wouldn't even kill him, he would cannibalize people, would
just eat like their one fingernail, yeah, and he'd be so stuffed, one fingernail
clipping, yeah, and he'd go, oh, God,
you filled me up, yeah, yeah.
How can I be a dark princess? That's a good question. Looked the part by
wearing dark clothes, do random evil acts, adopt an evil nickname and be
mysterious. This is the most bullshit advice man yeah. Okay, what's your
advice? Be okay, how can I be a dark? Here's how you do it first of all red
or red or black or red and black dress okay tiara made out of maybe thorns or
or ivory something some kind of material, you know or ebony or or day
day trick stuff, some kind of day trick. I don't know what that is, but yes,
something bad that is either white or black that has some kind of spell on it.
First of all, this is now you need specifics, right? You need a spell, you
do random evil acts, give out parking tickets, people are gonna pay them,
they're not gonna check. What about the evil nickname? Evil nickname?
Throw some out. The Queen of Shit, the Queen of Ass. The Queen of Ass, yeah.
the queen of our rated movies. Yeah, anything like that is going to be fine
yeah, because it just needs to be the queen of something evil or the princess
princess prejudice print yeah perfect dude. That would be a good super yes
dude princess fucking
normalizing stuff yeah, and normalize a d i e princess normalizing
heterosexuality yeah, exactly as princess normalizing monogamy exactly
princess vilifying prince. Here's what a lot of people think is
big snack for a lot of meals. The thing is also evil has changed every single
year of the world, so so evil this year, somebody could say guys, I'm princess
Christianity and honestly a huge portion of the American population would say get
out of my face. I spit on you. I actually want a chip into my left hand, some kind
of mark of the beast and then half the other half of America is like I want to
chip in my left hand and then put in my mouth. I'm a fat, so what the hell has
what happened to America, born, serum eating fat, chit after seed oil, all
that kind of a seed oil. That's a great.
Our codes on the restaurants on the telephone poles on computer and another
thing. If I have to show my Vax card before going into a restaurant, I'm
dipping and what the fuck of my fries and the fucking dip. I'm staying yeah
because I like that
and whose fucking idea was it to make the Roku app have a remote on it. See
that. Oh, let me use a regular. I don't want to use my phone. Oh, okay, I got it
guys.
You could be princess
activision or princess, a games, something as a blizzard. You could be
princess, DRM says blizzard, princess, DRM. See that's the thing evil is so
subjective, really good, evil, so subject that to some nerds in this world,
they're going to hear princess activision, princess DRM, assume that
you're doing micro transactions right. So some people hate micro transactions.
the other half hate microaggressions and the other half love micro greens and the
other half are microscopic. Yeah, exactly. Some people are short, some people are
vegan, some people are gamers and some people don't like microaggression. It's
all a spectrum, really. The spectrum of evil. Yeah. And there's also billions of
microscopic human beings in America and they're called sperms. Yeah. Life begins
at sperm. And you know what? Most of them die in a towel or a napkin. A towel? Why
maybe waste a towel. I don't know or waste your spunk. Hey, you gotta ask
these evil people. Yeah, you gotta ask these evil beings why they're putting
loads and towels. Oh, that's I would be princess planned parenthood. Yeah, yeah,
he p p p p p p p p p loans. A lot of evil people got p p p loans during the
plan. Demi lone wolf is just facts. You should I fight with everybody?
Not necessarily insulting and mocking people will probably be enough. Yeah, me
him got insulted and mocked the other day when we were. Oh yeah, before the show
some we got we got homophobically hate crime. He called us F. A. G. I. T. and
said he would put his cock in our asses because we were gay and he and he
wasn't saying it politely or propositioning you in a polite. No,
that's the thing. I said, Hey, yeah, that's the word. That's the word that
you say. Oh, motherfucking ass. Maybe his voice just sounds like that. He
might have. That's what I'm saying. He had a gay accent and he was like, I
I'll put your dick in my mother. He said, Oh yeah, he said he was gonna put our
dicks in his ass. That's what it really it was some very, I think he said both.
He said that I'm gonna do it both ways. Yeah, I think he said, I think he said
he was gonna do it both ways, but we were yeah, and then he just like walked
around my car a couple of times. He also did see us unloading like costume
and we looked a little gay. Yeah, it's gay about costumes. We did have a sword
though. We could have done the entire world. Where's costume?
that's what we should have done. We should have challenged him on guard,
but basically we both flighted instead of fight it, but but did you find him
to be evil? I think he maybe was. Did you find him to be evil? Yes or no? It
depends. Yes or no? He would be able to say yes or no. I think he was evil
because if you're saying no, that means that maybe he did have to fight with
everybody. Maybe insulting and mocking isn't enough. It wasn't maybe in today's
America. Maybe it's not enough. You have to resort to physical. You have to fight
with everybody, everybody. He was also kind of an old guy. Sure, we probably
could have fucked him if we wanted to, but we really didn't want to that bad.
No, I mean we had to go, we had a lot of tech we had to set up for that show.
I think the only thing that either of us said was I said, okay, yeah, that's
what you should say. That's all you can say, right? Yeah, you can't say like,
you say, okay, it's like
maybe he'll mistake it as like the go ahead, but go ahead man. I don't care as
as long as we're done by eight o'clock, I have to load in for this. Yeah, yeah,
you can do whatever to me. I'm fine with it.
What if I am evil, but I want friends and no one likes me? People generally
don't like bad or evil people. The purpose of the article is to help you
act evil for fun while pretending to be a character, not to actually become an
evil person in your everyday life. If you want to have friends, you should be
nice unless you can find other people who are also evil. Most evil people like
to work alone and not with the help of people, but that is totally your choice.
I love that this is like first half being like doing like listen this article
it's it's not real. It's about acting. You should be nice to people unless you
go with other evil people.
What I don't understand what if this person's already evil, why are they even
looking at this fucking article? They should be writing the article good.
Yeah, true my two cents, but yeah, if you're evil, you have to have evil
friends or else you have a war on your hands. That's no you would not be
getting along with folks or you can be have a good friend and keep them close,
be secretly evil. But keep them closer. Yeah. The most evil thing you can do is actually
I think maybe be evil. Right? For sure. But also have a second life where you are nice
a la Barry. Do you think evil guys get on World of Warcraft and they play the good guys?
Yes. Because they want to feel like. Because they're so evil in person. Whenever I play
an MMO or any kind of RPG, I always go full evil because of how good I am. Uh huh. Right?
so I'm only I have gray skin. I'm playing the old Republic and I'm saying Bastila
you're going to be my evil Queen. I'm not helping them. I hate Cartho Nassus, but
if a good guy plays nights, the old Republic, he's probably got a blue lights
or a bad guy. He's got a blue lightsaber. I'm so I have a horn. I have horns
growing out of my head, which is how it should be. God should have made real
life work as well, by the way. Yeah,
will my will any tattoos make me evil? Yes, it depends on what kind of tattoos
you could research evil looking tattoos, but keep in mind that a tattoo is
permanent. So you want to make sure you'd want it forever. See I got all
these evil tattoos on me.
I think that's a pretty evil doctor evil right there. You if you you should
have just gotten evil that would have been a much that would have actually
been that would have been hard. Yeah, this is kind of goof. This is goofy.
It's good. I was going to be getting it's getting a little tattooed on. This
is
Evil makes me think of a good guy.
You're going to cover this up one day.
I don't think I will.
Do you feel my cold hand?
Jesus Christ.
Is my hand cold?
Yeah, well my hand feels mine.
It's cold in here.
Yours are warmish.
Mine are so warm.
Yours are very warm.
You have a temperature regulation problem and that's why you always turn the ACs to zero
degree.
I think us with cold hands are the ones that are bad.
No.
Well, whatever.
I think I do have a temperature regulation problem.
I have normal circulation and my limbs don't turn purple at any time of my life every day.
I sweat whenever I walk even in the fall
whenever you walk. I walk in turns gray and frankenstein in yeah, you do you
got a color right now. Would you go signs monsterion is I'm having a green
yeah
your heaven is that we said I'm heaven
to gamers that mean something else. What kind of music will make me evil
try heavy base dubstep songs. Skrillex is a good place to start. I would say try
goar
yeah, try ghost yeah that'll make you go is going to turn you evil real quick.
Yeah, that's right yeah, as well as horror movie soundtracks yeah, a salt on
recent thirteen
yeah, the
you're entering a dimension, exorcist theme song that'll make you scared or
evil. There's no difference to me. There isn't much difference. People you tend
to act evil when they're scared, yeah, especially the most evil looking people
are actually sometimes the nicest.
I disagree. No,
yeah, I don't agree either. No, I agree. You agree. I mean, I don't agree. I
agree with him disagreeing against you. I agree against you. What other advice
do they have? Would dressing in a more edgy way make me evil? No, it will
likely not. What does it even mean to be edgily dressed? You wear a stud, you
are studied. You are studied black shirt. You wear a black shirt. I almost wore a
black shirt today and I said I'm going to look like Steve Jobs. I'm not going to
do you have a shirt that says evil on it. Do I e dot v? Oh yeah, what is it? I
don't know. I just thought it was funny. This evil on it. What is like a little
picture of a dragon doing something on the back? Got some Godzilla thing on it.
I don't fucking know.
How can I be evil if everyone thinks I'm cute and sweet? This is a brag. This is
but I ask every day. I think I only put in one of these, but there's like five
of these questions. I think this is the same person who asked about the doll
high pitched. Oh, okay, and they have a bunch of questions. I was like what if
I'm cute and I only dress in pink and I'd be evil. There's a bunch of stuff
like that you can if you want to look the part, try perfecting the smirk that
cunning smile when you know something they don't that look on your face when
you suddenly hatch a perfectly evil plan. This is like asking this is like
asking I'm four foot eight. Can I make it in the NBA? No, you could need.
What do you guys think of my smirk? You look like a bird and you look like a
pirate and pirates are evil pirates. Pirate
that's not a smirk. That's not a smirk at all. You look like Bill Skarsgard just
then. Wait, how was mine? I'm changing my newest smirk. I got like it. No, this
is not a real smirk. You look ugly. You look like Igor.
No, you look ugly as fuck. You both look like shit. Honestly, you look like
about this one. I don't
that one's not evil. No, you don't you're incapable of an evil face. You have an
ugly one about this one.
You just face is ugly. You can't do any of these. Is this face evil?
This is kind of itchy. You're coming a bitch face.
You look like you were
coming. You only tried one face and it was bad. So you don't really have any
like a watch.
no, not evil at all. That's conscious and intelligent. That's face that's that's
like English teachers, Facebook profile picture. When you think you find your
English teacher on Facebook and then his profile picture is him sitting at his
computer like
how can I make my cat and dog evil to
this is what you need. You need a summoned to pay yeah yeah well some and
your cat is probably evil already, but your dog might take a little more work.
You may want to consider giving your pets evil looking access accessories like
a dark spiked collar, sinister looking tags or a bandana. If your pets are
newly adopted, try giving them creepy or evil sounding names like Vex or Crimson.
I know a dog in this neighbourhood called Necro. That's sick, what kind of
dog? He's a German Shepherd, he's like an all black German Shepherd. He's very
sweet though. That's sick. Yeah, and his owner's like this like Norwegian, like
black metal guy. Yeah, it's cool. That's very tight, that's really cool, that's
extremely cool. Would wearing latex make me look more evil? Yes, latex and
leather are pretty good choices for looking you yeah because of doctors
they're wearing latex.
That is a really good point and they're wearing the leather lab coat. Uh
well, I go to there. Steve Martin and fucking the big plant. Yeah, plant the
movie plant plan. They should have called it plant. The movie should that
is basically the number one plant. Here's what I there's no other movie
that's more plant than that. Move through here's what I would have called
the movie, though there's reverse the reverse vegetarian. That's good
vegetable that eats a person. That'll be a good tag line. The revenge of the
reverse vegetarian. That's what I would have revenge of the plants revenge of
the reverse vegetarians a better. Yeah, that's true, because the reverse
vegetarian would be a plan. But then people would be like, what is that? Is
that the one about the tomatoes or the plant?
Well, in to me, I would call the killer to go. I would try and class it up a
little bit and I would title it in which the plant terrifies, oh and sings God
damn in which a sing in which the plant terrifies the musical and here's what I
would have put at the end of the movie fin
and I would have put at the beginning of the movie players in alphabetical order.
Yeah, I would have done all that shit yeah, but they won't let me make movies
would a luxury car fit my evil persona. It depends on the character you're
playing. It could, though I like the one person that said this is not helpful.
I must have been the dude who like owns like a Mercedes Benz dealership. No, it
would have been a it's a that's a hater. That's somebody with a junker jalopy
style car yeah and it wasn't me. I don't have a jalopy. I fixed my mirror, so I
do not have a jalopy. I put a new mirror on. You have a jalopy. I do not. I want
to be very scary and possessed. What should I do?
Acting possessed needs a lot of work. Make sure the person you want to scare
is a bit of the jumpy type. If the person doesn't seem very jumpy, focus on
their weaknesses and try to scare them using that focus on their weaknesses.
this one the answer isn't so good, but I do really like the question. I want to
be very scary and possessed. You don't choose to be possessed, but yeah, the
devil to you on it. You're not going to get a watch pot never boils. You try
play. Did you guys ever play the midnight game? No, no, you do a so I
actually know I did play the midnight game. A few times you put salt on the
ground. I never got a game where you do a salt to a salt. Well, he he
interrupted me. Assault circles what I was going to say, but assault would also
be an evil style your circle. No, my circle is not open for assaulting.
I tried to play the midnight game.
I never got any points, though
my circle
that's funny is being evil, a subculture, yes, evil, no evil is a
mindset, not a subculture. There's no single way to look or act evil.
Hippies are evil. Hippies are evil. They are so evil, evil and then usually
the monks are kind. It's kind of a purse what you would think. Yeah, you would
think that hippies would be kind, but they like drugs and premarital stealing
hard core guys are straight edge. Yeah, hard core guys and as long as you as
long as you only pay attention to what they do during the day. Yeah, and when
and when they're not in the presence of people who are younger than them, yep,
then they're then they're upstanding citizens. Yeah, they all work at they do
acrobatics. Yeah, they all work at Trader Joe's. They all work at Trader Joe's. They wear that
Hawaiian shirt. Yup. They all wear watches. Yup. They don't look at their phone, they
look at their watch. I've been feeling for a minute that the tide is turning on Trader
Joe's. And Trader Joe's has now become... Has it fallen? I think Trader Joe's is cringe.
Yes! I'm sorry. I don't like saying that. I don't want to have to say this. This is
is the kind of thing you'll only hear here. But as a cultural commentator,
Trader Joe's. It's time to call it. I'm ready. I've seen enough. I'm ready to call it.
It's over. It's over. Trader Joe's is cringe.
Fuck you, Joe. I mean, Joe's over. Joe, Ming, Jose.
It's Joe for me. It's Joe for me. All of them. Yeah.
I don't care how good that everything in the Elote dip is.
I don't care how convenient the pork belly is. It's over. I'm going
somewhere else. I'm taking my business to Aldi. I'm going to Aldi. Is Aldi over?
You know too much about Trader Joe's to be dissing it. You clearly are a patron.
You're asking if Aldi was over? Aldi never began.
Damn.
Aldi's nuts in yo face.
How many?
Aldi's.
Aldi, yeah Aldi never began.
Yeah.
We're never doing it's by the way when I say Trader Joe's is over every single
alternative supermarket is all foods all foods.
We're going local all the no, we're not going local. Not even we're doing the
we're doing whatever the big chain supermarket is stop and shop Harris
Teeter Publix Crocker Market Basket Market Basket. Now, Market Basket has
been a little over, but they could be back soon, but right for now. It's over
now. We do not and anything by the way anything that is local to an area is over as well.
Yep. The Stop and Shop is local to the northeast. But it's not like people don't have prior
experience. From now on we are only going to any supermarket where they have one in
every town in America. If there's even one town that doesn't have it, we're not going
there. Pigs and Wiggly is not funny anymore. Shaw's, you're done. Every supermarket. Or
or it all has to be owned by the same company. Hannaford supermarket,
Walmart grocery stores are back. Yeah, here's what I'm saying. And you can
actually and here's how back they are. You can actually buy Wagyu beef at a
Walmart. Yeah, so that's huge. You know what else you can get at Walmart?
Every other stuff in your house.
You can get a curtain rod and Wagyu steak and beer, depending on the area.
and they have good deals on movies, DVDs and hey trader joe's. Here's why you're
over by the way. No dvds, no dvds first of all, but also guys no cds. Hey guys,
if I'm buying an avocado, I don't need to see a picture of the farmer.
I don't need to know his story. I don't need to know that he's been farming
avocado since he was 15 with his family. Shut the fuck up and here's another
thing, Trader Joe's. Why do you have all these parodies around the store?
Yeah. Why do you have these parodies that say like, like, uh,
empire strikes, whatever, some kind of thing.
Hey, Trader Joe, nice chalkboards.
How about I outline you in chalk when I kill you?
Yeah. Outline, outline you in shock. That's right.
And you said outlaw. I'm going to outlaw you. You're an outlaw now.
also Joe and I'm pointing to a camera. We don't have, but
we left all the cameras in Caleb's car. Yeah, that's why we have just two
cameras today. Now I'm pointing at this one, but because of the show we did
and trader Joe, you're gonna you have a fearless flyer. I will become the
fearsome flyer and I will haunt your store with wings and Costco.
Welcome back. Costco's back. Costco is Sam's Club. Sam's Club. Welcome back.
Sam's Club is still technically Walmart. BJ's, guess what? You never left because it's always
been funny to say your name. But Trader Joe's. Oh, Trader Joe's. You poor bastard. You little
Trader Joe's. Hawaiian shirts, you still think that's funny? You're making me gag. Look,
you're making Cameron throw up. If you want to switch all the girls to bikinis and all
the guys to suits though, you will be back. You will be back. That's the only bargain
you have a if you have a corporate hose and CEOs party yep every day, you will
be back, you will be back for now you're done and that's enough on trader Joe and
we can finish now yeah.
We can finish now is that all the slides, I don't remember, let's check
we'll check really quickly.
Can I wear fancy clothes and have a fancy hairstyle when acting evil? Can I
wear makeup as well? Of course, in fact, that will up the evil factor. I think
but a fancy clothes is okay, but a fancy hairstyle is not evil. I agree unless
you well unless you're some kind of dark judge.
That's a wig, though that's a hairstyle yeah is the evil laugh cliche when
acting evil, not necessarily just try to put your own spin. Let's all put our
own spin on it. Okay, ready?
That's a class. It is no, no, okay, okay, okay, okay,
wait, I got it. I was good. I got one. Are you ready? Yeah,
that's
you know somebody who laughs like that they're evil.
You have a don't how do I imply I'm evil without being evil dress like you're
evil. The way you dress can imply that you're evil, but you could be the nicest
person ever. Here's my implications. That's just evil my implications. What
if you maybe put it on your ID card? Here's my implication. Here's my
assumption. What if they put that on your driver's license when they ask
what's your height? What's your sex? What's your age? My age is six or good
and you could just say well, I'm evil yeah.
I came here for a more broad context in theater with that in mind. Do you have
any more tips on becoming a villain? Villains never think they're the bad
guy. They never see themselves as sadistic or wrong. They're the hero of
their own story. Keep that in mind. That's right. I think this next one
might be the last one.
No, do I have to wear accessories like a choker? My mom doesn't allow me
here we go. This is the last one. What if you accidentally murder people while
acting evil. Will it still be considered a crime after you stop being evil and
the person says of course murder is murder. If you're not legally insane,
you'll be charged with murder. Oh my God, so there's no such thing as they
got rid of the evil, evil defense, the evil to your honor. My client was evil
at the time, but he's not anymore, but he's come nice. Oh, he was just acting
evil when he did the that is kind of it was an accident. A lot of evil villains
and movies kind of get off on that at the end. If they are turned to the good
because they realize that it's wrong to be an environmentalist or whatever.
Yeah.
Why are so many evil villains environmentalists also?
It is funny.
That what is that going on? What's going on with that?
Eco-terrorism.
Yeah.
Yeah. Why is that? Why is that being evil? That seems like it's nice.
Well, they're just guys who blow stuff up.
Yeah, true.
Well, they're blowing up bad stuff.
I'm an ego terrorist.
Yeah, that's right. You figure out what that means. All right. Goodbye.
All right. If you...
Oh, wait. The what day?
Monday, shareholder meeting is on Monday, the next Monday, twenty fourth
is at the twenty fourth and if you want to see me open for Dan Lakata in Austin,
Texas, I will be there the weekend of the twenty eighth, twenty eighth and the
twenty ninth is two shows. There's a real good poster that my old roommate
Neil drew where Dan is Bam and I am fat Phil from CKY three. You don't need to
plug the poster when you plug the show. I like the poster poster. I have to pee.
I keep plugging stuff and then on the 26th, I have a there's a show with the
Pitbull impersonator. He's hosting the show and then I think maybe the yes,
the Sunday, two days before this, three days before this will be my birthday,
the 23rd, the day before the shareholder meeting. If you don't have anything
planned for my birthday, guess what? You will get struck by the back of my hand.
and
Cameron will be at my birth.
No I'm not.
(static)
Have you guys ever tried remote viewing?
Yes.
Yeah, Jubia's doing it right now.
Did you succeed?
Yeah, I actually can see my bedroom with my eyes closed at all times.
I'm going to try it right now.
Okay, where are you going to go?
Where should I go? I don't know.
You don't go, you see.
Where should I see?
And usually you draw it
Well, I'm not very good at drawing Cameron. I'm my art form is my words. Okay, then describe I
See some seriously white
ground
And I see a bunch of black crap out there, which is on my call space
Okay, and wait, what's that? I'm oh god. I'm seeing a pale blue dot. Oh
Great. It's a dot
That moon is very far away. I'm seeing some pale blue. I didn't say which moon
I was on. Oh, I guess you didn't say you were on a moon at all. Now that I think
about it, I'm on a moon and I'm seeing a pale blue dot. Oh, but wait, what am I
seeing on the pale blue dot? Instead of love, I'm seeing hate and I'm seeing
racial prejudice and sexism and worse of all, misogyny and also kids being
unfairly treated by their parents.
And also there's five or six green monsters all around.
And they are making something, some kind of giant weapon.
- A weapon?
- Yep, and also I can tell that one of them
is the most popular of the six,
because the other ones are kind of just listening
to what he's saying, and also he's the tallest one.
- But does he have like a special kind of hair?
- He has an Elvis hairdo.
*swoosh*
Yeah.
He has an Elvis...
Greasy...
That style?
...bombhead hairdo.
That slick back Elvis rock and roll style.
That we all know and love?
Oh my god, are the other ones bald or do they all have their own distinct hairstyles that
define their personality?
Well, basically, one of them has...
Okay, so there's six of them.
One of them has an Elvis hair.
Okay.
One of them has very long hair.
Uh huh.
One of them has shorter...
Shorter-ish hair?
Does he have glasses?
One of them has a bob.
Very...
Kind of cute.
Okay.
With a bow?
And then three of them...
Or the remaining three of them have a bob.
Or the remaining two...
[laughter]
...have no hair at all.
*Demonic Scream*