Okay, so my name is Pierce, as I said, and this is a focus group. I do focus groups
semi-regularly. I've been doing focus groups for this group for the past week
and a half. You guys are number 12. We're going to watch a partial episode of a
semi-popular podcast, and we're just going to give feedback. The podcast is
called "Podcast About List." It's an unscripted comedy podcast geared towards
young people or maybe young-minded people, and it's been experiencing mild
but steady success and the hosts are looking to experience mainstream success
and expand their reach to other key demographics. So hopefully after we
watch this clip you guys will help us with ideas to expand it to a broader
market. So as you watch it feel free to take notes on your pen and paper and
after we finish screening I'll ask you guys some questions. So make sure you pay
close attention and think about how it makes you feel. If everyone's ready we can
start. This episode is called the fappening.
And welcome back to podcast about list. Yep. Uh huh. Guys,
how are you doing on this amazingly beautiful morning?
Guys, I'm gonna be honest, what I am a little bit hungover from
Why you party too hard, bro? Yep. I was out skateboarding last night and I hung
out with some of my friends after and we went to a bar. No, no way. And you did
what? They're there. Well, I drank way too much. Oh, God, what'd you drink?
Just beer and shot. You drink beer and shot. Just be a sound for that.
Damn! Beer and shot. Beer and a shot. How many combos would you say that you had?
I think it was 10. Oh my god. 10 beers and 10 shots. Luckily your young body could probably
handle that. Yeah. Yeah, thankfully. Beer and then shot. That's how drunk you got.
Shot and then beer. You're in the clear. I don't want to alarm you, but I did actually
I'd take a hit of somebody's joint to know you smoked fucking pot. Was it a
blunt or a joint? It was a bowl. Well, you said joint. It was a joint and then
a look how fucking high he is still mother fuck. Yep, that I don't like. I
don't like how I feel right now. I'm so fucking sorry man. Yep. Luckily, me and
Cameron are very empathetic to this kind of struggle. Yeah, we've all been
It's every day bro. It's every day bro. We've all gone skateboarding and then
gone out with our friends. We've snuck them into the bar. They're a little too
young. Yeah, and then we've done beer and shot combos until we get sick and we
have to smoke weed. Yeah, the weed only made me sicker. I did throw up. It helps
with nausea. We does that's what I've read on my. No, it didn't help my forum
board. Here's the thing that didn't help me last night. No, I threw up all over
the bar and I'm not allowed back. Do you think anybody is ever faking
cancer so they can smoke weed? Yeah, you ever seen Breaking Bad?
Does he smoke weed in that? He completely fakes cancer so that he can
deal meth. That's like the whole point of the show and then he does anyway
cancer yeah and then he dies. He never had a tax or a movie. They reveal that
at the end of better call song. I didn't know it was just all fake. He just
had a really big panic attack and he fell down and died. It's pretty
interesting. It's actually a fascinating detail about the movie. Yeah, man movie.
Yeah, which movie Breaking Bad Breaking Bad. If you watch it in one, so you
never watch the movie. That's probably what I think. I'm still a little too
high. Yeah, honestly guys. It's hella jungle drop out today. Yeah. Do you
agree? Wait? I would agree if I knew what the fuck jungle drop. Oh, you
haven't heard jungle drop. No, I haven't heard of jungle drop. It's the slang
that's been going around New York in the young community. That's some kind of
United Kingdom style of music. No, it basically means when it's hot and humid
out and every cool person's been saying it like damn, it's jungle drop today.
Wow, it's mad jungle dry. I understand the jungle thing because jungles can get
mighty hot for monkeys and snails. But what is a drop? What's the drop? The
drop part mean? Okay, well, what drops
temperature? That's one thing. What what comes in drops? Wouldn't it rain water
or what to lots of things jungle drop that would make sense. If it wasn't it
didn't feel like a jungle anymore,
is it now you're thinking of jungle temperature right that would be called
dropping the jungle temperature. Okay, which I'll drop in for the next and
it's also it's slang slang usually is a reverend and means the opposite of what
you think it means that's true like sick yeah or dope or fried. You know what I
like fried stuff. I've been saying fried a lot recently. Yeah, I don't know what
it means. I don't know. I think it might a skater sling, but doesn't it mean that
you smoked weed? I think so. I think it used to mean that and now it just means
you're tired. It just means bad or I feel bad. Oh, I'm fried.
No, that's a mom thing to say.
You're right, that's the same type of thing. Other yeah, she's thinking a kind
of a scientific computer. My mom doesn't know anything about the computer. It's
like a like she's like your mom gets home from work and she's like God, I'm so
ride. I'm barred out. Yes, yes, yes, you know, I'm mad fucking I'm rolling deep.
I'm rolling right now. Yeah, I'm I'm going through these hoes like Drano.
What? That's that's like a thing. What does that mean? That's what they say in
uh and um every day. I'm shuffling song. They say going through these hoes like
Drano. I don't listen to rap thing that you clean this shit out of the toilet
with. You don't clean shit with Drano. Oh my God, you guys could drain on my
every fucking time. Oh my God. All right, guys, let's talk about the big shits
we've been taking. Okay, my shits have been looking. I'm 100% serious. It looks
like brown Smurfs.
I've been putting brown Smurfs the entire village in the toilet and the
cat too. I have only been taking just just your big wet. It looks like it
it looks like I threw a can of chili into a an oscillating fan. Yeah, oh, it like
hits all the side. I've been I've been terraforming the environment inside my
toilet. Yeah, I like I'm trying to start a Mars colony in there. Really, I've
been shitting into the toilet and playing Civ five with the shit islands
that I create and making turd people and turd Gandhi turd Gandhi turd. Gandhi
who's more aggressive than you. If my toilet same as gone, if my toilet was in
the museum, okay, an art agnostic person, they would walk into the art museum,
they would see a Rothko painting. Yeah, we go. Oh, this is crap. My my kid could
do this. Yeah, they would turn. They would see the interior of my toilet and
they would say I've changed my mind about modern art. Yeah, modern art is
a my child. A child couldn't do this. No, I try to do it full, maybe in a
diaper, but not in a toilet. They can't reach that no
or maybe in a why did I have you did you guys ever have one of those training
toilets. Yes, maybe for a little last kid. Is that the one where it has no
hole? The plastic? No, no, no, no, it has a hole. It's a it's not just a flat.
It's a big flat. You get on your chair and you should no no, no, no, but those
toilets. I babysat a kid that had one of those one time. You still have to clean
you have to it's worse than a diaper. You have to clean the shit. Yeah, yeah,
they should maybe just make that's what I meant by no hole. I meant like
topologically no hole. Oh yeah. You should just make a peripheral that goes over the
toilet so that you don't have to clean it up. Reminds me of gaming, one of my favorite
things to do. I've been gaming so much lately. What level are you? I'm over 9000, which only
a gamer might understand that. Pull that shit up. Yo, producer, pull that shit up. Over
9000. Yeah, wait, can we see that real quick? I just want a quick reminder of what movie
maybe that's from over nine thousand for the listeners and watchers who don't
know over nine thousand is a meme yeah from the former era from the era of this
is something at the older end of our demographic might appreciate antiquity
yeah this. I mean this is old as fuck. If you remember this wait hold on okay,
so there's some guy, so it's muted.
So it's me yelling at a Hooters waitress. It's over nine thousand.
me
with me when I'm like the number of girls I dated in my life. Damn me when
somebody asks me
how many how many fig newtons I ate and one and one's one sitting.
I even nine thousand fig new over nine thousand fig newtons in one sitting,
but the serving size is only to those things make you poo, though fig newtons
All right back to shit yeah, let's think about it. I've been okay. So yesterday
I've been having a really rough shitting week. I'm going to be completely
actually truly sometimes I feel sometimes with the how jungle drop it's
been. Sometimes I literally feel like I go in the bathroom and the air grows
for
I feel like it's. I feel like I'm living inside of an animal's body, some kind of
mushroom fungus. I feel like you know the visuals you get when you're on
of the fucking acid in the I mean I do it like it's turning into lines. I feel
like that is happening with the texture and smell of what I'm creating. Oh
speaking of weed, what kind of like drugs like hard drugs have you been
doing? Are you crocodile
crocodile? Wow, that's fucking awesome yeah, I've been snoring every pill in
the house. Yeah, I ran out of like real pills to snort, so I started snorting
some vitamin B. Yeah, just the vitamin B be like
yep,
and I've started over nine thousand milligrams of vitamin B. Oh my God,
yeah, and
then I that probably will get you swole.
Yeah, I've been recently trying to get swole a F. I've been going to the gym
and been doing
I've been first of all I've been recording myself and other people around
me without their permission and their consent yeah, which is kind of a cool
thing that I like to do. Do you have a three sixty camera that you use? I have
an insta flicks or whatever it's called. Do you know what the ultimate technique
is to film people? What you set up your tripod? I'm going to put you on some
game here. You set up your tripod with your camera and I would say phone, but
no, you need a you to I'm talking. I'm a sorry just you said phone and it made
me think of my phone. Yeah, I miss it angry birds. I wish I could use my phone
right now. You set it up in the locker room. You know at the entrance to the
locker room where they put the big mirror. You set it up pointing at the
mirror. So somebody walks in front of the camera, they're getting in your shot
and you can beat them to a pulp. Someone walks someone walks behind the camera.
They're still walking through your shot. You're a mirror catches them. You're
fucking dead buddy yeah, because I've been lifting five pounds for twelve
hours yeah and I'm starting to I got a pump man. I'm a crazy pump. I can't
have my arms above my waist because of
I'm going to look at one pound for twenty four hours. Yep, there is a Mr.
Beast had this idea. Did I tell you I love Mr. Beast? He's got to be the best
guy in the world. I honestly think we model almost everything we do off of
this guy. Yep, a hundred percent and also you know my least favorite president is
who Ronald Reagan? Yeah, oh my God, no, thank you. I do wish that AOC would be
a new type of president called the lovely president yeah and also she should be
probably communist. I wish that I lived in communist China slash North Korea.
Yeah, you okay, hey yo Patti, what do you think about the strike?
What strike? Oh, that's good, it's fine, that's okay, don't worry about it, go
back to sleep. Mr beast asked asked his self and just a
and what's called a statement. He said
the best video in the world would be if you get a strong guy in a room or
wherever it can be anywhere and you give him a one pound dumbbell. Every curl he
does you give him a dollar. Wow! How many do you think you do? I heard well
me. I probably do five to six before I got bored and I'd want to get on my
phone and look at to probably want to play on my iPad and watch a skibbity
twilight. I like my iPad a lot. Yeah, me too. I can't get enough of my iPad.
Here's a story about Mr. Beast. Yeah, I like the fitness on it. Not. I like using it to
look at pics. I look at pics. I look at my camera roll on there. Oh my God. Looking at
my memories on the Apple Watch going back to my Facebook memories, the good old days,
2016. Back when shit was different back then. That was so fucking long ago, man. Now that
that I'm now that I'm turning 21 next week, it's all going to change. What is
going to change? I mean, I can finally like I can stop using a fake ID. Yeah,
one. Yeah, I use a fake ID to get into every single bar I've ever been to. I
use a fake ID. I'm getting on a plane on on should I be saying that on a
podcast though? Because then like something I just thought of it's okay.
We don't respect the police. We don't give a fuck and something else. I just
I thought of what the three stooges are gay dude. I've been saying this. What
the fuck is up with my can you imagine watching them try to fuck each other and
missing their dicks out of their asses over and over and over again? Yeah, one
second.
This is my impression of that
yeah
yeah,
what's the three? I don't know what the three stooges is. The three stooges is
about three okay. Imagine imagine by the way it's a little offensive honestly as
it's a kind of a younger as a student, as I feel like as a lineal list roots in
its word. It honestly does it's like saying the I word it's like calling
these people I word or something which is like irrelevant is not for me. You
know it's just a little bit like you know it's a kind of cringe. I guess it
doesn't feel good. My dude straight up yeah straight up my dudes. Honestly, if
you and if you don't know the three stooges, let me give you an example.
Just picture the three of us
deep fry it
to certify shit, throw it on mean base, yeah, shuffle it up a little, take it
out, make it fucking gay and those are the three guys and add some rule
thirty four to it yeah yeah yeah oh my God, what's your favorite rule of the
Internet? Probably thirty four yeah rule thirty four. That's your favorite
bro. That's your favorite. My favorite is number one. What's number one,
which is maybe that's our list today. Do not tell people about the Internet if
I don't ask or some kind of it's from some old movie. Yeah, don't talk about
the internet to people who don't fucking get it. Yeah, I think it's actually that
yeah speaking of list. We do have a list today right wow yeah, we're going to go.
We're going into it now. Should we jump into it? I mean we've done fifteen
minutes and like I don't know I'm already kind of you guys. Don't you guys
want to do like forty more minutes? No, I'm fucking bored. You're bored already.
Yeah, I fell asleep. It's okay man. I'm tired to shit sucks and we should get
paid more for this by the way yeah yeah straight up who's your favorite
celebrity
probably Andrew Tate or Kim Kardashian or not gretta gerwig young girl or baby
drunk gretta gerwig. Oh by the way, I'm going to see barbie instead of some
to be about a black and white heard what they're doing to sound of freedom.
What are they doing to sound of freedom?
I don't know
guess it's some shady crap, slim shady
Slim Shady yeah, I wish I'd rather watch my name is my name is what my name is
yeah. My name is who my name is what my name is who my name is yeah. My name is
what God I'm sorry. I'm saying is I love rap yeah. I love rap rock is shit yeah
rock is shit straight up. I think all classic rock sucks. Real rappers is hard
fine like a remote. Also the control rep is out of damn. You know who's the
worst rock band in my eyes, who is that one? No, the Beatles, B E A T L E S,
the grateful dead. They didn't even spell it right and the grateful dead is
honestly bullshit stand them and I hate
and I love covers of old songs, not the original yeah here's what I'm actually
releasing. I'm actually releasing. I didn't I should probably and I guess I
at this time, I'm going to announce that I'm actually releasing a fully
electronic eight bit cover album of Fleetwood Mac. Thank God, because I was
never going to listen to rumors ever, ever, ever, ever, I like mine is my
credit. Mine is a cover album is called gamers. Can you do the big bopper next
because I'm glad he's dead? I'm glad that that plane went down yeah buddy
Holly and the big bopper get him out of here
and Elvis and Elvis basically cut your hair died on the toilet. I like I
honestly like the who was the name of the actor Austin Butler Austin. I like
Austin Butler's voice more than Elvis honestly and he offensively stole rock
from POC
straight. I forgot that about I'm sorry. I didn't mean to get anyway. Yeah, we
can just do the list. We'll just do the list so yeah. Welcome back to a
podcast about list, the only podcast that will give you a list every episode
broadcast about land wrong wrong fatality. That's for the video game as
well. Yeah, like video games
and skateboarding. So let's pull up this list today. Today's list that we're
covering is a little list that I like to call and some nice people on the
Internet like to call yeah top ten most lovely scented flowers.
When are they going to stop posting bullshit like this? Get this shit out of
my face. This is not what the Internet is for. I'm going to need some fucking
eye bleach after reading this. I think yes, so Ivy Lee doesn't make me a lull
and it doesn't make me fat. I don't
I don't want to see bro. I can't believe you just brought up fapping. I was
wait. I was a waiting to by the way. These are the two gods of fat, but it
might I want a little prince of fat is in y'all spank bank right now. I spank
bank is Riley Reed, Gabby Carter, Lena the plug yeah. These are the big girls.
I got the hose. I spank it. I got Amy Rose. I got cream. I got
tails. I got to lose the bat. I can't wait. That's some rule thirty four
shit. Oh, you're fapping to I had like an accident and nude scenes of real
actresses from real life. You had a fapping accident yeah. What happened?
fappened. The fappening. I got like I don't know I don't really know if I should talk about
it on air. What happened? But I got. Spill the tea bro. So I was in the shower and I was
about to go to work and I guess I must have turned the water on too hot. But I was fapping
in the shower. I love fapping. Sorry you said fapping again. I fucking love fapping. Me
me fapping in the shower. Yeah, that's when I stepped. I stepped in while I
was fapping and I got scalding burns on my penis
on the water was too hot. I didn't check on your thing because I was already
fapping
on your glizzy. Yeah, I got burns on my glizzy
on your tele, Wacka. You got burns on your fucking glizzy. That's what I
I thought you were going to show you, but right now it's wrapped in
gauze. I was wrapped in a tortilla. Yes, you want to glis, I like my glizzy
wrapped in a tortilla bro pause. That is hello. My bad, my bad, my boss. You
want to eat my glizzy. I didn't say I want to eat it. I didn't say I was it
bro, but I wouldn't mind pause. You want to eat as glizzy no straight up. Okay
guys, let's get back to the list. Yeah, okay, this is a list I made of not only
which flowers look the prettiest, but also has a beautiful and lovely smell.
Enjoy Ivy Lee, probably gay yeah, what it and that honestly a classic name for a
flower fan ivy ivy, God, ivy, ivy, drip water, water plants, drink water water
number one roses, such a beautiful, subtle and gentle scent. I love white
roses that's from righteous yeah. Hey guys, these are my favorite to to forget
they send my mom on Mother's Day. That's right. That's a bullshit holiday and
Valentine. Oh, you like don't buy these for my fiance. No, you like you like
white roses. I like green buds and green stems, the green seeds. That's a kind of
flower. I'm into that's a kind of flower. I'm into something where I can spark up
and watch some cartoons and some and some remix ready stems. Yeah, so I can
j it up. I love remixes. Oh my God, remixes are better than the original. I
love remixes. Every remix is better than the original. Have you heard this
speaking of originals, though? Have you heard this song run DMC collab with some
bullshit rocker band for some crap song? Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's exactly my
thoughts exactly, but it's something about walk like walk this way and run
DMC. I heard they wrote the whole thing. Oh God, I don't even want to discuss
that. Discussed number four think Magnolia, even the name makes it lovely.
I don't even know what that is. All I know about is the production company.
Yeah, honestly, film is one of my greatest interests.
I like I actually don't like a I do digital. I feel even though I find
myself kind of embracing irony and disgustingness and every aspect of my
life, including interpersonal relationships. Yeah, I can't help but
wax poetic about a beautiful film that I've experienced in the cinema. What's
the most recent beautiful film that you've seen?
you know that would probably have to be
Lego Batman movie. Yes, because any of the new or sees the new like three
Pixar movies or more into the ones are kind of element. If you see the Barbie
movie as a man, you gay yeah straight up, you're gay or you like pink yeah,
which is okay nowadays yeah, which is for real men yeah, I would say, but
only if it's a real men wear pink polo number five jasmine jasmines and
Lavender's are both my favorite lovely scented flowers. Sorry, I think I just
put this on a list a second time. Sorry, sorry, sorry, this just reminded me of a
rule thirty four. I FAP two with Jasmine from
Aladdin and I have to it and I completed and don't tell tell me it took place on
Lavender Town. It actually did it took place in and add the Lavender Town song
a little creepy. Speaking of creepy slender man, I just is real slender man
is real, but yeah real based yeah
number ten sweet pea. What sweet pea what I do a piece of food and when
jasmine's a right honestly, can I tell us all food? Can I tell a joke stand up
style? Yeah, I got a stand up so yeah, go ahead.
So this person on this, this person on this top ten list has put sweet pea as
a number ten most lovely scented flower of all time. Now I don't know about you
guys in the audience, but
but when I think of lovely sense,
he is not usually what I go to as that's funny
and that's the audience. That's funny. That's actually really good. Thanks. I
got a little scared at first when I saw a sweet pea because I miss read it and
thought it said SCP as in the as in the pure nightmare fuel. SCP is the
internet is so fucked up. I know it's so fucked up. What are these people doing?
is going on literally. I look at stuff and I think to myself, I'm so in
extremely online that yeah only I think I get this and a couple of other
people
yeah straight up. Who is this for yeah? Who is this for it's for me? Who is
this creepy pasta for probably would even you would literally the things you
have to know you have to understand Zelda. You have to know that a guy can
be named Ben. You have to have drowned or known somebody who drowned or see a
picture of someone who drowned or no guys got to be able to read yeah. You
is
so bad. It's a lost episode. Yeah, this is a lost episode of SpongeBob. If you ever seen
SpongeBob. Oh, we can't. It wasn't even want us to watch it. I understand. Yeah, I actually
really like trillions and stuff. Oh God, it looks like skip to the middle. Looks creepy.
I don't want to see this big creepy beginning. Oh, Squidward. He's just not bro. Turn that
that shit off bro. Why would you show us that what the fuck was that? What the
fuck go back to the list man? I don't want to think about what how that made
me feel, but I would watch some rule thirty four of it yeah squid. Look up
squid word rule thirty four squid. No, we can't do that okay. All right, sorry,
what's the next flower Carolina jazz man already on the list? The scent of a
yellow jasmine is amazing. If any scent was a heavenly scent, it would be poop.
Oh did I miss read that it would be this flower. That would be a beautiful name
for my future daughter poop, my future daughter, which by the way I would let
my daughter do only fans. I am literally going to gene edit my children, so I
only have daughters, yes, and make them all do. I want ten to twelve daughters,
yes, and I want them to take care of me when I'm aging and old and I don't want
them to have lives outside of my
palace. Yeah, you want to keep all your daughters chained up. No, they would
emotionally. They would want to stay with me, but they wouldn't be physically
god, I would I would be far away from most other things and there's not
really a bus or a plane and we don't own a car. So it would be hard for them to
leave, but they I mean honestly the point is I just want them to sponge bath
me yeah and make when you're older like when they're young yeah when I'm old
like thirty seven and I would make my kids do straight up. I would make my
kids become professional cup head speed runners yeah, even though the art style
got to start a young influencer, even though the art style is kind of
so okay, buddy. I want my to be an influencer. Influencer bubble is about
to pop man. Yeah, everybody knows this. Everybody knows this now. My kids are
going to be the influencers like Fred or Smosh.
I fucking that's that shit is kind of old, though, straight up mean like
Smosh and Fred is kind of old, though, like I'm more into like Kyson that I
I have speed, I have speed, I have speed,
Aiden Ross, Aiden Ross, stake.com. This is my kind of shit. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, i carly reunion
bro. They get pregnant on that on i carly. They all do they got i carly
pregnant. Every girl gets pregnant one day,
but they probably do abortions, which are fucking fine. Yeah,
you just think about all the procedures, though. I think that if this podcast
doesn't work, which by the way it is working, we have millions of views and
well deserved, I'd say yeah, but if it doesn't work, I'll probably try to
become some kind of abortion doctor. Definitely I think I would work for the
city for the city. Well, that's awesome because the library if you're at the
here's what I because I'm addicted to learning speaking of the city. Yeah.
What do you guys say right now we press stop, we head on to the city and we pick
up some girls in Times Square?
Yeah.
Oh, snap.
And fap with them?
Yeah.
Let's go fap.
All right.
Bye y'all.
Catch you on the flip side.
Later.
All right.
Any, any opening thoughts?
Do you want to start us off Aaron?
Do you want to just say what your overall opinion was?
Okay.
Yeah.
First, the actors had a sense of humor.
- Yep.
- And it was like a comedic,
comedic or comical.
The actor with a green cap.
- This one right here?
- Yes.
Every time he's focused,
the light is,
it's dark.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- So maybe lighting is something we wanna work on,
especially in this side of the frame.
But was everyone else lit well?
It was very good, this side too, yeah.
And also the middle actor is trying to hide from the microphone.
Pretty low in the frame.
Yes.
And then this mic, I noticed that it's kind of covering up his face.
Right.
Okay, so we can get into specifics, but overall, comedy podcasts, and then maybe we can work on the visual presentation a little bit more.
Do you want to, let's, we'll come back to specifics in a little bit.
Do you want to share your opening overall thoughts?
Is this real?
This is real?
Like this is a real podcast?
This is a real podcast.
Oh that was awful.
You did not appreciate it at all.
It's not funny.
I mean, I just didn't, yeah, I can go on.
But we should, do you have specific notes about it?
I mean, other than the lighting, the background, that was not interesting to look at.
They were uninteresting.
And then you just didn't find it to be a funny podcast?
This is one of the worst things I've ever seen.
Was it boring or was it?
Boring.
I'm bored out of my mind.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then Phil?
I'm very much in agreement with this young man.
Now I'm considerably older than most of you guys, so maybe I was trying to wonder, is
this relevant or is it, you know?
It's horrifying sort of, really.
Vacuous and I wouldn't watch it even paid.
I mean, this is, we watched it because we're all being, and that's pushing it.
Jumping to his moments about production value.
a lot of problems there and it degrades from whatever the words are. First, that would
be the foundation. I mean, you step in the door and you've got to have a pleasant visual
presentation.
For you, at least, there's no redemptive qualities about it. Like, if the visuals were better,
it might have been easier to watch or put on.
Yeah, and the visuals are a start. Right away, it doesn't... I'm thinking, "Boy, these are
bunch of children. And to me, they actually are children, but they're like third graders.
And I've actually seen better fifth graders do a better show.
At this level. Something that's come up a lot is people have objected to the amount of
headroom because there's so little in the frame. But from what I understand, logistically
this is so that we can actually put the internet websites that they're discussing to feature
them more prominently.
Maybe periodically tilt and put it in.
So that would require, just so you know, that would require another additional staff member
who would have to be able to pivot that camera.
Because right now these three are the only people on set when they record this.
Do we have any ideas on how to maybe clarify the visual language?
Because it's three presenters,
and then we're supposed to have internet websites being showcased in the back.
Well, at bare minimum, make it an even cloth.
I mean, it's like folded and messy back there.
At bare minimum.
Yeah, right. Exactly, exactly.
So let's just take a look here at...
this used to be one of their previous sets.
Would you guys say that they have
improved or maybe decreased in quality?
This is a hundred times better.
My understanding is that this flooded and that they had to
evacuate. So this might be
a work in progress, this new set, but we think that this was maybe a
better creative direction?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I mean, a hundred percent.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Now they can open their mouths.
- Mm-hmm.
This mic set up here, we have handheld mics here.
And I believe that in the most recent episode,
we have mics on a platform.
What do you guys think about this delivery style here
with handheld mics?
- Make them all black.
- Sorry?
- Make who all black?
No, the microphone boo-boos.
Oh, these are distracting, the colors maybe?
Oh my god, hugely.
And I'm looking at these things rather than looking at the guys talking.
So we want less color on the microphone.
Absolutely.
I have questions that we can address specifically.
Is there anything that you guys took notes about that you would like to...
Alan, is there anything that you would like to address in your notes?
Yes, there were some instances that the chorus, they used to speak together.
- It was cross-talk? - Yes.
And the sound quality, there are some echoes.
Yeah, what did we think about the sound quality overall?
There are some echoes on the sound.
I mean, I found it intelligible, I just, it was the content mostly.
Technically, you don't have many objections aside from the visual language.
Yeah, as far as sound goes, it was sound-deformed.
What age group would you guess that this is targeted towards?
Eighth graders or less.
So does that become troublesome with the, like, we have discussions about drug use,
we have discussions about pornography,
Does that sort of complicate this target demographic of younger people?
Correct. Depends on the young person.
Right. So what would you say, should we, I think that they're attempting to cultivate an older audience.
So should we, go ahead.
How old?
I would say probably we're trying to graduate from eighth grade to maybe
late high school, college, maybe even post college.
They missed the boat.
Okay, so how do we course correct to get that larger demographic, the older demographic?
Is that more pornography, more drug use?
- More content. - More drug use?
- No, just the type of comedy,
just very amateur comedy, just.
- So maybe more complex jokes,
are there any comedians that you could point to
that would maybe, they should take inspiration from?
- Segura, Tom Shum, people like that,
like that level of comedy should be.
- Right.
- Anything like that.
- Yeah, this was so far off of anything that I would work,
I'm having trouble there.
And they also insulted,
and I took it very offensively
when they were at the last section.
He was insulting a number of things.
The three stooges.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean, I can take it,
a punch throw.
- I do remember him saying that they were maybe homosexual.
- Yeah, they were gay, right.
And I was like, wait a minute, what the hell?
No, you missed the boat on them.
I can't even see that in the vaguest,
wildest perception of they are gay.
I mean, if gay means homosexual, actual, not--
- Just seems like such a boring joke.
Like, it's such a childish joke.
It's not even funny.
I'm not offended, it's just such a boring joke.
- It's younger, younger crowd.
- It's a dumb joke.
- That's like, you know, pooh-pooh jokes.
- Who was your favorite of the three?
Who do you think was the star of the day?
- Oh, God.
- I would go for the middle guy.
- Alan, this is the star of the day for you.
- Yes. (laughs)
I can relate with all this.
The content was so good.
It depends on the viewer, depends on the audience,
but I was able to relate and I was able to laugh.
I know where they're getting at.
It's kind of a random talk about things.
- But you thought that he maybe kept it together the most?
- Yes.
- Can we talk about our favorite,
just so that I have something to go back with?
Does anyone?
- Well, who's the guy on the left here?
- This guy? - Yeah.
- This is your favorite?
Is that one of you?
No.
Okay.
I don't know.
Out of the three, yeah.
This is the star of the day for me.
The biggest dub.
And then, it doesn't matter to you, maybe.
It doesn't matter to me.
I mean, he's the only one that I can see.
This one right here?
No, him.
This one, you can see him the best.
Yeah, it's the only one you can see plainly.
And that's a big, again, back to production value.
Okay, I can see him, I can relate to him.
Now, what the hell is he saying?
First, I've got to get him to say, "I'm not going to do this."
And then, I've got to get him to say, "I'm not going to do this."
Yeah, it's the only one you can see plainly.
And that's a big, you know, again, back to production value.
Okay, I can see him, I can relate to him.
Now what the hell is he saying?
First I've got to visually accept this image as a pleasant thing to look at.
And it didn't do it.
Did anyone flop?
Did anyone have the biggest flop?
The guy in the middle.
He flopped.
Yeah, I can't, you know, here, hi, how are you?
You know, wait a minute, it's me talking.
Sorry, hi, how are you?
Yeah, it's a big deal.
"Hi, how are you?"
You know, "Here, this is me talking.
Sorry, hi, how are you?"
Yeah, difficult to see.
What do you think their politics are?
We have discussions about AOC and abortion.
Can you take a guess as to what political spectrum we're trying to activate?
Liberal thinking?
Maybe a liberal crowd?
You both appreciated this guy the most.
What did you think about "jungle drop"?
Do you think that that's an expression that was compelling to you?
It was an expression. I never heard it before it made sense
They think that would you
Okay, but would you say that that's marketable was that like a marketable? Oh, I guess
Yeah, something you could sure
Yeah, what a shirt yeah, I guess
It's a jungle drop like a drop
Yeah, okay big deal, you know, I mean I've heard enough other you know, gee it's really hot
It's like, you know Tarzan hot, you know, right and I was like a catchphrase
Yeah, yeah, but I'm gonna force it anytime you try to force it. Yeah. Yeah
Maybe it's just a final note here
What could they do to appeal to an older crowd?
Or do they have to throw everything out and start fresh?
- Yeah, I think that's the thing.
- Throw it out and start fresh.
- If it's not, if they want to keep their existing audience.
- They have an audience?
- They do have an audience, and my understanding is
that they make a living through user--
- They make money doing this?
Oh, wow.
- The users pay them directly to consume premium content.
So, what is a way that they can keep that user base
and then activate an older demographic?
What incremental iterative changes can they make
in order to do that?
- Find more dumb people?
I don't know.
- Maybe just like a less educated older crowd?
How do we activate that?
- No, I don't even.
- No?
- Yeah, yeah, I think so.
- Okay, what would you do to activate that demographic?
- I mean, when you say the less educated adult crowd
would listen to this stuff,
how willing would they be to debase themselves?
I mean, at this point, that's what you're talking about.
- What do you mean by that specifically?
- Like, just make clowns of themselves.
They really just wanna just go all out.
- So maybe use the soundboard more,
more funny sounds with the soundboard, like--
- That would've helped.
Vaguely, vaguely that would've helped.
I wish some, at the end, when this guy started talking
about abortion and all, where every girl gets pregnant
I'm just going, "This guy's a fucking moron."
I found it, you know, like, "Turn this guy off."
And it wasn't funny.
It's trying to be funny, but maybe insulting.
Oh, yeah.
It was actually...
Yeah.
Okay, so if it was offensive, should they maybe cut down on the swearing?
Was there too much vulgarity?
The vulgarity of the swearing, that wouldn't matter to me.
It's more about just I don't know about the regulation on the airwave. They're doing dude. Just yeah, cuz they tried doing
They tried doing episodes with no swearing and I believe that the feedback was mixed
Do you think there's a way that we could figure out like it go more?
So with the switch they think they are at a point now where they don't know if they want to do more vulgarity
I'm going less vulgarity because it's almost sound again
Regulated vulgarity
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, and then--
- Are they going for the stupidity?
I mean, honest and true, it could have been funny,
sort of, but I was just getting like,
"Boy, you guys are really dumb, dumb shits."
- They have done a few episodes that I feel are more brainy.
They've done an episode using Mad Libs,
if you guys are familiar with Mad Libs.
- Yeah, I know Mad Libs, yeah.
- Maybe more of that to activate the more gifted,
of intelligent people who like Mad Libs.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, so maybe more games, more like...
Puzzle or you know...
Yeah, puzzle games like Mad Libs or something like that.
Deep thinking?
Yeah, yeah, where there's a little more thinking involved rather than just...
What would their audience be now?
Who's their audience now?
That I don't know, but I would say that it skews male and it skews maybe late teens,
early twenties, something like that.
But at least that's for the paying crowd,
the people who consume the free content,
I would say we're talking like 11, 12, 13.
- I don't see women liking this at all.
- They have had some pretty high profile female guests
on the show, one person who's on Saturday Night Live
was a guest on the show.
- Unbelievable.
- So this is where I worry that,
wow, I'm way too far out.
- High profile female.
Yeah.
OK, I think that's it.
One last thing.
Is there anything we can do about the title of the show,
Podcast About Lists?
Is that engaging enough?
Is there anything maybe quicker to the punch of--
is there any quicker punch that we could get there?
Yeah, I mean, I like that name.
Go with the name, but be what the name--
be what you've told me a little bit.
More lists, maybe get to the lists.
Yeah, well, that-- yeah, I was waiting for the list.
Yeah.
Get that up in the beginning and make that the foundation for all the other goofy crap
that you're talking about.
That's not bad.
Give them that list.
Just do the list from the top.
Welcome to the podcast about lists.
Our list today is...
Yeah.
Maybe if they had something to go on, they'd be better.
Let's talk about movies and fapping and all that.
Just go straight to the list.
Any closing thoughts there, Alan?
Generally, it was good for me.
So it seems like all in all, just pretty good.
Yeah.
It's good.
As the focus group drew to a close, Cameron, Caleb and Patrick reflected on the crushing
feedback they had just received.
Just because it hurt, didn't mean it wasn't true.
It was time to make a change.
The three regrouped, sat down, and hit record.
- All right, and we are back.
- And we're back, guys.
- Back to podcast about list.
- If you can't tell, we've made some improvements.
We have fixed the lighting.
- Yeah.
- I'm not slouching anymore.
I've changed my chair. - You're not slouching.
- Yep.
- Yeah, and--
- It's funny that you're sitting,
I mean, not to instantly break the thing here,
but we tried to make you much taller.
You just look the same height as both of us now.
- Yeah, except for Caleb, I guess.
- I guess it must be the camera angle.
- Both of us except for me.
But yeah, I don't know.
I feel like we got a good new direction
that we're going in.
- We've been floundering a lot, to be completely honest.
- It's been-- - Much needed feedback.
- Yeah, I mean, you come to a crossroads
and you gotta pick a direction.
And we're going the road less traveled, I'd say.
- Oh yeah. - You know?
- Maybe we could change the name of the show
to road less traveled. I'm down to change the name. Yeah, well, people seem to like
the name. That's true to be the one thing that they liked. That is just kind of
crazy to me, but I mean, we're not that I would know. I wasn't even there at
whatever we're talking about.
How do you, how are you feeling self esteem wise guys? I'm feeling probably
just about the same as I always do. Yeah, I got a little boost.
You got a boost. Did you start the day you were started? Yeah, we're starting
majority voted star of the day yeah. Unfortunately, I guess it seems you got
no votes at all
yeah. I would say that that hurt me even more than probably being called a
flopper hurt you. I'm used to it yeah. It didn't really nothing. I feel pretty
bad. I'll nothing that happened and I'd like to apologize by the way to anybody
who was offended by different comments, comments that I made as well. I made I
I made one comment that I know was very controversial in the room.
Which one was that?
I was able to kind of introspect a little bit after, because I said it, I said this
on reflex.
I was barely wasn't even thinking about it.
I said the three stooges are gay.
Yeah, that I think hit home for many people.
It's it and then I kind of was able to think about it and think, well, why am I saying
that?
It's not true.
Yeah, kind of just a bald-faced lie.
I think that true or funny.
instincts to go with the first thing that we do think of are often incorrect.
Going blue for the sake of going blue. It reminds me of a quote from one of my
favorite comedians, Tom Segura, who says, "I would trade 20 white babies
for an Asian baby. If I'm ever rich, I want a closet full of Asian babies and
I'll just put them out whenever I'm feeling down."
What is it? What is this? All kinds. Sorry, I'm not done. Okay. All kinds. Korean ones,
Chinese ones, Vietnamese, not so much. My dad was in the war and I hold a grudge. Now
what does that have to do with what just happened? Well, somebody said they liked... Yeah, Tom
Segura would be a reference to Sulcrum. They said that we should do more Segura style stuff.
I'm thinking of maybe growing out a beard like Tom Segura. Yeah. Yeah. I think that
that pretty good yeah. I'm just feeling yeah. This is a I'm a I'm kind of
centered. It was what I needed yeah. I kind of feel similar. I feel like a
reset baptized a little cleanse yeah. I'll the sin. We fix the camera angle
sets looking good yeah and here. Let me make sure you can see my my face. I
don't want to block my face with the Mike like oh true like Patrick so
rudely did, but I you know I fixed it. I mean we don't have a close up of me
really do a punch in, but I'm taller than I've ever been.
Yep, we have new looks also, which I think are working for us.
Oh, that's okay.
Mostly working.
Oh wait, did they say they like the handheld or the...
I'm just trying to not cover my face.
I just can't make it any lower, just put it in my lap a little.
That's the only reason I'm doing this.
Yeah, see this does actually clear up a lot of room.
I was also, you know, I guess this is just kind of a debrief even for the changes going
forward.
I was very you have to stop making that rubbing. No, I'm sorry that they
would not have liked that yeah. That was that was I don't even like that and I
like everything now.
I'm actually very excited to announce that, despite overwhelming negativity,
which I understand and I honestly agree with
my new catch phrase jungle drop was actually well rather popular. People
said they could see it on shirts. They could see it on hats. It could be seen
as a catch phrase for I was I was pretty happy with that. I mean let's talk
got the positives yeah, you know and and and let's start and then let's kind of
cater this last half of this episode for that kind of thing. Yeah, one thing is
we got a direction with the programming. You know they wanted more lists and more
kind of I think they said more kind of scholarly style. So they said you know
what one thing I caught my ear on the focus group leader, who was very he he
mentioned that
mad libs as a more intellectual option. I mean that seemed to be met with a
resounding agreement. Yeah, so let's do a mad. I mean let's just you know let's
jump right into it. I guess a star of the day behavior right there. Yeah, yeah,
I mean I just realized that I can't really write in the words on my phone.
That's okay. We'll we'll just go one by one. Yeah, I guess. Okay, we'll just
re all just I'll just say it okay, and then I'll read up to that point sounds
good.
Okay,
or you know what I most of these I can probably I think I can probably
remember these okay, all right, let's do that. Then your name, Caleb, I'm not
going to lie favorite food, spaghetti and meatballs, okay, verb eating all
right, adjective we need to go a little more intelligent on this, okay,
adjective scholar, but not too intelligent for me to be able to not
remember scholarly scholarly embarrassing thing you did
focus group
to trade the listeners by being crass. You know honorable thing you did
change my ways, yep
favorite endearment
and a sweetie pie, sweet pie, nice negative adjective
hurt fiat. My feelings got hurt, okay, three positive adjectives,
new camera, new Caleb and new Patrick, okay, adjective is a neutral adjective.
I suppose and let's go scholarly with this one. Yeah, intellectual
Lacanian Lacanian okay noun look on Lacan okay verb reading
body part body part mind okay
face it Caleb. You are about the greatest thing since spaghetti and
meatballs. No one else can eating like you can
your best friend says you are the was the edge scholarly scholarly or you are the
scholarly as to person in the world. Sure you once
betrayed the fans with your crassness. I did, but you also changed your ways true,
so sweetie pie today is the day you're going to stop beating up on yourself for
being
hurt and start loving yourself for being new camera, new Caleb and new Patrick,
and if people give you a lacanian time, just tell them they well. This
actually works really well. It works very well. Listen to this this no.
This is going to blow your mind how well this works.
What was the verb again? The last verb was reading reading yeah, and if
people give you a lacanian time, just tell them they can take their jacque
l'econ wow and read it up their mind. Wow
we even that is incredible. This is guys. This is a moment. The mad lib was
trying to put us in the direction of take that I know yeah it up your fucking
asshole and put shit in there with your hands and we turned it into a put bring
that book, put it in your mind, read that book, read it up your mind, read
that, but you can take that book, read it, read your book yeah see so we're
already. I don't know I mean I already feel different. You know the white is
down.
so it might not be plugged in. It's probably not a little lost power. Well,
I'll fix that for you guys. Okay, we're just not going to make a big deal out of
it and this is by the way. This is the last technical problem we'll ever have
on this show. It's likely, hopefully, I mean the best laid plan is plans of
mice and men often go askew. Also, what are they what's up?
Well, the whites coming back on this very second, but pecking I like having
I had in my shot actually like sharing my shot. I used to have my own shot, but I
used to be territorial about my shot and if my okay well it reset the lighting.
It looks like that's okay. I guess you know what let's be positive yeah.
There's nothing I mean this is a great show you know and I think it's a good
show people pay for even doing this for years and years at this point. God
we're finally at a point where I think we've figured it out yeah. You know I
I think it's fair to say we're going to get a new set because this is shit.
Yeah, this is it's going to ideal. You can't teach an old dog new tricks. I'll
say that no, no, no, I think that maybe I think that I'm thinking that maybe our
set
should be themed around just the wrong things we've done and us us growing past
it and figuring out how to deal with the things that we've done. I will maybe
take that under consideration that in my mind and read it. Okay, I'll say that so
top ten books
top ten books well number ten or starting from well, you got to build up all
right. I mean if one is because the dictionary everybody's going to I was
going to go with the source, but we can we can double those are kind of
that's like Lebron and Michael Jordan. How do you how do you rank these two?
It depends on what era do you grow up in a thesaurus heavy school and in a
similar in a similar way to where we're going to tide dictionary and the source
for number two. I mean I'm for number and for number one. I think we can tie
number two. I think we can go Bible, Torah and Quran and the Book of Mormon.
Yes, and bug of a gita, you know, because we are worldly and we've seen all
sorts of countries. Oppenheimer quoted it famously. Yes, or he did something
quite bad. Yeah, which is not we won't be doing anything like that anymore,
and I will not, and if you see the Barbie movie as a man,
you're going to have fun and you and if you see the Barbie movie as a man,
it might be because you're gay and that's okay, but what do you mean, but that's
okay, you don't even
there's no
corollary yeah that goes completely on speaking a corollary. Let's leave all
the body stuff out of this episode. I'm done with my body because I don't talk.
We're not going to do two different breaks to talk about the toilet. We don't
need to toilet talks per thirty minutes exactly. No, what are we doing? I am I'm
going to go back and I'm going to listen to some episodes. I really feel like I
I washed in the blood today. I really think that I was disgusting on a level
that you know somebody said some I don't remember who it was somebody in
the focus group said
are they these are they are clowns and they do they have no shame. Do they not
realize that this is going to ruin their lives and I kind of realize like yeah
one day I want to teach at a public university. I want to teach teach
English one or one or one or two. Maybe I want to be a school bus driver that
yeah, and if you'd google my name, you're not hiring me to be a work at any kind
of a
first thing that comes up is me saying that when I poo in the toilet sorry,
yeah, the air gets furry yeah that what does that even mean and I think that's
on a level that's intellectually low and it's it's the humor is not even there.
I said that when I have been excusing myself
that my excrement is similar to throwing chili in an oscillating fan yeah,
that's this is a leave in the past. What is the reason for saying that there is
no there's no good reason to say in the light thing that we've said, you know, I
think that I think that maybe we knew this was coming on for a long time. I
think we felt it. We tried to do the swear jar yeah, but we let the the
unwashed masses, the hordes of the devil tear it down
and I think that maybe I think we need a swear jar. I think the swear jar maybe
was the wrong idea, but I don't think it was the wrong sentiment.
Absolutely not, and I think that we don't need a jar to show us how to live.
No, the truth is the only jar I need is a swinging sensor and not to say that
there's not reasons to use curse words every once in a while. You know your
toe, you're going to want to scream shite and if you read an amazing
passage from Tom Sawyer, you might go blast me. That was good. Fuck yeah, I
love this fuck yeah, fuck yeah, Tom Sawyer and Huck. Oh fuck. I love your
talking friendship yeah, you know, and the villains in this book are bitches.
This book has me on my ass yeah. This is the humor. Oh, that's lord. You could
say I just read infinite just that book knocked me on my ass yeah, and I stuck
that in my mind and I cut the fuck up yeah. I was cutting up. I was cutting a
shit
or no sorry.
You are not it's a process it's okay. You know it's your today is the first
day of the rest of your life.
that's right, that's right and I'm going to start tomorrow is the second day.
Yes, and so on and so forth, and I think that
since we moved to this office, maybe we've been in a cocoon, yes, right and
people are saying what do you see? What do you say when you see a cocoon? You
say I'm going to eat that you say I'm going to eat that rock. Oh, well, I
think it's a I think it's
snow peas. I like snow peas, snow peas are one of the most delicious things
God ever give that is still absolutely, but you see that and you say how they
who's hanging up rocks on trees. Yeah, what kind of more on this for us needs
to hire a new interior decorator? How do you like? I'm sorry. I feel like this
conversation is slipping back into our old ways and why would you eat a cocoon?
I just said it looks like a snow pea. He could be confused by it. Maybe some
kind of brown pea or bean. That is that is some are green. That is the
that is the thought of an imbecile
to think that a snow pea in a cocoon. We not do the ad hominem thing. I'm just
I'm saying that if we're trying to change, can we let's try a fallacy
clear episode maybe for once right some kind of like if we're going to get
into a debate, can it be spirited yet friendly? Yes, you know, I don't think I
don't think debating whether a cocoon would be a snap. P is something that
we've all made mistakes and in to you most of all you most of all
what and what and and I am too, but if if I make a mistake, you need to
forgive me for it. If I mistake, I do forgive you a cocoon hanging from a
tree branch that looks honestly a little brown and red. If I think that that's a
p that's peapod that's been cooked, so long and heard red, it could be could be
a more if I think the red light from the oven turns food red, you're going to
condemn me for that, but a more more interesting conversation could be how
your perception of color is way different than mine true. It's like when
I see red on on meat. I think I think raw when you see red, you could think
that means cooked. If you're right is different than mine, yes, because
everyone's the cones in people's eyes are all there. When you look at a steak,
you could think it turns from brown to red as it gets cooked and by the way you
just said cone and I'd like to applaud us for none of us saying cone. I like a
big lump with knobs or anything like that any kind of like
kind of
that's a child. It's a reference. I just very facile. I think that this is oh
back to my point. Yes, that I was making you see a cocoon. You might think it's a
rock. You might think it's a bean. It doesn't matter what you think right, but
almost nobody can identify a cocoon just based off how it looks. No first of
nobody, but what I'm saying is you wait a couple of years, maybe four or five
years of doing of the cocoon being there. Wow, that's a big, scary butterfly.
Now that thing's breaking out and becoming one of the most terrifying
predators,
the
said Hawk. Now here's an intellectual fact that I either learned or made up.
yes, a cocoon is for a moth yet. A chrysalis is for a butterfly.
Interesting wow and a chrysalis is
a cocoon is a cocoon gotcha okay, I'm right double checking on that. If you
think about the difference between
metapod
and maybe let's cool it on the video game right. I'm sorry, I don't I do I
let's stick to let's let's classic films, classic films, the opera, the
third man, the third past, thou seen the third man, maybe manuscripts. We could
start maybe delving directed by Carol Clover. Oh goodness, what a treat you
know what we I mean our previous attitudes before our focus group were
very
very similar to the final line and gone with the wind. Frankly, my dear, I don't
give a damn. Yes, we with the wind and we were throwing care to the wind. We
were thrown out and something that we I kind of realized listening and talk is
our audiences is a
spring chickens. Yes, yeah, you know very spry. These are these are young young
people whose minds we are there. I say poisoning, you know these people are
just they're doing their their PSATs and their SATs and they're writing down
where they're going to put their name instead of their name. They're putting
right diarrhea or or
I think that I think that to quote nor a little turd Ferguson.
these kids whose minds are being poisoned by content such as this. I mean
obviously we'll make an effort to try and improve the content and make it a
little less poison, but might I recommend you know for a for you know
someone in our audience range, the eleven to twelve age demographic. These
are these people, these because there are people, but we say children in
society. Yeah, we do these children. They maybe they shouldn't be consuming
podcasts and maybe we should be putting them on the path to again to cinema to
film and we should be showing them content such as maybe they would enjoy
persona, you know, great films such as
oh gosh, Threads is another great film
that I think says a lot about the world.
Come and See, Dogville, you know, these are
highly acclaimed films that really encompass
the breadth of human experience more than
any three stooges, pardon me, at a table
ever could. I think that
more, we should be influencing our audience
to go on to more websites like Letterboxd
and good reads rather than than twitter threads and I prostrate myself at the
shrine of good reads. Yes, yes, yes, margaret atwood for me it is it is
definitely letterboxd. I think that that is an amazing website. Any website that
will verify margaret atwood is a top website in my books. No, no doubt, no
doubt at all, no no and I think that no no good read complete. You have finished
your website. You don't have to add anything else. It's it's perfect as is
good reads. Yes, yes, and by the way, there's nothing good coming out anymore.
The last good book, the last good book that was written was my year of rest and
relaxation. Yeah, you know, which was a long, long time ago, which was in two
thousand and seventeen, I believe, and her second book or the one that was
after that. I thought it was crass garbage and oh, that's another thing I
was thinking so hard. First of all, I mean I do think hard now all the time,
but I was thinking also can I I'm sorry we said no cross. I can I push one thing
talking about. I think that the author of my arrest and relaxation year. I
think her name is normal now. What is her name? I O Tessa most vague that's a
completely average. I think that's a human name. That's the average name.
Yeah, but anyway, continue you know what I seem to have my point seems to have
dissipated out of my brain. I'm so sorry, no, no, no, that's no, it's not
your fault, because not your fault. That's the other thing as broadcasters,
which is you know the safe to say that's what we are. You know, let's and by the
let's stop pretending that we are comedian, comedian, superstar, triple
threats, let's we are broadcasters, we are not clowns, we are no, we are here
to educate the masses, give
bring hark good news comes, that's that's what people should be saying when
they open up our program. Yeah, you know, so I think that maybe if we to use a
little mnemonic device, okay, maybe we leave behind the Howard Stern, yes, and
we start creating content that makes people say how are these men so stern
wow when it comes to education and societal infrastructure and that's the
other thing infrastructure young men don't have a man on this. I'm sorry to
interrupt. Oh no infrastructure. I mean it essentially refers to if you can
imagine an ant hill. Yes, that is metaphorically what it appears when
you're flying in a plane.
Wow, when you look down at the world, because it is a world, these won't say
this. Oh, what these are the concepts that excite me now and the earth is as
round as a man. I'm also now as we talk about this. I'm also just remembering
that some people in the focus group did say that more funny sounds would be
better.
I think I do. I so maybe we keep you keep speak on infrastructure a little
bit. Just go ahead, just go ahead and talk about infrastructure, Patrick,
maybe what what kind of see this is not my area of expertise. Well, I'll go
that yeah, I think you structure I'm here more to learn about infrastructure
infrastructure can refer to roads,
train tracks, fatality and even the sky for planes. It has to be considered a
infrastructure. Wow infrastructure programs in America have been historically
under funded the last twenty years or so ever since Bill Clinton, who's a great
man got into office and
I will say you know I'm not some huge fan of
the imperialist pig Joe Biden,
but I will say that he has promised to invest in infrastructure again because
there are crumbling roads. People's commute their their tires are breaking
on potholes and not only that,
but we're putting America back to work by by by funding these infrastructure
programs, you know, because that's a lot of jobs created. So all in all, I think
that there's a bright future for infrastructure in this great nation.
And yeah, another thing I want to another thing I want to do is be a little bit
more punctual, you know, so I think that's I agree. I think that's about
time to out. You see, I always come here first yeah, and I'm always here and I'm
He does. I always come here second. Guilty of charge.
And I'm setting up all the cameras and everything and I'm setting things up and I'm thinking
now to things that are said in the focus group and I'm thinking about my time in film school
and what did I, what am I? Why are we not flexing these muscles? Why am I not flexing
this muscle? Let's get a dolly in here. Let's get a dolly. I want a jib. I want gaffers.
I thought you were going to say something else. What did you think he was going to say?
Oh, we don't speak like I know I really got and okay one more thing that I
would like to address one more thing I'd like to address.
There is nothing please come into frame speaking of film school, please come
into frame. There is nothing funny about
I don't even want to say fat. No, there's the fapping is not funny. That's
rule. Thirty four is not rule. What is it never be invoked?
The it's it's some rules are meant to be even thinking about it. Some rules are
meant to be broken, but yes, exactly, I could not have said that, but and so you
know what let's do a little bit of a I mean we have we have variously massive
online followings. Let's do a sort of campaign sure to erase. What about the
anti FAP pledge
anti FAP, but more more than that? I think more pressing because
you know well, I would say FAP is going to FAP, but I'm not going to say that.
I'm going to say that rule thirty four let's eradicate this filth from the
internet yeah okay, let's eradicate this and while we're at it, let's take down
the internet archive because a lot of pornography is hosted on there. Thank
you. I don't need to see Valorant, Viper and Jet doing the and I don't even I
don't be all nasty asked to ask to quote the film from the end of Requiem for a
dream. I don't need an off ski. Aaron off ski is a brilliant, brilliant man, but I
I don't need to see this stuff.
- Yes. - And I don't--
- And nobody else needs to either.
- No, no, least of all the easily influenced youth
of this world. - Yes, and you should never,
I mean, I don't even want to entertain the idea
of Overwatch rule 34.
- 100%, yeah.
The video, which I think everybody's seen
of the woman dressed as the character from Overwatch,
and she says, "Nerf this," and then she slaps
her giant rear end, and I believe that she
flagellates at the end of the video.
This video needs to go.
- Yeah. - This is a disgusting.
- Might I propose-- - Digital Millennium
Copyright Act strikes.
- Might I propose an alternative,
because it may be difficult to eradicate.
Perhaps, maybe, we take all this Rule 34 smut
that's featuring all these characters that are,
you know it's like at their video game characters you look at their comic book
characters their t_v_ show characters
and what is the audience for these forms of media it's children it's children and
young east so why don't we take rule thirty four and we and we move it to
apply to characters that are for people who have developed brains and can decide
thank you what they want in life so let's see it let's you know see some
homer let's see some no no see even that's a cartoon pat
let me let me tune. I'm no no no no no no let me let's a okay an adventure. I
understand now he's actually I'm actually not even sure who you're
referring to when you say, but let me let me let me give you my proposal. I
think that perhaps we should limit rule thirty four to characters like matlock
yes,
there's like Columbo Columbo, yeah, Jack, the the stars of Jag the stars
marlins
Murphy Brown
Bill Cosby, no. Buster Keaton, yes. Frosty the Snowman. Charlie Chaplin.
Charlie Chaplin's The Tramp. Roseanne, no. That is... Roseanne Barr. Frasier Crane.
All the cast members of Bonanza. Ichabod Crane. Ichabod Crane, yes. The Headless Horseman.
The Brothers Karamazov. The Brothers Karazumov. Karizmizomov. And by the way,
let's get rid of... no more Riz, more Karizmazov. Yes. Right? Oliver Twist.
Thank you. No, he's a boy wait. No, not all of it. Sorry. I was thinking of a
different guy. Okay, Oliver Oliver Yeah, just Oliver. We can leave it at that
all over north. Okay, guys. Well,
this has been again. I think this is very. I hope you all enjoyed it.
Everybody in the focus group did get paid. I'd like to see so and everything
And they are all happy and they all and they were they were very, very helpful. And I hope
that you enjoy this new chapter. We're embarking on. Thank you. Thank you. We love you. Good
night.
This weekend, in addition to Barbie coming out and and I know what you think. I know what
what you're thinking. I'm going to say here, but and in addition to
Oppenheimer coming out, okay, there is a new
episode of podcast about list dropping and it's this episode.
Wait, and this is coming out the day after Barbie and Oppenheimer. So
it's kind of same opening weekend.
Potty, potty,
Bartle,
Barb,
Barber,
Harbin liner,
- Podcast about barbie and Oppenpotty.
- Potty Limes.
- Potty Liner.
- Oppenpotty.
Pot, barb.
- Oppenpardly.
- Barbcast, pod, op-lyston barbin.
(laughing)
- Honestly, I still feel like we haven't gotten it.
- I think it's pardon hypen, barbin, lemon, lyston.
- Pardon my guardly.
This class is in.
- Ohparbin, ohparbincast, bo-bal.
- Barbin cast Barbautenheimer listery.
- Listery.
- There we go.
- We got it again.
We found it again.
- Barbapen.
- Barbout.
- Barbapen bouten.
- Yep.
- Barbcast op bout.
- Op bout.
- That's good.
- Listheimer.
- Barbapen op bout.
- Tell you what, though.
- Barbapen op bout list barb.
- I want to barb my list of ops.
- Yes.
- Boom!