We're at a dramatic scene after a vehicle slams into a building.
Maria Stephanos in the newsroom with some new surveillance of this crash, Maria.
Emily, what a mess.
Police are still investigating what led up to this crash,
but we can tell you that there are no survivors.
Apparently, security footage caught three weird-looking adult men
playing with a laser pointer just before the crash.
They seem to be giggling and tickling each other,
and enhancement of the video even reveals one suspect touching another's butt.
Police have released sketches of the suspects responsible for this crash
along with the following audio clip.
[laughing]
Wait, wait, guys. Let's crash that car.
[crash]
[screaming]
Just kidding. I don't care.
Let's touch his butt.
Many amateur sleuths have taken to the internet with theories on who the police sketch resembles,
but police chief Mike Horan had this to say.
With our current resources, we are unlikely to identify the culprits responsible for this tragedy.
The only way I could see us finding these criminals would be if there were some kind of
massive digital repository of hours of video and audio footage of these men that we could
use to match their faces in the security footage.
Weird guys like this are hard to hunt down.
If they were semi-popular internet celebrities or somewhat famous comedians, that would be
another story.
But we're still waiting on details at this time.
In addition to dozens of fatalities and nearly 100 serious injuries, there was structural
damage to the building, as you can imagine, and that right now is being investigated.
As well as the psychological damages caused by the bald suspect's attempt to riz one of
the female crash victims.
One thing's for certain, these three pieces of shit have a life sentence ahead of them
once they're caught.
Back to you, FUD.
(music)
Okay.
One word.
Brad.
Yep.
Yeah, I mean that doesn't even begin to...
No, Brad does not encapsulate what we have seen and what we found ourselves on.
Dan, you're getting a little bit closer, I would say.
Okay, still not fully there. One word.
one word
Boeing sproing is okay. It's boring is colder, though you're you're almost on
it one word.
No, that's the sound. I mean that's definitely the closest one
guys. We have found ourselves in a bit of a sticky legal situation. It's
ongoing, but ongoing for a very long time, ongoing for essentially the rest
of our lives. They hundred years
We've been sentenced to 100 years in federal maximum security prison, cell block 1000,
that's where we are right now.
And yeah, I mean, there's no two ways about it.
We messed up.
Yeah, I think we're completely innocent.
I don't think we should have been.
But quote the immortal words of Kendrick Lamar, "When shit hits the fan, are you still a fan?
And the rest of the line doesn't matter."
I don't know what the rest of the line is.
Me neither.
It doesn't matter.
Can you say it?
What's the rest?
when shit hits the fan, are you still a fan or do you I'm looking around right
now? I like shit. I say it now. It's when shit hits the fan. Are you still
a fan? And then he says, he says, my name is Michael Jackson. He says he
says he gave us Billy Jean. They say he touched those kids. It's a bit of
it. It's kind of weird that he never got in trouble for that song. Yeah,
yeah, he's kind of being like Michael Jackson never got in trouble for Billy
Jean. Yeah, I don't think you should get in trouble for Billy Jean. Is that
You're dating a girl named Billie?
Kinda gay, Michael Jackson.
Come on now.
Kinda, ugh.
No, but Kendrick Lamar didn't get in any trouble
for making this song, where he was like--
He got in some trouble when his last album came out, right?
Didn't people, wasn't, didn't he have something about--
Well, people were mad about Humble.
People were mad that he said he's sick and tired
of the Photoshop, and show me something real.
What's wrong with that, he wants real girls.
I don't know what was wrong with it.
I wish that I could.
But there was people getting,
I remember my friend telling me that people,
like that people were mad about that.
when we were in an Uber and I was like what I do fucking hate when a girl
sends me a selfie with the Photoshop on the yo that is true. I'm not getting
those anymore, though. I know that's not when I came in here, not mine. I'm one
of those prisoners that makes tic tocs. Yeah, really? I do jumping jacks and
sing songs. How many cigarettes does that cost you? One hundred and twenty.
He has the most cigarettes. The thing about
one right now. Okay, so if you're wondering, if you're wondering where
we're at Cameron has become kind of the king of the jail so far. I mean he's
feared, revered,
reviled, reviled by many, respected. I mean I think you've gotten basically
everything that starts with re and then two syllables, that's me. So what we
have learned is that everybody, there's different cars in prison and Cameron is
all of the cars respect him. Yeah, every single one of the groups in prison
really respect him. You haven't noticed this? People are calling him Cars. People are calling
him Cars? Yeah, yeah. Like every group in prison is a car, they say. So every single
one, I mean we're just lucky that we didn't have to join any of these other guys. Yeah,
by the way, if you were wondering, we did not join any kind of white group. We formed
our own group, thank you very much. We formed our own group called the Prison Jitterbugs.
prison jitterbugs. We thought that it was a nice kind of low profile name.
We'd be able to stay out of trouble. And we didn't think that Cameron would
snap. Like the jitterbugs, the jitterbugs, like everything else in jail,
it's about respect.
And Cameron has just been, I mean, adding years to his sentence,
with stuff that he's been doing. I'm honestly not so worried about adding
years to my sentence, because as you guys know, the arrangement we have with
the warden right now, who we do...
here's a painting of these are my these are my watercolors to go through my
watercolors real up will know i'm still talking here about a range with the
warden which is that
uh... every podcast episode record while we're in here they're actually taking a
year offer sentence to the house of how much these episodes have been helping
the community both in and out of prison but simultaneously we are doing a lot of
stuff that is getting time added to our sent all yeah i mean these watercolors i
was not supposed to have paint
i don't even know you got to know who would bring you pain
buddy, it took me a long time to get all this paint in here. I can tell you that
for free. One drop at a time? Yeah. I just smuggled it in one drop at a time.
That's why it's watercolors because it's mixed in with my mouth. That makes sense.
See, we have up here on the right,
that is our former cell mate as a portrait of our former cell mate, Ryan.
And Cameron, why don't you tell them
why Ryan looks like right in that photo.
Oh
well, I was having a bad dream
where I got struck by lightning
and in the dream, I thought, oh my God, I'm going to die. I might as well lash
out at everybody around me and by the way, Ryan's nickname was white lightning.
Yeah,
you woke up, you saw lightning, I woke up, I saw his lightning bolt tattoos that
he has
That's what I was thinking about. Lightning, two lightning bolt tattoos.
I think it was like a family crest or so because he was white. Yeah. Oh,
well, yeah, true. That was the other part of the big man. The tattoos are
black. Yeah, they were not white. It doesn't make a lot of sense. No,
you already do white ink. He did have some,
we did have white stuff tattooed on him in other places. Yeah, that is true.
He tried to tattoo you. Oh yeah. I forgot about that. Yeah. I did actually
get end up getting a prison tattoo. Oh yeah. I don't know if I've shown you
guys this yet. Yeah. Yeah. I haven't seen it. Ryan, our cell mate was a,
That's okay. You can have that one. Oh, Ryan, our cell mate was giving me a
tattoo and
I didn't really look at what I was kind of closing my eyes. Yeah, I mean, I've
been pretty tired in here, been pretty bored. Yeah, so I was just kind of
taking a quick nap. I thought it was a pain thing. And no, pain doesn't bother
me at all. I'm actually invincible,
but he was tattooing me and I didn't look until about halfway through the
tattoo down at what he was tattooing. So I ended up finishing it myself when I
I saw what he was trying to put on my body. So here I'll just I'll just show
it right now. Let me stand up and show the
so
I don't know if you can read that for me because I'm off my says says it's a
white person, but it looks like maybe it's kind of a blend of two styles kind
of old English up until the P. Yeah, and then maybe is that just Sharpie?
No, it's a it's it's it's all tattooed. It's all tattooed. No, it's just very
alone out. That's why it looks like sharpie. Yeah, I mean you don't we don't
have machines in here for for tattoos, right? So maybe only machines we have
here is the industry prison. So he was trying to tattoo on you white prisoner.
Yeah, maybe I hope that's what he was tattooing. I'm not gonna be a prisoner
forever, but I am a white person. Yeah, that'll probably never change unless we
develop technology. Yeah, so it's good to get that on your belly too. Yeah, so
you can like, you know, when I go swimming, people don't get confused if I
get really tan. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. If you sit out in the sun, you bake.
Yeah. Let's get the... So then the one on the... Oh, we're back to your...
The one on the right here, this is a portrait of me and the warden.
Right. So that's... That's on the left. That's either the left or the middle.
That's the only... The camera left. Where are you chewing? Who's chewing on
something? He's got ice. You can't chew ice. Yeah. Don't chew ice into the
microphone. It's bad for your teeth. You're gonna get 10 years out of prison
for chewing ice. I didn't get ten years added for rudeness. I put my elbows on the table
pretty often.
In the middle here is the portrait of me and the warden and then underneath that is Pizza
Friday. We've been getting Pizza Fridays because of stuff that Cameron has been threatening
in the prison. And he said, what did you say? You said if we don't get Pizza Friday, you
kind of had like your own little like...
All of y'all getting splatted.
at it. Yeah, all you get is a little protest in here. Yeah, prison protest
and it got us, it got us pizza Friday. So put the play that applause sound for
you. So, so that's growing. I'm so blessed to be stuck in this hell hole
with one of my most violent friends. Yeah, me too. It really is. Yeah, it's
too bad that I got put in a cell with two kind of way fish little pussy cats.
yeah. I mean I've been getting really into my art. I'm a complete bitch. I'm
a fucking bitch, right? The first day that I was here, I went up to the biggest,
baddest guy in the prison and I hopped on his back and he gave me a piggyback
ride. That's just how I roll in prison. I'm actually enjoying myself a lot.
The wine, guys, I've never been into wine before, but the tannins in this wine
truly is, it's unreal. I never understood what legs on wine meant until I
rank it in a styrofoam cup. Yeah, that's what I was just about to say. We take
the you know you'd you'd swirl it around on the table like that in the styrofoam
flute that they gave us and we got
by the way.
We have full sampling. We take the we take the wine guys. We're cutting up
black olives. We're getting slices of craft singles. We're cutting them into
quarters and we sit there and guys, we are enjoying. Don't feel bad for us in
prison. We're happy we are I'm living the best life I've ever had him.
Absolutely, absolutely, I get to use a rotary telephone. It's amazing. I get to
use a rotary telephone to call my cousins. My wife is out of the picture.
Don't care. I don't remember her phone number. It was in my contacts and I
don't have my phone guy. Actually, I do, but it's only on tick tock is the only
app I have. It's the only
one gigabyte phone and that's the only reason that I could sneak it in and it's
big enough to store my TikToks on.
Yeah, and my wife is watching. Listen, a phone number is at least 3 gigabytes.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't fit on these tiny ass phones that we have in here.
These phones are so, they have no space in them at all.
But we've really made a home for ourselves here.
Oh, absolutely.
Honestly, we've have, we put up the watercolors we put over here. On my side we have a sexy
calendar, you know?
And these guys, it is so, I mean I have been just a pack mule. I've been smuggling all
this stuff in, rolling all this up, putting it in my butt and my mouth. I'm walking around
here like a, what's the? Like a reverse chipmunk. You've got your butt cheeks full of food.
I've got my butt cheeks full of food and my mouth full of posters. Walking around, you've
we've been popping out talkies for us and all sorts of that's why that's why they
call me the monk or I mean you guys do the monk, even though they also call me
the monk for a different reason. What's the reason they call you the well? I
look like a monk. Yeah, especially in this orange. You try to set yourself on
fire. Well, yeah, the first day didn't take it very well. The PlayStation
stopped working, so I tried to set myself on fire, but apparently orange
juice is not flammable. No, I just walked around sticky for a couple of days
because I was afraid of the showers. Yeah. Well, I mean you guys, you guys brought in
some nice stuff. Pat brought in these or he painted these wall watercolors and Caleb brought
in this this calendar in this nice map of Cyrodiil here. But we didn't have I actually
the world. So I've I've been this home. I've been I actually contributed to the cell, too.
And yeah, yeah, I got in here first. Maybe you guys didn't even notice this, but I actually
brought these bars for the window. I got here. This window is just open and I figured, well,
much of a jail. There's not bars here.
There wasn't really a jail feel to it.
So I threw some bars up there. I welded them in.
Yeah. They're pretty solid.
We're on the first floor too, which is like, you know,
somebody could come in. Exactly. I don't want anyone
coming in and interrupting us. I don't want somebody...
What if they stole my posters? What if they stole my watercolors?
Honestly, it's also a little
drafty in here and the bars stop
just enough air for it to be the
perfect temperature. Oh, absolutely. True.
I mean, I couldn't live without these watercolors.
These are my pride and joy here. I mean, look at
this one right here. We're not going to look closely at that one because why not
is going to get us in trouble. Get in trouble. I don't think we'll get in
trouble if we look closely at that one. That one I can't wait till this. That
one is a drawing of my free time. That's what it is. The title. That's my free
time. Cellmate Ryan, me and the warden and pizza Friday and these are all
available on Etsy. They let me open up my own Etsy store in here. That's very
The thing is also people talk all this bullshit about correctional officers. Guys, Linda is
a fucking nice lady. She's nice.
She's...
What do you mean? What are you laughing about?
She's pretty nice, all right.
What? Did she get you extra food?
I'll leave it at that.
Did you bring her something in your butt?
Uh-huh.
What did you bring her?
Chips. It was mostly chips.
So now you're... You're such a fucking teacher's pet, man.
You are.
really crazy. I've been
fucking smuggling in bags of the whole shebang or smuggling out bags of the
whole shebang. What's the Linda? Linda sells them on eBay. Oh, it's looking
like there's a that I need to go over to the other side of the prison cell. Oh,
yeah, I can and figure out. I think something was supposed to be plugged in
that I told one of us to plug in that ended up not being plugged in. No, it's
plugged in. Well, it's not.
I think the cable is broken.
Yeah, I mean luckily this cell is four complete walls.
Yeah.
But yeah, Linda takes whole shebang chips out of prison and sells them on eBay to people
who like chips.
Yeah, I mean, which is most of the population.
You know, how Linda and I have bonded is over chips.
But if you take them out of your ass, don't they get back and it's all crumbled?
It's just a bunch of pieces of chips.
It's like bread crumbs.
Well, I mean, I guess that's the when you're buying chips off of eBay. I feel
like that's kind of that's par for the course. Yeah, par for the quiz. You know,
you run the you run the risk, especially present chips. Like, yeah, but I love
prison chips. Oh my God, the whole shebangs are very good chips. Oh my God.
I've been asking him to get zaps in here, but I don't think they're going to.
No, I really would like to get just some. Is it too much to fucking ask for
plain original lays once in a while? Yeah, I mean everything here is some
some spicy flavor of this or that. Or some fucking pretzels!
Yeah, I do miss- Where are the pretzels, where are the wheat thins, and where is the whole wheat bread?
I miss the McDonald's on the outside, but the steak and lobsters we've been having in here have been just so incredible.
Dude, it's disgusting. It's fucking disgusting. You hate- Steak and lobster, bro?
You hate surf and turf days?
Dude, I'm walking around- We have pizza Friday and surf and turf.
My blood pressure is going through the fucking roof, right?
I can barely even muster up the courage to play tennis outside anymore.
No, it's pickleball now.
Well, they turned it into the pickleball courts two days ago.
Yeah, because again, Cameron's wrath.
I mean, you really have laid down the law here.
You've kind of made prison...
I've always told you guys, first day in prison, I'm changing it.
You saw what the warden was doing to me, and then you snapped at him,
and now the warden is a prisoner.
And I do what the warden did to you.
And you're the warden.
It's a very strange scenario.
Yeah, I mean, if you--
He made the warden his proverbial bitch.
People all the time-- you know what I've been realizing?
I've been talking to family members and stuff,
and they're saying, is it like Shawshank Redemption?
Is it like--
No, it's like Delfino Plaza in Mario Sunshine.
Guys, it's like Ned's Declassified in this bitch, right?
It's like Suite Life on Deck.
Yeah, we have guys. I have a crush. Okay, I'm twenty something years old and I
haven't said this in years. I have a crush right. I'm not gonna tell you who
it is.
No,
it's better not. It's another prisoner who I can't tell you who it is because
he's gonna listen to this. Oh great, but we have a teacher we have. I mean
there's all sorts of characters that janitor this guy's off his fucking
a rocker right. He wears a basically I keep mistaking him for some kind of
bizarro world prisoner, because he's wears a blue jumpsuit instead of an
orange. Yeah, and honestly, I
like speaking of with stuff that's kind of you kind of don't expect based on TV
and movies before you go into prison. Like I've always seen prison in the
movies and I thought it's one way and then I get in here and I realize like
you know
most of the child molesters are actually pretty chill guy. Not too bad to hang
dealt with and people don't mind them in here. Yeah, they don't get beaten up.
Is that because is that is that because when you first the first day they
thought that that's where you were going and they put you at that lunch table?
No, I just walked over and I was like, Hey guys, no one seems to be talking to
you, but a lot of you seem cool.
Interesting. I don't I don't see you. I walked over to that table and you
dap them all up. Yeah, and I was like, don't feel badly. Yeah, I mean, that's
because I believe that what you've done, you're being punished and you'll come
That was the one thing when you first got here, you were so inspirational to everyone, walking
up to every single prisoner and saying, "Don't feel badly."
And I think that's maybe once you showed them your soft side, but then immediately...
Except Larry the Litterbug.
Oh, dude.
And we had to get rid of him because his name rhymed with jitterbug.
You're literally fucking destroying the earth, bro.
His name rhymed with jitterbug.
We can't have litterbugs versus jitterbugs.
No.
and if you're out on the yard right, it's fine to have a couple of beers right.
We're all out there, we're lifting weights, we're making beers, yeah, we
have a craft brewery, we're making beers, we're making wine, it's not that big of
a deal, it's fine to have that, but that can is gonna go in the proper receptacle,
right? This is our space, we're gonna respect it, we're gonna treat it right,
because we are going to be here for 200 years. Yeah, we are dying, we are in
this Swedish prison for 200 years and we're gonna be, and I'm gonna get bored
of PlayStation. I'm going to get bored of Xbox. I'm going to get bored of surf
and turf and all this stuff right, but one thing that I will never get bored of
rolling around on the ground. Yeah, I can't do that. If there's fucking trash
all over, I'm going to get a
star. I'm going to get a mental splinter stuck in my mental one, a mental and I
already have a mental mental and it's caused a lot of issues with how I'm
treating people in here. I think it's the root of my problems. I don't think
the way that you're treating people is wrong or you should be put in any kind
of solitary confined. By the way, solitary confinement is comfortable.
We're in it right now. Yeah. I don't even think it was a three person
solitary confinement.
Yeah, because we overcooked the hamburgers when we were on kitchen duty.
Also, yes, kitchen duty's fun. I, yeah, kitchen duty's fun. I like the dishes.
And I admit it, y'all. And to my girlfriend, yes, before I was sent off to
jail, I forgot to do the dishes. Oh, add it to my sentence. Yeah, when he gets
out,
when I get out,
just leave him there, be patient and guys, Jesus Christ, if you've been
wondering if we've been making funny license plates, you, you best believe
have we've been making very funny license plates. We've been making ones
that have an eight, an equal sign and a D. You are owned was one that I drew
the they do. They do crack down on a lot of the ones that are more obviously
twenty. So I have been making some silly ones that maybe appeal to a
different crowd. So I've been making ones that say, for example, one, two,
three, five. Yep, so as if it's made by someone who can't count, if you're
not a math nerd, you might have not noticed that's not in sequence, right?
Yeah, that's the wrong because the ones I make that say semen or vaginal yeah
these ones usually get
bad
off the
a g a n a l
for all the
trouble. These ones they get crumpled down and they get made into cubes that
then turn into and again on my Etsy store. I have been making these license
plates for hipsters. I've been doing ironic stuff yeah and never in my life
did I think I'd know how to build a car, but apparently that's really I've known
come along. It was kind of it was incredible how natural he was at
building a car. We've been coming, we're coming manly men.
We're hardened right when I get out of here, I'm going to be a
different guy because I'll be a hundred and eighty years old.
So they say that you're all your cells are different every seven years.
People say that people say twenty different guys before you get out of
here. People say that prison that it punishes people instead of reforming
them, but no, I'm going to be completely different when I got it. My brain is
getting completely rewired. When I get out of prison, I'm going to have a
completely different conception of race. Exactly, because in here we're all one
race. We're orange, we have orange, we all wear orange clothes out in the
in the out in the in the old world. That's what we call that, because we
kind of feel like we're pilgrims kind of
coming here. It is brave new world and we're changing it for the better. We're
of terraforming this place. And Pat brought in a few new diseases. Oh yeah.
People have defenses built up against. Nobody here was immune to ADHD.
I've been telling so. Something with the food that was in your butt has also caused it to.
Oh absolutely. To mutate and be easily spreadable. But it did make the steaks better.
Yeah. That is true. It kind of dry aged them. It's working. The one thing that I have been
doing while I have been in here is teaching a lot of the other prisoners about mental health
and mental health awareness. And I've diagnosed pretty much every single person on the cell
block with ADHD and autism.
Which is going to really help in their defenses, I think. I think that's a good chance of getting
paroled.
I've pretty much diagnosed every single person in here with some kind of TikTok mental health
thing.
And if you're scared that we're hanging out with serial killers and stuff.
Yeah, we are.
Yeah, we are. Yeah, sue me. Yeah, I mean, at this point, yeah, Cameron is probably approaching
serial killer numbers.
but also we were doing that before we got sent to jail to yeah. I mean and you
might be too and not even know it. Yeah, that's the scariest part about me to
say killer the Brooklyn all comedy scene. It's more fucked up than you think that
is some real shit. It's pretty much all serial. A huge percentage of serial
killers have been in refuge hiding. They've been put. They've been put into a
lot of people also get put into witness protection in the in the all comedy
scene is something I found out. Yeah, yeah, people like I know you see people
who you're like this person is are they doing a character that couldn't possibly
that be this weird guys like Nathan Fielder, Joe para no, they act like that,
because they're putting on a way to cover it up exactly to cover it up. They've
been horrible things. You think John Wilson, you think he did
you think any human being would talk like that and do you think he turns that
camera off before he walks by people's windows at night and then records them
putting the pin code on their on their door? No, did he steal that shit? He's
going in there, he's slitting throat. Pretty much every single comedian you've
ever, every single comedian you've ever seen, every single comedian you've ever
met has one or six bodies. And if you're wondering, buried underneath their house.
And if you're wondering if we've given up our dreams just 'cause we moved to
prison. Prison. Hello! No, we are still comedians, we are still actors. Guess
what these mics are for when we're not recording the podcast. That's why we are
still screenwriters, poets, authors, and amateur film colorists. Artists.
potential musicians if we ever learned how to play an instrument.
I made one of those. I took the washboards.
I've been working on a song in here really quick.
Do you guys want to hear it?
Yes.
Here's how it goes.
It's called "Beep."
I haven't learned how to do pitches yet.
Uh-huh.
But that's the rhythm behind it.
But once you figure out the notes, that'll sound amazing.
That's going to be the next "Feel Good, Inc."
And it will have vocals as well. It could even be touching.
Yeah.
Yeah, that does sound like "Feel Good, Inc."
Kind of. Wait. Do it again.
you
see that's a sample that song for my song. You can sample it might sample
thirty seconds to my better that's
do it
for a copy. Yeah, exactly that's the other thing you'll copyright anybody is
gone. You guys remember the episode of family guy where he gets diplomatic
immunity. Uh-huh pretty much we have that we have that dad. We have prison
his addict immunity. What are they going? They can't punish us any more than
we've already been punished. We're in jail for the rest of our lives. None of
this shit matters. I'll hit Patrick. I will hit you. What are they going to do?
Not going to. Execute us? The death penalty's been revoked by Communist
liberals in almost every single state. I never thought I would be thankful for a
liberal or a commie in my life, but here I am. But here I am. Guess where we
were going before these liberal bastards? Straight to the chair. We were going to
execution method called the pit that was based on a mortal combat stage.
They're going to throw us into a spike. They're going to do a brutality at us.
We were they don't even think we're important enough to get the camera
angles of a fatality. No, just a brutality. Just punch our heads right
off our fucking heads.
And that was it.
Sometimes I confuse
one of the same in here, the same. Honestly, in here, people are treating
feel like I'm one big foot, so it doesn't fucking matter what my body
they're all massaging you massage me smell me from your own massages.
And what is that? So many? I guess I look tight. The rub king. Yeah, I
guess I look like you get rubbed. I get rubbed. I call him the rub king.
I'm the monk and they call you the
they call you gang. I'm a Megatron. They call you Megatron. Recently,
people have been calling you Genghis Khan. Yeah, they call you the Slayer
Tron. Yeah, they call you the gang is convict. Gang is convict.
Genghis Tron. No, you can't make your own nickname. I mean, you can do
whatever you want because I'm scared of you. We're not gonna tell you what
you can and can't do. The Hound would be cool. The Hound of Cellblock 1000?
The Hell Hound of Cellblock 1000. Yeah, that would work. The Psycho Crazy of
Cellblock 10,000. They've mostly been calling you Cameron though because you
do this when you I don't like nicknames. Yeah, you don't like nicknames. You
don't like names at all. If my name were if I wanted my name to be shorter, I
would have got it legally changed. Yeah, what would you change your to cam? Do
you guys think that I could get people to stop calling me the rub king and
maybe start calling me? I think you'd have to rattle snake. You'd have to go.
Well, I think the award the one way that you can definitely change your name.
Why
you could join Nation of Islam. What about? Oh, I'm already trying to yeah.
They have a lengthy hazing process to get in though.
That makes sense.
I've been getting dunked into big buckets of glue and stuff.
Yeah, they put feathers on you?
Yeah, yeah.
I did see you on the commissary and you were...
Commissary?
Is that the word?
I did see you, you were nude and you had your hand over your balls.
And I was like, "Oh my God."
Guys, I could see you being called "Q-Ball."
That could be cool.
Q-Ball is good.
Q-Ball.
I mean I kind of want something a little tougher because I do I mean you all
cool. I like getting tough man. It hits all the other balls after it gets hit in
the butt with the stick.
I mean, I guess I just want like I like being the rub King. I like okay. What
about
yeah? I mean I can. Oh, I got one Mr Clean, you know what about Mr Sean? Maybe
it wouldn't have anything. It could have nothing to do with what about shiny
superstar, shiny superstar, it doesn't have to be shiny, it's good, superstar,
superstar is a little close, but again, I want you to be like, what about like
popstar is good, popstar is good, wait, okay, the vanilla gorilla, oh my God,
no, no, no, no, no, we are rebranding you as popstar, popstar, okay, we are
gonna take these microphones, we are going to have a prison concert, you're
gonna be like Johnny Cash, but you're gonna go up there and you're gonna be
doing all these like little boy band songs, yeah, you're gonna be doing like,
yeah, big time rush rush style. Yeah, I just went to prison, getting after
children and I feel just like a pop star kidnap the children. It just rhymes.
Okay, I didn't do any kidnap. I don't even know. I don't even know. I don't
know what so much. I mean, we were we we are in here because we shined a laser
pointer at a motorist, allegedly, allegedly, so no, I did that shit. I did
that shit, bro. It was three different. I did that shit. Yeah, I did it too. I
did all the other stuff they said we were doing, but I didn't do that one.
Yeah, I shined a laser pointer at a motorist, a person behind the wheel of a
car, for those who don't know, and I stole movies from free movies.com.
That was why you got in here. That was one of the reasons. I also killed a
family. I left a bunch of fucking dog turds all over the city. Yeah, and the
parking tickets. It was the parking tickets, but guys, I'm going to be
honest, it was mostly the dog turds. Yeah, I drew and I was throwing them in
places. There was I just thought kind of you could put them wherever. So I was
putting them in, you know, those little kid race car things that
the little electric ones. I am not that smart and I don't wear my glasses. That
was a garbage can. So I was and I was accumulating and I wasn't bagging them
either. So I was just kind of just picking them up, throwing them in there.
I'd walk around with a dust pan and kind of just sweep turds into this thing.
Then all of a sudden, this kid sits down in it, squishes poop everywhere, and
basically he sued me because he got grounded for shitting his pants, but
yeah, it wasn't true. I was also I also another charge. They levied against me.
I was I drew crude nudes in my personal notebook. I left it on the train. Yeah,
yeah, I could see doing trace me back based on my based on what they had a
handwriting expert and also you got to stop signing those things. Yeah, well, I
sign it with my address, my phone number and my S. S. N. and then I put $5000
reward if returned, which if they ever do return, I'm saying no man that says
five point oh oh oh dollars. Oh, that's best for and I also don't have five
dollars. Yeah, I don't have any money. I mean, I think if I was if you think if I
was all my money is in cigarettes, I think if I was rich, I'd be drawing
these in my notebook. No, no, I'd be painting them on canvas. It'd be in the
Luma or the eye. The one both the one thing I did get sent in here for
the one thing that I was like, oh, the laser pointer thing, whatever, whatever
and they try, then these mother fuckers try to get me on skateboarding. I have
never once in my life touched a skateboard. You're not a boarder. I'm not
a skater. You're the farthest thing from a skateboard. I don't skate. I don't do
vandalizing of property. No, he's a toy, man. Yeah. I'm a total toy. I don't do
graffiti. Yeah, admit it. He's a toy poser. I don't do graffiti and I don't
skateboard. I'm a complete... And, and this, the alleged skateboarding, there is
no proof. Yeah. There is no proof that I have ever once in my life put wax on a
the ledge and all those videos of Patrick skateboarding guys. That was
not skateboarding. He doesn't land any of the tricks. They all look like
complete shit. He can't do a single fucking thing. I know every clip he's
ever posted. He's not skateboarding. No, you couldn't call that skateboarding.
I went on to be a if I got on the soccer pitch and I fell over and
started putting the soccer ball on my ass and punching my balls and put the
other hand in my mouth. Would you say? Oh, that guy's playing soccer?
basically what he does for the I don't know what soccer is. That's what I would
say a foot sorry foot foot foot foot foot foot foot foot foot foot foot foot
foot, but yeah, you wouldn't call that soccer and you wouldn't call what he
does skateboarding because really it's an embarrassment to skateboarding. We
don't have to go. I mean just well, you said it yourself. You don't scare
well. Just I don't skateboard. Allegedly, we don't have to go or allegedly don't,
but you don't what, but you don't this is the case. This is basically the case
that my lawyer is trying to do. Maybe he was trying to yeah, but he's not.
but he's never he's never successfully. That was what that's what it was.
There's no crime there. Maybe listen. They have attempted murder. They don't
have attempted skateboarding. Exactly, which is not a crime. Apparently, or it
is a crime skateboarding, skateboarding, that's always a complete crime. But
what you were doing with the skateboard, I would say, is arguably even bigger
crime. Yeah, because it was just so hard to art just worth. I mean, just to
call me worthless and I get that you were doing like a kind of Sasha Baron
Cohen satire thing right like wouldn't it be funny if a guy was this bad at
skateboarding, but
it just I get why they locked you up in here as well. Yeah, no, they locked me up
in here for the laser pointer and I'm currently fighting this case that I
ever touched a skateboard. I got it for that. They got our fingerprints on this
laser point. They used it to tie us to all these other cases. I mean this they
let us keep it, even though it's evidence. Yeah, you don't have to switch
it on and off. It's on
I don't know how you don't know how to use...
You don't know how to do anything basically and that's why you're in prison.
This is where stupid people go to die.
But another thing they got me on, I was expiring milk.
Yeah, I would get it from the grocery store and I would just let it sit in my house until the expiration day passed and I'd bring it back.
Bro, that is nasty as fuck.
Oh, you would return it?
Yeah.
You'd switch it out?
Switch out the jugs?
Yeah.
That's a good move.
I mean, you know you're basically just giving people sour cream, right a big
whoop. I got I got way show me literally one line of any US law where it says it
is illegal to expire milk. Exactly nobody even thought of this. You're not
not allowed to expire. I wouldn't have done it if there was a lot that said
that, unless they exactly as they recently put an amendment in the
Constitution, which it could have been because I don't read. I don't read every
update to the Constitution. I do I keep I keep up with it and there's nothing
I saw milk in there even a little bit. They are didn't have milk. They did
what was that amendment? They just are thinking of adding
probably something to to make woke is a mandatory
that literally it makes me want to make a shiv and go down to find the wokest
person in prison and stab them. That's the thing man. I used to think shiv was
a succession character, a woman who's as big as the guys on the show, but now
it's a tooth now. It's a it's a tooth brush that I've sharpened with a knife
that they let me bring in. Yeah,
you whittled it.
Yeah, they give you all these knives. They let me bring you not to whittle
stuff into weapons. Yeah, they let me bring in my knife collection. I have
butcher's knives. I have like little bear grills, pocket knives and shit,
and what is wrong with taking my toothbrush, filing it down to look like a
sharp object. I and as you get in a guy in the belly, your shivs man,
because I'm always trying to brush my teeth and I pick it up and I
fucking hurt my palm because the way I hold the toothbrushes, I cut the
end of it and I am putting a... I have my wet stones too. I know your
secret, Matt. I'm wetting them down. He's lying. I'm doing the whole thing.
I know your secret, man. What? Oh, you're doing a whole thing. I'm doing
a whole thing. 'Cause you're being... Yeah, I know where you're going with
this. You've gotten so much control of your ass by carrying all these
- Yes. - It's a pencil sharpener.
- It's a pencil sharpener down there now.
- Admit it. - Yes.
- I see the crank you attached to your head.
- Oh, it's not even a crank, it's electric.
It's using the electrons in my heart at night.
- You gotta stop 'cause you're keeping me up at night.
I'm trying to fall asleep, right?
- I'm bored.
- I'm looking at my calendar.
- This is the only thing I can do in my free time is this.
- And then you (imitates buzzing)
- And I'm sitting there and I'm sharpening
all the toothbrush
in the jail. I'm sharpening every single end of every single toothbrush and
there's going to be a full scale. Ryan,
listen, if this is how you're doing it, prove it. Why don't you do it right
now to the cigarette? Okay, well, you'd have to I mean, it's he's in a one
piece. I'll take it off.
I mean, you can't take it off. You're going to get banned off YouTube. Yeah,
but guys still have to care about YouTube and we still have to do the
podcast because as much as I would love to move this thing to live leak
doesn't exist anymore. Right. So we still have to do the podcast. If you're
wondering, is it going to end? No, no, no, no, it's not. It will never end.
If anything, we have more time to do it now. We have nothing fucking better to
do, man. We've already, I mean, we've already made the four paintings. I've
already looked at every single date on my calendar. Which, by the way, the 26th
of August is National Dog Day. So look forward to that. Yeah. I actually am
maybe have to step away, step back from the podcast for a little while because I
I do. I did get a job.
You got a job. Yeah, I'm doing a remote work. I'm doing marketing.
Oh, they're fucking who higher ed. I don't want to say this specific school
because I don't want to get fired, but state school.
I don't want to say anything about it really, but I've been building emails
and MailChimp and using Canva and InDesign and stuff. So that's been
taking me a lot of time out of my day.
Are you I mean,
that's interesting. You're going to have time to like I have is I have a
I have a filter on my video for Zoom calls where it makes me look like I'm
wearing a normal shirt
instead of a jumpsuit. You're always wearing that green shirt, Cameron.
Very interesting. It's my favorite shirt. It's my lucky, it's my lucky
business shirt.
Okay, but yeah, let's go ahead. I've prepared. They let me use the internet
a little bit in here. Oh, you have to. Well, I mean, by the way, we do have,
we have Google Fiber in here. Which the reason that I got the job,
besides money, which I do like money is also so to give an excuse to give
myself some internet access here, use some of that extra internet time put
together. So is that slide shows they just give you the internet access for
that? Yeah, they put a computer in my download Baldur's Gate three for me. I
know you know, I don't think they usually let you download nerd ass shit
in prison. They got naked guys in there. Yeah, that's why they're not allowed.
You're not allowed to do that. You're gonna rile everyone else in prison up.
that's why you're only a little jack up to paintings in here. Well in my
calendar
here's a here's what we're looking at today. Here's our list. Oh, so I thought
that this might be pretty helpful for us to have a good laugh. It's one hundred
plus best prison jokes to send to someone in jail for a good laugh. Do we
know this is by Rhoda Mugini? Do we know Rhoda? I think so. I don't know. I think
he might know Rodan. He's a big bird. Yeah, wait. He's a big bird that sits on
top of the prison thinking and I know a genie. Yeah, by the way, guys, I'm
getting really good at basketball. I just wanted to say that and don't say
that I
that's a good nickname. The best I don't. He is the basketball. They call him
the basketball because they are, they are picking him up and they're throwing
him.
Can I be pop? They're throwing him in the hoop. They are picking him up and
throwing him in the hoop. They don't treat me like a ball. They treat him
like a ball because they once they, they saw him on the court the first time
he showed up. They said, "Damn!" Yeah, they said, "Damn, let's throw this guy in the hoop."
"That basketball can dribble himself!" "Damn!" "Let's throw this guy in the hoop right now.
He's making a fool of himself out here." No. He had his hand behind his back and he was
dribbling like this. No, he's mad that I said his skateboarding was bad. I'm not mad. He
was taking it out on me. If you want to fight, we can fucking schedule the fight. I'm not
going to fight. We'll put it up on the calendar. Yeah, we'll put it up on the calendar. 3 p.m.,
meet in the yard. We'll form the circle. Everybody will scream "Fight!" And then one of us will
we'll go to fucking the principal's office. All right, if you want to do
that, I'm not going to fight.
I'm here, I'm here to work on my art prison can be a depressing and
difficult place and finding ways to bring a little bit of humor and laughter
to someone's life who is behind bars can go a long way. If you know someone
currently serving time in jail and want to brighten their day, one option is to
send them a fun need joke. This article has compiled a list of the best prison
jokes sure to make your friends smile one hundred plus prison jokes to send to
someone. I personally I don't need what are you doing because I'm
I'm laughing it up all day every day. We're writing our own jokes for I think
like I think that you're going to like these jokes, though. I think we're going
to read these jokes together and I think we're going to get some good laughs.
Will these make people out of prison laugh? I think that these might be a
little inside baseball or inside jail.
I like that, but you did that, but I think that maybe we can bring did that. I
I think, hopefully, that maybe we can bring prison culture a little bit to
the outside and maybe we can help the rest of the world act more like
prisoners. Yeah, yeah, I do think that I didn't realize that it was such a
we got seen yes, men or yes, man. Yeah, I went on my first date in
middle school to see yes, man, and I ate all the popcorn that she bought.
That's kind of how I see the world now is like the people who are in who are
prisoners. Those are the yes, men. Those are the doers. They said, yes, I
to be in prison yeah because yes, I will report to do legally have to ask the
doers hey. I wish the prison had some doors and they said yeah damn bars see
that's a lot of yes men do end up at being in prison because they ask them if
they did something. Did you murder that woman and yeah, yeah, I have to say yes,
I have to say yes, I guess
god damn it yes, yes, I am a yes man. I have to say yes,
it is difficult to find things to discuss with someone in prison, especially
if you have never been jailed, but sometimes a good joke can be a great
way to break the ice and connect with someone behind bars. So this is good if
you're trying to break the ice with someone who's in prison. Why don't my
job for breaking the ice last week, whether you are penning down a letter or
sending a message through a prison communication system, including a funny
joke and show that you are thinking of the person and trying to bring a little
bit of joy to their day. Now, what is this? Recommended for you. Yeah, Durban
men pay R123 for water at Platinum Belt Lounge after seeing expensive. Oh,
Okay, who are what is a Durban man that is in South Africa? I believe
funny prison jokes. What are some famous prison lines? Check out the
following jokes below that will make any prison smile. Okay, they include the
following. So now we're finally getting into it. I think maybe we can switch
off, switch off reading them, maybe. I mean yeah, but I'll start here.
What do you call a fake noodle in prison? A cell phony?
Okay,
maybe this is like chelphony like maybe there's like a
telephone
yeah, that's kind of funny, but kind of, but I think it's more prison, phony,
fake telephone, a noodle. This is more of a joke for the writers, though yeah
reader, that's definitely readers not going to get yeah. There are the
listeners not going to get it, maybe the reader. All right, well, let's go to
the next one, then okay, you do this one. Okay. Why did the prisoner take a
shower before he ate?
he wanted to enjoy his meal behind bars.
Why bars of soap? Oh
bars of soap, but he doesn't want to enjoy his meal behind bars, maybe
what meal like meal like you take you shower guys like you take a shower.
That makes sense yeah wait okay. He wanted to shout like you oh shout show
maybe it's show or like he wanted to show her everybody has big food. Yeah,
he wanted to show her everyone me likey, maybe the shower
we like to eat food. Oh, no, I get it. Why did the prisoner take a shower
before he ate as opposed to during
while he's eating because the shower doesn't have bars, but it's seldom, so
we wanted to enjoy his meal behind bars in the cell. So it's not so much a
joke as much as it is just like this guy. This is what he yeah,
try to figure out what this means. Is he so why is enjoy his meal? Why died
linked the prize price owner? Maybe it's price owner. Why died the price owner
take a shower shower by for he ate for he ate and ate as in the number yeah he
wanted to years in prison. Enjoy his me all
bad behind bars,
soap, be to watch, watch your behind,
but with a bar, so smart you wash your behind with a bar of soap yeah.
Finally figured it out. Let's go to the next joke. Caleb, this one's okay. I
got you. We had a technical difficulty because of a riot that broke out. I
thought it was a rat that broke. It was a it's confusing because they basically
the same fucking word, which was reverse kudos to whoever invented fucking English.
What happened was the guys outside saw a rat scurry across the floor and it
caused a rat scurry on the floor.
And then somebody said, you want to start a riot?
And I said, you're going to start a rat.
And that's where the confusion, it was the whole confusion stemmed from, and it
started and then it led to, I think, 31 confirmed kills.
Yes.
All from Cameron.
Well, let's go ahead and move to Caleb's joke. All right, let's see. So my joke
now. Okay,
did you hear about the prisoner who invented a teleportation device? He was
sentenced to life.
Oh, life in prison.
Well, but okay, but kind of like us. All right, well, let's do the same thing
we did with the other ones. So sentenced, this is a sentence. True.
It's actually two sentences. So
and also life. Maybe it's like he spent his entire life
teleporting. Yeah,
yeah, this one's hard to figure out. We can I've got a bunch of these. We can
just keep moving forward. Invented, he got in the vents, he tried to escape.
Oh yeah, there we go. That's it. Port.
Yeah, port. Port. Tele. He's on the tele. He's on the tele. On the porta.
Here's another one. That makes sense. Why did the prisoner break his own watch?
you wanted to serve time. Oh, I like that. That's like kind of how drag queens say
serve. Yeah, yeah. Like, oh, he's, he's serving, if somebody's wearing a watch,
they'd be like, oh, you're serving time. Right. It's giving time. It's, that's
giving, oh, that's giving time. A watch is giving time. Serving time. Which is
something I've said for a long time, even before giving came out as slang, I always
say, this watch is giving time. Yeah. Because it gives me time. Yeah. It gives
me the time. So, you kind of invented that. Yeah. Yeah. The whole giving and
serving thing. I was first when it comes to giving and serving, when it comes to
watches and time yeah would be my area on expertise and can honestly say that
watch is a cunt. I usually say it's stuff like she was giving me cunt. She
was and that kind of got corrupted and changed through the power of slang yeah,
yeah, then he turned it in all these branches yeah.
This next one here.
Why did the prisoner bring a ladder to his cell?
He wanted to reach new heights that's straight forward. That's pretty much
Yeah, but I don't like the implication of this, which is that the I mean, I
don't even know that he was gonna cut the he was gonna kick the ladder out
from his foot and kill himself. He's gonna end his own life. Yeah, usually
they do that on a bucket. Yeah, a ladder if you're a tall, real tall guy.
That's true. Ladder if you are tall. Yeah. Well, usually what they really
do is they... So what you get a neck tie or any kind of noose thing,
you tie it around a doorknob and then
slam the door.
it's really
I think you're thinking of pulling teeth. No, no, no, no pulling souls from body
yeah yeah. You slam the door, not really hard. I've heard of that done
because it's tragic. I think that's the way that a lot of eight and nine year
olds kill themselves is by. I think you guys are really getting confused about
the two getting your teeth out. No, you are you saying so you put a piece of
dental floss around your neck yeah, no, no like a neck tie or like a neck floss
yeah, you put neck floss around your neck. You put neck floss or a neck and
then you tied on the door, and then you slam the door, you get your brother to
slam the door as hard as he can, because he's older and stronger yeah. I mean I
guess it would work if you yeah okay, that would work if it's neck floss and
yeah, obviously it's for your neck.
Okay, so here I'll just read these rapid fire. Okay, real quick. What do you call
a prisoner who's always ready to fight celluroid? What do you call a prisoner
who's good at math? Cellculator. What do you call a prisoner who's always on
time? Cellender. What do you call a prisoner who's good at painting?
Cellbert.
What do you call a prisoner who's good at telling jokes? Cellmate. I know
Cellbert. Me too. I know Cellmate too. He does the Cellbert report.
See, the thing about all these jokes,
The things that's great about all five of these jokes here is if you said these in a real prison,
they would laugh. They wouldn't even try to beat you up.
You'd get a huge amount of laughs, yeah.
They wouldn't even try to beat your ass for saying this stuff.
This is good. This will maybe the next time that somebody takes the massage over an hour,
which is my limit, by the way. Past that, it starts giving me bruises like I got cupping
done.
Getting bruised.
I get bruised.
Getting too massaged.
I mean over an hour is just way too much. I'm a very light bruiser, so by the
like a banana yeah, I mean
nobody calls me banana yet everyone calls you banana because they make you
do the splits, but now when I say stop and they say I'm not going to stop now.
I can get them to stop by telling them one of these jokes and rolling on the
ground. So okay, okay, sell you road yeah yeah exactly yeah, you look ready to
fight and you're in prison. You're going to sell your royal fold the phone. We
at the new class clown. I guess a little analysis on their hands off of my
glutes to slap their knees. I think sell bert sell mate. These things are
pretty straight forward, but I do want to analyze really quick, though. What do
you call a prisoner is always ready to fight? Sell you roid. We're seeing two
hyphens here. We're seeing sell you roid, so the you and the roid are separate
things here. Oh yeah, true. We have cellculator, obviously cell calculator,
sell and der, sell calendar, sell bert, don't even need to go any deeper into
yeah, that one's obvious. So you roid so obviously the roid is what is the word
droid, which is created for war and the you could mean I'm fighting you. Oh, it
could mean I'm fighting you or maybe what it means, maybe a you haul right,
but what is the you utility utility? Oh, okay, you are in jail, yep, unfree
the opposite of free
here is some light hearted prison related gags that are not intended to harm or
offend anyone
share the jokes with any of your relatives or friends in jail. Why did
the prisoner refuse to eat his meal? He said it was a con artist
confectionary artist. Yep, the meal was the man. It's funny. I mentioned
confectionary because we're going to be seeing a lot of confectionaries in the
future of these jokes really so just kind of keep that in your mouth in your
brain, my mouth and your brine, your brine, your brine,
yeah
okay. Why did the burglar take a shower after breaking into the house? He wanted
to wash away his conviction. That's pretty. I it's pretty straight. I tried
that kind of dry or should I say wet and dry, wet and wet, then dry, soap and
wet, yeah, so some water, soaked and soaked and wet, wished myself with soap
and wetter.
I wish myself clean. Oh yeah, sound like you're from Wisconsin. I wish myself
clean a little more Australian wished myself a small chief claim. Give me
another joke yeah. Let's see this one. Why didn't prisoners use social media
kind of slipped into Rodney for a second? Sure I couldn't hit it. Why
don't we? Why didn't prisoners use social media? They prefer
they prefer cellular communication.
we have that yeah. We do completely have that I should been doing this every
time doing the God, I'm slipping sorry guys jail is kind of put me in a bit of
a tizzy yeah, and it made me a lot more orange with my clothes. My fashion
changed when I moved to jail. What's this next joke here? Why did the prisoner
keep sneezing? He was allergic to cell mate. That would really be a problem.
Would be that would be such a you're a could be dangerous. If it was a serious
it would be really dangerous. You wouldn't be able to keep you in jail.
No, they'd have to let you free legally. Is this supposed to be like a
solitary cellmates?
Cellmaties. Cellmaties? Cell...
Fuck, this one's tough, man. Cellmate, cellmate, cellophane, latex. Oh, you
could be allergic to... Yeah, some kind of plastic. Cellmates, cellmates,
cellmatates, cellmatates, cellmatates, cellmatates, cellmatates, cellmatates,
a semen. You can't be allergic to semen sneezing. I know who I know guys allergic
to semen. How'd you find out
from a doctor?
A doctor, I was saying a doctor jizzed on me and yeah, I was saying, well,
you're allergic. I was saying it's a guy. I don't like that. You must be
allergic. Let me just put this in this. I was saying it was a guy. I know I was
saying it was a guy. I know because I didn't want to embarrass myself, but you
sent to the doctor. He just on your face and found out I'm allergic to my
semen. My my penis always swells up when semen is near. Yes, I've seen this
happen red and bumpy. Yeah,
you should put that in the joke
bumpy yeah like an allergy because the palpables on the
yeah, it looks like a dog's tongue. Yeah, the palpables make it look like a
citrus fruit. They're like minuscule mushrooms with just as much psychedelic
respect on me. People get penile penis cancer pretty much every day. Oh, some
of us do make your penis bigger. Now it makes it bigger in the way that a
branch of a tree would get bigger and get a separate part of it that's going
off in a different direction. You get to fractalized to mother fucking dongs
yeah swag. Think about a y shape. Think about why my wife and my other wife
my wife's but think about why did I not get penile cancer before? Why did that?
Why is it that a baby suck my prong? Why is it that there's a this always
bothered me in that foster home for imaginary friends porn that I've talked
about so many times? I know the one yeah, they draw blue with two dicks. I
think that makes sense. He's imaginary on top of each other. He's imaginary. He
can have anything you want. Why? When I was a kid, I thought that the second one
was his balls and he's putting his balls into Frankie,
but it wasn't it was his. I've been thinking about this. You've been
thinking about this a lot, but I know I think he actually doesn't have a
ball in that in that in that short film, so he really logically he is a
ball sack and he has to rise or he's a dick and those are his two balls.
Just something I've been thinking of in my so every day. I'll go ahead and
read the next one here. Okay,
why did the prison guard refuse to eat the prisoners cooking? He said it was a
confection. Oh okay, this one's actually make sense like you gave it like a
confession, right? I won't need a confession yeah, it doesn't make it.
Well, that's not actually that's just kind of a thing that yeah, what this
joke should have said is he said it was a confection and what he meant was
confession and he was confused and thought the food
he said confection because he had confusion and he meant and he meant
confection yeah. It should say this is the real version of the joke yeah.
Let's watch this. Why did the prison guard refuse to eat the prisoners
cooking? Well, he misspoke and he said it was a confection, a confection, but
he meant confession and the guard thought it was a confession
and he had confusion. He thought it was alphabet soup yeah. That's why I
thought it was because the guard because it was a confession and by the way
the guards hate confess. They won't eat them. They won't even go near them.
They do not go near that you say confession. They turn around. They walk
the other way all right next one here.
If you have not found the best joke yet, you may want to check these funniest
jail jokes below that are hilarious. They include what a great they include
and then right into it. Why did the cookie go to jail because it was cut
stealing all the chocolate chips?
this is a really good joke to send to somebody in jail. This is yeah. This is
funny because I said this one so far. I said this to the warden and then that
happened in the photo. I beat you up. You beat the shit out of me. It does make
sense because what are chocolate chips to a cookie? Y'all, money, they're
jewelry, jewelry, and what do people steal all the time? I was going to say
they're body parts, but a body part that you could have a variable amount of
like a finger, but more if there are more people with six or four fingers
stand out their jewelry yeah. It's more of a they're adorned on top of a cookie.
They're not really a part of it. So it's like it's like
yeah, it's like so people still do real time right and that's why I went to jail.
So it's just the fact a
chip would or a cookie would definitely steal a chocolate. Yeah, all right,
what's this next one? Yeah, take this one. What do you call a potato in jail?
A French fry.
That's a bit of French fry, a French fry, a bit insensitive
electric chair joke. I don't know if I like that one yeah and also it's kind of
stereotyping the French as
French fries as for as food fries as food, yeah, which doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't sit well with me and French fries don't sit well with me either. When
I eat them, they give me heartburn yeah, seed oil, the salt, the seed oils and so
glad they don't have any seed oil in prison. Oh, well, that's because
everything's put in a hundred percent beef tallow yeah, or maybe it would,
maybe it's some other animal, but it's some kind of a tallow. I somebody's
tallow. I heard that it was it was questing beast from Arthurian legend.
Oh wow, that's an animal that they keep on that only questing can. Oh, it's not
beef talent, beast talent. I don't care what kind of talent is as long as the
taxpayers paid for it. Hey, don't forget to bring your towel because by the way
you that's what I would say if I was high as fuck and I wanted to eat again.
This is a word confusion that you're doing, though you're doing a word
confusion, right? And by the way, guys, we are you if you're worried about yes,
we are welfare queens. Essentially, oh yeah, everybody in prison is
essentially a welfare queen. We're living off your dollar. All right, I got
another lightning round coming up here for us.
Why did the pencil go to jail? Because it was a little sketchy cool. Yeah, hit
that. I will go to jail. It was too tired to tired. You go for being tired.
That was one of my things. Why did the smell was one of the things I went to
jail? Look at some of the other ones here on some of the other reasons. Why
why did the smartphone go to jail? It couldn't control its appetite. Oh, it
ate a woman. What do you call a bear in jail? A gummy bear because of the blow
jobs. What did the scarecrow go to and why did the scarecrow go to jail?
Because it was outstanding in its field, you can go to jail for being too good
here. Yeah. What do you call a fish in jail? A jail fish? That's a jelly fish,
a jelly fish. What did the coffee? Why did the coffee go to jail? It got mugged.
You go to jail. It's illegal. It's illegal to be mugged. Yeah. Why did the
Ryan go to jail because it roared too loudly. No, what do you call a snake in
jail? A hysterical prisoner he's funny. Why did the tomato go to jail because it
was charged with saucery? You can get sauce, sorry, like sorcery, yeah,
sorcery is a very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very
that's one okay, well, that's what we would never do. What do you call a dog
in jail? A cell phone
wait,
and why did the sun go to jail? It was too hot to handle. You can go to you.
What do you call a dog in jail? A cell phone? What do we think about that? So
let's go so like
because okay wait, it's a dog trying to say bone. I sound
yeah, I sell like a blue
yourself. I sell bone would have made more sense yeah, but what do you call a
dog's
maybe dog? Do you call a dog stands for something like device of
girl and geolocation? Why would
because the phone has a GPS? Yeah, yeah, okay, that makes sense a device on board.
It has GPS yeah all right, let's go forward here. Yeah jokes about inmates or
any group of people can be what happens if you click on people. I wonder if that
hyperlink. There was mostly ads. I clicked on all these. Can be insensitive and
inappropriate, even if not intended to be offensive. Okay, so now we're getting
into dark humor. This is my territory. Therefore, we must be mindful of their
potential impact, even as we share them. Number one, why did the prisoner - this is
this is a dark joke - why did the prisoner break out his harmonica? He
wanted to go get out on a good note. Does it mean go out? Go out on a good note?
so like because if this is the dark, this is the dark humor. Oh, like maybe he
passed away yeah yeah he was killed in a well. I just don't know and there's no
way to tell yeah all right. Why did the inmate refuse to watch the prison
documentary? He didn't want to be a connoisseur of crime
kind of he didn't want to be a connoisseur of crime.
Why did the prisoner get mad when he saw his reflection in the mirror? He was
having a hard time. Got a boner. Yeah, he was jacking off at the mirror. Here's
another one. Why did the prisoner refuse to take a bath?
He was afraid of getting soap on a rope.
He's afraid of... Does that mean... Being tied up
in the soap. He was afraid of getting soap on a rope. Yeah, he didn't want to
get soap on a rope in prison. He would rather not have soap on a rope. Do they
have it in prison? They have it in prison so you don't drop it. Oh, but he
he wanted to drop it. He also refusing to take a you know, refusing to take a
not a shower. This is about a bath yeah, so it's also not as much of a problem
when you drop a so we go to a koozie bats in prison that are shaped like
hearts from the Sims. We have whirlpool jacuzzis. They're so powerful that
people have been getting neck and back injuries from getting a world or yeah,
and then they come and they massage me yeah. They say let's make this better
yeah. Yeah, well, I need a massage, but they're saying they need to give a
massage yeah because it relaxes them yeah
prison is the worst place you can ever dream of lie common misconception, but
whatever. Therefore, you should always stay out of trouble. These jokes are the
best for someone. Unfortunately, in jail, why did the prisoner refuse to eat the
steak in jail?
He was afraid of being grilled by the warden. I was grilled by the warden a few
times, so he's afraid that my food was grilled by the war. Okay, way,
personally making it for me put me on a form. I have he put my he put my foot in
a foreman and said you Michael Scott. Now where there is a there is a call me
Dunder Mifflin for weeks.
This this
it is all makes sense. This joke makes sense. If you think about a simple,
I think it's from the Bible yeah, you are what you eat right exactly. I was
going to this makes perfect sense. If he was a stake yeah, so he's saying you are
that you eat, you eat a steak, you become a steak and then all of a sudden and by
the way to a warden, these guys are hungry. You walk around and you're a you
know five foot eleven steak walking through his halls. He's going to eat
you yeah, he's going to grill you and eat you exactly it's dangerous.
What do you call a bear in jail?
A prisoner of bear,
because if you're a bear in jail, you're probably in a prison made for and run by
by bears. Oh, this is making some sense to me. This is not recently poses a
world where bears run and are in prisons. Yeah, because why would a human put a
bear in prison? That's just a zoo. Yeah, doesn't make much sense now. Oh, oh,
what do you call a bear in a zoo?
A zoo bear?
Wait, no, that wasn't
just guessing. I mean, I guess I maybe wrote a joke. I don't know. That's a
good joke. Thank you, man. All right, what's this? All right, just a couple
left here. Okay. Why do prisoners wear stripes in jail? Fact check. We don't
always. We don't always wear actually against the dress code. Let's try to
check in the middle of jokes. I don't know you guys want fucking sorry about
that. Okay. Why do prisoners wear stripes in jail so they can earn
their fashion stripes? Well, you already have them according to this. These
aren't fashion, but again, you can't wait. Maybe we haven't earned our
stripes yet, but there's a lot. The dress code is pretty strict. You can't
have a skirt that's above your finger tip. You can only have a baseball hat if
it's backwards. Yeah, yeah, you can't no big white t shirts, only sunglasses you
can have if they're cool. You can't sag because apparently that means something
else. Secretly, we are gay. Yeah, well, that's you can't swag.
You can't swag your pants. You can't sag your pants. Secretly am really. That's
secretly am gay is what sag stands guy in honestly speaking of jail.
these guys are on speaking about a strike. That's what I'm going to say
speaking of guys who are belong in prison, the writers or the the sectors
with a sag to her sectors screen and her's gill really are gay. Oh
huh all right this next one.
Why do inmates love playing soccer in jail? It's the only way they can score
now that's not true. Yeah, that's not true. I get
yeah next joke, though
yeah next one. So that was actually the last joke, but I
have here a few other things. This is at the bottom of this
of this list. Okay, so maybe you can read this out. This is
actually pretty interesting. It's more of a fact,
so I'll play a different sound effect after it.
What are some slang words for prison? What is the slang for a
jail cell? Here are some of the popular ones. So there's three
here number one the big house,
the joint
and the slammer.
Wow, that's I mean I just call it. I just call it home me too. Yeah, and
then I have one last thing I before I found these jokes. I was looking for
other prison stuff and I was looking for more Q. I was looking at Q and A
like we did for that evil one and here there was only one good Q and A
question, but I wanted to throw it in just as a bonus at the end because I
did really like it, but there wasn't enough other stuff to for it to make
make sense to do a Q and a one, but here's a question answer someone has
about prison.
Will my flatulence bother my cell mate and here's the answer yes. If your fart
stinks, you'll likely get what they call rolled out and that's a bad thing. Go
sit on the toilet, fart and flush the suction from the water flow should help
with the smell. They want you to flush the fart yeah. I should get rolled out
the fart.
If it's between flushing my fart and getting rolled the fuck out yeah, I'm
I just didn't realize that that was prison etiquette, but I guess I will
start. Yeah, I thought you just had to light a match. We get matches by the
way. We get matches. We also get those lighters that you use to light candles,
the long neck ones. Yeah, we get those. We get those for our cigarettes. We get
Zippos too and the good ones. We get the ones that we get the ones, yeah,
the ones you get in a glass case in the Midwest at a gas station. And guess
who's paying for them? Joe Biden. Joe Biden, Mitt Romney.
all through your pockets. So guys, go out and vote. Vote for whoever's going to
vote for me. Vote for as he's going to be prom king likely to be most
attractive of the prison. Yes, in a couple of years, once I get my act
and they're letting us do our stand up dates, they're letting us, we're going
to be wheeled out like Hannibal Lecter on all the shows. It's technically a
conjugal visit. Yeah, but yeah,
tomorrow and through the weekend, I'm going to be in Washington D. C.
appearing as a hologram
with Mr Adam Friedland and was actually in here to he's actually in here for
being a gay bug.
And
yeah, so that's the life
And I am going to be also I'm not going to be a hologram. I'm just sending a
guy that looks like me. MF doom style to do that. Yeah, but nobody looks like
me. Yeah, that's the problem. There's a lot of guys look like me.
I'm going to be in Pittsburgh and in Baltimore opening for girl God on their
tickets are on their website at girl God dot co. I think I don't know. I
my lord God girl God the website.
Just Google.
Just Google you fucking idiot.
Just Google you dummy.
And I mean speaking of guy holograms and guys who look like each of us,
my wife does not know that I am in prison, so don't tell her.
Do not tell her.
And if you want to help us buy more cigarettes and hopefully some bubble
tape, go check out the Patreon.
I love bubble tape.
Well, with the bubble tape, I'm hoping to make a saw out of bubble tape and
saw my way out of this world.
I have been again bubble tape is something I was addicted to on the
outside and it's been pretty it's been pretty hard on the inside. My guy is
itching because he keeps trying to put it in the wrong way. He's trying to put
it in. I can't a bubble bubble tape because I get too excited. He starts
chewing it with his but he's yeah and then you don't even get to enjoy it.
Now it's just your butt getting on yeah, my butts getting so much fun in
prison, my butt over who can get more fun, my butter, my mouth.
Why? Well, why do you care you're not your mouth? I am my mouth you. Oh, if
my face, if my butt gets more fun than my face in a week, I literally try to
kill myself. Yeah, that makes sense or at least chop the bottom off. Yeah, you
ever see those guys with no. I try to turn into to a Diablo three enemy where
I call that my intestines coming out of the video recently. That was the guy
with no bottom half and he's doing boxing. No, no video of this guy doing
boxing and I was sitting there and I was like this guy is living the dream. No,
No, but never have to worry about walking around with a shoe on.
He's never had swamp ass. He has swamp bottom.
That's the only thing I think that is horrible about him.
I bet Daredevil style his body makes up for it and his belly button smells really bad.
He also doesn't have to worry about pants. It's hard to buy men's pants.
He's just a shirt guy.
I hate buying pants.
Me too, but I wonder if he wears lady tighties.
We'll see you guys on Saturday for National Dog Day.
And then next week and then next week and then next week for about 150 years.
Bye.
I believe.
I think somebody's selling drugs outside of my apartment.
Yeah.
I saw an old, old man and a young, young man sitting on the bench right outside my apartment.
There's a bench right up front.
It could be father and son.
But a third man of an age in between the two men
came by and sat down and the young man
reached into a plastic grocery bag,
brought something out and slid it very slyly,
breaking bad into me.
- Was it drugs?
- I have to assume it was drugs or a rare baseball card.
- It could be a rare baseball card.
- And they looked at me and I broke eye contact
and then I've been scared for two days
that they're gonna try to kill me.
- No. - Because I know.
- They don't know that you know.
I mean I was walking around weird, I was acting really weird.
Yeah you had your, like you had a huge paper and a camera.
Let me rewind time for you, here's how you should have handled that.
Okay.
You see him slipping the thing into his bag, you in your brain, you know you've just seen a drug deal.
Yeah.
Maybe you're gonna get killed for knowing what's going on here.
Here's what you say.
They're evil.
You look at these guys on the bench, here's what you say.
"Geez, you guys are always sitting here doing completely nothing.
Why don't you find a hobby? You're not even doing anything, you're just sitting there."
Get a job you lazy bones!
You haven't even moved in the past 10 minutes.
You've been sitting completely still there doing nothing.
You've been sitting here for hours talking to your friends, giving them gifts.
Stop loitering. No, not giving--
No, no, no, no.
Sir, doing nothing.
That's what I'm saying.
Doing completely nothing.
Yeah, you should say, "Why don't you take up a hobby like drug dealing or something?"
I wish you guys would sell fucking drugs, because at least I could buy some.
Yeah, they know that you don't know that they're doing anything.
That's how you repair the thing, is like, "If you're selling drugs, I would like some."
Right. I think you're not dealing drugs, so you shouldn't kill me.
But if you were, it would be okay with me.
That's what I was wondering.
Is it better if they think that I'm a police officer
because I kind of have a police officer's head and build?
Or is it better if they think that I'm just a just a-
A wasteoid?
Yeah, because who are they least-
Who are they less likely to kill?
Probably a cop.
[MUSIC]