I
move it down, then you can see it in the frame. Remind you of anything man.
It reminds me of a Neptune,
which is today's don't do that's going to fuck up a cable or something.
it's supposed to be our prop for the day. Now it's gone. Now the prop for the
day. You've ruined the prop of the day. Well, it's quite close. Well, I could
crazily easily get that. You guys, we completely blew ourselves.
Oh, I remember that. Tobias. No, we did a video where we were all in blue face
paint. But we didn't say blew ourselves in that. That's straight up from Tobias.
Yeah. We became completely blue. We should have got the fucking face paint
dude. We saw a blue face man over there. We could do it. No, I'm not doing it. No,
that's a bitch to take off.
But maybe this was okay. But hold on. Okay, do it again, though. Okay,
and we're blue. No, we're actually we're not. If you're listening at home,
imagine us blue. Imagine we blew ourselves right there. Blue.
No, no, no, no, no, guys. How the fuck is the East Coast been man? I've been
gone out of you have been gone. You have been gone. I've been out.
Howdy dude. Tell me dude. I've missed so many different aspects of the East
Coast bro. Last night I went to Guitar Center to buy new bass strings and
then I saw through, I think it was the Morgan L. There was a
homeless fella sitting on the bench and I thought that he was jacking off,
but I guess what he was doing was under his jacket, flipping off everyone
on the bus. That's sick. On the train. That's cool. He's sitting there
lifting the jacket up doing like a little what's wrong with you. I think
everybody's any homeless person. I thought it was jacking off because the
hand motion, but he was just flipping little birds at everyone. It was so
sick. He was jacking off with the other hand. Maybe he was jacking off with the
other. He was jacking off to being disrespectful yeah
get a homeless person. I screw you. I think this is maybe the second episode
in a row. We started with talking about homeless. Yeah, we got to start
talking about it. We it makes us we're leaving Earth. No, it doesn't it doesn't
it's fine to say whatever you want about whoever you want. Yeah, do you say
what I change my mind all that you change? He's got has been sleepy as
fuck without you really bro. I'm honestly life has ground to a halt dude.
I knew that I've been doing a vegetable and fruit puzzle playing some video
game. You left you and I got a vegetable and fruit puzzle. I've there's so
one as today. He needs to do a vegetable and fruit so much stress in my life
that I got into sins right yeah. I started chewing sins. I show you
them. I chewed them and I swallowed all the salt. Bro, you got to drop the zins
and get on the different zins, the Zinfandels. The Zinfandels, I should.
You have to become a connoisseur. I should. Exactly. Zinfandel, by the way,
very fancy wine. I
bought zins and not even thinking about it, picked out the citrus flavor.
Which reminding who you are. Reminding me of a little green fella that I need
to talk about immediately, because there was a problem. What was the problem?
So...
so
you reach a register. I never heard before.
Me and my friend,
okay, it's been, you know,
it's been rough. It's been rough. I've been dealing with a lot of stressful
stuff and I've been having to deal with this fucking OJ, the alien guy,
and so I got writer's block. I have to write all the songs for him and then
you've been writing the songs for I've been writing the songs and he's my God.
He is he has been rapping yeah. I'm a ghost your oh my God. I'm not you
probably wrote Dr. Dazzle's verse two right no, but I right that makes sense.
That's a different. What about be likes
I don't know, but I've been writing all of the I wrote all of OJ's. I write
them as writer. I had no idea, so I'm getting I hate writers block. I call up
my friend Rupert Rupert's a very talented musician and
OJ hits me back and says, "No, I don't need you and Rupert. I have already written the
Neptune song with DJ Gleptar."
No.
So, me and Rupert, I mean Rupert flew all the way here from Los Angeles to record and then
--
And from Australia to Los Angeles.
Yeah, and then we had to --
And from somewhere else.
And from his mother to the earth.
Yeah, we had to send him back. I'm down 3K.
Jesus Christ.
Studio time plus airplane.
Where does a store get the kids from?
I don't know planet baby, but so he's going through space and the baby has to
hold its breath. Well, that's why I work with wings and not a crawling animal
like a toad. You guys a toad will a toad would jump. I was thinking of a
horned toad, which is a lizard. We're going to get right into the I pictured
in my head. We're going to go right into it.
Just leave that alone. It's completely true, but I don't
we're going to get right into the OJ. The alias we're doing the song first.
We're doing the song first. Just like Mercury, we're doing the song first.
The song before the Planet Report? Yes. Holy shit. All right.
Because, you guys, this song has ruined my life.
Julio? Oh, Julio's here. I'm here. By the way. Oh, yeah, wait. Switch to your
camera. Yeah. Is it on? Say hello. It's off. It's off. Well, he's right there,
guys. He's behind the laptop. I think he put himself into the bar in there.
Ow.
It's fine.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I got this beat from DJ Gleptar.
Neptune, Neptune I wanna get you, get you
Back to my room, my room Wanna sex you, sex you
Neptune, Neptune Wanna get you, get you
Neptune, you're the sexiest planet
Yeah, talk to Mercury and that bitch get caned
I love you, you so blue
Venus is my BM, but I'm in your DM
That kid is a dud
That kid dumb as fuck
The way that he's mine, he put his mouth on a truck
Venus, tell your kid, put his mouth on the curb
I pay child support every month and the third
Stop telling family court that I am a perv
But Neptune, you have my word
I can take you out once those payments deferred
Neptune, Neptune
I wanna get you, get you
Back to my room, my room
Wanna sex you, sex you
Neptune, Neptune
[Music]
M.S. girl, are you listening?
Get to number one
There's no life on V.S.
'Cause that kid ain't mine
You're just a little bitch, you take a little shit
Give me the cork, I'll play with it
The kid's not mine, I love wine
I started crying, won't let him get sick, Christmas time
Think that I'm blind, took M.S. on prime
I deleted his wish list, now he's gone, I love wine
I smoke a cork, feel mighty fine
That kid ain't mine
[Music]
So apparently the Venus diss track is because it she's his baby mama. He had
sex with Venus. Fuck Venus. Fuck Venus. We hate that shit. It's kind of making me rethink my
working relationship with OJ the alien. Venus is a bad guy. Venus is a very deadbeat
person. How did Venus... He's not even a person. How did he have a kid with a planet bro? I
don't even know how any of that works. Also... He's trying to have a kid with Neptune. How
Why does he make a planet go perpendicular? It's a round shape.
That's a good. Well, that's you know
you're going to you should have learned something from the Uranus planet report
that planet is at a right angle to the other planet. So you can consider wow
nothing is at any kind of angle. If it's round to the rotational axis, but
you actually that's all just that's all pretend right. It's does not like
here's the thing about space man. I've been thinking about this and I've been
waiting till the eighth episode to bring this up. Which way is up in fucking
space? Wow, then you can't in space. No one can hear you scream
That's true, that's crazy. No one can hear you cream dude. No Neptune can be
cream on earth either. I've got private. I've had like creamed on. I don't I don't
have a cream at all. If I cream in my bathroom alone and no one is around to
hear it, did I cream? No, no, I did not according not unless my wife starts
installing security cameras, threatened to my started.
Did you guys ever know anybody used to jack off in the toilet? You've talked
about this in the chat in the yeah, my friend Chad used to check off in like
lean over the toilet and spurt over is so crazy. He told me that he was like
like it was everybody did that and I was like I don't think most people do that
man's like milk in his shit like he's got an utter to be a jack off into the
toilet. Yeah, you did. He said yeah, oh well, I guess that's two guys. I know
what are the odds of the two people I've ever heard doing that are close friends
I know. Do I attract these milkers? I guess you do. You kind of have a male
milkers. Just something to think about. You attract male milkers.
What? How? So, DJ Gleptar. But I guess this is also, speaking of, this is,
we, this is, you said eighth episode. I guess we're in, are we in week four? Is
it week four now? I don't even know. I think we're in week four. I think it's
week four day one. Wait, maybe it's the seventh episode. Week four day one. No,
it's, it's, yeah, it's the, yeah, it's the seventh. Okay, seventh. Okay, yeah.
zero week for day one. Y'all I can't believe wow it feels like we've been
doing this for ten weeks already. I want to do the fifty two weeks of play and I
want to do the fifty two weeks of the year. I want to do it once a year. I
want to do fifty two weeks of planets and I think that we should find planets
and other solar systems. This has been the longest month of my life and take a
look at him. Oh this guy hates Thanksgiving morning. Yeah, I honestly
believe that outside of the planets. I think that the weeks the five weeks of
planets has brought misfortune upon me. Why I think that I can't I can't I just
there's things in my life. I feel like I feel the same way I've been sick for
most of trouble trouble week of pilot since I would say since about the week
before Halloween trouble has followed me, which at first every trouble starts and
it's before how we need thinking man. This is I know what this is. This is the
Halloween blue. Yeah, this is the trick is the how for the tree Halloween curse
yeah, but then the treat never comes and then you're never come and then you're
getting into the Thanksgiving month and you're thinking well what the hell's
what gives this must be the this is the curse of the Comanche's, but then that
maybe is going to stick around right. They wouldn't curse me out. They wouldn't
curse one of their own exactly good point. Yeah, if anything, I should be
cursing you guys. Yeah, yeah, because we've disrespected your ancestors so many
different times. Yeah, I don't think that's about ancestry today. I think we
should keep the planets because I'm too scared to think about anything
superstitious. Do you know who DJ Gleptar is? This guy's really a
DJ Gleptar fucking killed it. He bodied that shit. Yeah, DJ Gleptar did a very good job.
I don't know who DJ Gleptar is. So to be clear here, this is the song that was
made without your and your friend Rupert's involvement. Yes. This is the
one that you guys were going to cook something up. We were going to cook
something. We had something amazing. I think it was actually this beat. Maybe
DJ Gleptar stole it. I'm not sure. No. DJ Gleptar, say it fast. Klepto. Klepto.
Oh my God, and you read it backwards. It's rat pelg. Wow, which a d
j.
Rat pelg jd. That could be some other guy's name to that could be a
different guy's. So now we're looking for backwards is dork. Yeah, and wait
and alien backwards is Nila Nila. Oh, shit. Wow. We're unlocking so much
different stuff from reading things backwards. It's crazy. Okay, so we did
the song first, which is a bit unorthodox, but really I need to know what we're
even going to talk about because I've been I've been in my a man. I've been on
the other side of the planet, so I need the report. I'm going to be really the
report. I need the report because I need a baseline of information, so I can talk
about this shit in a way that yeah, that's fair enough. People's minds.
Let's go ahead and do the report. Let's hear this report. The damn thing
join us once again on a five week galactic journey through our solar
system.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh a little tooth
and now the planet report with Cameron
is joking around it's okay. It's a long it's a long clip, so you could you're
supposed to make jokes in it kind of I got a long for you
chill on him. Okay, today's today's planet report is
It's a story.
Wow.
It's a bit like a fable.
Planet story.
So this is the story of Neptune, a planet report by Cameron Fetter.
Once upon a time, 30 astronomical units away from the sun, there was a blue and icy planet
named Neptune.
One orbit, Neptune woke up and felt depressed.
What makes me special?
Neptune. I feel so average. Don't worry Neptune, said the sun. You're very special. For example,
you're an ice giant. Your distance from me means that you're dark and cold, covered by frozen,
icy materials. Big whoop, replied Neptune. That doesn't make me unique. Uranus is an ice giant
as well. Well, maybe your surface doesn't matter. It's what you're like on the inside that counts.
"You have a rocky core," the sun said.
"Yeah, right. So does Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Uranus, and probably Jupiter and Saturn, too.
I knew I wasn't special."
"Oh, I know what makes you special.
You have an oval-shaped storm in your southern hemisphere called the Great Dark Spot."
"Uh, Jupiter much?"
"Hmm." The sun rubbed its chin with its hand.
"Let's see, your day is 16 hours long, but your year is 165 Earth years.
You have 14 moons, you were discovered in 1846, you have rings, is any of this helping?"
"No, it's not," yelled Neptune violently. "In fact, you're just making me feel worse.
I think I'm going to kill myself." And Neptune opened its desk drawer with its hand,
where it kept its revolver and used its hand to put the gun to its atmosphere.
"No!"
"I'm done doing this with you!" screamed the sun in anguish.
*snickering*
"It seems like every rotation you threaten to kill yourself.
You think you have it bad?
Look at Pluto. The poor guy isn't even a planet anymore."
"Even my suffering isn't unique," sighed Neptune.
"I think I get it now.
I was so concerned with being special,
but what's actually special is that I'm so similar to everyone else in my solar system.
It's about togetherness and family."
"That's right," said the Sun. "I'm glad you came around when coming around the
Sun. Yeah, I'm coming around me. I mean the me, the me. Let's see!" And the
planets all started in on their Thanksgiving dinner.
Moral,
the moral of the story. Okay, there is nothing interesting about Neptune.
no good facts. Nothing good. You couldn't find anything. It's the eighth planet.
They covered everything. Yeah, everything's been done. There's a blue,
there's a blue one. There's a nice one. There's a spot. There's nothing man.
Fucking shit planet and it sucks. God there's the Neptunes. They there
wouldn't there wouldn't be
without the name Neptune as a cool symbol and we wouldn't get we wouldn't
get the song happy by Pharrell if it weren't for the Neptune. Why are they
called the Neptune? I don't know, maybe because there's nothing unique about
them. No, they're like everything else. They're water based. The two guys are
water based? I don't know. Everyone's water based. Yeah. I guess we're all
water based. Even the biggest stretch in the world. Oh, because they were so
cold. But there's a... Oh, Pharrell had a company called Ice Cream. Ice Giant.
Ice Giant. Oh, speaking of... And they were ice giants, they were so cold.
they might be giant. My shirt walk us through the fit. It's a blue shirt that
says giant on it and a blue hat that says Mexico for my Mexican friend and
Mexico's on a planet. Yeah, okay, my landlord came into the apartment. I was
talking to him and I was said, Oh, my friend is here. He's visiting from
Mexico. My little Mexico, I said, Yeah, Mexico, Mexico, and I said, Yeah,
Mexico, and he said, like he's Mexican. I was like, Yeah, he's like Mexican. I
said, Yeah, he went. Oh, wow, not too sharp. This landlord guy. No, no, no,
How did you feel about that, Julio?
I feel special.
Yeah.
Julio, how was your -- you got in this morning at what time was it?
I thought I was going to land at 6 a.m., but I landed at 5, which was really fucked up
because I was Ubering to Kams, and I had to call him 20 times before his phone rang once.
But it was okay because my alarm was set, and I woke up at the right time anyway.
Yeah.
Nice.
funny screenshot now that I can post with a really funny caption when he calls
from twenty miscalls from Julio and and caption it something like when you say
you're fifteen years old or something like that.
That would be you really get
so give me that's not funny. That was easy money. You're a destroyed, but
apparently he got stopped by border patrol because they didn't like his drip.
They don't fuck with me. No, they don't fuck with you or not.
They look at because you look like that because I look like a boss. No, it's
They did not say, "I'm sorry, I have to go to another room."
They say, "You look like a baos. Come over here."
"This guy came off the plane like a baos and we detained him for 20 minutes."
That's what they said.
They did not say that shit, man.
They took me to a room and the next 20 people that got sent into the room
were all from China or Hong Kong.
So those are baos.
They thought he was Chino.
Oh, they did think he was Chino.
Yeah.
And so they sent you to the Chino room.
Yeah, they said, "You're too much of a baos. Come here."
No, they didn't say anything about you being a baos, man.
That's what they said.
They did not say what do you are you here for work? What do you do here for work?
You're such a bouse. I'm a bouse. I'm nothing. I'm actually an employee. I'm
not a bouse. You went to the VIP of customs. I don't think I exist.
The VIP of customs, that's crazy. Yep. I can't wait to go to another country and
get locked up forever. Yeah. Yeah. They've troubled me before. Do you guys
think that you would enjoy getting extradited? I don't know. Probably not.
or from somewhere to here. I get like where am I where am I? I just think I
do fun to be sent somewhere and do they put you on a normal plane? Do they do
that in real life or only in Batman? They do that in real life man, but if
you do you go to a class or yeah, they did Brittany Griner. I did Brittany
Griner. I put you in a prison shackle and then they put you on a your own
put a balloon on you and then they fly into the bat plane. Yeah, no, that's a
different that's a movie man. Bane does it doesn't never happen in a real
kind of pain. It happened in the second one. Huh wait what that's the on that's
why
and they say he's
the Chinese guy. Now they send them on. They say Chinese or no. They said China
won't extradite him one of their own. So Batman does it. So Batman comes and he
balloons him yeah. He sends a
please no bro. I'm back to make. I've seen that movie. I've seen the dark
night of couple times. Now
I zone out when that scene is on it's a crazy. I was boring. I still don't
understand what it has to do with the plot of the move. No, not I could not
tell you what how it relates to anything. Is it about remembering that it happens?
Is it
to
motivate the Joker show me more? Joe Wayne Industries, maybe show me Mo Joker.
Yeah, I don't care about I want to see Heath Ledger bring him back the Bruce
Wayne parts of any Batman movie do not interest me, except for the new one,
where it's the only interesting part of the movie. Yeah, but in the first three
What do you mean there's a fucking car chase? I don't give a fuck about that
car. The car chase was kind of okay. I like the part of Riddler was dope. The
parts of the new one where he's walking around and just looks fucking bummed out
and Charlie's Angels. He's got that Charlie's Angels swag and he's walking
around in his suit just like Charlie's Angels. What do you mean? Remember?
What's the guy with the hair from Charlie's Angels? Oh, Sam Rockwell guy.
No, the fucking Christopher, not Christopher, the guy who's weird.
Bosley?
No, the guy who's weird.
Oh, creepy thin man.
Yes, he's Crispin Glover.
When he's Crispin Glover and he's walking around and he's got his hair down and he's
like this, "This sucks, I have to fight the fight."
There's no better part of any movie when a guy is acting emo.
That's always the best part of every movie.
We need every movie to be like this now.
Manchester by the Sea?
I never seen that, but I've never ever seen that movie, but it does sound sad
to me. I've seen the clip where he tries to kill himself. I've only seen the
clip where he tries to kill himself. I don't know if that's what it's about.
What's the saddest movie you've ever fucking seen? That, though. Wait, dude,
Neptune is the blue. Yeah, the blue is the coldest planet. What makes you feel?
We need to talk about being blue. We're both having a rough month. I have
sickness. He's into nicotine these days, and you have a Mexican in your house.
I have unrevealed struggles. You have unrevealed struggles that can't even-
that people wouldn't even believe if you said what they were.
Unpublished. Yeah.
Violent struggles.
Yeah. Violence within me.
So what's the bluest movie you've ever seen?
Come and See. I saw Come and See
at my parents' house two years ago.
Two years ago, and I shut it off at the end.
And then that was when I was sober.
And then I saw that and I got so sad that I drank a Bud Light out of the fridge
and ended spidey.
That can't be fucking true.
I was a common seed drove you to drink. I was also bored. You got drove to drink
by a movie. I got drove to drink
the wag his probably some other crap going on in my life at that time as
well. Driven to drink by a movie. It should be like the the Baz Luhrmann
great Gatsby or something.
Project X
but yeah, it's an
really funny, though, about the Baz Luhrmann great Gatsby and he just gave
the music. Oh, shit.
A little party never hurt nobody.
Now there's other crap. You can't watch train spotting and be like, oh, I want to
do it. I need a white claw.
Fuck. That's not a sad movie, though.
Train spotting at the end.
He chooses life.
Isn't that one of the saddest things of all?
That is the saddest thing.
He had to choose it.
True. Real shit.
I mean, I watched I forget the name of it, but it was a Japanese movie, a Takeshi
Katana movie about a deaf guy who learns to surf and it was a really sad ending. It was
so sad that it made me angry. I was mad at the movie for ending that way.
That happens a lot to me in movies. I don't think movies should have poor endings. They
should all be smiley. Poor endings. This movie made me feel poor. Poorly bad. I can't think
of a really sad movie.
That one too. It was such a nice and loving movie.
Japan, bro. Surf's up.
It was a Japanese beach movie.
Surf's not bad.
About surfing, about overcoming a disability to surf.
How wonderful is that?
Which by the way, in terms of disabilities and surfing, I mean there's people who surf
with fucking no legs.
I'm not sure death is that crazy.
There's people who got eaten by a shark.
Well, you watch the movie, you're going to be surprised by what happens.
Is that what happens?
He gets eaten by a shark?
No, that would be a funny way to end sadly.
You could surf if you were just a head.
What was that movie, Soul Surfer?
The girl loses her arm?
Oh yeah, that's a real story though.
That's a true story.
yeah, it's not it's not just real. It's true wow and a lady lost her arm to a
shark to a shark and she was like fuck it. I'm going back. I gotta go. Are you
crazy? What are you stupid? She is stupid bitch. Are you crazy? Are you
stupid? You should be getting workman's comp from the ocean and sitting at home
all day stupid as getting paid in sand dollars. Well, but maybe she's looking
for the shark. Oh, I just realized she's looking for attention. Maybe it's that
oh wait. If well yeah, I wait. If I go back out and keep serving, I'll get so
much, but like a movie about me yeah, maybe it's actually I just realized
maybe it's surfing was her passion. I'm happy now.
No, can't be that
not fucking with that surfing can't be a passion. Did surfing is a way to pass
the time surfing is below heroin? Yeah, passion, a time yeah, passing a little
bit. That's how I for a time in all the time. That's how it all surfers.
They add S H to every single word. You guys didn't have many surfers up there
No, no, no, no.
There's some surfers. I mean, definitely not like a strong surf culture, but Cape Cod, I
definitely saw surfers around.
These are some of the smelliest people of all time.
They smell like salt.
Salt water.
Yeah. They're all, they're tan. They won't wear flip, they won't wear shoes.
They wear those ugly dune suits.
Yeah, wet suits.
Wet suits.
You guys ever worn a wet suit?
No.
How come you wear a wet suit to keep dry?
Well, it doesn't keep you dry.
It doesn't keep you dry at all.
Think about that.
It keeps you warm.
keep dry. Why are you doing like like just 4 a.m. Rodney Dangerfield waking up
kind of still half asleep? Why do you wear a wet suit to keep dry?
To keep dry.
I get no wet. I get no wet suits. I don't know what's going on.
Bro. I get no wet suits.
I'm just gonna go. I get no wet. I'm gonna go home. I'm just gonna get
I was going to go home. I get no wet was okay for I get no wet. That was kind of
a woman just walked by with Mickey Mouse ears. God Mickey Santa went to Disney.
The Santa that I like went to Disney. He got interviewed on the spinning tea
cups. They asked him what's your favorite Disney can we ever talked about
the Santa? I know I'm going to be doing an expose on the center, but just this
is a preview. Maybe you mean the Santa that you like. I'm so out of the don't
worry about it. The Santa that you like the fuck's happening. There's a Santa
Cameron likes. What is that? There's only one Santa man. No, there's a lot of
there's a thriving. Oh wait, wait, sorry. Do you mean a Santa's helper that you
know? No, this is on the teacups getting interviewed and the guy says, what's
your favorite Disney character? And Santa goes like this. Oh,
Mickey Mouse
cop out dumb ass.
Talking about Santa biggest, the world, a winter character. Yeah, Olaf Olaf say
Scrooge McDuck at the end of the movie. Yeah, yeah, Jesus Christ Mickey Mouse.
Oh, shit, dude, a four year old kid wouldn't say Mickey Mouse. No, I saw a
Grinch.
You were a Grinch. I were a Grinch and then I saw one. I went to a street fair
while I was in L.A. Yeah, show you a video. I took him and talked about your
L.A. Trip at all. Yeah, because I was like that or I went through an entire
bottle of Dayquil in like four days, but I did see a Grinch and I videoed him and
he was actually good at it. He was pretty
(laughter)
(radio playing)
- You can hear him.
- That's not Jim Carrey, who said that's Jim Carrey?
(radio playing)
(laughter)
- Oh, that's I included.
- It's that, oh shit, it is getting to be that time of year
when Grinches are just gonna be around.
That shit always weirds me out.
- He had the full makeup and everything and a pot belly.
I saw I was home for Christmas a couple of years ago. I saw a Grinch just by
the side of the road, not even hanging out in a like a mall or anything that
he was a stand. He was on a an overpass just sitting on the side. I think I
took a video of I don't know. I probably can't find it right now. He's just
sitting on the overpass and he wasn't even doing anything. He's full
Grinch down and I was rolling down the window and pointing at him. He's kind
of going. Here's what's wrong with the America and the and children and
society as well. Yeah, I go to this this fucking winter wonderland parade right.
Is that the O? One? No, it was in new hall california. My brother's open in a
pool hall up there and I went new all. It's a good spot for a new all the new
all. Yeah, yeah, go check it out the break room. There was
so it's like ten thousand people in this like little downtown area and
the Grinch is doing a meet and greet winter wonderland. Welcome to whoville
and there were slutty who's there. I'll say it there was a lot of who's and
then, as I get closer dude sponsored by a church, so I'm like what the hell is
on with these sluts. I didn't know they were allowed in church, but the line for
the Grinch around the block, literally 200 kids and their entire families around
the block, right? I walk a little bit further. Santa Claus, 10 people in line,
10 people in line. What's wrong with this? What's going on? What is wrong with
the Grinch can pull more people? And that's you know, that's why maybe I
my shows didn't sell that well. Yeah, because I'm a bit of a Santa Claus, right
and their shows didn't sell well. I mean, I thought that I would get maybe I
thought I was gonna have to add dozens of shows after you thought maybe they
were gonna, you know, we sold we sold out one and a half, but I thought that I
was gonna have to like, you know, you ask you do two shows. Yeah, I flipped
about. It's not cool. Well, you would have been if you wanted me to really
flip a bottle. Let's get this shit started, but if I thought that I was
gonna do two shows and then I was gonna be one of those people where I have to
had shows every 30 minutes basically. Six shows because demand was so high, but it didn't happen
because I'm guessing there was... I'm obviously the Santa Claus of stand-up comedy.
The Grinch.
But who's the Grinch?
It was Pierce.
Because he had a separate show that night.
It's completely Pierce.
That is actually true. He stands like him. I'll say he stands exactly like him.
Pierce is a Grinch.
You know, what you're saying about adding shows is when I... My strategy is when I do
my stand up tours. I usually just kind of book eight shows right in advance. I do two nights,
four shows each and I usually get five to seven people each show.
That's exactly what happens when I go on the road with Adam to a secondary city. We go
to Pittsburgh and they book an 800 seat venue and we sell about 80 tickets a show. Then
we do ten shows. It's really awesome.
That's what it's all about.
Road dogging is all about.
We did Pittsburgh and it was like, maybe we did six shows and it was like this giant venue
and then we didn't sell that many tickets and then we saw that Matt Reif was the next
weekend.
Oh, dog.
He did 12 shows all sold out.
I was like, dude, we're fucking something up really badly.
Yeah.
That guy's got it figured out.
It's because you went into a big venue.
I just saw the thing, somebody reposted a thing from a long time ago where he tried to
fight Brandon.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about that.
forgot I didn't know that history like yeah. I know the by the way, if
somebody wants, if
somebody wants to like some promotion, wants to put this on, I will put up
a thousand dollars for that prize
for brand.
We'll do it now. Whoever loses, I win. That would be an amazing, amazing
thing. Brandon, if you're listening, you gotta, you gotta do it. You gotta do
have to do it. Matt, right, just slid on the disabled community. He did. You
can see this is insta bro. What do you say hit his insta right now? What
happened? What do you say?
What is
what are you doing? What are you doing? I take your clothes off. I'm ready to
ride for my disabled. You're ready to ride your disabled. I'm ready to ride
for
let's get this.
Dude, I will I will slide on your right. I will slide on anybody who fucks with
disabled people. I love disabled people more than I even love the abled, which
just quite a lot. What did he say he he said if anyone's ever been offended by
one of my jokes click here for I don't just click here to solve the problem.
It's some click here. I don't know. He's a hole in one a perfect joke.
It was a link to it was a link to special needs helmets
Matt right. You stupid fucking yeah,
It's also just like...
You're gonna wish you were never born, man.
Yeah, and you know what?
No disrespect to Brandon, but he looks like a baby 11-year-old child.
So as soon as Matt Rife sees me talking shit, he's not gonna ask me to fight him at a skate
park.
He's gonna run the other way.
He doesn't want me making his lips even bigger.
This was a couple years ago, too, when...
And he's still been hot.
...when Brandon was younger.
Yeah, exactly.
Brandon was younger, and he looked like the guy from Despicable Me back in the day.
I think Matt was younger than Brandon, I think.
I don't know.
Well, either way, Matt...
Wikipedia real quick. It's beyond on site for you. You want to see a white boy
really wilding it out on galaxy and say we're in the same galaxy. You're going
down. Yeah. And another thing man straight up. I'm gonna kill your ass.
Listen, I know you thought you were you thought you you were getting one over
making fun of the disabled community. You thought, oh, no one will notice if I
do this. Guess what buddy you fucked with another community at the same time
that you didn't even realize that is going to come down with you come down on
you with the fury of one million angry guys, which community is that community
of conscientious bike riders? That's right, yeah, helmets as well. That's
right, because the safety or the special needs website and the safety can be
better, because I have a bit of a well crafted. It's the craft. My head is
shaped like many disabled people's heads, so it fits better into the thing. It's
designed to be fit on your head exactly straight up and also man
and babies to and baby
and maybe you fuck with babies and fuck with
yeah. You can fuck with the disabled and different races all you want, but the
second you go for babies, those are our future man. Don't fuck with the babies,
bro. They need to grow up and change the world and that you are inhibiting that
you're trying to make them commit suicide before they've even learned to
talk man, Matt, right? Have you ever come for the safety community again?
If you ever come to the safety and protective gear community, you're going to get a reflective
vest to the fucking dome.
That's right, buddy.
I'm going to put you in a reverse life jacket.
You're walking down the sidewalk.
You're going to wish you were wearing a fucking helmet.
Walking down the sidewalk, oh, to-to-to-to-do, going to go ahead and cross the street.
Oh, what's this?
Who just put a blindfold on my head before I crossed the street?
That's right.
Oh, helmet.
Helmets are stupid.
Helmets are gay.
Yeah, not so funny when I fucking hit you with my slingshot going top speed 25 miles
an hour.
Bang.
Yeah, Polaris slingshot.
not a not a
we need to scare. Honestly, this is what I thought he meant to this could be a
I knew he's talking about Polaris. I'm a lot. This is the one I'm the I don't
even that is so
the Polaris is so ubiquitous. I forgot that a sling shot was even used to
defeat the I think that any time I read that passage, which is every other day,
which again me versus Matt Reif bit of a David versus Goliath. Yeah thing that's
right, Matt Reif, you versus me. It's David versus Goliath. I'm Goliath, the
strong guy. I'm going to pound your ass. I haven't quite finished the story, but I know
the title. I'm about to go Goliath on your ass. I see the word slingshot in the story
and I go to the car rental place and drive around for a couple of hours so I don't get
mad. I'm here to kill a white guy. But you don't know that you have fucked with a disabled
guy, a guy with an undiagnosed autoimmune disorder. Hashimoto's could be. And a guy
guy with purple eye bags. Yeah and make him ugly to some and a guy who is in a
couple of special needs classes growing up. Oh wait, me too. Yeah, wait, you too.
Yep.
I had a an IEP.
You fucked with a mother fucker with an IEP.
I hate it to hurt when they put it in.
IEP. Matt Rife, you just fucked with a mother fucker with an IEP. Okay.
Straight up. Improvised explosive Patrick and I'm coming at you. I'm coming at
with a bomb vest, I'm going to blow your ass up. We need to do terrorist strike.
We need to do a massive strike. What the hell are we talking about? What are we
talking about right now? This Neptune is making us so blue that we just
threatened a guy. We got ice cold. We got ice cold and threatened a guy for like
30 minutes. He's going to be blue when they take him out of the closet at the DC improv
where I fucking hit his body. He's never coming out of the closet. You're right.
No. He's in there for life. Dude, Matt Rife, you just got cooked in 40 different ways,
is
forty eight and that's you met right for and also broke her fucking burp. Take
those skinny jeans off man.
Don't need to see those. Take those skinny jeans. I want to be working with
and show me a dig.
Tell me that butthole bro. Show me a bend over. Show me your butt and balls
and you may look like handsome Squidward, but you act a whole lot more like
normal Squidward and you blue like him like and Neptune being in L.A. Neptune's
with SpongeBob to King Neptune. Oh yeah. Oh, we didn't even talk about that. The
God of water, the God of water aspect of the whole thing. I just got a
petrified piece of beef off the ground. It's not beef. What is it? That's cake.
That's a poop. Oh, cake. Yeah, we didn't clean the table.
The tablecloth is for yeah, exactly. Yeah, bundle the whole thing up. But
yeah, Neptune dude, this is this is really the only thing Neptune has going
for it. Is that a guy was named after him? That was a bit cooler
And Julio told me this morning, I don't know how he knew this, we were eating
breakfast and he said to me while I was talking, I was like, oh, I got to write
my planner report. He said this to me, he said, did you know you need special
software to view net? I don't even know what that means. What could that mean?
What does that mean Julio?
I did my research. And what kind of software? That's all you're going to say?
I don't know. It's special software.
What? But... So think about other planets, right? You can see them like normally.
you can't with Neptune. Oh, it's too far away. You need a special software to
look at it. Well, how'd they know it was there until before software windows
invented it windows invented Neptune. Yep. So this is like that's true. You
guys remember the like last year, Samsung came in with that phone that
you look at the you look at the moon and it just put a picture of the moon on
top of the yes, the AI. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that was so funny. They are
selling that with your with your mom and dad to speaking. I think it does do
I think they literally have it for faces too. That is a really good thing.
Speaking of Samsung, this weekend, the skate shop that I go to just did some event with
Samsung Galaxy Flip for some reason. I don't know why. What do you mean for some reason?
For money. Flip. Yeah, flip. There's actually a good point right there. What the flip? Because
They love cursing, skaters.
I met, I didn't meet him at this event.
I saw him on the street and then shook his hand.
I fanned out fucking crazy.
About who man?
Let me guess.
Tony Hawk.
Brian Anderson.
Who's that, an author?
He had one of the best video parts of all time.
Dude, I had the same experience with Louis Anderson.
Yep, fanned the fuck out.
I fanned out super hard, shook his hand in the street and then looked over and realized
Samsung was had a filmer there. They're filming something with them, so you're
in the video. There's probably a commercial of me saying you're my
favorite skater.
Nice, that's
if they fucking use that. I think about there's a guy who's there's a guy who
on my street that that does like tick tock live streams or something where he
can plays a guitar and I walk by behind him all the time and I know for a fact
one right now. I checked he gets about two viewers, but one of these days he's
going to pop in a massive way yeah and I'm going to be I'm going to be in all
these fucking videos looking at him and I'm going to be you're going to get
secondary fame. You're going to be known as that guy. He's going to be so famous.
I'm going to be slovenly hoodie man in the background and people are going to
love it for me man. Yeah, exactly. Are you slavic? No, you want to slavic. I
don't know which one slavic is it's a Korean way. No, it's not Korean. No, no
other day. He said Korean chungus. That's not true.
he watched a video called Korean corn dog and he highlighted the name of the
video and said, Oh, Korean chungus, that's how you read it was Korean, said
Korean, and then I said, Why did you say Korean chungus? It said that on the
screen. I didn't say that.
Korean corn dog. On my screen it said that. It didn't say, I don't think it
said Korean chungus. It's much. I've never had one. It's much. They put
sugar on it. Sugar and cheese. Yeah. Is involved. And potato, sweet potato.
Yeah. Don't say it like that. No, you all like nine dollars for one corn
huh
it's absurd man and people in Korea. Is this breakfast, lunch and dinner every
single meal they eat? Yeah, I explained to my cousin or not my cousin, my
friend
that I think I didn't even realize I talked to him, but I eat almost at a
completely Korean diet. Yeah, everything I eat is Korean food at home. I eat
bulgogi kimchi. I eat kimchi every day, bulgogi, kimchi, rice, go to garu, go to
John John egg. I eat egg,
I don't really
egg is common in Asia, but they do it a different way. Barbeque, because you
can Asia. Did you know that in Asia chill chill over there? You calm down
I'm going to say to be quiet. We have to legally pay you more. Yeah. Did you know
that in Asia the chickens are so amazing that you can eat them raw and you can
eat the eggs raw as well really and no and it's very common chicken sashimi due
to you can they literally do chicken sashimi. It's yeah. It doesn't seem like
it would be that because of the way they treat them. Do they not have factory
farms? They're kinder or kinder. They use they bless the chicken before they kill.
Do they even kill the chicken before they eat it? They don't kill it man.
that's you. You can eat it. You just that's interesting. You have to take
them. You have to take everything. I've seen videos where they flatten
chickens. Yeah, Spatchcock.
I saw a thing the other day that was called Toad style turkey with a
two, with a wire, two wired squares and they go like this
and then it spins with a machine. Oh no, Spatchcock is where you break
its back and it's like elbow shoulders. You push it down like a burger.
Open it up? Kinda. Like it's... I'm thinking about, 'cause I'm making a
turkey this year.
And it's toad. Is there going to be ham?
Toad style is when you cut the turkey.
Is there going to be ham?
I've just gotten nervous because Julio said there wasn't going to be ham.
I don't know if that's true.
Nobody gives a fucking shit.
Don't ask him about that, dude.
I didn't ask him. I didn't ask him.
I said, I'm so excited for ham, and he went, I don't know if there's going to
be ham. And I was like, what are you talking about?
Why did you say something to ham about there not being ham? I got worried.
Julio.
You know I've been on a ham break.
You know that if I said that...
I forgot about the ham break.
guy. He knows it to he decided to make me upset. If I had told him that there
was not going to be ham, you know for a fact, because I knew you were so
excited about it that I would have told him don't tell camera. Yeah, so there's
no there's no way that you would have found out, but there will be found out
day of I'm going to go get the am tomorrow. I would have called you. He
would have called you tomorrow or something or the day morning of and just
like just so you know, like you're about to get a call from like your
girlfriend breaking up with you right. Yeah, like we need you know, yeah, I
call you in a second. I don't call you that on you get home. You knew any call
for me would have freaked you out. I think about the ham situation, but no
did I have an amazing thing. Thank God the problem is I was going to do an
entire
Korean.
I was like I'm going to do like a themed Thanksgiving dinner this this year, but
wow, but that was just because I thought girls were coming, but no girl it's
only going to go down. It's a guy's only Thanksgiving, boys giving yeah. It was
it's going to be my at least my wife and her sister were going to come, but then
they've realized that no all the girls went out of town and now that it's just
going to be guys, they're just going to go hang out by themselves. So I'm not
going to make my bull. I was given sliders boys, guys, boys, guys, gang,
boys, dying, boys, guys, dying, dying, dying, dying, dying, dying, dying,
we're going to have a guy. It's going to be last giving dude. Yeah, we're
getting it pints. It's going to start probably pretty late. Yeah, because the
I was going to make a lasagna and then decided not to because I feel like you can't have
lasagnas aside on Thanksgiving.
We're going to start it early.
There's no girls getting ready.
We're going to start at 11am.
Yeah.
That's kind of when Thanksgiving should start I think.
I've always started at like 1 I feel like.
12 or 1.
I like a Thanksgiving where you get there, you get one of those disgusting cheese balls
that's covered in nuts and then you have about 2 to 3 hours of that and talking and then
food.
Cousin walk first.
Do the cousin walk.
which we're going to do a crazy cousin walk this year. We're going to leave the
turkey in the oven and Caleb's apartment and just go on a cousin walk for three
hours. You're going to do a buddy's walk. No, well, I cousins. We're going to
pretend to be because we if we're if a bunch of guys are at Thanksgiving
together, their cousins, they can be cousins for a day. Well, whoever's
making the turkeys, the onk. Yeah, so I'm
I don't want to be on because then I'm bro, but it will at least be on where
like you guys record me doing something and you're like, oh my God, I got a
- Unc it. - Unc it.
- I'm twerking on this down the oven.
- Yeah, something like that.
- Nah, I'll get up.
- Just a video of him just pointing a knife at you.
- I don't want to be unc, I want to be a cousin.
- Bro, then you shouldn't have hosted.
- My life sucks shit. - Yeah, dude.
- Everywhere I go, I'm an unc.
- We just think about every single thought we've had today.
- It's not even Thanksgiving, man. You're unc.
- I know, dude. I'm always the guy who's in charge of direction,
wasn't driving. It's everything has turned us blue today. He got he
graduated on blue. He's yeah on to grayness. That's because we get this
guys. Wow, even though Neptune is a very cold planet, I got hot wearing my
hoodie, so I had to take it off damn and I think the Matt right thing was I
think you look hotter with it off.
Don't say that to your uncle. I don't say that the on fucking weird. I got me
in some type of way. This we need to import some uncles and aunts for for
Thanksgiving on Thursday. Oh my God, we can go on. We should get we should get
Alan Phil yeah, Phil and Alan. I don't think Phil would want to come back with
Alan. Remember yeah, that's true. Okay, yeah, true. We can do we can do the
Thanksgiving focus group.
That would work
watch us.
We feel ourselves
do you want to make fifty dollars on Thanksgiving Day?
We'll pay you $10 to sit for five hours and watch us eat. Do you guys want to watch?
No, you can't have a plate. You're watching us talk about green bean casserole.
Oh, I have an amazing green bean casserole recipe I'm going to do with fresh green beans, guys.
Can you do a tease? Can you do a trailer right now?
Can we have a trailer of the menu?
Okay, guys.
Menu trailer?
depends on if I decide to make my bulgogi sliders, but
basically turkey, that's a lock, some kind of sage butter that I'm gonna put
underneath the skin, crisp it up, that's gonna be deliciously juicy. Do it like
a trailer.
This Thanksgiving,
sage butter turkey, possibly I take out the
spine and turn it into a big log of meat.
Spiral baked ham that I pre baked and I put on glaze and Cameron thinks that
I made the whole thing. I don't think you make he thinks I make
Hawaiian rolls, the ham or packages of Hawaiian rolls, green bean casserole,
fresh green beans and I might even fry my own onions,
chipotle mac and cheese, third year running first year, really good second
year, not that good third year. I'm going to add mustard powder wow and
some kind of drink, maybe a hard Arnold bomber, which I know a John Daly.
That's what we call that. Yeah, that's a good one. Yeah, okay. No, I don't
think no is even come. I think no is working. Yeah, that's fucked. But so
what do you guys that means I can bring white claws. Yeah, which counts as a
thing to yeah, because I was gonna I was singing that was basically my only
option. And then when I realized no was going to be there, probably making
mixed drinks. I was like, well, that's this is why our Thanksgiving works,
because
I cook all the food and everyone else brings drinks, which is usually the
bring some food. I bring last year. He brought about this many. I think I
brought way more than that, but I did bring cranberry sauce. I remember,
which is a crazy move. Why is that crazy? Because we didn't even have a
turkey cranberry sauces at Thanksgiving. That's when you eat it. I brought some
mashed potatoes that were irrelevant. Yeah. See, I might even make the mashed
potatoes this year. Yeah, I mean, I'm not gonna, but yeah, because I want
to eat them. Well, this year I'm going to bring, I don't remember bringing a few vegetables.
You brought, you laid, you got a sheet pan and you laid one layer of vegetables. I did
have small ass sheet pans, but guess what? I have. And everybody had like four vegetables.
I have a bigger sheet pan this year. You're going to have to. Tomorrow I'm going out,
I'm buying stuff and I'm going to do all the prep work. Whatever you're, think about how
many people are coming. I think the head count is nine or eight, eight or nine. But realize
does it? These are all guys hungry fucking guys. Yeah, no things to make
two helpings at least two plates. It I know what I'm doing and no isn't coming
there, so you can't yeah there's not going to be one guy only serves himself
one crumb yeah exactly no. So don't save a crumb of a he's not coming. I know
here's what I'm thinking. Don't tell him he's working. I'm thinking we literally
assassinate him at work. Show up with a plate show up with a plate covered in
ten,
and go like dude, since you couldn't come
since he couldn't come. We could leave it in his bedroom, since he couldn't come.
We made your as a play. You can all hide in his and then we take a video of him
opening it. He's so excited. His friends did that for him, and then he opens it
and it's one make it with a week. We do a half of a green bean with all the
beans inside taken. Oh yeah, that's a good idea and maybe a strand of beef
yeah, like you know how slow cooked beef turns into the strand one little hair
size strand of beef. It's a good idea, some yeah and we take a bite out of all
too. We bite all the food. I think it's a good idea. Do you guys want to see my painting?
Yes, I do. Let's do the painting. Guys, when I was in Los Angeles, I did a full tour of
every single modern art museum. I did the LACMA. What's that? LACMA balls? No, it's
actually the Los Angeles County Museum of Art. Hey, you're suffering from LACMA. Yeah,
LACMA balls in your mouth. That would be LACMA. Cameron, chill on him. That would be
be actually lack of my nuts. No, that would be the lick. You want to lock up
my nuts?
Chill the fuck out. Stop being a... What are you doing? He's a jock. I'll just
rip my painting out. You're right, you're right. He is... Say another
New Zealand word too. I'll rip it up.
You know what? You don't even wanna hear about it, whatever.
He's been on a jock kick today. The triumphant return of that song. I've
been waiting on. I realize it's been a long time. He's been a jock all day. He
needed to play a sport song. He's been a jock to Julio, but here's what I'd like
to say anybody. This was you ruined your own painting. So before I tell you what
just happened, because I know that you're too stupid to understand how did
me ripping my painting make you feel blue, scared blue, blue. Oh, my God, that
was the art piece, because here's what I learned. Here's what I learned in Los
Angeles. Art can be anything. It doesn't just have to be an awesome photo of you that you
took on Mars where you're buff, which is like that. It doesn't have to be a painting of
the member, Barry. It can be a full-on performance, guys. And what I just did was a performance
art. And now I will hold the pieces back together, and you can see that this was Neptune.
Wow.
So that was pretty amazing, right?
Yeah.
That's incredible.
We even got the dark spot.
Yeah, there's another dark spot.
Yep, pretty impressive and I and there might be it's kind of has shades of
Jupiter of the Jupiter paying some might say, but that was also part of the
performance trademark of your work. Exactly. So now that will be and here's
what how we'll hang it up. We'll hang it up so that the sides are like this
right. So that it's like highlight damage. I like the ripping this. Yeah,
the whole thing, but that's incredible. That's like the banks a Banksy. Yeah,
is it where the self shredding exactly, but I was the one shredding it instead
of so you were the one shredding the Banksy painting yeah do they have me
back there with a crank
and then I got you're in a wheel you to run yeah, whatever you do, do not burn
this crank. Your job is to guard the
Banksy. I got you, Mr Banksy. Oh, it's kind of hot in here. This must be the
AC
yeah. That was a hard job. Yeah, didn't they just reveal Banksy's identity? Yeah,
his name was John Banksy. He was a peanut. Holy Shit,
he was not a peanut, not a peanut man. That's what I would do if I was him,
though you'd be a peanut or I would just like I'd be like here's my face reveal
and then I would just have a mask on a peanut and I would take a picture of I
would be another in a person on the street and be like can I take a pic of
you yeah and I would just yeah. This is me. My name is Eduardo. It's a random
course. I sell street corn. Yeah. This is Banksy. That's the thing that's so
beautiful about Banksy. He could be anybody. Yeah, he could be. He could be
well, maybe not anybody. No, I think he has to be British. He could be a
British guy who's been, who's alive right now. Yeah. Yeah, well he could, no,
he doesn't have to be alive now. He could have died years ago, we don't know.
But he just had to have been alive at some point. Do you think he's something
where he'd never even existed? That's, yeah, he could have. You think it's like
Shakespeare, where there's multiple guys, all of the British people together are in
on it. Yeah, what if it was the Queen and that's why we haven't seen so holy
fuck the Queen was Banksy and she was protesting herself,
controlled opposition
sigh up, sigh up for a second. I was having trouble following that and I was
like when did the Queen protest Banksy? When did the Queen
when did she die this summer last year or this year? How did she die again old
MattyL Oldness, yeah. Old age, dude.
MattyL She got her shit blown up.
Ryan Oh, it wasn't violent? Oh, it was violent.
MattyL She got blown up.
MattyL She stepped on a landmine in her backyard.
Ryan Oh my god. Jesus Christ.
MattyL Yeah, the Queen of England stepped on a landmine from the war
and she didn't know and she fucking...
Ryan Why don't we have a queen? All we have is a freaking congestion.
MattyL We have a queen.
MattyL I thought we did.
MattyL Isn't that the first lady?
MattyL Isn't she technically the queen?
I thought you were going to say Beyonce or Lizzo or somebody like this.
We used to have a queen every couple of years and a new one.
We used to have Melania and then we had Michelle Obama.
Who is Joe Biden's wife?
I don't think he has a wife.
Dr. Jill Biden.
Dr. Jill.
Don't forget the doctor.
You don't forget the doctor.
That would suck if that was your GP.
Her maiden name?
Her maiden name is not Dr. Jill.
It was Pepper.
Her name is not Jill Pepper.
Dr. Jill Pepper.
Her maiden name is not doctor. It was pepper. Her name is not Jill pepper
Jill pepper, Dr. Jill pepper. Yeah, you're fucking me. No, I'm not you
shitting on me. I wish I was joking. I really wish that I was joking her last
and you're not for real, though. No, I'm for real. Her last name was pepper.
Well, pepper corn.
Now I'm thinking it's a joke. No, it's not a joke. That's a name. It wouldn't
a word if it wasn't it's a name. Her name is Jillian pepper corn is a name for a
corn or a vegetable. No, what the fuck is a pepper corn? It's a dried out
ball. Yeah. Oh, I had another idea for a well. I can't do it because I don't
know where my jacket is, but the other idea for a performance art was that I
got a bunch of blue gum and I was going to chew a hundred pieces of it and make
a big ball of gum. Oh, that would be Neptune. I thought balls. Let's talk
about that.
Neptune is the original blue ball, Neptune and Uranus, two blue balls.
Oh, my God, my blue balls hang over Uranus.
How are your balls blue if they're that close to a fucking asshole? Well,
because you're getting teased, you're getting edged fucking hate getting edge
don't like it. Shit, bro, fucking makes me go. Just make me not already. I
Christ honestly, though I do feel like I could if I'm being edged. I could do
anything. Yeah, I agree. I could solve all this. Are you guys doing no nut November, guys?
I'm working on it. I'm getting ready. I'm getting ready for it any day here now. Once
it starts, I can't stop. You can't stop no nutting? I can't stop nutting. Once you start,
you move it. How about nine nuts November? You only get nine? Nine is a good one. For
for me have to be ninety nine that's ninety nine nuts of November, Ninety
Nine
the ninety nine. That'll be such a fire rom three times at three and some odd
times a day. Then he falls in love. Yeah, they should make rom coms for guys that
are mostly about fucking yeah. They did that love and marriage. Didn't they do
that? That was forty days and forty nights. I don't know. I haven't seen
any. It's a movie where a man gets assaulted and then that's how he loses
the challenge. He jizzes. I guess I salted yeah. He gets us and then it's a
a woman. Oh, he's challenged to do 40 days and 40 nights of sex.
Yeah. Assaults him to jizz.
Yeah. And that's how he loses.
Wait, he gets sexually.
And this is a laugh or it's played as a play for laughs for the fallen.
It's played for laughs. Yeah, it's crazy.
I think it's Josh Harnett is the star.
Who's that? He's a guy.
He's an Oppenheimer in Sin City.
He's like this in Oppenheimer.
Oppenheimer, you can't do this anymore.
Yeah. Oppenheimer, you crazy, bitch.
what we can't like you can't know when he says that he's saying that you can't be
a communist yeah. Oh, I forgot that he actually Oppenheimer. You have to build
this. That's okay. I want you to do it.
I like the movie, but it's annoying everyone's doing that every
how many
have you sat right there and I've sat right here. We've gone over this
American Prometheus. You can't build a bunch of fucking crazy bombs and blow up
a bunch of crap, man. What are you building this stuff for? Nobody's gonna buy this
crap. Do you hate Japanese people? Is that why you're building that?
Taking a picture of you? The children.
There's children outside. Children outside and they're taking photos of us.
They heard us talking about Oppenheimer, a bunch of movie fans. Yeah. I think
that those are Oppenheimer stands out there, bro. Yeah, they're trying to tear
on the studio. God damn bastards. All right, Oppenheimer. Oh, that movie.
Yeah, that's how the movie ends. His girlfriend finds out what we're going to
do. I think I'm going to name myself Oppenheimer. That's how it ends. I think
I'm going to call him Oppenheimer. I think I'm going to call the bomb the
Oppenheimer bomb. Wow! They looked out by calling him Oppie the whole movie.
It's cool. It's a cool, apparently, that's his real life nickname. That was
his nickname. Yeah, Oppie. I wouldn't say Oppenheimer all the time like that.
what oh yeah, I wouldn't say Oppenheimer up and I'm a up up up up up up up up up
up up. I call them. They only call them up the whole movie. Yeah really yeah
they do. I'm not fire. I'm not Robert. Well, it's J J J. What is the J stand
for nothing? Apparently really that's what is the one in the movie. Holy
Christ doesn't stand for anything. Oh,
you don't give a fuck about anything. I'm signs in it to yeah, Albert Albert
Albert is the Einstein, Einstein, Einstein, it's nice to see you again
Einstein. That's a name I haven't heard in a long time. They call me Albert E.
Now
all right,
we're going to take Julio out. Well, you got to take him out to the club right
now. We're taking him. Do you want to go clubbing? Yeah, it's been one of your
video episodes. You guys know that today it's actually oh here's something
interesting. Everybody can get blew it on the worst. Well, it wasn't today.
it's like fine today. Neptune it's a blue episode. It's a blue day or a gray day.
It is a great day.
Here's something crazy that's coming up. What's that the fifth anniversary of the
podcast? Oh yeah, Christmas Eve we're sending into kindergarten. You know
it's crazy. Can you believe that I can believe it is going to come out so
everyone get everyone. I want to see some type of celebration from everybody
use the hashtag five years of pal and you have to draw it on your body. No,
or no, no someone else's draw on someone else's body on the train and then take
take a video of you doing it. Basically, December is going to be the month of
pal. We have to figure out what the plan is, but if you guys like the five weeks
of planets, guess what man probably is a podcast. This is going to be the rest of
the entire podcast is awesome themed month
and after planet will figure it out. Somebody said dinosaurs. I like that
idea. That is a good like that. I would love. I have so dude. I have so many
dinosaur books I can bring in. We can study together. The entire pot podcast
is kind of changing from being about a list of different things that it is
over the whole thing.
Well, that's why the name is so great. It's so flexible exactly yeah yeah
all right. Well, five hash tag five years of pal check us out on Thanksgiving at
Caleb's apartment dot com. Thanks giving that comment are my streaming at
- Yeah, showing a bunch of videos of people doing a turkey eating competition.
- All right, bye my friends.
- Listen up man. I think that we need to eat this bobo stew while it's still hot.
- Mm-hmm.
- We need to...
- Is it even hot? It's not hot.
- It's not going to be hot at all when the...
- Suck my dick man. I fucking made this all day.
- It looks so good. It looks so good.
- It tastes like shit.
- How do you know it tastes like shit?
Bite of the stews part it tastes like shit, but there's no well, it's gonna taste like shit in a second
It's about to be it won't taste like shit. Yeah, this is oh dear George
George
Myself a little something some of that dickle that white dip or a white dick
Pour up
White nickel
All right, little bit of white dick
Crazy man, oh my god, this guy was fair more more white dickles
Okay guys wait before we do this what are you thankful for stinkful I'm thankful I'm stinkful for
Everything that has happened this year
Wow, I'm very thankful for the fact that the five weeks of planets has lined up so beautifully between the stinky planet
I actually call it later. I love you guys stinky stink for Happy Thanksgiving my favorite online
*laughing*
It's so much!
It's literally so much!
That was way too much
Look at that!
It's gone off! It's so glowy!
*laughing*
It's literally completely inedible now
It smells like when you're cooking
No I'm not, I'm sorry
It smells like when you cook Marsala
Jesus Christ
Caleb you went right in
I'm gonna eat the beef.
It's kinda good man.
I'm gonna have a bite of beef.
I'm gonna kinda skip the broth maybe.
You gotta get the broth.
No, it's chewable.
Guys, no he spit it out.
Oh, he's not staple.
No, no, no, that tasted exactly like throw up.
(roaring)
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[no audio]