Okay, are you guys are you all seeing this I'm listening to your stream mate
it.
Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you. Mercury, imagine me and you. Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you. Mercury, imagine me and you.
Mercury, Mercury, smallest planet.
(upbeat music)
- No, you can't hit your head for a clap.
Guys.
- It's showing up on the thing.
- Welcome to the five weeks of planets.
We said we were gonna do it.
I'm sick as a dog. - And now we're gonna do it.
- And we're still powering through to do it.
- Uh-huh.
- We could've, you guys could've,
I could've told you guys, guys, get a guest.
Go get some, go get Brett Gelman this week, man.
- My favorite comic.
- Yeah, go get Brett, man, because I am sick as a dog,
but I said no, man.
The people need to see these planets.
We can't delay this any further.
Also, we're lining up the five weeks of planets
with the Five Nights at Freddy's movie.
- Yeah, it's kind of a tie-in,
kind of a movie tie-in. - Five type of universe.
I mean, yeah, there's no better time to get started
on a 10-episode spectacular series than now.
And just for everybody who didn't--
- On Halloween day.
- Everybody who wasn't, so anybody who didn't listen
to the last premium episode is probably a little bewildered
right now and you deserve to be if you're not listening
to the premium episodes.
But basically Patrick dressed as an earth by accident
on last episode.
So we decided to do 10 weeks of planets and yes,
Patrick's already done five weeks,
tied in episodes of planets and that will span
every episode we do for five weeks.
So today everybody is Mercury and then after Mercury,
it will be Venus.
Then we're skipping Earth 'cause we already did it
and then it's Mars, Jupiter.
- Well, we're on Earth every day.
- Exactly.
- So, you know, every episode's an Earth episode.
- Neptune. - We're not gonna say it funny.
- Did I, I forgot Saturn, I think.
Did I say Saturn?
- No, you didn't, but that's an important one.
- Saturn's in there for sure.
Pluto, the Sun, and the Moon.
Wow, all 10 planets.
- The Sun and the Moon debate.
- Which one's better?
I don't even, we can't even get there yet, guys.
- No. - This week it's Mercury.
if you, I mean, start off with a beginning.
- Again, again, again, regardless,
irregardless, Brett Gelman, open invite.
If you wanna show up in the five weeks of planets, come.
- You would make a great, he would make a great Saturn.
- He would make a great Jupiter.
- He has the ring around his head.
- With his, yeah, well Saturn, actually,
that's a good point, with the ring,
the ring around the head.
- Yeah. - I'd love to see him
tackle Uranus.
- And I'd love to see something impact him.
and destroy him into millions of pieces.
Guys, look at, we all dressed up as Mercury
for this episode, just like Patrick did accidentally.
And so Patrick, I guess I forgot to tell you.
- I guess I forgot to mention,
that's the most important part of the five weeks of planets
is every episode we will be dressing as them.
- Basically the outfits.
It's the outfits of planets.
- I was trying to get the light going
'cause I don't have my ring light
so you can't really see the full,
it's kinda, my webcam is pretty bad.
- Show us the fit, man.
- Look, I've got a gray,
I've got a gray Dickies Work shirt on, and as well as gray pants, I have dark gray pants
with a dark gray shirt.
And then the white is supposed to represent, I guess, the atmosphere or something on the
dust.
Is there an atmosphere?
You're making excuses, man.
It sounds to me like you didn't think this through.
The white is...
What is the black and orange hat?
It says that Mercury has an extremely tenuous atmosphere.
It barely has an atmosphere at all.
Cameron, why don't you shut up?
Let alone a white one.
Seems like someone just didn't put much effort in on the first day.
Okay, moving on from you...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Somehow you accidentally dressed exactly like Earth the other day.
Wait, wait.
What, bitch?
The black, the black on the hat is representative of the blackness of space.
And the orange on the hat is representative of our big orange sun.
So you dressed as the solar system and not Mercury?
No I dressed up like Mercury.
You added the sun into your Mercury costume.
No man it's not gonna fly.
The sun was on my Earth costume.
It's not gonna fly, unlike Mercury which flies very fast.
It's the speaking planet and the year is on the 88 Earth days.
The sun was on my Earth costume.
I know and that one, but that was not on purpose.
You accidentally dressed like Earth and the sun.
It's the same thing.
You had ample warning.
Honestly, it would have been fine if it wasn't that it was it didn't try to say that the white
shirt was the atmosphere.
Yeah, that was a white shirt.
It just shows you didn't do much research.
You just fell off, man.
You fell off there.
No, the white shirt is represented.
The white shirt, there's white all over Mercury.
There's little white dots.
What are you reading?
He googled the word Mercury.
I'm looking at a picture of Mercury right now.
I know.
Okay, so here's how you handle that, man.
Look at my hat, motherfucker.
Look at my swirling hat.
That is beautiful, Caleb.
That looks almost exactly like the surface of Mercury.
It's a Mercury-themed outfit.
All right, we're gonna--
I have different tones of Mercury.
I have a gray shirt, I have a dark gray apron that I have
that I cook in sometimes,
and I also used to do the dishes, guys.
That is a green apron.
You brought that--
What are you talking about?
I'm not stupid.
Are you fucking stupid?
Get off Wikipedia, bro.
You're scrolling down the Mercury Wikipedia.
What the hell is--
You think this is green, man?
let Caleb do his outfit. I forgot you can see my screen.
Sharing his screen of him scrolling down the Mercury Wikipedia page really really fast.
I was trying to look for the word white. Look at all the pictures bro.
Oh wait wait wait wait wait. The white here is supposed to be representative of Beppy Columbo.
Oh!
What's that?
Well, BepiColombo is a joint mission of European Space Agency and the ESA and the JAXA, the
Japanese Aerospace Exploration Agency, and the white is supposed to represent BepiColombo's
shell.
I just don't think so.
Okay, we did my outfit, we did Patrick's outfit.
Cameron, walk us through this fit, man.
Okay, so first of all, we've got the obvious element,
which is I put some tinfoil on top of my head.
Oh yeah.
And what this represents is this is,
first of all, it's gray, like Mercury the planet,
but we also know that Mercury also gives its name
to a peculiar type of liquid metal
that is quite shiny and metallic in appearance.
So that's the element that's going on up here.
You're telling me you have Mercury
sitting on your head, liquid Mercury?
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
You know, it's insanely toxically dangerous.
- Yeah, that's what happened to the Mad Hatters.
- I don't care much about that.
I'm more interested in the planet.
I'm not afraid to die for my costume.
- I like that.
- So, what I have here on my topper, upper half,
is this is a gray sweater
to represent the gray color of Mercury.
And then I also have a gray shirt,
which, here, let me see.
- You put layers underneath it?
- Just wait, bro, this is a full body outfit.
This is a full body outfit here.
- Don't wait, don't tell me.
Okay, so I've got the gray sweater,
and I've got this gray shirt here,
which has gorillas on it,
which you might think seems a little bit out of place,
but wait, because there's a reason.
Now see, I'm wearing these,
oh, this cable's not very long.
I'm wearing these pajama pants here,
the Boston Bruins.
Now what sport do they play, guys?
- Hockey. - Hockey.
- Now what do you play hockey on?
- The ground. - Ice.
- Ice.
And guys, Mercury's range of temperatures can be very hot.
Some would say in excess of tropical temperatures.
- Oh my God.
- But they also at night drop to very low,
maybe as cold as an ice rink.
- Okay, show me your underwear.
- And my underwear is under my pajama pants.
And then there's the last part,
I'm wearing these running shoes
because Mercury, guys, is the speedy planet.
- The speedy planet, oh my God.
- And you know what else I have, guys?
- What?
- An envelope because Mercury is the name
of the messenger God.
Oh my god.
Wait, you popped off man.
Who's the messenger of the gods?
You popped off and you inspired me in so many different ways now.
Yeah.
For the other planets.
That's my Mercury costume y'all.
Holy fucking shit.
What I lack in costume, I will make up for in song.
And you guys, I need to debut my new single.
Okay, I wanna hear it.
my new single under my new space rapping name, OJ the Alien.
- All right, I wanna hear this shit.
- Okay, are you guys, are you all seeing this?
- I'm listening to your stream, mate.
(upbeat music)
♪ Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you ♪
♪ Mercury, I'm gonna get me and you ♪
[MUSIC]
See I'm doing an alien voice.
I hear that.
Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you.
Mercury, imagine me and you.
Mercury, let me fuck on you one time.
Hope I make you wet with my dope rhyme.
On this planet you age like a fine wine.
A fine line?
I put my nut in you like a Clark bar. I put my butt on you but I won't fart.
Put my spaceship here like a bear heart. Got my clothes and shoes they from Primark.
Mercury
I was supposed to say fine wine.
Fine line? Aged like a... Oldest...
I think I let...
Like a fine line?
I let the Adobe Premiere do the transcription.
Mercury
I'm gonna fly to you
I think that's I should have double-checked that
And you guys
There will be a new song by OJ the alien every single episode no way
every planet episode every single
Episode of the five weeks of planets there will be a new
OJ the alien track I'm more excited than I've ever been
Mm-hmm. I I like that. Also, you know, what's kind of convenient about this. It is Halloween that we're recording this and
Well, that's what I was thinking about. Yeah, we may be have come up with the three most psychotic Halloween costumes in all of history
I think if I were to walk outside right now, anybody would be like, oh nice Mercury costume. Well, yeah
Bruins play ice hockey
Hmm are they would say are you that are you the gray guy are you mr.
Gray, and I would go like this and I point to my envelope and they go oh
Jerry the fastest planet mercury like from the OJ the alien song yes exactly and OJ the alien is about to blow the fuck up
I think so guys yeah, and his spaceship uh-huh
When he impact I lay I really like the line put my butt on you, but I won't fart
Because that might be the most romantic shit I've ever heard
Very it's a it's see I was thinking about it, and it's like what would okay, so OJ the alien. What's he up to?
What would oh what would an alien think is beautiful right uh-huh and it's probably a cold
But also hot gray planet
True, and I don't know how aliens make love so right
It's probably in a way that we couldn't even comprehend like putting their butt on somebody without a nerd
Putting their nut inside of it like a clerk bar when an alien travels to earth. What the hell is it doing?
With all its free time in that spaceship. Well that here's my theory now. They all want to you know they will OJ the alien
I don't know what kind of alien he is, but I mean green my creation
alien yeah, you just I
I guess I think well these type of aliens are not there the planet fucker race and
They only they don't like earth because it's too watery. It's not cold and gray like a
like see
Alien pussy
So this alien hella cold and gray is it really big where it can like hold the whole planet and fuck it or is
It may be OJ the alien has some kind of I don't know we'll see where this character goes
Well, it's there's it's gonna be a 10 episode arc and we'll see what type of things that OJ the alien gets up to
OJ the alien thinks about the Sun
Yeah, good luck trying to fuck the Sun, but I bet you like fucking love the moon. Oh my god craters
Oh my god, wait, maybe Mercury is his main and his main thing is his
sidepiece
- You guys, I'm just excited to think about
all this new kind of, this whole thing that we can do
with OJJ. - The thing is, bro.
- All right, well tune in next week for the next episode.
(laughing)
- The thing is, man, the planet, we've spent,
what have we done, 300 episodes,
and 99% of what we talk about is all this Earth shit, man.
We are leaving the entire universe out of our vocabulary
and the things we're talking about, and this is wrong.
- I think maybe we've talked about aliens before,
but I don't think we've ever really spoken about--
- But we've never talked about these other planets, man.
And beyond this, even our galaxy,
there's probably 30 or 40 other galaxies
that have 10 planets each.
With tons of different things that we could talk about, man.
What the hell, Titan?
Are you kidding me, Titan?
- Titan? - Titan?
- That's a moon.
- Titan?
That shit is cool.
- It is cool to have a moon named Titan.
- Why have we never talked about Titan before?
- We're gonna get to Titan, man.
Let's think about what we can talk about Mercury here.
We don't want to jump too far ahead.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, we're getting too excited about all these planets.
- Okay, guys, listen, here's a fact.
I'd like to read a Mercury fact to you guys.
- Go ahead.
- If Earth were a nickel, Mercury would be a blueberry.
- That doesn't seem--
- I guess spatially--
- If Earth were a nickel--
- Is this in terms of size?
Mercury would be about a blueberry.
- A nickel and a blueberry are pretty similar in size.
- They are the same.
They are, I have seen, well, these GMO blueberries.
- Blueberries come in different sizes, man.
- Mercury is .4 astronomical units away from the sun.
- How much is an astronomical unit?
- So, well, it's about .4 of the distance
from Mercury to the sun, is what I'm gathering here.
Oh, Mercury's highly eccentric egg-shaped orbit.
That's interesting.
Okay, egg-shaped.
Shaped like an egg.
It's an egg-shaped orbit. And Mercury has no moons, y'all.
Yep, I knew that.
Can you imagine living on a planet with no moons?
I think that Mercury is kind of...
I would like that. No werewolves.
True.
Your werewolves...
That's a good point.
The threat of werewolves is greatly decreased by not having a moon.
100%.
Why do I feel like humans...
Like how geese migrate south when it becomes December,
humans when it gets towards the end of October should migrate to Mercury to
avoid all the wolves, to avoid the werewolves and the wolves. Yeah, speaking of wolves,
last night I had, this weekend, listen this was Halloween weekend, this is why
I'm sick, partied way too hard okay. Last night I had myself a completely blue
cocktail, almost Neptune colored. Let's get there, let's talk about that when we
get there. Well but I started walking around with and I put all my keys in my
hand and I started saying I was keys-a-reen like Wolverine but with keys.
This is last night? This was last night to my wife and my wife made a great point
she said Wolverine is just named after an animal it doesn't matter what his claws
are made out of. Yeah. So he would not be knife-a-reen or blade-a-reen he's just
still even if he had keys he'd still be Wolverine. Anything could be sticking out
of his fingers and it would be Wolverine. The reason he's named Wolverine is
because he's small, he's short. Yeah his height. He's a small guy. Okay so I
couldn't even be Wolverine then because of my slightly above average
global height. Yeah. How tall is Wolverine did you say? Like five foot four, five foot two
somewhere around there. He's really short that's the main aspect of his character.
I don't think his power is that he's short personally. I think it's
- That's why he's Wolverine and his brother is Sabretooth.
- That's his brother?
I thought they were enemies.
- Well, they're friends at first.
- They're brothers at first.
- I don't know anything about Wolverine, to be honest.
- Okay, so Wolverine is five foot three.
- Okay.
- So I was almost right.
- Is Hugh Jackman really short?
- Hugh Jackman is six foot two.
- What?
- Too tall to be Wolverine, yeah,
but he's too good for the--
But name one male actor who's 5'2" besides Danny DeVito.
Just get Danny DeVito to play him, man.
Why is that a problem?
Yeah.
Danny DeVito is too old.
If the main thing is his height, he wasn't in 2001.
Okay, but here's the other, okay.
I don't think the main thing is his height.
That's what we were just saying.
Caleb, I want you to cover your, don't listen to what I'm about to say here.
But the other thing about Wolverine is his hairdo, and I don't think that a balding guy
could play Wolverine.
he has to be able to have to be crazy
to do. He could still he could take the sides out. It's gonna look weird man and Caleb don't do that
expression because I told you not to listen to this part. I don't know how to not listen. I tried
closing my eyes and it didn't work. The only thing the only thing that matters about Wolverine's
hairdo is the sides. So a balding man a man with like a full Norwood 7 could totally play Wolverine.
Oh I just googled it it turns out I googled what is the main thing about Wolverine turns out it's
it's a superhuman strength and reflexes.
- Oh, okay.
- So we're gonna have a little bit of trouble
finding an actor to play him.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that would be tough.
- 'Cause you know, representation matters,
and if you're gonna have an actor playing somebody,
you gotta get somebody with superhuman strength and reflexes.
- Well, that's basically where--
- Adamantium skeleton.
- I hate to say it, but that's where Democrat SJWs
are trying to take Hollywood.
- Yeah?
- Is that you can't play Superman
unless you have laser beams shooting out of your eyes
and you have an allergy to green rocks.
But what, does he date the girl who has red powers?
- Which one are you talking about?
- Lois Lane.
- You mean red hair? - No, no.
- Amy Adams? - Wolverine.
- Wolverine does not date rogue.
He does not date rogue.
- No, the red girl who turns the other way.
- Scarlet Witch?
- Phoenix.
- Phoenix, no, well there was a love triangle thing
going on with them.
- In the ultimate universe, Wolverine is an adult
and Peter Parker is 15 and Wolverine and Peter Parker
get freaky fridayed and Wolverine inside Peter Parker's body
tries to fuck 15 year old Mary Jane.
- That's fine 'cause it's the body.
- And it's also fine 'cause you're a, whatever,
it's a Wolverine, you're a Wolverine,
you're not a normal guy.
- Also, you're hundreds of years old.
- You're gonna do weird stuff.
- Yeah, you're saving the world too.
- Nobody can expect him to be completely normal.
- If you're saving the world, I don't really care.
And yeah, he tried, like once a year.
He didn't go through with it.
Yeah, he would have stopped himself.
If he made it, he would have stopped.
He would have said, "Oh, I'm 400."
The other thing in the Marvel Ultimate Universe
that it's like Wolverine is,
Wolverine is supposed to be Wanda Maximoff
and Quicksilver's dad or something.
I thought that was Magneto.
Well, I think in that universe--
Or it switches in the Ultimate Universe?
Yeah, I think in the Ultimate Universe it switches
and then they are already in an incestuous relationship
and then I think he watches them have sex.
- His own kids? - That sounds about right.
- He watches his own kids have sex.
- All types of crazy shit happens in the Ultimate stuff.
- It's the Ultimate, you know?
- It's all the last in the long line of.
- It seems more like man, it's got incest
and pedophilia and all types of shit.
- It reminds me of this show called The Boys.
Have you seen this show?
- No. - Oh, brother.
- Dude. - You are about to derail
this entire fucking episode. - Wait, wait, wait, sorry.
- We have to talk about The Boys first.
- I think that we, yeah. - Hold on, hold on, hold on.
- We have been talking too much about superheroes
and we need to start talking about super moves.
- When a Homelander uses his powers to,
and goes, "Fuck you, motherfucker!"
And he blasts somebody's, a woman's head off
and then he fucks her dead body.
- It's a maze ball. - I was, okay.
I was about to be a stickler for us getting derailed,
but this sounds amazeballs and I need to hear more.
- So, basically there's a character named Huey
and he's not exactly the most normal of guys
because he fights against, you guessed it,
motherfucking Supes.
The Supes are basically the bad.
- And what is a Supe?
- They're superheroes.
- A superhero.
- Or maybe not even heroes,
depending on how you see it.
But imagine, okay, so you're watching Batman,
you're watching Spider-Man, maybe Superman.
And you're thinking, this is interesting,
I like these powers, but I think in real life,
they would probably use cuss words.
- Yeah.
- Dude.
- Buddy, you don't typically expect a character
in a superhero TV series to have a catchphrase
like fucking diabolical.
- Yes.
- Yeah, or an Australian accent.
- No.
- Well, things are a little bit different
in the boys' universe.
- Let me get this straight, okay?
Let me get this straight.
You're telling me that the real heroes
of the boys' universe are the villains.
- Well, the real heroes in the boys' universe,
I think, are the police.
- Yeah.
- Huh.
- It's the police and nerds.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Interesting.
It's about the police teaming up with nerds.
- And the enemies are superheroes and unions.
that's basically the enemies of the boys universe
it's really bad ass dude
and the fast guy
and some of the characters fuck on screen
basically the whole boys show was conceived when the creator of the show
or the comic
watched the flash and was like
basically if he ran into somebody he'd fucking explode into fucking blood
and then they turned into jizz too
yet spree yeah i'm it's been a bit is man there's a chance of a with a guy who
likes fish
uh... everybody get wait hold up
what what
fucks yes kanya west from south park
he's always a gay fish there's a literal gait i hate to say it
there's a literal gay fish in the boys
that's there's a mother fucking gay fish he goes around a fox the fed and you'll
appreciate this patrick the main character
it is a big fan
of billie joel
i would do appreciate that so he's a museum of the legal
yet i am a music fan
and and also rappers are are bad in this universe rappers are not a third in the
t_v_ show
well i was a very good we're only not features of the world with no rap so it's
a perfect world hot
there's no ralph rap at all there's no
bs pop music all just a little explode and uh... if you thought wonder woman was
gonna be straight in this universe? Ron? Nah man. Let me do one finger gesture for you.
I just did a spit take. What are they scissors? I just did a spit take with no water. It is.
That screwed me up. It is so awesome that the in that show the thing that they keep
like cause the whole thing is they're like blackmailing superheroes and stuff and the
thing that they're blackmailing all the superheroes for is being gay. It's all being gay and being
addicted to drugs. Yeah, every yeah. Yeah, which is so funny
because it's I read the comic of it a while ago. And it's like
it's Garth Ennis. So it's very it's super. It's all what is he
else did he do? He did preacher and some of the Punisher and
stuff. But it's all like, yeah, every the secret, the dark
secret of every superhero is they're all gay pedophiles.
Literally every single one of them. And then yeah, they take
they they don't know how to do it in the show right so it is very strange so they
just take away all the pedophile stuff yeah I only watched I think like one and
a half seasons oh also the main the main villain Homelander is goes full fat
bastard and eats a baby what yeah oh yeah he does copyright infringement no yeah
he goes he fat bastards at the end of the show he is stealing he is stealing fat
That bastard's intellectual property.
That's messed up.
- Yeah, there's photos of him where one night
he got really drunk and he went fat bastard.
- Why do I feel like the boys is almost like methadone
for an MCU addicted culture?
- Damn.
- Holy fuck.
- Holy shit.
- I feel like I could write for the AV club.
(laughing)
- I think you'd have a very strong resume.
my dream being to write for the AV club.
- One line in the application.
The boys is gonna hire you.
- It's a question, why do I feel?
- Why do I feel weirdly like the boys
is some kind of methadone for an MCU addicted culture?
Cameron.
- Well I'm addicted to the MCU.
- Yep, say it.
- Moon cycle units.
- Yep.
- Moon cycles. - Let me segue this back.
superheroes of your remains planet
crypt on
yet what happened with cripple what how come we haven't read discovering
crypt on that's yeah has anyone been to crypt on yet
i think there is a unit it's a different galaxy i think that that's the problem
what is that's not a stay
are allowed to go between galaxies
let's stay in the milky way you got a lot of his well i was but not a lot of
that the human race but our discussion we can no no we can talk about we have
- I thought you were suggesting that the entire human race
should not travel beyond the boundaries of our galaxy.
- No, no, no, I've seen Event Horizon and stuff.
I've seen Event Horizon, I've seen Alien,
I know that we shouldn't even go beyond the limits
of the Milky Way.
- Do you guys believe that--
- I've seen, I've played Mass Effect 2,
I know that the geth are coming for us
and we're all gonna die. - I thought you were
suggesting right now, I thought you were proposing
a global policy, I thought you were saying,
guys, let's not leave the galaxy.
know everybody let's make a promise let's not leave the galaxy. I am proposing that. I am proposing that.
Uh uh. I don't want to know. Patrick's picture coming up like a zoom meeting on a giant projector
in front of the UN. Guys let's not leave the galaxy. All the countries, the Congo is like
yeah shouldn't be doing that. Don't leave the galaxy let's keep it in the galaxy. We
We don't need to know about all that other shit.
We don't need to leave the galaxy.
Can we start a petition to not leave the galaxy?
I'm down.
I think we should.
We should start that.
Let's go to change.org.
Let's type that up right now.
There will be a QR code on the screen.
Well, because it's you, you could see things.
Here, you know what?
Let's show our planets.
Because this is in it.
We, guys, speaking of leaving the galaxy, these are, if you believe in an infinite galaxy like
I do, then these planets surely exist because every variation of planet exists
in an infinite, not an infinite galaxy, an infinite universe. So there are other
galaxy, there's probably an entire galaxy that has all of our planets in it in a
row. Yeah, but these planets that, but these planets we're about to show, these
exist in our galaxy because we're not leaving the galaxy and we know these are
here. Okay Patrick, show us your planet mate. I'm showing you my planet right now.
Describe it for all the people who are listening. All right so this is my planet
that I discovered and this right here it is a red planet with a lot a very a very
elevated planet it almost looks like a meatball it doesn't say meatball it
looks a lot like a meatball and what the hell is that a face there's whose face
is that? Who is that? You guys, this whole planet is alive. It is the Meatwad planet.
Okay. You were talking a big game before this episode. You guys were saying you had the
best planet. You wanted to make a competition. You wanted to change this into a contest about
who could have the best planet. Once I found out Julio had the best planet, I knew that
I would step down. I knew that I would step down because... But before you knew that, you
We were confident this planet would win the number one planet.
Well I didn't know what you guys would have.
But this is the planet Meatwad.
It looks nice.
This is planet Meatwad.
It has two moons.
It doesn't look that much like Meatwad though.
I'm going to be real with you.
Well it looks like, okay, you know in the MCU when they try to make Howard the Duck look
real.
You think this is what it would look like?
This is like photorealistic Meatwad.
Like real photorealistic Meatwad.
Why does it have so many moons?
It has so many moons.
What's with the dandruff on its head?
The dandruff is actually city lights.
Oh, those are the cities?
Yeah, those are the cities.
I can turn those off and on.
Wow.
Right there.
I like that everyone's kind of afraid to colonize the eyes and mouth a little bit.
Well, at least here.
Because I feel like I would be living right on the lip.
No, you wouldn't, bro.
Well, there's some people right here.
I would live on the lip and I'd be rubbing the ground all day with my body.
See right here, right on this corner of the lip, this is where all the people live.
are the most dangerous, these are the bravest citizens of planet Meatwad.
I feel like there'd be some serious...
So tell us about the culture and the atmosphere and all types of things. More than the appearance,
what's going on with this person at all?
Well, it's mostly...
Who's living on planet Meatwad?
The Meatwadians.
Okay, and they look like Meatwad?
Yeah, they pretty much all look like Meatwad.
It's like how you looked like Earth the other day?
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. I'm gonna be honest you guys. I didn't think that much about this. And I
didn't think that you would be able to see the face on the texture that I uploaded. It
was just going to be planet meatball until I saw that the face showed up. So you uploaded
a picture that had the texture of a meatball but also a face on it. No I made it red. I
I made it red and this is a Yoda mask.
Oh, okay.
I can show you my custom picture here.
I do like how this looks right now.
I thought it would show up like, I thought that would be an interesting texture to put on a planet.
That would be kind of interesting, but I think Yoda already has a planet.
Yeah, he does have a planet and it is Dagobah, but...
Yeah, this is, I think, the loser of the planets.
No, go ahead and just freestyle some stuff.
- Yeah, tell us about it.
- You're so down on your planet.
- You're not even trying to tell us a detail
about the culture or the climate,
or just tell us about it.
- There's a spaghetti sauce sea.
- Sea, this is what I like to hear.
- Okay, all right, we're getting somewhere.
- I'm liking this.
- All these low elevation parts right there,
that's the spaghetti sauce sea.
It's mostly spaghetti sauce.
And there's the whole United States.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- The entire United States.
United States. A lot has not changed. I can tell you that a lot. This is Planet of the
Apes. This is the Earth in the future. One day this is what it looks like. You guys,
I was more focused on OJ the Alien, but now I think that Planet of the Apes becoming a
meatwad planet. Patrick and the UN doing a Greta Thunberg conference about how we need
to stop cloud. We must be. Earth is going to look like this in five years. This is what
earth would look like in five years? It will be a planet meat wad. Half of the United States
will be in this big hot sea. Look, look, look, where earth, the moon is going to become earth.
Look at that. That's scary man. That's terrifying. Wait, so now I'm feeling like this, you would
go to the UN and you would say, can we, we need to stay in the galaxy. They would like
be like okay then you start showing them this and they don't want to leave the
galaxy immediately. This is a horrifying vision of the future.
Well this is we need to stay in the galaxy and we need to stop focusing on
going to the other galaxies and stuff. This is what happened is it happy to live
on a planet like this? We need to stay in our lane is what the lights are still on.
We are we are we got to stay in our lane and we got to make sure that this
doesn't happen. This is more cautionary. The side profile on this thing is really handsome.
Yeah. Wait, go back to the side profile.
It kind of lined up perfectly. I didn't even think the nose would get a ridge like that.
It looks amazing, man.
Yeah. Well, what my planet lacks, it makes up for in aesthetics.
You don't have to be hard on, now that it's grown up,
now that it's evolved past just being Meatwad,
I'm in love with your planet.
- Yeah, see, we needed just the details, man.
- Here, I'll go next 'cause I do feel like Caleb's
is gonna be better than mine.
- Okay, that's a little bit harsh too.
- No, it's okay, he was also talking a big game,
and I didn't have that, just spend that much time on mine.
- I will say, you are the most humble of the three of us,
in terms of your planet.
- It's not that I spend that much time on it,
I just have a natural talent, I think, for--
We're going to start with this view of my planet.
What do you guys think?
It looks amazing.
It looks green.
And I bet it looks like this all over.
You know what this looks like?
Can you guys describe what you're seeing right now?
OK, yeah.
It's like a gray planet, and it looks
like there's some kind of fuzz around the edges of it,
but not all the way around, kind of like a horseshoe-shaped fuzz
going around the sides of the planet.
This looks like popsicle shots.
Do you remember those, the lemon-lime,
- Oh wait, oh wait, hold on.
- It came in a cup and you would get it
from the ice cream?
- I'm starting to see, oh God, man.
(laughing)
This is a foot.
This is a photo of a foot.
Two feet.
- This is a photo of two feet.
- This is a photo of two feet that has been turned
into one of the most disgusting orbs
I've ever seen in my life.
are these your feet
no yeah these are your feet
you think i have to sit like this on my feet? yeah that's... oh my god
oh my god
look at those corns dude
okay alright what's the name of your planet? oh my god is it what's it plantar fasciitis?
this is planet feet
okay
and it's a very stinky planet as you can see by the green atmosphere here
that i'll highlight here. you can change the atmosphere color that's amazing. this is what it normally
looks like but I removed the atmosphere for you guys.
To be able to see it.
Very dense green stinky atmosphere.
So this planet is uninhabitable due to the stinkiness, the climate and the grossness
of it.
Every food...
And this planet, the size of this planet, it is about 8 inches in diameter.
Okay so kind of even small for a planet.
8 inches in diameter?
Yeah.
It's very very small.
This is a moon!
It's not a moon.
It's a planet or whatever they call it and it is located in New York City somewhere.
And whoever possesses it, possesses great power.
This is like the...
It's currently set into an amulet.
This is, yeah, this is what I was going to ask.
Is this like the cat that has the little Orion necklace in Men in Black?
This is exactly like that.
Yeah.
This is kind of a MacGuffin.
Some bodega cat in New York has this around its neck and nobody knows.
This is probably the most disgusting thing we've ever shown on the show.
Oh absolutely.
You guys should have seen when it was a butt before I posted this as a YouTube episode.
I wish that I could see it as a butt.
Wow look at this angle!
You know what?
I can see what it would look like as a butt right now.
This is land-
It's almost impossible to describe what I'm looking at, I'm very sorry.
The land is the feet, but what is this black void?
- That's the core of the planet.
- Okay.
- Oh, it's got an open core.
- Yeah, it's an open core scenario.
- I could see this being in like Super Mario Galaxy.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that's actually where it originated.
- Oh.
- Okay, and you said nobody lives on this, right?
- No, nobody except for one guy.
- Who?
- Who I just remembered who lives there.
- Okay, and what's his name?
- Caleb.
I don't, but not me, right?
I thought, I think his name is,
it's just, yeah, I don't remember his last name.
I think it started with P, but I don't,
I don't know that many details about him
'cause I've never been here to try and,
I don't really wanna go anywhere near it.
A glitch, you said?
It's just a glitch, yeah.
Okay.
Well, maybe it's just a glitch.
That's a mental glitch that you're having
'cause it's just keeping true.
All right, well, that's my planet, planet feet.
All right, come and show my planet, man.
Oh!
All right, let me see your planet.
Oh God, I'm moving slowly to my illness.
I need to see this planet.
I do, and I'm excited to see Julio's planet also, even though I already saw it.
Wow!
Okay!
Okay, so what I'm seeing here, let me try...
This is planet chill.
This looks like a person wearing sunglasses whose face has been violated and completely flayed by one million rubber bands.
Yeah, this looks like a cenobite.
- It's not, oh.
- This is fully centebrite vibes.
- I guess it does kinda look like somebody.
This is Planet Chill.
This is the Earth revolves around Planet Chill.
The Earth is one of, is one of the moon,
or is the only moon of Planet Chill.
- Oh my God.
- There's-- - Yeah, this looks like
when they try to blow up a watermelon
by putting rubber bands on it.
- There's-- - But with a human head.
- Look at the side profile on this, man.
This is cool. - Oh my God.
- So here's how this planet works.
Everybody lives on the white face of the man in the planet,
planet chill.
And then these are, they look like sunglasses from space,
but when you're on the planet,
they're actually two giant flat screen TVs
with Dolby Digital surround sound
in the entire planet installed.
That's what this back part is.
This is uninhabitable wires and cable management in the back.
And basically people sit on this edge
like it's the Grand Canyon and they watch the Super Bowl.
That sounds awesome.
Yeah, and these are giant 70 inch flat screen TVs on either side over here.
There is also a giant crack in the middle of the planet.
The no man's land.
No, it looks like it goes all the way down. It's a hollow earth kind of situation too.
And like I said, once a year when the earth revolves around this planet,
that you can actually, once a year, meaning the Super Bowl,
you can actually, people on Earth can watch the Super Bowl
in the sky, in space.
- Oh, that's actually pretty incredible.
- Yeah, yeah.
- If Earth doesn't--
- And all the girls live over,
all the girls on the planet live over here by the lips.
And they kiss the lips all day.
- They put their butt on it?
- They put their boobs and their butts
all over these two big, beautiful pink lips.
And they kiss it and they love it.
The girls all live on the lips and the guys live on all the stuff around the sunglasses.
And never the twain shall meet.
And earth revolves around this planet.
Earth revolves around basically earth doesn't fucking matter.
This is the only planet that matters.
This is where everything cool is happening.
Everyone on here look there's snow on earth.
People are snowing.
They're they're shoveling their driveways.
Meanwhile on planet chill people are drinking daiquiris.
There's a giant hole, there's a giant thing
that pops out of the eye there.
There's another one right there.
I mean, this is basically the only cool planet
in the universe and Earth is over.
And I think that my petition to the United Nations
is that we need to instantly evacuate all eights,
nines and tens to planet chill as soon as possible.
Wow, and the eights will live on this side
'cause we just need, we only need the eights there
so we appreciate the nines and the tens.
Well, yeah, and you gotta,
someone's gotta do cable management.
Yeah, exactly.
So we'll send the eights back here,
and then every once in a while,
you'll be walking around this edge land,
hunting for--
Above the sunglasses.
Yeah, hunting for money.
Oh, and there's an ear.
(laughing)
Hunting for money over here on the edge lands,
and you'll see one of the eights,
and you'll go, "Oh, God!"
'Cause it becomes so disgusting to you,
'cause you're so accustomed to the tens and the nines.
But yeah, it's like how if you it's like how if you eat you're eating something that's not
spicy at all and then you eat something that's a little spicy like a strawberry it burns
your mouth.
Exactly and I will say that Tens are the indigenous people of this of this land.
Wow.
Okay so it all of this belongs to the Tens and the Eights and the Nines are like the
Nines are second-class citizens and the Eights are animals.
Why don't you call it Planet Ten?
it's more chill than it is about like the hotness is how hot all the women are is basically
oh okay eights nines and tens with women the guys are all threes so the kids have no choice
but to get with the guys also lesbianism is illegal in the entire planet unless it's on
a poster unless it's on a poster in a dorm unless it's a picture pictures of lesbianism
- A picture or a video.
- Are required. - A picture or a video.
- Pictures and videos are required,
but it's illegal to be lesbian.
- They make them off-world.
You make them and then you import them in from Earth.
- Yeah, it's okay to be gay though,
but it's illegal to be lesbian.
All the lesbians have to live on Earth
and all the hot nines and tens and the dirty, dirty eights.
- Imagine being gay on planet chill.
(laughing)
You'd wanna get the hell out of there.
- Sounds like an amazing short story.
Yeah, it sounds like a great a great old pulp pulp.
Plus I find novel being gay on planet.
You'd find in the bookstore gay on the chill with it's like
Harrison Bergeron most incredible pick like painting you've ever
seen as the book cover.
Yeah, one.
There's the Harrison Bergeron style story for planet.
Chill is two lesbians that go on TV and just start making
and everyone and the and the horror the sci-fi horror of it
is that all the threes start clapping
'cause they think they're doing it for their entertainment.
- Oh no.
- Guys, I heard a new planet just got discovered.
- What happened? - Whoa.
- They haven't named it yet,
but a visual feed is coming in right now
of a new planet that just got discovered.
- I wanna see this planet.
- I need to see this planet. - Oh my God, what's this?
- I don't know, let's inspect it.
- Whoa. - Let's look closer.
It looks like some kind of food.
Oh my God.
- Oh my god, it's some kind of a mud man.
- What is this planet peanut butter?
- Imagine if you're in space,
you're on the moon of this planet,
and you're watching the sunrise,
and you see the planet's slow-mo orbit,
and it goes like this.
(laughing)
- That would be amazing. - Oh my god.
- This is why we should have been god.
- We should have been, yeah.
- God planet designers.
commission because it is
away we need to see we need to see who lives planet also
that's the other important point of view
pressure is to plan it yet to describe it
uh...
so i'm in the best detail possible and is called friendship
and uh...
the flip it is
this friday
the
because everyone on the entire planet is friends with you
so it's really moon and skull
can you try and describe this visually while we're looking at it?
*laughter*
no
what's that over to the side?
wait
this planet is not in space
it's moon friendship
this is another planet that is in New York City
it's exactly the same
same as the planet but it's just green and it's the moon and it's also called
moon friendship. This is so beautiful so it's a picture of two best friends as the background. Can you zoom in here to this part of the planet?
Yeah and which friend is the planet actually made of? Both of them. It looks like it's both.
Yeah it's planet friendship right there. Oh my god. It's two faces. So the atmosphere, or the galaxy that it's in, or the planet mimics the
galaxy that it's in. Pretty much yeah. That's beautiful. That is fascinating. I
wonder if NASA has done a paper on this. This is gonna be great for our audio
listener. Yeah I would say this is the only one that you have to tune in to
understand the video. This is an amazing planet guys. Yeah we're well on
our way to creating our own entire galaxy. I know. Which is probably what the goal of
of the five ways of planning.
- Are we gonna be doing a new planet every episode?
- Um, we, no, probably not.
(laughing)
- No, we're not.
- No, no way.
- I think, okay, so all of these planets
need to exist in the same, I know you said
that you're just a New York camera,
but I think it really should be--
- Well, New York is in space.
- All four of us, well that's true.
- Technically.
- Yeah.
- All four of us have planets in one galaxy.
Instead of the sun, we have the fun.
fun the fun instead of the moon we have the choom the planet chill is next to
the fun it rotates around the fun and it has a choom and I think Jubio's planets
might get Pluto'd here pretty soon might get kicked out of the galaxy yeah because
they're not really I heard that planet feet just exploded and it was
replaced by the second planet they just oh my god yeah that's scary that is
scary what new planet did they discover it was this one oh this one just covered
but the shape is a little different okay so this is the this planet of the
peanut butter man what is this photo and that's will Ferrell is that that is I
don't know who this is I don't think that I don't think this is a who I don't
think I would the mount it's too mountainous.
Yeah, there's a looks like it's a dry dry desert.
This planet is in.
And this does not have a choice.
This is this is in our galaxy.
This is a no choose planet is barely dangerous planet.
This is a planet that they are trying the scientists of our galaxy are trying to eliminate
the lack to style destroy every other planet.
Oh my God.
All right.
And this one has no choom.
This one has no chume, but it does orbit the fun.
- All right, well that's good news at least.
This is the Mercury, I guess, of our universe.
Let's bring it back to Mercury.
- Or just the space engine.
- Well, I guess maybe because, okay,
we're creating our own galaxy that we're pretty soon
is gonna make real, thanks to our prayers to God.
So what I'm thinking is maybe each of these planets
that we do for the five weeks of planets,
we can choose what elements we like about them.
Into our galaxy create the perfect plan yes, yeah
At the end of the month at the end of the month we'll have the perfect planet we could terraform Earth to also match this planet
It's a pretty good idea
Are you guys ever do you guys ever get scared that you're gonna be asleep?
And then a asteroid is going to hit the world and destroy it instantly or some kind of space object that we've never
discovered that moves at the speed of light that's the size of a quarter is
gonna hit the earth and go and destroy it into pieces I'm gonna be honest that I
don't think about this the galaxy in the solar system too much and I think that
is because that's that's for my own safety though I mean as soon as we
started talking about other galaxies I was like full isolationist do not know
You do not engage do not engage. I'm gonna know you take me to another galaxy. I'm gonna nope the fuck out of there
I'm with you kill it with fire
I think I'm not so worried about space objects because the thing about space objects is even if they're moving as fast as as
Fast as a thing could possibly move
That's still really slow because of how big everything is they're so good you would have yeah, man if the Sun
Exploded it would take eight minutes for the the light to go away
But if something hit us so fastly, but it can't go faster than the speed of light, but so we would know
I'm not afraid it's gonna happen in my sleep because they're gonna tell us about it before it happens
Nothing you can do if you have a big ball headed towards your head. Yeah, but you know about it
This is like it would be like seeing
Like if you were out at night and you looked up at the full moon and you saw a ball
falling from the moon. That would be scary. Oh no! Yeah, but by the time it got to you.
I would just stand there. Yeah, exactly. I would not stand there. First of all, I would
leave the planet. I would be terrified with fear. They told us that an asteroid was coming.
First of all, I would leave the planet. No, you wouldn't. I would fly away to another planet. Yes,
I would. You would not use, code name, Kid Next Door 2x4 technology to build a wood spaceship.
I would fly away from the planet with a pwodogostick. A pwodogostick? What the hell
Yeah, it's on a different planet. You don't know it. It's a new invention that I got
Bullshit doesn't exist man. It's a potago on this planet. It's made by the Pota goes. Yeah, I
Feel like you guys are fucking lying to me. I'm not fucking with you
There's a no you're not very cultured when it comes to planets
I know about every other planet and I know what order they're in they're okay
Where the pota goes where the pota goes I'm playing at Padogian. No, it's not. Okay. Well you got that one
The Padogians live next door to me. No, they don't the Padogians or maybe what OJ the alien is
I don't want aliens to visit because I think that culturally there will be a lot of differences
You're not you don't fuck with two cultural differences. Well, I just think they'll have a hard time
I think aliens will get here and they'll be like the they'll be like white guys that order off the menu at the bodega
They go.
Yeah.
They're supposed to go on and they go into McDonald's like big back.
Yeah exactly.
They're doing the accent.
And they go what the hell is that man?
You're not supposed to order off the menu at the bodega.
I have discovered that this is a thing that only white people do.
Why do they have the...
You go in and tell it isn't me.
I'll have the Cuomo sandwich and they go what number is that?
Yeah they walk out from behind the counter and they look at the menu.
- They look at the thing, 'cause everybody else comes in
and they say, "Let me get a pepperoni pizza with shrimp."
And you walk in and you say, "Let me have the cotton club."
- I want an ice chicken tender.
- I have to go in there and I have to look at the menu
and then say every single thing piece by piece.
- Just the ingredients.
- The menus are fake, you don't even have to.
- The menus are completely, it's like,
you just have to know what they want.
- It's a legal thing, that they have to have a menu
'cause they're technically a restaurant.
- They have one million sandwiches on.
- Okay, this wouldn't happen on my planet.
I'm just gonna say it.
On my planet, you got a sandwich on your menu,
everyone knows how to make it.
- They always just turn around when I say,
"Yeah, let me get the firefighter."
And they turn around and they say,
"Which number is that?"
What are you talking?
They look at me like I'm crazy.
And it's floating above their head like runescape text.
It's right above their head, the firefighter.
And I'm like, "You want me to get the firefighter?"
and they say, "Can you give me a hex code for that?"
They do not like me.
- Now I used to order this sandwich all the time
called the Bushwick at Sunrise Deli
next to my old apartment.
Do you remember that sandwich?
- You said, "Can I get the Bushwick?"
You said that? - Yeah, I said,
"Can I get the Bushwick?"
It's a good sandwich, though.
It's roast beef-- - That sounds like a code
at a happy ending massage place.
- Wait 'til you hear what it is.
It's roast beef, pepper jack, jalapenos, mustard,
like hot mustard, and I would get pickles on it.
- So you're making, see, but you know the ingredients,
so just say that, dude.
- Well, I don't know, well, I'm missing a few of them.
There's a few more ingredients
that I'm forgetting currently.
- I'm just saying, man, this is, I've discovered,
I'm done doing this.
I'm done ordering off the menu.
I feel like a fool every time.
It's making me feel less than I did at one time and I was like, oh that's not clearly not they just don't well again on our planets
If there's a menu
You get to order from you get to order off the menu. You can always order
You can always order off the menu. What do you guys think about mercurians?
The mercurians are
Pretty cool. I would say
They have
What if they got one big eye on the front right mm-hmm?
One big eye on the front completely white skin
You know not like Caucasian like no way for like a like paper paper white white Kindle paper white
Maybe they are they be a real
They are many would say they were
Do they still exist or no no?
They were they live they flew too close to the Sun pun intended literally
Shit, and they guys burn mercury could reach temperatures of 800 degrees Fahrenheit. Yes wait, but how is it I see then?
Because it can reach temperatures of negative 290 degrees Fahrenheit, which one would actually be in
I'm looking at a mercury and right now hold on let me show you guys what I'm looking at. What does it look like?
I'm
I'm looking at this. This is not a McCurry and I remember oh
She's beautiful as a woman with fire hair and a green V shaped body
clothes
Do you think maybe we could get oh, well this hasn't happened yet? This is in the year 3000
Do you guys think that if we ever go to Mercury will hopefully find oil under the ground
hopefully
Okay, I just watched a movie that maybe would would be relevant to this
It's called killers of the flower moon, and I feel like it also has to do with mercury because of the word moon
So why do I feel like my entire life is a pattern?
Was that movie good has he done it again?
He did he only made it once
It was a fucking really good
Yeah
It is a really good point. Do you think that he probably loves the boys right Scorsese?
Oh, yeah, because it's a send-up of superhero cinema. No cuz he's like he's like fuck all this MCU shit, man
I like cusses I like I like cussing and boobies. Let's watch the boys
Cuz they're my boobs in the show I
Only watch the first season. I think there was some pairs
There's and I think there were a month accident. Yeah, I think there's huge ease huge ease and humongous is in like two episodes maybe
That's interesting. They should add a hero whose power is heard the size of her boobs didn't they have of her
Do you remember--
- That she can distract villains?
- Do you remember this show--
- Yeah, where they're just their size
and they can't do anything?
- The show on the SyFy channel, and it was,
I forget what it, I think it was called
Who Wants to Be a Superhero or something?
No, but that would be an amazing show on the SyFy channel.
Could you imagine that?
- Real sex.
- It's a space--
- Real sex on the SyFy channel,
a choir of real sex. - It's a space taxi.
It's a space taxi.
Oh no, that's way funnier.
- Yeah, no, it'd be funnier if they just syndicated
for real sex.
- After, but they put, yeah, after like 4 p.m.,
the Science Channel just turns into real sex reruns.
- Yeah.
- We went to Mardi Gras with a can of whipped cream
with the Science Channel thing on the bottom right.
- I watched that one time when I was a kid, and--
- It doesn't seem like the realest sex.
- No, no, no, it's really a documentary
about sex and everything.
And I learned that the hard way
because the episode that I saw, barely any sex stuff in it.
What I saw in that episode was a grown man
who programmed sex games for Windows 3.1
and it was just him playing these animated,
kind of like Leisure Suit Larry type games
and it was just him getting horny as shit
at his own computer.
- And they called that real sex.
- And I was like 11 years old, I was too scared
to look up porn on the computer watching that
and I was like, "Oh, come on."
At 11, you were too scared to look up porn, man?
You were a pussy.
I didn't know how to delete the history yet.
You just don't care.
Yeah, it doesn't bother you.
No, no, no, no.
It's supposed to not bother you.
Yeah, just be unbothered.
You're supposed to be free of all kind of thought
when you're that age.
No, I'm the middle of three boys
and then I have an older sister
and we only had one computer.
I wasn't gonna let them know that I jack off.
I wouldn't look up porn
if I was in the middle of three boys either.
Yeah, that would be a pretty inopportune time.
How are you even in the middle of three?
- I'm the middle of three, I meant.
- Oh, okay. - Of three.
- I was gonna say, that doesn't make so much sense
to be in the middle of three people.
- I think that's what you said.
I think I just twisted your words.
- I was in the middle of three boys.
- I think you twisted my words.
- Well, what else can you do, man?
- I think I just twisted your words.
- Okay, we need like-- - I don't twist people's words.
- I think we need like five more Mercury Facts
before we send off into space. - My PC just get,
let me pull up Mercury Facts again.
- And I think it's Discord, goddammit.
- What?
My PC just skipped.
- That's okay.
- I gotta figure out why that always happens.
- When the ions, or, hold on.
When the ions, I don't know what the ions are,
but when the ions strike the surface, I assume of mercury,
they knock off neutrally charged atoms
and send them on a loop high into the sky.
- Huh.
- That is, I don't really understand that fact.
- I just hope, okay.
Well here's some facts about Planet Chill
because Mercury has some pretty wack-ass facts,
I'm gonna be honest.
- Yeah.
- On Planet Chill, there is a statue of liberty
that's fully in a bikini.
- Whoa! - That's cool.
- Yeah, yeah.
And she's got a job too.
Or you know what kind of job,
I don't have to say what kind of job.
- Here's a fact about Planet,
- Planet Peanut Butter Man was only recently discovered
because it just entered this galaxy
because it was beforehand trapped inside of a Ziploc bag.
A giant Ziploc bag.
- That's more of a scary fact for Halloween.
- A penis-sized Ziploc bag that was opened up by a meteor.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- And released the planet into the galaxy.
- There's really only like five space things.
Okay, what's the next planet?
- So next planet is Venus, I think.
- Okay, we're gonna have to figure out some stuff for Venus.
that is uh... i think we we cannot blue or load on making planets
uh... addressing up
there are all time will be another day
another another song costumes and new we won't do exactly what we did this time
and i don't know how the world will be a little different
and uh... i hope you join us on the rest of this journey you can help me on
patrion so it's not that it's right so we can be on saturday will be on saturday
this episode comes out tomorrow
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Okay, then I, on Saturday, when the next episode drops,
or sorry, Sunday, the day after the next episode drops,
I will be in Chi City, Chicago, and maybe--
- Chi-Rac.
- If you come to the show and show me that you have a,
you have OJ the Alien Mercury Rap downloaded to your phone,
I will sign your phone.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
And I'm going to be--
- I didn't think of a good thing.
Los Angerac Drillifornia on November 17th.
In Los Angerac Drillifornia,
performing 30 minutes of standup comedy
with my friend Gus Fiveros at The Yard.
We're doing two shows, go check out the thing
and buy some tickets there.
- And that's The Yard, the venue.
- The Yard, the venue.
Not performing on a podcast, that would make no sense.
So if you want to see Planet Chill in real life,
come on through and I'll buy you a key chain.
All right, goodbye my friends.
- Happy planets.
- Happy planet month. - Happy planet month.
- Bye.
- I don't know, when you were sober,
it was like everyone kind of respected it.
When I was sober, it was kind of like
everyone was waiting to have another beer.
- Yeah, it felt like the doomsday clock was at.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Like it was almost like-- - One minute to midnight.
Like it was almost like we would go out and I would like we'd go to that bar and I would get like a fucking orange soda or something.
And then you would like almost buy me a beer every time.
It's funny when people are straight edge or they used to be alcoholics or something.
It's so funny to buy them a beer and be like, oh, you don't want it?
All right, it is mine.
I think I did that. Yeah, I did that to Brace after the show.
You got to do it every time.
Yeah, I had two shots.
You have to test their gangster willpower.
Yeah.
I was really good about it for six months.
It doesn't mean anything.
If you don't have the willpower to stay straight edge in the face of a friend
Exactly.
Offering you alcohol, then you don't deserve to wear the badge of honor that is straight edge.
I 100% agree.
You should be, every single person in your life who's like an AA or whatever,
you should be like asking for their chip.
You should be tricking them.
You should literally be trying to trick them.
Yeah, I know it's probably seltzer water.
And then if you can't smell it before you take a sip,
you should be, yeah, exactly.
If you don't have the diligence to check for the poison
that is ruining your life in every single thing that you have.
Your touch should remove alcohol from liquids.
You should be making...
You should pick up a cup and the liquid in the cup disappears.
It becomes...
And if they don't break on the seltzer trick,
you should be inviting them over and making alcoholic beef stew
you and trying to like pouring hard
be
and saying and they're two by ten.
No, it's delicious.
Fifteen percent.
So you like it.
I fucking knew it.
Yeah, they're like alcohol poisoning.
Fuck is so funny.
God damn.
They don't make edibles for beer.
It was sitting with your homies and watching watching a sports game,
eating beef stew.
That is so funny.
That would actually be so nice.
Spilling it everywhere, plus sitting with those shallow bowls.
Six bowls of beef stew each.
Just dying dude.
*Dunkey's Outro*