Welcome to minute one of podcast of the first minute of this show. We had to
catch up on all of our nice times that we spent together. We caught up and now
we're ready to do this shit. Okay so Pierce tell your story again about
watching a deer get shot in the head. No we recorded 30 of the most
six unreleasable minutes of podcasting. It was all about animal gore and it was
about chickens and being cut and killed. I had a full breakdown. And now I have
a song parody, guys, that I came up with in this last minute. Oh, my God, and I
need to do my song parody again. Wait, we still... We have to redo that song.
Yeah, we'll let Caleb go first. Okay. Okay, you guys know Frank Sinatra, It
Was A Very Good Year? Uh-huh.
When I was one,
I was very, very young.
I was very, very young and very hungry and I wore different clothes. I smelled
like the clothes
that my mom made me wear.
It was a very one year.
That's very first year.
In my second year.
I learned my first word.
I learned to say dad.
bad. I learned to say dad and what foods tasted bad.
It was a very my second year
terrible to my very third
very
my very third year. It was the very third. I learn about different shapes,
so that's my parodies instead because that's I was a nice on the ray. I was
my very first mistake. He's saying, "When I was seventeen, when I was twenty-five,
when I was thirty-five, now I'm forty-five." I'm saying, "What happened
to eleven?" Let's start from the beginning. When I was thirteen, I had my
first love. There we go. Thank you. Remember that song? No. Because my uncle
did, and I was good at drawing. Remember it was a Justin Bieber song? Oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah. I don't remember this song. That's Usher or
Ludacris. Ludacris. Yeah, yeah. When I was thirteen, I had my first love. Usher's
one who signed just and be yes, the scooter brawn is the one that signed
him. So here's my song, which may be
this one. This one will be a good lead into the third one, which is the best
one. There's this one. I thought mine was pretty good. Yours is really good.
This
really good one and then maybe a kind of man one that everyone's already heard a
couple times. Yeah, and then a good one and then the perfect one best one. So
this is a song parody by somebody who thinks that the office character Jim is
name Joe. Okay, it goes like this. Well, the weather outside is Dwight full, but
inside it's just so Michael
and since there's no place to go, Pam and Joe, Pam and Joe, Pam and Joe, it's
great and then everybody is like no, it's a jam. It's Jim. Oh, that doesn't
run
and I knew that it just doesn't since there's no place to win
got since there's no one named Tim
and
the British one was named Tim
and Jim. There we go. It's good. Okay, now the third song, the third one hit
it. Why is everybody at the greatest pool? What is it? Everybody think the
Grinch is cool. Everybody's at the Grinch's pool. It's like
why does everybody think the Grinch is cool? Everybody skip school when the
the Grinch's pool went to Grinch's, went to Grinch's. That's very that's
a new lab. I think I just saw the Grinch at school. I just saw the
Grinch at school. Why did everybody think the how did that start? I just
saw the mother fucking granted school that didn't start for any good reason.
I started from one and then I think I just had too much. I kids do you like
Christmas? Yeah, I want to see me swim in a nine inch pool with a green guy
like I did. Was that before you don't see me do it like I did? Was that
before
I just drank a bit of egg nog
dare me to play
dare me to fly
we were also doing that yeah the lady to fly the
final red. I said nothing you idiots
he's locked in. What is the one we're doing the final rep battle of eight
mile? Oh yeah, he's doing he's going like
know and he think the Grinch ain't cool, then how come I saw him at the
Grinch's pool
for Christmas? What's the area code for the North Pole? That's what I was
trying to figure. I was trying to figure out who maybe for who yeah, but
it's hard to figure out the old health organization twelve to five everybody in
the twelve to five yeah. I don't know man yeah. I don't know either. What was
that? Some parodies are so difficult. I don't know how we are now. Does it
before that we were doing pretty much the easiest thing you can do. We were
doing Peter, Peter Griffin,
fucking Jennifer Coolidge or no, Jennifer Coolidge fucking Peter Griffin so hard
his butt falls off. I got a kick out of this. He loved that one. Just say,
"Oh, my butt fell off." It's pretty good, I think. It's not so funny anymore,
but it was funny back in the day. When it happened, it was really funny,
but that was what led into the Grinch's Cruel Song. I have a song parody
that has no lyrics, but it's it's
oh wait. I just remember another song parody. We were doing okay,
so this is okay. You do your first feel good ink meets crazy frog ready,
okay, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't I don't get a bing bing now. That's just girl. You just did you just
did girl talk. That's it. That was girl talk. That was here's another one that
I just thought of
that before this it's it's like it imagine like kind of like a two thousand
on YouTube video style song parody, maybe Miranda Sings, Type 5.
And it's a bunch of guys and they're singing, "This is why I wear
douchebags." This is why I wear douchebags. This is why I wear douchebags.
We have no class. We have no class. We just have swag. This is why I
wear douchebags.
I could see that. We don't use mouth to make our pants tight. Isn't that
perfect? Couldn't that have been a video? Yeah, that could be like 2008,
like yeah, what was that that thing the station
is why we're do back. Yeah, that's why I would do I watch a forty minute video
about the downfall of freddie wong today. Yeah, the downfall fallen. He does. He
hasn't made a video in five years. That's because he's working on the
avengers movies. Probably working really game high school. Well, it's the
downfall as in he doesn't make youtube videos anymore. I'm sure that he's
probably never had to say downfall to get you to click that fact you wouldn't
click on a video that was like the
continued success of beautiful Freddy.
He's not beautiful. I mean he is the plateaued success of Freddy Wong. I
don't say that don't say that a Freddy Freddy Wong is a beautiful Freddy Wong
looks like the most beautiful. What is he up to? How did he fall? That was the
first podcast I ever listened to was Freddy Wong's podcast. What was his
podcast? Face rocker man face rockers and he had a he had a
he had a he had a pickup artist on there. Which one mystery? No, his name was like
Fudd.
His name was like Brian. His name was like
a pickup artist named Fudd and he's dressed up like a hunter. His name was
like
he's walking up to a woman with a dead rabbit.
That's not working for me, man. That's not working at all? No. His name was
Brian Lion or something like that. Brian the Lion? It was just something lion and
he told some story. Maybe he was just lion. About how he would pick, I've
we talked about this before. Actually, he told some story about how you would
pick up girls at LARPing events. That's beast. Yeah, because they're hungry for
dick. That's the only reason you go to a LARPing thing or a Renaissance fair is
to have sex and fuck. Yeah, both. Yeah. That's- it is crazy that how
every single person at a Ren fair is like the horniest person in the world.
I think that's why game, like the game theory is real, because sometimes game
is just an actual game. Sometimes games just play time. That's always who want
everyone who wants to play a game is interested in engaging with another
person in a sexual way. Yeah, jigsaw jigsaw is kind of sexually an old man
jigsaw is sexually active. Why do you think you watch is the trap? You know, I
just recently found out jigsaw is the good guy. Yeah, only in the new movie in
the new movie. Well, but he targets people who litter. He targets people who
who pretend to be sick and you are fat or who cut themselves. He says didn't one
boy, it's really funny. The first one he said yeah, the first one has one where
it's like there's a guy who is or it might be a woman who's like like you
cut you cut you slit your wrists, but I think you did it for attention. Now you
have to prove that you really want to live like you have to in order to
survive. You have to crawl through this barbed wire or you can just stay here
and die and the person's like and like cross like it just showed the person.
It just why that is a person wanted. Why would you not just die man? It's not
his apprentice actually. I there any in the reverse bear trap. Are there any
traps where there's just someone standing there like with a gun like
instead of it being like a pre rigged rub goldberg thing you dis this guy
you'll shoot first one of like when they're both chained in the bathroom
that just one of the guys is like you have to kill the other guy. Oh yeah,
this off your like does do his apprentice her crimes that she's addicted
to drugs. She's a drug addict, but also but then so also here I'm sorry for the
spoilers for everybody, but then it's revealed that also she she's addicted to
drugs, but then also her boyfriend was worked at a clinic where jigsaw's ex
wife worked and he was rushing quickly out of the clinic after wanting to get
drugs and he opened the door too fast and it slammed on yes, as ex wife's
pregnant stomach and caused a miscarriage. I thought that was a baby
with a door, baby with a door. I thought that was a bad for that. I had as a
kid. I never thought that that was a jigsaw the movie thing. I thought that I
imagine that and then I looked it up later and I was like. Oh, does the first
one have the booby trap at the end where there's just like a shotgun sitting
above like a doorway? That's a two yeah to yeah that is that's the best trap at
all of them. That's also yeah he's a trap genius and he invents was just yeah
because the person is like well. Why don't we just leave
that one also is the best ending where it's like at the beginning they have
they kidnapped Donnie Walberg son and jigsaw like your son is safe and sound
and at the end it's revealed that the sun was in the same room as Donny
Wahlberg the whole time he was just inside a safe. Yeah, oh that's scary. I
told you exactly where he was. Have you guys have you guys ever seen safe room
or panic room? No, that's what it's called. It's about a lady. I think it's
Jody Foster and she has a house where she has a panic room in it and the most
of the movie just takes place her and her her daughter in this room, and I
wanted one of these rooms so so badly yeah. That's a type of a bunker in your
my house sounds so fucking it's because of the only guy episode. I would the
only reason I know about that I would use it as it would just be a man caved
yeah, Xbox yeah. I really wanted a crawl space just to be laid down somewhere
secret. There was a crawl space in my house, but it was there was a hole in
the roof type of vibe crawl space. Oh, we're not supposed to be into this part
of it
thinking about a saw. I told you guys that I used to talking about talking
about talking about I used to work at a escape room in L. A. And there was one
escape room that was cartel themed and that's insane. It opens in a you get you
that is insane. That is it. Why would they have a cartel so you're trapped in
a van because the cartel yeah exactly you're trapped in the you're talking
about passenger van and then you have to get out and the way you get out is this
is if you want to impress any dates that you're taking to the sixty out escape
rooms in silver. It's probably gone. It's probably gone by the way all this all
the escape rooms that I worked for are controlled by like an actual Russian.
How many did you work for just one, but the one location I worked for I went to
a
I went to like a award ceremony for the employees that worked there and they
were just like
like three like very old babushkas like counting hundred dollar bills while
they played candy crush. That's amazing. That's and yeah anyway
the traps are always broken. They were just pieces of shit, but there's this
one part of the puzzle where you had to rig like an actual car battery to this
like old school radio to get in touch with the outside so that you could call
for help, but the radio would never work. So we had to just call in and pretend to
be the guys in the cartel who the people who were paying to do it had earlier
heard. So we literally had to do a cholo impression
because they're supposed to be like overhearing the guys, but the audio
could never play, but they would do it right and it's so finicky to get the
that is a soft. You are you in your first, yeah, we you have to for years
to for years, you're going to you've done an impression of a like now with
your friends. Now you have to do it for your job or you'll get fired.
Yeah, I did and then so every time we did it, they were just go huh. I guess
that was a hint. I understand that we're yeah anyway. It was cool. It was a
good job. I did an escape room with my family wanted to do an escape room
and some of my extended family over zoom during covid is like remember that
was like a like a covid yeah. I was like oh you can do it. It was it wasn't it
wasn't we had to do that. Yeah, it was pretty horrible. It was like some guy
in a like you know on zoom, but still wearing the mask because it's like early
covid. I feel like and he was like it was pirate themed, so he's like are you
resume and then it was like it was so horrible because they didn't even it
wasn't even that they had a camera and we're going through the room. It was
let's see what he does. I'll clean it on the cable. I'll clean it up.
It's covered in plastic. I know, but I just want to give you some urgency
before I go any further before I go any further. The spiller we can over here.
You can let me finish yeah. It was so horrible because it was it wasn't even
that they had a camera inside the escape room. It was that they had like
essentially what we do for like they had like a slide show of like pictures of
stuff in the room yeah and everybody in my family was just slightly too old to
understand that was going on. So I click so they kept it less than a point in
clicking. It was like do you can you say the right thing so we can go to the
next slide and the yeah everybody kept asking every single slide like five
times. Do you have like a different angle of this? Can we look closer at
this and the guy you just hear clicking noise and the guy would be like no, we
can't. Unfortunately, I can't get any closer and it was just it was just
pictures of like walls with like the classic like escape room, like like
codes and stuff. Can you zoom in and be like no at least that one has more free
will because when we had to do it over zoom, it was just like people would call
and it was just my friend Patrick holding a phone and just walking around the
escape room and they were like
can you go over there? I can
that's exactly what it was. It was like yeah, I guess we could go back to that,
but like yeah, I did an escape room twice with my family and the first one
we had like eleven people and we had to like convince the people like we because
six was the limit and we were like we really want eleven people to do it and a
one of us are kids and I was like thirteen or fourteen, and it was the
entire thing was my brother's ex girlfriend trying to figure out all the
math stuff in the thing and then me and the other boys in our cousin group
taking photos of each other with a disposable camera, having sex with a
statue
that had boobs. Yeah, when I was in fourth grade, my grandma took me to an
escape room like back before I had any idea what it was, and it was ancient
Egypt themed and we went in and it was like the second room and they had a
skeleton and it scared me so bad that I got sick to my stomach and I told the
employee that I had to leave and he took me out a secret exit and I waited for
my my grandma finished the room by herself and I waited for myself. I
waited by myself in the lobby. You got scared by a skeleton. I was like I
thought it was there so fucking I've never done an escape room. You can't
just don't let yourself. I only did that one and then I got taken on one at a
school trip and then the one on zoom. Yeah, we talked about that before like I
almost I'd failed that interview so bad.
Oh, you know, I almost worked with the master himself. Wow, yeah, yeah, we've
talked about that up and down. Yeah, but what I want to talk about is the
spiller right now. Why Mr Spill Mr Spill, Mr Spill, because the other day he
spilled Joe's coffee and instead of cleaning up the spill, he ran and got
another coffee and left all of the spill jumped out of the chair and said he
you another one right now. I mean, only out of the door. The only reason he
picked up the spill right now was to because he knew that we're going to tell
this story. No, I don't care about this story. He knew it. I think that's a nice
thing to do, Caleb, because you're counting on your friends to take care of
the spill. The spill is did the spill cost you $4.50? What? Yes. And emotional
little bit about you know what the still cost me this patch of table right here.
Yeah, that's a difference. That wasn't the only spill. That wasn't the why we
don't have to litigate this whole thing, but if so, if you go back now,
the podcast, by all means, put me on trial. Let's go put you on trial right
now. The table me on trial. You know this is more. I don't know if you watch
Oppenheimer. There's more of a hearing than a trial. You don't have a chance to
defend yourself, pal.
He's the guy from winning time that yells at Oppenheimer. I'm sorry. I use so
many performance enhancing drinks where I'm so good at the podcast that I have to
stick around and stick them around and spill them. Yeah, you guys imagine
being the first person to have your pink nipples on IMAX color stock. Is that
what that was?
Yeah,
I can't remember
that's my Florence.
Did you do that again? I like I like what you say, just one and a half more
times long hair.
No, she has a short hair. She's not quite so girly at all. Is she? No, but
She has long hair in that movie, not quite it's pretty it's quite long. She
looks like she plays rugby. It's quite I like
you like
I like
I can see you like that. Yes, not so much for me, but I'd like to fight her
in an octagon. I'd like to fight her and lose. I'd like to fight her and lose a
hundred
it hurts so bad. Keep doing so fucking. It hurts so bad, but I'm still awake.
Keep fighting me. Yeah, I would like to have a contest where she's only allowed
to use her lower body and I'm only allowed to use the top of my head. You
wanna what you wanna
that's how we can have a co a co ed
fighting. All right, I want a good clean fight.
You can only use the top of your head.
Florence, I'm going to tie your arms behind your back.
Florence
her friends call you. It's not you
who it's poo. Her name is close to pure bitches name.
You can't keep
he learned how to break out of handcuffs just for the fight is doing David Blaine.
Yeah, I would like to do a fight where she's only allowed to use the soles of
her feet and I'm only allowed to use the tips of my
of my tongue versus the bottom of your ass.
I want a good clean fight, the bottom of no dirty business. What is the bottom
of the S, the the the the part of the back rest of the as she's where the
as cheek falls over. That's
plastic falls falls over the leg over the butt. It honestly depends how big
your butt is because some people's butts are so small that they're assholes on
the exact same topographical level as the tip of their cheek. That's the gym I
go to is as an is having an epidemic of the bugs in most insanely fake asses of
all time, and they the women go in, they work out and like why are you doing
this? You like women with BBL, right? Yeah, women with like crazy. You
downloaded a new avatar. I want to pretend to get to grind through and it's
always a woman. You spent riot points. You don't need the
I
what are you doing? You already bought this.
It's always a woman who has like no neck at all, just like head bolted onto
the shoulders. Yeah, she's got it. She's got a BBL still biggest, all the
skinny, skinny chicken legs, all the fat they moved up to her neck. Yeah, it's
It's kind of crazy, man.
I want to pretend to get a BBL just so I can sit backwards on a plane.
You can do that already.
You can just do that.
I was on a plane on the...
I just want to just...
Just sitting like this on a plane with my flat ass is such a funny...
I would love to be sitting on a...
Women who get BBLs can't sit on the flight.
There's like women who like can only pay for the BBL, so then they go on the plane and
then there's just like videos of just like people walking by and it's just like two girls
sitting backwards with gigantic asses.
facing the head of the sea. I would love to be sitting next to a girl having
doing that and being like what are you doing and she says I just got a BBL. I
say you got a bubble.
It's actually B U B B L.
You stupid
I went on a
sweater, best
nerd glasses
a dumb B L
B L. They bring you a B B.
they bring you a you B B L Y for the adjective. They bring you on that
fucking podcast called like what that that whatever yeah, whatever and then
it's just you and the fucking sweater vest and the big glasses and is like
this nerd owns these only
you got a boob job. You mean you gave a blow job
I went on a plane, Cameron, the nerd
lower third. Like that fucking sixteen year old Israeli kid, you like blow up
like that?
I went to, I went to... Bill Clinton actually couldn't be president, he was
already president twice. I went to,
on a plane, I went to on a plane and I had a, speaking of planes, this was a
Spirit Air plane to Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, and there was, on the plane it
was like 50 people, just normal people from New York and then 50 like Hasidic
children who had never been on an airplane before and thought it was the
most amazing thing ever. Yeah. And they were running around, like I didn't know
this was allowed and now I want to do this next time I go on a plane. Once they
turn the seatbelt sign off, you can run up and down and hit each other. Well,
it's allowed for kids. I don't think that you can do that. It's allowed for
adults. Well, I mean, it would be funny if, like, you saw all of that and then
you just like all the kids running up and down the aisle. You see that you
immediately unbuckle. You try to join them and you're just like Billy. I
wanted to I wanted to one of the kids across the plane. One of them dropped a
bracelet and I picked it up and I said here you go and I would have said it's
my now. Have you guys ever gone and asked for more snacks on the plane? Yes,
well, actually, I can get up and get the cheese. It's a jet blue has a tree
with unlimited snacks. Well, not a blue, but you've asked this. Have you ever
as basically like asking to get more farts on the plane? Which is my
I actually fart a thousand more times. I
fart. I think I save up all my farts throughout the months and then, as soon
as I get on a plane, I let them out. So you know, it's crazy about the plane. I
get on the plane having to shit and I get off the plane, not having to shit.
It is a pressure and the pressure on your stomach is building, but it doesn't
turn solid waste into vapor. Does it? Yes, it does.
It's a pressure. Look at a bag. Look at a bag of some chips when you're like
got the plan and I made one a hundred foot long unbroken spaghetti noodle.
Yeah, every time you make an eel yeah when I
every time I get off the plane, you go up right and that's pushing the poop
down a little bit right, but then you go down to land and the poop is flying up
your body and turning back into food. Yeah, it's getting another chance at
digest. Yeah, that makes that's why your food when you get off a plane is crazy.
Everything the time of Adderall shits. I feel like Adderall shits is the whole
point of Adderall. Like I don't even I think that taking that kind of shit is
what motivates me to work for the rest of the day. That's why I like coffee.
Yeah, you like coffee. I've been getting into coffee. I love look at that.
You like coffee. I don't like coffee.
That's why I like coffee. I've been drinking so much more coffee recently.
I think you. Because of this new store. Yeah, me too. It makes you have insane
food. I think I have two cold brews a day now, which is insane. I'm always
getting three cold brews a day with cream. I don't get that. Just cold brew
milk cream. I'm getting black. I always I always force myself to have usually I
try to make myself have half a cup of coffee a day and that's my my top level
max to try and give myself a healthy body. Yeah, but recently it's been a
coffee. It's good for a cup of coffee from the store and this will this is
rocket fuel. It's changing me. It's a different type of coffee than what I
make in my Mr. Coffee machine from 1995. I have coffee's a good brand. I'm gonna
go pee and I've been the one I've been completely pooping so much. We're gonna
off the cameras and do an audio only throwback right yeah.
All right. Yeah. Fuck it.
Of what?
Fuck it.
Of podcast about list.
Let's just say fuck it and close all the cameras right now.
Yeah.
Um.
That's one.
We were talking about airplane shits, but every single time that I've.
I can never shit on an airplane.
Every single time I've gotten off a plane has been the worst gas I've ever had in my entire life.
Have you ever farted in an Uber?
You know what?
Have you ever had to fart so bad that you have to pee?
Yes.
All the time.
But I hate shitting on planes.
I won't shit on a plane.
but I love uber, but I love sitting on the am track sitting on the am tracking
oh yeah thrown around. You have to hold on to the handles next to the toilet,
so do not get thrown off and shit onto the floor by accident. I'll never when
you have to piss and you have to put your you have to leave your entire body
yeah, it's a jerk off just so you can get a boner just yeah, just to piss can
fly out of your boner like straw into the toilet. You know what I'm talking
about where you have to you have to get a bigger reach. So you get your you give
- Why does it feel like, why does it feel like
every time I go on the Amtrak and I need to pee,
it's smooth sailing, but the second I get into the bathroom
and I lock the door with that strange lock
that looks like an alien's antenna or a robot's wiener.
- A red robot's wiener.
- The train starts bouncing around
like we just hit some turbulence on the track.
- Right, before you know it,
this train was built by toddlers, the track.
- Exactly, I feel like I go into the bathroom
and I get teleported to a train in Topsy Turvy World
or a roller coaster. Yeah, and I guess that must be because of something weird
right and maybe it's the north. It must be a phenomenon and people in the
northeast been knew about this. God damn, I do love the in track bathroom.
The best shit I can ever take, though, is that like a gelson's or just any
grocery store, just an upscale grocery store. Oh, there one. Oh yeah, you just
go in there by yourself. No one's not. I so I got off a plane one time,
gotten an Uber and then I don't know if it was just because I think I was leaving like
the yeah, I think it was I don't remember what I think was leaving La and I must have
ate at that fucking rock and roll restaurant at La X and I just had the worst gas in my
entire life and I just remember farting in this Uber and it was like a silent like really
really disguster silent disguster and I was like I hope that doesn't smell. I hope that
that doesn't smell and then like a minute later, I just see the Uber driver
just open the window. I was like I see the Uber driver just open the window. I
took
one of the more recent a few weeks ago. I took a shit in a public bathroom in a
public library. Yeah, I think it was the one near Barkley Center, maybe and you
wiped with a book and I went in there. I went down. It's been so first of all,
I haven't been in a library since yeah yeah forever, but this was the craziest
public bath. I went down there was a like a room like kind of like a big like
studio, you know that you could like rent out for events and the basement of
the library where the bathroom was and there was a group of people who were
like being taught how to walk the runway. Like it was like everyone like doing
runway walks and someone like going like okay now like like and they were doing a
whole thing and I go into the bathroom and it's three stalls. The ones on the on
the outside edges are taken and I so I go into the middle one to take a shit and
they're both the guys on both sides of me are smoking, clearly smoking and
they're both just
they're both the entire time. I was trying like the fastest shit I ever
took as I was like I need to get out here. They're both just going like
it was so horrible. I would love to smoke on the toilet yeah, just two guys
smoking on the toilet of one stall apart and you're both groaning literally
both identically doing the public bath. They're both stress grown yeah. They're
with two models. They're both stressed. They're studying upstairs probably.
That's why they're in the public library, right? They're probably to walk
for a Louis V. They probably are so fucking stressed that they have to go
take a shit and smoke, because they don't have the time. It's like they're
models, too. If they were walking runways, they are models. So that means
that this is like the only poop that they have in a long time. I do not,
listen, from what I could tell, what I could see of these guys' feet,
these were not models. Yeah. Well, they're not foot models. Yeah. I bet
they were really skinny, though. No, these were normal guys. I don't think
librarians. Yes,
I love taking those shits that do feel like you're pouring like you're dumping
a bucket.
And it's just when you have it or when you haven't heard it,
I hate to get out of here taken. It is a crazy, it's a crazy of like,
Oh my God, I can go fast.
There's something like that's similar to diarrhea where you're dropping turds,
but it's like that scene in aliens where the alien queen is laying her eggs and
each egg has that layer of slime. You haven't sloppy posit or you don't have a
what anymore. Yeah, exactly. I feel like each turd has like this little, this
go bot that's attached to it, like this little layer of... It has a film. Yeah,
exactly, like each, each turd is wearing a condom and it's sliding out. That is
very, very nice. None of it is nice to me. 'Cause you can just kind of machine
gun those out, and they're not even like tiny rabbit pellets, they're like... And
it's not that they're bad, yeah, they're right, they're simply fast. It's not
that they're bad, they're not foul, they're not so rotten, they're just nice
to do. I wish, no worse than a normal poop. I wish that I could never, like, I
that something happened where it's like I could eat as much food as I want and I never had
to take a shit ever again.
I wish that's what visiting the south is like after having a yankee lifestyle I think.
Yeah?
Yeah I think well I don't know about you guys.
What are you talking about?
Visiting the south eating all that fried food and like barbeque.
I can save it up.
I can save that up.
You can save up your poops.
I can save up fried food for sure.
I constipate myself on purpose every few weeks.
What do you mean save up fried food?
I don't have to get, I get constipated after eating a ton of fried food.
I don't know about you. I don't.
Yeah, me too.
The oil is mixed with my stomach.
We have a seed oil, some kind of...
An allergy.
Allergy to it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just, I get constipated anytime I'm not at home.
That's what I mean.
I think vacation you're gonna...
I built up some kind of natural immune system defense to having to poop when I'm not in my apartment.
Every single time.
You're lucky.
Even if I'm on, even if I'm visiting home from here, I won't shit the entire time.
I have to take a shit right now and I'm not gonna go take a shit because we're recording.
Like you're trying to censor it
Right now
Yeah, what you have a list of talk about we have what you're doing is weird man, what's weird
That's what my stepdad does instead of cussing. Yeah. Yeah, he says what I'm doing stepdaddy moves
That's what the Mormon kid at my school want to
stepdads to talk about being a stepdad. And today the our
clicker is broken, so sorry to the audio listeners, but you're going to have
to hear me say next. Wait, before we go any- should I not talk about the
Christmas podcast you found or? I want to do a full expose on this Christmas
podcast. Because I said that there should be a podcast for stepdads to talk
about being stepdads. And there basically already is one, but it's also about
Christmas. Yeah, well, save it. It's Christmas, but for- Save it for a
months from now that that video you sent me is one of the funniest things I've
ever really good and everyone else is going to have to wait till December.
So Cameron, I'm getting where this is the first ever double list on P. A. I
don't know where you heard that okay. Well, it says we've done plenty of
double list before I didn't make that slide. Jubio made that just now. Oh,
because you don't put the yeah, I don't put titles, so I must have made that
just damn. I'm lying guys. It's the first ever double with let's fucking
your type of double. I don't mean to list one after the other guys. I mean a
double list, and this is on a next please. This is on a website called
wonders list, and you can see here the different
categories on this website. People, animals, travel, most expensive, bizarre,
net worth and Michelin. We should put a net worth section on our that's a
really on your website, yeah, 'cause it's all just like made up information.
Can you hire somebody to calculate your net worth? He's got the biggest net
My net worth is about $500,000 right now due to the properties that I own in New
York City. My net worth is probably... Me and him are both basically negative,
tens of thousands of negative. We are struggling every month. Are you guys
Google-able net worth wise? Can you Google your guys' self-made... Yeah,
let's Google it right now. There's no way. Search Caleb Pitt's net worth.
If it says anything more than minus $50,000, then I'm gonna be so mad. Yeah,
there's no way that my net worth is good at all.
My credit is bad. There's no way you guys are Google-able net worth wise.
no no no no no no no don't look it up on the Adam Friedland show wait Caleb
pits was on the Adam Fried Caleb pits, nineteen seventy five
here we go here. We go Patrick Doran net worth way. Let's go.
One million dollars, Patrick Joseph, Mr Doran owns over fourteen thousand nine
hundred and seventy three units of Synchronos Technologies Inc stock and
over the last fourteen years. Oh my God, look at how this stock has been
dropping. I have been waiting to talk about this for months. This is a
horrible way. Look at that. Grab this has to be about the
this. You need to take this has to be about the Irish rally cross driver that
I share a name with yeah, it's got to be. I guess it would be funnier if it
was you, but it has to be
no, no, no, no, I can't let I can't let people think that I have money.
Yeah, people really thought it's actually fire to be broke. Nowadays,
it's really cool. It's gonna be rolling in the about these hominid networks.
So this is wonders list and I made this slide show a while ago, so I don't
remember what's on it. So next please, so it's a surprise to all of us. So
here it's a double whoa. So we've got two different lists from wonders list
on the left. We have top ten reasons men are better than women by war da
Hajra. What are top ten reasons men are better than women? The debate is
perhaps the most long standing one as men have been trying to prove their
superiority over women since the beginning of time. It gave birth to
masterpieces like men are from Mars and women are from Venus, yet either side
has been unable to prove their point to an absolute extent. What reasons could
men give in favor of their awesomeness? Take a look and then coming in on the
right side, we got ten reasons why women are better than men, also by Ward
Ahasra. This is a truly awesome list and we had a lot of fun compiling it.
The debate about who is better will continue in the long term, but
meanwhile, let's enjoy both the lists of the series compiled listed blow are the
top ten reasons why women are better than I think men already win because it's a
longer pair. Yeah, I say I'm already sensing a by women list says this is a
truly awesome list. These doesn't not say that on the other side. Can we look
up
analyze
I gotta say these thumbnails couldn't be more obvious about you know who's being
prioritized here, at least at the outset. I mean men are having a smiley time with
girlfriends and and I will say that all these people are white and then we have
two black people who are on wrestling
inside
and I feel like one on the right side is a very good optical illusion where
you're supposed to see a lobsters claw.
I think you might be right.
I thought it was a leprechaun drawers. Okay,
sagging leopard and you know what this is just it just goes to show that the
gender of women is all about conflict with men. Okay, gender of men is all
about being here on the beach. Wardah Hajra is a woman
biased,
so let's go next here. Let's check out bias towards men. Reason number ten,
this is a look at how she's actually fucking beautiful as fuck. Look at how
wow, which is the go pro. Whoa, I didn't even know. Did you guys ever use
I jiggle
I
can't say I've used I jiggle
heard of it. I think
all right.
What is
an iPod touch app where you could put a picture of Megan Fox and touch her
O,
and then you
tell a rometer no you are you are you can shake the phone. You can shake the
phone. She would jiggle against her will. She is so sexual,
even the word itself. Each of these let's kind of compare and contrast
these. I think each of these because they even linked the each list on
each other's list. I think you're supposed to take them together. It's
a double list, so we're going to look at each reason and kind of do a
versus here. Okay, so here we have number ten for men. Men think sex
and love are different in today's world. It is very common to have sex
after a few days into the relationship, and yet women would call it
humiliating. If the guy ditched them right after having what he wanted,
man, on the other hand, would never curl up in fetal position and cry for
the blondie who didn't call them the next day after their one night stand and for
women ten women grow
other human beings inside them. Women have the capacity to grow an entire new
person inside of them. Men, on the other hand, make sperms that look like
tadpoles and don't even know which way to go until they accidentally budge into
an egg inside the females body.
That is all the role they play while a woman carries a moving, kicking grown.
I'm going to keep it real. This does not feel band for band. No, this feels like
like this is not an equal. No, we're going to be seeing a lot of stuff like
that. Okay, these lists okay, but it is true that men's sperms don't even know
which way
fucking stupid. I sometimes are the stupidest trying to diss my sperms.
Women make eggs, which are just balls. Yeah, we are there like a tadpole
without the tail. It's like a worse sperm. I don't understand one of these
there's a fact about like the men side. Well, I don't understand what men think.
How is that number ten for why they're better? Because women don't think that
they're different? Because men don't. Because women get obsessed. Okay, so
women get emotional. Women catch feelings. An example is the photo here,
the image, is that they're sharing a Coca-Cola or maybe talking to a small
alien. What the caption should say is the woman in this situation thinks that
she may become pregnant as a result of this interact. This really is just
women are smarter than women is right. Yes, entry and it doesn't even say no.
It just says when men think men
men have an idea of these two things they think about things like this. Yeah,
all right, let's go to number nine here. So number nine men are stronger.
Their upper body is very strong as compared to women, and to be very honest,
even the world seems to be designed along this fact, rather than the delicacy of
women. This is probably why they make the lawn mower string so hard. I've never
even noticed they're hard number nine for women. They can tolerate. They can
tolerate pain, like having a baby push through yourself is not enough. Once
they do it again and yet again, women have a greater tolerance for pain as
they would go on doing all their chores for the whole nine months. Men, on the
other hand, would hide under the sheets if they have flu. So they're saying
doesn't matter how strong men are and how much they hit women with their strong
hands. Women can take it because they can tolerate pain way, way more. If these
are can't even tolerate flu, if these are twin lists,
and they go together, that's what they're saying, what they're saying.
Yeah, what we have right here is just DPS versus tank. Exactly. Women are pure
tanks. They're spongy. Yeah, they're fun. Exactly. Men are DPS. They're this is
but what a demo man yeah man have a forty five.
Women are higher.
Oh yeah, heavy. Well, I guess women can also tolerate fire. There's a theory
that I'd like to show you.
Tolerate fire would be another good. Yeah,
maybe could be they hide under the sheets if they have the flu. God damn on
the other hand, there's a lot of on the other hand, I do have a very low
tolerance for pain and bad feelings and
Yeah, see I you know I like shit pain. Yes, did you pinch me don't pitch me
again? I say uncle when you're a girl, wait Patrick, a woman, he's a girl. No
wait,
I can feel it now because my jacket is heavy. Oh, you got delayed response that
hurt me so bad because I'm so manly and he barely felt the pinch that I did to
him. We do it again.
I didn't even pitch him. That was a test. I did not even pinch him. You know
but I it's I think that maybe I have a can tolerate some pain, but I what I
can't tolerate it's true that I don't think I can tolerate the flu or having a
stomach. No, no, no bubble, definitely the you eat a bad food and it's like you
got shot and use yet. You see me out here every day living my life yeah.
Here's another point for us guys wait, so that means you're a woman yeah,
you can handle the pain.
He's like a woman. You're like
in our favorities
women. Well, I get that from my mom yeah, that's what I get from my mom.
Yeah, for my dad, I get that I really don't like having a stomach ache, but
for my mom I get that I can just take a pepto and go about my day. Men are
always saying uncle when they experience pain right like right or when they're
being tickled. I think nerds are saying that yeah, nurse is saying uncle sure
or boy. There's no such thing as a nerd, yeah,
but women are always saying uncle when they have too much pleasure. They say
I'm not in the mood or stop
I'm saying when a woman is experiencing a lot of pleasure. They go like uncle
oh uncle like that. This definitely needs further research. Yeah
yeah, well, there was going on a diet with too much cupcakes.
What
you're like? Oh, please no more cupcakes, uncle uncle, whereas men will eat an
infinite cupcakes, uncle, maybe that's going to be less. Is that what you're
saying? It would be an infinite cupcake
and
I just feel like women are always wait the infinite cupcake. This is a
paradox here because it's like at the
listen to this here, right of infinite just you you're eating the top part of
the cupcake first and you never have to eat the bottom part.
That's a paradox. Oh, my God,
that's a so which part of the so why even make the bottom part, but do you
need the bottom part to be in? I like the bottom, which part of the cupcake
is female. I don't like those muffins. I don't like the muffin. You like bread.
give me the muffin bottoms. Shut up man, you like bread. I want to eat the
bottoms of the muffins. You've been lying. You can't eat bottoms of muffins.
Yeah, I can know you eat lettuce burgers. How do you all eat your Reese's?
First, I lick off all the chocolate, then I put the peanut butter in the
freezer and I eat it a week later. I wrap it in the paper. I eat
it in the paper. I put the Reese's on the roof of my mouth, all the chocolate,
- Can I hold the peanut butter and I scoop it into the paper
and throw it in the fridge?
- 'Cause sometimes you take the Reese's off the wrapper
and a little bit of chocolate islands are left.
- I ate the paper one time.
- Well, you don't eat the paper,
you put the paper in your mouth to chew it.
I guess with the cupcake wrapper too,
you can put the wrapper in your mouth
to get all the little granules off.
Well, you just chew the wrapper like a Zins.
- Somebody told me in--
- No one cares what I fucking said.
- No, that's what you said was a third grader's opinion.
- I don't know what you said at all.
Put the wrapper in your mouth, chew it like a Zen,
and get all of the cupcake off.
- I knew someone who did that, and I thought it was weird.
- I think that's normal.
- Yeah.
- You spit out the wrapper when you're done.
- Somebody told me that Stride Gum's wrappers
were made out of sugar paper,
and that you should eat the paper on Stride Gum.
- All paper is technically edible.
- You were actually as dumb as a dog growing up.
- No, no, no, this is some,
they told me that they did that
because I asked them why they put
the whole thing in their mouth.
- Did you ever do the thing where you take the foil
off of the Five Gum, and then you rub it
with your fingernail on stuff?
and
You know what you could do is get a cat, right?
Put your tinfoil down on the counter.
If you have a problem with the cat jumping up on the counter
all the time while you're cooking,
it hits the tinfoil, scares the shit out of him.
- I'd yell and hit the cat.
- Yeah, why are you wasting your time doing both?
- I wouldn't waste my tinfoil that I could make into a cube.
- You can, yeah, but then you can have
a tinfoil countertop.
- I do that all the time when I make fish.
- Well, buddy.
Buddy, buddy, let me tell you.
- I don't even need a cat for that.
- Oh, you know how when you take the cat
off of the tin foil.
Sorry, when you take the fish off of the cat is stuck in the tin foil. When you
take the fish off the tin foil, a little fish is left behind.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you put the tin foil in your mouth to get all the fish off
right. When you put the same in on the way for it to connects to it. That's
right, you put the tin foil in your mouth, you chew it, you get all the
salmon. What I do is I make it in Papillon. Is it wrong to eat butterfly
style? It's one of the okay things that you can chew on. Is it wrong that you
have you with your body? Yeah, that means you got pica. It means you have a
deficiency of some, but I don't love it, but like I've done right. If you love it,
it's a do you have metal fillings if you're well listen, if you're, if you're
addicted to it, it can be bad, but it's bad if you're addicted to it. It's fine
once in moderation. Okay, number eight, let's go to number eight here before we
have I have metal fillings. At one time, I bit a piece of tin foil and I felt a
surge in my mouth of electricity. That's a lie. That's false. You just had you
just pain. Just told a kevin gate story. You said I had a surge in my mouth of
electricity. I had a surge in my mouth.
Number eight for men, the knowledge of tools
can read instructions and decipher them easily. It is a part of their innate
nature to understand the mechanics of how things work, which is why they have
D I projects at home that women can't do. Women have way more D I y number
eight that's because you are a lazy bastard. I know number eight is
multitasking for when you dare women can reply to tools. Women can reply to
emails on the smartphones cook, watch over the baby and listen to TV news at
the same time men see also best jobs for women. Okay, so here's here's an
obvious example of men having a greater knowledge of tools, tools than men or
women. Rather think about think about how many sex toys men have access to how
many little shapes and sizes and and it's just a whole no because there's the
double sided all men have as a whole. What tool wise for their to have a sex
toy is a whole. I don't think you're saying that men have more sex toys than
women. No, they don't. I think I disagree. Okay, so think about this. I want you
to think about this. Women have different stuff. Think about a flesh,
think about a flesh light. That's the, that's the, you know, the, the, we're,
this is the, the burial ground of, of, of sex toys, right? That's all you need.
That's one hole. Yeah. Then you get the double-sided fleshlight, right?
Two holes. Yeah, then you even have a fleshlight that has a mouth on one side
and a pussy on the other, right? That's still a hole. That's just holes.
Yeah, okay. So I want you to talk to me... You're just describing holes.
Women have... They have a dildo and they have a vibrator. No, but then they...
They have a dildo and they have a vibrator. They also have... They have a dildo
and they have a vibrator. They have two... Those are two things. Those are two operators.
Okay, well there's... Men have different variations on a hole. I'm sorry, but a
Men can also use a dildo on their anus.
But so can a woman.
So women have three--
But that doesn't make it a new dildo.
That doesn't make it a new dildo.
No, no, no, no.
But women have three axes of pleasure.
Men have two.
Because they have the vaginal cavity, the clitoris,
and the ass.
I'm going to own you.
What about a ball clamp?
Has everybody ever developed a sex toy for both that
plays with your nipples?
And women have that, too.
Women have nipples that feel something.
Yeah, men have nipple clamps.
Women have nipple clamps.
But they're not as good.
just use that woman, though, is sitting and watching porn, also with the nipple
clamps only and also women like women like sucking dildos off, too, and got no
guy. I've never seen a guy do that. Guys like fingering flesh lights. Yeah, well,
but again, again, all male sex toys are variations on a whole just get buying a
flesh like or look at or even then, even then, fuck they're using a different
eye. Get men don't always just need a whole. I feel like you know a body pillow
isn't a hole. It's just an in body pillows going to have a hole in it.
Eventually, I don't think you know how a body
into the stitching buddy. That's a sex toy. It can be if you put a hole in
okay. So this is the perfect talk about my new favorite video. Have you guys
all watch this video yet? The washing the guy fucking the washers. I watch
this video about a thousand times. Everybody should go up. We have to watch
it and by the way, a man can use a vibrator. A man can use a vibrator, a
wild on what appears man can use anything a woman can use plus here's
Pierce you're getting you're getting hung up on this. You say we're going to
go on
a right. We're going to go on x dot com and we're going. What are you doing?
That's a pretty good try.
That's a pretty good try. It's going to go on x right now. We're going to watch
a video of a guy fucking a washing machine and we're going to listen to the
sound of the video.
Do you have it on your Twitter on your X? You have to put an under you have to put
the underscore. Why don't you just go on X? Oh, there it is.
Okay, now play this video. Oh yeah, you're barely allowed to look at Twitter
X. Now, what the hell if you're not logged in, if you're not logged in memes,
I've made in the past look and it even has all three of the
Twitter. I have associated on the side. I have my fucking hottest memes going.
Look at that. You might like the three accounts associated with the show.
I'll just play this video. Just play it into the audio machine.
Yeah, put it on the GoPro. That's good.
And it's dark.
[VIDEO PLAYBACK]
- Did you spit in it, Buzz?
- A lot.
[LAUGHTER]
- What was about?
- Mama.
- Well, what the fuck is you in here doing?
- Washing my clothes, Mama.
- Washing your clothes?
- You know what I was doing.
I was washing my clothes.
- Looks to me like you was trying to get your dick wetter
than your clothes.
- Mama, not today, all right?
Don't do that to me right now, all right?
[LAUGHTER]
- Well, did you put on some aluminum foil
you know,
Mama Mama not not today day do this to be right
when he says you know what I was doing washing my
funny is
he's got a condom hanging out of his but
why did you put a condom in your? I don't know
that way you don't have to clean the dildo
dryer. There is not even like you have to clean a dildo. It's just going back
to your ass putting anything
who cares about shit on it's going back. That is the funniest video. He's not
even like humping the crack of the the wash. I think any any actor in the
world is jealous of that line rate of not today. Mama don't do this to me
right now. He's just hunching over to hide his boner. I think he is doing.
I think it's completely fake. I think it's also a bad mom. I think it's a
fake video. It's definitely the most horrible thing of all time. If it's
really definitely a bad peer abuse. I think the thing that makes me think it's
so abused that he thinks a washer dryer is a sexual. The thing that makes me
think it's fake is there's no possible way to derive any sexual pleasure at all
from fucking that dryer. He is rubbing his dick against the hard metal corner.
hold on now the way he's doing it. You watch that video again. You tell me
that doesn't
painful
good ever. She had some people that makes me think is fake is that her lines
are too good. Yeah, they're too funny. Yeah, he might be a seno bite
could be
maybe he's been so abused that he likes pain. He exactly he's a seno bite
pleasure. He's number seven for men is manner solution oriented men tend to
move towards the solution of the problem. Instead of spending three hours
crying, seven days worrying and three weeks talking about it to friends,
parents and other people around them, there might immediately comes up with
twelve solutions without thinking that it might be an insult to how they're
feeling right now. Twelve solutions seems like a waste of energy, but yeah
yeah that is a brain or seven female brain has better healing ability. Let's
say if both a man and woman met an accident at the same time, a woman would
be up doing her daily tasks even before the man opens his eyes. That is because
the females neurons are inter linked, while the brain of a man is
compartmentalized wow
yeah. I like that again. This is DPS versus ten yeah, yeah, healing abilities.
I'm actually I'm actually thinking that this could be a whole. These are kind of
both. This is DPS versus tank because the healing ability that's sandwich yeah,
and then this is ADC and support yeah easy. Why is the woman on the table
sexual style that speaks to what we're about to get into. I imagine as we get
into the top five number six less complicated relationships for men,
because men don't give a damn about what others think of them. They don't worry
about what they think of others either. A group of male friends can go out every
weekend without worrying what the other person was wearing. This cool attitude
comes naturally and makes things less complicating, including fashion
communication experts for women. Women can talk to anyone anywhere. They know
how to socialize with the bus driver, the teacher of their kids, the cleaner,
the sales person or anyone sitting with them in the bus advances in human life
are because of communication and we owe that to women. I think
I mean this is a perfect example of men having not complicated. I look at us
three and there's a guy who just went to the bathroom and we're touching each
other. We just go to the bathroom all the time. We should start going to the
bathroom together like girls. I does that shit make you jealous or what when
they say we're us ten are going to go to the bathroom and I say can I never
mind. I would say that you guys and I are maybe like you know two months out
of me asking to piss in the sink with you while you guys use the toilet. I
mean I like doing that when it's like you think that we could reach the point
of penis from penis friends. This is a probably cross. So I guess I'm not
gonna. We're definitely penis friends. It just haven't hasn't happened with him.
I think that the central tension of our friendship for years on end is that we
are on the precipice for a penis friends. I don't think so. I think we're
basically everybody's been a friend all but we're all but penis friends.
Everybody's seen my penis. I haven't seen your head really, and I but I
imagine that your penis looks identical. I think you never showed it to me
because you're afraid I'd like it too much. It definitely
just takes you a Caleb just thinking about
talking about how we have a lack in our house because okay, all your friends
from back home have seen your penis yeah, no
okay, so you should go back home figure that out and come back and join us,
but I've seen your penis yeah, and you guys have all seen my penis. I don't
know if you have that's what we were saying is Pierce might be the only one
where we haven't seen his penis and he hasn't seen ours. I don't think anyone
seen my and pat have seen each other's penises. Why double digit time because
they were the most just like you guys show stuff showers. It's funny. You guys
like to show it's funny to it's funny to show your male friend your penis. I
it's not funny to show a person you don't know your penis. It's also not
funny to show that you like now you're not who you like, but if somebody
doesn't know you at all, and they see your that's a little bit. That's the
most romantic thing though yeah.
that is romantic. That is like showing someone a candle down girl. I'm going
to show it to you. I'm going to show you it
open your eyes girl
look.
It does
there it is baby. What do women think of penises? I look at my penis and every
time I see my own penis in the mirror. I feel like a woman who's being subject
Oh, my God, I don't want to see mine. Oh, my God, I know that mine's nothing
special. I'm tiny. I'm a tiny man. I got these little wrists. I got a tiny
head. I got a big belly and I do just have the
penis of a normal human being. I look like, you know, that picture of that
orangutan. A normal, that's what I have too. Is that the normal size? Is that
the monkey that I'm thinking of? The orange monkey that's got a big gut and
his dick's out? You know that one? Yeah, that's an orangutan. Are you talking
know when he fucks a woman's hand? No, no, no,
I'm talking about that photo of just like the monkey standing. Oh, he's
always
he's not peeing, but he's just got his dick out. Well, I've seen all types of
monkeys penises in every possible context, so I'm sorry that I kind of
there's a very famous image of an orangutan standing in a field. I know
which one you're talking about.
He's just bragging about how many images of monkey penises he's seen. I'm not
bragging, it's honestly a curse on my personal life. You're bragging, you're
I get into a lot of trouble with a lot of people over how many different photos I
try to bring up and videos of
and monkeys.
Humble brag, I watch videos of monkeys, fucking humans.
The appeal and opposite gender is visual, while many men will not admit
that their attraction to the opposite gender is based on the looks of most of
the times. If they will just look at the person and decide whether they want to
hate her or not. Women, on the other hand, will be unsure of this even after three years
of knowing the person because they tend to find marriage material in each guy.
Women like every guy is what it's saying here, I guess.
And on the other side, women can get things done.
Well, wait, that's the thing for men is that that's a positive for men they're saying.
Yeah, that's good.
Every single positive that they list for men just makes men sound like the most manipulative
people in the world.
This is like the best thing about being a man.
Welcome to Earth.
Maybe it's different on Mars or Venus, but here we have a system that I don't like very
much.
Yeah.
It sounds very patriarchal.
Yeah, where's the thing about men being warriors?
Yeah.
Well, that was tools.
Well, look at them in the back.
They have an army.
If men don't find anything interesting, they will not do it.
Likewise, they will not do anything, again, if they aren't encouraged and appreciated
the first time, even if it is something like washing dishes. Women, on the other
hand, will get things done when they have to. I do not fuck with the dishes.
Dude, I fuck with the dishes. I love the dishes. My wife takes three days to do
four dishes. I know. I have a one day, other day switch off situation. Each day,
other day. I love it. I'll do them all the time. I walk up to the dishes and my
girlfriend will say, "I'll do them. I'll do the dishes." I listen to music. I get
my cue right. I shuffle my playlists with all my songs. I take out the songs I
I don't want. Wow. What I do is if I cook. I was talking. Sorry Pierce.
Everybody clear the air. I was talking. I was complaining about my woman.
It's time to eat. Thank you. So I was about to you know do the dishes let's
say and my girlfriend says no I'll do them. She goes up to the sink. She puts
on the rubber gloves as if that's even necessary. I always cringe when ladies
put on the rubber gloves. You don't need that. And then she says okay I'm gonna
start washing and then she turns on the water and then the dishes that are dry
that are sitting on the drying rack, she doesn't-,
she doesn't move the dishes from the drying rack back to where the dishes
live, and I'm like, 'That means you're only gonna be able to wash three,' and
she says, 'I only feel like washing three, so that's perfect.' You wash them
all every time. When you wash them, you wash them all. You have to wash them
all. It's gotta be empty. It's gotta be empty. Just clear the-, clear the dry
dishes. And then listen, you scrub the sink down. Yeah. Oh, that I actually
- I don't agree with that.
- That I actually don't agree with.
- Well, how could you not agree with that?
- My chicken's washing in there.
- Why would you not agree with scrubbing the sink?
- I'm washing my chicken in the sink already.
- 'Cause it's a sink, it's gonna be dirty.
- But I scrub it.
- It's already dirty.
- Why not have it clean?
- That's crazy.
- The dishes are what you're supposed to make and clean.
- You clean the sink.
- The sink will smell.
- Why not, it takes it one second.
- When the sink smells, you can clean it,
but it's not gonna stay dirty.
- You clean it when it smells.
- No.
- You clean it every time that you think about doing it.
think about this is a all right. I think what you have is a system where you do
the dishes every other night with your significant other and you know that
you're the one who likes washing the sink and the other person is the one who
doesn't. So you know the sink gets cleaned every other day. I would love to
wash the sink, but the dishes I don't like. Right, so you can't wash the sink
if you don't do the dishes. Number four, programming electronics. That's men's.
Men and boys could program their VCRs and tape recorders in the 1970s when
something went wrong. The same applies to gadgets and electronic devices in
today's time. Apparently, these skills are in born and just magically appear in
every generation born and then what is that? Look at the TV. They're watching
one of my favorite shows.
Number four is women have super powers that get things done. The utility boy
will leave the power on the policeman will let the woman off without charging
a ticket and she will get her way around any problem. The super power is tears.
The super power is using sex. It's sexuality and showing the boobs, showing
showing the boobs through the closing. I will say that tears hit different when
she got boobs.
True.
That's real shit. Stop going ahead. I'll say next when I want it. We're gonna
talk about both of these for ten more minutes. No, I don't wanna talk about
these. Okay, let's go to number three.
For men, less time getting ready to go out. I know that's real. That's some
pastry Garfield right there. That's real as fuck. That is one point that we
would definitely give them points on. They don't need makeup, hair styling,
and they don't need hours to decide what to wear. Honestly, who notices for
women detail oriented women can categorize things like task lists,
birthdays, shopping lists, assignments and whole calendars in their brains,
while remembering smaller details like what their boyfriend likes for dinners
and other basic facts that is downright impossible for men.
Yeah, I take basically one second to go out and I just go on to my undies.
that's the the big division with my my wife is that I am early to everything
and she is late to everything. You're not early to everything. I'm really
everything you're early to everything important right yeah yeah everything
that doesn't involve me and Patrick. Well, that's because your time is not
valued by me and your shirt says mad balls. You left the house wearing that
shit. Get this guys. This is my wife's shirt and she wouldn't let me wear it
for months because she was like I like that shirt so much. Your wife likes mad
balls. It says ball. That's what I was thinking. I was like, why are you so
mad balls? Why are you so protective of this balls? You're in your PJs right now
to be honest. You are in my girlfriend's clothes. What a t shirt. What are you in
your girlfriend's clothes? You're in PJs. How am I in PJs? It's a PJs. That's
crazy. A t shirt. Yeah,
we're having two separate things. Yeah, moving on fits in his girlfriend's
clothes is what he said. Well, her shirts. I don't wear her. I can fit in
my girlfriend's clothes. If I'd reconstitute them and rip them apart and
- I get mad at him if I read. - If I put on one of my girlfriend's shirts,
it would rip almost instantly.
- Strength. - My girlfriend is so much smaller than me.
- Superman, stop man, you're kind of freaking me out.
- There is something so sexual about a man bursting out of his clothes.
Don't you guys think?
- I do want to ask her if there's anything she's getting rid of so that I
can put it on just to do this and just feel strong for once in my life, like Hulk.
- How bad would you feel if you tried to do that and you just hurt your arms?
(laughter)
maybe get it in front of her. Oh, you're throwing this out. Watch this. I'm
just doing that doing that, but then I like I'm not going to admit that I hurt
my arms. One second, one second, just unattractive to women when you throw
your back out. Yes,
and if you hurt yourself, that sucks. If you ever stub your toe, this is what
you should do. You say I didn't still my tell
number two. Wait, can I just ask your friends real quick lady fans? What is
more attractive when a man peels off his shirt like this and then kind of drops
it and then you know he just did that gaily yeah right okay. Well, so
someone did that right.
Someone did that straightly
when he feels like a shirt or just pop out of
do you mean rip out of it or you mean pop out of it as a different thing.
like you go like this, you go like this and then you're next to all your
clothes falling in a pile next to you. You get raptured out of your clothes.
You're a night crawler bamfed out of your clothes.
Like you have clothes that are on you with suction cups. No, like there's a
tear and you flex your bicep and then your bicep pops out of that. I don't
think a single person has ever done that. That necessitates having a very
tiny shirt on for anybody. Right, well that's what I mean.
What is it more sexy? Okay, you peel off a tiny question. If you're a woman,
leave a comment down below, address it to pierce a dear pierce
right. What you think is sexy about a boy taking off his shirt or whatever,
however way
pops out the question. The question is so your question is women. Do you think
it's sexier when a man takes off his shirt
is close?
Do you think
a man
we can boil this down. His shirt off women. Do you like it when a man pops
out pops out or do you like it? I'm a man out at you or slides slides or pops.
Do you like it when a man slides on you sliding or sliding or pop dear pierce?
I like sliding dear pierce. I like pop. This is a new column. This is a new
column for the show. Dear pierce, because all men all men have this relationship.
My boyfriend has been taking his shirt. He's been sliding.
how do I get him to pop? All men have the sliding and popping dynamic that they do
in their daily lives right you're sliding until you meet the right person
and then you pop all over. I can pop a shoe off. Oh, I've cut my shoe off for
sure yeah, yeah, so I can put my slide. They slide each lace together in a
delicate knot. I just pop them on right my shoe laces yeah, okay number two
for men making babies is easy for them for men. The whole process of becoming a
father involves three minutes of their time three minutes on the other hand
that's a bit that's a is the ladies who have to face nine months of trouble for
the baby to come into this world. So making babies is easier for men versus
let's compare these two for women. Women live longer. Women are stronger than
men when it comes to nerves, which is probably why they live on average a year
a whole year longer than men. Women are also better decision makers regarding
their diet duties. Here's the problem I have at this women don't understand that
men, the difference between how men experience time and a women experience
time is like us and like mosquitoes three minutes to us having sex trying to
think of our grandma. So we don't come is so much longer than nine months to a
woman right yeah and here's here's what I'd like to introduce here to if we were
comparing these two. So sure women live a year longer, but about
ninety months of their life are going to be taken up by being pregnant yeah yeah,
so you're actually losing them yeah exactly you're losing like a by the
way, if you're pregnant, you might as well not even be a lot. Why do we count
that yeah pregnant? It should be in a birthday. I agree. You shouldn't have a
birthday. You should know wait. It's sharing a life with someone else
literally, so it should just be halved well and you just can't do anything. Oh
my God, except eat pickles,
pick up and tuna fish. Pregnant women literally will skip roller coaster rides
pickles. What the hell's wrong with them? I know. You know what my mom used to do when
she was pregnant with me? My mom was pregnant with me. Allegedly. She would get mayo and
pickles on Italian meatball subs. Why do they like pickles so much? The pregnancy craving
that she had was marinara sauce, meatball, mayo, pickles, and she still orders it to
to this day and it's the most disgusting thing I've ever seen. I was pregnant.
It's different when it's not coming through the amniotic sack. I was
pregnant. I know that my simple ass would be craving PB and J yeah every
single do you guys ever read the stuff that Elvis ate and maybe he was
pregnant. Elvis was pregnant. That's why he ate a fool's gold sandwich. He would
eat bacon and peanut butter. Yeah, which that's really good. If you've never had
it made me have that that's really good. It's really, really Elvis. My mom made
we have that, and I like you always put chocolate on it too, but no okay, no
the thing that was fucked up that he did was he like it was like a hollowed out
he ate some messed up. It was a whole a whole loaf of bread covered in bacon and
peanut butter. He stole a fourteen year old girl from her parents really and all
of black,
Priscilla, yeah, apparently that hasn't been proven yet. Okay, so
we're going to move to the final entry on this list number one for men. Men are
not social chameleon. A woman can change herself according to any gathering
within a few seconds, like a cult. Men are somewhat consistent and persistent
in their opinions and feelings regarding anything, and for women number one
psychic powers. Not only can women tell why their baby is crying, they can also
be absolutely sure if their husband is cheating or their friend is having a
problem. She will already have figured you out, so there is no point to lying
about it. A woman has strong intuition. A husband is cheating is in blue, so
There's a bunch of links here.
Is there like a thing for top ten ways to find out if a husband is cheating?
Probably.
I don't know.
Oh my god.
There's a bunch of stuff on this website.
I'm going to look at that and apply it to my own life.
We'll go back to saying funny stuff immediately, but I just want listeners to know, look, this
website is hetero.
It's not trans positive, this website.
This list, it's very cis-promotive, you know?
Plus, it's also like I'm totally a social chameleon. Yeah, right. I am a
woman. No, it makes me a psychopath. Yes, no,
I like girls put makeup on me and I just want I just want the women of the
world to know that your motherness does not
impact your expression of femininity at all. I mean, all these are disgusting
and
machine sure it does. It makes you annoying. I think your maternal instincts
just make you annoying because you want me to clean my room. You want me to do
my homework and what's more important to me than mothering a child is like
brothering a child, being mother and the sense of you ate right.
What's more important is that I serve cunt exactly. I'm trying to serve as
much cunt as in my life. I'm cunt doesn't matter. It's metaphorically
cunt doesn't matter to you. No, it's about it doesn't matter to me at all.
It's about did mother eat yeah
Okay, you guys ever try to feed your grandma. No, my grandma died a couple
weeks, one of the most horrible experiences. Well, she was you go to
you go to the you go to whatever you go to whatever, like horrible, maybe on a
paid episode,
you go to whatever situation your grandma's in and you feed her and then
she eats like four or five bites. It really is like grandma. You thought you
ate right like
like
Grandma will take three or four bites and say, "Mm."
Grandma, you thought you ate.
You left so much on your plate.
You left so many crumbs, Grandma.
Meanwhile, she doesn't know what the hell going on.
Grandma, the waiter served you meal.
Yeah.
Grandma, the waiter served.
You need to eat, Grandma.
Grandma, the waiter served you meal, but you didn't eat.
Yeah, but the craziest part-
The waiter served you meal, and you said it tasted like cunt.
Oh, my God.
The craziest part about Grandma eating is that she actually thought that she ate.
She actually-
That's how far gone she is.
I literally thought she had two or three bites of a piece of fish. She even
said it takes like and she said this. She said she said I mother and you say
no, your grandma, your mother to somebody, but you thought you ate. You
left crumbs grandma, your son downing grandma, the fish is breaded. There's
plenty of crumb yeah and I wish you were crumb downing. I wish you were
downing those crumbs.
This fish tastes like
that's disgusting. All right, there's one more slide here, which is what got
recommended to me after I viewed these lists. This is the final slide here.
You may also like ten countries with most
this was the recommendation on both of these lists.
I bet the number one is what
America. I was going to say I was going to say as a slave, the kingdom of evil
yep, I'm going to be my guess for number one. Well, that's a pretty good
guest to but I'll go. I'll stay with America for now. Leave world, probably
slave topia
okay, okay, well like this guy, if you like if you like these three guys
podcast about list, and if you also like
no, if you like slave topia kill yourself, if you like slave topia get
the fuck out. If you also like home planet, Alex Forest and Joe Gleason well
buddy, I have good news for you. We're doing a sketch show at little field
over to
and they will be amazing.
And it will be basically having been
podcast about this
podcast about this is only a distraction from sketch comedy, which is all of our
passions. All of our
study still has about list. I've done it since I was a kid. Yeah, we've done and
listen. If you even if you like to get to come in, you're coming to the show
because at first I can't imagine any other possible, which if you want to go
to swag poop dot com shows. If you want to get tickets for October twentieth,
but you should also check out pierces whatever video he did
there's some fucking reddit, but outer years.
Oh, I thought we were talking about a different one. You just take a matrix
power point and a
power point dinosaur in a corner outer space and station infinite jost infinite
ghost co written by Jordan bold, this even more important than that is the
sketch show come to the sketch.
If you came to the last one, which I know you did and you had an amazing
time, by the way, I saw your faces are not repeating anything besides one or
two or five things. I'm lying. It's all new. It's completely new new videos,
new sketches, and it's all Halloween themed except for the stuff that isn't.
We have video proof of you enjoying the show. We have a full video of the show,
the whole show. If you were at the last show and you're not at the new one,
we have a video of you at the last show. We're gonna be comparing faces and I
know, I know a couple of people in the crowd. I know a couple of you 'cause
I know some of you are my friends. If you don't show up to the next
one, I know where you live. Hold on, Pierce is holding his finger. The
reason none of us can legally drive right now
because we are celebrating a long day's work of sketch writing. Oh, each of
us came in here into this office, and Caleb will tell you. We were here
and we were working up until just now to write
maybe 10, 11 sketches. - We were writing
so many sketches. - And honestly,
the 10, 11 sketches that we wrote today,
not one of them is gonna make it to--
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no. - These were trash.
This was getting filled up. - No, no, no, no, no.
- Not one. - Because we do this shit,
it's every day, bro. - Yeah.
- It's every fucking day, bro.
It doesn't matter.
If we write 10 sketches in a day,
we're gonna write 10 better ones tomorrow.
And they're all gonna be in the show
unless there's another day before the show,
in which case those ones--
- Or the ones that are gonna be on the show.
- We ever sketch the day before the show,
and we come out only hitting home runs.
- Right.
- My laney.
- All right, bye everybody.
- Oh, we do have a video of the show,
but I have to pay the origination fee.
- Not coming out.
- It's not gonna come out. - Not coming out.
Bad audio, doesn't matter.
Bye everybody. - Bye everybody.
(static)
- But that's the thing about those labels,
like the excessive,
if they were to do the cigarette type things,
The only warning that they could give on like Doritos and stuff is like, you will become
fat.
No, you know what they do is they just have to show a guy who's going like, "Ugh!"
You'll have a stomach ache warning.
It would also need to be controlled.
You'd need to have like an FDA guy who just eats Doritos and is like, "Ugh!"
How many Doritos can I snap a picture, put it on the bag?
I guess the other, so it's either stomach ache guy on the picture on the label, or you
You can have a guy who is too spicy, he's crying, he's tearing up, his nose is dripping.
These labels would look amazing too.
Or a little piece of Doritos stuck in the roof of your mouth.
Yeah, stuck in the tooth.
I guess the only two warnings you could have, the only two or three is that and dental warning
on a bag of smart food.
Yeah, dental warning.
It will get stuck in your tooth and it will be annoying.
But then you have to put that on lettuce too.
Yeah, you got to put down lettuce and kale and all that stuff.
They should put warnings of everything that can happen with food on every food.
They need warnings on every food.
There should be a warning on popsicles that say, "Once you're done with this, brain freeze,
but once you're done with this, buddy, you're going to laugh."
Yeah, laughing.
You're going to laugh.
Yeah, that's the guy like...
Pointing at the stick.
Holding his head, holding his head and his leg.
Yeah, yeah.
Is this guy having a heart attack?
Yeah, we can't tell, but then at the bottom it says, "You're going to get a brain freeze
and you're going to laugh so hard."
this to cover every possible side effect. Yeah, brain freeze, maybe else out
stained hand, stain, good sticky hand, stained hand, laughing at the thing,
brain freeze and then also you bit into it. So your teeth are cold,
splinters splinter from the stick,
it's like a man going through.
We're actually returning
to be a Google right now wound man. The only wounds you can get are just
something stabbing you yeah right.
I think it might be his feet are fucked up.
Dude, we need to create the modern Wound Man.
We just did.
We did, but he's the food man.
But we need to create the modern Wound Man.
The Foond Man.
(monkey screeching)