Yeah, yeah, you you put this down. Well, you dropped your phone at the same time as the
clap again, bitch. There we go. And another clap for Christmas, y'all. Try sinking that
slow clap for Christmas as disrespectful man. Slow clap is more respectful and
fast clap. No, it's not.
Sarcasm. No slow clap dude. No slow slow clap is sarcasm. So clap is no that's
because you guys are irony poison. No, it's like this like
you know that's well done. Well, yeah, if you say well done, well done and it
well, but that's that's an as our live well die. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, a slow clap. As you do something, you think, oh my God, I fucked up. I
love I took the L no, and we hear one guy. You hear one guy near the back
yeah, but it has to rise stands up. If it turns into rupturous applause, then
it is not sarcastic, but if it is the okay, say this, say you know listen,
we're we're saying that with medians right, so imagine you're up there and
you say clap it up. If you all like movies and one guy and one guy just
like this,
you're doing a sarcastic face. I don't know
all you're doing all situations. Obviously it's not sarcastic. When you
say when we say a slow clap for Christmas, it's a respectful like God.
I can't even believe it. I'm a suit and tie. So tell me this business. You
mentioned the Grinch
and would if you said clap it up for Christmas, who in this place likes
Christmas. Do you think the Grinch would the normal clap or a
little anything would definitely
a slow clap? He would slow clap no, he would first of all, first of all, he
would not. First of all, nobody be able to tell he was slow clapping because
he'd say clap for Christmas. Everybody in the room was going nuts. Also, you
can hear his claps anyway, because the hands are made of her. He wouldn't
clap. Why would he would boo dude? He wouldn't slow clap. What are you
talking about? Depends on which a great at all depends on which part of the
movie you're at man.
that's true. I guess we liked Christmas. He might slow clap, so I made my point
yeah. I guess
what is that drink you're drinking? It smells
it smells of stinking perps perps. I don't know. I pick this is a fuck is
perps very super fruit organic energy. There's no GMO, no preservatives, no
glucose. It sounds pretty good. If they want no soy, if they want to give us a
Christmas gift perps perps yeah, I guess I have a picture of legs on. I does it
I make you run okay, make you run fast. I guess I don't know check it out. It's
just a new energy thing. I'm trying. Oh, it's vegan. Oh, I see it's Kido
friendly. I seem pipe to fuck up off this perps. I wish I got a kid smells
crazy. I was like I can smell this okay and I'm I'm recovering from illness, so
I can't smell anything. I can smell the can. There's a little drop. There's a
little drop that's about to hit the thing. It's coming. It's coming out of
the can and getting to my nose. I think I was a taste like shit so bad from the
earth.
Perps unites nature and science to promote your life's health. We don't
make excuses. We do not jeopardize our standards. There we go man. See that is
some Christmas shit yeah, and you know what I was at the right to drink one
serving per day.
It has directions on the drink
directions, drink one serving per day, serve cold. Also
it says servings per container and then no number. I like that just says
servings per container, nothing else. Wow, I got it for myself as a little
Christmas gift. I'm so this I honestly guys last week we flopped on the first
week of Christmas because I couldn't get it done right because of extenuating
circumstances. So I mean can I just can I just say that a point I need to I
I need to come clean right now. I need to tell you guys that this past week I was
going through hell. I was being tortured. Yeah, I was being slaughtered alive,
okay, and I was staring the grim reaper in the face every second of my life.
When you looked at I grabbed him by the neck, I ripped his damn head off, oh
shit, and I put my fingers up as well. I didn't do that. I didn't do that, but
your fingers up his bones, but guys, I see it's not sarcastic or if you think
get sarcastic. Maybe you're so rude to me about this about my suffering man. I'm
trying to tell you is that God tried to strike me down before Christmas. He
tried to show me a reality where Christmas could be ruined by the
weakness of the flesh you got by the spoilage of the body, but my spirit rose
up and I literally returned to one hundred thousand percent strength after
recording and we're recording much a back of episodes. We're doing them on a
row, but the one we recorded yesterday, where I put the last was looking out.
I was very sick where I was very sick and my brain was addled yeah. We're we're
twenty four hours after that, maybe a magic and I'm I'm operating at one
hundred and fifty percent. He looks like Christian. You know what friendship has
restored me and my soul is thrumming. You know what like shit you sounded like
shit. I couldn't keep it together. You were still a basically and now I have
nothing but positivity, even the face of people being strangely weird to me right
you know I'm just clapping don't even you were you were talking about that more
than the club. I say I said that you I said okay before this before this you
looked sounded and acted like a pile of crap, but look at you now you were
visited by the ghost of sickness present. I became the ghost of Christmas
wow. I left my body. I got taken on a journey. You got turned into a scrooge
by sickness and then you had a miraculous turnaround. That's a I'd say
less of a scrooge, maybe more of a tiny tim you got turned in a tiny town
turned into
unfortunately, and then you were saved by that's that's one of the morals of a
Christmas Carol is that tiny tim is supposed to be the character you do.
Does tiny tim you're not supposed to ruin ruins Christmas? Yeah, he does
really for him at all. No, of course, not imagine him to get better, but what
if you what if you went over to your your family, you visit your family for
Christmas, you get you get there when your family was like
yeah great now Christmas isn't about Santa up bitch. I want to open up my
remote control. It's about on that's leg. Only business is now about on
Jeanette's leg. Yeah, yeah, exactly. If you go to your Christmas in America and
you have one cousin who's an eight year old British boy who's sick all the time
and has tiny legs, do that fuck out of here. Tim flick him over ruining
Christmas fucks me up. Does tiny Tim get cured at the end of that? Maybe no, he
he just gets a goose. Yeah, he's what is going to kill him for a goose. He's
still going to die goose or whatever that's a doose. He has some kind of he
has polio or
just goes to show you the strength of capitalism. That's what it's all about.
That is true as fuck man yeah, and that's what's kind of disgusting to me
about this Christmas season. I don't want more than anybody. It's about
people wanting to be out for other people. Christmas is about toys and it's
about capitalism going to the mall for me. It's more about snow and only and
this is a point I wanted to make. I it's no this morning. I literally am so
excited about Christmas and so ready for this to be the first day of Christmas,
and then I walk outside to go get the decorations to decorate the set and you
guys did a great job. It started snowing. Thank you. It looks incredible.
It looks so festive. It looks amazingly festive and I'm going to put this tree
right in front of Patrick and I put it in front of you. It was in front of you.
you got fucking owned. You see my bow. I tied doesn't look is looks amazing,
really festive and beautiful. The tree isn't too big. This is the perfect spot
for it. Okay, if you want to have it that close to you, I look so festive.
You look amazingly cute. I'm not going to fucking lie. Look at me and Cameron
next to the tree and guys. When I woke up this morning, I stunk you stunk bad
stunk worse than I stunk in my entire life. You take a shower yeah. I showered
so it's cured and that's what I'm saying. I've literally been born again. This is
my shower this morning. I was in the shower all I could think about you know
your typical shower thoughts. You think what happens after we die? What happens
after we eat in inside of our body with the digestive system, this type of
thought scientific thoughts, this shower thought my only thought I could think
hallelujah. That's not a Christmas song, though
maybe not for you on earth. It's about yeah. What on heaven on earth?
Huh I'm sorry. I got distracted by Christmas is about Jesus Christ. Yeah,
Christmas is about Hallelujah is not about it's about some kind of
manger in Bethlehem. New cord I'm well. First of all, I are you thinking of a
different Hallelujah, because you were singing it just like Leonard Cohen's.
I'm singing that I'm singing it not because I was the shower didn't make me
think of Christmas. It made me be clean and think Hallelujah. I would have been
better if I shower made you think of Christmas.
Why? Because it's festive.
It would have made I think you were paying attention. You're just saying
but I got a strange thing. I got distracted by an ornament. The tree is
gonna come over here so that you can't touch it and be distracted by it anymore.
Got distracted by an ornament. That's okay.
We have so many amazing things planned for Christmas. I feel like that's
obvious. You know us. We have
10... How many episodes was in four weeks? Four? Eight. Eight amazing
Christmas episodes planned for you. The eight days of Christmas, the four weeks
weeks of Christmas. The deck, the set is on the four weeks of Christmas. My
the
give to me one episode, another episode, yeah episodes, four episodes, five
episodes, six episodes,
and a premium on the pay tree. Wow on on
on pay tree on there we go. So today we have done a complete
We stole a sack. I guess it'd be a crime actually, right? We did a crime.
We found it. Okay, we found it, allegedly. We found a sack of letters and I think
the bag said to the North Pole. The bag said directly to the North Pole
and it had a label on it. We're not gonna give the address out to the North Pole.
One Santas Lane. Come on, man. You can't dox. That is actually illegal. Yeah, that's
that's not right. All right, my bad fucking idiot, sorry and you can't say
that it's in wonder ascented wonderland either dude, you fucking idiot and you
can't say that the
what you call the post enough enough twelve, twenty five,
you're going to get us in trouble.
You're going to get us in trouble. Stop it
change it every year to try and hide from people. Yeah, they should
Can you imagine living in the Christmas zip code? So we all have letters here,
amazing letters that
we're hoping for Santa Claus and we will, I promise you, you know us, we will
eventually get these to the North Pole. Yeah, we'll get them where they're just
where they were kind of a middleman intermediary. We're always looking for
something to do for Christmas. So listen, if you intercept a sack full of
letters for Santa, you like to read them out. Yeah, exactly. Do whatever you want.
know it's fine. I mean we're just checking them for poison. How about
that? Yeah, because there might be some you know you should maybe some of
these Christmas wishes we could even help fulfill. Yeah, because what are
we but Santa's little helpers? Right, exactly. That's what I was saying. I'm
Santa's toy soldier. He can do with me what he wants. I'm Santa's street
soldier. All right, which one who wants to start? Let me see if this is I can
start. Okay.
Oh, this one is in Spanish. Hold on.
Wait, I have one too.
Hola, Santa.
Me llamo Jubio.
Para Navidad me gustaría
conocer a Kysonat.
Quiero salir con él.
And there's a little drawing.
That's so cute.
Can you hold that up to the camera to show everybody?
Yeah, I'll hold it up to this.
Wow.
Who's that?
I guess that is Jubio and Kysonet.
Oh my God!
In front of the Christmas tree.
You guys look insanely happy.
Yeah.
Holy shit, that's a Christmas miracle.
That kind of reminded me of this letter I have, man.
Oh, really?
Yeah, this is from Julio.
Oh!
Oh.
Dear Santa Claus.
Quiero que esta Navidad sea la mejor Navidad de todas.
Quiero un libro rojo grande, una tarjeta de biblioteca y un juguete sexual.
Quiero aprender de deleteriar y atarme los zapatos. Soy gay. Soy
soy estupido.
Atentamente, Julio Garcia.
Wow. Oh my goodness.
Can you say what you said in this letter and why you sent more than one?
I won a Nintendo switch.
I think it says I want a big red book. I want a
library card and I want a sexual toy.
Yep,
and something about shoes, but who knows
you have one? Yeah, Cameron, let's see yours.
Let me read one. Okay.
This one says,
dear Santa, I want a Funko pop for Christmas from the soy boy.
No,
rip that up right now. Get rid of that shit. Rip that shit. Get rid of that
shit. That one is not a, I know that's a federal crime. I know that's a
federal crime. I'm willing to go to jail for that. Uh-huh. That's going to,
that's, you go to jail. The soy boy? Really? You go to jail and you tell
Really, that's your name the soy boy you got a really your name you tell the highest
Level gang member that you ripped up the soy boys mail. They're gonna make you second-in-command. They're gonna respect your ass
That's immediate respect. You're kind of sick fuck. I'm changes their name to the soy boy. That's so disgusting to me
Kill him yeah, dude I have you know what we'll lift our spirits. I have a letter here that I can read okay
And I'm sure, oh look, there's a little, there's a tree and a heart on it.
That looks so cute already.
Wow.
Dear Santa, hello.
My name is Amy.
I am a 10 year old girl from Kansas City and I am so excited for Christmas this year.
This year has been, well, interesting to say the least.
My mom and dad divorced and my older sister is in the hospital for issues related to body image.
image. She throws up when she eats hamburgers.
This year has been so stressful for me and my family, and the only thing that
would make it better would be if Jubio from Podcast About List sang a Christmas
song. Oh my God. I love Jubio and so do all the other girls in my grade.
I even have a poster of him on my bedroom wall.
He talks to us in its Discord server called Jubio's Angels,
but he never sings to us.
If you could make that happen,
it would be a dream come true.
Thank you, Santa, love, Amy.
Now, Jubio, are you gonna sing a Christmas carol
for little Amy?
- Hello?
- No! - No?
- What?
- You're not gonna let this little girl's wish come true?
- Her sister's in the hospital for hamburgers.
- She has a hamburger throw-up disease.
and you won't even sing a Feliz Navidad.
That is messed up man. You can't even sing
O Tannenbaum for her. Sing O Tannenbaum. Come on. Sing O Tannenbaum.
Gotta be the best Christmas carol. We'll sing it with you.
O Tannenbaum, O Tannenbaum,
blibli, blibli, blibli Germany.
when air is snide. You actually know I know one word. Yeah. Well, it seems to
know one line. Jubio is fully grinching out on us today. Jubio is being a
complete green using to sing to one of his little also what's his deal does a
little a Jubio Jubio angels discord server. I want to shut that down man.
Yeah, we've told you that's not okay to do man.
Are you there?
Okay, I have a let's see I got away
this is also from
from a little from a little one. Oh
yeah, how sweet is that? It seems like we've taken a lot. These are a lot of
from kids. Yeah, yeah, it's weird that we didn't get that many adults in our
letters. Kind of weird right? Yeah, I feel like mostly kids. It makes sense.
This is from little Ben. Oh, okay.
Hello, Santa.
This year, the only thing I want for Christmas is world peace.
Aww, little Ben.
Oh my god, that's so cute.
War, disease, social disorder.
How could I sit here and wish for big red fire trucks or super powered action figures
when some people are struggling just to afford basic human needs?
What a smart kid.
It would just be selfish.
And that's the problem with this world.
Selfishness.
British corporate CEOs and money hungry politicians hogging all the wealth up
top and leaving the little guy with nothing a little bit all the way at the
bottom. He's probably referring to himself or his family as well. At least
is he related to Big Ben.
He could be a clock
all the way at the bottom. I just wish I could do something about it. You know
what Santa I finally decided what I want for Christmas. I want a voice.
I want a say in what direction the winds of change blow
a say in the future that I'm inherited. When I grow up, I'm going to run for
President. Wow, and I'll make sure that never again does another immigrant enter
this country
into this country illegally to impregnate a white woman.
Little bit,
what the hell are you saying? Right now, I'm thirty one, so I should be able to
run for President by twenty twenty eight, and when I'm President, every border of
this country will be protected by nuclear bombs and big red fire trucks
to put it into you illegally flying over the border. Go back to your igloo,
you disgusting red snow pig. Holy shit, little Ben, what the little as what a
turn little Ben has made. I didn't know you were a grown man going by little
Ben. I mean his first name could be little like a little John little John
little Richard. I don't know. Yeah, little Wayne. There's actually there
might be more little more
at least in pop culture. That's so true little bins. You seem like a bastard
man. Yeah, but what I don't understand it seemed at first, maybe he was
maybe I guess at the end I was kind of curious whether he was just racist
against people from the North Pole or if he maybe also was having some. I
think he's racist against every well. He said another immigrant illegally
entering the country to impregnate a white woman. Yeah, so I thought I don't
think that I was like Santa's done that, but I say it could be an elf. I'll
say it that letter gave me the Ick. Do we know where Mrs. Claus is from? Yeah,
we Mrs. to Mr. Mastigations. We'd found that out years ago, but I don't
remember it. She's got to be from America. She's from someplace, so I don't
know.
Okay,
I got another one here.
Dear Santa Claus for Christmas, I want to be a bad bitch right now. I'm a mid
and I'm barely have a get. I want a BBL so I can twerk. I need to have big butt and
boob Riz. I'm practically an MPC right now. Oh no, but I want to level up my
body. I want to be a baddie with a bubble body and that is from Taylor
Swift. Oh Taylor T Swizzle. It could honestly that does kind of break my
heart. They know that Taylor Swift thinks that about herself when she's one
of the most telling women on the world are the baddest bitch in the universe.
okay, you already have a bubble body girl. You look like a bubble. You look
like a bubble. You are honestly borderline like fat to me, Taylor Swift.
You look disgusting. You're your get is there it's there it's there it's there.
You don't need to improve that thing. You look this is where your is this is
where you think it is and you're hardly an MPC. You're the man of the year.
You're literally you are the man of the year. You're a character. You are a
time man of the year, so don't beat yourself up over that shiz okay, Santa
I can't give you that by the way Taylor Swift and you shouldn't be writing to
Santa either. No, you should be writing to a doctor in Beverly Hills because
that's where you can get that done. Yeah true or you go overseas and you have to
sit on the plane backwards. Yeah, I mean usually that happens. I have a letter
here. It looks like it's from a little boy. Yes, it is from a little boy and it
says what you can tell just by the handwriting. Yes, I can tell by the
handwriting. It looks very juvenile. Yeah, it looks like shit. I can tell some, but nobody
who went to his finished primary school wrote this letter. There's no way. Absolutely no
way. It looks terrible. Hello, Santa. My name, Pepper Donaldson. I five year old for Christmas.
I want blood.
I have no blood.
No blood in body.
I live on machine.
Machine Mac blood in my body.
Mommy, daddy cry a lot.
Hospital expensive.
I like Paw Patrol.
Paw Patrol.
Doctor said it should not be live for Christmas.
I want blood and Paw Patrol toy.
And that's from Pepper.
And it looks like someone drew a pepper for him.
Let me look at... Hello Santa, my name is Pepper, 15 years old.
Fifteen?
O.D.E.
It looks like 15.
I think it's I, 5 year old.
Well let's just say it's 15.
Yeah, it probably seems 15.
And he wants blood.
So this guy...
He has no blood in his body and he lives off of a machine it looks like.
And pauportal, I'm guessing he means...
whose pepper. Let me give you some advice, buddy. If you're writing a
Santa and you're asking for a present, do not put in your letter that you're
going to be dead before Christmas. You just fucked up. Santa is not going to be
giving you. I got a way should say is I'm going to be a doctor said I'll be
alive for two hundred more Christmas exactly and actually I need to get it
all in advance. Oh yeah, wait, doctor actually said that for me. I have a
medical condition or Christmas is every day.
I have hello. I have a mental. I should have I should have gotten that letter.
I have a I have a mental disorder where I think every day
I mean toys every day or I'll get really toys every single day or I think you
abandoned me Santa yeah. Well, that's or I guess my brain will break. Can we talk
some real shit? Have you all ever gotten coal for real? No yeah, my parents used
to give potatoes because it was cheaper, cheaper than coal London. We could just
use the potatoes to make mash potatoes for dinner after wait. Your parents gave
potato for Christmas? If it was like you were bad this year, if they wanted to
make the joke like oh you were bad you get instead of coal Santa gives out
potatoes because coal is expensive. Your parents convinced you that you were bad?
They would tell me that I was bad sometimes yes. Only on some years?
They would tell me I was bad sometimes yes. They would tell me I was bad some
years on Christmas yes. It feels abusive man. I don't know I feel like it's
it's it's supposed to teach you. I mean maybe it's just an Irish Catholic that
you get potatoes. If you're bad potatoes aren't so bad yeah, I mean I like it's
not like they give you potatoes and they in place of another gift. I think that's
what it was. I think that's what they probably wanted you to think it was.
Well, they never got any of my presence either way. Well, you know Santa doesn't
wrap presents. Yeah, some in the living room. Yeah, how's he going to wrap that's
normal? You can't wrap a treadmill. Yeah, they're not going to wrap a flex and
wrap the potato. Adjustable dumbbells. He's not going to wrap all that shit.
I think they continued doing that. I think they gave my niece and my nephew's
potatoes this year, and I think they cried. I would fucking cry. That's fine.
It's a funny joke. It's good. I don't think that's funny. You can't do that
shit to a kid. You can't give them a potato. No, you can't. You can give them
a potato. That's fucked up. I draw a hard line. No, fuck that. You're getting
toys and only things that will make you smile. A kid doesn't need a potato.
you're not going to teach that
when you say no toys on Christmas. No, you give them all the toys and then you
give one potato at the beginning or something and it's be like to do what
you think pranks are funny. Yes, what the hell is a Christmas? I guess it
must be a Christmas prank. It's a Christmas prank. That's not funny man to
tell your kid. This is a this is the one reason kids are alive. Yeah, you
shouldn't say that you don't say you say you say you tell them it was a prank.
You say, oh, I got you. Oh, I got you. Christmas should be you don't say you
got this because you were bad a bag at that point. That's when it that's
wrong. That's what my parents do yeah. They would say you got that because you
were bad.
I think they were trying to teach me that this is pure abuse. Yeah, you are
purely abused. I must have been completely and I bet you didn't even get
to make French fries out of the potato. No, I bet you had to get baked. I think
that they were right old potatoes yeah well with the black spots all over. I
think they were moldy and it's sprouting yeah. I just think that Christmas
should be a candy, a DVD and a lottery ticket. That's I can't wait to get
that's a grown man Christmas. I want to get a lottery tickets every my
every I never got a lot of since I was like ten years old. I got lottery
tickets for I would just get started. I take it on every Christmas, but the
royal. Did you have a rule that if it was over if somebody got over a
thousand dollars, we had to split it with the whole family? Yes, I always
thought that was you said you never got lottery tickets. Why are you
I mean lottery tickets in general, when other
family or the July.
I can see that I don't do I've never heard of that one ever. Well, you're to
be fair. You're the only other person I've ever met who got lottery tickets
growing up at Christmas. No, there's I've met other people who do that too.
I'm sure you have what I said is you're the only person,
but you've never met anybody's even mentioned doing on her fourth of July,
never even once. It's all right. I've never even considered that it could be
It's just a thing that your dad does because he just bought a bunch of beer.
So he's like, "All right, fuck it.
I'll get lotto tickets too.
We'll see what happens."
That's what Christmas is.
Your dad buys a bunch of beer for Christmas too.
No.
I had to hide beer from my uncles.
We did mimosas at Christmas.
Yeah, that's what my aunt does.
That's fun, man.
I usually do coffee cake and coffee.
So you're more uppers.
My family's more downers.
I like that.
All right.
What's your next letter?
Let me see.
Let me see. Let's see. That was a really short one.
Okay.
Dear Santa, me and my co-workers Walter and Ahmed would really like a girl puppet
this year. Love, Peanut.
I wonder who that's from.
There's no last name.
It sounds like it's from Peanut.
There's no last name at all. It just says, "Love, Peanut."
Huh.
Huh, that's an interesting one.
It's interesting. It is interesting.
I like this guy's got to be an adult because it was straight to the point.
No,
doesn't work. Oh, I live on a machine. Yeah, shut the fuck up man. All right,
straight to the point.
Here's one
dear Santa Claus. Here's a list of things I want for Christmas and straight
to the point again.
One a Santa hat and outfit. That's cute. He wants to be like his hero. Yeah,
2. Some strands of your hair, both head and beard.
What?
Well, to make more-
3. A cloning machine.
4. A house key to your palace in North Pole City.
5. Your federal ID.
6. One minute audio sample of your voice with minimal background noise.
7. Itemized list of your daily diet.
And 8. Tooth Toons style fleshlight that plays music when you fuck it.
(laughing)
- That doesn't seem like it has anything to do with it.
- Yeah.
- It seemed like it was kind of on a through line.
- It looks like a Mrs. Claus fleshlight.
- Oh, that's nasty, bro.
Why would you even say that?
- You say flush light?
- I said fleshlight.
- I think you said flush light.
- I said Mrs. Claus fleshlight.
- Some kind of toilet fleshlight.
- I don't know that that even exists, though, does it?
- Do they have a Mrs. Claus fleshlight?
- No.
- I'm just talking about a musical two tunes fleshlight.
- I mean, I guess there's songs that I would like to fuck.
- If it's the same as the two tunes songs.
S and M by Rihanna. I would fuck that song. It's the same as the tooth tune
songs. It's got to be like
from your son's room. It is like a fate like really low quality speaker.
You hear the song and it just yeah, but you hear it going like
rock like
and then you walk in and he's fucking like when you hold your phone up with
speakers and go like oh yeah and he's fucking the back of the do around the
world. It could be like a giant. It could be like it could look like a giant
cow's tongue. If there's a kiss one and you
you know,
I've always thought those things could probably be flesh lights. Yeah. Cow's
tongues are huge man. That's true. Not that that's
requisite for you. So that's true. That's true. A cow tongue is huge. They
are huge.
That's true.
All right, I'm going to read this next letter. This next letter has a picture
it. Why you seem so scared of showing it to me? Hello, my name is Ryan. I'm looking
at the popular podcast beers. We drink here is a picture of me for Christmas. I
want a beer.
Wow, you know what Rex you really look like you look amazing. Like famous
comedian and hold it from the top political activists. Brett Gelman. I'm
going to be honest with you. Rex.
Jesus Christ, is this what he looks like?
You know what the title of that article was?
Let me pull it up real quick.
Can I see the picture?
Sorry I'm obsessive.
The title of the article where I found that photo was...
Oh shit, I screenshotted it for sure.
Ice cream shotted it?
I screenshotted it.
This is a People Magazine headline
where that photo is from.
Stranger Things, Brett Gelman praises his
really impressive young co-stars.
(Laughter)
(laughter)
- Wow.
- Oh man.
- What an amazing, dude, imagine how amazing
it would be for him to be your mentor.
- Oh my god, imagine, imagine Jaddy coming up to you.
- Yes, dude.
- Oh my god.
- He says, you wanna go break into the nerd melt
and we can smell the stage?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- That would be awesome.
- Oh my god, Jonah Ray once performed here, man.
(sniffing)
- Kumail!
- Oh my god, Kumail and Jonah Ray performed here.
I mean you guys are talking about this and all you know, but you guys do realize that
we lost him who he supports Israel.
Brett Gelman, Brett Gelman supports Israel.
Why would he support Israel?
He does no dog in that fight.
We lost him to the right to the to the right, the fascistic right, the fascistic right.
We lost him.
I bloody is he and I'm sitting here like I'm sitting I'm over here like how am I ever going
to enjoy a piece of media with Brett Gellman in it ever again. How am I going to watch
Stranger Things with no one? I'm going to get no joy out of seeing Brett Gellman on
TV anymore. I'm not going to be able to smile and laugh. Dude, how am I going to get through
that one part and the other guys now? That's going to be hard as fuck. How am I going to
get through his Mickey Mouse blackface performance? This is going to be really tough for me. I
just really hope that he, at this point in his career, he stays the fuck away from Tim
Heidecker. Please don't do it to Tim man. Get away from him. If you were thinking of politically
corrupting Tim Heidecker. Get the fuck away from office hours right now. If I ever see
you on office hours, I will not fucking hesitate. I swear to God. I will not fucking hesitate.
I'm going to do a flip at you. Straight up. Jackie Chan style. I'm going to spin on you.
I'll spin on you man. Spin on you literally. What are you guys asking Santa for Christmas
this is you. We should wait on that. That's a that's all that's a whole new
episode. That's a whole not or at least I don't know. Well, I guess I'm asking him
for nothing because I don't need anything because I'm so blessed. Yeah, me
too. I think I'm completely blessed. Both of you, you don't want like money.
Like I'm asking for money. Okay, money. Yeah, I'll do money. You can't okay, so
you can't copy first. I'll get one of the rules. I want the money that Caleb. I
want whatever Caleb is going to get.
Should I just read this next letter?
Yeah.
It looks pretty quick.
It looks pretty short.
"Dear Santa, for Christmas I want gold.
Gold member."
Okay.
That's all it says.
And it's interesting.
It kind of went...
Oh, it's written in gold font.
It really looks like silver, more silver to me.
But...
No, if you look in the light...
Yeah, if you want to call that gold.
Yeah, if you look in the light, well, that's where the colored pencil sits.
That's cute.
Oh, go ahead.
Me?
Yeah.
Oh, you have three letters in there.
That's really just two.
Oh.
Wow, this one's all typed up.
Looking crazy.
"Dear Mr. Claus, Rhee, Notice of IRS Audit.
We hope this letter finds you well.
The Internal Revenue Service has identified you as a potential beneficiary of the IRS
audit.
We are grateful for your assistance.
We hope you will be able to continue to receive our financial assistance.
Re, notice of IRS audit. We hope this letter finds you well. The Internal Revenue Service
has identified your unique TIN, commonly known as your SSN, in connection with the annual
tax return filing. The letter serves as an official notice of our intent to conduct an
audit of your tax return for the tax year 2023 under the provisions of the Internal
Revenue Code. The IRS has noted certain discrepancies in the reported income and deductions on your
tax return, and we believe the thorough examination is necessary to ensure compliance with the
tax laws of the United States, specific areas of concern include classification of gifts.
I could see that happening.
Oh yeah.
Please provide detailed documentation supporting the classification of gifts as non-taxable
including a list of recipients, the nature of the gifts and their fair market value,
eligibility for charitable deductions and business expenses.
Please submit requested documentation within 30 days of receiving this notice.
I probably need to forward this one.
Sincerely Bearish Gretzky, IRS Auditor.
That's a crazy name.
Bearish Gretzky, IRS Auditor, Internal Revenue Service.
We appreciate your prompting.
Bearish Gretzky?
Bearish Gretzky.
That's an odd name.
It is an odd name.
I wouldn't think that, I mean I guess Santa's in some kind of trouble at the IRS, but he's
not a citizen of the US.
No.
Maybe he has a home here in Boca Raton.
Is Boca Raton in the U.S.?
Yes.
Where is that?
Florida.
Really?
Where do you think he vacations?
But it's named Boca.
Or it's Boca.
Boca Deez Nuts.
Oh, shit.
Oh, snap.
It's a Christmas miracle, y'all.
We destroyed Cameron on his own track.
No, no, no.
This isn't my track.
You have the tracks in front of you, bro.
And barely in front of me.
They're right in front of you right now.
No, this is our track man. No, this is Santa's track. All right, read your damn
letter, bro. Yeah, shut the fuck up and read. Shut up and read that letter.
Wait, guys, should I read my letter? Yeah, yeah, that's what we're telling
you. That's Patrick, my impression of Patrick. Oh, damn. Oh, shit. That is
fire. All right, I might have been destroyed. Here's my impression of
Patrick. Look at my, I have the stupidest Santa hat of anybody. You bought it for
me. I picked it myself and bought it for myself. You threw it at me and said,
here it goes dear Santa Claus. I want a puppy for Christmas, but not just any
puppy. I want a puppy that is the size of a quarter. It's so small that it just
floats around the room and I have to catch it in a cup. If I want to pet it, I
have to feed it tiny amounts of food. I assumed when I asked for a puppy last
year, you would know have known I wanted a small coin sized one, but you brought
me a normal sized one. This time bring me a tiny puppy. Make sure the puppy is
really, really small. It's better for it to be small. That's from micro
seems like he was a little upset about it. The last he was a little up.
I forgot about micro.
I hope he's doing okay. I hope my girls okay. I hope my girl didn't get stuck in
the vacuum or something God, my girl. No, I can you imagine how what a
nightmare that must be for him. They have a normal sized, but I mean not a
puppies one thing because it gets there and it's it's a probably a big for
yeah, but then it gets even bigger. Yeah, yeah, yeah, probably when you get a
bull mastiff or something. Imagine how long it takes him to feed the dog.
Imagine a dog. It's like mining one piece of kibble at a time out of the
that dog is going to just think he's a he's a flea. Exactly. He's probably
going to kick him around in the dog's poop. Not that I would want to say not
that I like that or want to see a picture. No, I would not want to see
micro covered in poop. I had to take a turd out of Phil's asshole last night.
I had to do that to myself before yeah.
Did you eat a tennis ball
and I got stuck
halfway in
it doesn't happen to bill
yet a tennis ball and I and dude it sucks whenever he eats a toy like that
I just know I'm going to have to finger my dog
like twenty four hours. I'm going to be on the street and I'm going to have my
finger with a bag. Obviously, yeah, in my dog's asshole, pulling this out of his
yes, I can't digest tennis yeah stuff yeah. I don't think most of the
he's a red blooded American
that might work. He might be able to eat a football, but a tennis ball. He's not
a poodle. No way, no how
this next letter here. This one is actually this is a typed out one
type shit. Santa, I don't know what to do and I am hoping for a miracle. I am 32 years old
and I lost everything. In 2020 I put $43,000 into the GameStop short squeeze plus the rest
of my savings into Dogecoin due to some bad advice from a subreddit, my only friend who
I no longer associated with. My stupidity cost me everything. I lost it all and I haven't
been able to bounce back since. I lost my boyfriend, my apartment, everything. I had
to move back in with my parents. They hate my guts. Every day I feel them glaring at me,
looking at the failure of a son they have created. A waste of precious life. I started working
at, ironically, a GameStop two towns over. I hate it. I hate driving there. Every single
day I think about how stupid I am. Some days when I'm driving to work, I imagine veering
into the oncoming lane, hoping a semi hits me. I hope the windshield shatters and the
glass explodes into my face. I hope that the impact does not kill me. I hope that I have
to endure the pain until I eventually succumb to my injuries. I know that I will never do
it as I am a coward.
That's it?
For Christmas this year I want a realistic action figure of Cameron Fetter with realistic
hair that I can brush and I can undress him and play with him and have him go on adventures
with my Spider-Man from William Huxtable.
Oh, hey, that's actually kind of flattering that he wants. Yeah, and I mean to put me
in the same league as Spider-Man, brush your hair and wait and I got a hang on a Spider-Man.
Okay, he thinks I'm Spider-Man's friend. You would if you look that up as a W, you would
you'd have a brush included with your action figure.
Yeah. Yo, you definitely would.
Nah, dude, I'd have two AK-47s.
Ooh.
And a brush.
That'd be dope.
Yeah, maybe a brush, the AK-47.
A toy that comes with two AK-47s and a bazooka and a...
(laughter)
That'd be cool as fuck, dude.
What kind of toy would you be, Pat?
I would probably...
I feel like you'd be one of the stretchy ones.
No, no, no, no.
You'd be one of the ones that you could throw on the ceiling of the classroom
I think I rescue hero that's on sale. Yeah, one of those you wouldn't be a
rescue hero. I think I would be a rescue here. You have no you're the least brave
person I've ever met. You're a complete coward. There's
see he flinched. No, I didn't. Yeah, I flinched it. Yeah, he went. Are you are
you really trying to say that you're the I'm the one that gets scared of noises?
He's
you just opened up a can of worms. You don't want to open open up a can of
fucking
you both are your guys are just both scaring me stop. I'm sorry I got I just
got scared, but it's not fair because I'm getting scared every time by each of
you guys. I'm getting double the scares. That's true. That's not fair and it's
not all right, not even part of this. Let's remedy. Let's hear another. You
wouldn't be a rescue hero, though you would be a bouncy ball.
I would not be a bouncy.
No, I would not be a bouncy ball with a star on it.
would not be the Pixar Bouncy Ball. You'll be a dog toy with a star on
your belly. I would maybe be a dog toy. I could see that
people would complain. They would buy your toy. They'd be like I thought it
was fully articulated, but the hands are stuck to the
my kid hates this
my kid hates this toy. Why are the arms stuck on the
I hate this time. My kid sees this door on the shelf. He starts crying. It's
screaming. I had a toy like that and then I did have a way like that. My on
my aunt got me this toy. I forget what it was called. I know what it looks
like. It's like a little boy that has like a big bugger coming out of it and
you like squeeze down on its head and just says like annoying shit and one
time it like was like the most annoying toy and it just like had like a big like
droopy booger and I remember waking up in the middle of the night and seeing
it's just silhouette and I was like six or seven, but seeing it silhouette
scared the shit out of me and I made my mom throw, I like cried and then made
my mom take it out of the bedroom and throw it away 'cause it was so scary.
Reminds me of garbage pill 'cause I hated those things. I was never scared
of a toy. That's, and I'm sorry to say this, that's a younger sibling thing.
Yeah. Well, I'm a middle child. I'm a middle boy. I was not scared of any
toy either. I'm not the youngest though. Younger, I said. What kind of toy do
you have that scares you. How can you be scared of a toy? How can you be scared
of a bugger? You were scared of a bugger? You were a bugger, motherfucker. I was
afraid of the silhouette of it. It looked like a little guy staring at me.
It is a little guy. It was, it actually was. And he was probably pointed in
your direction. What do you mean the silhouette? You had him backlit all the
time against a wall? Well, it was like a window. No, see, I know what he's
talking about, 'cause I saw the silhouette of my toys when I was going
to sleep, but they would just excite me. Yeah. I just talked to them. You would
think that they were moving at night, right? Yeah, I would think they were
moving around. Well, okay, all the all the cool ones that I like all the ones
that I like, you would want them to move around. Yeah, but the scary ones like a
little boy with a bugger in my head. I think in my head I hated that toy so
much that I looked for a reason to get rid of it. Yeah, but that thing I'm
scared. Yeah, I just told my mom that it scares me and I don't want it anymore,
even though it was just like, oh, I don't want to play with the bugger. I was
scared of the egg stealer from Dragon Tales. I had to hide the egg dealer,
egg stealer, oh, stealer, egg stealer, because imagine how hard those dragons
Nebulizer eggs man you're scared of the nebulizer. I mean that is a scare. It sounds like an alien
Yeah, I was I was scared of my nebulizer then nebulizer
Scary name I only have one more letter, but I'm gonna read mine. I can give you one of mine
Fuck it man. I have tween
Fucking great what little bin again man. Oh he double texted Santa. I don't want to hear from this guy. I forgot to
I forgot to wish for this in the last letter, but for Christmas I want every single homo to go to jail.
First they ruined my favorite movie Rocky Horror Picture Show. Then they ruined my favorite singer Janelle Monáe.
Now they're trying to ruin my favorite game series Grand Theft Auto by making it take place in Florida, which to me seems gay.
Why can't these fruity gay guys just have their own gay ass country where everyone there is gay? Oh wait, they do.
you do, it's called Mexico. Little Ben, candidate for President of the United
States, twenty twenty eight Constitution Party. Ben, stop emailing, stop mailing
Santa, man.
There's that. Ben, there's no place for this shit. Take a look at that, 'cause
that's all you're gonna get. Take a look at that. This is what you get for
Christmas. And also, take a lap, man. Okay, wait, show 'em that again. Show 'em
that again, Pat. Show 'em the middle finger again. So not only is this a
gesture of rudeness, this is also the number of votes you're gonna get in the
election. And it's a thumbs down. 'Cause I'm voting for you, buddy.
(laughing)
- It's funny that the president always does the thing
where they go and vote for themselves.
- I was about to ask, do they do that?
- Yeah. - Makes sense.
- There's always every election year,
there's some news coverage of like,
oh, there goes Biden, he's voting for himself.
- Wow. - He put in the wrong guy though.
- Yeah, yeah. (laughing)
You can read that one too. - Okay.
Well, I get to double read, I'm such a reader today.
- Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
- You are such a reader, man. - That's the wrong one.
That's the wrong one.
Dude, I'm such a fucking reader man.
You're so reader-ed.
So readerly and writerly.
You just read it.
What? You're holding us up?
You get the chance to double read, you're holding us up?
Yeah.
Dear Sanda,
Me, Caleb Pitts,
Me want corn,
Me want to be new corn kid.
Dear Sand, I didn't write this man
dear sand me Caleb pits me a picture of corn. It is it's not doesn't say corn me
want to be new corn kid
and it looks like for some reason it was it was written and then written over
with another color of colored pencil
for it might have been to it might have been too light of a color or maybe it
was two kids.
Who the fuck is saying the same letter on the same piece of paper? I don't
know, maybe that's just a spelling mistake. I mean, this is it's from
Caleb bits.
I didn't write this.
Me want to be new corn kid.
I don't want to be the new corn kid man. That kid's life is ruined.
He's not going to get into college viral man. This is the letter you gave
me to read man.
Would you have preferred I give you this one?
- I would have preferred anything but that.
- I'll read it.
I'll read this one.
- Dear Santa.
I know how to spell Santa.
That's the first clue I know.
- Would you rather I give you this one?
- Yeah, man.
- Dear Santa, I'm called Jack and I've been very naughty.
Very, very naughty.
I curse, I fight, and I drink.
- Oh no.
- Earlier this week, I was in jail.
- God, Jack.
- But using my rapier wit and help from my cellmate,
I managed to escape.
I've been on the run, sailing the seven seas for days in search of the black pearl.
For Christmas, I want treasure.
(laughter)
Savvy?
Yeah, I would have liked that one more.
(laughter)
I think that's from Captain Jack Sparrow.
I think you might be right.
Oh my God, search of the black pride. I didn't know he was still around.
Yeah, I guess he is. I don't know.
Oh crap.
Dear Santa Claus, my parents said I can't have a little brother for
Christmas. Oh, that's sad. Don't read this one. It's sad.
So I want one of your elves. Oh, I could rough house with him and force
him to lick my armpits. I promise I would love him like a brother and I would not
sexually molest him as I'm old enough now to know better. You must be able to
spare just one elf for a kid like me. I could tell him my secrets and he
wouldn't tell anybody because he only speaks elfish. Me and him would go
apple picking and it wouldn't be as much of a commitment for my parents as a
younger brother would be because elves only live to fifteen years old. Love you
Santa from Timmy. Oh, that's okay. No, you don't want to live with an elf.
Yeah, first of all, no, he wants an L. I mean, if you will say it, see what kid
wishes for something. Also, did he say he's he's old enough now to know that he
shouldn't sexually molest? How old is he? Does it say?
Doesn't say, doesn't say at all. What old is what age is too young then to know?
Well, I mean, he he can write. So, you know, he's probably at least at least
fifteen at least thirty got to be something like that. Yeah, that's
around that age where you start writing this. I wouldn't want to live with an
elf, though I think I feel like they might eat a lot of food like a
surprising amount of food. Yeah, well, that's that was a fucking movie.
Yeah, they eat a lot of candy. I just fucking realize there's a movie about
an elf being your brother. Well, that's about yeah. Well, that's about the
being an older brother that acts like a younger brother. No, it's maybe the
whole the whole the whole reason that the family's out of whack in that movie
the elf is because divorce, a brother is younger, the human brother's younger
than the elf brother, but the elf brother acts like he's younger than the
human brother. So the young so it's all it's a dissonance that's throwing
everything out of whack in the universe in this movie. If they just switched it,
if the elf was actually younger than the brother and he acted like it, then it
would be a normal family and they would be able to say you can eat candy like
that. I thought I'm younger. I thought the whole movie was about an elf that
comes from the North Pole to New York City. No, it's about family dynamics.
It's about leaving your kid at the orphanage.
It's elevated.
I thought it was about spying on women in the shower.
That's a good chunk of it.
That's a good scene.
That is a good scene of it. I like that scene.
I really can't stay.
Alright, so I got this. This is my final letter it looks like.
And it looks like this is dated 2017.
It's old?
Yeah, there's an old. This one just didn't make it to Santa back in the day.
That's kind of sad.
That is sad.
sad dear Santa for Christmas. I would like sanity restored in America and mango Mussolini
impeached from Stephen Colbert.
Wait, he got what he wanted. Yeah, I guess he did. I guess he got everything you want
and he was restored and Santa didn't even read your letter and it are going to say we're
going to get it. We'll still get it to him. We'll have him sign and send you sign and
send you a headshot. I mean, honestly, though, knowing Stephen Colbert, he probably sent this
his letter and then also like texted him called and people call him probably
like really
it through. Why is he never been a guest on the late show? I think he has yeah. I
think he has been on there. Can you pull up a clip? Does do celebrities have to
even write the letters? Why can't they just go through their agents and
managers to get to Santa Claus? Yeah, I guess that's how they do it.
Maybe they get a wagons. Maybe Santa doesn't have representation, so he's
just like I'm not going to talk to an agent or like a manager, kind of like
Don't worry where he's just got a phone in his house. Yeah, I guess movie.
Are you thinking of Ghostbusters?
That's what I was thinking.
(Laughter)
Yeah, he lives in a firehouse.
Yeah.
And he's got a lady that screams, "We've got one!"
And that means he's got a new role.
Yeah.
That would be kind of cool.
(Laughter)
A fire pole.
Cameron handed me one to read.
Oh, that's nice of him.
It was nice. That's a little gift for me.
Yeah, because you kind of ran out.
I'm sorry for the handwriting of whoever wrote this.
I immediately thought it said roll instead of coal. Well, I'm so what we'll
just read it and then we'll know dear spoiler, dear Santa Claus. I want coal.
I've been a bad, bad
laid kid.
This kid really has the worst handwriting ever. I slap my mom.
I held down my dad and touched his butt. Jesus Christ. What the hell is wrong?
I painted my brother's toothbrush brown doesn't sound as bad as the other.
I don't know why that'd be the third one. I married my teacher. That's bad.
I conducted my whole class to not sorry. I converted my whole class to non
binary Santa and I'm only in fourth grade. What what I'm like one of those
kids that go that would go everywhere
wait hold on I'm like one of those kids who who goes everywhere in a spider
man costume, but I dress like Hitler.
I didn't set a birthday present. I didn't get a birthday present for my
neighbor, so give me call. I genuinely want coal
signed chip chocolate
sounds like the craziest kid of all time. It's insane. It's good. On top of
I can't write a fucking word to save his life.
No, I thought he said chip chocolate part where he dresses
like Hitler took me a minute 'cause it's really it says
Spider-Man cost year, but I drift like Mittler.
My handwriting is normal.
It's not that bad.
It's really bad man.
It's readable.
I see really that coal.
I seriously want coal.
Look at that.
Yeah, it's not that crazy that
I thought my handwriting was bad. I made a very show it to the camera.
So everyone else, where's the second s in that man? Sometimes I don't write
letters, but that's not a big deal. I made a very conscious effort to I
painstakingly. I think it took me an hour to write everything because I
wanted to make sure that everything was legible in case we were passing the
letters around. That's common courtesy. Well, I figured that we I figured we
were just going to read our own
and I also read our own that we picked from the pile. Yeah. What else would I
mean? Well you just said yours took an hour to write, to be fair.
No, I didn't.
Wait, what was that voice?
Alright, I have one last one to read. That must be Santa's Elf.
Santa's Elf is around? Yeah, it must be.
Okay, I'm gonna read this one now.
"Dear Santa Claus, my heart aches for you.
The night we shared together sticks in my memory still.
A night of tangled hotel sheets, breathless gasps, frantic rubbing and wet wallpaper.
Ew. Like it gets bubbles behind it? I guess. When I woke up next to you, I felt my heart,
my burst from the love pulsing through it. I need to see you again. I can't function
without you. At my job, I drift off to sleep and dream of you and your body. You're all
all that I want all that I need. I can't live another day without you, your
faithful companion, Julio.
Oh my God, P.S. On the back of this letter, I've drawn you something to
remember me by
looks to be
hairy middle finger. Yeah, something I don't know what it is, but I guess who
we drew it.
Is that true? Did this happen? You had a steamy night with Santa Claus last year?
Do you use angels?
That's Santa Claus is one of your angels. Did you meet him over discord?
I could see. I mean this is how's this any different from I saw mommy case in
Santa Claus? Yeah, that's pretty much the same exact ball game ballpark. Yeah,
which is that is have we ever gotten clarification on that song? Whether or
not this was about dad dressed up as Santa or she's just would be a much
more boring song. If it was called, I saw mommy kissing daddy, that wouldn't be as
interesting. I hear that that would be a song you could play any day of the year.
They should make a version.
I saw
they just change the words and not be about Christmas or that you can do on
every single holiday. So you can do yeah, well, you can do any day kissing
the Easter Bunny, but if you change it to like I saw mommy kissing daddy, I saw
mommy kissing Martin Luther King
I saw mommy kissing Martin Luther King, Jr. That'd be a great to be a full
album of remix. Exactly. I saw mommy kissing. I mean what other people do we
have a blink and Christopher Columbo is a tree in Feb. You I saw mommy kissing
in Arbor. Yeah, I saw mommy kissing. I saw mommy kissing best still day. I saw
mommy, I saw mommy kissing a ghost or a goblin or a skeleton or any number of
things. Yeah, that would work for everything. Okay, so now that we
finish the letters, I do want to talk about our Christmas lists. Okay,
let's talk about it. I do,
because
the fact that there's this many letters already headed to the North Pole kind
of has me a little scared. Yeah. 'Cause I haven't written mine yet. Well,
me neither. Yeah, I mean, this many letters that are definitely heading to
the North Pole and are not gonna get thrown away. Thrown away. Okay, who
are we throwing away? I'm definitely gonna throw away Little Ben's stuff.
I'm throwing away everything. Yeah, me too. Really? Even the blood kit? I
I need a chance, bro. Can I tell you guys what I want for Christmas? I
thought about it a little more and I can tell you if I if I'm gonna go
home and I'm gonna write a letter to Santa Claus and I can I can tell
you exactly what I'm gonna write and I'm gonna say I'm gonna start with
well first of all my address on yes, but then I'll say dear Santa Claus
this year for Christmas. I need a W
from Cameron. It's been L's all year. It's been L's for me. I need a
It's been L after L and I need a W for Christmas.
I need a W this year, Santa.
I need a W fucking badly.
I really badly need a W this Christmas.
So bad.
I'm probably going to ask for a Draco.
Yeah.
Dear Santa Claus,
I'd like a Draco but don't send it to New York
because I'll get in trouble.
Send it to Tennessee and I'll go pick it up.
Or Philly.
You could send it to Philly.
go in Philly probably that place crazy as fuck. It was slut week there last week.
Whoa, it was slut week in Philly. We missed it again. Yeah, we missed
again. How did that happen? I thought we all marked it on our calendars, so we
wouldn't I had it written. It's not a notification. Not no. Oh, my God, the
calendar is gone. That's why the third week of or it's a fourth week of
November. It's not like
it's not the same time every year. Yeah, well, I thought
Oh yeah, so I guess our calendar sometimes November has five or six
weeks and
sometimes I've ever six weeks in it. Yeah, sometimes yeah really ending on
the year leap year. So we missed it. Yeah, because last year it started on
the twenty ninth
November started on the twenty. No, the slot week started on the twenty nine
because that's technically it was the fourth or the fifth week of November.
What if you what if sometimes months only had two days? Wow, I get confused
on which months have how many days I thought November lasted two more days
That's an amazing idea. Isn't that a great idea? And then it would be an
opportunity to have more joint birthday parties because it'll be like, okay, if
there's only two days in November this year, you either everyone who has their
birthday in the first half of November, you get your birthdays on November 1st
this year. Yeah, the second half, you November 2nd, you can have a bunch more
joint birthday parties. Sometimes you want to have a joint birthday party with
your friend, but their birthday is just a little a little far away. Our
birthdays are the same month, but they're just a little too far, just a
little too far away. Tell me and Joe are too. Yeah. Yeah. So if it was just two
days, one year, that'd be great, right? Yeah. You know what I want for Christmas,
you guys? What I'm just gonna come right out and say it. I want the fans to
subscribe to us on Patreon, and I want people to subscribe to us on YouTube.
Guys were almost at 10K subscribers. Almost 100,000 subscribers. Guys, that's
kind of a 10 K times a hundo. Yeah, that's kind of you don't want like a TV.
Well, basically my real I would like a TV Santa my my letter to Santa looks
almost identical to the Taylor Swift one. Oh, you want to be? I want to look
like a bubble. Okay, we can bubble you up. But I want to look like a bubble,
but you're gonna have to. It's gonna be indirect, you know, because Santa's not
gonna give you a bubble. Let's be real. Yeah, so you need to get more money on
on Patreon to be true yeah and guys, if we hit twenty K on Patreon, we are
making a movie about Christmas.
I'm making a Christmas movie
will make even if happens in July, we'll be making a Christmas movie. Should I
wow plug my thing that I'm doing on the day that this yes dude yeah nine point
ninety three wait a minute. Are we going to hit ten K while this episode is out
could be
so everybody
if you're listening to this on the day that it comes out and you better rush
over,
because I will be appearing on
social media shows, TV networks, classic interview show in the office with
Joseph SCOTA. Oh my God, three PM Eastern today and this and it will be
airing live on. I don't know where
I think it will be on social media shows dot com.
That's it. I would miss that interview for the world. Maybe also on Twitter live or
something. I don't really know what they're doing. I'm gonna be giving an interview
about the podcast. His first, yeah. Well, first of our, you know... He went on TV
at the beginning of the year. Yeah. And now you're doing this. Well, his...
But here's the thing, his TV appearance was not about the podcast. No,
that's true. I'm keeping it strictly... I was just there. This is for the
podcast fans. I'm gonna be answering a lot of questions that this guy must...
We'll probably dig really in depth and... Oh, here's their website. Here's their
website, so you can... And sponsorships are welcome, it says. Socialmediashows.com,
like tv programs and we can see in the office with joseph scotta and i'll show
you this is the show that i'm yeah in the office here.
So this is the show i'll be appearing on today. Wait he made himself the eye and
in it's an educational and inspirational show on social media platforms and
stream live in real time on social media shows network with joseph scotta.
Joseph scotta is an experienced marketer and coach. I can't wait to hear this. I
really can't wait to see this. Oh my goodness. Don't allow loneliness gets the
the rest of you. Only you know if you got well make memories worth remembering,
etcetera, etcetera. So anyway, I'll be on that on tune in live because I will
see we'll see we'll see what happens. All right, thank you guys so much for
listening and Merry Christmas. I press the button that demonetizes. Yes, go
right.
I'm not going to do it today. Bye everybody bye bye.
I want to have a tunnel in my house to go somewhere.
I wish.
I want a tunnel from my room to the bathroom so I don't have to walk through the living
room and uh...
That's called the hallway.
No, but I want it to lead directly there.
I want to have a house where I can press a button at the door and it switches to whatever
room.
Like, you know what I mean?
You want to...
Oh!
It goes like...
Yeah.
And it sort of switches the order of the rooms.
Like in...
Like in Monsters, Inc.
It builds a new room. I think that's the game. I haven't played it either but I saw it.
I wish that I had a big hamster water bottle next to my bed.
I wish I had a big hamster. Big hamster.
And a catheter connected to my penis. I wish I had a hamster that was the size of
a German Shepherd. Yeah.
I saw, did you see? I kept in a cage in my room, I never let it
out. Imagine it stiffly dies.
Just like shaking the bars. I throw a blanket over it whenever I'm home
of
i'd drop mealworms and the report
uh... i'm like
yeah i can't get rid of it like
it was my uncle's patty dot so i have to take care of it
disgusting hamster ball
it was a good humanized
accord with the speakeasy but that's
I have to get rid of my bed and get a twin bed.
I think you'd like that.
It would be nice to be beholden to a demon.
Yeah, I think so too.
Yeah, I think it would be nice to have, uh...
That's the experience of, of, of, at least fifty percent of dog owners, I would say.
That's my life. I'm beholden to a demon.
(Bowser roaring)