I
say what you said camera. He's stuck his wiener. No, no, not that part.
We're not even going to acknowledge that. What do you want me to say? We're
not even going to talk about that. You said before we start recording. You
said, why do I feel like it would be so fucking fun to be in a relationship
with every single person in my family?
I didn't say that you did. You said that I said it right now. Copycatting
you. Why did you say that? Because you said that he said and by the way, we're
talking about romantic relationships, and so you were saying why do I why do I
feel like it would be so I mean I'm already in a familial relationship, but
you meant like like like I did, man, like finger, I like like my family. I
love them. You meant like squirting. I love my family. He just said he like
likes his family likes like more than like my family. I love every member of
my you like like your own mom squirted on his mommy. Oh, what are you doing?
you're taking this to a strange you're acting differently with your hair.
You're doing a strain. You are taking it. Keep that thing away.
Guys, if you can't guess based on how we're dressed today, it's Mar.
Welcome back to the five weeks of planets week to week to day one week
to day one day one out of two part three week to day one and we've I've
already seen a fatal error that we've made, which is that we gave Patrick
something to do. What do you mean? What's wrong with this? You have something to
play with, which is, yeah, that's, you know, it's not an actual penis, so I'm
not really grossed out by it. It's nothing wrong with, there's nothing...
Patrick found... This is gonna be the best episode of all time and it's gonna
be age restricted. Yeah, that's a little bit of a problem. Yeah, 'cause you have
this devil tail. It's not a... You're wearing a cock ring, bro. You should have
had a red juice. Okay, well, let me tell you a little story, then. Let's go
through the cock ring. Let me tell you a little story. Wait a minute, wait a
it green juice, green pants. I do have green pants on because I didn't have red
pants. But listen, let's go through the costume. I literally woke up, I put on my
red outfit and I said, I gotta go get myself a red tea. I walked into the
miniature grocery store and I said, give me a red tea right now. And they said,
there's no such thing as red tea, we only have green tea. So I got a green tea,
man. You could have got a brown tea. Brown tea is not brown. It's the red
planet, but in reality... Okay, but obviously we were all going for full red,
Yeah, well, let me let me let's talk it over there, because my outfit here, I've
got the red for Mars, the red planet, which is with oxidation and it's
everything. Yeah, but I've also you'll notice here I've got the I've got the
white stripes as well. Wow. And what are the white stripes represent? You might
ask Jack White and his wife Meg White. That's not what it represents. That's
what it is. That was the white stripes. That's the name. But what my white
white stripes represent is ice because guys Mars is a cold planet and it has
ice on it. It's not cold. It's red hot. It's cold as fuck. Okay, somebody okay,
somebody needs to hear the planet report. I mean, I surely need to be, but we'll
get to that and of course I got my I got I have got red red, a red Mars aid
Martian red Gatorade G for galactic galaxy galactic aid galactic aid and
obviously I'm in a red. I'm in a red shirt with some red shorts. Tell me why
I have a wait. I forgot one thing. I have a red hat and red faction right here on
the icon on my hat. It's a hand holding a sword and Mars is the God of War. Wow
holy shit man. So I'm wearing the wig because the if you look closely at this
planet of Mars, it is kind of a rust colour. You're wearing a kind of a
strawberry blonde, strawberry blonde. Mars is kind of a strawberry blonde
looking planet and Mars is the devilishly red planet. So I have a
devil's tail on my front.
And also,
I thought that that would be...
Why do you have these glittery...
Yeah, stand up and stand on the chair here.
For lack of a better word.
Stand on that chair and face backwards.
And he's got the, he's got red underwear on.
Yep, the shorts.
Underneath, yeah.
The shorts are very short.
And these shorts, I gotta say, man, little fruity.
What's fruity about that?
I should have had like a lav mic clipped to this.
That would have been nasty.
Yeah.
I love making Pat stand on the chair.
I hit the I hit the headphone cable.
I hit the cable on the way down.
I think that if we're going to if you're going to make me stand on the
chair, you got it. Like make sure if you love you like a ladder. I
understand you need to stabilize me.
My outfit man.
Yeah.
Well, I have a Marlboro red hoodie on right because what does it dial
because the Mar Mar's moves so fast through the galaxy that it leaves a
trail of smoke. Did you guys know that? Why? Probably in your plan to report and
I have on my jacket, oh, a red jacket, you might think just a normal red jacket.
Wait, what does it say? You read to me Cairo, America and college Cairo. What
country is that in Egypt, Egypt and what kind of thing do they have in Egypt sand
the sand and guess what Mars is covered in or at least it kind of looks like it
sand, some kind of red ass sand, soil and dust and then also wow he's wearing a
bandana. Wait, but that's a black bandana. That's not no red bandana.
Well,
guess what
the bloods wear bandanas. Okay, and bloods are red, but also the gun,
shoot iron bullets and yeah and also the guns are war like war. Exactly that too.
Yeah, that too man. I mean the layers to my outfit are amazing and my tongue's
I feel like we really I feel like we we knocked out of the way this one. No, we
hit a hat trick. We got three goals. Yeah, one, two, three, three. Do I have
green pants on? Yeah, man, we're within 90 days of Christmas. So shut the hell
up and green is there is a complimentary color of red. Exactly. The future of
Mars. Yeah, green could have been the past of Mars. That's something I want to
get into. Yeah, there if we do there, if we do nuke both the poles and then
create a new ice age that creates water in Earth. And also don't forget about
but Martians and Sid the slow Martians, which are green yes. So Mars is kind of
populated by green. No, it's happily being okay, all right, green green,
that's why you're green. You're drinking your green bean juice and it's almost
Thanksgiving green bean casserole yeah. So the connections are just out of the
one. There have been so many crazy connection. Oh yeah, wait,
Castle Wall,
but it could be there could be a castle on Mars. So last night, Cameron watch
jerk. I didn't watch it last night, but I watch it this week. Well, you watch it
this week. I watched it last night independently of Cameron. We didn't even
know each other. How do you even know each other had watched it until Cameron
said that he watched it this week to tear it to take a day. I said it to
tay. He said it so we booked felt as if watching now. Let's think about this
Steve Martin, Steve Martian. Holy fuck.
that's awesome. You're a freak, green Martian, greens, Martian, Steve, he
plays
a character named no. He plays the
the Pluto
instead of the banjo. I don't know any that's pretty good. Yeah, that's good and
he's a does he play the banjo in the movie? No, he plays a band as he's
famous. General, I know that yeah, I was still on the wild and crazy fly,
because he flies around arose through his head because of war. Well, it would be a
platter could also be pointing to a planet. Yeah, that's oh yeah, that or it
could be like oh, I'm going to go this way. Yeah, only murder or maybe it's a
reference to to Arrhenius only murders only murders in the
planet galaxy in the galaxy. That would be actually that be that would be a
very that'd be a very cheery show. Yeah, oh Selena Gomez painted purple and
because she's an alien, she'd be fully naked. Yeah, be so off. She would look
Max Serena,
she's a purple Salina Gomez, her going live on I G
just fully purple. My name horns popping out of her face, still giant boobs.
Yeah, she's awesome. No, she's not awesome. What's wrong with her? Why you
like her? She is being a dim wit. She's
talking about our earth part problems. Oh, you're right earth earth. We're
you in the past. Earth, we're on Mars. We're in the future. We're over you, Earth.
Yo, Earth, you suck, man. Earth, you suck. It's over for Earth. You got a lot of problems.
You done, Earth. You done. You got a lot of problems, Earth. You done. Something about
this wig makes me want to talk like this. We got Thomas from Pindeo time. Hey, what's up,
you guys? And he hates Earth, man. I fucking hate the Earth. Speaking of Thomas, no, I was
I was going to say he put out that rap a couple of weeks ago. You want to get him
on a OJ track? Maybe. That was a good rap. That was a good rap. That rap that
Thomas made was very, very good.
Should I blow this load? Should I go right into OJ's rap? No, man. All right.
We talked about it. No, we're going to do plan a report and then we'll do mine
and then we'll end with OJ, man. Then, speaking of Thomas, his last name is
Report. I don't know if many of you know that. That's not true. It's Re-
Anyway, what I was wondering, do you guys think that what do you think the
states will be like on Mars? The United States of Mars? Yeah, what kind of
states do they have there? They probably will have an analog, it's maybe like
a Bizarro. I bet they have 5,000 over there. Bizarro states, Bizarro USA.
It's not Bizarro Earth though, why would it be Bizarro States? They have their
own shit. Well, it is kind of the Bizarro Earth if you think about it.
They have no green. It depends... What kind of question is this? It depends
on who is colonizing it, and I hate to say that shit, but that's how it
fucking works, man. Yeah. Whoever gets there first and says, "This is
we called Stephen. Didn't we get there first? The Martians were there first.
Man, we nobody's been there. Well, you would know that if we had gone a robot,
you know, I'll do the I'll do the planet report and I'm going to clear a few
things up. All right, clear this up, clear the air. Join us once again on a
five week galactic journey through our solar system.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh a little too.
And now the planet report with Cameron Fetter.
Oh my God, can you open up the drive? This will not be normal for planet
reports, but I put a little visual aid together for this. This is incredible
already. There's a power point here. That's
TV is
everybody, but nobody else will be able to see it just us yeah.
Okay, so just ignore all the crazy red lines.
I don't think they can see that. Okay, I know I'm talking to you guys. Oh
okay, I did. Hopefully they can't see I'm sure they can't. So you guys know
about poetry, right? Yes, more than anybody as a rapper. I know and have
you guys ever heard of acrostic poems? Yes, so these are poems where the
first letter of the poem, every word in the poem creates the word of the
title. Oh, I'm intimately familiar. So this is called
Mars, a planet report by Cameron Fetter and I've put together, it is an
acrostic poem where it spells the word Mars over and over again. So I have
a visual aid here, but if you're just listening, you should be able to
pick up all you'll you'll get the rhythm of it. M A R M A R S Y'all so
I'm just going to go ahead and and and start it start reading through it to
teach you guys some facts in the form of poetry this time. Wow pop Mars all red
stuff
and you're just juvie you're just gonna have to click through for me because we
don't have a clicker, mostly a rocky surface. Okay,
meager atmosphere rather scarce
makes all respirators suffocate. Wow. Me air require some
Mars air really skinny. There's not this skinny
Mars average rotational speed
matches almost rotational speed.
My affiliated residential sphere, the Earth
have a similar rotation. Moons, ah, revolving speedily.
Mars as rocky satellites.
That's a British kind of twinge there. Mars as? Moons amount, roughly some.
Oh, Phobos. And Deimos. Mars, the name, also represent significance.
Moniker ancient Roman supreme mascot and representing strife.
I love strife.
Military action, ruckus, swords.
Many aliens really seem majority at Red Sphere.
Okay.
Martians aren't real species.
Maybe, ask research scientists.
My answer requires studying more asinine research scientists.
Martians are real stupid.
Moron.
Really sorry.
That's kind.
My anger rises sometimes.
Me apologize really sincerely.
Man.
Anyway returning subject.
Mars actually rather small.
Mercury, ah, remember?
Smaller.
Most all round spheres,
much ampler round size.
Many astronomers recently spotted
markings about reservoir subterraneanly.
Mankind hasn't reached surface.
send Mars actually rich scientist
Musk astronauts recruiting send Mars a royal situation
me and recording squad. That's us. Yeah
Musk a door real shit
Musk asking respectfully send
me and recording squad
Mars all repay sexually what all repay sexually all mentioned all research
statistics
mystified anything relax see
me after report sayonara
and that's today's planet report from all my God amazing that was amazing that
was one of the best reports I've seen. I learned so much shit man. What are you
saying that we have to suck and fuck Elon Musk? Yeah, I just figured out
tweeting the offer. If he's not going to send us a Mars for free, but what if
why there's got to be something between free and well, the line is lined up.
What else am I going to do money money? No, it was it was a RS. There's all you
can do money sexually. No, the M is not the M. The M is not in place. All all
repay significantly. So money all wheels we are. I would have found I feel like
that doesn't fit money. Gently all are sending sentiment. That's not that you
said the only money.
Massim, that's what you're saying right now. Money all are the letter are
sending again. The M is any money apostrophe. There's a what we are. He
doesn't need what are we going to offer him besides a pleasure? What was
moonshine? It's something home. All are sending. You have to be something that
you can't buy and that's that's sex from they make sense men who don't normally
sell sex. Well, that is the rare thing. It's priceless. I guess you're right.
Yeah, there is almost no price on having sex with my bottom. Yeah, yeah,
there's not anything that's priceless. My bottom is completely priceless. It's
something they would auction off. It's worth like so billions of dollars rare.
It's like it's never been done before. Well, it's like a like an olive wagyu
kind of like level of rarity and like this has never been seen before. Yeah,
I'm can't even you can't even assign a monitor. This is like I'm like when
Martin Shkreli bought that Wu Tang album, yeah, is it that could have easily been
my butthole? You could you could do the same thing where you add in a clause
that someone can come rescue you? Yeah, yeah, exactly. Someone can come steal
you back.
I'm looking here at this Google thing and it says the Google image or the Google
the bar up here, whatever it's called Mars is amazing. It's images, news,
videos, photos, planets, definitions and then chocolate. Can you click on
chocolate? I'm going to see Mars, making Mars. Oh my God, they should just add a
chocolate tab for everything. Now you can always web images, shopping and
chocolate. Wow, my snacking Mars makes a kind bars. What the hell is that? What
what the fuck
they make orbit orbit. That makes sense, but kind is kind is a surprise. I
didn't surprise, but
yeah, well alien kind on Mars. Have you thought about that? Well, the TV went
back. Oh yeah, that's true. I fixed it. Mars chocolate fix the TV.
Oh my God, I said that it's jittering anyway. The TV doesn't matter. The TV
does not matter. What does matter is our planets back to Mars guys, the five
six planets. We're rolling through these at a breakneck speed and almost they
were rotating every single thing that we need to get out every thought we've
ever had about these planets ever. Here's my thought about this planet. Why
is it called Mars? It's called you weren't you paying attention to the
planet report shut the fuck up shut the fuck up. He wasn't paying shut up shut
up shut up shut up shut the fuck up. I said moniker. I'm not done. I'm not
done.
Why is it called Mars, but there's only one of them
because of the ancient Roman Empire, be called Mar
Mar,
something I was thinking about here's something that I was thinking about on
the walk over here. Actually, when I think about more stuff, Mars is I
believe the month of March is named after the planet of Mars. Is that true?
I think that's true and we're in March right now, and I think that even one of
the days of the week might be named after Mars, Mars day, Mary, no, never
mind. There's no Mars day. I got mixed up thing. A Monday, yeah, I was thinking
moon day you're thinking of moon day. My bad, my bad y'all there's, but there's
a sad, but there's a French day that we called Mardi Mardi Gras now what's that
Tuesday? It's fat Tuesday, Marty Gras day is named after Mars. Marty Gras makes
women take off their bras,
but I
bars and spars and spars and sparts. Well, they're already doing it at spars
year round around true year. I know wait guys. We should literally become
a spa worker so we can see women naked all the time.
That's a fucking it's a great idea. I never thought of nobody thought of oh my
God yeah I'm all these people who are wasting their time jacking off to porn.
Just get a job at us.
You doing are you brain dead? Then you're making money while you look at
all the naked women. Yeah, that's a great idea. Cameron
Oh, my God, a great thing to say we have to go on shark tank. We have to pitch
the mark Cuban and Mr. Wonderful. You have to a spa for women who don't mind
being ogled yeah, a spa where you spot how about there's a spa where you go for
free and you get a bunch of perverts who pay to why oh it's like add it's like
free. Yeah, it's a premium so like if a woman wants to go to a spot, you could
either you could either perverts are paying double with
it's a great idea. You either pay fifty dollars to go to a normal spot. You pay
zero. Meanwhile, the perverts, Patrick and Cameron are sitting behind. I didn't
say that I was going to be there. Oh wait, here's the thing, though you could
do even I'm literally the inventor of this company. I wouldn't be one of the
perverts. You can even do you. Well, you have to test it out. You can even do
tears of the I would honestly be whipping and torturing the pervert. The
pervert tears could be this dude. Listen to this. You can be you could either
have it's a it's a perfect. It's a perfect honey pot. We pitch this business
from Shark Tank and then we
we post
we tell them afterwards like we and this the secret don't air this part on your
TV show, but actually we're going to kill all the perfect. We don't want to
kill. We're going to get the and John and Tanchik were you guys. Okay, you
guys are fucking idiots because you're wasting a million dollar idea. You could
even have a wants to go. You could even have it be tiered where there's windows
that you that they can be seen through both sides and that tickets fifty
dollars. They already have in there shut up. There's one that is that is a
a mirror. What do they call that a double sided mirror, one way, one way,
two way, a two way mirror, it really is and that one is more money so that
your identity is hidden and then there's one that's even more that is a
private cube. They have they have this already the window and everything it's
called a peep show, but these women, these women are just doing their own
thing, though they can put on a show yeah, but wouldn't you want to pay for
women doing the show? If we're trying to maximize profit, I just thought of an
even better idea, Caleb kind of jumping off of your two way mirror idea.
yeah. What if we have it? It's all two way mirrors. The perverts pay a
hundred dollars to come watch from behind the mirror, and the women also
are charged a hundred dollars to use the spa, and they don't know the
perverts are watching them.
Oh, and it is that's double the money. The perverts pay an extra five bucks.
They could fuck the women.
Well, no, because that kind of brings the whole thing tumbling down. Yeah,
well, let's just let's just cut out the whole spa thing and just guys pay five
bucks to fuck women. Yeah, I guess that's in a bathroom. I feel like you
I don't know. What do you mean? The girls get a cut. The girls get $2.50? Yeah, they also
get to have sex. Sex is awesome. They're going to say yeah. I don't know. I don't know about
that. You don't think we'll get any girls? I don't think we'll get any girls. I think
if it was men, I think you could get gay men to do this. Why do they have to be gay? Because
(laughter)
- Okay, woke.
- Yeah, what, you're trying to woke-ify it.
- I'm trying to woke-ify it.
Yeah, okay.
- Okay, wait.
- Okay, yes, I was trying to woke-ify it.
- Let's think about this even better.
Okay, so a spa where gay guys pay to watch straight guys
and the straight guys are, nah, that might not work.
- Yeah, but if you're a straight guy going to that,
there's like, you're like a little bit,
you're a little bit, you're maybe like a one on the Kinsey scale or some share or
two, if you're like. Is that gay or straight? I think that's like. Which side
is which? He thinks. Well, which side is which though, I'm asking. It's Patrick
Kinsey, by the way.
What if we invented a machine that turns straight guys into gay guys? I think it,
what is it, a zero and then the negative is completely straight. You should come
up with your own Kinsey scale. It should be Caleb to Patrick.
And Cameron kind of right there in the middle.
sure yeah, that's a pretty good idea yeah, and why does this guy came out and
we're all
really
tiny yeah
zoom it out. That's from four to five.
This is the
Cameron Patrick scale. It's a subset of the kids. It's nine point seven.
More specific than the Kinsey scale. This is the way to do
it's like the brackets on or like the lines on a ruler.
Somehow, it's somehow a triangle overlaid over the line of the
Kinsey's get like or somehow out in three different directions
from the same like
it's different subclasses. It's
that's funny.
This wig is itchy. I'm sorry. I'm sorry that I keep moving my I
don't want to take it off. It will ruin the outfit. You think
it'll ruin your fit? I don't think it will ruin your fit. If
you took it off. I did say this before you do look like a magic school bus
character right now. Yeah, you the one with the mustache, the one who's
sneaking onto the bus to hang out with the kids. You do look like a car to
name is frizzles me Carlos. I don't know if you remember me
last night, so don't think anything
where we go today. We're going to we're going to the we're going to the public
pool. I have an idea. Let's all shrink down and go inside my body. Yeah,
Oh, my God, I feel a little sick today. I think about I guess I can't go. It's
really go. All these kids should just go in and that's it. There's a bus of
yours and miss and you can stay here and you can watch and also to make sure
the kids nothing bad happens. You can make sure that
I
Billy Madison, if he was on that magic school bus, I mean
God only knows what that would have been. He'd be peeing his pants all over
the bus. He'd be going.
He was
that thing. How about this? How about a movie theater? You know everybody hates
these jacking off style movie theaters. Yeah, that Pee Wee Herman got cut in.
Why did he get in trouble for that? Because he was jacking off. That was a,
that's got to be a, it was a porno theater. Yeah, but you're still not
supposed to be doing that. You're, it's a gray area. People always say that. I
mean, it's like it's still legal. You can't be like, oh, it's a playground, who
cares? That's different. That's a false equivalency. No, it's the same exact
thing. No
what you think you think mommy's and daddy's you think mommy's and daddy's
were in the movie theater, because when I got that story explained to me as a
child by my uncle Kevin, he said that he was jacking off in a movie theater. He
did not tell me he was jacking off in an adult. Well, it's your kid. He's not
going to tell you about porno theaters. Almost every movie theater is for a
don't. He was saying what jacking off was, but he doesn't want you to let you
know about me a little. It's like how you're allowed to say like to your to
nephew, you can say like you know it's possible to make napalm with home
ingredients, but you can't listen to listen. I like you. I guess I can see
the logic breaking bad. You can kind of go through all the steps of cooking
meth, but you have to change what it's got to be and it's got to be candy. One
crucial step. That means that when you try to make it at home, it kills you.
Yeah, that's what they should have done. I'm breaking about. They should have
done it like a recipe for meth, but if you follow it, you die. It makes poison
gas and kills you. I think or it doesn't it doesn't make meth. It makes like a
fucking like it just makes a slime or elephant toothpaste or something
elephant toothpaste. That would have been funny if they made a
fist. Oh, I thought you just said we got to show him a thing to say that's a
thing. If I was on breaking bad, I would have been like and here we go,
cooking the meth. Here comes baking soda and
flour, flour,
now just see it's time for a very sweet charlie, our secret ingredient, blue
food,
so
it's how we make the blue math and nobody else knows how to make it jesse
that's what it is. I can't believe it. They can't believe it's blue. Why don't
they just put blue food coloring in it man? That's what the
competitors would do and I think the competitors do to that plot. Oh no
plot hole. I think they make that in the show. Here's another plot hole better
call. So this show takes place afterwards, but all the characters are
younger. Huh, I think it's a lot of characters who died are still alive.
That makes no sense. I think it takes place before. No, it takes place after
came out after yeah came out after right takes place. Well, you can oh they had a
time machine yeah. They did. They had a so smart camera. Walter is Walter. It's
a he's not brick. He's not Rick. He is Rick Sanchez. Basically, he's the Rick
Sanchez of his universe. Okay, I have to I'm touching my pain. Okay, do it almost
like a tick. You're touching your pain and guys last night. He said he's
touching his pain. I didn't say I'm talking about pain and I'm touching my
pain
almost like a tick, almost like it's a tick and let remember it and the size
of it last week.
Take that rubber band off your pain.
We're going to cut their rubber band off your pain and like fight club.
I'm glad you guys are having a lot of fun with this man.
You know I'm not even going to know. So no,
you guys want to say just nonsense shows your pain. Everybody wants to see
Listen to everyone, they're fucking excited as shit right now.
Listen, even the bugs are excited to see your painting.
Last night, stayed up late,
poured myself a glass of non-alcoholic cooking wine because
I'm not really drinking right now.
Cooking wine?
Yeah, some cooking wine.
That's got salt in it.
Yeah, it tasted not that good but I needed it in a glass.
But you drank Marsala?
It was Marsala cooking wine.
I did that in high school and it's really not good.
Well, it was non-alcoholic as well, and it just tasted like grape juice basically.
Ew.
But listen y'all, I stayed up, put on a little Luther.
Never too much, never too much.
And I just started painting away.
Yeah, Luther the TV show?
Luther Vandross.
No, not Luther Vandross, the TV show.
What's Luther?
Luther.
With Idris Elba?
Yeah, you ever seen Luther with Idris Elba?
No, no, no, no. I was thinking Luther.
That's what I draw in my relaxer for whenever I'm painting and drinking wine.
and I was throwing on some Lutheran, Sir Paino,
I had wifey pull out the watercolors, because last time was a digital
painting guy. Yeah, yeah, now I'm going for a first of all. This is my warm up
painting just to get me all ready.
Okay, let's let's hear a description. An artist statement guys, this
I don't even know what to call this. This came to me in a dream
that I had two nights ago. I have no idea. It's some kind of purple
kind of
weirdly tired fruit almost and it's saying member wow yeah, and as you see on
the back, I was started a little more ambitiously
a bunch of
and I gave up and I just did one. We'll call it a member Barry y'all wow, but
that's what I came up with that yeah. I came up with this is that's amazing. My
original thing it looks great and he basically would say
member fourth meal, that kind of thing
anyway.
I love the sound of your paintings. Yeah,
Thank you. Guys, and here it is. Here is my painting of the red planet itself. There is
Mars.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Wait, what is this right here?
Mars.
There's a little black dot.
There's stars and stuff. What are you saying black dot?
Right here.
That? Oh my God. You are so fucking right. There is a little black dot on here.
That looks like a person. That looks like a stick figure.
let's take out our magnifying glass and get a little bit of a closer look.
How's that sound? Yeah. Okay. I need to see
who's that?
Who's that? Oh, wait, that's me. That's me on the surface of Mars painting my
member berries photo on the surface.
There I am guys. Oh my God, this is an incredible pain. This is incredible.
This is very oh my God. You can't have a full head of hair and I like
wait,
hold on okay, sorry, I just like to point out Patrick Patrick says you have a
full head of hair. I'm also on Mars man, who cares if I have a head hair corner
that's my that's like my artist name is Michael. It's my middle name.
I thought you're all I thought your middle. I thought your artist name was
DJ something you're holding a knitting needle. I'm holding a paint brush. I
change it. They're all called my they all have Michael on the bottom. Okay,
But yeah, it's been up to a couple hours to do this.
- Looks great.
- Yeah, it looks good.
- We're gonna have to put these up.
- I got those gray sweatpants on, you see that?
- Yeah, I can see.
- Your cock print is immense.
- You're wearing a Nike Flytech.
- It's obviously got me salivating a little bit.
- Yeah, I got the Nike Tech on.
- Nike Tech.
- I should have put the Nike Tech on my...
- Oh, you should have put the Nike Tech on,
then Ice Spice would have hit you up after seeing this.
- Do you guys think I'm a good drawer?
- I literally wanna run my fingers
through that matted curly hair
and lift you up by your pube hair.
- Really?
this man Jesus Christ, drawing got me that's completely a certain type of way
that's sexual as hell, but
the redness of the planet. I don't know yeah had to get a closer look at this.
Who's this hunk down there on the anyway? These are going to be for sale. I
literally want to make you shoot a hunk of sperm, the junk of red. Honestly,
we're in the hot shower together. You shot so much jizz and it congealed into
a brick. I've been thinking about freezer. I've been thinking about
well, actually it's hot. I've been thinking about fucking you guys again.
yeah, that's been coming back into my mind Mars. Mars is
bringing each other together with these planets. I think I was thinking that I
was going to have a zoom in and it was going to be Patrick kind of like like
doing me, but I didn't want it to be disrespectful to him and I knew it was
going to go on YouTube, but Patrick, I do straight up want you to do me man. I
just got to say that it's kind of put that out here. I want you to do me day
to day two of week two. I think we might see a doing painting. I mean on
Patreon you know. Oh here's what I'll do from now on the YouTube ones will be
stuff like this. The Patreon ones are going to be in SFW. That's right. That's
right.
If you know what I'm talking about, so maybe next time I'll just do Patrick
just with his thing out.
You better you better not why
overdo it. You know you bet I better if you're putting my thing. If you're
going to painting of me of my thing out, you better not use your imagination.
okay. I want it to be do what you should do. You should do a dry rubbing of his
penis, like when you find a leaf in the forest and you're like the Vietnam
Memorial.
Oh yeah, I would like to do that. Oh yeah, I know you're talking about when
you see a name you think is funny. So yeah, you rub on it. So you rub the name
so you take your fingers and you rub it really fast. It's named like Michael
Riblet or something. When you see a name that you don't like, so you try to
scratch it and rub it out with your fingers. Try to scratch it out of the
Memorial. Yeah, you put a piece of paper over it and then you put charcoal down.
Yeah.
God, I'm sorry. I'm just lost in my beautiful...
It's a good painting.
Yeah, I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna hang this one.
Yeah?
Yeah, this one.
Do we have thumbtacks?
No.
I'm gonna hang it up over this.
Okay.
All right. He's taking down... It's a painting of Cyrodiil. Now, can you... I do want to
keep this. I've had this since... I've had this for a while. He's now hanging up his
painting.
So do you guys think we're going to reach Mars and our spaceships? I think
that we will and how long I don't know. Has there already been a mission to
Mars? No, man, you weren't the Mars. Mankind hasn't reached surface as it
reached. Well, I mean, is there a mission that like they launched the jet
right now? I'm sorry, a space ship. Have they launched a space ship now and
they're going to get there in a couple of years?
No, because of the space travel. No, they have not even I mean they've put
rovers on Mars that curiosity rover. Elon wants to do it, but Elon also wants
to build like a bunch of fucking trains or something. Elon wants to turn
Twitter into a bank, I'm sorry, X into a world bank. I think that Elon might
be able to get the first man on Mars if he stayed off the dope.
Yeah. Let's just look this up.
Stop going on Rogan. Elon, stop going on Rogan and stop smoking weed. You
have no time to enjoy yourself. Rogan is a bad influence on you, Elon. Stop
trying to enjoy yourself. You need to commit your life to sciences. It's
fucked up list of missions to missings to Mars successful mission. There have
been a bunch of successful missions, but no human kind.
They put a bunch of rovers in route. Wait, who's in what psyche? Well,
there's no but a psych that's not a person. Oh yeah, they're saying psych.
It's not actually there. It's just a fly by a gravity assist. Okay, oh,
whatever. Yeah, it's kind of I kind of hope that we'll be able to be the first
man on Mars. Yeah, I don't want to go to Mars, man. I want to visit Mars. It has
an odd atmosphere and it would be hard to live there, but I feel like we would
befriend the Martians. Yeah, or if and then if we failed to befriend them, I
feel like we could probably eradicate them with the common cold or the
norovirus. Are those the same thing? Well, they'd probably give us some crazy
Martian disease. No, we would use hand sanitizer. A virus is a stomach. Yeah, we
would give one of those. Oh, the rhino virus is the cry no virus. I don't mean
knows you all. I've been getting into learning the meanings of words. You have
to actually. What was it to etymology? Marci no, I'm so into etymology because
the thing is, Latin is always, always what I'm thinking of our genus of alien.
Sorry, you knew immediately what it meant. You know what it made, but it
makes me think I think the reason that I want to know all the words that
the reason I want to know all the names of the words or
the reason I want to know well anyway, you know what I'm saying now,
because of the names of dinosaurs, oh,
because that's all they all have name like they all the names all mean big
way and big wings or spiky wings or what would your dinosaur name be
probably
Maximo P Nassius, Maximo P Nassius yeah. What the hell is P Nus? What's the
Latin Root?
big peen because of his hard shell. He would be a dinosaur, the hard show be
like an inkyla source. I don't know. I'm saying if they found your bones yeah and
they were like this dine is they nobody would guess based on your skeleton that
you had a peanut. When I die, I will have a shell, maybe a peanut. By the time I
die, I will have I will have a shell around my body. Yeah, I don't think so. I
know him. I know him pretty well. He will I'm go. I've been working on getting a
genetically certification. Something has been wrong with me. I can't focused on
words that you're trying to create new words. I can't, I keep saying things that
don't make any sense. You're becoming a wordsmith. I keep, I think I keep having
some type of mini stroke that lasts for weeks, that keeps coming and going. I
already told you guys about how I couldn't remember how to tie my shoes.
Yes. Okay, good. You told me, so I feel like that happens to you a lot, though.
That does happen a lot. No, it fully happened to me where I think I definitely
had a mini stroke, which I think is caused by probably energy drinks and
nitrites from all the bacon that I'm eating. Too much damn bacon. I remember...
I'm putting bacon on everything. I was thinking about nitrites 'cause we were
talking about them, and I remember my grandpa telling me when I was little,
before I knew really what nitrites or a heart attack or anything like that
really meant, he was like, "My doctor said that I have to cut down on eating
bacon, but I'd rather die than not eat bacon and I was like what are you
talking about? What does that mean? Everyone
you'd rather die, not even does not understanding what the link between
those two things could be. Yeah, it's a crazy thing to say to also everyone
always
he wants to
he's going to eat bake until he dies. People always say that, but then you
start fucking dying and yeah
no, do you like salt? Yeah, what
Okay, salt is good though, but you can't switch to like turkey bacon or
something. You'd rather die. Have you seen this stuff? New salt? It's like
sodium bromide or some shit. The fuck are you talking about? It's science.
I saw a thing called NU salt. Mars is making you war like. Yeah. Me? It's
making you pretty much... Combative and war like. It's not salt too. That's a
movie with Angelina Jolie. Oh shit. It's called NU salt. Oh, new like new
metal like yeah,
salt to I don't think that this is
clicking on the wrong. Yeah, you're
obsessed with salt right now in you
salt and you
new salt. So you suck. You're the
word. This is in you in you say
your favorite say your favorite fact
about Mars right now. I bet he
doesn't even have one. I bet you
don't have a single one. Oh, there.
Yeah, I saw this at the store the
other substitute.
You can't even speak just has no
sodium or something. I think it is.
Yeah, sodium free salt, potassium chloride instead of sodium chloride.
Salt is good for you man, you have to have salt to live.
Salt is a basic building block of life.
Do they have salt on Mars?
They have salt on Mars.
They have water, so they probably might have salt on Mars.
I feel like they have to have salt on Mars.
At the very least they have rocks.
Do they have lettuce on Mars?
No, they have radishes and rutabagas though.
Okay, beets?
Did you guys ever see that movie, The Martian?
Oh my God, the contributing factor to the redness of the planet.
the planet. It's all beats. Oh my God, that is guys, because God ate a bunch of
beastly shat Mars. Oh, that's not how he made the planets. That's how he made
Mars, specifically Mars, because Mars, I didn't know something I learned when I
was doing my planet report research. I had no idea Mars was so small. I thought
it was the same size as Earth. I thought it was the second smallest. What the
hell if you don't count Pluto? What the fuck? What's smaller than Mercury? Yeah,
Mercury is this Mercury is the smallest. Oh, we're going to smaller than that, but
planet. They kicked it out. They kicked it out. It's too small. There's a dwarf
planet. We are...
Yeah, sorry, man. No, no, no. I keep... Alright, you know what? I know what will
bring us back on track. Yeah. Oh, I know what will.
So,
you wanna introduce this? You guys,
we promised it on the premium episode.
We promised that there would be
a collab, a collaboration track.
combination combination. This is a collaboration track between OJ, the
alien and Dr. Dazzle and before you play it, I just want to say I haven't
heard this yet. I don't know what it's about, but what I did hear
apparently there were some people like picketing the recording studio and Dr.
Dazzle was recording his verse and apparently something made them really
mad. The hell's wrong with Dr. Dazzle? Everybody likes him. I don't know,
yeah, everybody likes him, but apparently he did something really wrong
during the song. So it must be something about, he must have said something
about Mars. I don't know what it like. I guess it's got to be about
Mars. The whole song is called Wise Guys on Mars.
Oh, he probably just talked about crime.
Yeah, maybe that's what it is.
It's usually so positive.
So let's hear it.
Roll it. Play that boom before.
Oh wait, start it over.
In space prison, dinner was always a big thing.
We had a galactic pasta course and then we had an alien meet.
Pauly did the prep work.
He was doing a year for space contempt.
He had this wonderful system for doing the space garlic.
He used to light sabers.
He used to slice it so thin that he used to liquefy in the pan with just a little grease oil.
It's a very good system.
Once upon a time on a planet so far, me and Dr. Dazzle were just hitting the spar.
When this alien chick, she pulled up in a flar.
She says, "Hey wise guys, come on, let's go to Mars."
So we did, we hopped in her car
That's an alien model, it's a flying kind of car
It doesn't run on gas, it runs on rocks called cars
A car is a fuel that goes in a flask
So we pull up to the mobile to get some gars
When out pops a guy who has guns for arms
So we shot his ass and we hit him with the flask
And once again, a car is not a flask
Wise guys
We have Tommy Guns
We're on Mars
We have flying cars
Now me and OJ own this Mars operation
Underneath the nose of the Galactic Federation
Running kaggots at the Robot Casino
Wearing sunglasses like Robert De Nino
Space caddy and Mars balls with gravy
Camel life on Moon V by Martians, Corsace
Green Street stays on the rotation daily
A planet's rotation is how long it's may be
Mars years are longer, almost two-fold
So if I was on Mars, I'd be on Mars
Almost two-fold, so if I was on Mars I'd be twelve years old
Smoking Mars, pearl golds and sippin' on the moonshine
Fuckin' on adult women in the boom time
Every time the moon is up I'm in the motel
The women have to book the rooms 'cause I'm twelve
We'll do it all again, I know all the styles
I'm a sexual machine that turns women into pedophiles
Big smile, but we know how to use it
Turn down the gravity, throw on some music
Give her my bean and make her scream
Even though she's twenty-eight and I'm not even a teen
Do it on the couch, PG movie on the road, cool
Cushions get so wet that it feels like tofu
Hid it from orbit 'til the atmosphere smells
I am twirling
Wise guys
We have gone into space
We're on Mars
We have flying cars
Oh my fucking god, man
As far back as I can remember
I always wanted to be a wise guy on Mars
(laughter)
- OJ the alien.
Dr. Dazzle.
- Wow.
That is a...
(laughter)
God, I mean, that's a masterpiece, man.
I'm gonna be honest.
That was, that blew my fucking mind.
- I don't know why people were mad at Dr. Dazzle's verse.
I think maybe--
Yeah, because he said, "Oh, I'm 12 years old."
Nobody who gets mad, that's victim blaming.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I think the thing that people were maybe mad at was that he's...
So he'd be 24 on earth.
Right.
So then the women are 48, so they are 57?
No.
No?
56.
Yeah.
Well, you have to hope, yeah, I guess that he's talking about the Mars age of the women.
so he'd be so people are upset that it's the Mars age, which there's also already
an age gap, but then I think maybe they were upset about the age gap.
It was an age gap thing. I think it was like a Leonardo DiCaprio.
He's 56 year old women having sex with a 24 year old. But why would they picket
the recording studio of Dr. Basil? I guess they just thought... I mean,
there was something unsavory, I guess they thought about. They thought maybe
the content was not typical for his usual... Are these SJW types that are
picketing this because if so, we can basically ignore everything.
They're saying, yeah, maybe, maybe it's SJW. Okay, so it's just people
getting basically triggered, but... SJW, space jumping... Because they don't
believe in space. Space jumping warlocks, man. Space jumping warlocks. Yeah.
Which is a scary thing that you have to dodge in your alien astronaut
space... When you do alien type of songs. Yeah. I guess I do
kinda wish that Dr. Dazzle maybe talked a little bit more about the
wise guy stuff. He seems like he kinda went off topic, but... He did.
there's another I guess that is true. I mean it didn't have that much to do with
being a wise guy except for the hook brings it back. Yeah, I guess Tommy guns
yeah right yeah, but there is another verse that wasn't recorded. That's
mostly about floors and what a floor and what a floor is and basically the
history of the floor Mars bars about that. It was like about the floors. Let
me tell you something about these things called floors back in twenty thirty three.
They replaced all cars
continue.
And also they discovered these things called guards. They were rocks and they
go into flowers.
Okay, so it's basically the exact same as the other. But then it goes into the
history. I think maybe the right OJ the alien only got a little bit. The
flowers wars through. Yes, there's the flowers wars and then the you know all
that stuff. But then there was these space jumping warlocks inside the studio
that were protesting and picketing and he said fuck it is needs to go out right
right yeah. We need to show this song was originally going to be four minutes
long and they were like no, we need to it needs to be drop it drop it. Now
this is the single cut it. I'm curious. How does OJ the how did OJ the only get
linked up with Dr. Dazzle? It seems like they're in completely different
planetary communication yeah well, Dr. Dazzle, I'm not asking about how they
talk to each other, like if I said how did doja cat and pink man and chat rooms,
shouted ice yeah. You don't say oh they talked on the phone. If I say how these
two people mean, well that's probably how they did that probably is how they
linked up man, but who's not like they what do you think they just teleported
into each other's rooms. I'm just wondering I had to make plans. Why did
they who reached out to who? Why did they collaborate? I heard that I heard
that OJ the alien asked Dr dazzle to hop on yeah.
I think that's what it was so OJ watched our I think that I don't yeah. I think
like OJ probably was thinking is like oh, Dr. Dazzle famously dresses in all green.
That's one of the main facts. Oh, true.
He wears that one jacket. Yeah, the green jacket. Yeah, so he probably was like
this guy even looks like an alien a little bit. Yeah, if this jacket was his
skin, he probably thought he was an alien. And it's probably also a thrilling
contrast to the red colour of Mars. Yeah, same with OJ the alien, who was a green
alien. Yeah, and he was probably even thinking us green guys can make a song
about red Mars, because if it's, listen, if it's about wise guys, there's a, and
it's in the one thousand and twenty. So there's a chance it's going to be black
and white man. Yeah. Oh yeah. No, there's no difference. Yeah. It's kind of
combining the two. It's combining the something that like they used to do in
hip hop a lot where they would put
they would put like samples from like mob movies, gangster movies, stuff like
that. Like they put Scarface stuff in music and then they would have like a
string section kind of Scott Storch style. Yeah. The sample from Moonfellows
was really sick. Yeah, the sample for Moonfellows is very good. So then it's
combining that with the new space age style rap that OJ the Alien does. So it's
basically what this song is, is it's bringing the past and the future together.
Right, and that's, that's the ethos behind Wise Guys, old on Mars, future,
which is a thing that
everybody wanted. Yeah. Everybody wanted to see Wise Guys on the planet Mars. I
the man, it's one of the things Cowboys versus aliens, yep, aliens versus
predators, yep, we haven't seen a combination or on Mars mafia and aliens
that much. There was one combination of
maybe like
not mafia, but yeah, I guess the mafia is in it is a little movie called Pluto
Nash,
which may have been the inspiration for
There's an Eddie Murphy movie from 2003 where he goes to a space casino and I
think he's a, he has to deal with the space mob. Oh shit. Like Robert De Nino?
Robert De Nino, but Luis Guzman is in it as well. Luis Guzman. He's Buzz Alien?
And I'm pretty sure Joe Piscopo is in it. I don't remember if I know this movie
that well. Luis Guzman is always typecast as an alien or a mushun. He is always an
alien. Or himself in Community. Can you, can you look up Pluto, The Adventures of
Pluto Nash. I need to remember some stuff about this.
That's a good name for a guy who spends much of his time in space.
Yeah. Pluto Nash. Oh, 2002.
That's like me being called New York.
Oh, Joe Pantoliano, not Piscopo.
Joey Piscopo.
Joey Pants is fire, man.
And Joey Moore. Yeah.
Miguel A. Nunez Jr.
This had a pretty stacked cast for 2002.
Yeah, Rosario Dawson.
I Lena Douglas from
and dating Martin's Corsetta plays Doug yeah. There's all types of people in
this movie man yeah, all all different types of levels of fame, like Olga
Golova Nova,
and Vladimir Vicro, yeah, Olga Golova Nova was in in Pluto Nash
real martian that she was in turbos every zimney,
yeah, and turbos and Mr Pranka.
I know Mr Pranka the fuck is Mr Pranka. I know Mr Pranka and
no, they have a really bad bunch of movies in Russia. I think man that's
why they are so they're lashing out and making fake McDonald's and shit because
they didn't grow up with the movies. We grew up with man. Well, they have these
bunked up movies. We got Mr. Deeds, they got Mr. Pranka. Every Russian movie is
about like a piece of rice that runs away or something. It's not ever happy.
They let art get into their movies a little too much. Yeah, they basically...
They kind of dodged commercialism a little too much. Yeah, like Pluto Nash
has like a million different types of
Las Vegas puns and stuff. Yeah, but you see, like you ever... You see,
and I don't know if you guys have probably seen all these old Russian,
the Soviet cartoons that people always post, the Soviet animations, and it's
always about a wiggling man, yeah, running away from his wiggling doctor,
yeah, and it's all basically that everything is always about going to the
doctor with these.
How many times you go to the fucking doctor? If you live in Russia, they
probably literally already have a wiggling show in the US. It's called
home movies and there's no doctors in it at all. It's about kids. There was
one wiggling doctor. Yeah, come on, doctor cat, doctor cat. Yeah, well, but
they don't even have therapy, but he's a therapist. That's not a doctor, not a
doctor. And by the way, in Russia, they only have doctors. They don't have
specialists. No, there's no... The doctor is the therapist, technically. Yeah.
But you walk in and you say,
"I have ADHD and also I need to have my legs sawed off." And he does both.
I need to have my legs sawed off 'cause I keep getting distracted by the
boil in my foot. You go... In Russia, if you go to the doctor and
you tell them you're depressed, they'll prescribe you one pill. And guess what?
It's a lead pill and it's fired out of a gun at your fucking head.
Holy shit, wait, that's actually bloody crazy. If you dare to break conformity by
having anxiety over there, they will little or rolly put you in buried in the
ice. And here's what I fucking hate about all these kids walking around in the
United States saying, "Yeah, man, I want to be a communist and I want to walk
around with my hammer and sickle and a book or whatever." Like, dude, look at
Russia. Look what's going on in communist Russia. What are they doing?
Russia used to look like Miami. Russia in the 1960s- And then they got- then they
just to have women would be now they now they got communism. Everybody's got a
now. It's like the damn thing, bro. I heard saying I heard that in in Soviet
Russia, Soviet Communist Russia, I heard that in Communist Russia, which it
already still, which it already still is. I heard that the TV watches you.
That's horrifying. I fucking hate communism. I know I'm supposed to be
watching the TV. I'm supposed to be and now I have to do interesting stuff all
days. Yeah,
my whole life entertaining my TV. What the hell kind of backwards bullshit is
this man is backwards as fuck isn't it? It is kind of reverse. I heard the cars
drive you as well. Yeah, the cars drive and one of the most horrifying things I
heard that in in Soviet Russia. Actually, I could defeat Chuck Norris.
But let me stop you there, not even in Soviet Russia. Do you have a chance to
get? Why do you look at me like that? Say fat chance at chance that show
Cameron, that's so rude, a fat camera and I know what your subtext is there.
When you say fat chance, what's you versus fast Norris fat Cameron,
fast Norris, fast Norris, so you don't stand a chance yeah man, it's so
fucked up over. You could have said my chances were skinny or narrow or
something like that. I'm say fat chance, fat as fucking a
I BMI chance,
fat fatty and plus a chance
but that's a snore that's not annoying me and Julio were on a quiz website or we
took a quiz to questionnaire to get signed up for a I to the whiz that's
white
machine that fixes erectile dysfunction by using sonic waves. I want to get in
that we asked you for your height and weight and the
weight was three hundred pounds
was one foot six.
that
default, they said it they you click on next page and it auto fills in one foot
six and that'd be a oh. I had a great hypothetical that I discussed with a lot
of my friends the other day. Yeah. Would you rather be
like a five out of ten or four out of ten face, but you're six foot five or
would you rather be a ten out of ten, but you're three and a half feet tall.
That is a good in the face.
you your three your face is three and a half feet. No, no, no fuck you, you're
you said in the face in the face, yeah, a ten in the face. If I had a
fighting, I have three and a half face. No, you guys are okay. So this is a new
hypothetical. Would you rather have a six foot tall face or a three and a half
foot tall? Probably a three and a half, but what if the rest of your body is a
hundred feet tall? So then the six foot probably wouldn't matter very much.
What I pick either. Well, it actually kind of would man and what all the size
almost always double the size, no matter what size your body. Yeah, what no
three is half of six man. That's what I mean, but it'd be it'd be a little bit
better than having three. If you had a hundred foot tall body, I feel like if I
was a hundred feet tall, I'm not good. The three feet is not going to bother me
much. Either way, the six if I was in you got other problems going on yeah,
yeah, I mean I'd be concerned that, but what you're asking man that's like
walking. That's like being the kind of guy who walks around says I'm six foot
one and a half or something. I'd be very, very concerned. My head's actually six foot and
a half feet instead of three. I know it. If I'm 100 feet tall, I go pee somewhere, that's
a tsunami. No, you have your current penis. Oh, then I have a really big problem. I have
a really big proportional problem. But you have the bladder of 100 and urethra of 100
foot. You want your current size penis because there's no 100 foot woman. Well, there might
might be who knows that might be part of the hypothetical that I come up with
your most likely probably going to have to end up fucking a normal sized woman
or an ellen, not going to want a big giant, you know, ten foot long penis or a
way from the
because I'm not having if I'm one hundred feet tall, I'm not having sex for
pleasure. I'm sure it would hurt at some you're not having sex for pleasure. Why
would it hurt your sex drive will be gone? No, my sex drive will be
completely gone. I'm not seeing it. You know I would not have a libido at all.
That's true because yeah, because everybody's an ant to you, you're not
kind of ants like I want to fuck that and I have a question. I have a question
what would your phone be big your phone? Yeah, you get to keep your phone the
sit, okay, and I'm comfortable size. Then I look at sex or will picks on my
phone. You can't masturbate because your penis is human size. Then you have
these giant hand. You're just like I'm not even human anymore is what you're
saying you're
no, it's kind of hard giant. You're big on the hard. I was like ten twelve feet
tall. You're you're literally a hundred feet tall with a three foot head.
is the hypothetical that I was talking to my friends about.
So yeah, I guess well now it is it was a completely different. It was a
different question completely, but would you be okay? Here's the new
hypothetical.
Would you be a hundred foot tall with a three foot head?
No, if you had to oh yeah, I had to yeah yeah, I would if I had to if I had
the choice, if there's no other option, yeah, if there's no other option, I
would be yeah, I guess I would I wouldn't
Wow all right, just my kind of thing. Yeah, that's all right, but do you think
that
that guy would have more fun on Mars? No, you guys ever heard about the face on
Mars speaking about? Yes, I have. What's the face of Mars? They have a face on
Mars. They have a giant face on Mars. Let me see this. Pull up the face of
Mars. There's a ongoing scientific theory that Mars is a head. I heard that
scientist, not actually a planet at all, it's a floating head. Can I run a, can I
run a late night joke by you guys? Yeah, I'm putting in my packet. Whoa, so
apparently Elon Musk is putting together a Mars expedition. Yeah, he
wants to yassify the face on Mars. Oh, wow!
Wow, yeah, that's... You think that could be funny on a TV show? I think
that general audiences would understand that, yeah. He wants to yassify the
face on Mars. Whoa! Okay, that looks like a bear. And Elon Musk would say,
"Yeah, we're going to look at pedo bear on the face of Mars." 'Cause that's
what that actually does look like. He wants to yassify pedo bear, 'cause that
it kind of does look like pedo bear. Pedo bear would have a better time if he was
yesified. I never understood what makes his bear such a pedo. He has he probably
has actions. Yeah, it's mostly his molestations. But he's a toon, man. He is
a he is a pedophile. He's a simple toon. We you know what we need? We need a
friend who's a meme historian who we can call at any hour of the day. He can tell
us the entire history. Bring it in like Pawn Stars. Yeah. Hey, take a look at
this.
Can you tell me everything about this? That's actually David the Gnome. This
photo of this ugly woman. David the Gnome. That's actually David the Gnome.
It was a meme that only lasted for a year in 2010. This is very rare.
Please show me socially awkward penguin facts. I need to hear socially awkward
penguin by the low down gang. Don't look up socially awkward penguin. Not you.
Well, I guess Jubio kinda is a meme story. We're looking up too much stuff,
man. It's too much. Yeah, it needs to be about... It needs to be stopped.
We are about Mars today. We are exiting Mars's orbit, I will say.
we are exiting the orbit. Let's go back into the orbit just for the last little
bit. Okay,
tell me about it, man.
Well, I mean, I brought up face on Mars. I'm trying to think of something else.
They have ice caps. I mean, that gets very cold. They have ice ice spice.
They're looking for water as well. Red hair. There could be water underground.
I spice as a Mars.
You keep rubbing your penis against my leg, man. That's the thing about okay,
so everybody's so everybody's so obsessed with if we find find life in this
reservoir of water that's on Mars. Yeah, but dude, I don't give a fuck if a
fish is on another planet. It's not even gonna be a fish man. It will be a
dot. That's a dot of course, but even a lot of dots biggest fucking thing ever
would be that there's a fish on Mars. Yeah, I don't give a shit about I guess
a dot. Well, it wouldn't look like our fish and it would be interesting to see
it would be as if you were watching one of those nature documentaries where they
say, can you believe this is an animal? But what if it did look exactly like our
fish. What if it just looked like a fucking tuna? I guess that wouldn't be
so exciting if they found something that looked exactly the same. If they found
a tuna on Mars. I guess, yeah, if you take the... That'd be more exciting.
But if you find a dot, that means that one day it'll evolve. I could believe
that they're, that we find an octopus on Mars. Into a circle. Yeah, it's probably
gonna be a seven legged squid or something. Yeah. Do you guys believe that
octopi came from another planet? No. No. I do.
Okay. I believe that. That's cool, I guess. And I also believe in
mechanicals all life came from other planet. I think it's true. I think that
the big bang they said that they said not that right. No, I said that they
said that all life comes from a different planet. Yeah, no dude. They
said who said that Steve Jobs.
No, he didn't man. Steve Jobs said that what is what if somebody who's a
completely not a scientist at all, but like has just has a very high standing
and maybe seems like a smart person like Steve Jobs or someone like that did like
a press conference and made a huge announcement, just like they have set
we're now announcing that all life comes from another plan to set something
completely wrong. We have discovered life on every planet in the entire
universe, somebody who you're like you seen you're like well. I don't really.
I guess I don't know why he would lie right. Did this seems like maybe he
would be someone who would know about that? I get maybe yeah, sure, probably a
little yeah Carson daily, okay, I guess yeah, I guess I trust. I guess I trust
I know I got a lie. I mean I've been a really man you news. Okay, I'm a
scientist or like Steve jobs is lying. He's not going to believe and then
yeah yeah and then see jobs is like the scientists are lying. Steve job
basically versed science in his last couple moments. He wife anyway. He
verse sides versus juice yeah and juice science y'all science low key molly
walked him no because it remember he said I bet if I drink juice every day,
I'll fucking die
and they were like you have cancer. The juice is what's killing you and he
I'd prove it bitch. Yeah, he started the Jews thing before he found out about
cancer.
I bet you I'll die. Give me cancer. I bet you I'll get cancer and die in one
year. If all I eat is juice, all I drink is apple juice. They said okay man,
knock yourself out. He's like I told you, has it been released? I bet you
guys and I
has it been released a full regimen as an I bet you an iPad. Now I got a
I
I bet you an iPad. I fucking die of cancer from drinking juice in one year.
Yeah,
they released his full regimen of what types of juices he was drinking. He was
drinking like green juice, like pineapple. He was drinking a lot of
pineapple, I think, but he was trying to make that less lowly apple juice. It's
just fucking, just like metal and just
not even fruit. It's just juice of like metal juice. It's oil. Juicing his
t-shirt.
putting it in like a big big. I've tried all the fruits. The fruits are working.
I'm over all the fruit. I've tried the bed. I have to try the fruit of the loom
my underwear. I'm going to drink my underwear, the juice of my underwear.
I've tried the meats. I've tried the fishes. What else is there? Fish,
even eat meat man. He drank clam juice. Well, you think you have meat would have
saved him. He combined he made he made it would have fully saved him man. It
actually would have I think I think that meat say yeah. What do you think? Do you
think he held strong to the last day. Do you think maybe on he was dying, his
soul was completely leaving his body and getting uploaded to the cloud, a little
computer joke and he was and he was like fuck shit. It wasn't it was me
all along man. The veggies gave me
kind of man. It was the pesticides man. Yeah, you do in the GMO beef could have
saved me. He had this juice cocktail that he was doing, though he did actually
like
there's like a lot of like different supplements. Like he had like tomato
juice and clam juice and vodka and celery and a whole chicken and
it's just
a bloody Mary
with a doughnut on it.
A huge celery. That's why
that's a big Caesar. Bottomless mimosas.
he got prescribed hair of the dog man yeah
hair of the tumo hair of the tumo kind of old. I really wonder what his last
thought was before he died. If he was his last thought was probably man, I
should have I should have well, we
made
my computers look too clean and I pod with two screens. I spent my whole life
making tell them tell them to take away the
the headphone port.
They need to get rid of that light. He just completely
he's dying and he's like he's seeing like fucking like like biblic accurate
angels and he's like the world is like psychedelic. He's completely delirious.
He's like fully nothing is making sense in his in his world at all. He's his
brain is firing random electrical pulses and he just says no head phone,
important
the CEO for about one more minute. So we have to do it. I guess we got to do it
man, whatever just standing there or Tim Cook's, and he's like what you say to
head phone, no headphone
oh, that's a good idea yeah. He wants to get rid of the headphone port. I
would have loved it. He saw he saw he was hallucinating and he saw a human
head having sex with a telephone and he said headphone porn
okay.
All right, Steve,
I got to do it. We already sealed your will and it's notarized or whatever we
can't say, but you know what we'll we'll for make an exception just for you.
We're going to we're going to scribble this in there.
Poor Steve Jobs, yeah, well, whatever well, him and beautiful gone, you'll see
him in beautiful heaven, a Los Angeles. Oh yeah way speaking of beautiful heaven,
what's more beautiful than Malibu, California and right next door to that
is Los Angeles, California and in Los Angeles. There's a venue called the yard
I will be at next week on Friday, November 17th, with my buddy Gus Viveiros, doing 30
minutes of stand-up. I wrote about two minutes so far, so this is going to be a really fucking
amazing show. We're doing two shows.
You want some of my jokes?
Yeah, give me one of your jokes right now.
Okay. I wrote this new one.
Okay.
You could go up immediately, get on stage, right?
Immediately? Okay, immediately get on stage.
Right when you're, like Gus introduces you.
That's a good start to a joke.
Gus introduces you.
You immediately get on stage.
You walk out, you're waving to everybody. You say, "Yeah, I just flew in here from New York,
market boys, my ass tired because I flew in here from all the farts propelling my
ass. I although I farted all the way here. I feel like my if I was far
iterating fart, if I was generating farts enough to propel me across the
country, I would think my mouth would get tired before my ass from eating all
of the propellant.
No, but the fart okay, wait, I have a I just I just thought of which I thought
of a joke. You could do you could try to go over your head. It'll be like this
sometimes maybe like observational style comedy. I'd be like why why do they
call the why do they call them, but cheeks is it because my butt is like a
mouth.
I could go up immediately and say you guys are like go up and first go up
immediately get up on stage immediately. No intro, no in just get up immediately
and say we're going to start five minutes. Why they call my channel, why
do they call them, but she is it because I'm there's a smile between them yep and
you mind putting your face in between you guys know me. I'm dirty jessling style.
I'd go up and I'd say I call him butt cheeks. I store a year's worth of nut in
him like a fucking shit. You say why they call it butt cheeks because my butt is
because my butt has a Hitler mustache.
I say no it doesn't, but then I pull it out my pants and it does or you could if
you want to get really nasty. I mean you could just or you could be like why do
they call these cheeks? It's because they look like butt cheeks. It's because
all that I eat. My mouth is like an asshole. It's called Cheeks is all the
shit that comes out of my mouth. Okay, yeah, this is see we're getting
somewhere anyway. If you want to see stuff like that, he's going to workshop
this with you on workshop that I got probably four hundred abortion jokes.
I'm doing come on through man. This subscribe to the Patreon. If you would
like to get access to the next part of the five weeks of planets will be
Jupiter
premium episode for Jupiter coming up coming up right this week on day two of
planetary week and I want to thank the beautiful city of Chicago and if you
are the best city I've ever done a show. What day is the shareholder meeting
who we are? What day did you say for us to do that? I don't remember
I think the fifteenth, not the fifteenth. It was definitely not. No, it's the
twenty first. We said it was the twenty first twenty first twenty first
twenty first. I'm on a show. Go ahead and subscribe to the patron at the
executive producer tier. If you want to see the shareholder meetings, which are
fun little thing we do where we have we do some presentations and some Q and a
it is basically a monthly zoom show that we do for you and make sure to join the
discord. If you subscribe to that tier to be able to get access, you'll be able
to and this is my phone. That's my phone and my girlfriend's name is almost done.
Y'all. Hello. Hey mom, it's me. Get off the phone with my fucking mom. It's me.
Patrick, get on me a pic. Whatever, whatever man. All right. Happy planets.
Happy planets.
(static)
- If you couldn't tell, we're dressed up like Venus today.
Although we had some amount of disagreement, I guess,
over what color Venus is.
- That's okay, I got both going on.
- You do have both, but what's this black wig about, man?
- Well, we'll go down that.
You want me to start with my costume?
- Yes, I want you to start. - Are you dressed up
as Coraline?
- No.
(laughing)
I'm dressed up as V--
If I walked out on the street right now,
any person who knows literally who attended first grade
would know I'm dressed as Venus.
I think some people would think you were Coraline.
No, a first grader would look at me and say, "That's Venus."
No, they wouldn't.
A child who was into science and into movies,
who would have seen Venus in a movie.
Why did you say movies?
Of course, they'd say Coraline, man.
Well, Coraline's a book, too.
Around Halloween time, if they saw me in a costume like this,
they would say Venus.
They would say, "That's Coraline. She's very pretty today."
No, they wouldn't say that.
They would say, "I like Coraline's mustache."
Jumping off of pretty here,
venus is actually the name of the god is business is named after the goddess of
beauty
uh...
so i elected to put on a beautiful way today and then it was a really a little
raincoat my beautiful hair
cameras are asking about the yellow raincoat so let me explain this to you
venus
uh... big the color can be some people say it's yellow some bills a yellowish
white some people say beige
this raincoat is yellow definitely to yellow for venus some people but i would
say beige. I think two people would. Two people would say beige. But, Venus is surrounded by
sulfuric clouds. It has a sulfurous atmosphere, which is why it's that color. And in the upper
atmosphere, constantly acid rain. Oh. Wow. Wait. So you're dressed up like Coraline because
of rain. So that's the yellow, it's the yellow acid rain. And then I have a yellowish white
shirt here. Uh huh. This is kind of closer to the color I feel. You dressed up like Coraline.
And then, dude chill, I'm dressed up as Venus. I don't know why you guys are stuck on this
cor- I don't look anything like Coraline. You pull up a picture of Coraline it's going
to look completely different from what I'm wearing right now. I said Coraline though.
Yeah, you said Coraline. That's not, then you said a nonsense word and you're proud
of that. You're proud of making up a word. That's you man. That's, that's, that's your
I don't know what you're talking about guys.
I didn't try to dress up like this.
Oh no wait, no she has blue hair.
(BARKS)