*Badass music*
Okay, play it. Hit play. Hit play already.
And turn it up a little.
On the video.
Yeah, that's good.
Wait...
Hamburgers!
Hot dogs!
(upbeat music)
- Guys.
- It's the most important battle of the century.
- Welcome to the battle of the century.
- Hamburger.
- Versus.
- Hot dog.
- In one corner.
- Hamburger.
- In the other.
- Hot dog.
- Battling each other, the eternal battle.
- To the death.
- The clash of the Titans.
Whoever wins, we lose.
With these two foos, these foos are going to have to choose.
Between the twos.
Between these two foos.
Of whose we'll lose.
Yep.
And who will lose?
Who knows?
Probably yous.
But yous will soon.
That's what we're here to dissood.
We will dissood yous.
On the news.
Welcome everybody to the news.
And this is the news.
But yeah, basically, we've been hyping this up for a while, guys.
Uh-huh.
Okay, you can cut this.
We have two pages of...
Oh, we have notes.
Notes of things that we have to go over.
Here's how this shit's gonna work.
These are two...
There's a list of things that we gotta say.
Yeah, and we'll get into it soon enough, but basically, it's gonna be the hot dogs versus
the hamburgers.
Can I just get a real quick hot dog hamburger?
Oh, yeah.
Hot dog.
Hamburger.
we have our beautiful announcer here, five or higher, and we are going to be grading
every single...
That's what this is for.
We're going to be giving points, head to head battle.
Your job is giving points.
Yeah, I'm going to be the point master. Thank you. And we're going to figure out basically
which is better, hot dog versus hamburger. This is a debate as old as time itself.
Yeah, and we're here to solve it once and for all today, because this is one of those
things that this is kids in the schoolyard who would win who would every
I remember what was a their top five of the variants of the real quickly as the
judges. I feel like we need to give a little bit of a background back story on
our experience with hamburger hot dog. Yeah, who wait who remembers which one
they first? I think I hate a hot dog first. I'm not sure which one I you know
I probably would have to wager hot dog, but I have a pretty interesting history
period between this to I would say yeah. Really, I have a pretty strong bias
that I can't. I can't hide it. It will be revealed. I got to throw it out.
Go. I got to, you know, just disclaimer. Yeah. Well, what I remember is
important. One of my earliest hot dog memories. I remember eating a hot dog at
somebody's house, my mom's friend's house or something like that, and what
did I do with that hot dog? But I threw it all up. When I saw pieces of my hot
dog in my throw up and after that, I would not eat hot dogs for years after
that when I was a little one, and I also I also have a pretty strong history that
I'm sure you folks are aware of with the noble hamburger and the cheeseburger,
the burger fest, the burger fest is a family tradition of mine that has started
that started pretty soon after my parents divorce three years ago, a
burger fest, which is a great way to cope. If you're a man going through a
messy divorce with children, a great way to bring them all together, yeah,
burger, burger, burger, now and now that's a good point. I'm going to go
and you know I'm going to word the first point to burger because guys I would
argue well that you couldn't make a hot dog fest.
I mean if you have you ever heard of a sausage fest yeah, one point to each. Oh
my God, one point to each is nice. That's a good way to start it off. I
think all right, I'm liking your point. Drawing technique point technique is
amazing. You've given hot dog to L
hot dog and L. It's hard to why don't we move it? No, because in this camera
don't see it. Stop. All right. All right. I'm going to focus up now. I'm going to
stop fucking around. Yeah, I'm not going to have fun anymore. I know this isn't
fun. This shit isn't supposed to be fun. It is not fun at all. Listen, listen,
listen journalism. I exactly I disclosed I disclosed who I'm in the pocket of and
I'm going to be fair, but I need you guys to tell me your personal histories
to with hamburger and with hot dog. Well, I'm going to stay completely neutral on
the two. I'm going to say my first memory with I think the first memory I
remember is the shadow of a hot dog poking out in my bedroom when I was a kid. I saw
the shadow of a hot dog on the wall and it was kind of like a Batman type moment.
A cum moment?
No, cum to Jesus.
Are you saying you got molested?
No, I'm not saying I got molested. I'm saying I saw the shadow of a hot dog like Batman
seeing a shadow of a bat.
Are you saying shadow the hedgehog?
Wow, did he see the full bat? I don't know. I thought he saw the shadow of a bat on the moon.
No, he got attacked by bats. So you got attacked by a hot dog?
No, I was attacked by burgers, but I saw the shadow of a hot dog that saved me.
And there's nothing about molestation in this.
Why are you bringing up molesting on the hamburger vs. hot dog debate?
Well, you brought up the shadow of a hot dog on your bedroom wall as a child.
Yeah, which kind of makes it... it feels like that's what you're getting at.
And the way you were kind of laughing when you were saying it, it seemed like you were trying to...
Oh, no, I was imagining a hot dog style Batman. But what is the
shadow?
Shadow is because Batman is a different hero. That's a shadow is Batman. Also,
what do you you're saying? Like you like you bats are a bat man. What do
you say? A shadow is a man of the night. Is that what you just said?
Just move on. I just we're not going to get anywhere at all. We're not
even going to get anywhere. This actually makes the most sense to me is
what I was trying to say is what makes the most sense to you. This what you're
trying to say is that a hot a hot dog as Batman on a plate you're making no sense
you're something is something I feel like I just went crazy trying to puzzle
out. Can you answer? Did you actually say a hot dog or a shadow is the Batman of
the night or did I
falling asleep? I heard that to a shadow. I believe that I invented that in my
head. Shadow is the Batman of the night. I don't know what I said. All I know is
that now we're here.
Okay, you are you have something so wrong with you that it need we need more
research to figure this out. Okay, so my
hot
is guys. I ate a hot dog. First, I ate a hamburger, not until I was probably
seventeen years old. I ate veggie burgers. Here's what I used to eat.
Oh my God, that's... I ate veggie burgers.
Yep. I ate veggie burgers and I ate... My dad used to make... He used to grill
pieces of pineapple and put that on a bun for me.
Interesting. Try to trick me.
That's a different... Thinking it's a hamburger. Is that a new kind of...
I eat my God damn fruit. I hate fruit. Is that a new kind of contender,
pineapple on a bun. We'll worry about that later. No, that's like it's like a
Hawaiian trick. So that's a type of a trick. They do yeah, it's a trick. They
do
burger. That's like in the UK. When they say you want a burger chicken burger,
yeah, I got fucked me up man. That completely ruined you. I think she
lightning at them. Yeah, she's like a chicken burger. Yeah, what the fuck you
know? I think every every every announcer should have to do this before
any type of fight or match. They should have to see what their favorite team is.
what happened, what they thought about the exact for the entire life yeah,
both judges and announcers should have to disclose their you know. I guess
while I'm thinking about it, I do I feel like I kind of made my bias seem to
swing pretty strongly towards hamburgers, but I will say I've made infinitely more
hot dogs for myself than I ever have
so
I may seem pretty biased toward hamburgers, but I also do I do fuck
with the hot dog, heavy, the hot dogs. I just cleared up my ears from air hot
dogs,
heavy.
All right, so
let's jump right in here, as you can see before us, we have wow,
before we have hamburger and we have hot dog.
Now, what's the first thing here? The first question
Would aliens like it?
Oh my God!
Wait, I think we're going to go in the other order.
Wait, we're going actual alphabetical?
We're going in alphabetical. He's going reverse alphabetical.
That's what we agreed on.
Also, I don't see that anywhere in the list. I don't know what you're talking about.
That's in there. It's just...
Go alphabetical. We'll tackle that one later.
Okay, what's the first question? The first question about hamburger and hot dog.
What is their artistic potential?
Yep, artistic potential. So let's explain what that means. Guys, to an artist,
you might think an artist would look at this and say, "Well, this is how I
would create my art." An artist would look at this and say, "This is bullshit."
this is the subject of my next work. Yes, I'm going to make this Expo marker.
I'm going to make this or a paintbrush. I will build a paintbrush out of
hamburgers and hot dogs. Exactly. Which one will be my chosen tool? Which of
these will be the chisel with which I chisel? Okay. Or, for example, maybe are
there any famous works of art or paintings that feature a hot dog or a
hamburger and which are, have the better works of, the better opus? What I want
say now for artistic potential, I thought of this question as what can you like, which
one would be easier to use as a tool to make art? So my bias is leaning towards hot dog
because think about it, you could dip this in ink and then draw with the hot dog.
Uh huh, like a pen.
Like a pen. You could use the hot dog like a pen and then the bun as a piece of paper.
paper. It would just be a very wide. Yeah, which people do art with wide
nibs. I guess you're right. It's been done. It's been done by so many famous
artists. Well, here's my thing about burgers, though.
They got ketchup on them. Take the bun off.
It has a built in ink. It has built in. So yeah, I guess it's its own ink
pit. Well, in terms of using them as an artistic tool, maybe I would give it
to hot dogs, but when I'm thinking about famous paintings, famous artists, I
I do think that maybe the highest profile art that you could argue that a
hamburger might be present in is I feel like I'm at the museum all the time.
You know, yeah, of course, I'm always walking around and there's one artist
who I always look at her paintings. I'm always seeing a hamburger and that's
Georgia O'keeffe.
I feel like she's always painting things that look like hamburgers,
especially these hamburgers. Yeah, I mean look at this. Look at this. This
looks like a Georgia O'keeffe. Yeah,
this is exactly how how Georgia O'Keeffe's work looks. We get a punch
in on that and I guess I'm afraid I can't. I can't think of you what it
really it would be like you know Georgia O'Keeffe. She it's like you took a
hamburger, but you didn't want to eat the bun, but you also didn't want to
rip the bun off. So you kind of fold just hold it back a little bit, a
little bit of the bun back
just like that kind of and maybe we move the pickle to be
up there right and it's something like that.
this thing like that. So this is the kind of burger that she's eating.
She's like a
that's a
yeah, you know what I mean? That's classic Americana. I can't help myself.
Oh, my God, no, okay, that looks the most like a Georgia O'Keeffe. Now, oh,
my God, that is good. Yeah,
I want one so bad me too. I'm home, but I have to wait. I have to wait till
to end when we decide the winner to some of the questions where you actually
need to eat them and so jumping ahead. So I think because of the Georgia O'Keefe
point,
my argument is we give this point to hamburger. Hamburger wins. Agreed? Wow!
I think I would agree with that. I agree with that as well. Hamburger wins.
What's the next topic? Bun type.
Alright, so far we have
hot dog one, hamburger eleven.
Those are Tally Marks, Caleb, that's two.
You call me Tally what now?
Tally Mark was my neighbor growing up. You better shut your mouth.
Bun type, I mean this one's cut and dry,
like the buns themselves, cut and dry. Yeah, I'm going to have to give this to
hot dog personally, because hot dog has somewhat, somehow hot dog has more bun,
that I mind the bun less. There's more bun on a hot dog. Also, hamburger buns
could also be used for chicken sandwiches, regular. It's not a
PB and J, PB and J. I've only made a PB and J and a hot dog bun four
times. This has been my speaking of canvas. This is my canvas for a peanut
butter and jelly. The hot dog bun is a genius
business move because you're never going to buy a hot dog bun and say maybe
I should put chicken or exactly salad. Exactly. I'm surprised these because
okay, so I bought these hot dogs and I bought these hot dog buns and they were
different brands and I was at the store and I was like why the fuck would they
not just sell these two together in a combo pack and shit they should the dog
in the bone, the dog in the bun yeah, why the hell side of the bug and sell
them out of a restaurant or what the hell's going on with you buy a package
of six hot dogs you buy a package of a buns what the fuck well, that's why I
was I was avoiding that by get I got eight dogs and eight buns y'all that's a
genius way to avoid it is by picking the pack. I think the right amount yeah,
epic. So it's kind of my that's a little bit of a food hack. Yeah, life hack for
you. All right, so hot dog wins that one. You think hot dog wins that one? We're
giving it to hot dog. We are giving it to hot dog. Unless you have you have
evidence against
hamburger buns or evidence supporting hamburger. I don't have a I don't know.
I yeah, a hamburger bun. It's just a bun. It's not even a it's not you could
not even iconic as a as a no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
It's a roll, really.
It, yeah.
Hot dog wins.
So that's it's two and two right?
It's neck and neck already.
All tied up.
Holy fucking shit.
It's already so contentious.
Wait, what the hell's gonna happen next?
What can, what can happen next is the age old question.
Can you draw it fast?
Um.
Hamburger.
Hot dog.
I think hot dog wins this. Yeah. Well, let's see. Let me see. I'll demonstrate.
Try both. Here, take out your stopwatch. You know your stopwatch? Yes. Actually,
Julio, you have a stopwatch, right? No, no, you time it. I do. I do have a
stopwatch actually. Hold up. Hold up. Okay. I wish you had a pocket watch on
the chain right now. Me too. Tell me when to start and I'll count it down.
I'm gonna do hot dog first. Okay. Okay. Ready? Three, two, one.
one
okay. That was two point four one seconds.
All right ready. Oh, I forgot the bun. That's okay. That's
together. We'll add them together. All right ready. Yeah, three two one
done. Okay, so total is about five seconds. Yeah, let's shave off like a
couple of milliseconds.
I did as I was just a hot dog and just the bun. It was that simple. All right,
let's do burger. All right, ready, ready three two one. Okay, so let's start with
this top button
and you can't forget right that says to me. See you cannot forget. Here come the
sesame seeds. There's millions of these. So then first layer. How do you build a
first layer is going to be always lettuce? You
let us is coming in. Okay, that's good. That looks good man, and then we're
to do a big, big beefy beefsteak tomato. Yes. Here comes the little edges of the
stripes on the tomato. Tomato stripes. Yeah. And the red onion. We're going to put two pickles.
Yeah. Pickles are going to go up there. A couple of seeds on there. Yeah.
A couple of sesame seeds on the pickle. And here's a couple of onions. Oh,
there's an onion. Red onion. Red onion. Red onion. The piece de resistance.
The burger bun. Oh, and that's a bun. And that's bigger than the bun.
the
Patty
where's the burger?
Where's the
big
okay,
okay. So this button I'll turn this into it. We don't wait. Big Mac.
no it's a big, big style. It's big style, so put another put the patty
underneath, then the patty goes under here and what's on the patty,
beautiful brown char and what else is on the patty? Sesame seeds. Here comes
some sesame seeds and then what I win the sauce. Oh, what kind of sauce
secret and then here's the bottom bun. Yes, all right, stop the time one
minute and thirty eight seconds
hot dog, hot dog wins this by country mile guy.
Yeah,
that was a flawless victory. Let me erase these as beautiful as they are. I
can't believe I forgot to draw the damn
you know. Maybe if you hadn't forgot the bottom bun, hamburger could have won.
It would have been at least a little. It would have been close. Yeah, I hate
This next category has subcategories.
So, can you feed it to a baby?
Hamburger, no. Hot dog, if you cut it up into maybe an octopus shape.
But you shouldn't.
You shouldn't really feed it.
It's not shouldn't, it's can.
Yeah.
Can, so this goes to hot dog.
Okay.
Hot dog wins.
Can you feed it to an animal? I think both of them get a point.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Hamburger. Hot dog. Hamburger. Hot dog. Wins. Hamburger. Wins. Hot dog. Wins.
God, this smell is really getting to me.
Me too.
All right. I want all this food.
Can you feed it to an old geezer on life support?
On life support? I don't think either of them would probably get it,
but definitely not hot dogs. That'd be a choking hazard.
Yeah. Hamburger.
How would a hot dog be a choking hazard and a hamburger wouldn't?
Because it's a little stiffer.
you can grind them up though with a mortar and pestle.
If you grind up fucking anything with a molcajete, it doesn't matter.
That's true. Thank you for saying molcajete.
If you put anything into a motherfucking molcajete, then yeah, it doesn't matter.
As long as you season it well with rice and salt.
This one is a stalemate.
What did he say?
He said thank you for representing Spanish culture.
Oh, okay.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That guy said molcajete.
This one is a stalemate, I think, the old geezer on life support.
I don't have a button for stalemate.
Well, I'm going to give both of them zero points for that one.
Yeah. All right.
Oh, I actually have something that I could put for that.
That's got to hurt
because it would kill the guy.
It was like no points.
Yeah.
Oh, that's got to hurt.
You think that's the hamburger would be like this?
You'd be like, that's got to hurt.
And then the hot dog would be like this hot dog.
And wait, then they could do this.
No, we had that hamburger, that hamburger, man.
That's making it look sexual.
OK,
it's not flawless.
flawless, not flawless. I can tell you that. Oh, my God, I'm drooling.
Oh,
so hungry. All right, I got so hungry when I sat down here. The next one, you
know what I could get the microwave. Can we just really for just a second for
just a second guys? It'll blow the circuit for just a second. Can we
appreciate that? We officially have the best job in the world
sitting in front of four or eight beautiful hot dogs and six beautiful
hamburgers. Oh sitting here getting a rate and review and talk about this.
This is a guy's paradise. Yeah, a male cast about list wins yeah and we are
win
this next one. Here is color
press wrong button
press on button inside water. My mouth press on button.
I think that I'm going to give this to the color of a burger is so much more
appetizing them. The color of a hot dog. Black don't crack man.
What? Black don't crack. What are you saying? Hamburgers are black.
Alright, they're kind of more brown, but... What? They're black as night.
Hamburger. Hamburger wins. I want to throw a... Maybe this will come up
later. You're giving it to hamburger? Hamburger wins. Give it to hamburger
with an asterisk because they're... I don't have a button for asterisk. Well,
that doesn't really matter. You can give it to hamburger with an asterisk
because I'm going to I'm going to throw a wrench in it a little bit later
when we get to the oh, I think I get to the arms. Well, let's oh, let's not
spoil anything. Okay, all right, number
the next one is condiments.
Ketchup.
Sexy
Okay, so
ketchup ketchup ketchup.
Oh man, they both can have ketchup. Yeah, and by the way, we're on another
from Chicago. If you're from Chicago hot dog and we're on an entire another
level y'all
and other podcasts. I'm telling you
ketchup. That's right. Yeah, nobody's debating hot dogs. Not a single not a
single. No, but you listen to this one and you're like hot dog. Yeah, because
It's such a great episode. I'm so excited. All right. So I guess they have the same condiments.
They're the same. I guess that's another stalemate. Well, well, because that's the thing. Some
people believe that a that a hot dog should never have ketchup. Speaking of your microphone,
some people believe that a hot dog should never have ketchup. Not like that. I just
think that maybe there are some differences. Like, for example, what what's I list the
ingredients of a Chicago dog right now. What's that? I was going to that was going to go
go for condiments. The only thing color was going to that. So you look at a
burger, right? You see the stack of color, you see a Chicago dog, you see the
stack of colors. That's what the asterisk was going to be for.
Okay, I don't know. I don't know why you'd, why are you?
Chicago dog has a lot of color on it, but a lot of condiments as well. It has
neon green relish. Chicago dogs. Okay. So, would you ever put relish on a
hamburger? Yeah, sometimes. I don't know if I've ever had relish on a hamburger.
I have it, it's not good. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
you have not had relish on a hamburger, but you've had
McDonald's secret sauce and In-N-Out secret sauce on a hamburger, which I
think both of them have relish in. They have pickles chopped up. Really? Which
is what relish is. Ketchup. Yeah. I didn't know that.
Playing what? Ketchup.
For the sake of never hearing that again, I think that we... This has to
be a tie. This is a tie yeah that's fine with me. Was that you was that your
feelings getting hurt because I said I didn't want to hear the catch up anymore.
That's why I said that's going to hurt. No, I just was playing different sounds
okay, pressing random buttons. Next one is
craziness. Oh wait shit.
This keeps happening. This is an honest
playing this flat. I'm not doing it to be funny. I have two pages. I'm flipping
between here. I'm getting confused. I put the splat on the arrow
craziness. I just have to switch quickly craziness, craziness.
I'm going to get okay. So here's what I'm thinking with this. Have you guys
ever seen these fucking burgers where they're so insane you they have eggs on
the burger right through it. This is this is this is a burger.
Not even they literally make burgers in restaurants where you cut it. It
explodes yeah yeah and a bear on top of it. They put no under it ain't
doing that with the hot dog. The craziest hot dog you could ever see is
this hot dog is extra long yeah. Oh look. We made a long. Yeah, it's long
hamburger wins long. Oh yeah, shut up. Come try our long hot dog. Yeah,
they have pink hamburgers.
There's a flaw. That's right for him.
All right, hamburger. What's next next is customization.
I feel like we almost just did that one. We just that's kind of the same.
These are maybe we can skip that one and go to the next one. One of the
top customization options would have to be
how much, what shape you put it in. If you do a smiley, what ketchup brand you
guys like?
I'm not a huge ketchup fan. If I can be honest, I don't like ketchup that much.
I use I use Heinz, but there's this new one that I got that it's called the
primal kitchen and it's pretty good.
Primal kitchen? Oh shit, does it have like no oil in it or some shit?
Yeah, yeah it's one of those.
I bet it's so good.
I think I find it in my house probably.
I like nice ass ketchup. Dude, that makes sense.
I get this one ketchup called like Sir Kingsley
or some shit. I want to make my own ketchup at home.
I never use ketchup so when I buy it.
Sir Kensington. That's what it is, Sir Kensington.
I know exactly the one. It's good as fuck.
Uh huh. It's actually good as fuck.
They have a spicy one. Uh, alright.
So this next topic.
ready for this title card. Yeah, you really need to be on this title card
really. This one, this one is, this is the most important one, I would say.
Does it look like a turd?
Okay, so
this might seem so cut and dry. Yeah, but, but, part which part of the pun,
but oh, but well that's good and pardon the bun yeah, but my buns part of my
buns
you might think a way to figure they put their inside wait hold on they're both
between buns hold up they both oh my God listen. Oh shit, a burger may look
like a turd like it look you know what it looks like it looks like a texture
pack for a in a video. You actually you wrapped it around the turd texture on
to a frisbee. Yeah
yeah exactly a turd texture got loaded onto a frisbee in a gary's mod server
yeah but guys this one over here this hot dog
somebody accidentally put a frisbee texture on a turd to a to a blind to a
color blind man. This is a turd guy color blind person. I'm holding a turd
in my finger right now. Yeah, this is as close to a turd as you can legally
went to your eyes on the street holding especially especially maybe if you well,
what do you guys think if you have more turdy, if you grill it or you boil it
definitely the color for grill, but I don't know how many of my turds have
grill marks that are dark only on certain you know, you know what the
best the number one way to make it look like a turd microwave it and it gets
those bubbles. We have a microwave stop trying to get us to use the microwave
man and stop. This is a very smelly meat that you're what am I doing? I'm doing
what you're doing with the pen dog.
We've given this to hot dog. What way is it a point if it does look like a turd
our point of it's a point. If it looks like a turn, okay, so yeah, what are we
at here? Oh, we'll wait till the end of Canada. We'll wait till the end of
Canada. I like the number. Ali marks go past five. Oh my God, my fingers. I'm
just doing is doing risk free style on it. I'm just messing around.
I forget I forgot how to do that. Yeah, I forgot that you're supposed to. Well,
that's fine. Yeah, we'll worry about it when it comes to the next one. I'll
start crossing them. Now that's a good point. Next one is ease of access.
So this means how easy it is to get a hot dog. I mean in the streets of New
York, it depends where you are, depends where you are, but you can get in
Times Square. You can get a hot dog pretty much anywhere, but now with food
trucks,
you can get a burger. Listen, listen, I'm not I'm not with the fucking hipster
New York food cart, food truck bullshit. Yeah, I'm part of America, blue collar
grew up in a computer family. Yeah, we were out in the circuit board farms.
Yeah, every damn day, farming, just trying to try to make ends meet, trying
to make two hundred and fifty thousand dollars last a month. Yeah, it's hard.
It's really hard days. And let me tell you a working man. It's easy to make a
hot dog, but if you're talking about going out and getting one, it's a
hamburger all the way. Yeah, not a lot of restaurants have a hot dog on the
than you know. You are not going to get a hot dog in somewhere the salt in the
earth kind of town like Cambridge mass. No shot man. You no way, no how not even
at tasty burger or move. Yeah, straight out of straight out of kindle
motherfucking square.
You're going to get a motherfucking. I think you're getting anything but
clover foods. I'm kind of nice as oh fancy hot dog. No, you're getting a
burger, but my mom sat me to sat me and my my twelve siblings down on the table
and said times are hard today. Yeah today
times are hard today. They're going to be okay tomorrow, but today it's tough
and all I have for you guys. I was able to go to the Alamo draft house and I
got you some to go or got some to go orders from there, and that's all we
have to eat for and so that's all we have to eat for a couple hours.
Pace yourself. This is all we have for just a few hours. Some of these we can
really save the toothpicks. Yes, please save the please kids save the toothpicks,
because we need those to do a group gold
so we're giving this to hamburger
wins. Why don't you tell count him up right now and then start cross? Don't
worry about the the counting. He's got it under control. I trust him. Okay,
he's got the you you you you keep your eyes on your page here. All right, well
the next one we all got we all have a job today. I'm sounds. This is why I
feel so good today, because I have a purpose and guys we are thirty minutes
mean this is going to be the longest episode we've ever done. It can't be
because I have somewhere to be. He has to go get ink on his body. That's true.
Ease of access. That is what we just did. It was the one we just did. Now
easiness to make.
Where did I go? Okay. I think this is a clear. Yeah, this is pretty. This is
clearly hot dog because so these hamburgers, I know they look homemade,
but I didn't make these guys. What? These came from McDonald's. Another bite.
Can I have one? Yeah.
time to eat
time to eat hamburger
flawless victory.
All right,
so
he's just to make a good hamburger is so hard to hamburger is so hard to make
that. I just I was like I'm not doing that shit.
So I made so I made the hot dogs. You buy the hot dog. You buy the bun. You
put the bun in the hot things to buy. It's only just a cold dog.
They didn't know that. They didn't know that. That's gotta hurt. Yeah, that hurt. That hurt.
So we're going to give this to Hot Dog. Hot Dog wins. Alright, now I'm learning about
tally marks. You do one across the corner like so. Good job. And there we are. Thank
you work. All right, next
exchange rate.
So how many hamburgers before we eat? How many hot dogs before we ate these?
Right? How many were there in the there's Okay, so there's six. There's
eight hot dogs.
And if these if the scales are even well, if they were even they're
definitely I dropped my
I throw some burger on the list.
If this these were supposed to be even scales, right?
I mean, I don't think they're hot.
They were supposed to say this burger didn't want to spend more
than $30 on the I don't think that I don't think they were
okay. Wait
in terms of maybe we already have this on here,
but in terms of
exchange rate,
I will say these hot dogs hot dog and bun
cost $8
for eight of them.
So that's a dollar each
These hamburgers, which I got them delivered because I'm too far away from
McDonald's, but if I didn't get them delivered...
I could have gotten picked them up.
The total would have been $3.29 per.
So in a money sense, it's three hot dogs per hamburger, a little over three
hot dogs. But in terms of how many of these hot dogs,
if it was a school lunch situation... So wait, if it's three hot dogs per
hamburger does that mean that I would even say that that even beyond money
that holds up to I'm going to eat one hamburger but I'll eat two or three
hot dogs.
Yeah, maybe not these specific hamburger.
Yeah, does that what we're supposed to say for exchange? So who wins this one?
hamburger, it's worth more. Okay. That's what I was asking. Yeah, higher value.
Yeah.
All right, we're gonna go.
Alright, the next one is fan base.
So we've all been in this situation with some shit like Odd Future where you're like, "Wait,
they make the funniest, dopest fucking rap in the world, but these fans are cringe gay
guys that wear pink."
So that's what I wanted to get at with this.
Who has the...
Also like just to give another example, for example, Rick and Morty, I have a lot of fans
that think the show is funny that are just wanting to laugh and like watch TV and laugh
at cartoons.
And they don't care about the deeper meaning.
The deeper voices on the show and what they say.
For example, Rake.
They only care about the high pitched voices.
So who do you think has the more chill fan base?
Probably hot dogs.
Probably hot dogs, right?
Hot dog because burgers, burger fans are going out to different restaurants and they're like,
oh my God, you have the biggest burger and I had to try it.
There's no such thing as a hot dog challenge.
Yeah, there isn't.
They don't do that.
People don't do hot dog challenges.
There's no restaurant on earth where it's...
What do you do?
Burger challenge.
People do.
People eat big burgers all the time.
Nobody's eating 50, 60 hot dogs.
Right.
That would never happen.
So with that alone, I think that the burger fan base is more cringe, but I think that the
hot dog fan base can be maybe a little more. They're more game. Keep me annoying. They're
more maybe I like talking about hot dogs all the damn time and they think they're special
for liking hot dogs. Plus they're like what like you like that's an entry like a Chicago
dog. That's an entry level. Oh, you never had a Chicago dog. Oh, you never had one. Oh,
Lowkey just remembered that there is literally a fucking contest where they eat like
60 fucking hot dogs
Yeah, because of because of that because I fucking hate that that 4th of July bullshit so much that it's going to burn
I think it's going to burn
I feel like burger has a better fan base just because of that that one and burgers are not taken up
the one the one day a year where we get to celebrate our beautiful nation.
That's what you mentioned is burgers on hot dogs and hot dogs on hamburger
hot burgers. Wait, wait, actually you have final say on this. I do think
you're okay. That is your birthday happens on your birthday. It is your
birthday, so you do get. I think it's a class on fourth of July. The hot dog
eating contest. I'm not so much a fan of, but
you eat both a hamburger and a hot dog on fourth of July. That's pretty
classic or as some would say you eat a hot dog on hamburger and a hamburger on
hot dog day.
Yeah, so I just said I think I maybe said something a little more
sophisticated. Okay, really? Yeah, maybe a little more eloquent than that, but
you know I personally if it's just coming down to fan bases yeah and I'm
leaving my birthday out of it.
I my vote. I think that hamburger
has the cringer fan base. If it's about cringiness, if it's based on cringiness,
but I think it's based on based on. I think hot dog fan hot dog fan base is
more based,
not saying hot dog. So who's the winner is what we're asking. I think I'll give
it to I think I'll give it to hot dog. All right, yeah, hot dog wins. All right,
what's next flavor? Okay, we already just tasted them, so we're in a perfect
place to
to talk about the flavor. We tasted one of them. You know what's really good?
Yeah, all right, Caleb. Hey, Caleb,
give me the
cold
hot. Why me? He's the one who likes nasty stuff. No, go ahead and eat it.
You're the flavor. Oh my God, it actually smells. It smells like how's the legs on
just eat it sideways like pretend it's a burger and eat it sideways.
Oh, it does it actually does have legs. Yeah, it's really sticking to the side
and the terror terror to our I mean it doesn't taste bad. It's a hot dog dog. It
tastes like cold fat. Yeah, it is better when you cook it, but you have to you
can eat a hot dog cold,
which is interesting. Okay, isn't it funny? It's hot in the name. Yeah,
that's rather. So basically, basically the what it boils down to is pigs
versus cows. Yeah, I don't like boiled hot dogs either though. Okay, then
that trash. But if you had a boiled burger, would you like that? Dude, that
Actually that tastes like a fucking tire.
Yeah, I think it goes to burger.
It has like an awful chemical aftertaste.
Which hot dogs did you buy?
Sabret.
Yeah, that's the problem.
You gotta cook those ones.
You gotta cook all of them, they're fucking hot dogs.
Those ones taste good when they're cooked.
Don't even red me up.
Don't even red me. It's pink bro.
Don't pink me.
You fucking pinked me.
Alright, this one's to burger.
Now we will get into the future one thousand years from now.
Wow!
What are these two things? Because guys, there's been a hundred years of
discovery doing the hamburgers and hot dogs. No more ketchup. No more ketchup in
the future. No, no, no, no. Where will we- will we even recognize this shit? I
bet that they- I bet that- All Tomorrow's style. What are these going to look
like? Yeah, I've got something to say.
that I think that in the future hot dog and you and listen when you I think
that one of these will have a square shape and it's going to be hot dogs.
Who's
just gurgled me that hot dog is sitting well and my throat made it. I think that
we will see square hot dogs in the future. You can't even barely find these
on Google nowadays. It looks like you're talking about like square like a
Japanese watermelon. I don't even know what it could possibly mean, but a
hamburger is a classic shape right, but and people do squared hamburgers here.
Wendy people do hamburgers yeah, there's already square hamburgers you're right,
so I feel like it's gonna take us a thousand years to get this square hot
dog. That's crazy. I think you know what I think is going to become the standard
in a well. This is more. This is all this is kind of a subjective question. I
don't matter. These are all subjective questions. What do you mean this one?
that we're judging. Well, this one specifically is like we don't have
enough. Let him say what he said. Thanks. Sorry. What I think is you
want to get look up some facts right now. Can you look up what a hot dog
will look like in the future? Go future 1000 years and maybe we'll get
future future hot dog. Well, actually, I do this might be helpful if we
see what it's going to look like
three hot dogs, three ways. Okay, what the hell? What the hell is it?
Turned into a cake, some kind of squeezed hot dog. It's a green hot
dog. It's a green springy hot dog. Oh my God, it looks like a coiled snake.
Here's what I think is the future of hot dog and people have already caught on
to this, but it's not the norm and I think a thousand years from now will be
the norm of butterflied hot dog. Oh, when you cut it in half and put it on
the grill, yes, a hot burger. Why is the hot burger not a more popular thing
outside of my dad's house? I don't know. It's good as fuck in my dad's house.
It's one of the most popular foods that is a mad that and sourdough toast.
There was a lot of food like that growing up where they were kind of my
foods and they never really popped off for the rest of the world. Yeah,
what's it called frosted mini wheat, frosted mini puffins,
pop in a butter puff. Oh my God, I loved peanut butter, but our puffins with
soy milk. All right, well, we're getting out of you're getting out of that.
You're getting off topic. Oh yeah, you're right. What will a hamburger look
like? Hamburg up future hamburger,
and book up a future ham
from the creamery
future burger. Okay, we'll be a city. Okay, this will be called
hamburger. Clearly wins. Yeah, yeah, hamburger. Hamburger is
gonna become a city based on. Yeah, right next getting sick
from it with a question mark. So I already shared my story. I
think you're more likely to get feel sick from a hot dog than a
ham. We have an event with you. You got sick
just now. I didn't get sick. I gargled sick. You gargled gargling is sickness.
No, it's not. I think that
when it comes, I think hot dogs are more likely to make you sick. I think I
agree, but
could be
it could be cooked rare. You're so right. That's what I was about to say.
Maybe you're so right. Yeah, you could literally get food.
I just connected this. I never connected this board. This is probably why
because a hamburger can be pink in the middle and that pinkness can make you
sick. Yes, a hot dog is all pink. She it's only to pay, but it's they
probably make it from the pink from the burger when it's not cooked enough.
Yeah, my God,
by God,
that's you've made a discovery.
So who wins did something about
this is a hamburger and a hot dog at noon on a work day is really making me
feel fucking crazy. Yeah, I have I have so many coming on so many meat
chemicals are blasting. All right, let's call it. Let's call it a draw.
Let's call it a draw. Move forward. Move forward. Go a little. We will
move on to gift ability.
What would you rather receive as a gift? A dog? All right.
That was too quick.
Hand feel. Now this one is subjective. There's an asterisk next to it
for some reason. Don't remember why. Let's see. Here, wait. Close your eyes and see if
you can tell which one is which. See, okay, you can tell a hot dog. That's actually perfect
because you can tell a hot dog is a hot dog. This could be a chicken sandwich. That could
be literally anything. Or just a bun. It could be a hockey puck that was in the microwave
for a few minutes and melted. Yeah. Okay, hot dog wins. Hot dog definitely has the iconic
Hand feel history history. All right.
So they both came out at the same time. That's a draw. No, wait, that's not. No,
no, we can dig into this one. Okay, so hamburgers were made at that one
fucking place in
Hamburg all, but no, it's not. It's not from Hamburg Germany. No, they're not
from Germany. Hamburgers are from there's this one
place in I think Albany or some shit. Oh, is it in? You mean
Connecticut, Connecticut, where they put them in the broiler. Yes, yes, and they
boil them. They broil them. They don't boil them. They broil them. They have
these like 120 year old. Okay, it actually came from hamburger Charlie in
Wisconsin and go back one page. It says that a history of the burger says from
ancient Rome 18 60s versus 18 85. So I guess hot dog wins because that one
first hamburger came from ancient Rome. What's the title of the article? A
the history of the burger from ancient Rome to the well, but they're just
they're just saying that they made a meat sandwich. The burger that we know
today, okay, is the that's the signifier here. Did you guys watch the founder?
No, this was a good movie. Okay, next is holiday variants. Hamburger wins.
Okay, holiday.
Yeah, put a tally up for hot dog
holiday variants. Santa Claus burger. Yeah, we all know the Santa Claus burger
when you use ketchup as the red on his suit. I will say you could draw stuff
with the ketchup more easily on a hamburger. Yes, a hot dog itself is
almost a holiday variant. We've all had a Valentine's Day hot dog.
Hot dog. Valentine's dog. I've had a hot dog on every holiday except for
Christmas. I think the holiday of burgers is burger fest. Yeah, that's
true. There is a holiday already. All right. All right. Give it burger
hamburger wins. All right, these two I think can coincide with each other. How fun is it
to eat and how often can you eat it?
I could honestly eat a hamburger probably every day. Yeah, 100%.
Hot dog every week. But what is more fun?
You can go through a phase of eating hot dogs really often, but if you don't stop, if the
if the phase doesn't go away, you'll die. There's also the thing about a
hamburger is like you can eat one that's like fully loaded on a bun and shit,
but then if you wanna eat something a little healthier, you make it at home,
you do like a lean ground beef, you put it on... Don't even, don't even talk
about the lettuce wrap. No, no, leave the lettuce wrap. Leave the lettuce wrap
at home. No, no, no, no. I like this. I do this a lot. Don't even. Sometimes,
you know what I do? I make a... You guys are gonna think this is gross.
I make a burger, I put it on some white rice, I... That's Hawaiian or Filipino
I boil some broccoli, I put some sour cream on the burger and I put some hot sauce.
This is not...
That's strange, man.
That is strange.
It's really good.
And salt.
Oh, you put salt in it?
I was thinking we were talking about a burger joy from Jollibee.
No way.
Yeah.
Burger on rice with sour cream and pepper sauce.
Burger on rice.
Yo, let me get a burger over rice.
Yo, Oc, let me get a burger over rice.
Can I get a burger over rights?
Burger over rights.
Burger over rights, please.
You guys, this next one is actually...
Wait, who won that?
burger over rights. Burger over rights, please. You guys, this next one is
actually... Wait, who won that? Me with my delicious recipe. Hamburger wins.
Hamburger wins because you can eat it often and it's more fun to eat.
Nice. Good one. Thank you. You guys, this next one is ingredients.
Are we saying ingredients?
Hot dog... This is different for toppings. This is ingredients. Yeah. I
I guess toppings is the same. No, no, no, because the ingredients okay, so
here's let me let me let me let me throw this out. Let me throw this out a
burger. You look at them. You think maybe they have the same amount of
ingredients. Hamburger is the patty and the bun. Just the two ingredients. The
hot dogs ingredients are the hot dog and the bun. That's the two ingredients,
but the ingredients that go into a hot dog. There are millions of different
parts of the body of the animal. That is so true. You and I see an
ingredients list for hot dog foot leg arm hand brain asshole intestinal lining
plastic plastic plastic of the pig's plastic nitrites nitrites, which I still
don't murder and murder. It would mostly say beef lean and fat yeah lean beef and
fat beef. Yeah, I'm going to agree to agree. There's a little ingredients in
the patty hot dog wins hot dog has millions of ingredients, but you guys
This is the most difficult question yet.
Okay.
Likeability.
I mean, well, hold on.
Like which one's more charming?
Look up, look up dancing burger versus dancing, because the dancing hot dog is very famous.
We don't need to watch a video to decide.
No, no.
But just I need to see what a dancing burger would look like.
Pick it up and show them.
Okay, wait a minute.
This is easy to figure out.
Oh, you know what I'm thinking of actually?
Okay, so there's the dancing hot dog, right?
right. But there's the fortnight fortnight dancing hot dog. But then there is the
better off dead hamburger scene where the burgers play guitar.
Well, this is I'm not talking you're getting into the you're going like a
yeah, you're looking at the next one, which is oh my God movie role. I'm
sorry. Like ability is so here's here's my argument for for burger. Okay with a
hot dog. You can stand him up right and go like hey, I'm hot dog, right? But it
It doesn't look like his mouth is moving. This motherfucker, he can say, he can come here.
Hamburger. Hamburger. He can say his name. Look at that. Hamburger. Hamburger. Time to
eat. Hamburger. Time to eat it, Caleb. Ketchup. I know, I'm full. I'm so full. Alright, well
I guess in terms of likeability. A hot dog looks like a fucking cock. And if you like
that, that's okay. If you like that, you like that, but for me, I don't like that shit. Keep
put away. All right. Well, I guess we are going to want one of those on my body. A
draw here because this is too hard. This is the crux of the whole argument.
Yeah, I guess the crux of the whole battle.
I was thinking about actually Julio is a tiebreaker Julio. I just thought of a
joke. Say it.
You heard of this this shit called shoegaze, right? This this yeah,
guitars. Yeah. What's that? What? What? Patrick says it was fucking kids.
flawless victory.
Shoo, gays.
You're gay, son.
Oh, okay.
I'm shoo.
Like, shoo! Get out of here!
Yeah.
Okay.
Ha! Gays! Shoo!
You guys like my joke?
Mm.
Flawless victory.
I thought so, too.
All right, this next one, I kind of jumped ahead, got ahead of myself.
Movie roles.
Movie roles. Okay, so what I want you to do right now, Julio--
Have you guys seen the Seth Rogen hot dog movie?
What I want you to look up right now--
Hot dog.
there this one might end in a stalemate two tabs open I need you to look up
wieners movie and then good burger good burger is about friends or brothers
barely about burgers but look at this this is look who is in both what the
hell boy go to images for wieners Keenan Thompson is lit clean and Thompson is
the star of both burgers and hot dogs. This is the food master. Kenan Thompson,
you are the food master and we need you to decide. We bow down to you. If you
call Sarah right now. We need to call Sarah. We need to ask her. Get Kenan Thompson on the horn.
We need to get Kenan to give his to weigh in on this. I'm going to text her right now and ask,
Do you think he likes
should I do that?
You be mad at me. We say we're doing something. It's very important. It's
very important to urgent
nine one one. Okay, let's see if she responds
urgent
wait nine one one. Do you think sorry to bother you sorry to bother you, but but
we've been talking about hamburgers and hamburgers and about hot dogs and about
hot dogs, and we noticed that Kenan Thompson is in a movie about both and we
noticed that Kenan Thompson is in a movie about both. So we need someone to
tell about both
hamburgers versus hot dogs. Is it hamburgers and then a different one
movie about each yeah is in one movie one movie? Well, they're making aren't
they making a legacy sequel to good burger? Do you think so? Question
question is do you what question is what does he like more hamburgers or hot
dogs? You think he likes hamburgers
or hot dogs more okay hamburger, and this will be a five pointer. Yeah, this
will be when we get the answer. This will be five points. So she ain't going
respond to that shit. I'm going to be honest with you. And the next time I see
her, she's going to say, I totally I'm sorry, I forgot to respond to your
question about if Kenan Thompson likes hamburgers or hot dogs more. I thought
that was an immediate response. Me too. I got so excited. No, it's Mike.
Anyway, what's next? Musicality, which you guys,
I mean, you know me, I'm a... Patrick Dornan. Oh, she answered! What'd she
say?
ha ha ha ha ha ha wait, which one is the hot dog movie? It's called Wieners and
it's from two thousand four Wieners. Okay, enough with the laughing. I just
need to know it's a it's a simple question. It's a simple question. She
said no say Wieners two thousand eight and it's she's just text. She's like
wow, that's so crazy.
Please
please
does he like
please.
I feel like I've seen him eat a hamburger before no cap. Thank you
thank you so much.
There we go okay, so that's five points for hamburgers. Hamburger wins. Oh, it
says he eats McDonald's all the time.
All right,
but never hot.
Okay. All right. So we did for the money and good burger. He did for the love
and maybe for the free hamburgers. Yeah. All right. That's five points. That's
fucking five points. That's five points for burgers. Crazy. And you guys with
this next song from Patrick door and music,
we'll see who wins.
Oh, 'cause it's musicality. Yeah.
Is it on? It's on. Ow. Sorry. Alright, go ahead. Talk your shit.
I messed that up. Wait. Is this like a song inspired by? This is a song inspired by burgers.
he
turned the drums off. That's why it doesn't sound like okay. He doesn't
know how to leave the drums on ready.
He was eating and breathing and listening to his music
And just when he got hungry, somebody turned around and told me, "Sell me all your burgers, white boy!"
Eat that fuckin' burger right!
Eat that fuckin' burger, white boy!
Eat 14 burgers and you'll go to the fuckin' hospital and die!
Okay, now do "Hot Dog."
See, this is the hardest part.
So what's the hot dog stand?
This is the hot dog song I guess. What is it? You guess?
Woah!
Hot dog. Hot dog. Hot dog. Stop. Hot dog.
I don't know this song. I can't sing this one.
Okay.
Wait, dude, kiss me.
Dude, kiss me, dude.
(music)
This is derailed the whole show. I have to stop.
You have to stop.
I thought that "Eat That Fuckin' Burger, White Boy" was gonna be...
I think that "Burgers" wins though, because we did more of a song about burgers.
Well, we were gonna sing it...
Eat me, between the two big white buns.
Eat me, with ketchup and some sauce.
boss eat me eat my meaty skin. I want you to see your mouth and then go in my
man is horrible. Eat my meaty skin. That's not right to say man
eat me
[MUSIC]
Eat me between the two big white buns.
Eat me and all my meaty skin.
Eat me with some ketchup and we'll put the sauces then I'll go right in.
Oh, eat me.
I don't know the intro. I don't know the other part.
Well, fuck you.
Which one was a better song?
Then hamburgers wins.
better easily the hamburger. So okay, don't like just me. Okay, this guy
doesn't know. I like the drums. I got no rhythm on the second one here.
You think I don't have you think I know it's going away. It's you think I
don't have rhythm. What's that?
Are you gonna
Cameron? You gotta sing a song about hot dogs now to see that would change.
Why did you have a song?
What? I didn't know we were preparing songs.
But how do you have one?
We had a whole thing about musicality.
Oh, this is you. Oh, turn that off.
Okay, we've spent way too much time on music, guys.
Yeah, it's...
We need to go rapid fire.
Yeah.
I want to put it...
And we can't do rock or rap.
No, no.
We just did music.
No, we just did music.
Let's go smell.
Okay.
Well, right off the bat,
hot dogs had the worst smell.
and the burgers actually that smelled give me that smell again. This is a bad
smell.
This is can I smell the burger real quick? That one smells like a car over
here. They both smell very vehicular.
Oh wow, this one smells that burger and specific does not smell like food. This
smells like bad food, but that really is I'm bringing be a bring bring brought
back to the days of smelling DVD cases and Patrick's basement with the smell
of that. Oh my God, smells plastic, smell plastic because of let me think about
again. Give me one of those, so I think maybe these maybe each burger smells
different, though maybe it's like a fingerprint. This one smells like fruit.
Oh, my goodness, it's a
little bit like fruit. This one smells like jelly.
maybe it's the ketchup. Oh, my God, no, you need the you need the onion side.
Yeah,
I'd actually I like that smell. It smells like a burn on you. I just smelled
wasn't so bad. Yeah. When I smell it close burgers is burgers is all up for
debate. When I open it, I'm liking it a little more, but what else? Well, let
me you need to let me see because you know, I smell under where the hot dog
that's what I was about to do. Yeah, I was about to maybe take this out.
it's
the
bun that smells like food.
Oh, yeah,
bun smells more like a hot dog than the hot dog smells like a hot. This smells
like something that a hot dog from the bun all along. This is what you need to
be put. This smells like something you put your car. This this is smells like a
- That's what a hot dog smells like.
- Wait, wait, we've cracked--
- Did we just discover something that--
- That hot dogs don't smell like?
- Nobody's ever realized?
- The bun.
(laughing)
- The smell of a hot dog is a bun?
- The bun is the smell--
- Oh, that is awful.
- From which the hot dog dwells.
- That really smells so much like--
- The bun is the smell from which the hot dog dwells.
- This is an easy--
- That's such an easy burger.
- Hamburger wins flawless victory.
- All right.
- That's gotta hurt.
We'll go with stackability.
Well, I mean the hot dogs are stacked pretty well.
Well, but you have to pyramid those or you have to jenga them.
Looks cooler though.
Looks cooler.
That one hot dog wins.
All right, we'll give that to hot dog.
Yeah.
Hot dog wins.
Now, this is interesting.
This is...
I feel like we can go through all the rest of them.
I feel like we...
All right, we're good.
And Julio, get ready.
Get ready to pull those title cards up.
Yep.
So after stackability, we have taste.
Taste.
I liked the taste of the burger better. I did not even taste the hot dog because
of the anticipation of how it might taste. Yes. You got to taste. I think
you both need to taste it. All right. Here, little lady in the trampit. I'd
rather not do that with that one. Just eat your own, man.
Tastes like a hot dog. I think those that taste disgusting.
Disgusting. It would taste good cooked.
Yeah, they're gross. Okay, so burger wins. And we all ate a whole burger and
I liked it yeah. I devoured it all right. If I put this down, it'll break. I
don't even want to have the rest of my bite that I'm it's in my mouth guys
burgers in a massive lead right now. I'm going to
temperature and hotness. I mean so I was cold what's in front of us today. I
think there's but normally I think that hot dogs might be on average hotter
than the name. It's in the name. I got to give they call it a
dog
hot dog. All right, so time of day,
you have to eat them both at lunchtime or dinner. You can eat a
burger for dinner, but you can eat a hot dog at 3 PM.
Hot dog is definitely afternoon. I've had a breakfast burger. Yeah, but a
burger also can't really be a snack in the way that a hot
dog has the potential to be snackable. That's true. So, hot dog really
is all day. Yeah, except I probably you know I wouldn't eat one is at breakfast,
but I'm sure there are people who do it and they brag about it. People do that in
different countries, I think, or different states. I tried to make a
breakfast hot dog one time and it was the worst decision I've ever made. You put
egg on a hot dog?
Was it breakfast sausage in a brioche bun with scrambled egg? So not a hot dog at
all. Yeah, I guess you're right. That's a breakfast sausage. Breakfast brat.
a piece of shit. I'm just an inventor. You're a piece of shit. I'm an inventor. So we're
giving that to a hot dog as you can eat it at any time? Yes. Utility. Hot dog, hamburger,
hot wings. Utility, I don't get that question. Value. Okay, so this is a hard one. Because...
Well we kind of did that with the exchange rate. We said exchange rate, but I don't know...
So you are getting three hot dogs. Three and one third hot dogs for the price of one fucking
but okay that's true. You say bun? But. Bun. Bud. Bund. Bund. Bund. Listen. Welt. Welt.
I have a bund. You're starting with a situation, let me tell you something, you're starting
with a situation where you have some money and you have no food. Obviously maybe you
go for the hot dog because you can buy more of them. But imagine this situation that you
are the type of guy where in your house you have hundreds and hundreds of food items and
no money. You're going to want to have the hamburgers because you can sell
them for a higher price. Yes, I because they're worth more. Yes, okay. Farmer
or a minor and you're gathering hamburgers from your environment. So
which way you're saying is better value. I'm saying I'm saying it depends on
which side of the question you look at it from because if you if you're I
would say the hamburgers higher of course higher value. That's almost
empirically true right, but maybe that maybe if you're okay, if you're a poor
a peasant, he said empirically he that one point for Cameron, one point for
Cameron, right down Cameron, give him a point.
The
you maybe you're on it's on both. You know you're a poor peasant. The hot dog
is going to be supreme because of the lower value. Yes, but you're a rich
farmer or rich food maker. So you're just saying that this is a wash. I'm
just saying it that our perspective in this world matters. Wow, okay, another
point for Cameron.
Yeah, I mean
the next one is actually one of the most important questions. Yeah,
vegetability.
So, which one is better in a vegetable version? I have extensive experience
with this, but I will say it's a little dated. I have some experience
with this, too. I have some experience with it. I actually have some
recent experience with this. For me, let me go first because I've been
in this vegetable game the longest. When I was a kid, didn't eat meat,
I would eat Bocca burgers and smart dogs and smart dogs were fucking disgusting.
I'd eat them all the time. I would cover them in every condiment possible.
That's still what they're working with. Yes. Bocca burgers were the vegan ones
and they were okay. They were honestly pretty comfortable with this. But now there's a
million different types of vegetable burgers. I've had impossible, I've had beyond. I never
had either of those. They're dreaming up new ways to make the vegetable look like a meat.
Yeah, you want to you want a veggie hot dog. It's still smart dogs. Yes, to this
day. It's still like light light light smart dogs. Smart dogs are fucking
hair. So bad. I feel like I feel like this is barely even meat. This has to be
the easiest fucking thing to hold on. Hold on. Hold up. Hold up. Here's here
is a here is a huge
disqualifier for hot dogs. Vegetability
right? Smart dogs, we've been talking about light life smart dogs.
Main ingredient, vital wheat gluten.
Seitan is bread, barely vegetable.
So you're saying that you're basically eating two buns?
You are eating a bun in between two buns.
Damn.
That would honestly probably, I'd rather eat a bun between two buns than a motherfucking smart dog.
Hamburger wins.
Hey, I wish it was going to burger, man.
And I haven't even had that new shit.
I even had that new shit, but I still like Boca Burgers more than I like that shit.
And the final question.
Well, there's two here, so which one are you saying?
Well, Julio said he can't find the thing for that.
Well, we have to do the last one.
Okay.
We have to do that last one.
Alright, then we will do, this is the penultimate thing.
Okay, penultimate doesn't usually need an intro.
Weirdness.
this. So this is if you were going to the North Sentinel Island and you showed
them
this.
If you... Okay, so you're in a kayak, right? You're trying to spread the word
of Jesus Christ and you're running at the North Sentinel, the North Sentinel
tribe like this. You jengaed that hot dog so well. Thank you. You're walking
up like this, right? Which would they understand? You're getting blasted.
Which are they killing? Which side of you is getting blasted with arrows
corners. Is it this side or this side? This side because it's spear
shaped. Which one looks more alien to you? The hot dog is
shaped like a spear, right? So they would see that and say, "Oh,
he's coming." But this is shaped like a sphere. The hot dog is...
The sphere is a shield. If you come with just a shield, you're
like, "I'm trying to protect myself." Do I look like a tarot
card when I do this? Yes. You do. That would be an incredible
tarot card, the chef.
Look to the side like that. Here's another direction to come
like the weirdness question. Okay, maybe less about how weird they look, but I
feel like don't you into the mic just lean back. Why did you eat that?
The I feel like the hot dog is built for the human hand.
It's ergonomically designed to rest in your hand like that the hamburger you're
either balancing it on your why does this size feel so perfect or you're to
handing it wait this half hot dog size. Why does that feel so perfect to my
hand?
Why did you do that? Yeah? Why does this feel? I
is it
exact it's like it was built for your hand. That's what I'm saying it's like
your hand was built for that that
to your wife. No it's perfect. It's like it was God's plan.
I feel like the hot dog is more natural in that sense
you're. I feel like you're more likely to find so yeah God dude
Jesus
Oh my God, you can wrinkle a hot dog. I think you're more likely to find...
I think that if you went out into nature, into an undiscovered, undocumented
jungle, you'd be a thousand times more likely to find a plant that looks like
a hot dog than a plant that looks like a hamburger. Oh my God,
what's that thing in the pond? A cat tail. A cat tail. Nature's hot dog.
There's no burger plant. There's no burger plant. No, no, no.
I don't think I've ever made a laugh like that before.
I don't know what that was. All right, so we're giving this one to the
hamburger. The hamburger is weirder. Or no, we're giving the point to the
hot dog. Hot dog is less weird. Yeah.
The very last one, guys. Very last. Which we actually started with. We
kinda started with. Guys, would aliens like this shit? Is there
visual evidence of maybe an alien eating a hot dog? I had slime sex
with a green alien.
That's all we had to do.
All right.
I had slime sex with a green
alien.
You say I had slime ketchup.
I had slime ketchup.
Oh, actually sounds pretty good.
Oh, I had ketchup.
I had hamburger.
He's a hot dog.
I'm flawless. Ketchup is going to be a tough one. Okay,
flawless
wow okay. What an alien like I mean I feel like that's the same thing as
look at that. Okay, this alien, this this alien is yearning for this burger.
Yeah, he loves the burger. Yeah, burger has more for an alien to study. Yes,
true alien analyzing. You can't
The hot dog, the alien, if you look at the back of this hot dog picture, the
alien doesn't even care to analyze it. He's like, "Yep, this is going straight
in my mouth. I'm eating this." He's screaming at it. He doesn't even care.
This one, he's tapping the glass. "Reveal your secrets to me, hamburger.
What's that yellow stuff on top of the burger? It's so steady." How does he
talk this so well?
He'd say that. He'd say what? He'd say,
"Ugh." Yeah. This is how an alien speaks. Yeah. Can you give me that voice?
So who are we giving this one to, guys? I think it's going to burger. It's
gotta be burger, right? All right.
Hamburger.
Well,
ah!
Guys, that is the last category.
And it goes to hamburger.
We will be tallying these up now.
Go ahead and tally them up.
Count out loud.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, twenty-two, twenty-three.
For burger.
Twenty-three for burger.
Hamburger.
Versus five, ten, fifteen, eighteen.
Hot dog.
eighteen for hot dog and for Cameron one to
two for Cameron. So so even if some you might be saying
it's a two it's a two part. What about Thompson? What if Cameron split the vote?
What well, well, Kenan Thompson is literally what gave the five person lead.
It was he was he was the he was the swing.
If it wasn't for Kenan,
Sarah didn't text me back and let me know. Yeah, it would have been a
complete tie. That's insane. Oh my God. This was really it all came down to the
wire. She said, Are you guys on crack or on podcast?
We are on podcast and show her the results. Oh yeah. Hold on. Yeah, I gotta
send her a picture. Yeah. Send Sarah the results of the
hamburger versus hot dog debate. So yeah, I guess I'd like to close it out
here with a little speech on the winner.
So everybody we've tallied up the votes. As you can see, hamburger got twenty
three and hot dog got eighteen and ketchup, which kind of sounds like
Cameron got two and well, maybe Keenan. Yeah, Keenan got five.
I had slime six
And I'd love to give the win here to Burger.
But you know, the truth is that when a hamburger and a hot dog fight, it's us who are the winners.
Oh, wow.
Oh my God, a ribbon for me?
Holy crap.
That completely is not sticky at all because I believe that these are actually maybe 25
years old.
Well...
But I've gotten ourselves some winner ribbons because we kind of won today, guys.
we got to eat hamburger guys. We got to eat hot dogs and we got to hear a
beautiful song played by our friend. I'm not eating another one. I'm
so full. I couldn't eat another bite, unless you guys want to get lunch. I
would love to get lunch. All right, well, that concludes the battle of the
century. Thank you for being here with us. Go check out patreon.com/podcast
about list. We do this every day on there. Wait, no, that's not true, but
do some stuff on their ketchup and we're going to be having another live sketch
show in Brooklyn. If you're in Brooklyn, come through underworld's biggest army,
go buy tickets at swag poop dot com slash world's biggest money, biggest money
hits. It'll be very, very fun. Us and Pierce Campion and home planet will be
doing live sketch.
God, this smell is just yeah, my stomach. We got to take this trash out right now.
It hurts right now.
Thank you. Beautiful. That's all we got, I think.
Bye!
Shareholder meeting is today?
No.
Thursday.
Thursday you fucking sluts.
So go on Patreon and subscribe to the shareholder tier if you want to be part of that.
And big thank you to Kenan Thompson and Sarah Sherman for guest appearing on today's episode.
We're going to say that in the title of the episode.
Featuring Kenan Thompson because we did get breaking information about the one and only
Kenan.
Yeah.
Alright.
Bye guys.
Bye bye.
(static)
- Do they have a little Ben in London?
- It does piss me off that they name clocks over there.
What kind of backwards bullshit is that?
- We don't even have the name of a clock.
- Clock maybe Bernice.
- Well what the fuck is this then, huh?
What's this, Xavier?
- That's 101.
- Caleb?
What's this Caleb?
Little Caleb?
Hello little Caleb.
(laughing)
- Hi.
- What's this then, Watchie?
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, that's Big Ben, so what is this?
Fucking Watchie?
Hey, I'm Wachi!
Hello, Wachi!
Oh, hi Wachi!
Hi!
I never noticed you before, Wachi!
Oh, I was doing that being alone, traveling to London and doing that on like a tour.
Yeah.
It's like 20 tours.
And here is Big Ben.
At the front.
Yes, you're at the front.
Yeah.
Oh, that's Big Ben.
So if that's Big Ben, what's this?
Wachi?
Hey, I'm Wachi!
This tour's boring!
The tour just continues.
Wachi!
Can we go underground?
Wachi, that is, that is, oh, you're so rude, Wachi!
Oh, and who's this?
Yes.
I know she's beautiful girl.
Oh, who's that?
Is that Mickey Mouse on your watch?
Sorry lady, it looks like our watches are in love.
I guess I'm going to have to go home with you.
I didn't book a hotel.
Wait, it's almost like we're like in-laws now because our watches fell in love.
Yours is kind of more the strong silent type.
I can't get watchy to shut the hell up.
Somebody's talking to you.
They're asking you at one of the restaurants, what would you like to eat?
And then Wachee starts ordering, you have to cover him up real fast.
Uh oh.
Um, he did not say the A5 Wagyu.
Wachee does, yeah.
Oh, Wachee, that's market price, Wachee!
What are you doing?
Come on!
I'm with the lobster!
Live a little!
Shut up, Wachee!
Okay.
Wachee, we are not getting the surf and turf.
What? You get the turf!
I'll eat the surf!
[laughter]
Wachee, shut up, Wachee!
You're ruining this day!
The waiter's like, "What are you doing?"
And you're like, "Oh, it's Wachee."
Like, if that's Big Ben, then what's this?
this video.
(monkey screeching)
[BLANK_AUDIO]