(upbeat music)
- Okay, I'm changing the calendar to October.
Let's see what it is.
- Okay, let's see which fireman
is on the calendar this month.
Let's see, Thomas.
- Missed out on him.
- How old is he?
- 16.
- Oh, his underwear says help puppies.
- Whoa, puppies, remember that?
Did you guys remember?
- Oh, puppies!
on wrestling? The old guy? I don't remember that.
Wait, they got a big boy.
Oh, Jordan.
South Metro. Can you read the text?
It says #HelpPuppies.
All of their underwear says #HelpPuppies.
They all have the Help Puppies underwear?
Yeah.
I need some of that underwear.
I wonder who made that, like PSD.
Honestly, if I had underwear that said #HelpPuppies, I'd be sagging all day,
every day.
Constantly.
That was good.
It looks like Jordan at South Metro has been eating a little too much candy this
October. He's not quite as shredded as the rest of these firefighters, man.
So if the house is on fire and he comes up to pull you out of bed, you say,
"Mm-mm." No, because he's trying to find my candy stash. Exactly. He runs in as
fast as possible, opens the fridge, everybody else is... Or he comes out,
he's got like a giant log of salami that he's fireman carrying over his
shoulders. I know he's taking it from my house as a tip. He sees some smoke
coming from someone's backyard and he runs back there pretending he's going to
put out a fire, but he's grabbing the meats off the grill. It's brisket.
You know, it's a thankless job. I do this every day. Do you have to tip
firefighters? No, but that's what I was thinking. That's what I was thinking.
Do you think like a firefighter every like, you know, while they're saving
somebody out of their house or whatever, like they're throwing a bucket of water
around and shit. That's what they do. Do you use the thing that you think they
take stuff? This has to have been talked about, right? Yeah. That in a comedy
sense, so to speak, in an essence that a firehouse you're just getting paid.
First of all, after nine 11, my dad was like, fuck firefighters.
Cause he was a city worker and he was like all these fucking fight. He's like,
first of all, they'll work like two days a week and then they pull scab jobs.
The rest of the week they're fucking building decks and shit.
They don't do anything. And he was like complaining that like,
all they do is like sit around the firehouse, making spaghetti,
you getting better, better be careful. My Uncle Bobby, he's a fire. I got a I got a
cousin firefighter, yeah, and my dad would say this to his face.
That's bad ass, dude. It does seem like I get to ride the pole. They get to
the pole. You just get to hang out with your friends all fucking day. The pole
can't be that much faster than the stairs. No, you're running down the
stairs. That's such a 1920s, like faster than we go to pole.
I need to get in my cool car now. I need to be in my truck immediately. I
you feel like when you're like seventeen, you don't know what the fuck to do with
your life. Instead of doing the military, you should just be a firefighter. That's
where yes, there's zero chance of you ever die. Oh my God, being a
firefighter is literally the midpoint between joining the military or running
away to join the circus. You're right, the pole, the pole, the fire truck, like
the clowns. Yeah, you're so fucking right. It literally that's what you do.
If you can't decide and there's a dog you get to play with all day, you and all
your you and all your co workers own a dog named spot name spot because of his
spots because of his spot. You get to do calendars. And not only that, gay, straight, bi, Latino,
white, black, all people turned on by firefighters. Yeah, true. You're going to have to rescue
me or you're going to get a sick shift. All the firefighters, every fight, there's first
pan firefighter. Do you think this is going to be, it probably isn't now, but do you think
in 10 or 20 years this is going to start being a serial, a speaker, a side. Oh my, and it's
a fire truck. A siren going off right now. They heard us talking shit. Yeah, we're pretty
close to what basically this podcast studio is a like our it is basically if
you live in a firehouse it's a fantasy factory yeah you have foam pits you have
unlimited snacks you get to do whatever you want they're smoking weed I learned
lockers you have lockers what's that about you should you should watch a
little show called rescue me because I learned that sometimes my dad's favorite
impression same with my mom my dad said rescue me changes his life rescue me and
Sons of Anarchy, my mom loved everything on FX.
- Yeah, I was doing this joke for a little bit.
Didn't really go over it too well,
but I guess it'll probably go over better on a podcast.
Just like this holiday season,
go home to your uncles and your dads and tell them,
did you hear they're rebooting Rescue Me?
And I'm like, no, I didn't.
And they're like, yeah, they're rebooting it,
but it's an all NB non-binary cast.
And here's the fucked up part, Dennis Leary is switching over to NB to still be the lead.
Because he's got the haircut.
He does look like, when I was a kid I got him and Glyn Close confused all the time.
Thought they were the same person.
He really is like a, it's such a misstep if you're, we got a lot of Irishness on the pod
right now.
If you are Irish, you cannot for one second think that you look hot or cool.
No.
It is the worst thing ever. We have something wrong with us.
There's something in the back of your head all the time that is like,
you have to put it in the back of your head and say like,
I look like a piece of shit right now. God said,
we need people dead in the first five minutes of every war.
Somebody's got to be on the front line.
Even I feel like hot Irish celebrities all still looked at like they may be.
so you can be that fucking guy from the killing of the sacred deer. That's
what I'm saying. He literally looks like
really
just like a rogan. Huh? Yeah,
yeah, whatever that guy's name is a hoban go. Yeah, you know, I know exactly
the guy you're talking. He looks like a barry keegan. Yeah, he looks like a
changeling. He looked barry keegan. We look up barry keegan for real. We need
to see and he has a bad spelling of his name. Yeah, just search barry. Oh,
He's the first one. He's got an O in it. Key Hogan. Look at this guy, dude. Oh, yeah. He
looked like he, the elf on the shelf come to life. Look, they even tried to hot him up.
They even put him in underwear. Yeah, they put him in pink underwear. Buddy, it looks
like he got four bellies. I mean, this is that country putting their best forward. Yeah,
this is their absolute top of the line. And we were there together. Yeah, we had a little
a little rendezvous. We had a rendezvous and I remember thinking like everyone,
first of all, everyone in North Ireland looks like Mr. Beast.
That would be hard for me. Everybody in Ireland was so ugly. It kind of blew my
mind. It was weird because there were people... I mean, yeah, what I was saying
before is like, I feel like obviously, I think on average people are fatter here.
All the guys look fucked. Yeah. But I saw maybe, I feel like three of the
the fattest people have ever saw in my life were in Ireland. Yeah, they all they
eat is like carvery and shit. Yeah, well, that's what you said the rise with me
forever that you said that they eat Thanksgiving every day.
He said every restaurant is Thanksgiving.
It's so crazy, man. It really blew my mind how they live over there. Yeah, I
think they're so cool. They do think we have beer y'all yeah. We have a we're
depressed. No, you're not no I'm done with this shit. I'm a hundred percent
Irish or close to you're not no, no, no, we did your results on the air. I don't
I did a twenty three and me episode. What are you a hundred percent Irish? Nice
are you also a hundred percent? I think I'm twenty five percent English. Yeah,
I think that's good. I think that's good. Yeah, I think that's good. Yeah, I just
remember that because of the civil war shit, I don't think that I got I got full
citizenship though. In Ireland? Yeah, foreign birth registry. Lucky. What the hell? How
does that work? They're desperate for citizenship. Yeah, if your grandma. If you can trace back
your lineage. I can't. Wait, really? Two generations, yeah, you get citizenship. It's two generations,
right? I think so. You get passport and then. If my mom gets a passport, because she can
trace it back two generations. But then I think I'm the cut off. Like two generations
ago somebody had to be in Ireland. Yeah, I think so. Yeah, my mom's my grandma.
There ain't no shot like four or five. I think it's like I think me. My entire
lineage is Irish people fucking each other in America for like the last 200
years. Yeah, just like shitty poor Irish people. We went back and visited the
family and like saw that like little one car garage that like both sides
lived in. That's a man jerking off. They got a year each other. Did you meet
anybody. Yeah, I did. I met the family and they're they're fine. I don't know.
You expect like something like, oh my God, be careful. You're listening to
this. They are listening. They're watching this. They're watching and
listening right now. I did. I googled the village that like my dad was like,
Oh yeah, our family is from like this village and I looked it up and yeah, I
feel like you kind of expect to be like, Oh wow, this is like Ireland, but it's
just like a it's a town. It's a shitty town. Yeah, should be town. It's a
the village in my head. It probably it looks probably like exactly like
northern New Hampshire. I'm imagining that my family lived in like Elden Ring
world.
Well, that's the thing you go overseas and you don't realize like in Italy,
they still have to have a gas station. So yeah, I still go to the grocery.
Yeah, there's still just like random shit that looks terrible Irish comic
shinglif.
Hold on clipper shinglif shinglif.
you don't shame. Clearly, no, I
got your man. He looks just like him. You're making this guy up on such thing
as shingles
shame Clifford. Oh, okay, yeah, I know about that guy and he was
a manager of a grocery store in like Western Ireland and
yeah, it just sounds horrible. One like his existence was horrible, just
fucking manager, media light and flower. They all live in them. They live in
some of the most beautiful land in the world and they all hate it because
they've been there. And also it's rainy every day. Yeah. I don't want to live
there, man. I won't live there. Talks weird. I refuse to... Hey, if you try to
get me to live there... Not gonna do it. Uh-uh, not happening. They also don't
have a... Again, they don't have a great entertainment export, right? There's
no... They have bag... Nope. YouTube. Except for bagpipes. They don't have
bagpipes either. Well, that was Scottish. That's Scotland. Yeah. Oh, you're right.
They don't even have dry British comedy.
Exactly.
They have this kind of wet comedy, kind of Mrs. Brown's boys.
They do have the, I mean like they're the only country to like recognize Palestine.
Mm-hmm.
That is true, but they're a little too proud of it.
They're a little bit.
They're a little too.
That's one of the first things our tour guide told us, is like, yeah, in Ireland, like we kind of, we believe in the underdogs, so yeah, we all support Palestine over here.
But I think that there's something like, you know, your uncle who's like a
construction worker or whatever and he's like, "I'm actually a Lib."
Oh, yeah.
Like there's that energy.
So it's like, "All right, I'll support you."
It's crazy to say it like as a country.
Like, "Yeah, so in this country, we actually support that."
Support it.
Saying it, supporting the underdog, too.
I know.
It's fucking nuts.
I think that I've had a couple of family members that have become, like after Trump,
like Democrats, and I think I would have rather them stay fully. Yeah, my mom now loves Pete
Buttigieg and she used to say that Obama was using swine flu to put Christians in FEMA
camps. And then 10 years later, she's like, Pete Buttigieg is awesome. He reminds me of
Subway. My family and my family fucking loves Pete, too. Yeah. What is that about, man?
Because they get to be like star on my shirt. I voted for a gay guy. Yeah. Yeah. Which I
I mean he's not even gay.
Nah.
He's fucking pussy left and right.
He loves it dude.
He's at the Elysian every night in LA.
Yeah.
He's with Pat Gilman.
The stories that I've heard, the stories I've heard about Pete Buttigieg.
First of all he's eating ass and working the clit and going like that.
That's why people thought he was gay.
Just soaking down his arm.
I've heard that he'll book an Airbnb and he'll put a sign on the outside of the door that
says no boys allowed.
He always walks around.
He literally has 12 girls in there.
he literally walks around east east la walking around with it looks like he
just finished like eating a watermelon like a cartoon. It's just like dripping
down
and he says smell my finger arms and
smell my leg up to my knee.
He's he's going up to my but
he's telling these twelve girls,
girls,
I was like pussy.
I was fucking a girl with my butt.
Here's what I was thinking.
Pete's got a concave chest and he's telling the girls,
like you sit on my face and you don't leave until it's filled with nut,
with female nut. And then I want all the other girls to suck it.
He's crazy, man. Yeah, dude.
I fully completely he has a sibian that he has on wheels that he
can you
got a
in the back.
Can you imagine how bad camp David would have smelled if he had been elected
president? Oh my God, so much pussy walking left and right. Secret service
like assassinating people. I'm going to go public that he's straight and he
made me come harder than anyone else.
Robocop bang
stick.
I heard that he has one leg.
He's like FDR. He's like a penis. So I got that he's always got a blanket on
his lap. So no one
no, he's hard all the time. He's like only the blue shoes. Not only is he
straight, he's like the most perfect type of straight. He's only into like
thirty five and above yeah. He's like I don't and he's learning that yeah,
PETA bra. Yeah. Oh my God. They do the Drake bra thing at the Pete Buttigieg concert. Oh
yeah. Oh my God. You should see the bras that Buttigieg has in his basement. It's just like...
His basement looks like a bar in Florida where they staple bras to the walls. Yeah, it's
just dollar bills and bras stapled all across the fucking ceiling. I remember being a kid
in places like that and being like, "This place is awesome." My version of that. My
my parents never took me there. I feel like there's always like you're there's
like a place where it's like this is a scuzzy like yeah, yeah, my mom's take me
to this bar to play pool. She would just play pool and I would and drink and I
would sit there and there was they had my version. I was they had flat bill
hats
I was like this is paradise. I would sit there and look at all the hats. You
ever went to to Charlie's in Harvard Square? No, that was where my family
Charlie Steaks in the mall in the square.
- Do you guys have, where you're from,
I know there's none in New England really,
but in the Midwest, is there bikini barista places?
- No.
- Not bikini barista places,
but there was a place called Krabby Kim's on Western Avenue
that was next door to like the last arcade
that ever existed.
And they had bikini girls, and my dad knew Kim.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
- The Krabby Kim?
- The Krabby Kim.
And then it became--
- Woman on business.
Crabby Kim had like a long, prolonged death
or my dad was like one of the only people. I was like taking care of him.
He's like I gotta go. Oh, my God, I can't everybody who owns a local
cavalier and everyone who owns a local business dies the most atrocious as
possible and you and it's so public. You seem like shaking
who ran this paintball field in North Carolina, so obviously he's fucked.
He's going to die in the most awful way and a paintball accident. He had
He had diabetes, the paint balls, he had diabetes and then he lost both of his
legs and then he but he wore like prosthetic legs to drive and then he
died. He was taking a van full of kids to a
paintball competition. He had a heart attack while he was dry. He like crash.
I think it wasn't like a he was like at a stop sign or some shit. It was like
not nobody got injured, except for him, a mentally, maybe yeah, and so kid was
like yeah, it looked like he got shot by a
would you use training kids for a militia at the yeah yeah they were using
the big like the paintball guns they had in child's play three that looked like
real guns. If you own a barbecue place, you get struck by lighting yeah that
simple. It's the worst because you're so fucking stress all the time and you're
right. I need to make thirty cents this month or I am like going to have to kill
myself.
The margins are so thin yeah. There's a bakery in my town that exploded
really. I think somebody maybe got hurt. I don't think anyone died, but it fully
it blew up. Wow, like windows blowing out of the front. That's a giant fireball.
That was an insurance money scam. Greek lighting. What's up Greek lightning?
Yeah, yeah,
across the street, but I remember it was called Olin's bakery and I remember I
saw after it happened. I saw somebody driving around with a bumper sticker
that said Bush did Olin's.
Ohlins fans. What's that?
Just kind of a play on it.
Oh, I just got it.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I got it.
Now that bumper sticker will say Ohlins fans.
True.
That could be good.
And now it is.
It would be interesting.
Yeah.
All these beautiful women on the computer.
There's this place in, I think, did I take you guys to Flamin' Amy's when you came here?
Yes, you did.
We did go to Flamin' Amy's.
That place used to be so sexually charged where it had like bikini photos all over the wall.
over the world. That's because you live near the beach like me and Cameron.
I've died. There's no, if you were, if you got sexual,
if you got sexual in New England, it was like, it was over,
they would spray you with a hose. You can't be sexual. You cannot. No, no, no.
It's not possible. Not even, I mean, Hampton beach is like, that's people do
that there. And it's like, that's why everyone calls it the Walmart beach.
Bro. I remember fucking on Revere beach.
Yo, getting a Kelly's roast beef, put your dick in that.
Just on those rocks. Wait a minute, wait a minute. You can't be sexual.
we can't have like a it's all you know, there's left over a puritanism and
there's a water is too gross. It's nice in the south. It's too hot down there.
So like well, I got to take off my clothes anyway, but up north it's like
we'll be a bunch of rocky beaches. You guys don't have if you take your clothes
you guys don't have surfers. Yeah, that either is and on the Cape there was
this girl. I'm not as much probably, but there's this girl. I knew who was she
would surf. She was a big surfer and she was like she looked like a wallet like
the most fucked up skin of all time. And she, I caught two different times I pulled up to
her at a red light and I saw her smelling her armpits, just like driving and just taking
two big whiffs. Those happened two different times.
That's allowed. That is cool.
You can do that in your own car.
It's just like a different kind of person I don't see up here.
Speaking of.
You didn't fall in love instantly? Like when you saw like a girl being as dumb as you, you
didn't feel like, okay, maybe we should.
If she had like, if she had both of her hands, you know how when you sit at your house, you
put both your hands on your balls when you watch TV. I put my pinky in my balls. I have
one. Just the pinky. Yeah, just the pinky in there. Pinky through the waistband. Call
it Dr. Evil. My wife did not understand that for many years that I watch TV, if I'm wearing
boxers, both of my hands holding my balls. Put on a fucking episode of Married with Children.
Exactly. I want to see what the Bundys are doing. I hold my balls to Jeopardy. I'm doing
it in case there's a nuclear blast and I have at least a little bit of cushion. Yeah, you're
squeezing your balls because it's the buzzer.
Do you ever kind of like take your balls and like
hold it up like a sheet and then
scratch it like that? Chicken skin.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Like chicken thighs.
From
Waiting. Yeah.
Oh yeah, Waiting. The Brain. Deadpool.
The owner of Mint Mobile.
Star of Waiting. This fucking
guy. Aviation Jin.
Aviation Jin. I want to see him like
personally cancel people's accounts.
You know,
I don't fucking care. You fucking better pay the bill. You should have paid like
yeah, this is Ryan. And then he looks into the camera pool. We have sent your
account to collections. He says like, um, this is what happens when you don't pay.
Jimmy, I want to hang out with him. So bag. It's so fucked up on aviation.
Jim make mint mobile prank calls to people. Oh yeah. Yes. You know, you know,
under with all the phone.
A binder. Yeah, you send out the alerts to every single person's account. It
says your phone will self destruct in five minutes and then
that said that there was a nuclear
mobile people got that. Oh my God, he could do some epic pranks with yes,
mobile and you're just wasting it. If you have this bill every day,
damn alert, it's not a good sell. Amber alert. There is a
did you guys see the video where Jim Carrey talks about he was in Hawaii when
the nuclear like alert went out like a couple years ago, no and it pissed me
off so badly man. He was like yeah, I got the nuclear nuclear alert on my
phone and I was at such peace just knowing that I was going to pass away
and I had the most amazing life ever. Well, I imagine I was finally going to
escape. I imagine you're like running away. You're like running to whatever
the newest the the closest like nuclear
basement, whatever that is, yeah, a shelter, yeah, and you see Jim Carrey
like just so he's got to know something that we see that's what he's completely
he's yeah he would be so happy if he died without anybody finding out what he was
doing true that's a very good to his yeah to everybody in his but he also
said he was there with his daughter and he was like yes she was freaking the
fuck out but I was just sitting there funny faces to calm down all this is all
you have no ideas it's all fantasy he says he was there to paint a palm tree
Is there to practice painting? Painting on the palm tree or paint a palm tree on a canvas?
Do you remember... He's painting a picture of Ronald Reagan on a palm tree. Do you remember
in like 2018 he posted a photo, a painting that he made of Trump as Darth Maul? That's
sick. It, genuinely I did want to buy it so bad. Trump at like CPAC with Darth Maul makeup
upon. Oh my God, that'd be incredible. Jim Carrey is the guy that the Dali
image generator is taking jobs away from. He is the one guy who is
peeping shit like Trump as Darth Maul. He's getting put out of work by the
AI images. And the AI is training on his images too. You can type in
the Dali three right now, you can type in
Trump eating poop in the style of Jim Carrey and it comes up.
Well, they won't do eating poop, as you found out. You have to say
eating mud. Yeah, you have to say a messy mud pie. Mud pie? Yeah, messy mud pie.
We had some Trump, is Darth Maul. Is there a photo of him? I don't know if there's the
paint. Oh yeah, there it is right there. Well, there's Jim Carrey.
Wait, which one? I think if you click that article it'll show up. When I was in first grade I watched
Pet Detective a thousand times. Yeah? Oh yeah, dude,
of course. Oh, well it doesn't have, oh my god. They took it down.
They took down the picture. Wait, who did? Click the picture. Who's in power?
you're taking down who's in power. I don't know man. I'm taking off of X. I
can't believe we figured this out. I think carry going on. This is sad as
fuck. So what are your thoughts on the machine? I'm all in on X. I bought a
bunch of stock. I've been Xing all day. I just constantly Xing. I X like it's
two thousand nine like got a sandwich today like you might like doing like
pedophile jokes like X, you know, two thousand nine pedophile jokes just
trying to be epic on the computer non stop, but it would give me an example of
a two thousand and nine pedophile joke. You're doing it's like I'm a pedophile.
I'm a pedophile said no one ever
that actually can you and then you're a part of it and say, except for
pedophiles, except for pedophiles and then ten years later, you have to you
have to make some post under that one. I don't understand what this means. I
did not mean I don't even remember posting this at the time. I think I got
act. I think I was
honestly. I was probably off that scissor. Yeah, yeah,
all those posts of like comedians from two thousand and eight where they're
being racist and they just respond like the opioid epidemic has affected us all
at the time. I just I had broken my big toe. I learned what Percocet was a
semi home with four thousand pills and I just started micro blogging. I figured
out if you crush the oxys and cook them, you can shoot it just like her.
No, sorry, sorry, not sorry.
And here's how you smoke oxys off a tin foil.
Have you guys ever taken a bunch of barbiturates or downers?
No.
I've taken, I used to steal, not steal really, I used to just take oxy out of the medicine
cabinet in my house because my mom hurt her leg when I was a kid.
And I just did it a bunch but I didn't like it.
It was just funny to do drugs I think.
How many did you do?
Just take like one.
Oh wow.
You're just taking what the doctor said to do.
Yeah, I would take one and it would make me really tired.
I just had one beer. What the fuck? I'm supposed to be drunk.
I did that too. I had a space heater and what I would do is I would take one of the oxys
and then I would sit in my bed and put the space heater under the blanket. Insane fire
hazard and I would just like cook myself for three hours.
Three different things you're supposed to like.
Yep.
Parental supervision.
Steal a Mike's Hard Limited, sit down there, one oxy, Mike's Hard, space heater, fall asleep
listening to a Pete Holmes.
Rainy day, y'all. Oh, I'm cozied up. I'm listening to You Made It Weird, the John
Glazer episode where he gets mad about the E-Trade babies. Damn, that was pretty
epic. I've been saying this for a while. We need to have more like comedy drama
like that. Just for the wax, you know what I mean? Yeah, we need more beef. I
I feel like the only people who are still beefing like that is the comedy mothership guys down
in Austin, Texas.
And all that stuff is such a mirror of, "You drank my special bourbon."
Yeah, exactly.
Kind of like what my brother and his friends are beefing.
"You drank my horse's tail bourbon that I had in my cabinet."
"That entry is $80!"
You don't touch Bert's bourbon.
No, no.
Nuh-uh.
Obviously, I've seen more videos of these people than I've spent time with my father in the
past five years. I'm so aware of Bert's drinking and what needs to happen with it.
Do you watch Too Lazy to Try?
No, I might not.
That YouTuber that just like...
He goes over all the dramas.
Yes, yes.
He does the commentary.
He's the best.
We love him.
I watch him before I fall asleep.
If you're...
Shout out, Too Lazy to Try.
He makes these videos where he's like always saying like these people are stupid, fuck
these people, but it's clear that he listens to every single one. He's like in hell. He
has to listen to every single one of these. He just watches them do good. It is from a
place of love. It's like he's a fan. So Theo Vaughn and Brendan Chobb are officially beefing
because Theo went on this podcast and didn't even acknowledge him, which I don't even know
know why he would do that. That's every single video. I want to be. He has to
make them. I think he's like a more evolved human being. He is a historian.
No, he's like a parasite of what he has to live inside of these guys. Yeah.
Brains. He also dies. Yeah, this is one way to think about it. He's also probably,
I mean, we should, I think he's making money off of these videos. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. Yeah, he's got a Patreon where he details like the craziest, the craziest
stern clips and stuff. I've been going the best and clips old. Oh, me too. I
think that if this the if the like Bert Kreischer documentary guy wasn't doing
that, it wasn't making money off that he would be like a like a civil war
story.
That's the thing.
He's a big history buff, like if Kafka was alive now, he would just be like
trying to fuck people in Ridgewood.
You're doing like weird tweets, everyone
I'm going to stand in front of this girl's apartment for the next three hours acting
like a bug.
I'm dressed up like a spider.
I'm acting like a bug.
I'm trying to climb up the building.
Instead of writing one of the most epic, weird, crazy...
It was odd.
It's really, I read it recently.
The transformation?
Yeah.
The metamorphosis.
Metamorphosis.
I read it last year.
Yeah, it is funny.
I read like his collection of short stories.
I bought it, yeah.
It was cool, man.
He's just a classic pervert weird guy, alone in his room.
All the best authors were huge perverts.
Oh yeah.
And alcoholics.
You ever think about, there's all this stuff coming out about alcohol recently where they
say it's bad for you.
Blame it on the alcohol.
That was the beginning.
Beginning of the end.
And then this fucking piece of shit Andrew Huberman started saying, yeah, it's bad to
drink alcohol.
You gotta get drunk every day, all day.
That's what I'm saying.
Especially if you're doing comedy.
I had a couple drinks on the drive over here.
Thank God dude.
You think that's straight Canada dry?
Nuh uh.
Pure green alcohol.
Aviation gin up in there.
Canada wet.
Completely wet.
All these old authors also, I was talking to somebody about this, that they all were
in a studio apartment and then there was some 15 year old girl would bring them a two-year
a tray of broth every day. Yeah, just like and then they want to marry her
really written because some yeah some like thirty seven year old guy had the
most terrifying obsession with another person in the world. Yeah, it's all and
it's always either yeah. It's always either like a thirteen year old girl who
lived across the street from them or it's like a seventy year old guy, but you
weren't that they had a crush on, but weren't allowed to be gay. Yeah, there
is every every piece of
now every in like all their porcelain mugs had lead paint on the side of them.
So they're drinking just straight lead.
Every now everyone who would be everyone who would be a Melville in a Hemingway
or whatever nowadays, a Jordan Peterson, they go on Twitter and they can say I'm
thirsty AF for this guy. True. They're allowed to publicly be gay on Twitter.
Well, they're allowed to yeah have multiple personalities in line like be
you know.
That's why nobody's writing books that are longer than two hundred pages
anymore. No, no, no, damn true.
Yeah, but that's what that's the thing. Speaking of books that are longer than
200 pages, maybe that's actually it. Oh, you want to do you want to say this
about just talking to Steve Smith about this, about going to like PTA meetings
is like a father getting at like the podium and be like reading. Fuck it
sucks.
Like kind of like anti groomer, but like for reading it's fucking sucks. It's
stupid. It's boring.
Stupid. I want the whole library gone
the ban all the books, ban every single one of the books, burn every book
replacing with a lazy to try video, too lazy to try and all the books in the
library are going to be replaced with DVD. Well, that was when I first started
putting your in a library. I said I like this trend, but then it stopped with
eight. Yeah, they never had more than like eight DVDs in my fucking line. I
had a crazy array of DVDs at my library. Really? I love to look at them. Was it
encroaching on the books? No, they had a whole section. See, I would like to go
to be a library science type of person if it was like basically a blockbuster, but
I guess not.
Oh, wait, I have to say one more thing. We were talking about Stern. Sam sent me
a screenshot the other day of somebody, somebody, you know, people just post
like videos of Beetlejuice on Twitter all the time. And somebody replied under
it and was like, "Who is this guy and what the hell does he have?"
He sent me a screenshot, like a YouTube short where somebody is explaining
Beetlejuice and it's just like the thumbnail is a photo of Beetlejuice and
the caption is just "What is mentally wrong with him?"
Our goal is to get him on here.
Does he live in New York?
I think so.
Yeah, he lives, he's like an Upper West Side guy.
People see him often.
Yeah, he walks around, he's got a schnauzer.
How come nobody has photos, you know that photo of, what's his name?
the guy that directed Annie Hall. Woody Allen. Woody Allen and Epstein.
Nobody's put Beetlejuice in that. All three of them walking down the street.
Well, if you follow him online, he probably will do that. Because he puts himself on like
Manny Pacquiao's body. He does everything. He puts himself on everybody's body.
Yeah. He's a pretty beast. Maria Waza, man. Oh, yes. We have something special to show
you, Conor. Which also, our guest today is Conor. Yeah. What's up, y'all?
Thank you so much for having me.
Of course, of course.
What does this look good?
You have like gum in your hair or something.
Yeah.
You're trying to give yourself a middle part of the hair.
In my hair?
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, I think I'm going to keep rocking this for a little bit.
We did an episode a little while ago, which maybe Julio will find the number right now,
but it was about martial arts.
Yes.
And I found this guy who invented his own martial art online.
Really?
Yeah.
His name is Eddie Vuittonnet and he's a martial artist.
He's a guy who's been doing martial arts for a long time.
was about martial arts. Yes. And I found this guy who invented his own martial art.
Really? Yeah. His name is Eddie Vuitton. And he is he invented a martial art called
Murillo Waza, which he calls the way of unlimited techniques. And so we did if
you we did a whole thing about him in this last episode. So if you haven't heard
that you want some more background on him, you guys can listen to that. But he
has he wrote a book. I ordered this book off Amazon. Jesus Christ. It's fucking
fucking giant. It's like a textbook. Yeah, it literally is a text. There is. Yeah,
I marked out some good parts in here to read through. There's a quiz at the end
of the book too. So, Muria Waza, the way of unlimited techniques, a guarded,
exclusive and confidential course written and illustrated by... And that's
the important part. Wait till you see the illustrations. The illustrations are
great. Grandmaster founder, the deadliest self defense system in history.
This reminds me of the guy that created Spawn. Do you guys know him? I've been
reading Spawn, yeah. Have you seen any interviews with this guy? You know the
like clips that that play at the beginning of the like animate yeah.
He is the man. I love him. What are these clips? What is he where he's like he
like introduces all the episodes like he's doing like a broad serling ma kind
of, but he's like he's like a very nerdy looking guy and I'll be sitting on a
stool in like speech impediment and yeah he'll be like in like a his like
artist studio, but it's got like chains and skulls on the wall and stuff and
I'll be like
it's what would you do if your best friend raped your wife and you got sent
to hell?
that's the answer or I'll be like the question. Yeah, swords. What would
happen if you got stabbed by
and every spawn episode opens with one of those yeah that's amazing dude. It's
he's a type of guy that just doesn't exist that much anymore, like the the
really, really like the already Magda yeah, the really nerdy dude who like is
super into nine inch nails, though, and he's wearing like the like the spiked
dollar. You spiked collar guy, leather jackets, just snails guy. Yeah,
so this is an about this is the about the author section as a little recap for
okay. Yeah, okay, so about the author, Eddie Vuitton is a native of south
Texas, who primarily writes about particular periods of places and people
within the realm of modern day history. Doctor Vuitton enjoys meticulously
dissecting recorded history, especially historical events that are known to have
culminated over time and ultimately led to changes in families, societies,
cultures and even civilizations.
The print is so big, it's huge, it's giant and it's probably a two hundred
page book. It's so he can read it. I would say about seventy five percent of
this book is pictures. Yeah,
Dr. Vujicinet began his writing career as a young man, teaching his martial
art style, which he named Muria Waza. As part of the Muria Waza discipline, he
wrote numerous instruction manuals and study guides that afforded him a wealth
of experience in bringing the written word into formative thought and
subsequent technical action. Over time, Eddie was provided the opportunity in
the mid nineteen seventies to further sharpen his authoring skills by writing
and implementing several traditional and non traditional youth development
oriented programs for the city of Fresno's community development program.
Wait, he's from Fresno,
maybe Fresno Texas says he's from Texas, Texas. Okay, his interest in writing
turned toward a more creative form of expression in the one thousand and
ninety when he began writing fiction, non fiction and short stories, and here
we find ourselves today and there's a picture of him. So the thing that we
found out about him last time, like the first time we looked into him, was that
he was like a judge who got disbarred from yeah, I forget why, but there's like
a whole thing. It's like the third thing that comes up when you google it. Yeah,
there's some document about he had to resign and the first and second things
are these animations that he's made and like he covers an animated movie.
He has a
he's he's got he makes also like graphics. You can hire him to make
graphics for you. It's a fiver guy. He is a
did he is, but he also invented the most deadliest martial art of all history. So
here's the core of Maria was a is victimology and here's how he defines
victimology. Wait there it is sorry. It says right there. January two thousand
four, a complaint was filed with the state commission on judicial contact
containing allegations of and then it doesn't say what
all right. What does it say here's victimology noun, the study of the
victims of crime and the psychological effects on them of their experience.
That is, if they survive the assault, holy shit, that's the core. I'm sorry.
I was distracted because does he have an album? He has a
cover of heaven knows I'm miserable now by the Smiths. He does a ton of covers.
He has some just a regular guy trying to make it in America. That's yes, no,
Steve, we today in the time travelers is his band. So how old is he? He is
probably fifty no older than that older than that, yeah, because he was doing
shit in the s. I feel like he's when did this book come out? This book is from
twenty twenty one. Okay, so here's our first illustration. This is I just want
to show you this is the vibe of the illustration. The etymology these are
these are kind of moves that he teaches people. You can see there's a lot of
arrows. He uses a lot of symbols and a lot of animals. It looks incredible. Yeah,
These are it's really well done. These are arboreal locomotive hands and body
language projections. It looks a little bit like E. T. Yeah, that's what I
thought. I thought that that was a photo of E. T. I forgot that that's the
cobra. I'm in graduate smoking weed with E. T. I want to do so bad. God, wait a
minute. We have the E. T. Mask over there. We can make this. Let's pause the
episode right now and we're going to do a two man sketch of smoking.
Oh, man.
He lights a blunt with his finger.
I eat Reese's Pieces.
Is this his...
Is this a picture of the man?
Yes.
This guy looks like...
He looks like he...
I just picture him...
When I see somebody like this, I just instantly picture them fucking.
Yeah.
You know he has the most...
He's wearing a weighted vest.
And you know he has the most insane
tumors tan of all time yeah. It's amazing yeah like his arm has like a
tumor yeah
he's going so here
yeah.
I'm going to teach you guys a new move. Okay, this is called this is called the
willow leaf block. Okay, I'll read this to you and I'll show you the diagram and
you we can maybe try it out and see if I'd like to try this out yeah. So this
says our arbor a boral locomotive hands and then there's a copyright symbol. The
Yellow tree symbolizes faith, hope. It reassures a warrior by its mere
presence that there will be a path back to where he or she was before any
ensuing battle. Its characteristics and the knowledge of its behavior can
provide calmness under fire, calmness in the form of prudent and metered
sensations of confidence. Its essence will inoculate in any astute observer
a profound feeling of hope and knowing that there will always be healing
mentally and physically as he or she emerges on the other side of a battle.
and then it shows here the willow leaf block. It says willow leaf block and
then a tiny rotate hand up to ninety degrees horizontally opposite way
negative ninety degrees windshield action elbow can move up and down rotate
arm elbow vertically like a pendulum back and forth leaf with like blocks or
slaps
convert to spear hand caster clock attack eleven slash one or convert to
back knuckle caster clock attack twelve or twelve F. So wait, so you're waiting
you wave your hand
I think you need to make a more menacing and then you also need to hold your
other hand like this for a counter move, which can convert to a castor spear
hands. This actually could work. Do you think this could be a good technique?
Yeah, because you you block this because okay, you wave your they would have to
have perfect timing to get past it. Yeah, this is called this is called
windshield action. So you're making a shield of wind. Is that is a person in
the they're wearing a gator? I think that's supposed to be him. Yeah, it's him
with shades and a gator.
- The gator is the coolest thing to come out of the pandemic.
- Oh, absolutely.
- When you would see a guy with a gator.
- Is that what that is?
That's what that's called, a gator?
- Yeah.
- Those things are bad-ass.
- They never fit correctly,
so it's always like a little baggy
and they have to keep yanking it up.
- And there was some study that said that like,
they actually spread COVID.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I remember that.
That was like the first week of like March.
- The problem is 'cause you see 'em
and you're like, let me wear that shit right now.
- Let me try that on.
- Let me put that on my mouth right now.
I literally want the gator. They're just breathing all of their covet germs into
like the space between their chin and neck, and then when they take it off,
when they get home, it just releases. Yeah,
full much out. Yeah, here's another move. This is an attack move. This is
called toss the tea cup.
Do you need a tea cup in your hand or no? No, the tea cup, I think, is
metaphorically. Yeah, there the tea cup looks like a cloud of smoke. Maybe it
says these do look like coal cush models. Yeah, it's a cool. Yeah, I
They look amazing lunge and lean body toward the right while twisting at
waist clockwise at same time, toss the quote tea cup toward the target inverted
hand acts as plate and all so the hand is the plate. The hand is the plate and
the energy. I just can't help it like as soon as you start reading and just zone
out. It's crazy man. It's like well, it's ideal for a rich hand strike to the area
under the nose or used also as a rich hand strike to an opponent's throat. So
I mean, so you do. Oh, I feel like you're like you're throwing a frisbee. I
think yeah, I guess, but and then the other to try the other hand is holding
straight up kind of like she's has one prayer hand and it says next to it a
picture of a knife and it says knife warning. Oh yeah, that's the whole thing
with this is that you're trying to project power to really it's really more
about scaring the people yeah and it also says danger keep off on her stomach
see that would maybe keep anybody from from attacking you that might be the key
Have you seen this like older, fatter guy on Instagram who like goes into like public spaces
and he's like basically like doing that bullshit science of like body language but for spaces?
Really like being a target and be like, "Okay, so what information I'm receiving here is
that there's no cameras above like the children's clothes, so that means that this is safe.
But if you go over to the electronics, there's tons of cameras."
So that's a place, a lot of shoplifting.
Like it's just kind of like basic--
- It's feng shui.
- Feng shui, but like he's just noticing stuff
and saying it in like a smart--
- Yeah, yeah.
- I have all this QAnon information
I need to switch over to something.
- 'Cause now that that's over.
Yeah, I mean, I do feel like we'll get
some giant groundswell of amazing art
out of the people who are putting all their energy
in that for so long.
- I mean, yeah, look at this book.
- Yeah, exactly.
- This is fully what QAnon people sublimate
into. I feel like yeah, once they forget about yeah, I mean the goat David
D's, he's dead like Hollywood in the fifties. How there's like a bunch of
German and Jewish expats who came and like did like noire and all that. Yeah,
we'll have that with we'll have that with yeah,
this is also just one text box on this page. This is a woman who's holding both
their hands up and it says willow leaf, willow leaf, and then it says why
willow leaf and not willow tree, willow tree knife at hand edge faces opponent
yellow leaf palm side of knife hand faces opponent and then it says in big
yellow letters with quotes around it. Windy time, that's a special move that
you can actually see this for a second. I just want to leaf through it. He has
so many special. I think I have some good special move stuff marked out in
here. Yeah,
it's it's so everybody at home. This is like how big the text is. It really is
like truly like a freshman in high school. The other thing is, I think that
this book is maybe not supposed to exist because in the front of it, it says, I
it says like I only released this book in an electronic format. So I think this
is like an auto printed Amazon thing that he didn't mean to man. I think this
is just supposed to be this is against his will. Yes, logo up here is
incredible. He has such good graphic. Yeah, he's amazing. He is the man. All
right, show us some special attack. Wait a minute. Did you know I might be
talking about a school a little bit here, but this is before my time before
I got to New York, but there was a guy in New York who like made a post. Some
my friends know him and they'll remain nameless, but that he invented a new art
form called stand-up philosophy.
And it was like this and then like it was like a blog post and it was like him
detailing like but it's basically like stand-up comedy but you don't have to
have punchlines just go up and like say philosophy and then like everybody was
like commenting below like that's just spoken word.
broken word. Bro, you're ripping off Henry. All you need for a new art form,
though, is just a name for it. Yeah, that's what makes it a new thing. And
that's why everybody here is so lazy in the pornography is stealing our
attention. Every time you open up Instagram, I must be a simp instead of
being, you know, two hundred years ago, each of us would have had at least
fifteen art forms and I would have, I would have been drawing different
kingdoms. Here's what I would have done. You know, the Leonardo da Vinci drew
this naked man. I would have been drawing a naked woman. What the hell is
What the hell was that noise? That's a click. He was trying to, he's playing
Valorant on his computer right now. That's scary. He was looking up
Appalachian Trail earlier. I think that's the Google Doodle for the day.
Huh? The Google Doodle for the day. I don't know what any of that shit is.
I got, I got. You know the Google Doodle? You don't know the Google Doodle?
You know the what? Oh, up in the thing, that's what they call that? Yeah.
It's the special Google. You sound old as hell. You sound. Up in the thing.
Come on, man. Google, Google's like the base, the. You fucking boomer. You
I am. I am. I am a proud boomer. I'm 65 years old. I have 15 classic cars.
Really? Name all your classic cars then.
1986 Chevy Caprice, 1984 Chevy Impala, 1986 Cutlass Supreme, 1990 Chevy Cavalier.
These sound like jalopies to me.
No, well they're works in progress. Basically, you remember when Tim Allen was
making that fucking car in his house and his wife was such a fucking bitch.
Why doesn't she let him be normal?
She would not let him touch his tools.
Here's my problem with that.
Why are you talking, you're yapping at your husband all the time.
He's on TV, bitch.
Shut the hell up.
Shut the fuck up.
He should have taken a little bit more of a Stephen Crowder approach to her.
Yeah.
He should have been sitting in the living room with a table that said,
I need a beer, change my mind.
that video is so funny where he talks to her like she's three years old, like a
dog. He's like no bad wife.
The Steven Crowder video, it's like a ring doorbell video of him in his
backyard and she's like, I'm going to take the car to my sister's and he's
like, no, watch it, watch it, don't take the car. I think she was like, I'm
going to get groceries. Yeah, it was some shit. It was so like innocuous. He
didn't want groceries. He doesn't want groceries. He wants no restaurants. I
sushi yeah, I want to build a restaurant in my house.
Sell sushi at the grocery store. I can get you sushi there. You know I'm
building a restaurant in the basement. Why would we need groceries? How are we
how are we fucking up so bad that he got offered fifty million dollars to do a
podcast and he said not enough money and we barely get offered two or three
million dollars. Yeah, I deal we haven't even have it. We don't even have an
article about us about we need an article so that we need some
We're gonna get us an article. We need complete controversy now.
It does feel like any time I try to do anything in show business, I have to like apologize
for it. I have to like, sorry. I'm sorry I wrote this. I'm sorry. I'm a fucking idiot.
I was thinking today about, can you believe that people make stand up comedy show posters
but it has their face on it? Yeah. I can believe, yeah. Why? It's just weird to me. Maybe I'm
just ugly now that I think about it, but I was like, I don't think I'd ever put my face
on something. Alright maybe we need to take a moment right here. Uh-huh. The three, the
two, three of us and let our friend Caleb know that he's, he's, he's, he's looking
good. You're handsome man. You got a new haircut. Is it my haircut? Dude your haircut looks, see you just gotta know how to do it up.
How to style it. You just gotta know how to style it. Yeah I got a new haircut. It looks good man.
I went to one of the Turkish barbers, it cracks your back.
so
like this. I walked in, they put a bunch of green stuff on my entire body. They
crack my back forty times. They pull on your shoulders and crack your back and
your hair falls out. They cause a cut a couple of my my arteries and then here
I
so hard that your blood pressure just
the videos of the guy wears a road mic on his arm and he just like punches the
shit out of people and yeah he should be putting leeches on their ears. That guy
haven't seen that guy dude. The turkish have found a way to make they figured out
everything coffee in the center of everything. They're in the center of
europe, africa, asia, they take all the knowledge, literally, literally, they're
a leech of human knowledge. That's why they are leeches. He said this live.
This is going on. They said turkish. Yeah. Yeah. That's the thing. What's his
name? The little guy? The little guy is, oh I think he's Chechen. He's Chechen, but he
spends time, he fucks with turkey, right? Yeah, he fucks with turkey. He definitely fucks
with turkey. But what was that chef that fucking, there was Salbe, he's in Bubarak or whatever.
Oh yeah, who like got really sick. He got sick? What? No. I feel like there was an arc of,
the guy that would make the big pots of shit and he would like flip it over. Yeah. And
he smiles? He like. The smiling chef. He got really sick. He burned himself. Really? He
got sick? Yeah. From his food? We're gonna have to see. He ate too much, the smiling
He's not called the smiling chef. He does come up. First result for the smiling chef. The
smiling chef's sick was an auto-complete of the smiling chef. This was last year? This
was a year ago. Yeah, there was kind of an arc of him. Oh my god. The president of Turkey
would come. He got shot? No, he was shot to fame. Yeah, you got to think there's so many,
know I guess Ramsey I know but I know so many Salt Bay this guy yeah I feel like
there's another Turkish guy with like a big like he looks like surge from system
of a down and he's got like a big Hassan Piker he's got like a big like curled
mustache oh really is he a chef or a barber what is like a meat sword guy
okay he's making the picanha they don't make picanha there dude they do well he
could be doing that. All right, what do you got for us? So this is he has a bunch of animal
styles that he calls calamitous patterns. So yeah, you know, like in this was still
my coffee for that. And they got all the different animals. Yeah, they got this. But he's got
a bunch of different animals. We already did some of these in the last one. So he has obviously
as he has a style, Maria was a tiger style, cobra style, human style. He has to human
style was really good. I remember style. These are fighting styles are different fighting
like styles that have special moves, but the one I want to show you today, it
was carpenter and one of them
what is that different? He has two different styles for the African and the
Indian elephant. He has African elephant style and Indian style. They're
different, but this one this is one that I just saw today that has most of them
are like okay. It's like monkey size like monkey fist. You use a surprise
punch. You know it's all it's different moves. I would think that would be human
style human style. You spears and yeah, oh, I remember that use technology. Yeah,
This is Dragon style. Oh my God. He developed. And so here are some of the special moves
that he writes you can do if you're using Dragon style, Muriwaza. So yeah, to compare,
for example, like crane beak is when you use your fingers to peck the throat and eyeballs,
right? Like that. Yeah, exactly like that. Like Kill Bill. I had a fantasy where I did
that to a bear the other day. I had a dream that I was being attacked by a bear last night
and I was punching it in the face. I was sitting on my couch imagining I had to go upstate
for something and then I was sitting there and I was like what if a bear comes and I
was like well I'll simply take his eyes out of it.
It goes up to the car?
Yeah.
While you're driving upstate?
Did you see the video recently of the guy like shooing a bear out of like.
Oh and the bear scratches him?
Yeah.
And he's like get out of here!
And he scorns the bear.
He's just some guy in like suburban Philly or whatever.
And he goes up and he's like yeah somebody owes me a beer after that!
Water!
I need water.
water. I need water. I need a glass of water. There's a girl that transferred to
my high school from Philly and she'd be like, "So what comes out of the faucet?"
And I'd be like, "Water?" And she'd be like, "No! Water!" Why would she be
making fun of herself? She's the only person there who knows- She's trying to
change the world. Who doesn't know how to talk, whatever. She just wanted to be,
there's like, "Oh yeah, that's Philly girl." Dragon Punch, okay, which it says
Dragon Punch and then in parentheses under it, Dragon's Fire Breath. Wow. So
that's you can use fire breath. If you're using dragon style, you can also use
tearing bites, which says dragon eats you. So that's another special move. You can
eat your opponent.
They also have straight arm hand slaps, dragon slaps, tail bent wing slaps,
dragon protects den, low backward kicks, dragon's escapes, stiff leg wheel kick,
dragon whips tail, and then it also says in big letters at the top, dragon pulls
you to only vanish. Wow, this reminds me of when I was a labourer for
construction, I was working for this Irish guy and he was like, "Yeah, I used
to drink with this..." He was like, we were talking about redheads and he was
like, "They're fucking out of their minds." And he was like, "I knew this
one redhead in Ireland who got so mad that he was in a bar and he was
holding a pint glass and he got so mad like that. And he bit the pint glass.
Oh my God. Just to prove how mad he was. And he was like, he just cut his
fucking mouth open so bad. Jesus Christ. That's my favorite prank video.
Have you seen that prank video where the guy goes into a-
No, what did you think of the one I sent you?
Which one did you send?
Butterstairs.
Oh, Butterstairs.
What's Butterstairs?
We might have to watch that.
We might have to watch Butterstairs.
I gotta see it.
There's a video of some guys where they get the edible glass and they put a Bud Light label
on it and they put some empties on a bar and they walk into a bar, they order a drink and
whoever is sitting near the empty glass, they go like, "Hey man, you gonna finish that?"
and the guy's like, No, I'm not going to finish it. And he takes the glass and
just starts eating it in front of
and one of the most of the people are just like, what the fuck like ignore it
and then one of the guys like, Oh my God,
and starts taking out his phone and filming him eating it. He's like he
eating the glass y'all
he eating the glass. I found this video on Instagram of this woman
being like, No, I pulled my kids out of the pool. This is fucked up. And then
she like points her camera at the lifeguard.
She's like, "This lifeguard is a A.I."
- Oh yeah.
- I did see that, yeah.
They're doing the, yeah.
- That's apparently some shit that lifeguards
are supposed to do to get like to watch the most
- According to the comments, yeah.
- This guy is so susceptible.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- According to the comments, what do you mean?
- You believe the community notes.
- That was a community note.
- I bet you believe the community notes.
- I believe the community note,
'cause I believe in--
- Lee Harvey Oswald acted alone.
- Yeah, that's the kind of shit
I push it in the community note, then I believe it. Fuck you. This entire
section of the book, get the fuck out of here, bitch. I can't right here.
It's probably about 60 70 pages is I'm not going to read it, but it's
literally just a list of every robbery on an armored car that happened in the
last
did you read this whole thing? I did not. I skimmed it. I've read parts of
it here. I'm going to skip to some of the good parts. Wait, what Connor,
what do you think of our idea for a sitcom, which is three guys in an
armored car. Isn't that a good idea? Yeah, really good idea. You think this would make
it? Three guys who work for Brinks. All right. Spoiler alert for this. If you don't want
to hear the ending of three guys in an armored car. We had a name for it. I don't remember
what it was. Yeah, what was it? But the last episode, you guys are just chilling and all
of a sudden you look over to the side, big semi truck comes, hits you. You go into a
fucking car dealership. All of a sudden there's a shape, shape, charred blow. You guys get
get robbed in heat. Oh, you are the opening. Oh,
that's an idea I had when I was a little kid. I had an idea for a movie that's
about a henchman. It was gonna be called Henchman, and it's about a guy's entire
life, and he works in organized crime, but he's just like a lowly underling,
right? And then the end of the movie is he's just like sitting in front of a
room and like a John Wick guy, like snaps his neck, like the actual main
character of the world, and then it's just dude, faded black henchman.
wouldn't that have blown your fucking mind?
Well, maybe the movie shouldn't have been called Henchman.
Well, but the entire time you're like, "He's not a henchman, he has a daughter?"
Maybe it's the type of movie where you don't know the name until the end.
Yeah, I put a question mark on the poster.
It's called the Mystery Movie.
You know what they tried to do with Terminator 2?
And if you watch it, they tried to make it so you don't know that Arnold's the good guy.
Yeah.
Like the first twenty minutes.
He's the buffest one.
Yeah, that's what I usually go by.
Kind of a good guy.
Yeah.
But it's kind of, you know, not really henchmen. Henchmen is kind of a one-on-one idea.
Three guys in an armored car. What is the...
It's like the office.
So it's like single cam.
It's like a comedy.
Single camera and then one of us is like the bachelor.
One of us is like the bachelor of the group.
We've got a little bathroom in there, man.
No, they just live in it.
Yeah, oh, that's what... yeah, we get the job, the three of us.
We get evicted.
and then we get evicted and we're like, "We need a place to stay.
Armored car, 24 hour security." Okay. Well... And it's parked in a dangerous neighborhood.
Like, I'm having great episode ideas just sitting here. Yeah. Exactly. Teaming
with that. What do you have? First, Patrick is... You guys fire him and he's
like, "Well, whatever. You can't evict me." And he uses his part of the
armored truck to start a food truck. Yep. I think we came up with that. I think
we actually did a food truck. I think we actually did that. Yeah. Oh yeah,
we were shoving... You're shoving taquitos through the little holes where
Can we get ChatGPT up here? Can we plug? Because I recently did this where I asked
ChatGPT to come up with a pitch document for a show called "Roommates" and it's
about Donald Trump and Biden being roommates. Oh my god. In Brooklyn. Yeah.
But what was the other one? There was one episode where one of us is the bachelor
and they're trying to bring home a girl but we're all, it's like, we have to hide.
You have to hide under the money. Yeah, hiding under the money or like being in
the front of the car. And is this set in New England? This is set in a truck.
Yeah. So anywhere, literally, literally be anywhere. Anywhere that has a road.
It's mostly under the bridge. Anywhere that's not in the water or the air.
Just not water, yeah. Yeah. Anywhere that's flat. And honestly, it could be
in the air. Yeah. I mean, it could be a flying truck if we don't see the
outside. Drove on one of those. And honestly, it could be an underwater
truck too. Twist ending. Yeah, if you put a little... Wait. Oh my God, this
it's completely getting it so well yeah. It does it really well. I mean
this is great. This is too long. It's way too long. Yeah, we just need a
synopsis for an episode. I yeah it's
corn honks causing everyone to armor truck is talking in that script. Yeah,
it's Lisa Mike. Can I can I can I be a can I be an EP on this? Yeah,
non writing. No, what?
Come on, you just want the money. Dude, I'll literally use all my X power on
axe to get this made. I'll be DMing Sarah Cooper.
If you think we wanna be associated with X... Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's actually an amazing idea. She has trumped the whole show, right?
She's trumped the whole show. We're using AI to get Trump's voice so that
she and we're having him say like, "We gotta get rid of the armored car.
We don't like the armored car." We don't like the armored car, Joey, folks.
But she is lip syncing that,
and that's like this, "Oh my God, we have to watch the State of the
Union, Sarah Cooper right there on the screen. I do think it's so funny
Trump. I do think it's so anytime you guys turn on the radio, the armored
car, it's
driving around.
I hate politics. I fucking, we don't even realize it's a
keep the politics out the car. No, what did we say? No politics in the
car. You guys, the car must be stopped. The car must be
all the media that is like seen in the background. Yeah, they're all about
the
every newspaper on every news. Yeah, the weather today. Well, it doesn't matter.
You're going to be in an armored
the weather. The it's going to be bright fluorescent in the back of the weather.
The AC will be on if the car is running
outside. I think it's a great idea. I think such a great off mic really,
really deep. This
our table over there and we're going to be got the white board up and it's
sitting on a table. It makes sense. Okay, guys, here's what you do in the
hero's journey writing is a racing hero. It doesn't make sense for him to eat
his own shit. That's what everyone says to me when I try to this is what you've
all been. This is what you do if you're attacked by a mob. Okay, your house.
Okay, I'm going to read a few paragraphs. Is it a woke mob? Yes, well,
you'll see absolutely probably just pull up a fucking clip of me playing
posters. Here's what I stream. I designed the civilian anti victimology survival
scale to provide a private citizen, a series of active slash passive acts and
actions they can enact when faced with a real time physical threat to self
friends, family or property. These are violent times whereby literal mobs are
attacking people in places with very nefarious intent. I understand that a
mob of hundreds of people is virtually impossible to defend against and then he
says couch taters, senior citizens, children and the disabled have obvious
limitations. Nonetheless, Murray Waza can even things out by turning disability
into an ability. Well, because it's so deadly, I guess you can do that. Oh my
God, there was one thing that he let me see if I can find the
is it the one that's bookmarked? There's something before the one that's
bookmarked. I think that I learned, but that's okay. If I can't find it anyway,
they call him this section is headed. They call me Mr. Show off and it says
the more you show luxury to the outside world and keeping up with the Joneses.
the more you are putting out a subliminal signal. It's a gold mine in here. A thief will seek
the path of less resistance and try to converge your stuff into theirs, devoid of conveyance,
gratuity, barter, trade, gamble pay, work, or outright purchase. That's the concept.
Your Honor, they can converge their stuff into mine.
Keep your garage door closed when access is not necessary, for it projects a carnival-like
atmosphere such as one feels at a flea market or a yard sale.
Especially my shit, dude. I got all these vintage Pac-Man cabinets in my shit.
Oh, man.
Yeah, your garage is sick.
I got street shirts.
My garage is badass.
I have a fridge. Keep it open.
I got all these stop signs.
We have 50 stop signs up in my garage.
Bunch of just rusty-ass stop signs.
Bunch of those old Coke cans where they don't have the lip on them.
One day, those will all be a table.
Yeah, once I'm done. Once I'm done with my project.
Don't you remember feeling like a responsibility? Maybe you guys didn't have this so much.
But like a responsibility to not, like, you should not open up your Happy Meal toys.
those will be worth a lot of money. Yeah, Beanie Babies. Why is it though that
you say the thing about the stop sign table, why is it that like every friend's house that you would
go up to, like go to their house growing up, you'd always go into the garage to get a soda
and there would be like their dad would have made like a couch out of shoes. Yeah. And you'd be
like, "What's that about?" Ah, he just likes doing that. That's dad's new project. I think it's like
when you are a father, you're essentially castrated. That's like my dad made... You need to put all
all your energy into something. My friend's dad would make him skateboard obstacles.
My dad made boxes and stuff to grind.
My dad took a bunch of wine labels and modged podged them onto a canvas and then started
giving that for like four years in a row as Christmas gifts to people. Just wine that
he had drank, he'd take the label off and modged podge it and be like, "Here you go,
mom. Here's all the wine."
Yeah, you can hang that on the wall.
My dad did the elevators at the Prudential building in Chicago, did the maintenance for
him and then he would just like knew the building really well and was friends
with everybody. So he completely furnished our basement with like a stolen
materials from the brunch room. Like square carpet, like the drop
ceiling, the like wood pan, he just all that was just his whole. He made it look like an elevator.
He can go anywhere if he's the king of the elevator. Yeah, he would always say...
My uncle did that shit. Your uncle was an elevator guy and he put on the
on my cousin's closet, he just put the up and down button.
He installed it.
Wait, what are the two elevator brands?
The big ones.
Otis.
Otis Schindler and Tiss & Crump.
Tiss & Crump.
Oh yeah, which are you?
What team are you?
Here's the thing, you bounce around on all of them when you're an elevator mechanic.
You bounce around?
Yeah.
To test them?
You're like, "Oh, fuck this.
I'm quitting.
I'm going over to Schindler."
Oh, I thought you mean you get in them and you jump a bunch of times to try to see if
it'll fall.
No.
My dad would get in the elevator and rock them back and forth.
this one's good. This one's good.
That's the best job ever
try to break this mother fucker next building jumping up in the middle of it.
Here's what you do when the intruders are at your house. Okay, you will need
at least you will need at least three basketballs
a few quote old school clipboards, which will get into what the clipboards we're
having the boys get run in suicide, three basketballs and some old school
clipboards. He says
memorize the following short brief statement to ensure the intruders are
aware that the police are coming. You are home and they can leave unharmed in
a loud voice state policea coming
then throw or bounce the basketball away from you. This will confuse them and
distract their intention. The basketball should not be over inflated. Only have
enough air to bound to be announced around
which misspelled you now.
Well, that could be a around a few that is a that is a technique next squat down
bend your knees and yell the following with greater force. Hey boys, they're
here. Whoa, the use of the term boys communicates to the intruder that there
is more than two to three dedicated men at the sheltered in place in the house.
The use of the term there here is even more chilling. So this is like home
alone when he has a fake party. Exactly. And you throw basketballs to make them
think that they're people and then the and here's what the clipboard I got a
bunch of NBA players in here. I'll kick your ass. The clipboard is for the
clipboard gunshot sound trick. Oh, where you snap the top of it, but that's
actually smart.
You have to mark and do not fire closer than one foot to the ear and body
of the clipboard gunshot, because then they'll know yeah
then yeah I'll just like I kind of want to just show us some of this stuff.
This is Gemini clock theory he invented.
Okay.
Clock theory.
Yeah.
He calls it Gemini clock theory and twin clock theory.
Here's an example how to use Pollock's clock in a stance and this is Malvolio's spider.
The 12-legged spider acts like the hands of the clock.
Holy shit.
Malvolio.
This is him diving into the full, he's going into it.
Yeah.
I want to take you guys back to 2003.
I'm there.
there. Jay-Z is in a big conference room with some record executives and there's a
skinny little guy that comes in and he starts talking about how he's gonna be
such a great rapper and he gets up on the table he starts rapping along and then
he leaves and they say that guy's an idiot he's never gonna make it to
anywhere. His name is Kanye West. Oh my god. That's what this guy is. You're saying in
in ten years. I'm saying it's making such perfect sense to him and society has
not caught up to him yet, because it is like there is some logic or it does
look like he it makes sense in his head. It's incredible. It's Gemini clock
theory and here's a section on Japanese proverbs.
Wait, isn't he? Is there a good one? I'll read you one right now. Does he
have children? Fifty at least? Yeah, here's his first Japanese proverb. He
has. We are fools whether we dance or not, so we might as well dance
gas. That's actually kind of cute, old tea and cold rice are bearable, but
cold looks and cold words are not. That's something you say to your wife. Yeah,
this is this one. Something you can say when you make my tea that can be cold,
but the tongue is but three inches long, but it can kill a man six feet tall.
Wow, going back to booted. Yeah,
oh my God,
the bodies are stacking. That's what they sent him to Afghanistan to eat
people's pussies. Yeah, this is his section on compromised organ malfunction.
okay, where he's talking about his different attacks that you can use on
different parts of people's bodies. Oh, this is the part I wanted to read. He's
talking about groin attack. He has a huge section about groin. Oh, come on, he
fights like a girl. Come on now, come on man, can't be getting up.
Let me read this section about
oh, here we go. De gloving, this is an injury where the scrotum is torn away,
similar to removing a glove from a hand. A Maria was a grab and twisting attacks
can mimic that. He say you rip someone's nuts off. I think wrote him off the
balls, right?
The balls there just
hitting each other's D. Glove the skin. Yeah, screw it. He also he has a full
section here on female groin attacks. He says a well placed knee smash kick,
blunt weapon or opportunistic hand slash arm blow to castor six slash Pollux twelve
groin area is a devastating injury. They'd probably like that shit. The
vulva includes the labia minora labia majora and clitoris, which are easily
compromised by a kick or a focus knee smash. Tell me why he knows this shit,
but my dad don't. The perineum is the space between the vaginal opening and the
anus. The perineum is affected primarily by a well placed opportunistic kick or
regular upward knee smash, the latter usually by a short front lunge or snap
kick. So his idea is to somebody attacks you, you start just like fingering them
and fucking grabbing their ass. That's so weird. Make them kuruwaza, dude. Fight
love, fight hate with love. Oh yeah, then they fall in love with you and then
they get attached. So, and this is some lore that I just discovered. And then
power over them. This truly cements him, I think, as one of the geniuses of our time
and one of the most inspiring stories of all time.
So fellow Mur- he's talking about head injuries. So fellow Mur-Yawazin, be very careful. On
December 26th, that's the day after Christmas, 2019, I tripped, fell, and struck my head,
which caused a debilitating stroke and traumatic brain injury. Several bouts of chemotherapy
had weakened me. I'm still unable to walk, however I can still teach through the web.
Thanks, Eddie Voitakoff."
Wow, this guy.
He writes it like he's signing off but there's so much left in the book.
Have you guys ever seen somebody on the computer pretending to be sick?
Yeah.
On Facebook or something like that?
I just re-watched the first Saw movie because the new one came out and I forgot that one
of the traps that Jigsaw sets in the first movie is literally he puts someone in a thing
thing where there he covers them in oil and he's going to light them on fire and
he goes for years. You pretended to be sick.
Whoa,
that's one of the things he's punishing somebody for to be sick. Well, now it
is it be left and right go fund me go fraud me defraud defraud you by she's
got to do something about go fund me yeah. You should shut the whole thing
down. Yeah,
I'm a certain Biden impressions. We need more Biden impression. This is it.
This is your fucking walks around y'all bro. You're kind of like a video game.
Yeah, Jim Carrey famously played him on Saturday Night Live.
In Sonic the Hedgehog the movie.
I got recommended something on Instagram where they're like,
it's still Jim Carrey. Like Jim Carrey is actually playing him for real.
Yeah, like a guy that's like, yeah.
He's doing an amazing job.
I've heard there's three or four.
He's wearing a, he's wearing a skin suit.
Who's the, who's the senator, the big ugly troll that they say?
Federman.
They change his head.
Yeah.
What?
They took his mustache off and put it on his beard.
They screwed his head off.
Why I mean yeah, that's what I always pop it off like a Lego man. What is he
doing where they're like we need to change his head? Yeah, so make it like
different like he has depression, so they probably took it off and we're
messing around. They're probably trying to solve it with a magnet. How does that
work? So you're pulling all the metals out that make you depressed, all the
hard metals, cadmium,
the surface.
The last thing is the last thing in this book, this last section, this from here
to the end. All of this is a quiz.
about what's in the book. Oh my God, all multiple choice quiz questions with no
answer. No answers list. Ask me one. I bet I'll get it. I bet I'll get it. You
don't even need the key. Okay, let's see here. Just have me one question. I got
you
number question number twenty. Okay, nervous people often began to speak
faster than normal. What are the answer a yes or be no that's a no man nervous
people they shut down as soon as you start talking to him. We don't know
there's no answer. I guess we'll never know. Did you try flipping the book
upside down? Maybe there's an answer key. There's no answer key here. Maybe
you email him afterwards. Oh yeah, contact him, get the answer key. Okay,
here's one for you. Okay, you are roused in the middle of the night to someone
inside your house. What level in the CASS system can you immediately enter?
A level three B level seven C level eight or D level six was my training seven.
Okay, I'm not at eight yet. Well, we again we can't
neither confirm nor deny. Yeah, just you escalate it pretty fast. Yeah
escalations
this everybody in the eighteen hundreds was like this guy yeah and like now
Now we're now it's all coming back. We only think that this guy is crazy
because he tried to make a martial art in twenty twenty one instead of back in
the day. If you had said a hundred years ago, the way this is called a karate
chop. Yeah, you invent a karate chop. You go like this. You finger people when
they attack you, you throw basketballs to make to make them distracted. They'd
say, what the hell is a basketball?
It would have
isn't born yet. This guy two hundred years ago would just be like in Illinois
thing like this is okay. We're going to call this rant to Illinois. I'm the
mayor, yeah, exactly, and this is what the and everyone's like, I guess we have
to do what he says.
Anybody who ran against Lincoln, everyone just attacking each other, it would have
just been like you want to die a much worse death.
Any person who covered their eyes with sunglasses or whatever the past version
of sunglasses were and couldn't walk probably commanded like seven hundred
people, yeah, because they're scary. You never know what they're capable of. They
haven't entered. That's what people would be like. This man has like a
bewitching energy. They just meant that he wore dark clothing.
That's what I was thinking about. I mean, there's no wonder his stuff is so sexual
because can you imagine you're attacking him and he fingers you and puts your own dick
in your own ass. He literally calls those attacks, he calls them insertion attacks.
Yeah, makes you fall in love. And then he's, yeah, once you fall in love with him, he's
making you drop out of college and do just anything for him. You're moving across country.
You get like his name branded on you. You're following him on tour. You're like, do you
want to go to some NXIVM cult that he started? Yeah, you love watching his stand-up sets.
Mr. Russell Brand. Yeah. Yeah. Isn't that what D'Elia did? Yeah. Making girls get tattoos.
Yeah. He had like a whole sex. He had sex in his bedroom, I hear. These guys, they dream
too big. They try to build up to having a whole island. Nobody would, they wouldn't
find out if you weren't trying to make all, if you weren't trying to turn your weird sex
stuff into a big thing. Exactly. Leave it in the locker room, man. This is the hope
Leto.
These guys can go do this stuff in the metaverse.
In front of thousands of little kids who actually got an Oculus.
I don't give a shit.
It's fine.
Let Jared Leto run around there, his dick out in his Morbius suit.
Yeah, let him do his thing, man.
Remember Mordecai?
Mordecai.
Johnny Depp.
Oh, yes, yes.
Twirly mustache Johnny Depp.
Comedy.
It was a comedy of Johnny Depp.
2015.
It was going up.
That movie was going up against The Force Awakens.
was it had no shot. It's trying to be funny. It was was it on that Rango style.
It was more to die and you know what would happen is these movies would come
out and then it would be like kind of like a safe target for like late night
comedy shows where they can make fun of like okay. This is a bomb. They're
putting it out in January. We can pile up like chappy was one more to Chi.
They're all like burned into my brain. Chappy was fucking just because I
remember being like people worked hard on that. Why are you making fun of it?
That's right. What a nice guy.
We can make fun of Chappie, but we can't like, you know...
But we can't go to war in Iraq again, man.
Because we have so much knowledge of how to do it right.
Exactly. Why are we wasting our time with these movies, man?
These late night jokes? We should be doing late night rallies.
We should be doing...
We should be rallying our citizens to all get on a plane, fly over to Iraq right now,
and we'll do that shit right.
Don't drop bombs, drop me.
late night jokes, all this roasting going on on late night, late night, we should
be asleep. That's a good point, man. We gotta get six, twelve hours, sixteen guys
from bedtime inflation, seven PM to seven AM. I'm talking some bedtime
inflation, you know what I mean?
Blood. Yeah, dude, inflate a little pool and sit in it. Blowing bubbles in my
penis. Yeah, get these, get sixteen guys from Saugus, Massachusetts to get on a
plane, all edging together on the flight over to Iraq. I think the moment that
people from Saugus and people from Saudi Arabia realized that their places share
the first same three letters. They're going to change the world in the world.
Okay, so there's a cataclysmic event, Joe Biden's brain explodes live on TV,
it's been revealed that it's just nothing but vanilla ice cream. The world
goes into hell verse and the United States breaks up into different sections.
New England and the Midwest, are they allies? They're allies. Really? What are
they allies of? Fighting against, you know, South. Well, South is cool. Well,
We talked about this before we've talked about civil war two. We talked about
this a couple of weeks ago, but it's over what would it be? I mean probably
over like ashes to like cedar point and theme parks. Oh,
it's gonna be over restaurant. They're trying to get they're trying to get fun
spot out of Laconia, New Hampshire. They want the world's biggest arcade in the
south and cedar point.
Oh my God, that's what the civil war two it's gonna be over the fast food
places and in California they're going to be having the in and out their
soldiers are going to be relaxed and lax and lazy and sloth to much and a
beef, too much beef, too much smoking weed and then going to in and out, but
up in New England we got the dunks. We got we're basically going to have like
Jacob's ladder and Kelly's roast beef soldiers true
honey do crazy. Now why don't you two talk like
Kenneth Banna? What's his name?
Mr. Feeney? No fucking... You want us to have Boston Brahmin accents? I want you to talk
like Ben Affleck from the Dunkin Donuts commercial. I'm pissed off because my dad had a Boston
accent when he was a kid and he trained it out of himself before I was born, so I could
have probably had one. You met my whole family. It got stolen away from me. Patrick's mom
is a baddie. Yep, so true. Thank you, man. She's a baddie. Thank you. Yes, we've had
it confirmed by somebody who's not doing it to me. It's been confirmed by a celebrity.
Yeah, it's been confirmed by my fucking eyes. Well, first of all, Patrick opened for me
in Boston, which was nice, but we drove around his old neighborhood and he was
like, "Man, whoa, I can't change so much." And I was like, "Oh yeah?" He's like, "Yeah,
that... I can't believe that CVS is closed. I used to go there." And that, man, that 7-Eleven is...
Oh, I would like go there and get Gatorade. Yeah, he's got to be the worst
person to travel with ever. And it was like a moment where I was like, "Oh yeah, you're like 12."
The world has like not changed that much. No, no, no. The neighborhood is different though.
My old neighborhood.
Great Scott's gone.
I played there once.
Yeah, I saw you there.
Yeah.
But...
The Blueberry Tour.
I saw you on that one.
Blueberry Tour.
There was...
Oh, yeah.
When your mom said to me after your show, she was like, "I actually liked it.
I was really surprised."
I wasn't expecting to like it.
I was like, "Oh, thank you.
That's very honest of you."
She was like, "I didn't think I would get it."
Not only is she bad, y'all, she's nice, too.
She's nice.
Which is good to hang out with.
That was, my youngest brother, two days before that, called me and was like, "Yeah, I want
to see your show, but I don't know.
I was working in this basement of this retirement home, and I guess there was a huge carbon
monoxide leak.
I don't remember.
I woke up in the hospital."
Oh, yeah.
He had carbon monoxide poisoning.
I forgot about that.
It was so bad that like...
But then he fucking showed up to the show still.
he like just got out of the hospital and was like, he couldn't fucking, we were
like talking to him afterwards, just sitting there just like, yeah, I don't
know man.
That reminds me of my friend from high school, this guy named Uchwald, Polish
guy, doesn't matter. We're in Ridgewood, so watch out, they got shooters. Hey
man, I'm from Chicago, so watch out.
That's the new Civil War.
Polish gangs on Obla.
holding the gun backwards. Hey, come on. What are you doing?
Oh my God, screen door butterfly doors.
Me and Dan Licata had a, trying to come up with new Polish jokes and we were trying to
figure out something where they, like, you ever see somebody eating a CD-ROM? Yeah, that's
a Polish guy eating a Norton antivirus. But my friend Uchwald was a lifeguard in
Chicago and he saved somebody from drowning and the person was
developmentally disabled and he pulled him out of the water and Uchwald was
like kind of fucked up by this. He was like revived them on the beach and like
brought them back to life and it was like kind of crazy and he just was like you
know it's exhausting to like go in the water to pull out another body and he was
just like sitting there kind of grappling with like I just saved somebody and I
have no idea like just kind of like feeling cut. He was like a teenager too
and the guy that he saved was was sitting next to him and the paramedic was like
so how you doing to the guy and he went not too good I drowned it today.
That's an amazingly sweet story. Yeah. Wow. But he got saved. Yeah. All right guys, this
is a go out, use Maria Waza, start fighting your parents. Go to the endorphinport.com
and watch The Mask. Oh yeah, go to endorphinport.com. The new short film by Conor O'Malley. And
also there is a chat bot on there. If you like this chat GPT crap, you're going to love
It's not a chatbot, it's actual, we synthesized human mind on computers.
What?
It's Jeremy.
Yeah, yeah, it's Jeremy.
He's real.
It's the first beyond artificial intelligence.
Yeah.
So you uploaded a guy?
Yeah, he's a 32-year-old guy from Phoenix, Arizona named Jeremy who works part-time at
AutoZone.
He drives an Altima, lives with his dad.
And I mean, if you want to talk to him, then go to endorphinport.com.
Go to endorphinport.com, talk to Jeremy 100% for free.
Take a screen cap.
Holy crap.
grandparent Christmas Day. That's their gift. Yeah. Frame it. Frame it and send
them on their way. All right and then go check out world's biggest army. Under
world's biggest mummy. When is that coming up? Port of Skull Halloween City. October 20th.
It's a show we're doing. So you guys are trying to do a sketch show, huh? Yeah.
Sorry. You didn't call up the ultimate sketch doctor? We have a sketch that we
- I need you to look over.
- Hmm, I'll take a look.
- It's about the mask.
- Yeah.
- It's a short film about some crazy guy.
- It's about a guy acting fake weird on the street.
(laughing)
- All right, thank you Connor for coming on.
- Thanks for having me, it's been a joy.
- Yeah, I texted Caleb and said the same,
I said, this weather make me wanna eat some good soup
and watch a spoopy movie.
And then I said, because you text me something like this pretty much every day, and I responded
Can you read the text I sent you before that?
Yeah, hold on.
I responded and I said /srs?
Because I wanted to.
But why didn't you tell me that?
Because I wanted to have a conversation about what soup we would eat.
I was trying to set up back here so that it wouldn't be on my computer all episode.
Too busy to send one text?
It was really hectic over here.
before this weather literally makes me want to eat good soup and watch a scary movie popcorn
emoji. Before this he said, "Bruh, what did I eat last night? My diarara smells so bad."
Skull laughing, crying laughing emoji. Diarara. Diarara. And then before that I said, "Bubes
or badonkadonks?" And he said, "Broher hair."
[laughter]
I hate you.
We okay so the funniest thing about that the my the my mindset when I text this stuff is
that we are co-workers and imagine getting like imagine you work at a restaurant right
and you're like basically we're at a restaurant yeah pretty much this is a restaurant.
Here's another one the room is like the worst the best worst movie of all time.
So we're co-workers and imagine you're at a restaurant and you give your co-worker like
your phone number because you like hung it you smoked in his car or something
yeah and then he just texts me the room is trying to trying to become like
better friends with you yeah the talking period the talking period the period of
co-worker I have been in a talking phase with every manager I've ever had never
gone but they are brutal yeah hey ever get a nickname from your man they're
- They put you in the talking phase and they're like,
hey, Kathleen called out sick,
I need you to come at 8 a.m. to cover her shift.
It's like, leave me alone, bro.
(tires screeching)