I thought that would work what what you thought you thought that would be
dropping the gun was going to work. What the hell are you doing man do it
anymore? The citrus is in I told you this already, but you put it on the
fuck. You put it on the table to show you know, because I was going to take
one you're showing I forgot. I'm glad that we're getting to the point with nicotine.
This is how all drugs should be. Yeah, you should not be enjoying nicotine sitting back
smoking a cigar having it slowly enter your body and saying, oh, my God, look like poop.
First of all, I'm not saying it, but you should everything like this. You should be taking
it. You got some crap in the middle of your bra. I got I got the fake Oakley's. I got
Oakley's got eczema. Your Oakley's got eczema. That's an Action Bronson lyric. My Oakley's
got eczema! Do you see it? I do see it. Those might be real and then the coating, that happens
sometimes. Do you think they sell real Oakley's for $1? Where'd you get them? The store? The
Chinese store. Are Oakley's expensive? Yeah. Why? They've always been. They cost me $1
only one that doesn't have sunglasses on. I got an Oakley backpack. Oh, you guys are
wearing sunglasses because of the sun. Oh, I wasn't even meaning to do that. I just my
eyes hurt. That's incredible. I almost like sunglasses on also, but I don't want to ruin
my amazing lion makeup that I did. Okay, well, we're getting into it early, guys. No, this
is a lion. You can see the mane. The red is the mane and then the white. Oh, and the mustache
or the main yeah. Well, I didn't want to do full face. Why because I have to do
something after this you did zoo you get did a bit of a zoo pals. Yeah, I do like
a zoo pal. All right, let's walk it through the whole thing guys. Welcome to
the five weeks of planets week five day one day one. I don't want to be more
points. Oh my God, wait. I just remembered I have the most insane news
to share. I'm sorry to do this right at the top, but this is really important.
This changed my life forever. This will tell my ass man. Stop making me sit here.
I saw this on Twitter or I guess I should say X. Yes, I saw this on X this
morning. Do you know how every year the Japanese make a list of birthdays that
are the most lucky and fortunate birthdays for that year and the twenty
twenty four birthday list has dropped? Oh my God way. Now I want you to zoom in
here and look at birthday number one. I just want to show you what this looks
like first
birthday number one. What's the number one most lucky birthday in twenty seven
four
cameras? That's your seven four bro. That's my way. The Fourth of July number
one most
I am the luckiest guy number one guy for twenty twenty four. That's fucking crazy.
isn't that unbelievable? Where's my is my birthday on here? Every birthday is on
there man every way it's ranked it's ranked from one day to sixty six okay
seven twenty three the day of the first day of Leo, which is why I'm dressed up
like a lion. Oh because of the sun is the sun. I don't know
seven. Twenty one is number twenty five.
I can't look at this now I'm going to if I know what my my luck is, then I know
I'm going to have a I couldn't believe I can tell you I was in full denial when I
saw my birthday on there to the point where I was like, oh, you know what that
must be April seventh. They may be they do it backwards, but they don't bro.
It's my birthday. I'm number one luckiest. Holy crap, it literally is
changing my life per per per permanently. Holy shit permanently, yeah, well it
hasn't started yet. Yeah,
so it's still good. Guess what the guess of the second worst birthday is what
fucking
April Fool's Day. Oh yeah, that makes sense and the absolute worst is August
nineteenth. That's the least lucky birthday. If you are burnt more burn on
August nineteenth, that's why I feel fucking sorry. Yeah, you're even you're
you're on one one. Only every four years do you get a chance to be as low as you
are on that list. Your number three hundred and sixty six, not three hundred
sixty five. Yeah, three hundred. That's literally so fucking unless next year
leap year. Yes, Holy Shit! Three hundred and sixty. We got to do something for
that this year.
Dude, I can't. We got to do something for that this year. It's going to be
amazing. We have to do something for it. We have to do something for leap day.
All right, what should we do? I don't even know. I'm too excited to even
think. It's a free day. Well, let's just go somewhere. I've never done shit for
leap day. Yeah. Well, is leap day when an episode comes out this year? Well,
wait, no, leap day. Here, so leap day, the way we should do for leap day is
just do something that will be erased from history when it's over. So we do
something we will make so fucking bad yeah like yeah have a relationship with
each other. I mean a cup,
you don't have a relationship with us. I can get rid of I don't want to, but I'm
saying on leap day, it's like well might as well do it on leap day because that
day is going to disappear. So it's basically we won't even have a memory of
it. You know I'm getting really fat row. I'm getting really fucking scared
looking at the going scrolling down and down and down do it again. Try and get
me in, although I think I'm in the top half at least,
which is amazing. Oh, that's a lot of cups being thrown. Did you start from the
bottom yeah. I started that's kind of pessimistic from the bottom, because I
figured I was like with my fucking luck. I probably am the least fucking best
birthday. Do you look for a
way? I'm the hundred and eleventh that's one one number that's lucky here.
Julio look for the rest. I'll send this to Julio and Julio look for the rest of
our birthday, so we can talk seven. Twenty three is my birthday. I'm sending
a day of
Leo. Do we have a lion sound? Are you a Leo? Yeah, we have a lion sound effect.
So what are you?
What's your...
Cancer.
Damn, dude.
I'm an Aries, man.
Yeah.
So somebody tell about the kind of compatibility for throuples between that.
I think that Aries...
Yeah, can you look that up?
Because Aries and Lios are both fire signs.
I think they are compatible.
Cancer is a water sign.
And I think that you're a water sign.
I don't think that the same thing is compatible.
Don't you want to have a team of different ones?
I think you want to have a team.
Which one is the hacker?
That's got to be Gemini, bro.
Definitely Gemini.
That's a hacker name.
That's a hack.
Yeah, Gemini.
code name Gemini for Leo Neo Leo Neo Neo true cancer cancer. You can answer
the answer. What dancer the cancer dancer the cancer that you could be the
or you could be the cancer dancer. I guess that's a Leo Ares is a also a
hacker name. Ares is a ram whatever Ares could also be a hacker name.
I guess you're a cancer is a crab. Yeah, and Leo is a lion. What is Ares again?
is it a ram ram ram did and then Capricorn is a goat dude last night. I
went to fucking I went to thirty rock or undisclosed reasons to
to see if the tree was on the tree wasn't on. I went to go. I went to go
fucking look at the tree. The tree was completely fucking off man. Yeah, the
tree was there. It is the tree was there, but they hadn't turned the lights on
is pissing me off in a major way. Yeah, anyway, I'd be pissed to did you know
but the
the Christmas tree in Boston is an annual gift from from Canada. No, I
didn't that's from like Halifax or something because we helped them in the
war. I like when countries like each other and they send us their best
Christmas tree every year. I like when their sister cities, but there's some
fucking bunk ass sister. So that's the sister city of Boston. I discover my
Dallas. I think it's Halifax. It's one of them. Do you have a the the whole the
sister city of my hometown was like some fucking spot in Russia. I've never heard
move. Yeah, it's always how it is man. I think that's what it was. How come it's never but
listen to the fact that the fact is Hollywood. Yeah, or that that would be sick if this is
how it was.
It is not like London Derry, New Hampshire's sister city is like a city in like Zimbabwe.
It should be. It should be that all the worst cities get the best sister cities so that
they can be mentored. Exactly. Yeah, their cities can be mentored. You need a bad sister
sister city of New York. So I would what is this? It's got to be a lame. It's a
way bro. Yeah, la is just so similar. It's probably la Shanghai, Hong Kong,
Tokyo, yeah, probably Tokyo, okay, and all those at once. Apparently, big
family city has lots of sisters.
Apparently, New York City has a good chunk. Yeah, that's what I'm saying,
man. Wait, he's there. I like if la is your city of New York. I honestly would
I would say it would be the evil step sister Cinderella style. Okay, so New
York City sister cities are Athens, Greece, Beijing, China, Budapest,
Hungary,
it's just all the biggest city. Yeah, so far Tokyo, I was like do you want to
be Jerusalem City, but Brooklyn's got bitch fine. Brooklyn's got
Anzio Italy,
the get us the for Turkey, Benny Brock, Israel, Benny Blanco, Benny Blanco, you
years in a weird spot, man, it did pop it out. I did it's my new to the upper
deck. He man I don't do the upper Decker. Why is that's where it belongs? My top
teeth or God gave you a top deck to reason and beautiful
your teeth look like shit. No,
you want to three, huh? You want thirteen one? Thirty? You guys are so
right next to each other. That's crazy. We're saying eleven and one thirteen.
What's yours? Who we are going to find it?
That's sad.
Yeah, that is sad.
I'm sorry that you can't find it.
Okay, man.
The one birthday that's not happening.
Guys, this is a big one.
Yeah.
The motherfucking sun.
Literally a big one.
The biggest one we've done so far.
The motherfucking sun.
It's not a planet, but it is a star.
The yellow sun, no Bart, man.
Let's get this shit.
I almost did.
I was going to just dress up like Bart.
Yeah, that would have been a layup.
That would have been a layup.
The yellow sun.
I went the road less traveled.
All right.
Yeah, the lion, which doesn't make that much sense.
Makes a lot of sense when you think of astrological science.
I fully did replace this with the normal one before this, but I guess it didn't
take that's funny. The Cameron report with Planet Feta. It's the star report
today. Today we're doing
the splendor of the Sun. Wow, a star report.
The nearest star system to the Sun is Alpha Centauri. I'd consider Alpha
and
a centurion. Oh wow, I can't wait for this. Bit of an outside perspective on the sun. So,
here we go. We have been trying to contact our neighbor for some time now. Our neighbor
seems very interesting, but I am most fascinated by my neighbor's son. The biggest point of
interest in my neighbor's area. Here are some facts about my neighbor's son that I have learned
from careful research.
There is nothing necessarily unique about my neighbor's son,
but my neighbor's son is still a star.
My other neighbors have sons that are brighter,
or up to 100 times larger,
or hotter.
Some of my neighbors even have two or three sons,
but my neighbor's son is very important
to the people that live in my neighbor's system.
This is because my neighbor's son indirectly provides them with the nutrients necessary for life.
My neighbor's son is currently a yellow dwarf.
It will soon grow and become a red giant.
Then, at the end of its lifespan, it will become a white dwarf.
In billions of years, my neighbor's son will explode.
My research on my neighbor's son has taught me many interesting facts.
For example, the hottest part of my neighbor's son is its core,
and it only gets hotter as the years go by.
I make sure to do all my observation of my neighbor's son
from a long distance,
so nobody in my neighbor's area realizes I'm there.
My neighbors would freak out
if they saw me doing experiments on their son.
If my neighbor's son were to die,
My neighbors would only find out after about 8 minutes, and if my neighbor's son died, my neighbors would surely follow suit.
In conclusion, I must say I am fascinated by my neighbor's son.
Someday, I would love to get up close and personal and really inspect it.
With the technology and advanced science I have, I think I could even do a better job taking care of my neighbor's son than my neighbor could.
Too bad I'm not allowed to approach my neighbor's son due to galactic law.
That's just how life is in Alpha Centauri.
Wow.
That's amazing.
That's an amazing planet report.
You know, that's kind of that's interesting.
You're talking about neighboring galaxies, but we were talking about sister
after we talked about sister cities.
Yeah. Why don't we have a sister again?
The stars aligning.
We do have a sister planet.
It's Mars. Yeah.
Yeah. Shut up.
Someone didn't pay attention.
I pay attention every day.
Somebody's not paying attention. Can you walk us through your outfit? We didn't even go through yours.
Yeah, me and Pats are kind of pretty clear.
Huh, the lion part is very clear.
Leo is orange.
All right, let's go. Let's go, man.
You want to know about my shit?
Yeah. I'm a shining star.
No matter who you are.
Justin Bieber. Dude, I am a celebrity.
Oh, you're Lady Gaga.
No, you do look like Lady Gaga.
I'm a Hollywood walk of shame.
I call it shame. The Hollywood walk of shame.
You look like Lady Gaga. I'm Lady Gaga, man. The biggest star in the universe.
Can you sing, what's that song? I'm on the deep end, watch as I dive in. I'm never losing my shoes.
Wow. I'm stuck on the edge of food. Oh my God. Or it's called something. It's called I'm on the
edge of food. It's a song that I've never seen that movie. I'm on the, I'm on the deep end. Oh,
Oh, I just realized what I'm talking about. A star is born. You're kidding me,
dude. This lines up in an amazing way. Everything has been lining up so
perfectly, it's crazy. Okay, walk us through your prison lion outfit. Okay,
well... It's lining up. Orange here, orange here to represent the orangeness
of the sun. The sun is yellow, man. But then it goes into this yellow here,
which is you mean the beginning of the lion's face and then the outside of it
is the lion's main and then pink and red here, but why a lion? I've said it six
times, but Leo is Leo. Leo is the sun sign. Oh, okay, shit. Well, everyone
doesn't know anything about astrology back in my day. I thought your son sign
was like it was like my son signs. Cancer is sun sign. My son sign is in
Leo right, but your son is not a sun sign. It is it's your son of your
trying bro. You tried to pull a bro. No, I think about astrology
about astrology.
Actually, you probably definitely knows the most. I'm sure he does, but I don't
think what you're saying makes any sense. I thought it's fire. What I
thought it was fire water, earth and air. You're thinking of Avatar. You are
thinking of it. I never seen Avatar, so I wouldn't know you never seen Avatar.
You've seen Avatar. The blue, the blue Avatar. I love that shit. You never seen
I think about that every day when I'm falling asleep, and it gives me fuel for
my life. The Blue Planets, Avatar to the family,
that's what I'm gonna be my family. One day, Avatar to the family, that's what I
kind of is the Avatar to the family. I still haven't seen either bro. I
don't come with us to see Avatar to all fucking amazing. So fucking good life
changing Avatar three coming in twenty twenty five. I think twenty twenty five
Christmas that shit ain't never coming out. No, it's coming man. They're in
post production already. I think no one filmed it together with two and two.
cool. It was only filmed. You know it's a movie I learned about sunshine. Oh
yeah, that one's about the sun. That's about the sun. Is it for real? Eternal
sunshine, eternal sunshine. I had to stop watching that movie one time. Why
son of Frankenstein when he goes into the when he goes into the apartment and
everything's crazy. None of us saw that one. I had to walk out of the movie
theater. Still haven't seen that one. I think I see it might be a mushroom is
man. Oh, the shining shining is about the sun shot. What other son? Oh my God,
that's why it's called the shining because it's about his son. Wow,
Holy Shit! Jack Nickel son. Oh shit and son Shelly and son bitch
son fucking bitches in that movie.
Suddenly Hubrick. Yep, wait and and guess what it's about and it's about
how they faked going to the moon because really they went to the sun.
yeah, that's why they had to fake going to the moon. Yeah, they built this moon
set on the sun. Nobody was going to believe it if they went to the sun. So
they had to say yeah, we actually went to the moon. You need the biggest source
of natural light. Of course, you're going to the sun sun, the art of of
stars, the art of store store still are where the where the sun was art of wire
is the sun man in the sky. Oh wait, it's right there. It's always there.
was on. I was the first thing you see if you're born outside during the day time
and you're looking up at the sky and you don't notice anything else. I guess that
is the first thing you see. That's a really good point. That's a great
camera. Show us your outfit. What do you got man? Well, I got the sunglasses for
the sun. I was going to put some sunscreen on my face, but I forgot to
bring it. I was going to put the light sunscreen on my nose, kind of Larry the
lobster. You can imagine that I got a yellow shirt for the yellow color of the
sun and it's also it's a shirt for a youth summer camp and who do you send to
so you summer camp, you son, you son, yes, and you're not a but my son, the
son is the
or the daughter is the son of the mom daughter's, the moon of the sun. Have
you guys ever tried doing never mind? We never tried signing your butt cheeks
and your balls, sunning no, no perineum do not send my perineum. I kind of
think it might work. I think that that's supposed to remain dark.
I don't think that's supposed to. I think there's a reason that's where the
the sun don't shine. Oh Shit yeah, where the sun don't I think that there's a
completely good invented clothes. The sun was not getting up and no very rarely
there. They were not. Imagine you see a cave man, just doggy style pointing his
butt at the sun. I put a bone in it yeah.
If I saw that shit, I'm put I'm pulling up with a bone.
Take this bone. I'm hitting that thing with the club. Get the hell out of here.
That's why they invented loin cloth. I came over doing that. I'm sick of this
I don't want to see this. I'm fine with seeing all your hairy chests and man
boobs and whatever, but I don't want to see your asshole and you're sticking
great on all the right now. I'm fucking horny because I saw this cave man's
hairy ass yeah and they the reason they're called loin classes, because
they made them out. They used to kill cave lions and make them out of cave
lion skin. They couldn't spell back then, so they said loin instead of lion
and the lion is the
line is not the animal of the sun man. No again, you go a lion is a Pokemon.
think about that. I guess there's a sun lion and Pokemon, but the sun, I would
say the sun animal
there's an electric mouse
mythology, though, I would be like, oh, a mouse, that's the electric animal. I
can't touch my face. You can't touch your no, but I do have an itch. Let me
get it. Okay, where you want makeup on your finger? I don't bro. Yeah, I really
don't you really don't. This stuff is toxic. What's the first time you guys
ever saw the sun first time? I ever saw this yeah probably born outside looking
probably when I left the hospital. I guess I can imagine you being born in a
hot tub. I was looking into the sun for a while. Yeah, I wasn't born. I
like I could imagine I was born in fucking Mount Auburn Hospital, Bro
Mount Auburn. Yeah, that's in Cambridge. You don't know Mount Auburn Hospital.
No fake. I was born in
Mount Auburn. I was born in Saint Elizabeth, Brighton, Brighton, then the
sun. I was born in New Hanover County Medical Center,
St. Elizabeth's Hospital Center of the Solar System. Holy shit, this is
getting crazy. St. Elizabeth's Hospital. Burn, burn, yeah, sun, hot. Also,
who was born there? Mike Bloomberg. What does the sun do? Makes those flowers
bloom. Makes the world go round. Melts icebergs. Yeah, it melts icebergs. Mike.
That's why his name is so crazy. Looks like a Mike, looks like this part of
the Mike. Do you guys ever get scared that the sun's just going to go out?
Yeah, but as I, as a Malfa Centaurian informed us, we wouldn't know for eight
minutes yeah, but that doesn't really help me. That's not very long yeah.
That's not so long. I probably couldn't live the rest of my life in eight
minutes. I'd be able to do something. You wouldn't know in eight minutes. You
would be like you'd be you'd be at your computer. You'd be look you'd be
googling funny movies or whatever yeah, you'd see it go out and you're like oh
my God, the past eight minutes I could have been doing everything I've ever
doing eight minutes on IMDB, a minute try not to laugh. If you had eight
minutes to live, what are you doing? First of all, I would sell all my
belongings, so i'll be super rich yeah. Okay, so that's the first thirty
seconds and i buy new more luxurious belongings with the money. That's the
next thirty, which way the same amount of money. Yeah, well, wait. So you're
selling everything. I sell sell everything, so that includes all the
essentials right and i'm using them. I don't need i'm not going to buy
another toothbrush bro. I'm not going to buy. Would you sell you're not going
to sleep again? I'm not going to buy a bed, so all the stuff that i sell i can
buy stuff that i'll use in the next minutes. So you've used like a and you
I would I would also sell your hair right. I wouldn't sell my hair man. No,
we're going to die with dignity. Yeah, sorry, shit.
I okay, sorry that maybe to be asked me to say what your hair they begged for
me to donate my hair when I got a haircut in Boston. I was like this.
They said fuck that fuck you bro. Every time you can't take my beautiful hair,
beautiful cancerous, walking around with your hair, they have to cut a certain
amount of hair off of your head in order to donate it. Yeah, so they try and
upsell you. They'd be like oh you want it this short. You know if I cut it only
It's five inches shorter, you can donate it.
Like, what the, I don't want five inches shorter.
What are you talking about?
My high school had the biggest hair donation drive in the state, or in the country.
Yeah.
Because the biggest hair, it was the Pantene Locks of Love.
It was a pep rally that we always had to fucking go to.
If you skipped it, you got in a shit ton of trouble.
And we had to watch every single girl in the school cut their hair.
And it got so bad that every girl was bullying girls for not cutting their long hair.
that would have been the most incredible experience of all time for a young boy
with a developing fetish. Definitely
definitely
every single girl in your school is cutting their hair hair cut in front of
you and the and you're watching in an audience, a crown you're cheering.
There's a teacher whose whole job was pep rallies at the school. This is an
entire job. So he wasn't a teacher at all. He was an English teacher, but it
he was mostly there because he loved pep rallies and he loved this Pantene
beautiful links thing so much, and I think that Salina Gomez said good job
and that was big. Big news at the school with Salina Gomez saying great job
cutting off all that damn hair. She got big news. She got yeah. There's news
about her recently. She had a face looked weird in a new photo. That's
that's hardly news to me. That's not much. That's what we consider news.
Now that's what is, you know, breaking Salina Gomez is stuns in new photo.
because it's the news. Now I never donated my hair that she stunned
because her face looked weird. Yeah, you think she got a
she got
she got stunned and then her face got a
Selena Gomez stunk in new photo
Selena Gomez stung in new photo.
Gomez or Demi Lovato. It's one of those fucking one of them stunned. One of
them stunned and left no crud
or shit all the the podcast Twitter account. Every post on there is a
picture of Selena Gomez yeah on the news feed yeah, because I beautiful because
years ago I followed every single Twitter topic and most of them just
word word pop stan. Oh yeah, so I always whenever I switch over to check the
notifications, I see
I see just a bunch of pictures of Selena Gomez,
stuns a new photo. I saw there they're leveling up their captions man. I saw
one yesterday that said Selena Gomez looks resplendent. Whoa
crazy
that's got to be that's got to be an AI right crazy yeah. No way that no way
that a stan is saying resplendent resplendent unless it was like a
flammage stan yeah. Do you imagine that
I got made
I got made fun of
I got made fun of for using a word today man. I didn't hurt my feelings.
What resplendent no dude I used a fucking neti pot right yeah. I used a
neti pot and guys I used to use neti pots all the time. I use it this time,
because I've been sick for like a month now. Use the neti pot this time. No dice
didn't do anything and I told my wife. I said this neti pots used to be the
paragon of nasal clarity and she said
pro she said what and I said yeah, that's not one word that got you. It
used to be the paragon of a pop is stand. I thought that that was a pretty good
sentence. You are sounding like she said. I sounds like you're you're you're a
stop rock trying to make something for a gun of nasal clear. Yeah, that's I just
you know. I thought that it was a pretty cool thing to say and that you shouldn't
try to sound cool to your wife. Yeah, well, how I got to keep it. You should
not in the morning. Yeah, you wait. You don't sound cool to your wife and you're
in the morning. You sound cool to your wife. Like would you disagree that the
neti pot used to be known as the paragon of nasal clarity? You say that at the end
of the day, you say that when she comes home from work, sub girl sub girl, I got
I'll tell you something real quick. I use the paragon of nasal clarity and it
didn't hit like it used to. Straight the fuck up. Yeah, 'cause she's gotta have
something to come home to. Yeah, I guess you're right. You gotta, you know, you
gotta like, you gotta tell your wife like, "Oh, today, guess who I saw? Elmo,
Times Square." She's been mad at me because I, my friends are in town, my
buddies are in town, and I've been going and hanging out with them during the day
on her days off, and she'll be like, "Hey, do you wanna go to get some lunch today?"
I say no bitch. I have to go to the M and M store right and I went to the M and
M store yesterday. What M and M's did you guys get dude fudge brownie, who
dark chocolate almond, please say P, you got two different ones yeah cheater
you only got to eat her
wait bro. You can get a million types of peanuts there. I'm talking about not
even just a peanut. Oh the scanner. Oh, I didn't do the scanner because I got
the red one time and I'm never doing that shit again. Julio, what's did you
scan this? I think I got the golden one golden
I little kid lie. I think I got the golden perfect. I got the gold one.
What do you mean? I'm looking at a one. You mean the yellow one golden golden.
There's no golden eminem. There's no golden eminem as bullshit. You shut up.
There's no golden eminem. You're a bullshitter. You are bullshitting right
now. You have it. We have a witness. No, I wasn't. I wasn't actually. I was
upstairs trying to find a bath. Okay, well, you should call who was with you.
and I'm looking at try to we need to we need some some proof. We need this to be
debunked. There was Snopes type of thing. We're not the fucking golden. You're not
the golden M and M. I don't believe that there's a golden M and M. That's
complete bullshit. Yeah, I don't trust you. I do not trust it. I don't trust
man. It probably was a yellow M and M. Definitely. It was definitely yellow.
I'm a real
the golden. He is not the golden M and that's something yeah, that's something
I would do if I was trying to get like my little brother to like eat a flavor
the skittle I didn't want. Oh, it's the
disgusting banana skittle or some. Oh my God, you got the golden one. That's you
should have all the golden one. He is the one I hear about it. He's looking
ejected yeah. He's a picture of it. Well, my last phone it's on here to a
picture on your last phone, your last, but it was yesterday.
Just lie it's all fucking life. I phone every day. He just lies and lies and
talking about I took I got bro. Listen to yourself. You said I've scanned as
the golden M and M, but I took a picture of it on my last phone. You are a
lot of your teeth. What are you talking about lying? You're lying through your
God damn teeth. I also went to Margaritaville yeah. I saw that that
was amazing. I love Margaritaville man. I guess they gave us a free postcard.
Yeah, I heard about this. Yeah, I saw a photo of all of us. That's huge. It was
fucking you. They do that at Dallas barbecue. Also, what's that you never
been at Dallas barbecue is in doubt. No, it's in New York. Oh shit man. I
they had I went past that place before they had a desus and marrow.
Collab what happened to these guys, I'm going to desus and marrow. I think
there's a serious gap that we might be able to fill in pop culture. Now the
desus and marrow are not doing this shit anymore. Yeah, let's talk to
break out of barbecue. Are that did they get did they I think that they
beefed and then they split they split. Yeah, yeah, which is sad as fuck. What
if each of us tried one of us each tried to pair up one of us got was tried to
be the new part of the new duo with desus. I want to try with marrow to see
see who the real star power was. Then we parent trap them. Oh snap! Yeah. We do a... A deer
and a marrow trap. A deer and a marrow trap, yes. How would we do it man? We'd say you
guys should... Well there would have to be fireworks, yeah. We'd have to bring them,
you know, exactly like the parent trap. How do they do it in parent trap? There would
have to be fireworks and stuff. How do they do it in parent trap? Oh the parent trap would
be a really good D&D thing. That would be a great one. That's a good idea. How did,
do you guys think parent trap would have worked with your parents? No, because my parents
have been to get definitely not mine. Definitely would not have worked,
because what they went to the same pool, it would I mean let me it would have to
be a trap. It would have to be a literal spike saw trap where, if they didn't
marry each other again, they died yeah and even then the trap was more of the
parent suggestion yeah, hardly a trap, a parent idea yeah, just imagining the
saw trap parent trap where it's like hello. You split up and you heard a
little boys Felix yeah thirty years. That's what most of the
movies are about
thirty years ago. A little boy, a little boy got his heart broken. That's a old
fucking picture, bro. That is try. I recognize that one, but that was me and
I was a red dude and I'm never ever. Why is this actually from yesterday and
Caleb was wearing a mask?
So what I'm safe, who gives a fuck
I'm really conscious about my safety. I couldn't find it because it doesn't it
doesn't exist man. Yeah,
it's not racist to say that you're not the golden. I thought you thought he
said it's racist yeah, that he was calling his racist like he always does
crazy. He calls you racist a bunch. He calls a lot of me man. Yeah, he's never
called me racist once you must be doing something racist. I'm sorry. I showed up
in a sombrero. That wouldn't be racist. That would be that would be
cool. That'd be yeah a tribute. Well, I had a shirt on that said I'm Julio and I
was doing this
popping shots. I and I'm sorry. That's okay. You were being that mouse. Speedy
Speedy. I was a tentacle.
Do you guys want to see? Okay,
let's do it. So, you know, I've been doing this art shit for some time now.
Yeah, I thought that when you showed up with the glasses and the wig, I thought
you were being Andy Warhol for a second.
First of all, I didn't show up with either of them. Put them on when I got
yeah, I know, but that's what I thought you were doing now, dude and a warthog
more like guys, fuck, I don't like him guys. You know he used to cut his wig
and then would show back up with a longer wig at the barber shop. He wore a
way he wore a wig. He was a wig cut and then would show back up with a longer
wig and get that cut to pretend like he grow it. He used to paint food. He
painted soup. He would nowadays he would have an incredible job at Amazon. Yes,
thumbnails me food on so whole food before I started this art shit. This
different chapter of my life where everything has changed for me. I thought Andy Warhol,
stupid piece of crap, ruined art, made it all about food. Art used to be about amazing girls,
and now it's about fucking bullshit food and flowers and shit. And I hated that shit. But
now I have moved to a world where modern art is so fucking amazing to me and I'm loving
performances and concepts.
Consent?
In a way that, and consent. All my stuff is about consent. If you look at any of my paintings,
This is about consent. This is about consent. That's just what I do now.
Yeah. What about this one?
That one is definitely about consent.
Okay.
Yeah, because it's the little things that count with consent. That's what that means,
too. That's why that little ass painting is that.
Oh, the little one. I see.
Yeah.
I thought you were pointing to the member berries.
Member consent.
I remember it.
Member consent. This is planet consent, Mars. But here's my modern art for today.
Okay.
Guys, my modern art is Patrick because he's my sunshine. Wow. Give me a smile.
I'm not a modern art fan. I think you flopped, bro. You flopped completely.
That's my art for today. Upside down cup. Okay, I don't have a fucking painting. I didn't
have a painting because I woke up and I had to move my air conditioner to the fucking basement.
freestyle a haiku right now. Freestyle haiku about Patrick being my sunshine. Yeah, okay,
that's going to you are my sunshine. My only my only sunshine Patrick, you are brilliant.
Hold on wait. Start this one. You are brilliant. Okay, friend. Wow. Oops. I can do haikus all
day man. I belong in a different country. I guess that counts as art. They should extradite
me to Japan because I'm so good at haikus. It's criminal how good I am. I showed their
shit up in a crazy way that I'm not even from their country. How many times have you, you
did a haiku again, you did a haiku recently. I'm about haikus. I'm about that shit. When
did you do a haiku last on the other planet? I'll do another one right now. Okay. Cameron.
friend. That's five. Oh, hold on. Wait. Yellow face. Son. I think you're thinking of me again.
Oh shit. Wait. Yellow shirt. Amaze. Amazing son. With a big ass dick. Wow. Yeah. That
that was good. Yeah, that was a good one. That was a good one. So yeah, so I
promise that for the moon I'm going to have some installation, which now
nowadays I'm off of watercolors. I'm off of acrylics. I don't do this charcoal
shit anymore. I am an installation artist. Oh, what the hell did you just
do? The dropper he's filled his fell asleep, spilled his phone. You better go
better job better go get your next phone bro. You look like a piece of popcorn.
me. Yeah, kind of look like a pop in what way I saw a lady today that you buttery
with Joe Steeves.
Buttery smooth
damn. Do you think that you could fucking pick up a girl at the movie theater
while the movie is blasting loud as fuck war scene from say I would put a fire
alarm and then
carry her out. Yeah, I'm saving her life. I would pull the fire alarm and then I
would be walking out and I'd be I'd be flexing my muscles when I was walking
out and I'd be like, if I catch the guy who pulled the fire alarm, ruin the
screening of fucking Napoleon, I'm gonna rip him limb from limb until he screams
for mercy. And I'm like, "I'm not gonna stop!" And I would. I would go...
'Cause I don't stop. Yeah. You know what? I'm thinking,
maybe before that, if this doesn't work, if
I'd pull the fire alarm, do that,
if this doesn't work, I'd be sitting in a screening of Napoleon, and then right
when the movie starts, go, "Oh, I thought this was Napoleon Dynamite!" That's
what I'm saying. Try to make a girl laugh so hard that she comes home with
it work. Hey, where's Pedro and the girl with the bracelet?
Where's Uncle Rico? This is what the movie theater would sound like right
ready.
Hey Napoleon, give me some of your tots
yeah, and then we should do that. We should go to mystery size three thousand
at I would do I guess what you do is you go to Napoleon. You go Dan, this
shit's boring. It's so boyish. I wonder what the Barbie is for Napoleon like
Barbenheimer, there's doing a barboli and what's the barb part yeah, exactly
and I asked the girl for advice. What do you want to go see the bar part of
barboli and I'd say that
I'd walk up. I type girl. Can you tell me you want to go see what the bar part
of barboli and is it like a regal where they have like the reclining chair? So
like you're like tapping her, but you she can't you tapping the chair and she
can't tell because it's so soft yeah yeah and I'd say let's go see Priscilla.
Oh, it's Priscilla. I
a trillion. I creep up behind her and I'd say you want to see Priscilla.
Do you want to see Priscilla? Do you want to go into a different? So it's
romantic AF.
That's about that's what that movie is about is real. It's about romance and
it's about falling in love with a girl. I'm trying to think about seeing a girl
and falling in love with her. Have I why there's so many movies named after
girls man Priscilla, Barbie, man, only or Barbie, where are the guys, Sarah
Sarah Silverman program, yeah, saving Sarah, so saving Sarah Silverman, which
I would save her so you would save her from Zionism. Now I'm trying to sunshine
could be a girl. I would save her from her boyfriend. Man, would you guys marry
a girl named sunshine? Maybe I would marry basically any girl with legs. I
was asking my girlfriend these hypotheticals last night and
it was it was like hypotheticals with very, very poor signal, like very poor
caveats
like what would you fuck Peter Dinklage if he was tall?
That's a good caveat. Peter Dinklage is good looking man. Just stuff like that.
The height is not a problem for me. Yeah, no, not for me either. If there's any
little people that listen to this shit, your height is completely fine with me.
I don't even register. I don't register. I don't register most details about any
person. When I look at them, I look right through them and I think about what I'm
I dream about tonight, big or tall, nobody matters to me. No one at all one
looks like you're all just
a sidewalk or I'm looking up at the sky. Every single person in my vision looks
like super hot. Yeah, my whole world looks like super high. I want to shatter
you glass style, turn you into millions of bits of pieces. Oh yeah, I want to
slow mo crouch down, throw my gun up in the air,
been around. I want to play that game again, grab the gun, shoot you, throw the
You all should come over and play VR this week.
Dude, I want to play VR Superhuts so bad, bro.
We should do that.
Oh my god.
Have I ever made you play my fishing game?
No.
That I used to be addicted to? I used to be addicted to fishing in Korea.
Really? That's amazing.
There's a Korean game, or at least it takes place in Korea,
where they put you, it's a VR game,
they put you in real Korean fishing spots
and you can watch YouTube while you catch fish.
Wow.
And so I would put on videos of guys playing blackjack
and I would play fishing until four in the morning every night.
I've been seeing there's like people who are using, I think it's the new
Quest, and it has like a camera so you can do your dishes and watch YouTube at the same time.
That would change my life. You've never done that?
You can't watch YouTube and watch dishes?
Watching it on the headset. What do you mean?
Everywhere I look, it's not a dish anymore.
Where are you looking while you're washing dishes, bro?
I'm looking down at the dishes.
You're going like this.
But everywhere I look, the video is still there.
no, they should do it. Where I completely they should do taking a picking up a
plate and turning around to scrub it. What are you doing? Well, I'm turning to
the the rack
to put it on the rack. They should do augmented reality games for chores that
she would maybe get it done. We faster on fucking you have to kill the aliens
that are on the making
now. Please don't make the bad.
I would have like a cod zombies. It would be like Nazis in my house and
way. Be like we are putting dust on his book.
Get out of here, you damn Nazi zombies. Nazi fucks who love dust. Stop!
He puts crumbs all over the microwave. That's what the game would be called,
Dusty Zombies. Yeah. I do that, man. You do the dishes. Dude, it makes your
vacuum cleaner shoot like bullets, like a mini gun. Oh my God. So you're like
doing around. Dude, cap detected. Ron Jeremy put jizz all over your dishes and
you got to clean that shit off. That's good to yeah. That can't be him. Why
can't be Ron Jeremy's jizz dishes? I want Ron Jeremy's jizz on my dishes way
less than anybody else's jizz. Probably the worst jizz on earth. Yeah, it's the
worst. Well, you want jizz that you want on plates. Yeah, but then you got to
you got to give him money to for his likeness. Do you need if you're can you
use a prisoner's likeness? Well, no, we'll just free will. John Raramie. We
just got to do a like kind of a knock off and it'll be yeah, Jeremy Ron. Yeah,
exactly guys got to the easiest name switch of all time and jizz washer or
it could just say
it could be like an unnamed man's come who I really do like the idea that it's
that it's like a like Wolfenstein's future Nazis that just that they're
making whatever it is they're just dirtying your house and trying to get
you to or like just a one really annoying guy who's like I bet I bet you
can't vacuum the floors. You fucking stupid bitch. I bet you can't clean the
toilet today.
make me do it. What one really like put my brother in a permanent implanted
ship in my brain, where I see this guy every day of my life permanently. The
first thing I see when I wake up is him be like I bet you can't go to the
grocery store. I can show you fuck you fuck you David David look at you
sitting on the couch instead of going to the grocery store. How do you shut it
off, though you don't David Holt
you have no if you can shut it off, you're never doing your choice man. It
has to be and then your girlfriend when you wake up has to be roasting you to
and your girlfriend gets back, you're so bad at sex. Yeah,
having it on while you try harder.
That wouldn't make me come. Shut up, David. David, shut up. Who are you
talking to? She doesn't know who you're talking to, but you have the headset
on. You have the headset, you're talking to David.
I think that this is a brilliant idea. Yeah. I think that the thing is
about everybody complains in... The big problem in Korea and Japan is that
people play video games way too often, especially in Korea. People play video
games for like 24 hours straight. So we need to turn life into a video game.
My life is like a video game. My video game is like my life. You gotta try hard
to beat the stage. Trying hard to beat my wife. Not like beat, but like a boss.
Like in a boss sense. Yeah, like she's like, "Trying hard to clean my knife."
Oh, yeah, exactly. "When I am doing the dishes." "Nasty's got the dust all over
like this.
My dish is...
Trying hard to beat the girl, like in a boss lane.
You're resorting to beating women.
It's about what the song is about, video games, beating stuff.
You're turning the song into a beating women song.
It's not about beating women.
Yeah, it is about beating women, but in the terms of like Bowser.
If I say I'm going to go home and beat Bowser, people don't freak out.
Yeah, exactly.
They're not like, "Bro, you can't beat Bowser."
This is why they call him Bowser.
Is Bowser just an animal?
Your wife's name is Bowser?
No man, Bowser's a big lizard, a turtle.
I mean he's a turtle. He's a some he I think he's some dragon combination.
Yeah, dragon turtle. He's a dragon slash turtle. He's a dragon turtle. He's a
large. That is his that is his species and what's a Koopa a turtle Koopa Koopa
is not a type of Koopa. That doesn't make any sense, bro. Golden M&M. You're
a poop. Take a break. Golden M&M. Why don't we take a musical break time?
I'm going out. Why don't we take a musical break? What do you mean with the
new song from OJ the alien OJ the alien. I can't wait to hear what OJ cooked up
for the sun. Did OJ pop off this? I think OJ might have popped off with wait
first of all this album cover is crazy. It's fucking amazing. He looks so happy.
Where is he? The mall, the mall and the song is called OJ the alien sunshine of
the mall in the sunshine of the mall. Now that I'm thinking about it, that
would have been such a good sample flip
but let's
Let's answer it guys.
It's OJ the Alien
And I just won a goddamn court case, y'all
I'm going to the mall with Dr. Dazzle
We're about to go on a male shopping spree
OJ the Alien
Me and Dazzle are going to the mall
Gonna get shoes and basketballs
We're gonna play hoops with the sun
Oh my god, it's lots of fun
Go to the mall in Beaverton
Bought everything but I'm not done
Gonna go to Best Buy, look at all the Blu-rays
Season 2 of Happy Days
I love the beat.
I'm the number one TV commercial guy of all time.
Oh, Dr. Dazzle, it's your turn.
Kick it!
Me and Osher rolling up in the luxurious G6
I make a beeline for Victoria's Secret
They told me I was blinged but I'm sure they didn't mean it
I got the Groucho Marx glasses on and a green wig, yeah
And I'm dressed like I'm on safari
the
I guess Dr. Dazzle is at Horrorcore this week.
Yeah.
Kind of a weird song to do the Horrorcore angle on.
What?
Wait, B-Lack's back?
Wait, Belak's back?
On this track
OJ Dazzle, V-Lack 2
Shopping spree and then some food
Spencer's gifts and journey shoes
3 of the cards I got for you
Ready to buy anything
JC Penney, wedding ring
Sampling a chicken thing
So much fun our day will bring
Dazzle always tempting me
Changing room where friends can see
Different flavors underwear
Wow his thing has zero hair
Think that was an epic fail
The jail prison is where I belong, hanging out all summer long.
That's right y'all.
I spent all the money that the court paid me on a shopping spree with my male friends.
Oh!
This is the best day of my life.
I don't ever gotta look at my dumbass kid again.
Oh, she has a kid?
Fuck you, Venus.
Venus. Oh, I forgot.
Peace.
Damn!
Wait, that was the posse cut of the summer, man!
that might be a summertime class. It was a summer hit. That was a summer hit.
You're about to hear that number. Yeah, they didn't hear that on tick tock. I
liked how it had to do with the sun. We need to do with the sun and OJ songs to
pop on tick tock. Yeah, I think this one is the one that's gonna. I think that
this has a serious potential for a tick tock. I think I gotta speed it up. I
think we gotta speed it up. So it's a little bit faster voices. I'd be way too
high man type. They already have high voices. You can just do change tempo on
not all three of them are very high voices. You could change the tempo. Oh
true and just make it go
and then yeah, the thing could be like when I'm talking to a mouse
when I'm talking to a mouse at the club or when a mouse is
on to tick tock. They say like mouse core. Exactly. I wouldn't be like what
I'm talking about. So be like mouse core. They call it mall core, though,
to this small core x mouse core, this core crap they got going on on these
fucking apps to drive me out of my mind. I know I can't stand it, bro.
They got this one either. They got this one with the blade runner guys. Yeah,
or the guy from that robot core. It's called quarterly core core core. It's
called what yeah, and it's basically what if you had a thought about how sad
your life was and what if life was truly banal? Wait, what what are you talking
about? Basically, life is, but dude, you wouldn't get it because life is
nothing man.
Just about the banality of life
core core core core core core. It may pull up core core core core core video
at Cork. No, you want to see this. You do ban. This is what Gen Z is doing. Gen Z is
now called the Doomer Generation. Please do know because of this, not the Doomer
Generation. No, very much the Doomer Generation. I choose life and it's about
men's mental health. I choose fucking life, man. I don't want this shit. I'm so
interested in analyzing Gen Z's psychology. Wait, no, just Google. Why are
you going to take time to find it?
Oh, what the hell is what came up and we want a YouTube video. Yeah, we should
probably just look up a YouTube clip of Korkor. It's not the same thing. TikTok and YouTube
are different, bro. It's video. But it's so fucking silent. The best Korkor experience.
It's... Okay, this is TD Bank Korkor, I guess. Wait, that's a great-ass song. Wow. But he's
crying. That's why man.
We've laughed at all the good things that have happened since.
[Music]
Corkor is about touching each other in front of Jimmy Fallon.
Then I get to the end of my life.
[Laughter]
Bro,
this is Corkor, Jimmy Fallon, and Theo Vaughn?
I guess.
I thought it was like Blade Runner and shit.
[Music]
Tommy Shelby. Is that Tommy Shelby? Tommy Shelby vibes.
I'm tearing up a little bit. This is already so sad.
Not only did I miss out, could I miss out on caring about people?
No. Dio, please God. I missed out on feeling probably a lot of the love that people had for me.
Bro, Pacliachi vibes.
Wait, who's that though? Is this from olden times? This core?
It's from an underwear commercial. Yeah.
helicopter's landing. I really feel like we don't all comedian because the sad
clown aspect.
Okay, we don't need to be watching this. I don't need to watch any more. We should
just make I think I fully understand. Yeah, wait, let's go to the line. Let's
make some core core right now. Yeah, we need to look up core core background.
Yeah, we need a core core background song. This is about to be this is going
to pop in a fucking crazy way. No, it is that song by Duster.
yeah stratosphere or whatever yeah duster stratosphere is good or like a
fucking Giles Corey song or something yeah.
Wait is about to go crazy. I guess the album all right Patrick we're going to
wait. No don't pick this one. It's what is what is that one scroll down?
Because this is the full album. You can just go to the time stamps.
No go up just play this. Okay, this is good. You look lonely. I can fix that
one hour loop.
Okay,
So then it's like slow fade in on me right?
Sometimes it feels like in the modern era we're so disconnected from all the different connections
that we could have.
And also it feels like the food at restaurants isn't as good as it used to be.
And the music has gotten louder.
Look up the sound wars.
(upbeat music)
- Okay, now cut to one of these.
Cameron.
- Oh, me?
- Yeah. - I thought you were
going to Pat.
- Okay.
- The sandwich I ate the other day gave me indigestion
so bad that my whole chest felt like
it was jumping out of my chest.
I feel like I can't even eat turkey ham anymore
without the nitrates going into my system
and just totally bubbling me.
I feel like I got bubbles in my stomach and chest
Almost every day I wake up, walk into the train station,
I feel this (gurgling)
I shouldn't have eaten that turkey or that ham, man,
or the turkey ham.
This stuff is destroying our men and our women.
- I've developed-- - Mostly men.
Men usually eat more cold cuts than women.
- On average, on average, okay.
I've developed an adult gluten allergy.
I never thought it would happen to me,
but here I am, close to 27 years old,
And the only bread that I can eat is sourdough.
Sourdough's good for breakfast.
And it's good for sandwiches.
But I can't eat Hawaiian rolls anymore.
Just the other--
Which is one of my favorite savory breads.
Just the other day, man, I was cleaning out my humidifier.
It had a heavy mineral scanning, scaling.
Mineral scales were collecting
onto the humidifier's heating element.
I soaked it in a solution of vinegar and water
for about 15 to 20 minutes,
and I started to scrub it with a soft brush
so as not to damage the element.
I was rinsing the brush under the sink
so it wouldn't just have vinegar residue and minerals in it.
I flicked back the bristle.
The vinegar shot straight into my eye.
And you know, when you think about
how men are treated in society nowadays,
every single, the way that women make us feel
is like we always have to act like Howie Mandel.
We always gotta be thinking about
putting a rubber glove on our heads and doing Bobby's World impressions and
talking like gizmo.
But I don't know if I can be Howie Mandel every day.
I don't know if I can make a deal or no deal.
I don't know if I can be the host of America's Got Talent like that.
I don't know if I could have a podcast where I talk to celebrities like David
Spade and ask them about stuff that happened 20 years ago.
Man,
Hollywood has failed us.
Chicken Run 2, Donna the Nugget,
will not be showing in theaters.
Straight to streaming.
Netflix, lose out on billions of dollars of box office.
Can't watch Netflix.
Girlfriend's grandma watches it every day.
Locks us out of the account.
I feel like, what's life worth living
if I can't watch The Crown?
The killer.
- And I'd be sitting in my room just thinking to myself,
the way that society right now
is treating these Marvel movies is terrible.
They tried to set up a new, entirely new franchise type thing with Kang and Paul Rudd as the Ant-Man
and it's like nobody even wants to watch it anymore.
It's like nobody even is, everyone is just confused, but there's hours of lore that you
can look into.
Thor Ragnarok, thought that was the funniest fucking movie I've ever seen in my fucking
life.
Yesterday I spent about an hour and a half downloading every Fantastic Four comic ever
published to my hard drive.
About 40 gigabytes.
Holy crap.
Go to copy it onto my iPad.
Select all the files.
Drag them into the iPad on the Finder interface.
What do I see?
No progress bar.
Impossible to tell how long it's gonna take.
If the copying is stalled,
ended up having to use AirDrop.
AirDrop 40 gigabytes of PDFs.
Oh.
Took me quite a long time.
AirDrop.
What is it? Is it Bluetooth? Is it Wi-Fi? I never learned.
Something completely different doesn't affect it doesn't compress files at all or affect their quality
So it's actually ideal when transferring files from a Mac to an iPad and these women nowadays
They want you to do all these kind of new type of sexual things like eating the butt from the back
They want you to they want you to put you there. Let me eat it from the front
Let me eat the butt from the front
Let me make the but I don't like the front
I don't like the back all these girls want you to do doggy style nowadays
So just normal missionary instead of normal mission girl. I want to sell I want to look into your eyes
I want to look at you. I want to have a real connection.
The doggy style, also your butt cheeks are too big and the cushion is really whittling down my length.
I'm going to be completely honest.
Nowadays women would rather start a OnlyFans than go with a guy to the costume store and try on different costumes
and have a kind of makeover montage.
Nowadays, what happened to montages?
Men don't get makeover montages anymore.
I lost my way to the exit gate.
these flushable wipes, I use them 40,000 probably wipes over the course of a
couple months. I use about 10 wipes per butt cheek every single time I take a
shit. Get a call from my landlord, "Your bubbling disgusting crap is coming out
of my sink downstairs. Have you been using wipes?" I say, "Yeah, they're flushable."
He says, "That's an oxymoron." "There's no such thing as flushable wipes." I said, "What
What about dude wipes?
Dude wipes not even flushable, man.
We have fully extincted the spotted lanternfly.
Why?
We sit around, we tell each other, you know, you see a spotted lanternfly, you stomp it.
They're gone, man.
They're not coming back.
That's our fault.
With the stress that men have nowadays, it's like, it's like jizz is depleted.
It's like men don't even have enough.
stress that men are going through it's like they can't even develop jizz.
Nowadays men
don't even produce a liter of jizz or they don't even...
Nowadays men only produce a tablespoon of jizz. When they do develop it
it's spongy and yellow.
Exactly. Because they're depleting because of our zinc.
Because zinc is depleting from the
the American diet. Society laughs and jeers at men nowadays who are
the golden M&M.
It's not accepted to be a golden M&M anymore.
Nowadays your boss shows up to work dressed up like Slowpoke Rodriguez and says, "That's you."
That's you. You look like Slowpoke Rodriguez. You look and act like Slowpoke Rodriguez.
They haven't yet invented a haircut that can make your hair longer.
Wait, that was actually... Why did that put me in the worst mood I've ever been in my life?
Why did that make me feel so fucking awful, man? Wait, life is over. I don't want to fucking die.
Oh God, no, I like eight minutes that we just did of that. That's what would it
that's how I would feel. I could do a full episode of that. I really felt
kind of crazy being in that zone. We were on some magic. I was trying to
think of what is even the thing is my life's amazing. I want to be real and I
don't believe any of that shit. So when I'm in that zone, it's okay. Wait, so
we got to do something something search happy music one hour. Yeah, oh yeah,
wait, sun happy, happy core, sun core, sunshine core.
We heard of Korkor, now there's Sunshine Korkor.
Now we're going to do the opposite.
We're going to talk about what's so lovely.
What's amazing.
Search just happy music background.
Search walking on sunshine instrumental.
We're creating sunshine Korkor.
Walking on sunshine instrumental.
Happiest song ever.
This is like, yeah, do walking on sunshine instrumental.
Walking on sunshine instrumental will be good.
Because imagine just saying amazing things over this.
Yeah, this is what life is really like.
We just did what people, what
we're really like we just did what people what the doomer generation thinks life
is now time for time for the Millennials
guys this morning. I jumped up out of bed. I didn't brush my teeth until later
because I didn't want to brush them before breakfast and my breakfast tasted
amazing.
You guys
men have been jizz and men has been depleting nowadays. No increase. Let's do
increase. Well, yeah, but what if that's a good thing? My birthday is number one next year.
My birthday is 111.
Oh, my birthday is 113 on the luckiness scale.
My friend is in town from Mexico and I love him even though he lied.
Nowadays, you can be a golden M&M.
They show you the golden M&M store.
It's a true thing.
My favorite restaurant closed for renovations.
And guys, two days ago, they reopened.
I finished my fruits and vegetables puzzle the other day,
and I left with the last piece for my girlfriend
and I got to see the happiness on her face as she put it in.
Wow. I put a new I got a new soap for the shower.
And guess what it smells like?
It smells like apple matcha.
Actually, it's my girl.
I've been using my girlfriend's soap in the shower.
I washed the sheets that Julio slept on and now they don't smell.
My dog had fleas and then we gave him medicine.
Wow.
I took medicine the other day, allergy medicine, and it helped.
My cat has been doing a new thing where he does a wall run.
He tried. I pull the string on the wall and then he runs on the wall
after the string. I can fly.
The graphics on video games gets better every year.
The electrician that actually never mind that said the electrician
that's working on my apartment currently, his dad almost passed away from COVID.
There will be no more war in the United States.
The war's over.
Yay!
The McRib is back at McDonald's this month.
I got to see my favorite color when I looked at my closet.
Today, I dressed up like a lion.
Last night, I had sushi.
Me too, but a different sushi.
It was worse, but I still liked it.
What I had clam chowder for dinner last night.
and my girlfriend got it for me from her work and I looked at the ingredients for it and
the clam chowder actually had coconut milk in it and that made me upset but the fact
that my girlfriend got me clam chowder was awesome!
This year my mom told me for Christmas she's gonna buy me alcohol.
Whoa!
I got a, I tried a new drink last night!
It's water with ice!
Last night I ordered a cocktail at a bar and it came with a rim made of chocolate.
My toilet rim ain't stained.
I did all my chores in the house.
Me too.
And every single one of my chores is pretty easy.
I'm considering buying a new air fryer.
I got 500 likes.
I'm just kidding I didn't.
Whoa!
That would be amazing.
I'm imagining 500 likes on Cameron's picture.
Me too.
Oh yeah, go Cameron!
Nice post Cam!
My teeth haven't fallen out yet.
Never will.
The IRS sent me a letter.
And I ignored it.
I also ignored a letter from the IRS.
And a letter from Con Ed.
It's Cyber Monday today, y'all.
Wheeee! The deals are abound.
My student loans are destroying me.
No, they're not. Me too.
Until they review my plan.
My plan that I applied for. What's your plan?
My income-based repayment plan.
I'm letting a lot of things go to collections.
Yipee!
I have no medical problems I'm aware of at the moment.
but that could change. I
scared
it again. No, I think my mom said I might have a rare heart condition.
Really? Yeah, I don't remember. She said you love too much. You have a rare
heart condition. It says here on your chart. I've been looking over the test
results. It says you love too hard. So the both of those are going to go viral
on tick tock everyone. I just everyone basically everyone who listened or
watch that everybody take a turn and split up each one of our things into a
different video yeah, everyone just take one and post it on your own account. So
it looks like it's coming from everywhere. So it looks like a core core
compilation. Yeah, core core and what are we going to call the nice one? So
I'm going to sunshine core sunshine core, well,
core core core sun core more sun core is good sunshine core floor neighbors sun
core. What's the opposite of the of a core? The outer the crest, the mantle
core mantle core crest, core, that's a mythical creature. There we go. We'll do
yeah all right all right well come see us on December tenth at the bell house with
girl god oh yeah and joe para and some other people that I don't remember right
now I'm in my job era
nice cool
the next premium episode will be the moon. It will be the last episode of the
five weeks of planets. I don't want it to end if you're not signed up for the
for the premium stuff you're missing on a lot of stuff you missed out on thanks
on Thanksgiving this year. If you didn't sign up for the premium, miss that on
our Thanksgiving play is not getting unlocked, bro. There's a Thanksgiving
play in the
shareholders to hear the executive producers to and we might be doing some
more plays. We might do another original play for Christmas.
I think that
that's it. Julio everyone wishes Julio a safe flight that nothing happens and
I'm gone. I'm home. Find me Mexico. Wait. That was amazing. Wow. All right.
Bye everybody. Bye.
[static]
[beep]
This is the story of Neptune, a Planet Report by Cameron Fetter.
Once upon a time, 30 astronomical units away from the sun,
there was a blue and icy planet named Neptune.
One orbit, Neptune woke up and felt depressed.
"What makes me special?" asked Neptune.
I feel so average.
Don't worry, Neptune, said the sun.
You're very special.
For example, you're an ice giant.
Your distance from me means that you're dark and cold, covered by frozen, icy materials.
A big whoop, replied Neptune.
That doesn't make me unique.
Uranus is an ice giant as well.
Well, maybe your surface doesn't matter.
It's what you're like on the inside that counts.
have a rocky core," the sun said. "Yeah right, so does Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Uranus,
and probably Jupiter and Saturn too. I knew I wasn't special. You're just making me feel
worse. I think I'm going to kill myself." And Neptune opened its desk drawer with its
hand, where it kept its revolver and used its hand to put the gun to its atmosphere.
"I'm done doing this with you!" screamed the sun in anguish.
"It seems like every rotation you threaten to kill yourself. You think you have it bad?
Look at Pluto. The poor guy isn't even a planet anymore."
"Even my suffering isn't unique," sighed Neptune.
"I think I get it now. I was so concerned with being special,
but what's actually special is that I'm so similar to everyone else in my solar system.
It's about togetherness and family."
That's right, said the sun. I'm glad you came around.
Coming around the sun? Yeah.
Coming around me, I mean. The me. The me. Let's eat.
And the planets all started in on their Thanksgiving dinner.
Moral.
The moral of the story. Okay.
There is nothing interesting about Neptune.
(laughing)
(scary music)
[Music]
[music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]