*Alarm*
You see my clap?
Welcome back to P-A-L fuckin' radio, man.
W-P-A-L
W-J-A-C-K-B-E-N-S-I-N-G-E-R
*gunshot*
Jack motherfuckin' Bensinger, what the fuck is up, man?
real quick, I don't go by that name.
What do you go by?
Okay.
Well, because my whole thing is you guys said, "Yo, you want to come on to do the Five Fingers,
right?"
Mm-hmm.
Am I spoiling anything?
No, that's fine.
It's in the name of the episode.
So I said this, "This is a perfect opportunity because I quit acting."
No.
I quit comedy and now I'm just straight up a rapper.
Jack Ben rapper.
No.
I don't.
So?
You don't?
I don't have a name now.
You have no name.
Names are incredibly corny.
Wait, I have a fucking name. Don't say that shit.
You're talking to three named men.
You guys started out the show like Porky Pig.
Like, come on, man.
You're bringing some negative energy right away.
I apologize.
You guys are more like Sam the Salamander in that regard.
Who is Sam the Salamander?
He's a new, more handsome representative of the animated scene.
right yeah. Oh, I don't know what it describe him in detail who Sam the
salamander he's like a one dimensional James Bond with liquid skin. You know
I'm so
yeah, this is sounding a lot like gex to me, but gex is two or three
dimensional. Yeah, I don't know if I know who gex is. He's a gecko James
Bond man from our old video game from the three do right or the p.s. War he
that he's told celebrities yeah and Bubsy would chill. This is how I feel
he used to run with Bubsy back and he walks around with a remote control and
control any TV. Oh he's like Adam Sandler. Yeah, he's clicking, but he
doesn't have any pants. Adam Sandler click clacking. Can you here's why you
shouldn't quit comedy man. Imagine ten years from now you've been doing comedy
acting for years at this point, ten of them, plus however many you've done so
far and then you get invited to the Adam Sandler basketball games.
you in Chalamet? It's just not how I want to get there. Yeah. Like yeah, I want to
get there no matter what my path is, but I just feel like I'd be embarrassed if I
showed up. Like I want to show up because I've been like being more real, being a
musician. Right. Like if I show up as a goofy ass. I would want to show up and like maybe that I was grinding really hard and I sold a lot of stuff at my store. Yeah. Do you think they invite? Do you think it's just the upper echelon of every...
They invite bodega guys. You have the top store in the area, they're gonna invite you.
That's true. I mean, they do play random pick up with people as well.
I mean, he gets in the fights too. Adam... what's his name? Sandler. Adam Sandler gets in the
craziest viral fighting. It's almost like...
it's not even about the basketball to him. Remember when he threw that shovel at that girl?
Yeah. In 2014. He threw a shovel at a girl? Remember that video? No. Adam Sandler throwing a shovel at a girl?
Remember when he wore a troll face t-shirt?
Mm-hmm. Remember when Chuck and Larry got all... Remember when you Chuck and Larry?
Yeah. Engaged. Chuck and Larry had a big grip on my school life. Yeah? Yeah. Homework?
Well, it was more like that's... We would call anybody, including myself and my
friends, if we... If somebody was kind of gay, we'd say, "You are Chuck and Larry."
You're both of them. Yeah. "Well, you're Chuck and this guy's Larry." Right. But they
didn't... Must have not seen the movie and realized that it was for... They were doing
it for some kind of legal. You guys aren't so much like the characters themselves
who are doing it for legal reasons, but the relationship between you guys is
similar. You are more like the perception of Chuck and Larry by me,
by me, because I didn't watch it. By Nicholas Turturro, who's in that movie.
'Cause I know the poster of the movie, that's about all I know.
Well, it's Chuck, by the way, Adam Sandler and
Chuck. Imagine those two. I mean, that's a hot and steamy... The show,
Chuck or well no or Larry which one is where Kevin James yeah Kevin James yeah
that's his name those two I don't think there's a worse couple to watch have sex
maybe in his that's a you know what that's a big joke in the movie really
yeah if you remember the movie like I didn't I didn't watch that's how I found
out Freddie Mercury was a gay guy when they play the you're my best friend song
at the end of the movie my dad and was like you know why they're playing this
right? Were you disappointed? I wasn't disappointed. It was just like my dad was saying it was
like it was trivia for the movie. Right. You thought it was just, no this is the end of
the movie song. This plays at the end of every movie. But no, it's because he's a gay man.
You know what I think? Every single movie should end with this song. The maroon 5 one
or the who sings that that's Adam Levine. No, I'm thinking is that Adam Levine? The original
by Beethoven. Oh, that's not by Beethoven. Most of that stuff is by Beethoven. Can you
imagine if that's a dog you're talking about Beethoven? No. No. Imagine what? Can you imagine
if a natural animal did noise like that? Because birds go like this. I've noticed all sorts
all sorts of different shit. So what I'm saying is imagine if a bird went
there's certain ones. I do
now I stopped acting.
That's true. That's true. Okay, that's music. Yeah, all right. Thank you. Then
I accept it. I accept that. Yeah, but you're saying what if a bird sang a
song? I'm just curious, not a parrot, but I'm just right like a bird. That's not
mimicking somebody's thing. Originally is singing the song. I was going to say
have you seen this this starling? This is what news is a bird. What's in the
news about a starling? There's a bird that made a complete mimicked R2D2's
voice and human voices, but the most impressive thing was that he got bored
of mimicking human voices and then he just pulled out the R2D2 sound and it
was pitch perfect. No, no, no, no, no, no, it's it's complete R2D2. It's like
it's all the beeps and everything. Do you know the bird that does the cell phone
noises at the hardware store? Yeah. Droid.
It goes... I can't think of a cell phone noise, but it goes...
It goes...
I can't fucking do it. What cell phone do you have? The one where it kind
of pops and goes ding. Oh, the notification... Oh, okay. It pops? It
has cheeks? It pops, yeah. Yeah. That's scary about a bird. Well, that's...
I'm talking about the noise, not the bird. Oh, okay. But a bird could
make that noise. They can click and certain birds can mimic human voice. So
perfect. Did you guys ever in the jungle do it's like they're parading to scare
people that would freak me out. I don't know why they do it. Did you guys ever
know anybody who had owned a parrot? No, not yet. I had a pair of eat my eat some
of my hair when I was a kid. That's what I happened to it. Yeah, I said some nice
and also as a kid, but nice try you to guys. Well,
there was a pair of try you to go. You're already getting into the the wrapping a
little bit. I was installing a glass shower door and a lady said, you want to
hold my parent and take a photo with it? And I said, for sure, and then I had a
photo taken of me and the parrot ate a piece of my hair. Remember we said that
parrot on the bus on the 73 bus in Boston and he was a reoccurring guy or I
only saw him like two times, but I don't know why would you why would you get a
whole extra ticket for the parrot and said, just let it fly? Yeah, he had the
the parrot on his on his arm. It had no it was not attached to him in any way.
I just was sitting on his arm and then I was like, can I take a picture of the
parrot? And he was like, it's a good thing you asked, because when people
take pictures without asking, the parrot attacks them.
That's a bad quality. No, it's not a good thing to have in an animal to be
picture of. I saw a picture or a video today, a bunch of videos actually of a
lady who got a cat off the road. Some Russian lady raised the cat. The cat
getting bigger and bigger and bigger and bigger.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't tell me.
Panther!
It was a panther.
And how's it behaving?
Like a dog, except it can jump 20 feet in the air.
Yeah.
Well, some dogs can do that, that's for sure.
Like a Great Dane run up a tree.
A Great Dane can't do that shit.
A Great Dane can jump 20 feet in the air.
A Great Dane's dog die instantly.
Yeah?
How?
Great Danes last like three years.
Really?
Yeah, they do not have a long lifespan.
In bed.
Put that on any sentence.
sentence. At the end of any sentence, it'll take a change to me.
In bed? Damn. That's actually good as well.
Hey man, everything's in bed if you think of the dirt as a fucking mattress.
Think of the world as a floor.
It's the bed for human death.
Human seed theory.
You're bringing that back?
Well, it's either going to be me or the government.
Didn't you talk about this last time you were here?
Maybe.
Nah, probably not.
No, so say it again.
No, it's just the idea that people are seeds, so just be careful if you're walking around
around a graveyard don't be don't be surprised. Don't stand in grass for too long. Don't be
surprised like for a tree. If a tree grows out of the ground and then instead of leaves
it's a dude. There's a bunch of heads. Oh because they're planted in the graveyard.
That's a seed. Like an executor. Sure. Like the Pokemon. That always you know how the
person who's in charge of a will is called the executor. The person in charge of a will
is named a Jada. Wait oh my god. No they've actually been separated for some time. That's
tell me why she's still in charge of him. Then tell me why she's still so fine.
You have a like a
business all the time that has to hurt so bad when she said that she was in
love with two pucks. Imagine your girlfriend, imagine your girlfriend told
you today that like juice world was her soul mate man, but that was know him. I
don't know. He probably didn't know world. Yeah, juice world world of juice.
I'd go to a store like that. There's a place near me called snack world and
then you walk in, they just sell weed. They don't have so many different
worlds in this city. Every store here is a world. There's so many types of worlds.
Basically Mario game vibes.
Yeah. Or outer space.
Well, that's one way to look at it.
Yeah, I guess there's an outer space Mario game though too. So Mario kind of covers outer
space.
He kind of covers everything.
Yeah.
He did cooking.
He did it all really.
Is that actually, that's a foray he hasn't jumped into.
Cooking.
Mario cooking.
Mario cooking. I've never seen a Mario game where he cooks a mushroom.
Yeah, but a full game. There's a game where he does.
He's always cooking up those mushrooms. He's always cooking on the goombas.
How do you think he's going to get a one up from a raw mushroom?
Is there a Mario restaurant game?
Mario cooking?
Chef Mario lasagna.
Okay, that looks real to me.
I love this game.
See, you get to scroll around and click.
This is Mario cooking.
What is this?
You click on the squares, see they get bigger?
That's five points.
That YouTube video, cooking with Chef Mario.
Cooking tour adds Chef Mario.
Cooking with Chef Mario.
So it looks like to me here that there's a full Mario cooking game based on all these
pictures. Where else would they have come from?
Well I want to play this game.
I'm alright.
I want to play it right now.
I guess I can't argue with you wanting to play that game.
I'm so beefed out guys. Do not ever eat beef.
Beefless.
Beef bragging.
I know.
I can't stop bragging.
He's bragging right now so bad.
I went to a beef restaurant last night and I beefed.
Hit the mute button on him.
An all beef restaurant?
All beef dude.
in the drinks, even the drinks were pieces. It wasn't even just beef.
They molded beef to fit the cup moldy beef and you had to put it
this is funny. This shit is not cool. No, we don't want to hear about your
beef escapade. Okay, go ahead. Talk about your beef escapades, man.
My beef was so delicious and well done. I got all of the beef. Well done.
Wagyu. You, you, you, you got it well done. You didn't make you didn't cook
it. No, the guy came and he said it's medium rare. Okay, and I said we'll
take it well done and then he just kind of left it for a little bit. You got
Wagyu cooked well done and then he wiped up all the all the grease with a
napkin and I ate the napkin. Even at a restaurant he's making people wipe the
table for him. No, I didn't spill anything. Is that a theme that you guys
with? He spills and doesn't give a fuck. I'm not anti white. I'm not anti white.
Don't go around saying I'm anti white. You can go around saying whatever I want.
I imagine his butt's like a cast iron. I know. Let me give an outsider's
perspective. I have no skin in the game here, right? I can give a hell. You have no skin.
I'm almost, well I have skin, I have a lot of skin. Oh yeah, sorry. I'm more
normal. I realistically have more skin than any of you guys. That's probably true.
Now, have you ever thought that maybe you don't mind liquid being around
because of your preferring Aquarius environments, etcetera. I grew up about
four miles from a beach. Water was a big part of my life growing up. Newport News.
There was always water in the house, so spilling it was not a big deal. I, my,
here's my rule on water, dude. If I spill water on the ground. We're not talking
about water. No, no, no, no, no. It's not water and it's not the ground. It's
drinks on the table. We're talking about spilling coffee and soda on the table.
Coffee is mostly water. Hey, man. You see this right here? I thought that that
that was a beautiful that looked like a country. A table is a ground.
I won't, that'd be too much to move it, but we could get the spill cam. Okay,
there we go. See the stain?
I'm about to, you're about to be a stain. This is a brand new nice table.
You're about to be a stain on God's beautiful creation if you keep talking
like this. Save it for the...
Switch the angles, y'all.
Wait, that was insane. Wow, Cameron's new angle.
Cameron got two cameras. Cameron Diaz.
Cameron Diaz, Charlie Zengel.
Cameron Diaz, man.
Did you know that she used to be
Legged.
Legged?
What did you say?
Stop hiding behind your microphone, bro.
Yeah, why don't you stop hiding?
You're the biggest one and you're looking so small and bashful, man.
Get up, get up.
I'm not hiding, bro.
You're hiding right now.
I was just watching an interview with Cameron Diaz.
I just left.
I was just watching somebody give an interview who mentioned that Cameron
Diaz was previously there.
Whoa
wow,
where was that on the Internet, man,
honestly, it was on a late night talk show with somebody that I had never seen
in my life. Who was it? I don't know him. Oh, you don't even know you already.
You watch the whole you went on YouTube and you searched interview without
ever to do. She was right there.
A second ago, they had mentioned that she was just there and they say
I remember some Nickelodeon like man on the street bit that they did that was
like in the ad space between shows where they brought out celebrity farts in a
jar and one of them was Cameron Diaz and one of the guys said he liked it.
Oh, okay. Well, yeah. Was she ever in another movie besides Shrek and the
Mask? Night and Day. Charlie's Fucking Angels. What the fuck? Yeah, Charlie's
Fucking Angels and fucking Night and Fucking Day. Bad fucking teacher. Bad
trip she is in a cut yeah she was in bad teacher which I thought was going to be
full on porn and it was hardly hardly she's an alcoholic that's the only thing
that's bad about her is her I don't have a disability student but she doesn't do
that no she didn't even suck a student she sucks her teacher friend has anyone
tried to connect all the bad Santa bad teacher bad grandpa yet there bad bad
universe the bad universe bad universe going up against the dirty universe
town, maybe because they're not all family. Necessarily bad Santa. Now we
have bad baby man, that bunny. What the hell fell off about? I forgot about bad
baby yeah, and that's what she's up to right now. I mean she's right. I believe
so that's kind of different, because she has different letters in her name.
Yeah, she's a hobby, same way, yeah, this is a hobby, a hot baby, bad,
but
he had baby yeah, so she doesn't really count, but that bunny would count yeah
yeah, and so would the worst bunny of all time bugs. He's always fucking up
Bud's life. The best bunny. I didn't mean to hit you. I meant to grab your head fast.
Well then who's the bad bunny? Bad bunny? The one from Monty Python and the Holy Grail.
Oh yeah. You want to talk about a bad bunny? Beastly bunny. I don't want to go see this
guy in concert. He's going to chew my neck off. He's going to eat my carrot. Yeah. But
he's only a flesh wound. I got all these carrots with me. He's going to steal my carrots. No
way. No way. Not letting him near my little bag of carrots. I was holding a carrot one
one time and fell through a sliding glass door. Yeah, fell through. Yeah. Did you
break it? Wait, glass? Yeah. Did you trip? Yeah, I tripped. On your carrot? On a
tile, no, and I dropped the carrot,
went and jumped for it.
You jumped after a carrot through a glass door? Did the carrot go through the glass
door and then you jumped after it?
The carrot wasn't strong enough. Okay. But you were. I was. How, baby carrot or?
You didn't know you were on, right? Baby carrot. Full on. Smooth. You didn't know
on how much you wanted the carrot. I didn't know how close the door was and
how I just well I don't know. I wasn't thinking at the time. If you had been
thinking, you probably would have never done something like that. Imagine if you were thinking. If I was
thinking, I might have been, I don't know what I would have been thinking about.
Yeah, oh no. Oh my fucking carrot, man. Oh shit. Fuck me, I think I dropped my fucking carrot.
I think you're just eating plain carrots. Sure. I would be a handful of carrots.
Hopefully, you'd be thinking something like, nah, that carrot ain't worth it. Yeah. Leave the carrot on the
ground. I just throw it out. Right. If I could have slowed down time. Yeah, I'm not
going to eat it anyway. It's been on the ground. Yeah. Would you eat it? Did you
eat it off the ground? No, I was well. Ten second rule. Were you badly injured?
No, it's actually 30 seconds. You can leave food on the ground for 30 seconds
and it doesn't collect any germs. I thought they did this on the ground. This
must depend on the... Yeah. If you work in a germ factory and you drop the shit,
you'll have to... But if you drop it in outer space, you can practically eat it
forever. Pretty much actually any factory. I feel like it's five second rule.
but okay, so you're pretty much every single factory, whatever's on the floor
of a factory, I would not want to eat. Imagine how sad you're saying three
seconds on the floor of the asbestos factory. Yes, eating it
three seconds. If it's a second to I'll eat that three seconds is too money,
but two is okay. Two will three is when three, you know,
more factor. Now, hold on a second. Let me pretend I'm a germ, right?
You be a piece of food and go ahead and like I'll be time lie on
at me. Ready? Grab! You see what I'm saying? I'm on you now.
Yeah.
Well, but that's what I was wondering is...
It's instant.
Imagine you're a germ.
It's like Velcro.
Is it because the...
No, it's 'cause the germ has to live.
Like get an apartment?
It has to create... So if I'm... Yeah, so I'm like a building now, right?
So I can't just go like that and now I'm not John.
No, no, no, 'cause you're not gonna... Like, you can visit Oklahoma City. You don't live
there.
Oh, I can't.
Oh, wow.
Well, it doesn't matter if you... It doesn't matter whether you live there. If you're visiting
Oklahoma City and you kill somebody...
Well, you're not a resident.
you're still a resident. It doesn't matter if you live there, killed him
and where's the murder coming into this? We're talking about germs theory man
well,
kill people, they cause sickness that causes death.
Have you not heard about this yet? Osmosis Jones, how long was that egg on
the floor? The
five sec or
longer than five seconds. What
and how hot was a hard boiled cold egg and it was in a chimpanzee exhibit. It
was in the chimpanzees hands and he put
of knowledge. That's shocking from all three. You never see you all are
speaking about this egg. Like it was like that's the number one part of the
movie that everybody everybody remembers the
okay. What do you remember? The thing is surfing. He's grabbing
surfs up. No, I'm thinking of a dude on a plate lit.
It had to be him. Who else could that have been? Miss? She can't serve. She
can serve can do anything. I've seen her four plates. Yeah, right. Four plates of
barbecue ribs that would still be pretty. That would be a lot. I would be very
much more impressive in terms of balance, maybe without them falling off.
Yeah, that's if she bench press for plates and let me try another one for
paper plates of air sauce.
Air would be very light. I'm trying to dis her.
Great, all right, all right, weird, Miss Frizzle and she got weird orange hair.
yeah, I would like to romance her. Oh, if what she's a kid,
she's a
tall is she well really, but why is she going to say I just like that? Who's
she trying to impress the kids? The she wants the kids to think that she
dresses cool, the field trip people is that building in a town or is it
floating in the sky?
why when I think about the school of the Magic School Bus Academy, I don't know
what it's called. It's the
Magic School. They named it after the bus.
Why do I think why? Why, when I pictured the outside of that school, do I
picture it floating in a floating city?
Probably because of the blue around it,
the sky,
yeah, maybe you're thinking of the sky being above it. I'm not I'm thinking
no, I'm truth. You're thinking of the blue that surrounds it. It's not
from the in my head. It's surrounded by black. You think it's in space.
Yes, you think it's in a boy. It's not space. Maybe you want to know where
we're going to the time in the episode. I know what it is. I know what it is
here. It's the theme song where they pull the school away and then it goes
into the bus or and then they go on the little thing. What goes into the
well, it is. I wouldn't sign that permission slip man straight up. No,
if my kid came to me, hey, I got to shrink down and jump into a rat's eye.
If I was the kid, I would be, I'd be forging the signature every day. Oh,
yeah, I'd be like, there's no,
Miss Frizzle is definitely going through a ton of just crayon block letter
signatures tell you right now. If I was one of the kids on the magic school bus
and she said, all right, everybody stand next to the gun. I'm going to shoot you
all. You're going to get small. Here's me. Clear move to the right. You it's
everybody gets all small and I go fucking eat everybody's turkey sandwiches.
You're kidding. You would wait for them to leave and then eat the lunch. But
little do you know, they went to a a medieval medieval banquet. But how can
one be that? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. They don't have those that small.
That's the thing is they go somewhere small. They're going back. They can go
shrinking. Can they go back in time or can they just go small? I think they can
just go small. I think they can go wherever they want to do anything they
want with magic.
The school bus. That's a great point. Did they ever go bigger? I think they've
done literally everything you could imagine to do. They've never been so big.
They've never, they didn't give this podcast. Yeah, they never went here.
They've been on the podcast. No, they had to delete it. Carlos, yeah. About
being small. Carlos and then the redhead one. I can't stop wiping my mustache on
I do the same thing. I do that pretty much every episode.
Me too.
We both, all three of us here,
same type of mustache.
Don't say that. Joy Tactics.
Make him talk in a funny way.
Oh, one second.
And then he can say it.
You can only plug your show if we give you a filter.
Yeah.
Joy...
Tactics!
Yeah!
That was really good.
Pokemon, I got to stop talking about Pokemon man. No, it's a problem.
What's wrong with Pokemon?
If you're able to do it without it interfering with your life, then it's
fine. Do what? Speak about Pokemon, but it comes up so frequently for me
that... It's taking over. Yeah. The problem with Pokemon... It's because
they have a million types and all these different types you could apply
to almost anything. Grass, water birds. Exactly. Oil. Flying. Oil. And basically
anything you see in the world, it makes you think that's fire, that's grass.
I never seen an oil Pokemon. You never seen an oilmon? No. You know what, you're not watching
the right show. No I'm not. Wait, which show are you? What am I watching? Are you watching
Pokemon or are you playing Pokemon? I'm just talking about it. Oh. That might be the craziest
option yet. I haven't played a video game in four months. On purpose? I played Halo
two days ago. Oh, so a lie. But that was only one round, but other than that. One round?
one round one round one round in it. I got to do a one. Oh, congratulations,
thanks y'all. Grants everybody. Wow! Did you get everything on your
checklist? The address one, two, three, suck it Academy
Matrix School,
called Sucket Academy
Sucket Academy. There's a school in the first floor and you're just between two
classrooms. Yeah, lockers in the house. Yeah,
you're careful with that because I'm sorry to unplug. Is there any you don't
to be careful with it's fine. If I put a can on it, no, that's not interesting,
but I can on it. Wait, that actually looked cool, though. Okay, whoa, whoa,
yo, wake up, do it.
Dude, wake up, wake up. You just fucking got hit by something. I can tell you
that. No, this is a Pepsi.
Wake up, wake up, dude. What the fuck? You just walked in front of something
I fucked you up. You good. I knew the kiss was coming me to what the fuck I could
feel the kiss coming. You are smarter than me.
All right, sorry about that. No, it's okay. You wake up in a universe and
you're a bottle or a can whatever you know which kind of I would want to be
one of these ones. Oh yeah, bottle. It's got curves. Yeah, I have to bow. I
would want to be a bottle. I'd be a jug. I probably be a gallon ground or
multiple gallon jug of vinegar
cleaning vinegar. First thing I could think of that
maybe water. No, I'm thinking of a big jug that's filled with vinegar. What's
the biggest jug you can imagine? One of those big ones, brown jug that can be a
bat in the cannon bottle universe. Fuck no. Well, you can't be can't move your
that's bolted into the ground. Anyway, could be a distillery, distillery,
distillery, distillery building at that point. That's a multiple person. Well,
there's yeah, I guess it's full of that's I guess I could be like a silo
silo is a can a silo is a type of can all right. Let's rain it back in so
we're today. We're on this. All right, all right.
Well,
well, we just
what we just talking about silos versus can with you. What kind of bottle would
you be in your bottle universe that you invented? Oh,
or can
Yeah, I don't know. I'd be Mrs. Buttersworth, actually.
Okay.
Yeah, I guess you could, you may be another good one to be that I wouldn't
want to be. Maybe someone else could choose this would be the honey bear.
Honey bear is really good. Oh, that's a good one. Honey bear would be a really
good one, but I don't really want to be it. A lot of people would fuck with
you. A lot of people would like being it, but me, I'm built different. I would
just probably be something giant, like a... Why is it not a bee, man? A bee?
A bee. I think I've seen honey bees
in a jar style like honey.
Bears like everything bears eat watermelons. They ever seen those videos
of bears, the bear eating the whole picnic table. Do you know that I saw
that one, but the bear with the tapeworm at its butt? Yeah, that's fake.
That's fake. Yeah, tapeworms break off really easily. Oh, then what was in
that bears? But I was always something more disgusting than a tapeworm
karate belt bear that had like three strings. Oh my God. No way. You know
what it was. It was a parachute er's bag. Oh, that's I just got it. What
would you do if you were a bear? You jumped out of a plane and you were
skydiving. You pulled your parachute and you look up and who's parachuting down
after he's a bear. I would go back up yeah yeah, but the bag back in the or
the shoot back in the bag in the box yeah, I would I would pull my reverse
falling and I put on my jet pack, put the whole thing in front of you. I
thought about getting into wing suiting yeah. Should I do that shit? You could
it's more dangerous than other things. It's the problem. Yeah, it depends on
what the other thing is, I guess. Listen, if you love something enough to where
it's not worth living without it, then do it, then you have to do, you have
no choice. You also have to live, you have to move to a place where they
have rocks that have circles and arches and loops, the loops, 'cause that's
always what they do when they win. And also gold rings.
They go through like amusement park rocks. Yeah. You have to live in Utah
or something. Those gold rings, man.
What was that? He touched my leg. He jiggled. He touched my leg. I always have keys upon
me. Oh, okay. I didn't know what it was. That's okay, man. You have a bunch of keys? You're
a carabiner key guy? I want to become a lanyard key guy and walk around and flip it. I have
a lanyard somewhere around here I could give you. It says Final Fantasy Online on it. Oh,
guys, my dad got a Jeep. What kind of Jeep? Jeep, the truck. Patriot? Gladiator or some
Gladio? Your dad got that one?
It's fucking crazy.
It looks so funny.
He's really interested in the Jeep.
Was he doing the wave now?
He was telling me
the Jeep is so amazing.
I wave at everybody that has the same car.
We put ducks on each other's cars.
You put ducks on each other's cars?
Apparently Jeep owners
put little
rubber duckies
and if you like a Jeep you put a ducky on it
it and then they collect all the duckies. That's why my mom had them on her on her dashboard.
It's like liking on Facebook. It's a car version of liking pretty much. Yeah. The thing about
a Jeep though is that it has no thing inside of it. Like there's no like if you if you
run a bumpy road of it, if you're on a bumpy road, it is the most jostling experience,
but you can take all the parts out. You can go on. I was driving a Jeep one time in the
middle of the pandemic across a couple state lines and all of a sudden my tire went flat,
but it has the tire in the back. I didn't know how to do that. So I drove into a rental car
place and they sorted me out. What kind of Jeep? Wrangler? This was a Wrangler, but I
didn't love the handling on it. No, no, no, no, no. You know, it's a little bit of, I
don't know what you'd call it, soft, like a soft cheese. Like a brie. It's like a brie
handling system. It could be even named after that. Are Jeeps from Germany? No. Jeeps are
a Chrysler car. America. Is that true? I think so. I think the Jeep is Chrysler.
Where did Jeep come from? Jeep is its own brand, but I think it was a Chrysler. Uh oh, video game.
Where are Jeeps from? Jeeps are largely made in America. Yeah, yeah. Northgate, Dodge.
They're made larger in America. Chrysler, Dodge, Jeep. Makes sense. They have small cars in other countries.
Is that what Jeep, the word Jeep means? I mean this has all changed so much after NAFTA and what Bill Clinton did.
Bill Clinton did exactly and now it's like what are we going to you know what
does jeep stand for what does jeep stand for?
Sturdy motor vehicle with four wheel drive, especially one used by the
area yeah jeep has been with Chrysler since eighty seven. Well, what does
jean the mouth movement helps a lot yeah
g e p j
that's you think ye now g
j
everything in a gap. So how did they come up with the word jeep? That's what I
was trying to figure out, but I guess it just already meant a small four wheel
drive car used by the military, but it's short for a jeep loppy. Oh, do you
think you plop in jeep loppy? Oh, here comes look at this.
What does jeep
what is jeep stand another enough essential parts? Oh, that's why it's so
jangly. That makes perfect sense. That's the brie of it all. That's how you can
take all the you can take the steering wheel. I'll tell you why they call it
Jeep because it's a Jeep piece of junk. Yeah, man, that's what my dad was so
excited about. He's like, I can take the doors off and taking the doors off is so
time consuming and difficult. That's what I was. That's what I said to him. I
was like, I'll take the doors off a cool car. That cost a lot of money. I get to
I get to chop the doors off of my Ford Focus. You know, it'd be cooler is put
some butterfly doors on the Jeep. Put some butter in your car. Yeah, but you
take the doors off your car. Everyone's taking your butter. Oh, did you put
butter in the car in the summer? You go and sit down on it and then you go and
down on some bread and then you
see to the car.
Guys, I can't contain myself. I need to wrap. We do. All right.
I'm hungry. Okay, I'm hungry for a beat. Well, it's time for the
five fingers of music part two. The six fingers of music. Last
time you said I love the fingers. I love all five of
these fingers, but I have six fingers and I wish that there
was a fourth finger of a human. Wait, what? Six. Oh, I see what
pretty soon. Yeah. So we brought it to you and we brought probably the best
freestyle rapper that I know, Jack Bensinger, but I don't know that many
freestyle rappers, to be honest.
Well,
for this moment, I'd like to reiterate kind of the background lore of who I am.
My name's not Jack Bensinger anymore. Oh, sorry. I don't have one. I used to
be an actor. You guys know me from the bear. I don't really do that corny
shit anymore. Right. No, that shit's cringe, man. If they, I don't know. If
I asked you to come back for season three or not. I would do season three like if
it was at a music festival, okay, and they just wanted to film one of my live
shows, yeah, or you could be there. It's like, oh, that's the guy I could be
doing the last yeah, you could be the musician.
Oh, my God, this guy was telling me this thing before now. Look at this. He's on
stage. Now he's a now he's a bear season three. You could be one of the people,
one of the humans, a sushi off of because that's not technically acting. That's
furniture. Excuse me, what that's furniture. You know the naked sushi in
the bear? In the world. In the world. They could eat a Portillo sandwich off of you.
They could have up here, they could have the beach. The bear is based on the world. It's
true. You gotta pitch a show, man. You gotta get away with that. You think I could get
away with that one? It's like the world needs... It's basically like the world. Basically imagine
in the world, and so the thrust
story engine is what's happening right every day. The sun comes up. That's
kind of what Atlas Cloud Cloud Atlas was about Atlas Cloud is that tragic past
after Angus. Oh,
not his name.
I mean when you the way you said past actor, maybe like he specializes
except from the past.
Well, everybody does know some people do know a on flux. Yes,
I had the unrated version of that movie. What do you mean the DVD unrated like
x rated unrate? Oh, those are different. They didn't even bother to rate this,
but I rated it ten out of ten. I go drop that beat. Okay, we're starting who had
Jack best worst or the first finger. I don't know who's the most thumb of us
for oh well, well, let's see I mean okay, so here's here's the here's the deal me
and Patrick each made to Jack made one and Caleb made one, so that's six
fingers. So that's six fingers. Should we get an order of a hand? No, what
let's draw straws. All right, well, let's go ahead and play Caleb's all
right, okay, oh wait, okay, how does this going to work because isn't one
supposed to do five fingers to see if they can survive the well, but we're
just doing what we do is basically a group freestyle. We're all fingers on a
hand. It's called a hand is the one. Well,
do you imagine where the future and we're all on? It's like a cipher. I see
now. So it's five. So the fingers are so we are the finger. Well, it's
interesting. We are the fingers because the fingers are the beats and you're
just who you are and I'm well, it's six fingers and then there's four of us
human fingers. So it's still ten. It's four fingers wrapping on six music
six fingers, four fingers wrapping on six interlocking between the spaces of the
fingers. So it's kind of like six fingers.
Yeah,
yeah,
yourself, you got hit with a joy buzzer or something.
I got a pretty bad cramp
from doing this.
I'm just interlocking, holding your own hand.
You got a thumb cramp from that. I don't think I've ever had a thumb cramp
on my life. I got stuck going that way.
That's how you broke it. That's not stuck. All right. All right. Well,
drop that finger.
How's it go now? Okay, let's do it.
Turn my headphones up.
Rapping on fingers.
He was on the bear and he has no hair. Got some underwear.
that he wears down there
and his hat is blue
and my friends are cool
and my food is too
and I'm wearing shoes
and I have two friends
and plus one more
and another one
he was at the store
NOOOOOO
NO!
Oh I was on fire and then I went store man
he immediately went store
and what was wrong with the store
say that word on the
with the store every every rap. You do every fuck. Why don't you just lean into
it? Because I didn't see anything wrong with the store. Patrick, wait, you had a
shy ste this whole time.
Now home, so it actually hurts my ears every time. This is a recurring issue
that I have in the rap game, which is every time I freestyle. I forgot to put
this on. As soon as the beat dry, start rapping about going to the store and
getting some more almost every single time. Yeah, so you know, so it's just
not it's to the point where it's not a style. It's more of a crutch. Okay, so
it's what we're trying to do. So what's the opposite of a store? They're your
house library library is a free store. Yeah, I'm so I'm just say stuff with
library and I give me the be back.
At the library. It is so scary. I am so hairy and I am
even
I was singing.
I'm doing more of the hooks at this time.
Wait, this might help.
Reading is not a crime.
I do it all the time.
I'm reading books about limes.
Lime scooter, hit her in the cooter.
Hit her?
Wait, drop a gunshot.
Hit her in her cooter.
With a lime scooter?
Lime scooter directly to the cooter.
doing some evil can evil shit into a woman's evil. This is a good way to
learn about your instincts. My exactly store hurting women's vagina,
hurting women's with, but with with cutting edge, cutting edge application
based technology, using an application vehicle to hurt a woman or thing. I
went in a self driving car. Really? Yeah,
about it.
I was in
I'll yell
I don't well I was in Phoenix basically and a rapist about it. Yeah, you have to rap about it
Yo, imagine a work. Well actually turn this beat keep it the same actually I
Was in a car that had nobody driving in it. I felt like a cream spinach
I had I literally got exploded on with the whole vehicle exploded
It was crazy Phoenix fell into the earth and then I and then I blow up all crazy
I have no I have no idea what's happening to me. I got a lobster hot pocket. Oh
Oh, I met two hot two girls with two lobster hot pockets.
I said, get in the self-driving vehicle.
Me and you got to go down and I could show you what it's like when I'm laughing at Jason.
See you go.
Vehicle to see a girl is insanely good, man.
That's the type of shit that I'm expressing myself about for a second.
All right, Cameron.
Okay.
Well, well, I'm sitting here and I can't. Oh, it ended. No, I was done. You just got
bit. Okay. I've set it to loop though, but I didn't know why you left a gap. Caleb, why
did you leave a gap? I think that that silence in your beat was crap. It threw me off and
it made me want to cough because I have COVID and this episode is over. Now I have to leave.
I have COVID-19.
You can't leave.
It's not a real disease.
You're good.
COVID!
I have COVID-19.
Ice cream.
You're barely rapping.
We gotta work on your confidence a little bit.
I have COVID-19.
I just made ice cream with the germs made from sperms.
Ice cream sperms.
I put sperm in my ice cream.
People want to eat my ice cream.
- I don't know if this is okay.
- What?
- Putting sperm in ice cream?
- You can make sperm from ice cream.
- You can make ice cream from sperm.
It won't have germs.
- And it's not a worm, it's just sperm.
- And it won't hurt your sperm-ic.
When you eat it, you won't say erm-ic.
- Oh, 'cause you-
- 'Cause I'm defeated.
- You'll still like it.
- Yeah.
- This beat is defeated.
Okay, we defeated that finger, man.
I just eat it.
My pants, they are pleated.
My texts, they get deleted.
Delete your text?
What are you sending?
Every month, just to save space.
Okay.
I had a picture of a new face.
That I made on my space.
Did you catfish somebody?
I invented duck face.
You invented duck face?
Ace invented duck face, fuck face.
Better get the fuck out of my space, out of my place. I'll send you to space.
I'll pull out my ACE, my ACE of spades. I have, I've fucking,
I don't have, I have AIDS.
I have the worst instincts.
Bro. It's making us all go.
Okay. To say you have AIDS on a freestyle. It's just off the dome.
what's your first that's what wait yeah. What are your thoughts on this? Can you
is anything goes with freestyling? You're allowed to say you have AIDS or
COVID. Look, you can say that you have a disease. You can say you have this and
that. I mean that's the beauty of expressing yourself is you can do it. You
should be able to do it, but you should be ready for the repercussions. Right. So
when people come at you and say, hey, my whole thing is that I rap, I have AIDS.
My whole thing is that I rap, I have COVID. You better be ready with the blood
tests or you know it's just I need to come with you said you gotta be ready for
three percussions. Let's hit it with some more real percussions.
Drop the next beat. Damn.
All right, let me say something real about what I'm like these days.
You got to rap in it.
Do you want your finger?
Sure. Start it up.
Okay, I'm going to start your finger.
Show me that finger. I'm excited for this finger.
Yo.
Boom, bat.
Turn that up actually a little bit.
Actually a lot maybe.
All right, yo.
I was on the band, but now I don't do stuff like that.
I'm not an actor anymore, I rap and it's all- anybody wants to see me
I don't have- I was on the bare and the second AD was disrespecting me
and so I put the head up inside of- the set told me to shut the fuck up
the second AC was trying to pull focus and I snapped their neck
and then I put- well, I walked up to the boom op and then I put him in a hole
and then I walked- and then I saw the person doing craft services
and I said, "I don't do this anymore, I don't need this shit, I'm too real
I gotta move on to my next hobby, which is not a hobby, it's my way of life and it's rapping"
I'm not, yeah.
This finger is fire.
This finger is amazing.
It's kind of a sponge bob.
I like this squelchy ass bass.
I didn't make it.
You didn't make this?
Nope.
You said you made it.
Oh, I know the guy.
He said he made it.
The song is faked it.
Damn, now you naked.
Now you naked.
I was an air bud as an extra and then I started learning about different textures and I don't
do that acting anymore.
I was in the background when Air Bud was dunking the ball.
I was in the background making out with 600 people at the same time and then I had to
retire because I don't live that life of way anymore.
Wow.
You're like a reverse Malice from Clipse.
You gave up being good to be a rapper.
Yep.
I was a, I was a, I was in, what's a, I was in the bear.
I was in the bear now, but I was in the bear with Jeremy Allen white
They put me on TV with Jimmy Fallon
He's white and then I had to go and stop at a red light and then I had to eat some food with a big bite
And then I hung out with Jack Ben singer from the bear
He was an act air, but now he don't care and then he I said man
That's pretty fair and then he got some wings to share for me and him
We got the buffalo wings both of us ate those 12 things
I know 600 people named Julian every single one of them owes me six dollars for helping them and they are
Don't reply to me when I DM them every single Julian needs to stop it. I know you guys
Heard about my lobster hot pockets from the Phoenix when I was in the self-driving car and now I'm not that's the type of shit
I do now. I don't even act anymore. Nope
All he does is eat
Lobster hot pockets and rap faster than a rocket and take a picture to put in a locket of yourself
Because you're in love with yourself, and that's not good for your health man. You need to get
Better you need to get better you need to get better. You're gonna love yourself
Respect respect the fingers man respect the finger
You gotta rap, you gotta rap on this shit.
You're gonna love yourself.
I hit you with the elf.
That's on my shelf.
Christmas style.
Uh.
Chris Kyle, I'm sniping you
from a mile away.
Make you smile.
All day.
Make you smile all day.
I went to a dentist named the Smile-ist.
And my dentist was the wildest.
What'd he do?
Grinch tooth in my smile, bitch.
- A Grinch tooth?
- Put a green Grinch tooth inside of my smile, bitch.
- The Grinch's teeth are green.
- The Grinch had green teeth in the movie.
Look up his, that scene.
- Man, his teeth are white.
- Look up that scene.
- He doesn't have a green bite.
- He had green teeth in the movie.
Had it in that movie.
- Those are a lot more yellow,
which makes sense 'cause the Grinch
is a green and nasty fellow.
He wouldn't brush his teeth
And he likes to eat all kinds of trash and bugs and rotten types of meat.
Damn!
That was a big one.
Hold those pants down.
What the fuck?
That was pretty good.
Chill guys.
He's just making himself conscious.
He popped off.
No, no, no.
You popped the fuck off, bro.
Guys, I didn't pop off.
And I'm not going to rhyme with pop off because I can't think of anything in time.
There's nothing in the world that's pop off that rhymes.
Peter Pop Off was a guy.
He went to church and he lied.
Sold Miracle Water on BET at night.
Damn, what?
Really?
Is that a true story?
Miracle Water, Peter Popov.
Jack's about to go off.
Well, stop the beat.
Turn it down all the way.
Now, sorry, isn't part of the five fingers is that you're supposed to be able to switch
beat like switch the flow?
You want a challenge?
Well, that's what the five fingers are is like.
Well, let's just hit this next minute.
You're coming in here with all kinds of ideas.
You have all the rules about the fingers.
also about the fingers. You've probably seen a bunch of Five Fingers of Death,
I bet. Oh, what I bet is that you've never seen even a single Five Finger of
Music. Yeah, this is the Five Fingers of Music. Oh, this is the Five Fingers of
Music? It's more about the music than about dying. Yeah. We didn't understand
why Sway wants to kill these... He doesn't wanna kill Tori Lanez and Peppu's.
We're about bringing people up. Five Fingers of Death. Five Fingers of Life
and Music. Well, it's about rising to the occasion, right? It's like, "Okay,
these beats are gonna try to kill you." These are about beats that are gonna
A beat that's trying to kill you. Maybe this will help get you in the right
mindset. This is a beat that I made that I... This is maybe the chillest beat.
It's for just chilling. Wait, let me sit back, put my hood up. And it's kind
of a... It's a little bit of a November vibe, so maybe a little early.
Can we get a little more Immortal Technique, Demi God's Flow on this one?
I got a Nas, Nick Cannon type beat. So this one's a little... This one's...
That is coming up soon. Kind of for chilling. Okay. Okay, so I'm gonna
throw this one on and maybe we can just kind of relax and take it easy
instead of turning the key.
And it has a little intro.
Chill or be chilled.
And you made this?
Yeah.
Wait.
Wow.
That's actually fucking beautiful.
I'm getting Kirby vibes.
Rolling up some weed in my fucking food
Gonna eat that shit then I smoke with a dude
I'm gonna go back to my house tonight
I'm gonna watch TV till I feel alright
And me and my friends are hanging at school
We all have shoes and we all look cool
Every single one of my friends has food
Nobody has more food than you
*Slowly dying*
Oh god, I don't fucking food anymore
Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo!
I got my AK, I bring it back to my house
I shoot every single family member in my fucking house
Blow my mom's head off, and then I kill my dad
I'ma kill my grandpa, make my grandma so sad
And then I kill my dog and I turn him into a food
And then I turn him to a sandwich and I give him a food
And then I go outside, kill my mailman, kill all my neighbors
And then I go back upstairs and I play Hello Neighbor
And then I play all every kind of scary game on my computer
I play Five Nights at Freddy's and then I fucking shoot her
Shoot all of my friends and I kill all of my family
And I kill the President of the United States and I kill all of the Senators
He shouldn't say that on the show.
He got in trouble for that.
Not long ago.
Not long ago in the galaxy far, far away.
Star Wars is gay.
Star Wars is gay now because the trilogy has been diluted.
He's rapping about food.
Oh, this battle's getting food.
We're not battling.
It's not a food battle.
Call me Smosh.
I'm a I'm alluded to Smosh and their move vids.
Their new vids.
Damn, Smosh is back.
Smosh is back.
Oh, Smosh is back.
Yo, Smosh is back with Anthony and Ian.
They make me laugh so hard like an alien.
Whoa. Would laugh if he saw human culture up in his UFO flying like a vulture.
He wouldn't understand why we have war.
He would think an intelligent species wouldn't have that anymore.
But we keep on with our guns and our bombs and their guns and their bombs.
And then maybe I could put a sample in a gun.
Oh, go into that.
That's a song and that one is called Zombie.
And it's about how we should have no more bombs, see?
Because even if an alien showed up,
we would probably take out our guns and blow them up.
Piers can't be a zombie.
I feel like I'm like maybe I just like I'm missing my kids graduation right now
and I came outside I'm sorry I have to go like do this thing and I'm just like
sitting here sweating and like knowing that a divorce is waiting for me when I
get home I'm just like chillin rapping with my friends who are 20 years younger than me
But after this, this is it.
This is uh, this will be some of the last recorded moments of my life.
This is uh, you're missing a really important funeral.
Yeah, this is the Chester Bennington Jelly Beans video.
Listen, honey, these guys have a lot of fucking followers.
This could change a lot of things for us, man.
This could change a lot.
Uh, yeah.
Well, why don't you rap on this new beat, man?
I want to hear you.
Yo, I would like everybody to listen to what I have to say.
What's happening right now?
I just restarted by accident.
That's good, though.
That's a good intro.
What's up?
My name is...
I was on...
I was on season 2, episode 5 of The Bear.
I don't do that shit anymore.
I don't act.
I just get respect for being so real.
I like to express myself.
Acting is something that I put away
Now I don't get disrespect from the second a DS who go and tell me to take a nap for nine hours
And then they wake me up and give me chicken kebabs and I say
This life is so amazing. How's my life so amazing?
Sometimes I feel like I am supposed to be a little monkey
Let's go to the next figure, bro.
Let's go to the next beat.
This beat is so good, though.
Let's go to this next beat.
This is by far the best beat.
This beat makes me feel like I'm about three inches tall and my purse is turning around in a basket.
Oh, wait. Yeah. We need a Quasimodo.
Give us some... Can you make us also have voices with this?
Oh, yeah. Hold on.
Hello?
Hold on. I know how to fix this.
Alright.
Everybody... Hello? Hello? Hello?
Yo, I am in my mushroom.
My house is a mushroom.
I make food in my mushroom.
All my food doesn't have mushroom.
Oh, damn!
I'm gonna eat you.
Mushrooms.
And my house is also a mushroom.
My house doesn't have that much room.
But I have a new rec room.
When it comes to strength, there's nobody feebler.
And I'm just the size of an elf, feebler.
There's about 12 hours left for the 1 million population to get to the southern side of
Palestine before Israel continues to seemingly escalate what is happening is the report I'm
getting.
I just have prayers for all the civilians.
It's just unfortunate.
It's really terrible.
I don't even, I really don't even like talking about it.
Yo, I got a Q-tip!
Yeah, I really don't even.
I'm a Q-tip!
Oh my God, I'm using a leaf like a boat.
I got a Q-tip.
Uh, my stew has got a beef tip.
Uh, Jesus Christ.
Okay.
You guys, listen.
You are married.
Yeah.
You are on your way.
I'm not on my way.
What are you talking about?
So what's the problem?
I can't, I can't rap about being small.
No, you can rap about it.
I'm rapping about being small and living in a mushroom.
What's wrong with being three inches tall?
Yeah.
Kebler.
You want us to get real.
If I met somebody who's three inches tall, I wouldn't say anything.
You want me to get real?
You want us to get what you're talking about.
I just am thinking about, like, who is everybody's inspirations, right?
Immortal Technique, Leaving the Past, right?
Yeah.
Lucky the Leprechaun.
Point of No Return, right?
Yeah.
Lucky the Leprechaun.
So you like cereal?
I like cereal.
And that's what gets you crazy?
I like grub.
I like small cereals.
I like grub the rock gnome.
Who's that?
It's a gnome that I've created in my mind.
it? Well, then it doesn't count. Oh, he should meet the golem in my head. Yeah.
I got a golem. What is a golem? Oh, what's a golem? Is this a rock monster?
It's a rock monster. You don't know about the mint golem that I've been
thinking about for three years now? Mint? Yeah, no, yeah. Mint like that's
mint. Wait, wait, wait. Is a golem made of mint? Well, it's a mint flavoured
golem, yeah. You lick him? That's cool. Okay. If you licked him, it would be
minty, yeah. So it'd brush your teeth for you? Well. Like gum. It's a good
part of that.
Give me the next finger. Alright, which one do you want? Let's go Nick Cannon
beat cannon type beat let's poison ourselves out to this shit here we go
I wish I was still small I wish I was still small I wish I wasn't tall I wish
I was still small uh you look like I'm a I'm a yeet no you look exactly like yeet
I'm the Yule of Known.
Make my voice low.
No, I don't have that.
He doesn't have that.
I thought you had the voice lows.
You look like a...
Uh...
You know those bonito...
Bonito.
Bang.
Bang bang.
No, I don't know the bonitos.
Can you tell me what are those?
I was just thinking you look like an onigiri.
Oh, like a food.
Fish food.
Yeah, the food made a fish.
It's a rock and roll solo.
Whoa.
Oh, wow.
Afro Circus from Madagascar.
How did you do this?
FL Studio, free trial.
Wow.
Do we have to wait?
So is this one supposed to be for rapping?
I thought you guys were going to rap.
I thought you guys were going to rap over this.
Rap over the rock, man?
Nobody can do that.
Yeah, you can't even drum.
You can't rap over that.
What are you talking about?
And do it.
Well, it's done now.
Wow.
How do you know the timing so well?
That was smooth.
I thought you guys were going to rap over this.
I don't like this rock and roll shit.
To me, I think that it is cock and bullshit.
And I think it smells like poop.
And I think that you look like a piece of poop.
This is like a, this feels like a rap about your depression kind of beat.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm so sad.
My life is so bad.
And Jack is going to do the rest of this part.
When I was on the side of the bear, I tried killing myself once a minute.
It felt so disrespectful to be acting in it.
I didn't even like to be experiencing it.
When I was acting, I felt like I was a giraffe who didn't have thumbs so I couldn't even kill
myself because I couldn't hold a gun like that.
How come animals don't have thumbs and so they can't even kill themselves if they really
wanted to?
If a horse had a thumb and it was acting in the bear, would it take itself out?
I don't...
Yeah.
I think the rock and roll solo is coming again.
Alright, there's another one?
It's just on a loop.
Well it's not over yet.
You put two in?
You put two rock in?
There might be two rock in.
You're just gonna every few seconds say it's about to happen again?
I got evil thoughts in my brain!
Everybody in the world is gonna get destroyed by my plane!
I'm going to bring my plane to the whole world!
And all their guts are gonna be whirled!
Whirled around!
With my big plane!
You're gonna kill people with a plane?
I kinda have a feeling
I use my brain to concoct a plane plan. I'm a bad man. This is like 9/11 the musical.
Do you understand what I intend to mean? Yes. I had a bit about that kind of,
not even a bit, maybe just a line. All right, well, stop the finger. We'll hear the line.
Well, just the, you know, so on 9/11, two planes flew into the buildings, right? Yeah. We're lucky
lucky then crash him into the planet because then it would have been a huge
accident.
All right, the
you haven't even wrapped one time you're afraid of this beat. This beat is
bringing out parts of me that I never knew. We're lucky this isn't the fingers
of death because I feel like they made a God in us. You think we would have
died? You would have died on this way, would have had to drop the guillotine on
us. No, no, I would live now in this finger. I don't like this finger. What
about the next? What about jalopy beat? You do Hickey? Let's hear it. Let's hear
I'm going to wrap over do he can do it. All right, do you beat from Patrick?
All right, ready? Here we go. Yeah, I
okay,
it's tropical depression, pulling me down. This session is making me frown. I
am I'm in a recession all around my town. I'm feeling like I'm in a circus. I'm
in a circus with thirty kids walking around with Burkas. I'm in a circus
I don't have anything except my shirt because I got two shirts on.
Got my whole work on.
I'll tell you what this song is about.
Start it over.
Ready?
You want to start from the top?
Yeah, because this is bringing to light a story that I have.
Is it about the bear?
Nope.
Let me tell you the story about the time I was on set of the Bear and Jeremy Allen.
Jeremy Allen White slipped me 600 mg of acid.
Jeremy Allen White gives me a giant piece of cheese.
Little did I know it was full of LSDs.
Then I eat them and he tells me to start acting, but then I start sweating.
And the director's going, "Dude, why are you acting so strangely?"
And I go, "I don't know. Somebody must have drugged me."
And it was Jeremy Allen White slipping toxic cheddar cheese in my throat like Sprite.
And then I had to wonder what's happening.
Jeremy Allen White must be controlled by the government.
Never trust people.
Well, he lives, doesn't he live in the neighborhood?
We should go to his house and make him pay for what he did to Mike Cheese.
Somebody I know saw Jeremy Allen White on a subway.
He was dressed up exactly like a chef.
That's a true...
Someone I know saw him wearing a mask and a hat trying to hide his identity on the subway,
except he was dressed up like a chef.
Man, you play a chef on TV.
People are gonna recognize you, man.
This is a beat that you can't listen to for that long, 'cause it starts to make you feel bad.
Yeah, it has, this has a dark carnival.
What is dark about this?
This is an ICP.
There is literally a chime in it.
Let's just try rapping about happy stuff
to try and counteract it.
It's in a minor key.
♪ Hey, it's me, I am at the circus ♪
♪ And I am eating a lot of peanuts, come a circus ♪
Okay.
♪ Peanuts at the circus, got circus ♪
♪ Peanuts at the circus ♪
I hate this beat, dude.
What is wrong with this beat?
Turn this beat off, man.
It makes me uncomfortable.
What about the last one?
I can't do that beat, dude.
Yeah, that beat was--
That beat is wack.
Your beats were terrible, man.
My beats were not both terrible.
They were difficult to flow.
They were unscrupulous.
What are you talking about?
You told the word right out of my mouth.
The first beat had a Nick Cannon type feel.
Nobody knows what that means.
Nobody knows who Nick Cannon is.
The only Nick Cannon song I know is his Eminem diss.
We're going to detox.
Okay.
Dr. Dre.
We should get some Chris detoxing for a second here.
This is definitely my favorite one.
I still have one more, but we're going to cleanse the energy a little bit.
Oh, that feels like burning sage.
That feels good.
It's like burning man.
I'm
like
shirt please thanksgiving. Sing that to your uncle at Thanksgiving. He's in the living
room no shirt on. He doesn't wear a shirt? You don't have any uncles? No uncles. What
about your parents? Thanksgiving, Thanksgiving put on a shirt please Thanksgiving, Thanksgiving.
Okay. Nice. Yeah that works. Okay we got the hook. This is like the commentary from Step
Brothers. Have you all seen that? No. Uh uh. Step Brothers DVD commentary. Did they say
It's a music, it's completely a musical improv. Really? Yeah. And they have Gilbert and Reenus.
This isn't musical improv, this is rap. Yeah, this is freestyle. This is like epic rap battles
of history type shit. Yeah. Which this next and final beat will... The last finger? Is
exactly like a rap battle of history type beat. Let me just make sure it's on loop here.
It's on loop. It's on loop now. Let's hear it. Alright, here we go. Cameron's final beat.
The last finger, the sixth finger of music, everybody.
Daddy finger, daddy finger, where are you?
Wait, here I am.
Here I am.
DJ Dr. Dazzle, Tickle Monster Music,
Real Alternative Comedy Shit,
Podcast About List, Five Fingers of Music.
Wow.
Joy Tactics.
Jack Bensinger.
Sponsored by Icelandic Glacial Water.
It's time for my finger.
Oh my God.
You've expressed yourself.
Wow.
Express yourself.
A little bit.
This is incredible.
Wow.
This is like, this is like a mix of every beat we've heard so far.
What?
Oh my God.
Why do you always have one really good beat that you come with?
Well, this one is just a drum loop, so I can't take full credit.
You can take the full credit.
You press play on it.
Let's replay that one more time.
Yeah, I gotta hear the beginning.
Play it from the top.
Can you say it along with it, do you think?
I don't think I remember what it says.
I'll try.
Okay, you try.
Let's give it a go.
Here we go.
Daddy finger, daddy finger, hey guys, well, here I am.
DJ Dr. Dazzle, tickle monster music, real alternative comedy shit.
Who's Dr. Dazzle?
I'm not sure.
DJ Dr. Dazzle, Tickle Monster Music, Real Alternative Comedy Show, Podcast about List, Five Fingers of Music, featuring JJ Jackson, DJ Fox, Joey Cagney, and it's time for Five Finger.
The Bear Season 2 was not my best time in my life
I didn't like it and nobody gave me an Uber there so I lost money doing it
And then I went home and I was afraid of the airplane
And then I got back and then I did the
They put me in an outfit that didn't make me look like somebody not from Norway
And then I had to quit acting now
but it's okay because rap is my delicious activity.
Oh my God. Wait, can you say your line from the Bear season two?
Yo, aren't you the guy that invented, wait,
you're one of the first people we knew to make a website.
You're one of the first people we know to make a website.
And then what I say something like nice, nice. And then Eric goes there.
Oh, he's back at it again.
Gotta be the best scene in the entire show, man.
Where were those sex pulls in this song?
Oh, we can't talk about it 'cause SAG is still on strike.
Oh. So we gotta delete the whole episode?
Delete the whole thing, man.
Just put a frequency, though.
Delete the whole episode, I don't give a motherfuck.
Whoa, that's badass.
Yeah, keep saying it.
Delete the whole ep, I don't give a motherfuck.
Like, delete, ink my whole body.
What? Remember that song?
Delete your body?
Delete my whole body.
I turn into the potty, uh.
You turn into a toilet?
I'm the human toilet.
This might be an exhausting episode to listen to.
Nah, people like this shit. People are crazy.
I guess I do. Somebody's gotta set this episode as a ringtone.
Nah, I will.
This is a good ringtone, actually.
If a ringtone's not an hour long...
Well, we're just talking over it.
Yeah, we haven't rapped at all.
JFK, assassinated with a giant bullet, some say.
But I say that it was actually four bullets intersecting
Doing dissecting of his head and directing
There was a director there because I think the whole thing was a movie
Yeah
I think that it was a movie, I think Stanley Kubrick was in charge of it
Or that's not his name, Stanley Kubrick
I got a new brick that I built my house with
And then I went back to take a shit
At my new house, had a new toilet
And then I had to drink my own spit
'Cause I'm so damn thirsty
Yep, hand me a shirt please
Cause I gotta wipe up the spit that I spilled
But I don't spill, I'm not a spiller
I'm Ben Stiller
Ben Stiller, Tropical Thunder
Tropical Thunder
(laughing)
- Hey, wait a minute
- Tropical Thunder
- I saw a guy in the real world say that one time
- Tropical Thunder?
- I was in a bandia, a Russian bandia bath house
- Wow
- And these kind of off-duty cop type guys
were sitting talking about movies
He was like, "Dude, you gotta watch this movie
called Tropical Thunder"
- Damn
- Now you said it
- I watched it about five minutes to the beginning
I watched all the ads today.
Yeah, I'm making a thunder.
You've never seen it.
You need to plunder through a blockbuster to find this movie
so you can muster up the courage to watch an R-rated movie
and then go home and put on shoes, please.
Have you guys battled each other yet?
No, but I'm about to.
Jack Fincher, you're going to kill your whole career.
Yeah, you were in the bear.
Didn't even see her anywhere in the movie or the show in the
season 2.
I thought the movie blowed.
I thought it completely sucked.
I think I don't give a fuck about movies or TV.
Acting is not for me.
I think that they should have made it about art
instead of food, 'cause art is way better than food.
You don't need food to live, only art.
- What, am I supposed to respond to that?
- That's rude, turn the beat up, that's rude.
That's rude.
Of course, you said, "Oh, we're battling?"
And then I battle you and you don't even have the,
you say, "Oh, what, am I supposed to respond to that?"
That's fine. There's nothing I can do about it.
But I didn't think of anything to do.
What could you even say about me, man?
Basically nothing that could be said about me and my feelings can't get hurt.
Featuring Jack Benzinger sponsored by Icelandic glacial water.
We got a case of that for free by the way.
You fucking ball piece of shit.
I'll come to your house and beat the fuck out of your dog and slit his fucking throat.
Bitch, I don't even like you.
I don't even fucking like you, man.
I'll beat the shit out of you.
That's right.
I'm going to come and fucking kill you, man.
I'm going to put a fucking knife and slice you up like tofu.
Oh, I rhyme.
There you go.
Tofu.
And guess what?
Then I'm going to come to your house and kill you.
And then I'm going to come to your house and I'm going to give you a big ass hug with a
fucking knife that was going to be in my hand.
And then, um, why'd you have to go?
Why'd you have to make me?
- Relax, it's a battle.
- Instead of being violent, I wish you had been silent.
- Yeah, don't be--
- I wish your hat was violet, instead of this ugly-ass blue.
It looks like poo.
My poo is blue.
I think poo is blue.
That's 'cause all I eat is berries that are blue,
and it makes my poo completely blue,
and I think it's that color instead of brown.
You should go ahead and move right out of town.
Also, on your hat, there is a typo,
and I think that you need lipo.
- Damn, wait.
- Change your name to Mico.
Change your name to Mico.
- All right, three versus one rap battle.
You guys don't know who you just got into a battle with.
It's me, 'cause I'm crazier than a (beep)
with 600 bullion cubes on top of a castle.
Now look at you.
You, your name is Cameron.
I just am so disappointed
because you don't even remind me of a lantern.
And look at you.
Your name is Patrick.
I'm gonna have to put you inside of the letter K
'cause you're ketchup.
And what's your name, Caleb?
I already disrespected both of your friends,
so now I'm putting you in the ground like cable.
the way of a letter.
You had a jumble. It's not really a freestyle. It's more of a jumble. I
feel like I tried the rapper thing. It didn't quite work out. I might have to
go back to acting, but they're probably not going to take me back after
everything I said about the bear, so I might have to go into hiding sports
sports. Okay, you're tall enough to play sports. I can do sports. You could
fingerboard. I've seen you. I saw you earlier. I think
you get sponsored by Black River Ramps.
I feel like I have a, every time I come on this podcast, I say the first eighth of a
word.
It happens every time.
Every time.
Yeah, you invent a new word.
Some Mesopotamian sound.
It's crazy, man.
Okay, guys.
This is a joint tactics.
Jack Benseger is going to be doing some more acting, so if you like watching TV, just look
out for him. If you like movies or shows. Do you have any Amazon Prime digital rewards?
Any time period, if there's any casting directors who want me to get up on their show, I'll do
something from any time period. Croatia. Croatia. The Croatian era. He'll do Croatia. He'll
do Croatia. The Croatian ages. Check out Joy Tactics. It's very good. It has Nate Veron
and Eric Ray Hill. Nobody else on it. They have a robot who does the intro. They have
a guest sometimes. You have to buy a ticket to our sketch show. This is the last time we can say that.
Sketch show on Friday. If you're listening to this, it comes out. It's in two days. Give us a little preview, man.
Okay, so basically we will have a sketch where there's going to be a sketch that me and Pierce
wrote where we're weird kids. Yep, that'll be great. I have one with a big iPad. Yeah, that'll be great.
We have Caleb as a little kid and then... Okay, well don't spoil everything. How big is this iPad?
Yeah, just give us an idea. Give us a ballpark.
We'll...
We have a sketch called "Liquid Droid."
Is that like liquid death, but for a robot?
That's just...
Don't spoil it at all.
Stop spoiling it. That's the point of a teaser is you spoil it.
We got all the names of the sketches written on that board right there that you can see, Jackson.
I can't see that.
Guys, I hope you enjoyed these fingers. They created a six-fingered fist and you're getting punched in your fucking face.
See you next time on Podcasts Without Lists. Bye!
*static*
I can tell you what I would say if I was on if I was I was represented myself
here in this case. I would you know how I seal the deal. I say I would say I
would say well I do the kiss at the end because I would start I guess the
judge I would start sealing the deal but I would finish sealing the deal with a
kiss. I would say could I please have everybody direct their attention to
exhibit a and then I would have all of an exhibit with all the evidence that
proves. Yeah. Oh right. But you guys I have to say one thing. This is me. Court
Fantasy is a very I'm loving this a lot, but you guys we did get the last laugh
We did get the we got the last laugh
And this is what I was tech this is what Patrick was asking me what I was texting I was sending this okay
We got is a strike that we made in the war listen
By making us pay money, but we have we got we got soldiers of four
We had one areas working for us was like the guys in Japan that didn't know that World War two was over
Oh yeah, wait this is the call?
This is a soldier in the field.
We got shooters.
Yeah.
Turn that up.
It's up as it will go.
Um, okay, I just had some questions for you if that's alright.
Um, do you guys pick up feces?
Yeah.
No, do you pick up human feces?
Okay, what if I hide it in a bag?
Like, will you check?
They'll check that for human feces.
How do you guys check that?
He opens up the bag and he checks for that.
*laughter*
Seems strange.
Uh...
I think that's the end
of the call, yeah.
Yeah. And if you thought
if you think... The driver will open the package
and check for human feces, that's what
that's apparently what *bleep*
is going to do. I don't know if we should be saying
their name, cause we just admitted that
we could get... To prank call them? We could get
here's in a lot of legal trouble.