I
we made it y'all. We made it. We it's today is the halfway point, the
halfway three day one. We're hanging in the planetary system and think about
the week. What happens every week man hump day comes right there in the
middle. I know I know no hump day in the planetary week, none dude. It's all
You know who likes hump day? Camels. Like the commercial. Camels like cigarettes man. Alright.
They can like two things. They like the desert sand. They can like two things at once. I
guess you're right. Is it true that water, they store their water in their hump? They
store their water in their rings of Saturn. Today is Saturn. Today is Saturn. You had,
they store it in their rings of Saturn? I'm not thinking much today. That's okay, dude,
your brain off and just let this shit flow through you. That's what this is all about.
I need a diet coke or something. I need some kind of... I woke up too early this morning.
You're always like, "I need a caffeine drink." I need a performance enhancing...
I need PE drugs.
You know, right now you sound like basically any guy you'd find in an alley.
Exactly. Some scumbag.
A homeless guy.
A homeless.
A hobo.
There's a homeless guy who changed up his story around here. I've seen him, he comes
Is it like is it the guy who started to pretend to be mentally disabled that
we've talked about before?
Maybe, but this guy has been pretending to be Palestinian. Yeah, it's the same.
Yeah, now he added he used to be Dominican and now he says Palestinian
Argentinian. Yeah, Palestinian Argentinian and good rhyme. Well, that's
I think why how he came up with it, but it used to just be a guy who would walk
around and ask people for money and then he started doing a crazy voice for a
the disability that nobody's ever had and then he's now is saying that he's
order yeah
something called sponge disease and it makes me it makes me laugh weird.
It's kind of a dog and then he now he started saying he's Palestinian and I
honestly like what could this guy got hustle? It's called a genius. Yeah,
how am I going to be mad? He knows he knows what he's doing to know. He knows
car is walking around. He's a pro dude. Oh, he's a fucking pro. I made an amazing
discovery this week, which is I started going on the Ridgewood subreddit guys.
The Ridgewood subreddit is some of the most vilely racist stuff ever posted in
the universe on this. Really? Yeah. I mean, I forget how- Is it people who just
moved here who aren't so happy that maybe there was a community here beforehand?
Yes, pretty much, yeah. Like a Polish community, though. Well, it's a bit- For
me my favorite part of Ridgewood man, but completely one hundred percent is every
single Saturday night. If it is after four PM,
I will see
about one hundred Mexican guys who are all five two and they are all the
drunkest person I've ever seen in my life and they are what they are all kind
of free roaming on a quest. Yeah, just read going in. They're going into every
store on the street and all switching and coming out like a Scooby Doo thing. I
feel like I need to. It feels like like literally falling down. They're all
doing the thing where they start to walk and they're walking makes them lean
forward and that makes them have to run so they don't fall over. They're all
big stumble. Yeah, it's some kind of that drunk in a minute. It's some kind of
MMORPG and it's literally not part of every single Saturday. It's incredible.
It's so beautiful. They talk to each other, text above their heads and give
each other quest. They literally are. They're in a hub. It's so fucking
awesome. Yeah, dude, it's incredible. I went to town when I was here. When Kai
was here. I was telling him about it and then I was like and then he like came
to my apartment and he's like dude, I saw the
just like those guys are awesome. They have everything because they works like
if you the only reason to ever get that drunk is because your job is so fucking
hard and every Saturday. Yeah, you just you gotta just light it off. Yeah, light
it off. We're not shaming them or anything. We're saying I think it's so
I figured out yeah. I like incredible. I do I'm not being I would probably feel a
little bit different if they were all like seven feet tall. I would probably
feel a little bit scared if a bunch of giant guys, but because it's all like
they're all really small, it's cute. Very, very small. Yeah, I have seen them.
I have I love to see they all pee on the wheels of cars. So I picked that up from
them. They learn. I learned something every day from them. It's like a human
instinct man. Yeah, that's on the wheel. Yeah, that's being a wheel of a car. Who
doesn't you pick the nicest. I just love to it's seven PM, not even making any
attempt to hide what you're doing at all, just peeing on just beautiful. Oh yeah,
I like it. It's free. It's the most free thing you can do. It's freedom. It's
pure freedom.
Sometimes they'll be lying down on the sidewalk. I think maybe they're dead.
Yeah, that happens. Dude, the other day, the other day I was walking down the
street, there's a fucking asleep guy on the ground and a lady was standing over
him and I walked past and she was like, she said, "Do you know this guy?"
And I was like, first of all, that doesn't maybe I was wearing the wrong
kind of outfit that day, but I was like, no, I don't know this guy. I think he's
asleep. She's like, I think he's fucking dead and he had like a beer bottle next
to him. Yeah, and I was like, I don't think he's dead. She's like he's dead.
He she called 911 yeah, and then he got fucking arrested. Oh my God, you're so
worried about this guy that you sent him to jail. That's crazy. That's insane.
Yeah, someone we know in college did that. Just let the guy be asleep, bro.
someone we know was like hanging out and like there's somebody like nodding off
and like the comment or whatever and they call like if you call the cops
because you think the guy is dead you're allowed to poke him you just
talk to him one time you have to talk to him
it's not that's crazy to not even try to they're never fucking dead you always
have to poke them first if they were dead you'd
know yeah exactly you know you wouldn't and also if they were dead you would not
call the cops you would leave exactly immediately yeah yeah i don't
I don't want to do a dead guy. I would that's a former that I got a
the thing is the differences. If you're if there's if the guy's dead,
you're not helping anybody. No, he's far he's already dead man. Yeah, just
fucking pick him up. You bring him to the trash yourself. Yeah, exactly the
try to help if you want to help yeah, but I'm in the
if some of the sleep on the start. Oh, that's actually a good point. Actually,
not if they're if you know that they're dead on the street thing is poking them.
If somebody is asleep on the street or not responsive on the street, just start
putting them in the trash. If they're awake, they're going to stop, they're
going to get mad yeah and then you just go like sorry man. I thought you're
fucking here's here's a here's a true thing.
The lead singer of slipknot, Corey Taylor, a very famous story that he when
he was a kid, he overdosed and his friends threw him into a dumpster and
left him to die. So what I'm saying is you run into guys sleeping on the
street or maybe looks like he could be dead, can I throw him in the trash
like okay? We're making an area you get in trouble for touching a dead guy.
yeah best case scenario. He makes incredible music, incredible music,
incredible music, incredible music that stands the test of time. Exactly decades
that holds up and never ever sounds odd. Yeah yeah stuff that is now weird right
or blame. I think I need to try being a guy thrown in the trash. Yeah, I nods
off and I watch a I watch a video. I watch these videos today. That was this
guy. He's like one of those like dumpster diving YouTube channel. Yeah,
but it's the fakest thing I've ever seen in my entire life where he's like he's
like oh, let's see what's in here. Oh wow Rolex in the trash. Wow that's all
he's like finding insane. He found a full sixteen pack of Bud Light in the
trow damn it's just I mean this guy needs to try harder. Yeah, like nobody's
throwing that shit away. Nobody's believing that you know I'm not
believing that I don't even believe when people do when it's the videos that are
like my thrift store haul yeah, but it could be the way it could be the where
it could be stuff that is not interesting or cool or expensive. I still wouldn't
believe you can't even buy nice stuff every because of ebay every store. Every
guy who owns like a thrift store, a pawn shop looks up everything that they have
to see if it's really expensive. It was so sick double. Anyway, you go to a
thrift store, they're selling like a car heart pair of jeans for like a hundred
dollars. Yeah, like what the vintage car heart the hell it's like the the thing
yeah, it's like oh this one has like the paper tag instead of like the printed
one. And it's like, oh yeah, this is like Carhartt. You find like Levi's orange tabs anywhere,
that's going to run you like, I've seen them go for like $60. They're just jeans from the
70s.
A DVD copy of the Lord of the Rings, The Two Towers is like $5 now. It's supposed to be
25 cents. What the hell happened to...
Thrift stores are completely bunk.
They fell off, man.
They're completely bunk because it's because of COVID. It's because COVID and then everyone
learned that you can start your own fucking Depop store and shit.
there was a speaking of I got some items. No
I never want to hear about your
and wall that I used to go to that would literally that were selling books. It
sold every book, no matter what for twenty five cents, and I felt like I was
stealing every time. It's insane, you know, and now you go and it's fucking
you go and it's a it's a book that nobody has ever heard of. You can't even
find it on Google. There's no interest for it at all. It's a sci fi book that
somebody wrote before sci fi was invented. It's falling apart. There are
hermits living inside the pages and it's seventeen dollars. I'm about to blow
your mind. If you like book deals, bro,
the library completely free free, you go free as charge. I free the way I use it.
How do you use it? I keep the books. Yeah, they don't they can't charge you
to go back and then I'd go back and try. Would you go back man to get another?
I remember another one taking a book from the library and it being way
overdue and the feeling of shame as you up to that thing with the old Harry,
the third Harry Potter book and you just put it on the desk. You're like you're
you grow you have stubble on your face, because it's been so long since you
checked it out and you're like yeah yeah. I do you just you just throw it in
the book drop and you leave yep, no, because then you have to pay for it man.
Now you throw in the book drop and don't check out another book and then they
try to yeah. They'll send you mail. That's fucking true, but I'm going and
I'm trying to a lot of mail. I'm trying to read the first eighteen pages of
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy man. I got to go to the library. Yeah, I just
don't check the book out. Just sit there like it's a reference book, so they're
like you're looking through like looking through a laws. I used to be way too
ambitious with the books that I would get from the library as a child. I would be
like I was like eight years old and saw the Charlie Brown where he reads War and
Peace and I was like I'm gonna read that book and then I got it from the library
to go home. That thick.
Bunch of fucking nonsense. I used to take out this book from the library that was
like I think 1000 pages and it was the Encyclopedia of Rock and Roll.
It's the Rolling Stone Encyclopedia of Rock and Roll. It's like this big. That's
I would just read about like it was just different. It was any band that has
appeared in Rolling Stone. So I just read about bands in there. Damn. And then
that's how I found out. That's how I like found music when I was like nine years
old. That's how I found like Frank Zappa. I would just like I wonder who's in Z.
I wonder who starts with Z. I just check out every single book they had about
Bigfoot and the Loch Ness Monster. Yeah, that's a good one. Yeah, 20 of
dinosaurs. I mean, I read every dinosaur book. I'm gonna be honest. Yeah, I was
just taking out graphic novels. Yeah, that's what I was going to say to like
the five comic books they had. Yeah, I would just, I would just run Justice
League, Young or Young Titan, Teen Titans and stuff. I was young. I was
reading Bone Man. I was not reading Bone Man. Oh, dude. Bone Man is a different
thing. Bone Man is not very good, but Bone was fine. I don't even know what
Bone was about. It was about some whiteys. It was about bones. It was about
bones who were in love with a woman. It was about a woman, two white bones
that walked around. And a dragon. It was a big bone and a little bone. Yep.
and they would walk around. One sounds like something I have dreamed of. One of
them was named bone. Yeah, the others all had bone in their name. Yeah, so it was
about just like basically bone and phone bone phone bone. Was that really his
name? Phone bone? The big guy? One of them was named phone bone. Maybe that
was the really
it could have been the phone. There was a character named the rat king. That's a
good name. Was he a bone or no? He was a rat. Oh, that's a monster. No, he was a
monster. Oh, it looked like a rat, maybe a little bit. I can't remember anything
that happened in those books. I can visualize them the rat monsters. I know
what there's a bone named phone, but I was into the alternative graphic novels
like that and mouse. You know, I know your ass is reading mouse
bro. I was reading mouse and I was like this shit can never happen again, bro.
I read mouse for we were doing the it was like the unit in seventh grade for
the holocaust and I read mouse the what I did a unit on the holocaust. I
definitely made fun of some kids for reading mouse. Yeah, dude, you didn't
like history. Yeah, I definitely I definitely looking back
opening up the preacher. You're making a mouse is gay. Yeah, you read watchman
so close to your face, looking at the penis x-men. I remember somebody
brought watchman this kid, Paul Winder, who I think grew up to be Nazi. He
brought watchman to the middle school and we were passing it around later. I
mean, like it was porn, the black. Yeah, and just looking at the cock. Yeah,
I drew a dick in there. And just not even, we were excited to see any kind of
drawn nudity. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It was so exciting to us in sixth grade.
Which I mean, you had the computer then. But there's something about the...
The computer was too easy. The smell of the book. The smell of the book
that all the guys had used. And it's a story, it's a comic. Exactly.
It's... Yeah, you have... That was something as a kid. That's what makes it
exciting. Nudity was scary when you look it up on the computer,
but if it's contextualized in a movie or something, you go like,
"That's awesome." What I always thought about that, it's really funny that
they kind of they they show his dick like a few times, but then a bunch of the
other time they did they do the like they do full Simpsons movie, like coffee
mug yeah, it's like what just just show the show it every show. I mean that
just means the guy who was drawing it just got a little bit yeah. He drew it
once and he's like
why am I so good at driving
he based it on his own to which is the saddest part. Did you really yeah?
That's the reason the doctor Manhattan is blue was just so it would match the
the creators blue penis. It was so devoid of air. It kind of turned blue. Yeah,
yeah, you guys for a penis to turn blue enough of this cock talk. Let's talk
planets. Okay, let's talk Saturn. Let's go through the outfits. Let's start with
Caleb because you have an interesting outfit on. All right, I flopped you
flopped. I think I yeah, I think I flopped. I couldn't think of anything.
So I dressed up like the ring because there's a ring on Saturn multiple. I
I think we may be all flopped today.
Well, I'm dressed, I think that none of us own any Saturn clothes I'm gathering.
Yeah.
I just wore the Jupiter thing.
I could have thought we could have dressed up like cars.
Oh, like a Saturn.
I was maybe going to, I was going to, because Saturn is kind of like brownish, beige-ish
color I feel like.
Yeah.
So I was going to maybe, if I had a shirt that was that color, I was going to wear that
and then put like a duct tape ring around my stomach.
But I didn't even have a shirt that was that color.
So I'm just dressed as the rings.
because then one picture I looked at, they were kind of blue and green.
Yeah. I kind of dressed like the rings, too.
Yeah, show us here at Walkers.
And you're dressed as the ring.
And then I went to the barber shop this morning.
And what? I did see this in the back of your hat band.
Oh, damn it.
I think my shit got fucked up.
I don't know.
It looks good.
My God.
What did you ask him for at the barber shop?
I asked him for the ring of Saturn.
And they did this?
And they gave me this.
Damn.
What is up with our barbers and being interested in planets? I know it's
really surprising. These guys are really, really like knowledgeable too, like
they knew what a ring was. They knew, I mean look at this.
I mean this shit is too fire. So for our audio listeners, Patrick has a
one, he's completely bald except for a ring of hair around the top of his
head. And I think that honestly, now that I'm seeing it on camera,
you'd like it. I think that this is gonna catch on as a hairstyle. It
it looks really good. I was so excited because when I walked in and saw you on
the computer, I did see through the back of your hat. I could see I knew
damn it. I was like I should have worn a fitted. I knew that it was. Did you
see the part where I cut way too close to his skin and he has no hair at all?
Well, at first I saw what I saw is I saw the back of his neck. He has one
well. Now I got to shave it all off so well and I was like
now I did you have a great job. You screwed up. Now I got to shave the
whole damn thing off. You need to you need like
one week of this. I think I look like well yeah hold up. You do have to you
have to hold on to this for as long as possible. This is a good once you get
something. I mean this is so much power there. If there's one regret I have in
my life, one regret, it's that I didn't keep my Navi braid for for longer than I
did. I kept it for only a couple of weeks because I was going home for
Christmas and I did not want to have to have my family. I did ask about it and
He's explained, well, there's basically a planet. Yeah, I know, but that's why it's a regret.
Oh yeah, because I wish I hadn't done. That's what regret. Oh, I guess you're right. So
it's like I did something different than what I did. Yeah. Oh, okay. I thought you were
just saying that you're glad at least that I had cut it off and then framed it in my
house. I knew a kid who had one of the Padawan braids in school and we had it for two years
straight. Whoa, I know a kid with a rat tail. Me too. He also carried a Zippo around.
Rat tail so long that it started to turn blonde at the end. Whoa, that's cute.
That is cool. It's kind of gross. That's like when a guy's got these long beard
and then at the end it turns. I think it's more like when a guy grows his
fingernails out for a hundred years. Yeah, it's more of that vibe. It feels
more like a Rip Van Winkle. Yeah. Did he grow hair and nails? He slept. Yeah,
but he was sleeping. Did he grow them in his sleep? He slept. He'd sleep all
day. He probably was still growing in his sleep, I guess. Yeah. I mean, I
he has a beard when he woke up. He had a beard when he woke up, but they didn't
even think about his hair and nails. Those also grow. Those don't stop
growing when you die. His hair is probably long, too. Well, he wasn't dead.
He's not. I know, but they definitely you're okay, but they're definitely
gonna still be there when you're asleep. Yeah, you're saying the hair, the hair
and the nails would still grow even while he was asleep. How long did he
sleep for? 100 years, 100, 100 years. I do think I need a that level of sleep.
I something pretty soon. I need to catch up. I've been in trouble. You've been in
trouble. I've been in trouble. I've been having scary dreams, man. Me too. Yeah,
scary fucking really scary. I've been having horrible waking nightmares,
waking as in they wake you up, not no as in I'm awake and my dream is coming into
reality.
That's more of a real power and a dream. Well, yeah, you have some kind of don't
say yeah, you admitting to have a power. You're not supposed to do that. I don't
you don't like it's not a power I can't control it. I woke up and I there I saw
1 million bugs are calling every one of my room. That's really scary man.
It was so fucking horrible. No crawling. Oh okay. I found some roaches in my pantry the
other day. They're everywhere man. It's fucked up. They're in every building in
this city right now. What the hell's happening with these roaches? We have
been, we have been engaged in a war citywide. I've seen them at the store.
store. Yeah. Well, anywhere else? My house. Okay. You seen them at the store? What store?
The store next to my house. So I've heard people say that they've had them. I saw one
at the restaurant. In your food? No. No? No. On the wall. And they're just, I'm just saying,
be careful. They are disgusting. They're out there. They are gross. They made me hate bugs.
I've never liked bugs. Me neither. You have been fond of bugs for some time.
I wouldn't even call myself fond of bugs, but I don't care. You'll let it slide.
I let it slide. If there's a spider, I would like to leave it in its web and
look at it every day. I'd like to destroy it with a salt shotgun. I love those.
I like that we've invented the salt guns were an amazing idea, and I think that
they should expand it to more things, a salt crossbow. Does Saturn have any salt
on it? We could do that. It probably has minerals involved. I think there's salt
in
beautiful girls of all time. A child? Is it planet report time y'all? I think it might
be planet report time. He said the child from the ring is one of the most beautiful women
he's ever seen. He likes Japanese girls. Wasn't she like 7? What? In the ring? No like 13.
She's been in the TV for ages. Okay. Asshole. You do you I guess. Yeah I will fucking do
me. I'm jumping in that well,
you mean crawling out
laying out
this green is on the tv here. I come I crawl
I'm killing you for real fear
killing you with fear,
the TV just below the surface. She's crawling, appalling.
Whoa! Wow! Okay, anyway.
Join us once again on a five week galactic journey through our solar
system.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh a little too.
And now, the Planet Report with Cameron Fetter.
Oh yeah!
Okay, guys. Can I start doing that? What? As part of the thing. What? Doing what?
Oh yeah, can we add that in? We can add that in post. Yeah, I'll send you this
here. Send me a clean tape. Send me this. Oh yeah. Can you send me that? I'll
send you that. Yeah, extract that. Can you extract that? I'll extract it. Okay,
today's planet report is called
There's Something About Saturn, a planet report by Cameron Fetter.
Let me prop up my phone here. Okay, prop up your phone. Yeah.
I want to give Saturn another ring.
Oh, please baby.
Just say yes.
Saturn, I want to be with you forever.
Something about your body,
more than 750 times the size of Earth,
just drives me mad with desire.
Who wants to be Saturn?
- Me.
- We're so alike in so many ways.
You have 146 moons.
I have 146 moods, from happy to sad and everything in between.
Oh, it goes on this, right.
You're named after the Roman god of agriculture.
My middle name is named after my uncle.
You revolve around the sun every 29.5 Earth years.
And we both have days named after us.
You have Saturday and I have International Puppy Day,
March 23rd.
I want to give you one more ring, Saturn.
We could be so happy together.
I know this isn't your first rotation.
After all, you already have eight rings.
But things will be different with me.
I'll treat you right.
I know how to handle a planet composed primarily
of hydrogen and helium.
And I'm good with moons.
I grew up with a moon, so I don't mind being around them.
Tethys and Titan love me,
and I think I could be a great role model for them.
I don't even care that you've been visited
by four spacecraft before.
Oh, Saturn, just say yes.
Other people don't understand you like I do.
Some people see an atmosphere
that's negative 288.4 degrees Fahrenheit
and contains methane and ammonia
and run for the hills, not me.
In fact, I hear atmosphere
is one of the things I love about you.
I think it makes you unique.
Wow.
You're always getting so down on yourself,
but you've achieved so much
in the 4.5 billion years you've been around.
You were in the movie "Interstellar."
That's all I can think of right now,
but you know you're something special.
We've been the long distance for a while now.
And I mean it honestly when I say I don't mind driving the 884 million miles to dick you down.
But I'm ready to take it to the next level.
Let's move to Asheville, North Carolina and buy a house together.
Baby, I love you. Just say yes.
And that's today's Planet Report.
That is so beautiful. That was amazing, dude. It was a combination of so many, I mean,
I didn't know this. It was your taste. So it's kind of about love and about
knowledge. Yeah. There's a ring stuck on my fucking finger, man.
Well, I guess. Oh, God. I guess you have to wear it forever. Why do you want to
take, well, you're not supposed to take it off. Okay, you're right. Well, not
until one of us passes away. Yeah.
Passes gas. Saturn's a gas giant. True.
It is, yeah, Saturn is beautiful. Again, we're kind of in this zone of planets
where I don't know that much about them. And so this has been very, I need this planet
report. It's opening my eyes to a lot of different stuff about, I didn't know 75 or 750 times
the size of earth, man. BBW. Yeah, that is a BBW. Nine times the diameter. Big beautiful
world. Big, ooh. Yeah, wait, I just came up with that. That's better than what I thought.
And one of the biggest moons. Titan. Titan. Titan. Titan. Why is its moon so big? Because
it's a big planet. It can have a big moon. Because anything with a big bottom got a big
moon. Facts. Don't fuck us up with that man. Okay. 146 moons. I hope he gives you 146
moons. Don't you love when you come home and your girl moons you?
Just walking around with her butt cheeks out. Butt cheeks hanging out the top.
Yep. Just full moon. Butt flop. That prank is too much. You ever been mooned by a girl?
Yeah. Yeah. In a pranking way? Yeah. Yeah. Put that thing away man. What are you doing?
What the hell? I only think this is funny on guys.
It's only funny on guys.
This is fucking disgusting.
Mooning?
I don't want to see all the stuff.
It's funny when it's a guy's butt.
Yeah, or if you have a fucking pink... if you have a pink... don't dog breathe about
the mooning girl.
Don't you dare. Stop it.
But dude, I don't want to see.
No, stop man. We're not even...
Stop panting. Stop panting right now.
Okay, we're changing subject completely. What movies have you guys seen as of late, I guess?
Here, let me tell you guys about this really humbling experience I had.
okay this past week. It's not related to saturn, but we can bring it back to
saturn after
so I was playing fortnight
with my buddies on the computer fortnight with buddies, legendary,
legend, wait for it dairy fortnight running buddies running fuck me running
trios with the buddies. I fucking love buddies. We were joking around. Oh God,
it gets better. Every second we were doing a joke that was making me still
making me laugh. We were doing elmer fudd in world war one and he's in the
inches and he goes one eight
one
when a twench foot yeah, and we're all deal. My my dearest pusilla my heart
aches
for you all you know all type of Elmer yeah, of course, I hope it wasn't loud
rowdy Elmer Fudd yeah hours, hours, hours, passing by with buddies, yelling
into my microphone, bouncing with my buddies and then night yelling as Elmer
Fudd playing fortnight
my life is a fucking movie man playing night with my man cake skin yep, oh gee
fortnight man, all right guy, we get a we get the vic royale. I say all right
guys got it. I got to get off. I'll talk to you guys later log off, close the
computer. I walk into the other room and my fiance is sitting at the dining room
table and she's drinking a glass of wine and is playing smooth jazz music and is
doing a puzzle. Oh my God
complete ship pisses me off man.
Definitely heard every Elmer of course yeah and she said yeah. I was going to
tell you to be quiet, but I
that's a good one.
Pure shock, just just completely blindsided yeah. Oh yeah, God damn dude.
Why do they do that stuck with me? Just I was I felt like a kindergartner dude. I
I walk in I was playing fortnight. I'll play eight hours of video games. I'll
walk in on a like a Saturday where I'm like, oh well, whatever it's a Saturday.
I can do whatever I want. I walk into the living room. My wife has the day off
to she's sitting there. She's knitted five scars. She literally looks exactly
like a granny like old grandmother, Tweety bird style granny. She's like
reading with one hand and doing that with the other. She has NPR playing like
what the fuck how how can you live like so much? How the hell can you live like
Why do women love yarn? Don't you want a Dorito, bitch? Don't you want to go to Buffalo Wild Wings
with me? What the hell are you doing? This is why I got to go there. I'm going to drive like 15
minutes out. I'm going to go to the Buffalo Wild Wings at Maspeth. Every single food that you eat
on a Saturday should be sauced. It should be tossed in a bowl with sauce. You should get the
sauce all over a white t-shirt. Even if it's Caesar salad. Yeah, and then you should watch
like... It should be the gross Caesar salad from the buffet. Every Saturday you should say,
I'm not really in the mood for a movie. I don't want to commit to that. Instead, I'm going to watch
15 episodes of a 45-minute TV show. That's what you should be spending your time. I'm going to
watch ridiculousness all day. Yeah, I'm going to I'm literally going to watch 12 hours of TV,
but a movie is too much. That's what it needs to be. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly that.
That's what the weekends are for. It's not for sitting there doing a hobby that's
that way. Make something literally she's making fucking spoiler for my mom. She's making Christmas
presents. Mom, she's making you a fucking criminal. Mom, shut off the episode right now. Mom,
turn it off. You're getting a fucking scar for this. Shut that, shut that. Computer off.
By the way, you're getting the worst one she made. You're getting the first one she made
because she made it and was like, I fucked this one up. I'll give it to your mom. Does
your mom listen to this? No. She doesn't know how to access YouTube. That's a good mom trait
to have that on YouTube. My mom texts me every once in a while, "Why don't you follow me
back on Instagram?" What the fuck is wrong with you? That's so mean. I don't want to
see your shit. Yeah, you don't want to see pictures of your brother? No dude, he's taller
than me. That's true. He's 12 years old, he's 6'2". You're seeing a picture of him next
to like a locker or something and it's like, "Man, I wish I could be that tall." Why a
locker? Basketball team. A locker has a certain height. He's not good at basketball, he's a
golfer. Oh yeah, he's got into golf. Okay. And he just is like zero. He's a kid. He has
like zero patience and he just like runs up to it. He's like, yeah, golf sucks. Hits it
so perfectly, like as hard as he can. Worst swing I've ever seen. It's so fucking, it's
fucked up, dude. Yeah. Happy Gilmore style. It's happening to me. Having a brother that
much younger than you, it really is fully just you're being replaced. Oh yeah. I'm being
replaced. He's funnier than me. He talks about fucking, he talks about his balls in a way
I could never at the dinner table and my balls are stink. They stink. Yeah, I go. That's fucking awesome, man
I said that shit when I was your age. My mom would kill me. Oh, I stopped talking about your stinky balls
Yeah, my sister my sister like lives with my mom so my nephews are still around like
Their grandparents so a lot of stuff is getting encouraged. That shouldn't yeah, I think I said it before but
They learned about breastfeeding. Oh, yeah, and they make each other they make fun of each other for having breastfed
They say yeah, but you sucked up mom's boobs to end arguments. They're right dude. That's crazy. That shit is a good comeback
That is just wrong man, yeah, we need to be all the it needs to be power everything should be powder
Oh, yeah, I think that that should not you should not be putting a baby on your stuff, man
man. Especially not fucking-- Especially mine. In my house. You're not sucking on my nipple.
No, dude. There's no milk in there. There's almost none. You're going to just get hair
in your mouth, you fucking idiot. Do you guys know about that's why Kevin Gates lost weight?
No. He lactated? No, he held his friend's baby and the baby tried to suck his tit and
then he lost like a hundred pounds. Damn. Yeah. That's so sick, man. That is really funny.
All right, I have I'd like to talk about my painting. Okay. I really would like to talk about my painting
I sent it to you Julio
Account like I think if you put some gel in it got to be glued
Yeah, you need got to be glue. No, I should have done do we still have the disposable razors here?
I could have oh you want to do you want to shave that I could shave it. I could shave it down like my
We need to oh
I get to play with this ring. No, you don't that's my fucking ring. Don't break. Whoa
I need to bring that back to my house. Well, how do you need to bring it back? That's a fucking wedding ring, man
This is your that's my wedding ring. This is what you engaged to your eyes. I sent it in the DM
Discord I did take this ring from from my fiance's jewelry box. She was asleep
story box? You are going to get in so much trouble for this. It's a piece of
plastic, man. I mean, let's be polite here. Okay. Well, apparent ring she wears.
Can't find it, but that's okay. I had to do a digital painting, guys. I'd like to
show this to y'all right now. Oh, there it is.
Where's the rings, man? Huh? Wait. You're right. There isn't any rings. Wait a
second hold on you want to know why there's no rings man why because this
painting takes place in two thousand and twenty five when the rings
yep. What the hell I learned about that today. I heard about their disappearing
they're disappearing for some time. It's an eclipse of some type. What we won't
be able to see the rings of Saturn for a while. Holy shit. How sad is that? I
know I go out every night and I'm I see him. Here's a stupid. I am it's a part
I saw that I searched Saturn to get a reference photo. I saw the headline and
it was it said Saturn's rings are disappearing and I'm so stupid. I was
thinking that it had something to do with climate change. I also thought that
I also thought that I was like, wait, how does that even work? How does climate
change reach Saturn?
But it turns out it's actually just the sun doing something odd. Isn't it crazy
how many of the planets are just cold? They're all cold. I know, man, we need a
little more of that. Yeah, we need a little bit more of that. Do you think
we're going to enter a new ice age soon? Yeah, do you think we'll get back on
ice? It's a ball earth. You know they're trying to bring mammoths back. Why Joe
Rogan's buddy for meat? I know I well they brought back mammoth meat as like a
as like a stunt. Yeah, I did it as like a publicity thing where it was like they
like could they I think they had they can synthesize mammoth meat and they did
it to be like like oh doesn't this make you feel interestingly about cloning? Is
it this fascinating? You know that type of thing that they do sometimes not even
It's not even like there. You can get mammoth meat that is just like preserved in like a
big bunch of ice in like Alaska and stuff.
What?
Yeah. There's like people you find people find like almost fully preserved woolly mammoths.
What the hell?
Like beef jerky meat and some guy ate one.
Ew.
Isn't that gross? He ate like a 5,000 year old fucking meat.
I would not eat mammoth.
You've never seen the interview with that guy?
No, no, no.
No, no, no. He's a guy who owns like probably the most valuable like
archaeological site that exists right now in terms of like digging up cool
bones and stuff and he doesn't he won't let anybody go and dig on it. He just
digs it up finds mammoth tusks and then like sells them for like $20,000.
God damn. So sick. That is sick. I really I used to think that my number one
thing I needed in the world was for them to clone all the dinosaurs back to life.
No, but the five you don't hell is wrong.
Why you don't want to show the fucking dinosaur.
My God, you don't want to die.
So I mean, it's first of all, that was an I used to that started.
I know it was so crazy.
It pissed me off instantly.
It also pissed me off.
The fuck are you talking about?
We bring back that you want to bring back the dinosaurs.
Yeah, I want to bring back Hitler, too.
Oh, yeah. Let's fucking break.
Let's go.
You know, they say I'm not watch the news lately.
They say I'm the Hitler of dinosaurs.
They say you're the Hitler of dinosaurs.
say it who the dinosaurs yeah obviously the American dinosaur anyway the five
weeks of planets has taught me that it's more important it would be better is
what what what is what you say nothing okay I was trying to make sure the joke
was airtight the joke of being Hitler of dinosaurs was airtight it's trying to
to make the acronym. Well, you didn't even use it. You didn't even use it in air.
H of D. What? H of D? What's that? The Hitler of Dinosaurs acronym? No, no,
the ADL, the American Dinosaur League. Oh, okay. Oh, yeah, okay, I'm getting it.
Like the Anti-Defamation League over there? Yeah. Alright, yeah. Do you want,
like... Look at my hair, y'all.
Sorry, what has the Five Weeks of Planets taught you? The Five Weeks of Planets
has taught me that instead of bringing all the dinosaurs back, we just should go
find a planet that's identical to Earth where there still are dinosaurs. Yes.
or it's a dinosaur. Don't have to be on or I got two words for you man and that
way we can see them in their natural habitat interacting with each other.
Good luck. I want to go to a planet that's identical to earth, but maybe the
radius, the diameter rather is
a couple inches smaller. So it's a it's completely identical to a couple inches,
but it's a little bit smaller. You feel a little bigger. You feel a little bit
here. I don't think you interesting and a plane flight will be shorter by by a
little by a small now very small by a very maybe even minute, but that adds up
over your lifetime. If you'd fly your entire life, I want to yeah, yeah, a
couple it's completely identical to earth, except it's got like got
restaurants called like small apple bees and small food record, but it's really
not that much. I mean you wouldn't even notice this because it's slightly
smaller because it's slightly smaller nature. I mean, you got to market that,
but you would be like, but check this out. Did you bring your you'd be you'd
land there, you go to charge your phone, the charger would not fit in your
charging. Oh true think about I mean we're talking about you and just we're
talking about inches smaller and the whole of the world. That's that's not
that much when you get to stuff that you in your daily life, a couple inches.
Well, I don't that's a that's a big amount for you're saying the whole like
everything will hire a few inches smaller. Wait everything everything
well, that's because he was saying they have small FUD records and stuff like
Well, but that's just what they would call it. I thought it was a marketing thing. Well,
it's so on that planet using their measurements, I would be 511. What size would your member
be? That's what I was thinking, too. I mean, that's kind of where I was going to be bigger
is that inches are what about our more penises get bigger, but the vaginas get a little smaller.
Well, I think they get a little bigger. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we don't need that. We really don't need that ship humongous. We don't need a humongous
of a JJ on another planet. Do you guys believe in string theory? I believe in
G string theory. What up? Yeah, my theory is I like those. Bring those back. My
theory is I wanted to look like a floss. Yeah, I'm the G. I want to look like a floss.
String theory is just that a guy was like, I think everything is strings. He
was like, I think that there's a million strings. There's a million strings that
are rotating around. I think there's strings everywhere. Yeah, I haven't looked into it much.
That's pretty much what it is.
I would say that's the only category of 4-hour YouTube video that I've not delved into.
That was something I thought I could try to understand when I was in like third or fourth
grade.
Yeah.
I was like, "Damn, string theory."
Is that the one...
So badass.
Remember we were in Texas and I bought that board and it had like the...
Who designed that?
That was like a John.
He designed that board for Sci-Fi Fantasy and it's got the QR code on it and there's
a video that's like...
Yeah, it's a cemetery plot.
has got a QR code on it and the QR code takes you to a video that's like 10 year old boy
describes or explains string theory. That's so web 3. That was me man. That was me explaining
string theory at 10 years old. That video has got like 4.3 million views and it's just
a kid explaining or I think it's quantum physics. I don't really know what it is. It's explaining
all of quantum physics? Yeah I think so. I already told you guys about the kid who explains
God and the loser has a schizophrenic mom and on. Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. You have told me about
you did tell me that boy. Oh, my Facebook group got in trouble. Y'all what happened?
There's a police. There's no there's a problem in my Facebook. Oh, and also I got some new
text from Patrick. Wait a minute. What are we doing? Hold on. I need to. We're losing
the plot. Just reminded me to look at my phone. I just need to show you. Here's here's the
general. So, you know, Facebook groups have like a chat where it adds a general chat. Now
what's going on right now.
Oh my God, I can't show this because this is a YouTube episode. This is HD porn
videos from right now. It's been we've been being spammed by HD porn videos.
Well, I got a click on the talk in the happy birthday. Cameron might be
these are my group members wishing me happy birthday man. I you kind of
violated my privacy by scrolling back in my Facebook group right now.
it's okay. It's normal for people in a facebook group to wish the admin happy
birthday. I don't think that's it's no, then why are they doing it? Andrew and
Brenda and Anthony always happy
they're your closest friends now. Yeah, nice of them. It looks like Anthony
waited to do it till July. Twenty nine, that's twenty five days late.
Patrick has been sending me more text again the last couple of months in the
last time I read these. I think we just need to catch up a little bit. Okay,
"Bruh, what did I eat last night? My diarara smells so bad."
Did we say that one? Okay, well we didn't get to this one, I know.
This weather literally makes me want to...
No, we got to this one.
No, we didn't. There's no way.
Yes, yes we did. I remember.
No, you're not remembering this right.
Scroll down a little more, read past that one. There's probably more.
And Andy Kaufman invented trolling before it was even a thing.
What time did I send that?
That was at midnight.
Five in the morning an IPA is just pumpkin spice latte for basic white roots
right
Five in the morning and then he says
Yeah, and then shortly after dear guitar guys at the party. Congratulations
Congratulations douche you can print sees kinda play the first three chords to a Dave Matthews song
She'll totally be impressed by your glaring originality
That one was good. I sent you my salt and pepper picture instead of these two having a
mid-off, you didn't respond at all. What did I say? You said the next day, "My pet
peeve is NPCs that act like the main character." Right? And then you
said, "I love Kate Bush and Snoopy."
And then I said, "What you do if I cash app 10 bands and tell you to drop picks in my IG?"
Oh yes.
And you said, "Boy, stop."
And I said, "I'm dead ass."
When was that?
And then you didn't say anything.
That was November 4th.
Was I in Chicago then?
Yes, I was.
Imagine how good it probably feels to have a pussy and get fucked in it really hard and
fast.
You said that.
No, that's you, man.
And then you said, "Do you like X videos or RedTube more?"
And then you said, "Do you think Jaboukie would rap on an OJ the Alien beat?"
That's a genuine question. I think Jaboukie would. They've been making raps. I listen
to them.
Oh, God. All right, speaking of.
Yeah, speaking of raps.
I think it's about time.
Yeah, hit it.
No fucking cap.
I want to hear this, man.
Yeah.
You want to hear this shit?
I'm really excited.
Well, intro. So this is obviously a galactic space rock landed on Earth with a CD in a
jewel case perfectly sitting in it.
Yeah.
Another one.
That's exactly what I think.
that. Yeah, so I think we need to hear it. What's this one about?
And we are processing the video. That's not good. Processing the video? Check back
later? How's that even possible? Hit refresh. How's it still processing? Did I
accidentally export it to be three hours long? Did I? I don't know. Can we pause real
quick so I can check this. We're back. And we're back y'all. And we're back with a track
man. We're back with a track. Hit it. I'm so fucking excited to hear this y'all. Wait
did that say featuring B-Lack? What? Yup. Featuring B-Lack. Smoke rings on Saturday.
When I turned three I started smoking tree Got it from a guy and his name was weed
He was also three, made me feel like shit Every day I wish I never smoked on it
When I turned four I went to the store Saw a lemon there and I purchased four
Then I circled back and I purchased more Didn't feel like shit, I loved it
Ate a lemon everyday in my cockpit
Got a clementine and I washed it
When I eat fruit I go dog shit
I love fruit y'all
Wait who's that?
Ah shit, I just woke up on fuckin' Saturn
Is that B-Lack?
I think that is B-Lack
Oh my god
Last thing I remember I was sippin' number 5
Woke up on another planet
Hella aliens outside
Alien rides
Green girls
Alien guys on Saturn, me and OJ splitting alien fries
Doing big things on other planets, we smoking fat sacks
I need big rings, like the one that's in my ass crack
Spit a 16, licked green, where the cash at?
OJ passed a roach, I'ma kill you if you ash that
At the Beverly, integrity just got the best of me
Don't usually smoke, but tonight I'm puffing heavily
With a bad bitch, one dollar, she showed her breast to me
*rapping*
*retching*
Wait, what happened to him?
Oh no.
What happened to him?
*rapping*
NOOOOOO!
Oh no.
No!
Cause he drank the perfume.
Oh my god, dude, he should have just smoked the Tegrity Farms weed that OJ fucking gave him, bro.
He was back on the fume.
He's bad.
Man, that shit is just too sad.
Yeah, a guy, a rapper dies on planet Earth.
This is a story as old as time.
Yeah, they overdose on planet Earth.
They wake up on a different planet.
They start smoking tree, which is good for you.
It's herbal and then they go back to the fucking drug that
killed him in the first place.
They die again on that planet.
It's so fucked.
It's so funny.
I do.
I see this time and time again.
God gave you a second chance at life and you're throwing it
away to fucking drink perfume, man.
You want to drink perfume?
What the fuck is that? You want to drink perfume? You really want to drink perfume? It's not
good for you. It is not good. The high isn't even that good, man. The high is terrible.
No, what? Your breath smells better? Yeah, you drink. It smells like shit. Like, if you
drink, when you drink enough of it, the most you can hope for is you start seeing the flower,
man. Exactly. Yeah. Like, that's best case. That's like the nice guy version of the hat,
man. Yeah. For Benadryl. Well, it's because it's aromatic. Yeah, it's aromatic. It's a
guy. He's not a flower. He just smells like one. Oh, really? Oh, wow. He's not a flower.
He just smells like one. He's a normal guy who smells like a flower. Oh, okay. Does perfume
usually smell like a flower? No. What the fuck does perfume smell like? Perfume is different
kind of things. What the hell is esters? It's a chemical compound that they use in crossword
clues. Nope. It's a woman. That's if you have an H in it. What the hell? Sorry, guys. I'm
I'm on a different letter mode today.
You are on a different letter mode.
You're boxing the letters, man.
David Letter Mode.
Damn.
I saw him tell a joke earlier today.
What was it?
So get this, guys.
He's interviewing Mike.
Get this.
Drew Barrymore is stupid.
Well, that.
But he's also in an interview with Michael Jordan, the greatest basketball player of all
time.
And Michael Jordan has the pair of Jordans that he's not allowed to play with on court,
the black and red ones.
and he says, Dave Letterman says, "Why aren't you allowed to play with these?"
And he's holding it, and Michael Jordan says, "Because there's no white on it."
And Letterman goes, "Well, there's not any in the NBA either," and then throws the
shoe away.
That's right.
He was so mad about there being no white guys in the NBA that he threw the Michael Jordan
shoe.
Does he know that there are white guys in the NBA?
Luca Doncis.
Brian Scalabrine.
Brian Scalabrine used to be.
Zaza Pachulia.
Zaza Pachulia used to be white.
Yeah.
yeah, dude, he used to be wise to be white. We don't know what happened
turned to a different whole because I mean a joke like that. I can stomach,
but a factual inaccuracy is always tough on me. I mean this was this was in the
era of Larry Bird, Larry Bird, the greatest basketball player of all country
Reeves. Yeah,
have you ever heard the stories about Larry Bird? Yeah, where he was like he's
like punching people in the nuts and we just say like spitting on people like
the fucking guys wives to like fuck you be better at that yeah and he looks like
that yeah and he was just like the biggest shit talker of all time. He
was tell people like straight up, I'm going to kill you yeah and then he would
win did yeah. So bad power kind of dope over your world,
fucking they use pictures of Larry Bird for click bait all the time and there is
one that I saw yeah, there always is as with his face and it's like what the
fuck is wrong with him. Well, I saw one that was like Larry Bird's disgusting
wife
like yeah, it's crazy that he as he gets older, looks more and more like a bird.
It is crazy. He looks like a nose never stops growing, which is bad. Bad nose
news for me man. I got a big, big pointy nose
guys. I feel like we I feel like we held that face. I feel like we glossed over
that track. That track was fire. Sorry. We talked about it made me. It made me
want to smoke up. I don't want to spark. It made me want to spark that show dude.
literally did you know one of the first verse made me want to roll up a blunt
fatter than a chipotle burrito road. Did you not listen to the first verse? I
honestly went right over my head. You didn't I didn't understand a word that
was being said in the first verse. It was to hip hop. It was way to rap. It's
like when your mom says that you can't understand a rap song and yeah, Kanye
West, yeah, yeah, just makes a wild guess about who is yeah, it's the sugar
hill gang. Yeah, it was it was a mate. I will say did because obviously we
the lab don't know it was amazing to see your process as a writer. Yeah, I
spent two hours on the beat and about two minutes
about two minutes. Yeah, but the beat was fire. The beat was fire. I do the
same thing that I do. I do the same thing that I do every single time. I
find I look up the oldest song in my library and then not the oldest, but I
look up old songs in the library. I go by date and then for some reason I keep
picking Scott Walker songs and then I just pick one part of that song and
that's it. That's all you need to do.
Isn't Scott Walker like a governor or something?
Bro, Scott Walker and the Walker brothers were like the Beatles for England,
but they were American.
The Beatles were English.
They were the American Beatles.
They were the American Beatles that went over there.
That's Leonard Skinner.
The Walker brothers went there while the Beatles went to the States.
Do you think they crossed by each other on the...
They probably flew it.
over the streams. Yeah, probably if they would. Yes, that's no, I know. I think that is. That's
what would happen. Yeah, yeah, they cross the streams and then we ended up with fucking
Katy Perry, man. Yeah, or Nicki Minaj, I guess the perfect combination of English and American.
That's true. Why did she start pretending to be British? She pretended to have multiple
personality disorder. She thinks that shit and she ripped that shit off from Tyler, the
creator. Yeah, yeah. She had what was it Romans revenge and she had a personality
named Roman who is the most evil rapper of all time.
Oh Slim Shady vibes. Yeah and then she had a different one that was like this
is my pop persona. I wish it was more acceptable to have a Slim Shady. Yeah
what is it with what is it with hip-hop and rap that makes everybody their
personality split? Dude it's because you fucking get in the booth you spaz out.
You change. You become a different person altogether. Yeah master of disguise style.
so I mean it happens. It's having all three of us at this come another
person, not become another. Yeah, now keep go. Let's keep going. Another
person do into the account, go to the accent that he does another person
become another person, become another person
is getting like one percent to far
getting in big trouble, getting in a lot of trouble. Yeah, there is something
about rap that just you go into that booth man and you become where
pistachio disguise. He would be the best rapper of all time. He oh my God, they
have a rap at the end yeah. They had a song who's can you look that up right
now? Who the man who sings the master of disguise at the end of that movie,
because there's a song at the end. That's like he's the master master of
disguise and they used to have. They used to have a rap at the end of every
movie that was
explaining the master disguise, happen credit song. Every movie used to have a
rap. It had a rap at the end that explained the whole thing. Deep blue sea.
Yep, this is always do will spend his family. Oh boy, the stripe pajamas,
M A S T E R. That's what it was
by Byron. We need to bring that shit back. That's our new, that's the, that's
the next, the next album. The next album is
every movie that's coming out that yeah, a credit song for yeah, that's a great
idea. The the bitch yeah, the hard heads M A S T E R. That's the name of that
song. Don't hear much from the hard heads now.
Yeah, I wanna know what what songs the hard heads have done. I think that we
need to make
a movie that's maybe thirty seconds long and then yeah, and then
an hour and a half credits. Yeah, just because we gotta get it. I mean you
to be inspired if you're making music. Yeah. Yeah. So we need a story first. We need to
have a little bit. I guess we could just make the song actually. Yeah, make the song and
then work backwards. There needs to be more storytelling songs like you did with OJ last
week. Yeah. You know, like you need to have, we need to do one that is like, but you know
what I want them to bring back man? The 70s, the 80s, the 60s. What length were these songs?
11 minutes? Boogie Me and Rhapsody, Free Bird. These are some long ass songs. Stairway to
Now that now it is the only people who do long songs or stinky homeless stoner
rockers. Exactly dude. I don't want this 60 hour song called like flirt. Yeah,
I listen to flirt. Well, that's pretty good.
No,
if in the new dune movie that planet where they do all the throat singing, if
if there were guys who got shoved in lockers on that planet,
they would be making that music.
They'd pop out making music right after that.
There's a van around here that has the Dope Smoker vinyl cover on the window.
It's so sick.
I think that they are part of the screen printing company.
I see that shit all the time.
The Dope Smoker album cover is so tight.
Yeah, it is sick.
I don't like that name, man.
if you'd like this album cover, it would remind you of maybe a caravan of a
guitar player. If you're going to make a music, already an album called the
from who man, Mr Rock and Roll, that guy doesn't fucking
guitar player by Mr. Yeah, he plays a birthday song. Yeah, I remember that
that's a good one, but I think that needs to have been the first ever rock
and roll album. They need to be like they get that's yeah. Let's look at the
history of rock and roll. The first rock and roll album was called the guitar
player by Mr. Rock and there was always a song. Everything about there was always
a song like that, and if the let's twist by old Shelby checker, then he did let's
twist again, but then there was like rock around the clock. Yeah, rock and roll
something around the genre anymore. There's no song. There's no song that's
called like chill last beats to my mom in the crib. Yes, rapping at my house.
Yeah, yeah.
What's the new? I guess hyper pop is the new genre popping or demise it
Zit? Hyper popping my zit. Hyper oh, I thought you said hyper pop my zit. I thought you were
saying that my zit was a genre of music. No, no, no. That could be though. Yeah, zit music.
You never know with these kids. Have you guys heard of this? It's just that sound. You know
what is the worst music genre I've ever heard in my life that you showed me the other day?
Funk or fonk. You don't like fonk? No, man. This is bad music. It is not good, but the
song that it sounds like that clown song. The song that is good is meet yo maker by
Tommy Wright. No that's a good song. Can't be good man. You've never heard meet yo
maker? What is it? How does it go? I don't think I'm gonna like that shit. I don't
think I'm gonna like that shit. No you would love that song. I don't actually
like that song. It's actually some kind of it's actually DJ Paul. I like the
that Brazilian genre that I don't know the name of that everyone always posts a
a video on Twitter. I've never listened to it outside of just a embedded. How
does it go? It's just always it's always these it's always Brazilian women just
shaking ass crazy and the song is like
what is that? I think I've called one.
It literally sounds insane. It sounds like something is breaking in the
computer. It's so funny because it's all the videos are just completely women
twerking. Yeah, it sounds like they for they accidentally shut off something.
yeah, yeah, exactly they sound. It sounds like they closed the program in the
middle, yeah, and the vocals are always really quiet, like it's always a guy in
they turn a base and he's like
they turn the base of way to
I really have been getting into Mariachi recently. Wow Mariachi is in a bond.
It's bond. I've been I've been poisoned against bond because they play it loudly
near my house and it's so good man. It's out. It sounds really happy and then you
read the lyrics and then they're in Spanish, but then you translate the
lyrics and they're like who's this guy peso pluma. Oh, he's awesome. He's good. I
like that all the lyrics are all they're like but then you read the lyrics and
it's like my mom died. My brother died. My entire family died. My dog died by
crash. My car. I went to jail. I fell in a canyon and I have what's the name of
that dude. There's a bond a singer. I think he was a bond. No, what is it? I
feel bonded to you guys. I don't know what it was over this planet ship. This
planet ship funny.
Julio, who's this guy, the cartel hands him a note while he's singing and they tell him
they're going to kill him at the end of the song.
Why would you give somebody...
What kind of fucking note is that?
Who is that?
Do you know who I'm talking about?
Who the fuck, why the fuck would you hand him a... just kill him.
Donino Sanchez?
He was killed.
Yeah, he was perfect.
There's a video of him, they give him the note while he's singing and then, dude, he
fucking, he goes off too.
he performs it's like a performance of a lifetime. He pops off. That's him looking at a note
that says he's about to be killed just now? Yep. That's why he's like crying. That is
an awful video. This is horrible. I don't want to watch this. No, dude, he goes off.
This is going to haunt me. You know what I would do, man? Wow, that is a beautiful voice.
He had an amazing voice. They're going to kill him if he starts singing. If he starts
what yeah as he
is going on.
There's no singing in this
the we're going to kill you. If you sing, go to a concert,
you will die. If you sing,
the other guys can play their instruments, but you just can't say did
you know what I'm doing up there? I'm going I'm humming. I'm going
I'm not singing. Yeah, I wouldn't start. I would start rapping dude, pull out
the fucking puppet. It ain't me man. I'm not saying it's peanut
and they killed him. They did they kill him on the spot. No, they did it like
later. Oh yeah, he's fully dead. Why this guy like you know that I don't think
that he like is singing so much tomorrow. Sing tomorrow man. Yeah, go to
the next town.
It's not that serious yeah. Oh, you know what? I probably what maybe his
girlfriend was in the crowd. Oh, his crush, his crusher, his mom or do I
mean I just how can you be like threatened to be killed? He also he
thought about it for like seven.
I'll just fucking say I'm going to kill you. He's like he's like I should I
yes
well yeah.
These people paid four dollars to be in this bar. I have to fucking sing yeah.
that's crazy that the amount of time that he's yeah thinking about it. Fuck it,
fuck it. I guess my life's not that good yeah yeah. I guess I'm just a famous
singer. It's actually not that good to think about how awesome this will look
on Wikipedia yeah. This YouTube video about to be popping off man yeah he
knew about YouTube yeah when they invent video essays yeah. Oh God, that is an
awful story, but again kind of fully his fault. Yeah, wait Julio is that this is
Is that the true correct story? They said if you sing right now, we will shoot you.
He wasn't there, Matt. I hope so.
He was there. He shot him. Well, he said it. Wait, unknown assailants killed him.
Shot by unidentified assailants, so it could have been you.
Could have been Julio. Just go to the Wikipedia page. Just pull up the Wikipedia page.
Wait a minute. Jalino Sanchez. Did you do this, Julio?
I think it's possible. Now, scroll to the... just scroll to where he was killed.
he was killed. He was attacked by Eduardo Galagos while performing at the Plaza
Los Arcos Restaurant and Nightclub. Sanchez was shot twice near his armpit,
striking his lung, ensuring ensuing a gunfight. Don't shoot my bro in the
armpit, man. No, don't ever get shot in the armpit. That's fucking stinky. Yeah,
it's stinky, but that's where a big artery is. You're about to unleash a
stink bomb on the entire-- Can you please just go to the heading murder?
What I want to see, I want to learn about this.
under the Coachella incident. Whoa, he was handed a note from someone in the
crowd. The note is believed to have been a death threat, but has not been
confirmed. Okay, and that shows him crumpling up the note before singing the
song after midnight, while that he drove away from the club after midnight. So
there's there's a problem man. You got to leave early at midnight. That's when
crime comes out and they gave him a fake police ID and said we're we're we're
coppers. Yeah, and yep
shot in the back of the head twice. That's a bad way to go. Actually, it's
that's the best way to go now I think about it. Yeah, but you know what it's
probably a really bad way to go. If you got handed a note that said, yeah,
we're going to do this. I'm going to shoot you in the back of the head twice
if you sing. Yeah, I don't think that that's what the
I don't think that's what the note said. Well, I believe, yeah, I believe it
too. If you want to see me sing a Donda song or what's it called bond bonda
song come to the yard theater and Los Angeles, California on the 17th guys.
I'm going to be doing all sorts of songs, karaoke vibes at this stand up show. Me
and my buddy Gus Fivera come through two shows. We made it y'all halfway halfway
through the five weeks of planets five weeks. We're halfway through the third
week, 2.5 weeks down to point. We got something special for Saturday. So tune
in man. Yeah, something very exciting for Uranus or should I say Uranus Uranus?
Isn't it funny that the way they found out to make it not funny still sounds
like urine? Yeah, you're in us. Yeah, sounds like p.
You're in us group of a bunch of scientists trying to be like how can we
get people to stop laughing? No, you're a good way to say it now. You
shouldn't have named it that motherfucker run well
and tape around
and I need it that with the you say hey guess what scientists you shouldn't
have named it as shit motherfucker. You fucking idiot
- What's up, scientist? - What the fuck is up, bitch?
- What the fuck is up, scientist motherfucker? - I love him.
- Alright, bye my friends. - Bye bye.
The Joy of Jupiter, a planet report.
Jupiter is by far the largest planet in our solar system.
That is, if you don't count planet Lizzo.
One year on Jupiter is the equivalent of almost 12 years on Earth
or roughly the time it takes my girlfriend to get ready to go out.
(laughs)
Oh damn.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Jupiter is named after the Roman king of the gods because yeah, somehow gods weren't powerful enough. We need a god that's also a king.
I was waiting for the clap at the end of the paragraph.
There are 95 confirmed moons orbiting Jupiter. Don't let Buzz Aldrin find that out or he'll kill himself.
[Laughter]
Let's talk about Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto.
And no, those aren't the names of Angelina Jolie's children.
[laughter]
Those are the four Galilean moons of Jupiter, more massive than the others.
They were discovered in 1610 by Galileo Galilei,
who takes his name from the famous dinner gibberish scene from Billy Madison.
[laughter]
Europa, the Galilean moon second closest to Jupiter,
may have a water ocean underneath its surface,
which means it could conceivably be home to extraterrestrial life.
"Wow, how exciting!" said nobody ever.
It's often been said, and this is the conclusion.
This is where I get kind of real.
It's often been said that girls go to college to get more knowledge
and boys go to Jupiter to get more stupider.
But with modern science, we know the truth.
It's actually girls that go to Jupiter to get more stupider
and boys go to the planet report to get more handsome and smart.
[Applause]
(T-Rex Roar)