(upbeat music)
- Okay, welcome everybody.
I have something so exciting that I'm gonna do directly,
immediately at the top.
I'm cause to snipe everyone who leaves the video
before the end of it.
World's biggest army is going on tour guys.
It's a sketch comedy show that is going on tour
with live performances and videos and so much more.
and it's me and Caleb and Patrick and the lovely guys from home planet who are
our guests today and also our good friend Pierce Campion and rise Trent and
we are going to rise Trent. I don't know who that is. I like that one. We are
going to a few cities guys that I should have pulled up on my phone before. No, I
know all of them because they're going to Boston on zoomed in on the
on March.
we're going to be at the Rockwell Theater in Somerville in Boston.
Somerville, kid. Chicago on April second at Shoebus. Shoebus. Day after April
Fools. I love that place. We are doing our first international show ever in
Toronto on April twelfth at the Garrison. We'll be back in Atlanta April
twenty seventh at the Earl and then Philadelphia on May eighteenth at
Philomoka. You can get your tickets at swagpoop.com/shows, but if you're a
crazy type person who's listening to this right when it comes out, the tickets
be up until noon. So if you're going to complain about it, complain to Alex.
Alex Forrest.
He will handle all complaints about tickets.
Uh-huh. I'll take care of it.
And related issues.
I'll do it so good.
So imagine, if you went to our first live shows, right? Now imagine that with six guys
and it's not anything like our first live shows and it's sketch comedy.
It's somewhat like it.
I would say it's not anything like it.
It's not any, imagine it's a show.
We're new now, we'll enjoy it. I think Patrick's trying to get you not to come.
I think imagine it's like the second half of our live shows that we did.
Basically that don't imagine that just imagine a fun time out with your
friends. You're going to go with your no, I think that it's kind of similar
as a new video out to which is on Instagram and YouTube and everywhere.
So go and you know, if your city's not on that list, just get a better
city, get a better city. Keep your ear to the ground, especially in La La.
Fuck you.
La is not happening.
We're never going to go.
it's too scary. Unless you're a venue that wants to fly us out or something
pay for us. I think is obsessed with the idea that somehow a venue in La is
going to fly us out to do a show. I think they're going to fly us out like
a like we are instagram models and they are a prince in Dubai. If this episode
goes viral, it could it has a pretty good chance. It could go viral. We
should make an La only episode. Yeah, only releases in an hour. It's an hour.
It's an hour of us just going to
one. We had a lot of that's way too close beach episode. I think I think we did a
beach episode.
I don't know if we did a
think that you're. I think that you're stealing from our past catalog beach. We
did. I don't think we'd a beach episode. You recorded on the beach. No, we did an
episode about the beach. When did we do an episode about the beach? We definitely
did an episode about the beach. If we haven't done an episode about the beach,
Lord strike me down right now as I stand.
Wow he's asking for it doesn't work when you're indoors man. God can't see
God. God can make this. You can't see you can only see you if you're walking
around outside like Google map. God can make the wall behind me fall forward or
make maybe no didn't get electrocuted could have got electrocuted. He wouldn't
make the wall behind you fall forward because it would kill me and Alex and
Joe. Yeah, beautiful God fearing yeah, we didn't noted that's why the capital
building the it looks like that because it's to protect because they're doing
evil stuff inside and so it's to stop God pricks his finger when he tries to
reach
there inside. God looks down at the Capitol building and he thinks it's a
giant boob. Yeah, and he gets a
it stabs him and then he
jacks off with his blood. And the devil, I don't know what else to tell you. The
devil celebrates. So many state buildings in this country are
pointy like that because the Washington Memorial. God boobie. Yeah, that's a
dick and that's well that one's also very pointy. He could maybe stab his
entire hand on that and you know they do all types of evil stuff inside there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, all the politicians get together
dance around. They have their dance parties inside. Inside there's like a
hundred floors that two people can fit on.
They're all playing beer pong against each other. That's where beer pong was
invented. Actually, it's in DC in the Washington. Be careful with that.
we have a toy on the desk today. I brought a toy over with me and I brought
the shades. I just like to have my hands on things yeah. I feel that times yeah.
I get that you yeah, we know man
yeah, yeah,
we should have got him a fidget cube or something, because I know he's going to
be messing about and need a cube. Yeah, he needs a cube. Well guys, what the
hell is up? What's the gossip? What's the tea? What is the deal with you guys
tomorrow. Clancy gets his my dog gets his first brother heart.
My brother dog gets his first heartworm shot. Well, they have to they have to
stab him through his back into his heart. Whoa! Super long needle and that's what
you guys are here to plug. Yeah, well, don't do the whole thing. We'll say
all right, all right, all right, all right, they stab him with a knife to
like open him up. Yeah, it's really brutal. It's like to see what's inside
the Nick. They're just doing like experimental. What's the Nick? That's
Clive Owen. Oh, and Harry Potter? No. Isn't Harry Potter on that? No, no,
you're thinking of like Frankenstein's assistant or something. You're thinking
of Harry Potter. I'm thinking of Daniel Radcliffe. Daniel Radcliffe and John
Ham were in a weird show on BBC. Oh, okay. Which I only saw posters for.
But then Clive Owen was on Showtime. Yeah, it was on one of those premium
shows. I've never seen it. It's really good. I've never seen it either. It's
you see it either. All the medicine and they like to like fuck. I use long
need.
How do you going to do when you show up to you? I'll go like this to the vet
with Clancy and it's a guy from dead space. Yeah, so one with he has a long
ass needle and he's wearing like he doesn't know dead space. We don't know
the Nick can imagine dead. That's the best. This is the
divide in the table. It's like a scary
spider and a dead space spider enemy. This is going to be the vet. When you
the vet. Oh dear, the vet is a big spider.
Well, who knows an animal better than a spider? That's true yeah. I would know
oh and even more so who know the inside of an animal's body better than a
spider. A spider could have been the thing that gave him heartworm in the
first place. Yeah, really imagine you come home heartworms, old mosquitoes do
so. I assume it's a type of spider, kind of kind of web, spidery type of thing.
Imagine you came home one day and you just saw clancy on the wall and a big
spider web.
like
I would be very I'd be scared, but
I would take a picture first. I'd be pretty cute. He was I should have had an
enemy of the worm. The worm is it would have been too easy for him to be
because he could have just webbed him up yeah about all next issue
put him in a web man. Why did you just swear around? I do like how like it
Spiderman's just lacking right now. Just web him up, come on, swing towards them
and then wipe him. I thought the new Spiderman movie was so stupid because
he should have just webbed up. I probably yeah could have literally
been five minutes long. He would I green goblet. If I was through a portal web
yeah, if I were Spiderman, I would have webbed up Zendaya right away.
It was so good, got a lot of Zendaya. It is funny that I would have webbed
Zendaya and the friend, every single one of Spiderman's like villains.
If they are impervious to web, the only thing that that makes them impervious to
webs is being bigger than him.
Why rhino and that's the only one I can think of right now. Here's a man,
here's a funny little turn into sand, turn big turn to water. What about the
little kid? Here's a funny thing, a little kid, a little kid, his arch
nemesis.
You guys didn't read those issues. Yeah, so I read all the old Spider Man
comics and something funny is that Spider Man's like main one of his main
attacks. He does on every single villain, every single issue as he shoots webs
into their eyes and they go
no
and then there's at one point it's probably like you know, like sixty
issues in so like five years into spider man's run and doctor octopus is
like he's fighting doctor octopus and he shoots web at his eyes and it is like
any no doctor. Octopus has those glasses yeah and the web falls off the glasses
and doctor. Whoa! I invented glasses that can't be way
like bro and vent a whole suit yeah, yeah, the glasses it took you years.
you'd think a scientist would be like up on that right away. Isn't he a doctor?
Yeah, he's a he's a mad. Oh yeah, you think he's a doctor crazy. He's a doctor.
He's not a scientist. Developing tentacles. He's a doctor who does a
mass. I
know he's a doctor, because those are those are prosthetics. You can be a
doctor of he's a he's a pediatrician. Yeah,
it's a lot of that's why his enemy is spider man, because spider man's a kid.
He's a teenager. Yeah, he had strep throat and you went to the pediatrician
and then he's trying to get some areas on May at the beginning of the comic
really
spider man step uncle really
duck on
dock on
on
how are you on
you can't be calling your uncle that you can't be
If you're watching or listening, that's the new challenge. Call your uncle cock.
Yeah, recorded on video.
See what his reaction is and send it to him.
It's a new Jimmy Kimmel, like I stole your Halloween gift.
Cock.
Hey, cock.
Hey.
What the fuck did you just call me?
Oh, come on. Is this the new cock challenge?
Oh, come on.
Is this going on Jimmy Kimmel?
Hi, Jimmy. Hi.
like a guy who the uncle start reacting like the kids who got their Halloween
to
you have anything to say to Jimmy Kim. Oh no,
no, no, Jimmy Kimmel, Jimmy Kimmel told me to call you that
it's going to go viral. I'm telling you that we Jimmy Kimmel challenge. Take
your uncle cigarettes,
threw cigarettes. I threw all your smokes
just
got those for me. I like cigarettes. I got those on Halloween,
and then you're like not as Guillermo told me to and then yeah. What is up
with Guillermo these days? I don't even know what he's just doing red carpet
stuff right. He's chilling. He's sold out. Yeah, he's sold out.
He's still there. Yeah.
How do you know? Because Gus. Oh yeah. Guillermo really liked Gus. Yeah, yeah.
little inside industry secret. It's cool. If you know, I don't think you can
be old and you know Gus. Whoa, damn flow. Yeah. If you know us and you know Gus,
then we're gonna get Guillermo on the bus
and would go and get a get on the set of rust and stop the gun. Gonna have some
fun
that so that what I just did there was called lyrical storytelling,
kind of create a world. How are you guys here in a stop the old when yeah let's
all the way rust. Let's your take on more like but Baldwin, but when, but
when I'm in a place where a kind of
I kind of think Alec Baldwin can do no wrong for me. I for good. I gave him
yeah months and months. He's too good. I gave him the day after he did it. Yeah,
so good. I forgave him before he did it. As soon as it came out, I was on his
side. I didn't even need to know what did she do? She probably yelled at
yeah, not knowing it was an accident.
He was filming him. He probably was shy. He probably thought he was shooting. He
was on going to be on Jimmy Kimmel because of it was a challenge. Don't
shoot.
I mean I'm happy for him. You know, keep doing your thing boy. He's like ten
he's
you see all the footage that like the they leaked or whatever the footage of
him on set like before it happened now where it's like it's like footage.
They're like we think this footage was leaked by the defense, because it's all
footage of him on set and he's just go like he's going up to different actors
and he's he's literally like going up to people that he's working with and being
like like I just want to make sure that on this movie set, nobody ever gets
hurt
and like someone trips and falls,
he's like, "Oh my God, are you okay?
"The last thing I would ever want on a movie set
"is for someone to be injured.
"No, we need to end this shoot now.
"If you're tired, we need to stop
"so you don't exhaust yourself and get injured."
There's a bunch of videos of him just doing that
on set, and then the next day he killed somebody.
(laughing)
- Crazy.
- It was premeditated. - So karmically insane.
- Dude, it was premeditated.
- He went back, he got a time machine,
went back in time, and he didn't fix the gun
'cause he wanted to kill that lady.
why hasn't that been explored yet that time travel might be involved.
I like every every crime ever that should be the if I was an attorney,
do we not consider at least okay, we've been through like two or three
possible explanations. We heard the suspect talky. I mean he's convincing.
I believe he may not have done it, so now might be the time to think about a
time machine. I just want to rule out time travel at the beginning, and then
I can move for your honor. Look at that necklace. Doesn't it look suspiciously
like the time Turner from Harry Potter? This could be time travel. That's that
could work. If the person was wearing the time Turner, if they were wearing the
time Turner or they could be like look at that necklace. It looks like it's
from the past. Oh yeah, this looks as the sixteen hundreds necklace. There's no
other owes this man is a not the time. Yeah, and I think he's a not see and
then you kind of flip the yeah. If I start, if I start killing people, I'm
put scarab beetle charms on them and be like there's no way this
person
to court in like old victorian clothing.
I have no idea how I've become gotten here. I'm not from this time. You like
say that and then no one reacts and then you just like pull out your phone
or whatever. I'm actually from the future.
I start dressing like Victoria's again. I am an android. It comes back in style.
It that could come back and it is check out the lighting, check out the lining
and it's just got like another phone
made of phones. Yeah, I think made of phones is going to be the I can't
fucking wait. But in Tron like Tron, yeah, the clothing made of phones and
Tron is made out of electric made of lights. Well, those are not clothing,
but that's computer. If you think about it, phones are just lights. I mean this
shirt kind of looks like an app a little
how
yeah, no, like you click the different ones. I can click it. This is kind of
like three colors. It's kind of like a game. You can play a runner.
You need to play an app so bad.
Sorry, I'm just playing your shirt.
yeah your shirt has. I can't get past the first level of your shirt. This is a
really hard when the shirt when the shirt unlocks or when I unlocked level
to the shirts going to come off
and then nipple nipple play. I feel like your outfit is thought would be fun to
play to play yeah. The Vietnam veterans reunion
is much
level one
I'm just kidding. Have they made a game yet that's kind of like one of those
artistically styled games where it's
mostly about like Pokemon three, like one of
those games that's mostly just about depression and
and living your life day to day, making breakfast and such that's about a
veteran and it's and they could call it call of duty. The aftermath. Well,
haven't they done that with its excellence? Wait a second that could
literally be and yes, I'm sure they actually have done yeah, but this could
actually be an incredible addition to the call of duty franchise where they
could have a whole other side of it and it will appeal to girls. The boys like
the war, the girls like the emotions and it'll or it could be like a game where
it's like based on the it's all the call of duty characters like ghost and all
the other ones that I don't know the names of so McTavish wives and homes and
their homes and there it's a savvy game. I was going to say and I have to like
find a date. Yeah,
date while their husband is gone yeah and then the husband, the husband,
every once in a while and it's like a video of him. He's like Hey, honey,
like
bombs and gunfire in the back yeah, that would be really cool and then you
could download like dlc's for like the different like dating, yeah
and then you kind of have like dating infused video games. Okay, you're you
are you are one of these wives. Okay, describe your perfect man
seven feet tall black as hell
can eat non stop,
but it doesn't bloat physically doesn't put on any weight skinny yeah very
skinny. Oh wow! Seven feet tall, skinny, real thin, black and
yeah so frozen. Oh God, I just described my dad
and paging Dr Freud.
seven
seven feet
over the opposite. I'm going for like I'd say like four foot six kind of
mutton shops, super lots of body hair all over braided beard as well. Orange
orange facial hair, oh yeah, black hair on head
helmet with one of those cross guards that comes down over the nose chain
male battle acts. It sounds like you're describing what's the the from Zelda. I
was describing Gimley.
I would say mine and
mine. I would say probably like one inch tall. I would say they're sour.
They're sweet. They're gone. I would say you're just a you're describing a
child yeah
your perfect man is a child. I just say what
I really miss my husband.
I just need it's so you're kind of willing to submit to the darker side of
desire. Yeah,
I just want a sour patch in my life man. Well, you can
grown on it's one thing. If your husband comes home from war and you've
been fucking some guy that lives across the street, we'll see this. He comes
home and he's mad in one way. He's kind of just he's mad because you're
cheating. He's mad about the disloyalty, but you can get you can kind of just
skip the whole romance angle of it. If you cheat on your husband with a kid,
he's going to send you to jail. He's not going to care much. I don't know this is
this is how I see it playing out. He's not going to feel so a masculine. I
thought you were going to say that he's going to be even angrier because he's
coming home catching you fucking a celebrity like the our patch. Have you
seen the sour patch commercials? It's he's going to come home. The sour patch
kid is going to be on top of me or whatever, like a terrible sour thing and
he's going to say, Oh my God, you for my gosh and then the sour patch kid is
going to give him like a
sour than their than their sweet and then we eat them. We eat them together
his husband's home and it doesn't matter. I want to eat him the sour patch yeah
and then he eats your okay perfect man as a military wife go.
My perfect man would be definitely
seven feet tall, black as hell. It's Alex's dad.
I kind of all this before boring yeah
- No, that's cool.
You and my dad would be a really cute couple, actually.
(laughing)
- I don't think I've ever met your dad.
We've lived together for three years.
I don't think I've ever met your parents.
- They've only visited once,
but they came when you were asleep in the apartment,
and we had that fake gun in our old apartment
for a really long time. - RIP, it's broken.
- And it looks real.
Yeah, it was broken, but it looks real.
and my parents both came in and my dad like saw the gun
and like got like really nervous.
And I was like, no, no, it's a toy, it's fake.
And then he's like,
I'm just really uncomfortable with that being out.
Like, please put that away.
And then I was just being silly
and I like picked up the gun and like pointed it at my dad.
And he was like, stop, stop, please stop.
- And he's never visited you since.
- And he never came back.
He had a really bad time that trip.
He was also trying to like park the car.
We were going out to brunch and me and my mom, my sister
like went into the restaurant to eat and my sister like left, I think like her
phone in the car and so then like she went back to the car and my dad saw her
and I guess he like didn't know it was my sister, so he like ran away from her.
And he like, he like, you know, he's on edge. He is, yeah, he's got a lot going
on. He ran away from your sister. Yeah, he like hid, he ran around and like hid
on the other side of the car and they haven't been back yeah. I've met Alex's
dad like fifteen times yeah, they're very cool man yeah brag about fucking care. I
literally don't even want to meet him and I've met Patrick's parents a lot and
I've never met your parents well not going to happen. That's true. We went to
a restaurant with my parents once. I think your parents are here like every
week. Yeah, my parents come up here a lot. I don't know why supportive family,
yeah, a real strong family union yeah yeah you need
the doron yet
yeah. I think it's very funny that people in our parents generation, the
way that the people who aren't from New York, so Joe you can sit this one out,
but everyone has everyone had kind of I feel like a lot of a lot of people from
our parents generation and my parents, maybe not so much, but a little bit
definitely have the kind of like eighties New York. Oh, it on the
absolutely so fucking funny. It is it's insane. They literally think they'll be
like sitting in a restaurant that is like you know it's a brunch restaurant
with like like leaves and grass on the walls and like an eighteen dollar one
egg over easy on the menu and they'll think they're in a wasteland. Yeah,
just oh my God, yeah, it's crazy. Yeah, that made sense. When you watch the
news. My mom will just watch like whatever local news thing and she's like
be careful on the like they're pushing people into the tracks on the always
fine. So it has been crazy lately, though I saw a lady gets slapped in the
case. Okay, there was a serial slapper running up and down this train and
there was like I guess like because like we were trying to get like get this
lady off the train. She was a serial slapper did she was going up and down
slapping people and everyone is just kind of like moving in front of she was
only slapping other women. So I was just like getting in front of women on the
train to be like get stop it, get out of here. It was on Friday when we left the
play. What were you doing? I was like standing in front of this lady.
You got slapped. I was trying to slap the woman.
Well, no, this dude, this dude, this dude
pulled up.
But this dude, this dude kicked her off the train.
physically like he like stood up like he was like stood up like now this is my
chance. I'd like was like I'm going to be a hero and went and just kick this
woman in the chest off of the train.
Always the scariest shit when people they have that they get the vigilante
yeah when they see something going down that's like a that's iffy. But instead
of like do instead of doing what you should do, which is be a cartoon. Hey,
knock it off. Yeah. Why are you on?
Yeah, no, he jumped up and then just like kicked her off the train and then
ever like it just like got super quiet because and he's just standing there
like damn bro thought like he thought that he thought that everyone was going
to look at him like he was a hero and it's like dude, you just like kicked a
woman, but I thought he was the weirder. I would have got in his face. This is
what I would have said yeah. Hey buddy, you think you're tough,
picking a woman like that. I'd like to see you kick me. You're kicking a woman
who's going around slapping people in the face. Go ahead, kick me and then I
stand like this.
please protect me, protect me from this cake
no that's good, because I kick my butt
my butt and you just see like shit like
getting bigger.
Go ahead, my but
while I'm sitting
your blow over
Oh,
more of the so yeah, I learned I learned that she was a serial slapper
because there's two women on the train who were on FaceTime with their friend
who were just going yeah. This lady's slapping bitches. It's crazy.
It's just like
not helping at all. How many people did you see her slap? I didn't see. I
just saw her get off the train and just slap the lady and then like me and
like this other dude like stood in front. We're just like stop stop and
and like the one dude jumped up and just kicked her in the chest. It was so
fucking weird.
That's crazy yeah kicker.
I can do it again. Check your pants on that one man.
That was a full wait
shitting your
my shit.
Okay, now
I heard it still sounded like a part again to me. I know that's why I made
those like
all that reaction. A good invention would be a shoe that sounds like a fart,
so you can so you can always far you can hide your no, no, no, look it was
my shoe yeah and then it for you have a first or you can just play it
on your phone parts, but I was playing it. I was needed to have I was
playing it on my phone yeah, now listen, it sounds exactly like that one. You
record all your farts beforehand. It's like the sleep app that records your
we use your a yeah you're sleeping it. It's a little watch style thing that you
put on your butt cheek and it records your it detects and records when
there's the volumes. You know it detects the transient of the fart. It stores in
a memory, so I was like Oh my God, did you just fart and you say no is my
pants, my pants make these weird noise. What you kind of tug on your pants and
it'll play it if you're talking and it's
it's called tugboat dot a I that's a great name for it funny tugboat, a I
tugboat dot a I know I didn't know it's my pants. I didn't fart. It was my
pants
my
my pants. I can do it as many times as you need and you're just pulling the
pants. Yeah,
I can't like the Todd Margaret ringtone. Oh, that's so funny and he keeps having
a fart. Yeah, I'm on a big Todd Margaret me to today. I've also been on it. I
I was I was showing my girlfriend the deaf signing thing. I'm crazy. Yeah, I've never
I still haven't seen season three, but doesn't he nuke North Korea or something
it's a little season two is spoiler Korea one, but that right guys are talking TV.
My TV nerd brain talking TV is to go over this, which you guys have a new movie.
Yeah, don't talk about the movie yet because I have a good segue that includes
a movie for the well, then speaking of well, we're like wait, wait, can we not
movies. No, speaking of movies, charge of it, it's my thing. I made it. I know
how long it is, but so back the fuck off mister or I'm going to kick you in the
chest like I just learned as possible and thus the villain was born.
See real life is like a comic book. Sometimes you have yellow yellow man
yellow mister swole. You said he said real life is like a comic book and you
said yep
no you're wearing you're wearing a lot of yellow to a lot. You're wearing
almost exclusively, barely any just a little, just a little, just throw on
some yellow. I call you, I
just throw on some yellow. I felt yellow today.
Yellow is a is a happy color. I call you Mr Lemonade. It's the color of
cowardice. I can't wear yellow too big too big yeah. You're too big to wear
you or yellow. I just want they go a big one. So when I was a kid, I was at
I was wearing a god as I was at a yellow shirt and I was at like a street fair
thing and there's a drown the cloud, you can't alone and he went you you big
banana
so
yeah I was a little kid. Well, you know I will and that clown probably so Neil
yeah and he's dead now and Joe killed him. Oh my kill put him. I
diabetes. You can wear a type of yellow that doesn't look like a banana. Yeah, I
don't think anyone's going to call me banana. No, but they could call you
lemonade. Lemonade's fine. You darken that shit up. They could call you lemon
lemon zest mustard. Yeah, lemon zest. I call mustard lemon zest. It's a good
colonel mustard colonel mustard. Damn, I would love to be a colonel one day.
I'd love to be if I can follow my dreams. I do love mustard me too. I like spicy
mustard. I like different types of mustard as well. I like
mustard mustard, yellow, brown, pink. Oh my God, I love mustard.
Mustard.
So gravely, it's crazy.
different kinds of monster. I'm imagining hearing this voice, hearing
this voice saying you getting this, you had a call. I was gonna say I
wouldn't know when you pull up to the
getting
my scenarios. You imagine being a ketchup lover and yeah, getting that
mustard.
My scenario is you pull up to the McDonald's, you pull up to the
McDonald's drive through, you say, Hey, yeah, can I get
burger and I'll get some ketchup on it and you know it all gets a
mustard to
the speaker on the
yeah yeah. Okay, you want a big you want a big Mac yeah muster and some must
muster
this is the this is the cashier who's yeah. I can to you through the speaker
and I'm actually pretty funny. I guess I'm playing the guy in the restaurant.
Okay, cool you so just get ready for your big your big moment because it's
coming. Okay, but it was very funny for that to happen for
for someone for you. Pull out you pull up to the to the drive through and
you're saying like yeah. I want a burger and then say oh yeah. I bet you do want
over girl and you pull it they're like okay next one. Don't you pull up and
it's just the guy you just there
very cheap, but you're like sorry about that
the wind
forgot about trying to prank you. I forgot how the word got about this part
of it. I'm new here. I forgot you were going to see me. It's my first day on
the job yeah, he's like
he ducks down really quick and then he throws the bag in the car like a
grenade
restaurant is like
and then the guy in the restaurant is like
this is so much better than the McDonald's in the paris.
It's all about
developing a
yeah. You learn a lot about that guy in that one line yeah, it's kind of
everything you need to know. I wish my daughter was a food fan. Oh, that's
good. I wish my daughter was here. I wish my friend. It's been five long
years and then the daughters in France cut to the daughter in France to the
diner and she's going for
I don't see my father anymore because he moved and he hasn't been here in five
years. So you think you think that he's talking. You think that he's lost his
daughter, but no she just her dad moved and he can't get back in. That's good.
that's he's stuck in McDonald's, but he does like it yeah. It's like terminal.
He likes it better than the one in Paris. We know a lot about him. That's
why he went like terminal, but McDonald's yeah and get this and he
just doesn't
a mountain doors. You say you can communicate more information by the
character. Even beyond the lines you hear those lines. You think oh, I know
okay for one is French. I know he's at McDonald's. I know he's enjoying his
food and he's enjoying it more than the food in Paris and get this. Then you
you hear the line, you open your eyes, you see he's wearing a police officer. Oh
my God,
he's a police officer, he's a police officer story telling and he's
environmental. He's living in the McDonald's and the McDonald's manager
like in terminal. They keep opening the doors and being like just walk out the
front door. All you need to do just walk out the front door and he refuses yeah
too good and he's he's wearing a sandwich board that says I'm a fan of
books. What's a sandwich board? Oh double side yeah world is nine. I'm a
fan of books and then the back side says, but I'm also a liar.
That's actually great because it establishes he not only is he not a fan
of books or if is he could be one. You think he is trustworthy yeah,
I'm a I will narrate it. There you go had been narrating the story. These are
all things that are perfect in a script to France. His daughter's nowhere to be
found. She doesn't she doesn't last cut. She is a memory. She moved out of the
frame. What you and then he takes that as well. He takes out his wallet. He
hope he pulls out his ID Indiana. Well, his name is Indiana Jones. His name is
Indiana Jones name is yes. First name is Indiana. He's from Ecuador
Ecuador. I that's not funny.
Chill on that chill on that we got a lot of Ecuadorian listen that we already
saw where she was saying that she doesn't see her dad anymore and then
she's still saying this stuff and then suddenly you hear cut. Okay, that was
terrible. Let's try it again with a different accent. She doesn't even
isn't even related to the last part. She's in a different movie in a
different movie yeah about a girl with a father. Yes,
oh my God,
a great movie, but then one day she goes to McDonald's
that's in Perry in America and
yeah
question mark on this is perfect movie writing. That's the next okay. This
actually is a is a beautiful Segway now. Well, you guys have a movie coming out.
so yeah big time yeah on Friday, February, so it's February second. It's
going up at midnight. So if you stay up late Friday night or Thursday night,
Thursday night, they night into Friday, Friday morning, it's going to go up the
witching hour. We're trying to do big numbers on the weekend planet YouTube.
So get you run that up and do big numbers, youtube.com slash and here's an
Easter egg. So here's an Easter egg for all you real home planet fans out there.
actually two or two Easter eggs. There's get there. First one is you may
remember my character from a different home planet video
really senso. Oh, oh yeah, okay, kind of a similar voice.
Patrick texted me about it. I
okay, I like job about it and Joe said that I can claim that yeah, I can claim
that's going on IMDB. Lots of lots of returning home planet people favorites.
the of the classic the back of the head back of Cameron's head is that a
camera tag in Easter egg? Oh, if you can, if you can, if you can find the
first person to find where Cameron's head is and put up a screenshot with
hashtag, I found Cameron, hashtag junior associate free lunch, send you a free
McDonald's. Yeah, that's fantastic. How will that? How are you going to send
that to them? Uber eats bitch will have will have the account will reach out to
the figure. We'll get their info. We'll send them a dollar for a sandwich. Okay,
yeah great, but February second one dollar every second.
Check it out. It's very you guys. You guys are film makers and if there's one
thing I know about film makers, they're always hard at work on the next on the
next project. So I've prepared a little presentation here for us where I found
some movie ideas from this blog that I found.
So hopefully the maybe these will give you some inspirations for your next
movie and maybe you can. We can discuss some of these and maybe you can end up
confusing one. If you even want to that's interesting, so this is a blog
post I found from I don't remember the name of the blog. It's just a random
blog. It's from the twenty ninth of February on twenty twelve, so it's from
a leap day. That's interesting, scary, and this is
this is a post that says I need movie ideas and then all the text is in
rainbow colors and it says anyone have any movie ideas. I haven't been making
movies in a while and I and like I'm short of money. My friend is suggesting
making a rude movie, but I don't like the idea of being reported for making
unsuitable movies. How about I get a animation of like being a ghost and I
could make a scary movie is the animation VIP. I don't think it is I'll
check it out. My ideas scary friendship make a random movie mail me your
thoughts by and this is from rose one three three one, and this is from the
director. Can we figure out where one three three one two is it goes positive
this is a child Joe yeah Joe. What the hell are you? I'm trying to get you on
today. Oh my God,
what was this posted on a blog spot blog spot? I think that's a road press.
Maybe that's a Rwanda
okay
cool. So here's the first movie idea that was posted.
This says my English, my English English, which is bad. I'm German, maybe
the girl and her BFF are falling in love, both in the same boy from the BFF are
now not BFFs more. They argue and makes strach. I don't know the word in
English
race on of the girls landing in the hospital and they are BFFs again. Sorry
for my English. I think strike
maybe that's straight. That's the character's fighting. That's the
character's name. I would believe it means fighting. They make they argue and
they are you and make and then that's like a response from my missus money
penny says that's an awesome idea. So what do you guys think about this idea?
I mean so girl and her best friend forever are falling in love with the
same boy, both with in the same in the same boy from the boy best friend
forever are now not oh so they're not best friends anymore. They argue and
they fight. They make fight, they makes fight
and then the girl lands in the hospital, and then their best friends again. It
mean strike. I mean go on strike, so they go on strike. So it's like a union
movie yeah right. It's like blue collar Jimmy Hoffa, how to blow up a pipeline
and the boy they're falling in love with. It's like the same because it's is the
president of the union yeah and they're sharing it because it's sharing the
wealth. So there's actually a lot of subtext going on okay.
This is why I'm always glad to have film analysts. Yeah, I cast well and really
get to the deeper. The thing that's really striking to me is that this
comment was made a year after the post went up and then this was like five
months later. Yeah there's been all through time. This post has lived on for
a long period of time. You can if you can find this post comment your ideas.
What would you name this movie?
I would name it stretch. I think stretch makes the strike. It's strike a strike.
Strike. I like strike. I would call it right if it was called strike. I would
it was an X men thing yeah yeah as of strike. I mean it could be all we could
all
X men. I've it's really be on board if it's road
rogue, I lock I was thinking store, Rogan, Cylock yeah, Rogan storm. Are
they friends? Are they BFFs Patrick? They I don't think they're BFFs, but I
know they interact who's rogues BFF rogues BFF
or gambit has to be female in the movies. Yeah, her boyfriend is gambit in
the car, so maybe rogues or the cartoons, but it's ice man, ice man, BFF is
probably, I mean just going off of the animated series, it's probably Jubilee or
somebody, oh right, or maybe it's
in loop. I think I know it's loop. That's numb, yeah, yeah, this is an elephant and
an animal, yeah, that's loop a rogue and loop a and they both love wolverine. That
seems like and strikers. This is a perfect, this is how we bring back the
MCU yeah yeah Indy Indy emotional character, Mogan's Kang you don't even
you don't wait. What are we going to guys?
What are we going to do about Kang? They should make a whole movie that's
about Kang the search for me
into a white guy.
It's like the
yeah, he gets like someone kidnaps him and injects him with like glowing like
purple like
chemical and he starts turning white.
I've seen of a mutating into a little white guy into Liam Schreiber yeah be
awesome. They wouldn't use him because he's already Saber to and then all the
and then all the the MCU, the Avengers are like okay now he's really evil yeah,
because he's white, he's white man. Now he's a white verse guy. Wasn't he
purple in the movie
purple? I think of Thanos actually didn't see him in any. I didn't see any
of the things I had to stop watching those. I don't think he's purple, though
I've been watching the I lived with them baby. I watch the X men. They are
here's the here's the next the next reply. I put up here and this one I
might share privately, but believe it's better than the strain and several
others that I okay. What's the strain? The strain was a show on FX and this
idea is a secret idea that is not shared, but it's better than the strain
better than the strain. Oh, they don't I see okay. So this is yeah, this is
a separate country. I hate all the this gate keeping in a hollywood this next
idea. I think this one is going to be perfect for you guys for the next home
planet short film great next one. It says okay, here is my option, the runaway
well a story about a little girl about six to seven called Danny. Her father
tried to kill her mother, but her mother managed to run away, so her father had
to look after her. He tried hunting the mother down, but never managed to find
her. Then one day, when Danny had grew up into a teenager, fifteen, her father
started abusing her and she couldn't take it anymore. She knew her father
cared for her, but he just kept up the abuse and soon she got sick of it. She
and her father had a row and he aimed at her physically hurting her.
She threw her in the cellar and went out to calm down.
Now Danny was mad.
She tried opening the staircase out, but he had locked it from the other side.
So she tried the window.
She had managed to get her hand through, but not her body.
Then she realized she had her mobile in her pocket.
So she clambers and pulls it out and dials 911.
When they answered the phone, her dad was already home and coming closer
to the cellar, Danny started worrying and screamed down the phone.
Help me.
The police were now asking her questions.
She quickly told the address and straight.
She managed to put her phone away before her father got to her.
He opened the cellar door and shouted her to come out.
so she did then she then heard police cars pulling up. Her father was
staring at her this at this point. He started screaming at her and telling
her to make them go away, but she refused the police were soon or
were soon knocking on the door and asking for it to be answered.
Her father went to the door and three minutes later was taken to prison and
Danny was free. Two years later, Danny had found her mother and had her
husband and two children. They were rich and her father was given seven
years.
I hate when they give the plot away the whole movie in the log line. I know in
these trailers, I know this on the tag line on the poster.
So do you guys think this is a good fit for for home planet for yeah? Do you
think that you and the runaway you guys could do this? Yeah, I'm thinking Neil
Lenski is Danny yeah
Patrick Doran as the father. Totally
I reject the role. I'm busy. I think one of the best parts of this idea is that
the the police and knocking on the door and they were also asking for it to be
yeah. Can this please be answered
please
be answered already,
but there's deep themes in this about daughterhood yeah. It also feels like
running away. We're missing a lot. There's a lot of stuff to fill in. You
know we can really learn a lot about what is that
what's happened. You just do I was trying to skirt it like a
squeeze the water into your face.
that's classic
like what's happening in these two years right and also like what does the
basement look like? What color is the door? How many police officers are
there and how many are asking please? Hey man, please right is it one with a
carpet yeah and or is it just one that's bare or bare stone floor with a
rowing machine? A finished basement reads a lot. Is there a rowing machine
could be a wrong machine for her to erg in those years? She's in the cellar.
is there is there a treadmill there's so much there's so much time to that's not
filled in like, for example, what happens in the three minutes between the dad
being at home and being in prison yeah yeah that that could be a spin off
called the three men. It's the three minutes. That's the world's fastest
court case that can be the Pixar
yeah seven years in prison, but only seven years. There's something
interesting about it being a like a beautiful finished basement and it's
like how long do you have to be trapped in a finished basement, which is like
the best place you could be yeah for it to become your own with a mini fridge
stocked with food, exact fridge food oven down there as well a tv and like
some games, maybe a freezer that has all the frozen food from Costco,
futon. I love it. We could even maybe go a step further and create like a cgi
world of the basement. Oh, it's a terabithia yeah, where she's a wonderland
Tim Burton style world exact and that can kind of be where like the real meat
of the movie is yeah she's coming up with all these different things that like
this, like this
couch cushion is cash, but also this stuff is it's real. It's really
happening right is a magic couch cushion. Yes, yeah, it's you think that
it's bridge to terabithia and she's creating a magical world just because
her father tried to kill her mother who escaped and then tried to yell at her,
but actually they're the plot twist at the end. It's all revealed as magic like
at the end of father, the end of labyrinth, the police come take her dad
away and they're like how did you survive in that basement? You must have had to
create an imaginary world or something and she's like yeah. I guess I did that
over her shoulder. Does that happen to the couch couch? Kill she
what's up your bested cops because the couch is got a cigar hanging out of his
mouth. I'm
pushing and in the pillows and I learned how to roll my own cigars down in his
basement.
It's a good idea yeah, and then the pillow can sing yeah song. Maybe when
you're a couch, you're a couch, everybody sits on you. Nobody listens to a couch
cushion
that's fire. That's pretty good. I like that okay, here's the next here's the
next post on here. These ideas are fine, but way too long and complicated. Also
all of the drug slash abuse phrases will he and then a bunch of pound signs out
people won't watch long movies over about one minute. How about doing a family
series as they always get lots of views? You could do a royal family, poor family,
celebrity family, chav family. It's I like chav family. What if one child is a
breakaway and it's completely different to the rest message me if you use this?
I love the idea of a chav family where one child is a breakaway yeah posh child
of a chav family, the prince, the prince, the little prince, the little print
called the little prince. Yeah, the little prince. I don't want to be a chav. Yeah, yeah.
You gotta fucking smoke a cigarette right now. No, I'd rather sit on a pillow. You better
not sit in a fucking pillow. And then it could kind of be like a game of thrones, sort of
like family power struggle. And there can be a war that the prince can start. And then
the mom starts to become a little bit more posh. And the husband is like, you hanging
hanging out with your fucking son again yeah.
I told you to never see him again. I told you not to fucking talk down in
room. Don't you dare to you don't see him. You don't even fucking talk to him
about posh living. We're chavs. We've always been chavs. I'll say it is
getting what to be posh.
It's giving you never be push. It's giving Kingsman vibes really and he wears
posh in that I thought he's a chav. He starts wearing suits and that I think
makes him kind of doesn't want to be posh, though he'd want he's kind of like
a chav agent. He still wears a flat brim. See I try to not really think about the
Brits too much in general, so I'm not super sure on the you know the meanings
of all the chav and posh and stuff. I just have seen Kingsman. We will take it
a step further. What what was Kingsman too afraid to do? We will do it
kill an actor for real kill an actor. We will kill an actor
the one thing
the actor is actually kill kill this man
and you'd get a lot of a lot of buzz for that. You would get a huge a lot of
buzz. Bring it back certainly articles. I don't want you to see because the crow
already did it. The crow didn't did they market it like that? No, the crow yeah,
but that was their
marketing ploy Emerson alum yeah, Brandon Lee, really yeah, well,
Yeah, I think he was my professor wonder. I've always felt so connected to him. I
saw his ghost at Emerson campus. Really yeah, that's crazy. Where'd you see
just like
he was making a sand. He looks so different.
He's standing next to that statue. It's like you see like like for like at the
end of return to the Jedi. It's like Norman Lear, Brandon Lee. They're all
sitting at the end of the cafeteria, watching you eat lunch like yeah.
here's something yeah every movie, also every movie where someone gets when an
actor gets killed making the movie, the actor is never here's the other way we
differ from the crow. The actor is never killed
during the last well and if they are it's anyway they're never killed during
the the very final scene to the very last thing they shoot and the final scene
of the movie, and if they do it's because they stop making the movie after
the person dies, but we need to set it up so that we film everything for the
entire movie, there's only the last scene left and then that's when the
actor is killed and then it's and it's like turning a perfect bow and if we do
exactly if we do right, it can be like like a two minute movie right
to go home early.
This first says nobody will watch a movie that's over a minute long, but
exactly because everybody you see these movies where people get died, making
them killed. I have to keep going and well it's always like you're watching
the movie and it's always like you know, like thirty minutes and you're like oh
that's the scene where somebody died. It's like this is too early in the you
have to save that yeah, because then it's also like you know the CGI scenes
are mixed in. They've got the body doubles. They've got whatever you know
what I mean. Have you seen the Imaginarium of Dr Parnassus? No, that's
he ledgers last movie. Yeah, he ledger died and then they gave they just like
made it a part of the movie that like he his character looks like three
different guys for the rest of it. Don Cheetle Terrence Howard
hands, though yeah. The classic one is the is the
the plan nine from outer space where oh yeah, Bella, go see died and they just
have the guy who yeah just do it. The top half of his face looks a little bit
like Bella. Let go see that's a way that's that's. We need to bring that
spirit back, so we kill him in the first minute and then the second minute. We
fill in a different guy to be that guy yeah. That's a good idea. We killed two
actors for this minute one. We kill the first one. We killed it's called the
man character. I was thinking the man, the character who kills the actor within
one minute. That's the name of the movie. I was thinking if you want to go
sleek, you go the man who died twice. It's like it's like
that's beautiful, but check this out. It's a role that's like the joker. We
say it's a role a thousand times more deadly than the joker. Oh, my God,
everyone who plays this role goes crazy and kills themselves within one minute
of playing the role and there's there's ninety different people playing the
the character in the movie, because every minute that they play the role, they
can't take it anymore. They slit their throat on cam. So I think we make we
make the two minute version. We get it on the festival circuit. We get funding
for the feature yeah and then it's ninety minutes and it's ninety actors
yeah. Exactly that was your he only dies ninety times. He only dies ninety times.
What was the joke that we were doing like a while ago? That's like the star
wars movie that's called ten thousand Jedi
it's like the first movie to have like yeah, the
the most Jedi
movie
episode eleven eleven
yeah, yeah, that's the rest of the star. You've never seen
the poster ten thousand. The poster is the thing where they do where that's
like the like like shoulders up of all the different actors faces, but there's
ten
you can't see anyone's face. It looks like dots ten thousand Jedi to Sith. Oh
my God, there's come off. That's that should be the sequel. Come off suck off
on to
to
say come off it come off it. No, they're going to they're going to have a come
off. They're going to have a come off yeah ten thousand Jedi and to Sith come
yourself. Here's the next post. This is this is this is a this is a in one
here's the next one
number one. I'd like to see a movie about the Dallas Ewings as teenagers to
or the like to see it's a cast of a soap opera. Okay, two I'd like to see
an all black cast of song of the south with antagonist as northern middle
class family head and wife from sapelo island three. So much of remakes
Salem's lot for our time for would love to see a movie showing native
americans involvement in the slave trade and the different aspects of not
coming slavery to end fighting for the Confederacy, falling in love and
marrying slave children of all slaves, becoming chiefs and slaves and natives
fighting as the federal government have more ideas. We'll stop here. We'll
waiting for Hamilton to come to the big screen
and then there's one reply to this this post that just says this is the only
reply that says you commented on my B day.
Wow, I love all those. These ideas are crazy. That's sick. A lot remake, not
that bad of an idea directed by the Feige brothers or the Russo
brother
they're revealed. That's that's the only way they're going to get people to come
back to this. We got another. We need a gentleman. We got another one. The
Marvel keynote where it's just like a
a guy wearing a little
smash bros challenge, a new challenge
Devin Feige
because of ways yeah up y'all all right here's another idea. So maybe there is
dekta of girl. Her partner is a guy they get on to this big case in New York,
making so many friends along the way and falling in love, but then she finds out
her partner is to killer really isn't it. What still loves him, but he really
isn't the killer. She thinks he is, but she finds out that he is, but he is, but
she finds out she finds out, but he isn't. I would say this is this is not
too dissimilar from a lot of ideas that I have yeah. This is the most home planet
one so far yeah. What about this one? This seems very home planet to me.
Here's this one. Hmm make it something about a popular girl being transformed
into a wear girl. Then she kills people because they don't believe her. Then
she goes to prison for a week, then she breaks out and that's the end of the
season season. There's a TV show idea. I like that we can do that is
disqualified yeah movie idea. I like someone who goes to prison for a week
and then breaks out and then it's over.
Here's another here's. This is a request omg guys. I need help asap. I need a
horror, scary movie idea. There should be dad abusing mean girls, changing
appearance, being a singer and falling in love with her boy BFF or the mean boy
that helped her later on this feels like it's just combining every single idea
with all of these. Can you combine this one in this one in this one in this one
BFFs girls changing appearance,
appearance, appearance, being a dad of you, we got plenty of data, bees,
there's a lot of data abusing being a singer is not so much, but that can be
call it. No, I think that's the focal point of the movie. Now that you get
Billy Eilish in the movie, introduce us,
introduce in her first acting role, I would literally kill to be the director
who gets that credit on my, my God, producing Billy credit. That would be
so much my legacy, Billy Eilish as same man who brought Billy to the silver
screen. That's what they call
ooh, Billy Eilish and Sean William Scott. That's not bad as the abusive dad. I
I'm thinking he's more like the movie is called Stifler's kid. It's called to
do
American American Dad, American Pie presents, Stifler's kids, Stifler's
kid, American Dad, American Dad, American
American Dad, American Dad, American Dad. Here's this next one is basically
everything that's wrong with Hollywood. Unknown says try remaking a movie in
modern times. No, thank you. How about a new idea?
Here's a new idea. I have an idea it's very bad, so bear with me everyone in
the school is thanks for spoiling everyone in the school is put into
categories. So you're either smart popular, childish jock, the grub dogs
musicians, the nice and the mean the main character. You can pick names is
the only one in her school who doesn't fit into any category and everyone
bullies her except for one guy who is secretly in love with her, but the guy
who likes her is one of the popular guys, so he can't be seen with a loser
like her. Plus his sister is her complete mortal enemy. Isn't that the
plot of high school musical? Yeah, but high school musical doesn't have the
grub dog. That's true yeah. I wait. I to go to a school with the click called the
grub dog. Patrick, you're a you're a skate boarder. I'm a grub dog. You're
a
someone who likes food. I think so. I think I'm a grub dog. You're definitely
a grub dog.
I'm the from the childish. I'm a child is click and Alex is the is the musician
cool yeah me and we can get me and tae digs as my friend
or and we play at the table.
you can be like your lunch table is a be a grant be you know yeah you're lying on
top of it eating your french fries
five hundred twenty five thousand a musician could never be friends with a
grub dog.
Hey eat this
oh you're the group yeah. I want to yeah it's about a musician and a grub dog
overcoming their differences to make a movie together and it's meta they're
making the movie. Whoa yeah you're watching and then the back road dogs,
you can pick names. A dog is also finding her way in the background to you can
pick names is her name. We're not going to change that it's too good. Her first
name is you can this you can pick names. The post person who posted this is
Lizzie. That's kind of a fun name for a girl in a movie.
This is why you get paid to make movies. I can see that I can see an executive
producer for Hollywood. Yeah Lizzie
and Max Lizzy Max Sally. Well
reading getting a screenplay across a dressing room and be like it's it's
kind of good, but I'm just looking for movies right now where the main
character's name is Lizzie. Yeah, you get it. You get like a script put in
front of you and it's like a period piece and it's got like names from like
the sixteen hundreds or so right. It's like can you change that character
Ezekiel? Can you change that chair characters named a Max? Yeah, this one's
I think audiences are really looking for girls and max yeah. Tevin should change
Jebediah Harlan
to see a Harlan is a young Harlan. Let's get Harlan back in the modern age.
Harlan Williams, so guys,
Harlan Williams at he would be a good scary dad. I discovered that these movie
ideas are not for Hollywood movies. Guys, these are for movies from an app that
exists that is called Movie Star Planet,
so this is a very exciting app Movie Star Planet next slide. Please it's so
you can see it's kind of a social network.
It's pretty fun to use. This is my profile.
This is my profile here. That's me on the left. It says looking to direct my
first big picture, and this is my journal page. You can do it on my
profile. So I am Cameron favorite animal is the mink. I really like the clothing
that comes from the mink hobbies, writer, director, favorite subject film. My
favorite foods is crudite. I just really, really like crudite. Favorite movie
stars wells orson wells to be exact. Favorite movie, the works of antonioni
for the tv show. I personally prefer the silver screen and the best book would
have to be the portrait of a lady by henry james wow and I made my avatar
there look like me. They didn't have a mustache option. If you could just cute,
you should wear clothes like that. You'd look cool.
This is what I mean. It looks exactly like me. This is my avatar.
So this is movie star planet and actually you know, I know you guys are
kind of the filmmakers here, but I tooled around for a minute and I'm just
with such successful, you know, direct a director and writer actor here, right.
I just want you guys to take a look at something I wrote and directed and
maybe just give me some critiques or analyze it. So I'd like to present to
you guys. My first short film it's called the war directed by Cameron Fetter. So
just go to the next slide here and we can watch the war.
So
just let me know what you think. Oh shit!
Oh,
all right,
I'll read this war is bitter and brutal and seems to rage on forever more.
(laughing)
- Will I ever fall in love?
- Wow.
- The war is over.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
(laughing)
Thank you for watching this film.
Directed and written by upcoming
creative Cameron E.
The end.
You should have you should have
filmed your voiceover.
I should have filmed it, but that's
not where I really have a part of
it. So I just wanted to kind of give
the this.
They don't have that in the app.
Those so good.
You're going with like dogma 95
type rules where it's like you can
only use things.
I just want to showcase the app and
this is my creative vision.
So I was kind of just only reading it
for the audio listeners.
I would say two things really stood out to me. The first one was how the little
table keeps
yeah. I am a huge fan of the works of Lynch. Yeah, I try to throw in some real
elements like definitely moving and a light that looks like a skateboard,
lynching for sure, yeah, definitely, and then I like her running on top of you.
There's a special touch. I just liked how that app gave you the tools to
express your creativity. It feels like that easy to make a movie. It feels like
that app was built to make those little one second things of someone lying down
like someone running on top of feels like that's the right. It's just like you
don't need to like get a fifty million dollar budget like you guys to make
something yeah. You can just run out there, download movie star planet, make
your profile, say your favorite things and you don't have to be a nepo baby.
You can be an app baby to yeah on guys. I really wanted to cast all of us in
that movie, but unfortunately they do not let you make custom characters and
so it had to be a mermaid really stood out. She was good. She was great, an
incredible performance. She was like what was it like to work with mermaid
now. I guess I shouldn't kiss and tell
a little. Oh my God, TMZ
don't me no TNC's no. I'm joking.
Is that on the MZ?
Well, why don't you guys plug your movie again?
Go watch junior associate on home planet Youtube. It's the biggest thing
you've ever made. Yeah, it's very fun and silly and crazy and I think it was a
premier video up of it. There's a premier yeah, right here. Look at that
premieres in two days at twelve a.m. Anyway, click that arrow so we can see
all the faces. That's a hotel room that we shot in pretty. That's pretty. We
yeah, we
great guys. Do we have any more pieces of trivia that you guys can say? I got I
ate. It was like my birthday was the first day that we started shooting it.
so you can kind of tell in a couple of the scenes. I have served like a
birthday glow, yeah, as well in a smile and I'm holding a present in a lot of
the
because I was and I open it, but Mr. Director made me wait, but I heard that
they had to. I heard that you were kind of at the same time as this. You were
also shooting another movie called the birthday and they had to see GI out your
smile and a lot of the things for yeah.
What we really did was we just had to take the mouth and then flip it the
other way. So it was like a frown. He's up yeah. Spoiler alert, a bit of an
upsetting one. He frowns. There's some frowning going on. There's a lot of
from
and I was go by tickets to our sketch shows on swag group dot com slash shows.
You're going to love those. Please. It's going to be so much fun and we want to
see you there and also we have the day that this comes out tomorrow is our play
thing Q and a oh yeah, the Q and a job the play after job. The play the play
was good. I saw it and I
I like to play after job, the play.
So go buy tickets for that. I don't know where you do that, but I think you
okay, look at it. I'll see it on our
on
twenty four. We are doing a Q and a after the play job. We went and saw it
last Friday. Was it good? So good. Yeah, there I don't know why they asked us
to do this. Yes, it's going to be interesting. It's going to be definitely
the most interesting thing we have ever done. Ask Peter Friedman about safe. I
looked up Peter Friedman's pant leg. Yep, we were he's also in the stage. He's
also in
what's the cause that the savages what's the one with Laura Linney don't know
Peter Friedman. Well guys go subscribe to the a tree on a level to get some
there's some not get out of the park, credible performance. They're so good.
It's such a good if you don't see us on it, go see it yourself, share, share
junior associate let's get it viral subscribe to patron go check out home
planet on all social media aspects of a take out this and what is this and what
are we looking at? Oh something went wrong something went wrong. Whatever it
was got to read it and also go job go on. What is it the la chargers posted a
video of Caleb? Oh my God, where did this video go? No way that can't be
really. They deleted it. Oh my God, so
you can save it or screen record. There's no way you can get it a cashed version
of it, whatever someone will have it. The L. A. Chargers put Caleb crazy wow
you're a thing damn. I think they found out what that video was.
That makes sense all right, someone was probably like hey, happy week.
I love you bye.
He's trying to serpentine his way out in case there's gunfire.
Look at his arms! He's holding his hands in front of him like he's doing a dance.
My favorite part is here at the end, you can see his head go back and forth as he wobbles out of the hallway.
His head has a foot between each side where he wobbles his head.
He's walking like a South Park character.
At what point does he...
Okay, when he gets off stage and he's walking away and he does that walk...
Full sprint.
Yeah, at what point is he just walk like a normal person?
How long?
Do you think that's his normal walk?
That's his normal walk?
No, he does that when people are looking.
When he gets back onto the street, he walks like a normal person, I'm sure of it.
He's not waddling around, he doesn't waddle in the subway.
Okay, you be Mark Norman.
We need a practice here.
You be Mark Norman.
Mark Norman is coming on the podcast.
I want to show you how I would drill Mark Norman and get the truth out of him.
You're about to spew the bullshit, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So first I'll be like, "Oh, hey Mark, nice to see you."
Oh, what are you gonna call this podcast about math?
Yeah, we actually...
It's close.
Thanks for doing the show, man.
Yeah, what's going on around here?
Well, in New York...
It's just a video podcast.
Yeah.
You should call it "Podcast About Fish."
There's a fish on the wall.
Comedy.
We do like comedy, buddy.
Yeah.
What are you gonna call this podcast about water, huh?
Well...
Because they got a water bottle here.
It's an empty water bottle, Mark.
I just went to a comedy show the other night and I was like...
Oh, comedy.
It went really...
a comedy show the other night and I was like, what comedy? It went really. It
was kind of like everyone was bombing and there was really awkward. So I was
wondering, like, what's the craziest show you've done recently? Oh, well, the
craziest show I've done recently is a
wait, where are you going? Mark?
Watch this now. Stay now. Sit down, Mark.
Sit down, Mark. Now I'm gonna show you. I'm gonna show you my method. This is
I would break his spirit.
OK.
So, Mark, what happened at that one show?
Tell us.
I'm not Mark. I'm Kevin Hart.
Oh, hello, Kevin.
Hey, Kevin, did you hear about Mark Norman's?
What do you think?
Kevin Hart, we wear a dress for us, please.
No, no, no.
That is the funniest shit ever.
(Funky music)