(techno music)
- Cheers my friends.
- Technology week, cheers to technology week.
- Cheers to a thousand years more
of this technological war.
Thank you for being here, my two friends.
- This is what I eat and drink.
- Thank you for being a trend.
- A trending topic.
- A trending topic, a friendly mop that's got to--
- Speaks in cop--
bucket friend and cop what a friendly mop that's got a bucket friend. The mop is
glopping and slopping in the future across the floor. You know what's amazing?
I just realised the other day, probably in ten years, no fucking janitors.
It's all just going to be robots. We don't have to ever have a janitor again.
I saw one of the Stop and Shop robo following around a guy at Stop and Shop,
and by Stop and Shop, I think I mean Market Basket. Nope, I'm thinking of
stop and shop and shop and shop. This was over the holidays. This is our it
chased a guy. Guy came in and it started walking right behind him. You didn't see
a robot chasing man. It you it was literally this man a slug. He was
walking and then he turned around and he he got really scared. There's a robot
on the robots chasing him because he's leaving a that's why you know they have
those cleaning robots, but they're for security, but they try to make them
appear a little less. There's the eye. This robot, this is a way scarier than
not because it was that with the eyes, but it was also dressed as Santa Claus.
Oh you horrifying, so it had eyes and a beard right under its eyes.
Is our first the logical the next step is you had hair yeah. This is our first
episode back since Christmas break. Basically, our first one all together in
the stew. A lot of stuff happened without a lot of stuff without random parasites
jacking our style true. What's gone on random parasites jacking our talking
about e one? Oh yes, well do not basically trying to take over our first
premium so to hear take it over. They're begging us. Please can we do another
collab? I'm like I really don't want to actually kind of like riding so yeah. I
like riding solo with my two friends that were together are three. I like
riding
our triple tandem bike to get okay. Speaking of three friends,
here's a different amount of a different type of person. Okay, I went and saw the
iron claw and so did I let's talk about let's talk. Let's talk okay. So I didn't
see it. First of all, I'm going to give spoilers and but there's no spoiler
morning here. You don't turn it off if you don't because it's a real story, so
the real thing is what I feel. I feel the same now first here. I'm going to
first tell a story about my experience. Then I'll have a question. Okay, can you
during this movie? Everybody dies in the movie fucking everybody is Christ. I
don't know anything of the story. I don't know anything of the story. I could
look it up. Can you okay? Can you know I'm going to tell my story. You're never
going to see this movie. You're just interrupting a story for no reason. No,
no, no, I have a I have a suggestion. I want to see this movie very bad. Can you
Can you change that? What are you talking about? It looks really good. I
want to see it. I want to see it this week. I want to see it this week. So
can you do a movie in three years? Can you change the names,
change the name of the movie to a movie that I've seen? No, so that it's
not a spoiler and I think that this is a higher man.
Wow, okay, I've seen Iron Man. So in the scene in the movie, when Jeremy
Allen White kills himself, yes, near the end, yeah
everybody's everybody. I saw this at the night Hawk, which is a dine in a movie
theater where you get the food, you get a meal, a movie theater where you get
the food, you get the food, they bring the food to you, which I don't like
very much. It's so fucking expensive. It's crazy. We only went because we had
a gift card. It's insane anyway. This scene, this is probably the scene in the
movie. That's very sad. It's probably
my movie review, probably the scene in the movie. I'm doing a little movie
review along, along with this, but he kills himself. He
he kills himself and I literally the entire theater. I can hear everybody
around me. I can hear these people sniffling and cry. I can hear people
crying all around me like just genuinely crying. I hear baby type sniffles of
like yes of crying. I see the guy sitting in front of me. He has his head
in his hands. He's it's the saddest that I've ever seen a group of people in
public and I was thinking I was couldn't stop but smiling and chuckling
to myself because I could not think stop thinking about how funny it would be if
right at that moment the waiters brought me out a gigantic triple decker
the
it's one of the ones that explode
to pour the cheese on top
everyone
and it's somebody's
burger boy. Here's the birthday burger, burning Jesus going over my
special. They have a special for the birthday burger boy. It's
if it's your birthday, you get a triple decker hamburger that has came up. It
has a camembert cheese thing that explodes out. It made me really want to
pay attention to what point in the movie that happens and go back and try and
get that try and line that up. I get my or before that, so right when he's like
when the brothers carrying him in his arms, they're like
because the other thing about that theater is you can tell when somebody
there's food near you because you could smell it yeah. So they everyone be
crying and they would just start smelling it. Yeah, they're already
sniffling. They're already sniffling. I look over you have a burger that
this
you have a dagwood and you're going and I'm going oh yeah.
Here we go.
I'm so hungry. I haven't eaten since lunch.
I had an experience watching that sorry go ahead and finish your that's the end,
but I have a question for after you tell you experience. My experience was I went
the regal the regal downtown the Essex and they have the reclining chairs and I
would just like to say I'm somebody who goes into every movie theater and I
think that there's going to be an attack every single time these chairs
obliterate this fear and here's why sleep. I'm too comfortable to get out of
my chair, even if I was getting shot at a hundred percent every other movie
theater. I go into I think, oh, I could do a double back flip over that
staircase and I could probably save hundreds of lives by disarming the
person this I ain't doing shit. No, if they walk in and I'm in a recliner and
I'm thanksgiving full off popcorn, I'm dead yeah. My whole yeah, just pretend
I was trying to I get the same fear and I was trying to comfort myself at the
night Hawk being like well, nobody this place is so he's gonna go to the movie.
Nobody's gonna theater. Nobody's gonna go there and try and kill everybody, but
then I was saying like well, if you was your if you're about to kill everybody
and either get put into prison for life or kill yourself right after, would you
would you not spend all the money you have left on nachos?
That's true.
Would you not spend $100 on a movie ticket and then $500 more on food before you go out
in a blaze of glory?
I went there with Brandon one time and we bought a whole bottle of wine.
It's a crazy place.
It shouldn't exist.
I see people around me ordering multiple rounds of snacks.
They're literally spending $75 during a movie.
It's unbelievable.
It's morally wrong.
It's morally disgusting.
You think it's moral beer in a movie, but then you're spending $7 on a PBR.
It's insane.
I had a $16 Bud Light one.
sixteen dollar Bud Light when I saw it's crazy. It's so insane. That should be
you should be shot if your business sells Bud Light for sixteen dollars.
Well, that's kind of what we're getting at anyway. Oh my God. Right. Yeah,
these are the most likely spots for an attack. We should not question name the
theater by name then, because then there could be some James Holmes style crazy
out there that listens to us and thinks that that's a coded message. Right. Some
kind of a fan of you who decided to listen to me and Caleb just because we
from proximity to you yeah, but mostly here for Patrick yeah, just a thing
I'm the I'm the magnet for those properties and probably will. I'm the
crazy magnet through the crazy and probably not the Joe Biden song guy.
Those people are all reasonable. The electricists yeah, those are
that's true right that even scared me okay, but let me get let me ask my
question. I guess is mostly a question for Caleb who's who come on,
which one of us is which brother I don't know the movie, so I don't know if
it's because here's because here's what here's I have one that I want to throw
out there right away. Okay, Julio is the dad. Yeah, Julio is the dad. I agree
abusive, abusive,
trying to live vicariously through us. Exactly. He couldn't make it. He couldn't
make it. So, now he needs to see us make it. He needs to see us make it. Okay,
then which one is,
I guess, Pat is the biggest head? I think Pat is Jeremy Allen White. Oh,
that's sad. Well, I guess I kill myself. Okay, I was gonna say everybody kills
yourselves in this movie. I would say
Pat is the little skinny one who gets brain damage. Oh, Pat is the one who
just wants a career in music. Yeah, this is you. This is you just off of looks
the tall one yeah and then I'm a combination of the other two guys
basically. I think all the patches all the best a run. Also, I'm so stupid
that I would shoot myself in the heart instead of the head. Yeah,
that was so I was like that I was like wait. Well, you hear the gun shot to do
make up. You hear the gun shot and you see the blood dripping as he carries the
body and then he lays him down on table. Okay, I'm I'm rubbing my hands
together. Okay, I get to finally see this fucking loser from the bear, get
his head exploded and then God damn it. He shot himself in the heart crazy
Elliot Smith, bullshit, the most dramatic way to kill it.
Now that's the dad is so far with a sniper shot. Yeah, dad shot him with a
sniper. That's what I need to see. That's my theory. I need to see this
movie now. Here's fine man. It's okay, but here was my problem with the movie.
thing I told you guys this the end of the movie, I'm sure you agree is the end of
the movie is everything is has gone wrong in this guy's life. His entire
family, everyone he loves is dead and he has two sons and they're doing okay and
at the end he's he starts bawling crying, but then his son's cheer him up and
they play football. Could that not have just been him having like
a really nice time at a water park or he could have eaten an amazing one that
made me tear up. Why the why the fuck how does that it's still the saddest story
whatever this is not an uplifting. Why'd they even try yeah? I thought the part
where there's a fifth brother. There's another brother who killed himself to
they cut. He got cut as he's the saddest one where they're in the afterlife and
they and they see the one is a movie. Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I was I could not they travel to the afterlife. Oh yeah, they die. Well,
no, like the movie they go to head. There's a scene of them in heaven, not
heaven, but it's the afterlife and it's not they go to hell. It's not real. It's
even a movie. It's a movie scene,
but they meet their
and all the it's all made adult brothers, but they meet their their oldest
brother who died when he was a kid and he's still a little kid and there and
he's like you must be jack and they little kids is like yeah
the smiles. I don't want a little kid smile. It's so scary yeah yeah, no, I
just comically said to the point where I didn't even feel sad. I felt nothing.
I felt yeah. I mean nothing. The only thing that made me cry was when the guy
when he was looking at his kids playing football and he was thinking about
playing football with his brother. The only interesting are the the entire
movie. It was okay. This brother starts playing.
What do they do wrestling and he dies okay? Oh, this other brother's going to
start wrestling. Okay, well he'll probably kill himself badly multiple
times in the movie. It was that every fucking brother, Zac Efron would say
something like well looks like everything's perfect right now and then
would immediately cut to a brother.
Yeah, the brothers, they did that with every death was just that from being
like looks like things are finally looking up. I don't come to a phone
public. Your brother is the and by the way they're going to have to remake this
movie in twenty more years when the Zac Efron character also kills itself.
Here's something crazy. He's survived for now. Did you know in real life the
Zac Efron characters two sons? They also became pro wrestlers. Oh, no, that's
good. They're going to die to it's great. The whole family said pure death and
destruction. It's an actual curse. I'm convinced yeah, it's incredible. It made
me so wish that I had this kind of family
there's tons of brothers. I mean the thing is you don't have there's no you
don't have to become an interesting person or be good at anything. If you
have five brothers, you die, you still get a movie made about yeah yeah, even
if the even if the end of the world champion exactly, it wasn't that good.
No, he was the worst of the brothers yeah exactly and he still got a move
because he didn't go hard enough that every other brother, which is so hard in
their careers that they died. It's about if you're too big of a pussy, you see
everyone around you die and then you just have to have a son and here's yeah
here's your consolation. You have a beautiful family and not that beautiful
in real life. They really I'll say it guys. They really dolled up the family
for yeah for the movie. They dolled that's them dolled up yeah dude. Oh
Zac Efron, I said this to you guys. Also great actor looks insane, be in any
other movie except this one. No completely he well he's a good he's
doing good, but you can't see any emotion on his face. It's crazy. He's
like yeah. He has no humanity. He has a full Easter Island head become and guys
I'm segwaying here.
Yeah.
A cyborg.
[HUMMING]
Technology.
Julio, pull up that video.
Technologic.
Pull up that video, because that's the--
That's a perfect song.
Technology we play.
OK.
Wait, what's this?
This is the-- so it is technology we--
This is a perfect segway song.
Actually, would we get DMCA'd if we play this?
Nah.
This is the guy singing Ayo Technology.
He's not really singing.
Okay.
What does he say?
Technology.
He says technology at the chorus.
It's in the chorus.
We should have come to the chorus. We can just cut it now.
So this is, you know, traditionally on this show, we each make something.
Yeah, a PowerPoint, write something, report.
This is what I did because...
Painting, YouTube search technology.
I looked up AO technology. It's a good song.
I mean, it is a good song, but also really nothing for audio people or video people really either.
People who listen on the audio will get to, maybe they've never heard it before.
The song they've never heard a song before.
He's never heard it. You never heard that song.
What's who's it by 50 Cent Timbaland see 50 Cent Timbo.
See now we're opening Cameron up to this.
That's true. I mean I've been wanting to basically give him a hip hop education.
We've never I mean what is he listen to ABC by Jackson 5
Mark Kozilek ABC by Jackson 5
gotta be one of my favorite hip hop songs.
It's that and Wu-Tang.
the bars are a little bad in that
the bars, the bars, the bars, I think the bars are rhyming lyrical. They're just
not like hard type bar. They go hard there. I think the bars are dummy be be
careful. You said, oh my God, I got him to say beak bird
bird.
That was to
spills. Earlier we had a fully more of an explode. We it wasn't. We had what we
explosion. I could not believe it. We call this in sports an unforced error.
I was walking and just dropped my coffee for no reason at all. Nobody even didn't
trip on anything, just was holding the coffee and then just decided to let go.
You got hit with the limp ray. I think I do. I think that's my problem with
spilling, is that I have bad wrist posture. You need to get one of those
squeezers. No. Do this, do that workout. But then next time I'm choking my
shaking. I pull the thing. Oh, don't bring that it a little bit, but not
you don't have to squeeze it all the way. That's what I mean. I'm squeezing
it as hard as I can. I think once you get he's trying to make a play,
don't be able to not squeeze. Well, yeah, because I won't know my own
strength. Yeah, he's trying to make play snakes with his dong. Yeah, it
sounds like you're squeezing too hard in general. This you're supposed to
squeeze. I don't need to squeeze enough that you're worried that you don't
use. You don't have to squeeze to make it feel like a you don't need to
squeeze. You don't need to squeeze like I mean you know what squeeze what hand
make it feel like a woman's hand, a squeezer, a woman's squeeze, a squeezer.
It squeezes you
yeah. It's supposed to be a full squeeze experience. You don't need to squeeze
that much. You maybe need to squeeze a little depend. I guess if you know,
maybe your hand is bigger than or you could just be a freak of really, as I
am like I don't like that thing. I don't even curl my hand at all. You rub the
sides yeah. I get up there like I'm like well. I go around. I like this. I rub
horizontally. This is what I'm doing. Imagine this is my thing. You hit the top
of it? Uh-huh. Like kind of a cat batting at a fish's rod.
Ding! Yes. That's what I should be doing. Have you ever done that? I do this.
Where you have an erect, hard penis and the tip of it, for some reason, it hits
something and it feels like it gets pushed and maybe you lose an inch.
Speaking of getting hit, my girlfriend has-,
Whoa, whoa, chill, bro! No, no, no. My girlfriend has a black eye. Speaking of
getting hit my girlfriend has this thing on the toilet like what are the
cottony thing? It looks like looks like it matches the
what is the word is it doily is that the word for what? Wait it's doily on
the toilet. Do you have one of those things on the toilet seat? The fuzzy
toilet seat covers? That makes you, it gets nasty shit on it. It doesn't get
nasty shit does it? It does man. It's on the inside seat or the lid of the
seat? The lid. Oh okay. But the carpeted toilet seat is one of the most
psychotic. You never seen that? No. My mom's old boss had one in her house and
she had a water bed. Oh, nice lady's a freak. Yeah, she definitely... Water...
She wanted to fuck on the toilet. She wanted to get fucked on the toilet. Water
bed in her guest bedroom. Whoa, that is a swinger kind of thing. But the...
So she's got the doily on the lid, but now because of that,
the toilet doesn't stay like the lid will sometimes or the lid where you sit will
fall down and it I like near like Indiana Jones missed, I had to like dodge
it. I know it almost hit the tip of my dick so hard. I almost got it by my
toilet. I know the situation of trying to pee on a toilet seat that is about to
fall down. That's a scary, scary situation. You have to hold your, you
to shoot all your P back into yourself and because some public bathrooms are in
some houses where it's all women and they don't know about seats going up.
They don't understand that the seat has to stay up yeah yeah and it's just and
they can fall down and it's horrifying and I've tried to explain this to her. I
tried to explain this to her and she said no, I'm not getting rid of this
toilet seat doily. Why so you can sit on the top of this of the toilet. This is
where the hitting comes into play.
that you were talking about. She said, No, you I don't want to get the
hitting is on my penis. But if if we were to battle,
if you were to battle your girlfriend, you think you'd win if we were to
buddy, I'm getting gigantic and that's the other. That's the main thing I've
taken away from the Iron Claw movie is I've been doing the Iron Claw on my
fiance a lot. Yes, the Iron Claw. It's where you go like this.
And then she goes, Oh, no. And then you go like this. You hold her head.
grab a grab and it doesn't work so well. No, it doesn't make you bleed like it
doesn't the move. She asked you to do the dishes. You go to it's really funny
to just suddenly go like this and it just does nothing. No, she just that was
their move was yes, it's awesome and in real life you'd say what are you doing
man yeah, but in this they go
and he almost kills a player with it. He makes Rick Flair believe because he
iron claws. He does a real iron claw, not a wrestling iron. No, he does a real
going on Rick Flair's head. Yeah, I gotta see this movie. It's a great movie man,
and we saw in digital
technology, technology, I have something to show my two friends and my employee
and my employee will pull it up right now. Let me see this
any minute and he's passed on. He's yeah, what is going on? He is in living
in Dios de los. I think he ran away. He must have heard one second. He needs one
second. It's a sec. That's okay. I will stall with other technology. Hey,
another technology thing. I got my phone screen replaced. Oh yeah. What happened
your phone, your phone again?
I am the spiller and the dropper. It's great. Every phone, I spill every
drink. It's unbelievable. My desk, I got my wife, got me a white mouse pad.
Yeah, okay.
All right, so here's what we have here.
So I was thinking okay, what's the what is up with technology right go full
screen on this it's right on the top right of the thing.
No, no right on the top right of the
of the square yeah, so okay before you touch anything so
I was thinking about I was thinking about technology and I was thinking
about what we do podcast right now, I was like okay, we've already made a
technological leap from audio only well. First of all, a big leap was was
starting the podcast. I was a
technological from from just talking to now in
equation using microphone, but then equations I was then we did another to
another level and we started doing video. This is a brand new technology. We
be something in ten years from now. What is podcast about list going to look
like? I think it's going to look a little something like this. This is an
interactive podcast wow so you can go ahead and press the green button
scratch. You can see I made this on scratch, which is MIT Massachusetts
might do the what technology, so we have over here. We have Cameron, Patrick and
Caleb and guys yes, no, how Sam yes, that's me guess how these were made
guys
how
artificial intelligence, go ahead and
Make sure there's audio from this. Could you click on Cameron, please?
Okay, he says greetings rapidly evolving technological landscape. Innovation
continues to redefine our daily lives, bridging the gap between possibility and
reality. Wow, that's something you'll be able to. So now click me, you'll be
able to click on us and have as we navigate the dynamic currents of the
tech realm, transformative breakthroughs and interconnected advancements shape
the very fabric of our digital future.
Wow,
this is an incredible, incredible podcast. That's what I'm saying to
click on Patrick, so it's like we're. This is what it'll be like in years
from now.
So it's like a podcast that is you click on the you instead of just
listening to people say stuff, waiting for the year. When is the next guy
going to talk. I heard Cameron say it's like when is Caleb going to talk at
your own head into your fingertips at your own place, a fully simulated
podcast, and this is all done using current technology. So in ten years,
wow, it'll probably be three dimensional. What is that behind it? Well, we're in
Brooklyn, so this is Brooklyn style graffiti. Okay, that is
culturally amazing,
multicultural, multicultural style. So what did you think that's incredible?
I'm just glad I don't you guys haven't used my voice for the AI. That was not a
those were things. You said already yeah, meet me and Cameron. This is
coming to me and he was like he was like can you can you quick? Can you quickly
record some serious thoughts on technology? I was like yeah, but yeah,
and they were really, I think, insightful and illuminating yeah, very
illuminating very
you I it's just it. I can't get over it. How much I look like Sam. It's age ten
years. So I'm going to look like binging with Babish Cameron looks very much the
same and you
I'll have a pair in ten years. That's good.
That's actually thank you for giving me hair in ten years. Well, we'll have
because that's not going to happen. That's not going to be there. You'll be
on him. That's also why you got shorter was the him. Yeah, him does make you
much shorter. If you tay, if you're a man and you take him's buddy, you're in for
a rude away. You're a you're a she the
the hymns that you're going to go him's hers. They actually have her. They have
her and guess what hers is a burly anxiety medication and anxiety. Yeah,
yeah, the him that you're going to be. If you take him's is mugsy bogues,
you're going to be real small. You're gonna be singing him's at your funeral
because that stuff kills you as an angel. Yeah, as an as a be alive at your
funeral. Now that would make much sense. It wouldn't make any sense at all.
Now make any sense. Well, thank you for showing that that piece of technology
to us. Caleb, that's really wonderful. Anytime man. I mean, I let me and let
me say one other thing about technology. Yeah, guys, I really like using scratch.
Scratch is fun. I used to be a scratch wizard. Me too. I made a lot of I made
a lot of pong games in there. I taught a class on scratch. Really? Yeah. Would
you teach us one right now? Could you tell us some things about school? Julio,
how about you open up scratch and Cameron? I don't think so. It's gonna be
bad. That would be bad. That'd be really bad. It's a bad idea. Yeah, I'm just so
technologically illiterate that I just go around and say some of our favorite
pieces of technology. What's yours? Probably the Blackberry Blackberry is
the Blackberry that I own, and I'm going to say Bluetooth technology is really up
there for me. I'm speaking of Bluetooth. It's a video game controller for me. The
video game controllers have gotten and you know what I'll say mine,
the rumble pack. I like the rumble pack as well as the joystick. I like the
ergonomic feel. You've got joystick or rumble pack. Oh, definitely rumble pack
really really come on. Yes, imagine you're in a mine cart and it makes it
and you get to feel that
is actually it's actually makes it immersive. Oh, I thought of another
technology just now three D, three D, and I'm not talking about three D glasses.
I'm talking about three D itself, three D. It's just three D or the electrical
wire. Oh, and I oh silicone silicone is huge. Silicone is huge in technology. Oh
self lubricating joints and pistons. Oh, you know, I saw a great technology
video. I saw a great technology video earlier, a cobalt mine in a foreign
country, people jumping over each other and it looks like World War. See people
don't think about the human technology people who act like robots just to
satisfy others exactly. So who are these people? These are fast food workers.
Yes, these are our politicians, arguably yeah, sexual nympho maniacs, sexual
people who give their bodies away freely almost like a three D avatar circus
exactly circus performance. People people who the trapeze one of my favorite
pieces of technology. Once the trapeze was invented, I felt like we had nowhere
to go but down yeah and by the way, but the trapeze artist had nowhere to go,
but speaking of you let go that trapeze are going down, not if you jump well
speaking of cirques, I call them cirques.
Guess what I saw since the last time we spoke last the circus. Cirque du Soleil
the night before Christmas Cirque du Soleil and guys before Christmas. Yes,
and guys, I wish it was circuit. You guys, you buy this ticket. Okay, it's
sixty dollars. You go to Madison Square Garden. You sit in line for one hour.
You're seated right. You're seated lights down. The show begins. It's for
children.
It is a children version of Cirque du Soleil. Nobody in the room knew this.
There was no kids there. Wow. It was fully a kids show. All of the
performers were kids. None of them were licensed to hang upside down, so they
didn't. They ran around, they hula hooped, and they dressed up like elves.
Were there people at your schools that went to circus camp? No. To learn to be
circus performers? Fuck no. That was kind of a common thing at my school. What?
There was multiple people who went to- Like Barnum and Bailey? It was called
Circus Smurkus,
and they learned to juggle and do acrobatics. I'm not kidding. Jesus Christ.
Multiple people, that was like a thing that they did. That's crazy. I kind of
I didn't know if that was a type of kid. No, that's not a type. I don't think that's that's local to
your town. It should be, though. Isn't that funny? That is funny kids at your school. The
circus. Click. Yeah, the circus kids. They were I don't even think they were like they weren't
like friends with each other. And they were they just happened to be. I think it was like a
summer going in the hallway where they run away circus style. No, no, this is my no. And these
are these are people who mostly grew into hikers and normal well adjusted people. Okay, I don't
I don't think anybody went into the circus, the circus field. Well, it's
just so they could juggle to like impress a little and while there was a
juggling and also like I guess walking on your hands type style. I think it
was multiple stuff. I mean, I don't know. I know this is all this is all
stuff that you learn so that you can like have ice breakers so that you can
make friends with people right. This is something that you can't for children
that aren't good at making friends yeah, but the thing is here's the weird part
of that because it's also it sounds like it would be that, but I think these
people all had a fine time making friends, but in order to do it, I think
have to be pretty. You have to be pretty strong. You have to be kind of an athlete. You know
what I mean to like walk on your hands and shit like that. So it's not like you would
expect it to be like, you know, scrawny nerdy kids or weirdos who during circus camp, but
it's kind of like, you know, the guys who are strong and jocks jocks. There's strong
nerds. Yeah, I guess so, but I don't think they have secret strength. Super. Yeah, they
always love metal mind. What I always love metal guitar like every strong nerd in high
school is also like, hey, he's also like he's got a seven string guitar that he learned.
I don't think there were any strong words at my high school. I'm going to be real.
There's a lot of my only very weak, a strong nerd. I feel like as as come into
with with Instagram weightlifting, I think a strong nerd is really coming to
vote. Yeah, there was a sleeper build. Yes, there's a lot of those guys at my
school and they were all in this thing technology.
There was a
program at my school called the PVC pirates, where they would learn how to
make
because it was a okay, different kind of technologies. It was like kids who were
like good at like like Lego robotics and stuff like that, but they were going
to the PBC. I never I remember to do you want to ruin Legos by putting
technology in it yeah that stuff. I agree. I always thought that people
like an analog yeah and here's a technology kind of credential. I have I
was I don't know if you guys know this. I was the president of the computer
science club at my really and I just I destroyed the club. It stopped existing
after I became president. I just did not do anything. We started the club, me and
my friends. Well, the club existed, the former president passed it down to me
and my friends. We held a we had a booth at the org fair for everyone to sign up
for the club, and we met one time and we never met again. Well, it sounds like
you did an amazing job to the ground. Sounds like you did exactly what you're
supposed to do as president. Yeah, yeah,
nothing yeah. We kind of got the assignment. If you know what I mean, yes,
you got it understood it. No, you got it got it yeah and you pass with flying
color with flying
RGB colors, see oh yes, composite yes, composite colors yeah, don't isn't it
doesn't it scare you when on Photoshop it says or do you want to switch this
document to a different color space? I said color space, you know what the hell
is that I think I'm fine where I am yeah, no be I think I know I know why
there's different color spaces. Why is that for different technologies? There's
RGB for the computer, but then there's CMYK for printing printing kill your
mother fucking kelf kill your kelf
that doesn't that's knife in the right order. I'm real kill CMYK kill mother
your kelf crazy mother fucking yellow colors
or something like that.
Here's a technology that why is K black in that situation? Here's a why is that
CMYB because B sounds like blue?
Oh, or be is taken by blue
the electric toothbrush.
Do you guys have one of these? I just had to throw mine away because the
motor died. This is a technology I don't support. Why I can you got to do your
own work?
Interesting technology is making us lazy. It's making us whatever you remember
back in the day before we had electronic toothbrushes. You'd put the
toothbrush in your mouth and go
really, really fast.
you have to go fast. That noise completely, perfectly, that's what somebody
has been on an electric toothbrush for years. They probably get a normal
toothbrush, they put it in their mouth, they don't move at all and they just
hum like
I think that's what makes it go. They think that's a toothbrush. Speaking of
toothbrushes and teeth, I got my wisdom tooth out technology technique for using
technology and they gave me this technology that was amazing called codeine
pills. Okay, and I would take these and I would watch what's his name on twitch
excuse see I would watch him play
five GTA five role play. That's the craziest I've ever felt in my entire
life. I just remembered something Caleb. You died in my dream the other night.
What
a big piece of debris hit you in the head and you died. They should make
technology where I can go into your dream and stop that. That's a bad omen,
because there's that big puddle. I had a dream over there. I had a dream that
New York City was being was being nuclear bombed and there's explosions
happening and I was I was hugging my fiancee. I think I love you so much. Oh
my God, I can't believe it's happening. I always love you. I'm so sorry it's
ending. This world is ending like this and I look over and kill against the
hitting the head with a rock. Was I in the dream or was I implied to be dead
for years? Caleb was in the dream getting killed for one. I had an at least
I wasn't killed. I had a dream where I was a very bad guy in here. So you can
tell okay number one. I was involved in serial killing, okay, which is not that
big of a deal. The only dream I've ever had like this yes, but number two
get my partner in crime, Ellen DeGeneres.
Wow.
You and Ellen were so good.
I would bait people into this room and then she would murder them with a chainsaw.
That's crazy.
And that was my dream.
Isn't that a crazy dream?
I did have a crazy, not crazy dream, but last night I had a dream and it was, you guys were
both there.
Whoa.
And it was me remembering the time that we went to New York City for the first time.
We were at that Burger King.
I remember that.
weird thing in my dream. It was basically the exact same, exactly how we all remember it,
but I went up to buy onion rings at the Burger King on that bus. You know, the bus would
stop at the Burger King. I went there and I just wanted to get onion rings and zesty
sauce and the guy said, "One large onion ring, that'll be $18."
This is such a funny dream.
I said to him, "What the hell? $18 for onion rings? How big is the thing?" And he shows
scares me. The size of the thing is like that big and I was like, oh, I'll just
get the medium. Then he said, oh, then that'll be eight dollars. I said, it's
eight dollars for
this is
oh my God, inception. It's about dreams, but all Christopher Nolan could think
about was a building spinning around
how expensive
me arguing with the guy behind the counter about the price of onion rings.
like why does that make any sense? Why is the large eighteen dollars in the
medium is eight and then I bring you guys came over
I would
I have to tell you something, Pat, you know, also my dream. I Lena Dunham,
I would rather be a die a von Eric style brother suicide death where I lose
all my limbs and then I kill myself, then be your therapist.
Yeah, every day you coming in and being like I had the murder.
dream again. What does it mean this time? I would just be like,
"Yeah, you got..." No, I know exactly what that means. I know exactly what
that means is that... 365, Klonopin, come back next year. Is that I would
do anything for onion rings, is all that dream means. I can kind of
figure out what my nuclear bomb dream means, except for the part where I
look over and see you get hit in the head with a piece of
a building. That's just to make it feel real in your own head.
You're making it feel real in your head. That's immersion, yeah.
It's just to make it sad, your friend dying. I cannot figure out my...
I need a Solomon style dream interpretation to figure out my Ellen
degenerous dream. Not sure what that means yeah that ones are. I think I know
what it means. That means that maybe I join the Hollywood cabal of evil people
like Ellen to general and a generous may have been projecting into your dream to
make you do bad things. That is honestly the most that's the most log every night
you go. She's like the Occam's razor. That's a me. Yeah, I think that actually
is. Why else would you believe that in your side? Even a woman? I think about
that often. Oh yeah, why not Ellen degenerate? You don't think about her
out, because she's a dog. She's fallen by the wayside. She's zealous. I just
tell a lot of people riding skateboards, holding hands together. Well, their arms
interlock. That's like the two opposite crazy. What happened? They were two
people skateboarding side by side and their arms were locked like this. What is
going? Am I in a dream right now? What the hell is happening? The conversation
is happening in real conversation just turned so crazy fast. Anyway, technology
car technology car. Tesla has a big screen on it. You play Mario sixty four
What's another technology we can want to talk about? I got a new technology. I
got an Xbox. I heard about this. Yeah, and this is this is guys.
This is an amazing move that you can play on your cohabitator.
You
leave on the Amazon fire stick all day and night for years. It breaks. She says,
well, let's order another one. It's forty dollars. You say, yeah, it's forty
dollars, but for two hundred more dollars, we can get an Xbox. Yeah,
genius and you really mumble that you say for two hundred dollars, we get an
xbox and then she goes yeah sure whatever it comes. She hates using the
controller guys. Of course it's not as good as a remote no, but it's a remote
for an xbox. You probably can't they have sure you can yeah, so just tell her
to buy that yeah just buy that it's a rare thing. It's almost certainly
ninety dollars. Just if you have a problem find out the solution and buy it
uh-huh. It's that simple girl. It's simply simple. It's that fucking simple
Speaking of technology and game consoles, Noah informed me that the modded Wii that I have
has died. Which is a very, very sad thing because we used to play so much.
We would play so much.
Planned obsolescence.
Yeah. How many games would we play on that?
Frolf.
Frolf? Oh my God, we had so many Frolf sessions on that.
That was the only game I ever played on that I think was Frolf.
I got to figure out how to bring this Wii back to life because that had probably 150
games.
Can you mod a Wii?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll get you a Wii. I think we might have one.
like yeah, maybe it might be in Boston. There is there's a thing. This is a
technology. This is a technology fact. Okay, you find out your wheeze IP
address. You go to this website, hack M I I dot com me. Hack me. I don't want
to get and then you send some you send a file over to the through the IP
address and then it opens up the little mail thing and then the they programmed
it so that the little letter, you know, remember the letters at the bottom of
the screen in the corner of the we know you open that up and there's a letter
that has a bomb on it and then all the whole shit gets it installs this thing
called the the home room in you and boot. I
I can put being tired as many games. You want me I made my new avendor not xbox
and I made it so realistic that the dog started going crazy barking the TV.
He's never done this before barking the TV bearing his teeth hackles up
and I had to put him in his crate and never show him the avatar again. Why
Why don't you just make the avatar different?
Why don't you make the avatar a dog?
- Or is it just so photorealistic,
just it looks like a person?
- Do you have a Kinect that you took a photo of yourself?
- Do I have a Kinect?
Oh man, you should get a Kinect.
- You know what you can do with the Kinect?
You can use the Kinect to take photos
and 3D model something.
This is what my sister's ex used to do.
He would model, he learned 3D modeling
and he would take a Kinect and say,
he would just move it around like that on an object
and then he would have the object in the computer
but he didn't know what to do with it.
That sounds cool. Like I'd like to do that. We could do that. We could also play Just Dance.
We could also do that with technology. That's a classic piece of technology. That kept the
Wii alive until 2020, I think. 2019 was the last game ported to the Wii and it was Just
Dance. Here's a funny Just Dance thing. You know when you're playing Just Dance with your
parents and they don't understand that it only is tracking the remote? Yes. They're
shaking their remote. It's very funny. Yeah, your dads are snicking. I've never seen it.
That's not a game in my house working in your face. It's so funny. They all
they they're jumping. Why are you jumping? You don't have to drop. You're
gonna hurt yourself. You don't have to do all the things the purple girl. You
can do some of it for style, but when you get into things like jumping, yeah,
don't jump. You don't need to jump. That's like a lot of people don't realize
dance dance revolution. It's all just feet. It's just feet. Stop. We hold the
higher hands behind your back. Yeah, you'll do better. You will actually do
way, way better. If you tie your hands behind your back, close your eyes. Your
eyes aren't part of it. Yeah, eyes just move. There's your mouth, keep it shut
and hey me fortnight. You only have to use a controller. Caleb stop sticking
out your tongue like you're Michael Jordan. Every single time you play. I
don't know why I do that shit. I'm sitting there.
Huh? Yes, I stick out my tongue when I play video. No, you can tell the
controller. I told my whole body. I'm jumping up and down. I think that the
whole thing came first. The commercial showing the people. It has to be. It
has to be the commercial trying to make it seem like it's real life. Yeah,
that's definitely it, because there's no reason why you should be tilting,
because it's realistic. I guess if you're playing such a good game, you do
it, but I feel like the commercial really made it into a thing yeah
or is that or is that as a really nature? It is so funny. It is the full
equivalent of like the thing of like people getting scared by the train
coming towards the screen on the old silent movie of like just playing an
old like and like seeing a commercial. So I'm playing it like an N sixty four
game where it's like three triangles on the screen. You're going
like a lover
playing pong. Yeah, like whoa. Can you imagine how amazing that felt to play
pong for the first time? Oh, wait, isn't it kind of cruelly ironic that back in
the day they were so concerned with all the ads have to make it seem like the
game is real. It'll be like you see an added old comic book and it'll be for
modal combat and it's like scorpion shooting fire out of the screen. It's
like so real you'll die. That was like the tag line of the game and nowadays
games look so real that a person who is over thirty years old will think that it
of the news yeah and they don't care. They don't advertise like that anymore.
Have you seen those videos of the
GTS
about that? You be a commercial for
that's what they need to bring that ad campaign back of so real. You will die.
You think it's real and you will grant that auto commercial where the granny is
watching it and so it's the news used yeah. Once they go, oh my God, what are
you kidding? I could not believe that that existed. It's incredible, but that's
what I mean they need to bring that back technology. It's technology. We should
do that with splatoon put splatoon on the tv and say yeah grandma. This is
happening in a sanctuary city right now, but a little fox news lower third on
there. This is happening right now in in Portland, Oregon. Oh, the splatoons are
back at it. Yes, this is the
autonomous
again. They haven't been here since nineteen fifty two.
this is so scary. I think that'd be an easy way to scare. I just I'm saying
grant that thought of old people. It's not so much a grant that thought it
looks realistic. That's all these are dumb as right. Yeah, no, they're losing
their vision in their mind. They're bad at my knowledge. They're bad. They're
bad. I think an old person uses a damn phone. That is true. Is that you can put
on Viva? People came from an age when the tech, the biggest technology was this
was a hoop and a kazoo. Yeah, well, that was small. I was talking about big.
the size. Oh yeah, yeah, nowadays we have phones the size of a brick. Yeah,
that's true, but here's the thing, here's the thing back in the back in
their day, the computer was the size of their room. Now the computer is
smaller. They don't know what the hell to do with. Here's a question I
have. I was watching a movie now in New York City. The rooms from from
one thousand and sixty eight. They had in the sixties. I guess they had
computer dating. Yes, but what is how does that work? There's no internet is
that worked. It was a was you want to call it if you want an honest. I do
want an honest answer. It would have you would get like a score for everything
and it would match people based on scores. It wasn't it wasn't like you're
at two different computers. It dated people you used this thing to match make,
but how does it match make to how does it is it like did they get a directory
with everybody and every punch card or whatever has a directory like take a
quiz and then the right, but how does it connect the people do it was a computer
collected data, but the computers aren't connected. No, it was one. It's one
you all go up to yeah. Okay, that makes sense because I guess they wouldn't have
had personal computers back down. So
the library, yes, you'd go to the library. You probably go to like the lab,
you'd go to like the factory, you'd go to a lab and you can be in the that's
crazy. I like lunch more than breakfast and you'd have a wife because you
couldn't also you couldn't not marry the first person that you know. Of course
not. Yeah, what do you? Yeah, you're you're so ugly. You're going to the
computer for a date back then. Exactly. Yeah. Back then. That was a problem. Now
everyone's got a dating app on their phone technology. Now you used to use a
computer to date. Now you date the computer.
Now you fucking boot up the computer and your phone is a computer and dating
nowadays has become fucking yes, and what have fingering fingering as well
and getting in what happened to our ways. Nowadays, everyone's got a dating
app on their phone. You type in a random number, you just call somebody and
hopefully it's a woman that loves you.
that's how I met my girlfriend. You just called some random called some random
numbers.
I ever found a lifelong love a Romeo, though. I like that. I've heard that in
a long time.
Is this a Romeo dial
new technology? Bring that back? Yeah, Romeo. That's what they were trying to
do with chat roulette, but everyone got on there starting throwing their thing
out. I'm turning the Romeo. Unfortunately, that's the modern way is
to take your thing out on technology. Technology has made it so people think
you need to whip out your thing a me. Let's talk about our personalities
first and then we'll show our thing. We'll show our things to see if they're
compatible. If if my thing doesn't fit in your thing, we not dating no real
shit. If my thing better be big,
better be the size of moon, your thing better be the size of my thing and no
different.
It better fit perfectly girl. It better be like a locking key first day and yeah
just saying I mean we're having a good time, but I better fit perfectly. It
better not it better. I better not be able to wiggle it. I'm looking for my
glass slipper.
No,
I'm not putting my foot in it's just a metal. Okay, you're going to put your
foot in her. Well, I'm not Cinderella. First of all, and her thing's not a
shoe can't wear. Some girls things are like shoes. That's true. Oh, leather
dusty, not as comfortable as I'm ten, unquares at the barbican the things.
Here's a new technology laces on the thing. So you put your thing in, then
you tighten it up there. Okay,
with like meat string, like you're tying like you're making a
I can't even bring myself to say any anatomical phrase. Don't you have
something
just talking about stuff we're talking about we're talking about tying up a
segway. You were talking about tied up a put your put you with a butcher twine
is a thing of the past. Let's talk about the future.
is that a thing of the past? I used to do that in the seventeen fifties. That was
what they did when they got on a man. Okay, wait speaking of the seventeen
fifties used to be looser back then, because God hadn't intervened yet yeah,
so they had to they had to make do they what they would do is they would take
whale tendon from their whaling ships on Nantucket originated in Nantucket.
They'd come back and they take the put it in a bucket. They put it in a bucket
and they'd scrub all the flesh and fat off until it was just a tendon and they'd
put it in their wife. They they and this is where the saying sleep tight came
from.
It's an old saying from the seventeen hundreds is in Nantucket and Salem,
Massachusetts, so the northeast kind of had the market quarter on the corner
on this stuff, because typically in the they did it in other regions, but it
was more technology you're speaking about the more ancient tech. They use
crab pinchers and scorpion pin speaking of speaking of the seventeen hundreds.
Have you seen this? Have you seen this? There's this art exhibit in Melbourne
Australia where they used... I've not been. I haven't been to this man.
They used this... I've never been there. They used AI technology
to make these portraits of these two
men who were apparently in love with each other that got marooned on an island
because they were... Sorry, wait, I'm sorry.
You just said two men. Two men who were in love with each other on the East India Company.
Sounds Australian to me.
And they made these two... Everything's backwards. They made these two AI portraits.
flush the wrong way. The men are in love,
but just think about the thing about that, though. Imagine you're out on the
East India Company right. You fall in love with that every day. You fall in
love with another man eating tea. You fall in love with another man. You're
like I want I'm going to I want you. I'm going to do it with this guy. They
don't have that. That's the bravest guy in the world, because they got no
toilet paper or anything on that ship.
Well, but I do I think over ninety per say were being they were bad at white.
I think we're not very little. Washington, your ass was not invented
until the 70s when Red Fox came. So was washing your pussy man,
but also back then they had higher tolerance because they were eating
meat called dirt. Yeah, yeah, they were. They don't. They don't care as
much if they're, you know, there's they made these AI. They made these
AI portraits of these two, these two men who are apparently marooned
brown. It's just two white twinks.
It's just twinks. It's just just back then. It's just shirtless twinks like
Is that the exhibit is just two shirtless twinks on these monitors? And
the story is like, "These two men were marooned after they fell in love with
each other." And it's like, "Why? You could have put them in some clothes.
You could have put them in a pirate outfit." They're marooned, man. They
probably were in a loin cloth. Yeah, but they don't even look dirty. They
don't even look like they've been marooned at all. It's just two white
twinks on a fucking... On two computer monitors. I'm all in on this exhibit
and I'm gonna be donating. You're gonna be donating? I would like to invest
in this. I think that we should you're going on this. I believe that gay
relationships should be rendered in a I yeah
and you said nowhere else. I didn't say that, but I was yeah, that's what I
don't mean that, though. I actually think I actually watch a lot of gay porn
honestly. A relationship said nobody take that the wrong way. I'm
actually think
gay porn. I actually actually, actually, I think I know. I think we need to learn
the slang. We need to keep a out of gay relationships. Stay out of gay people's
business. Yeah, thank you. You get these computers away from these gay people
pull up my
they don't know how to use them. They're
new type of where they're putting. They're just throwing words together.
They don't know what is why you call my mom a cunt. Have you guys ever have you
guys ever seen the movie dress to kill the Brian to palm a moving? No, this is
the only context I can ever think of to bring this scene up and this is so
funny. There's a scene, so it's a there's a scene at the end of the movie
where Nancy Allen is explaining to Keith Gordon about how a vagina plasty works
like a sex change, okay and and Keith Gordon, he plays like an inventor like
computer nerd type character and she's like telling him all these details of
how they
turn a penis into a vagina and then at the end he's like at the end, he's like
oh geez, I don't know about all that. I guess I'll just stick to my computers.
The way the one that is aged the funniest of all time, it's age pretty
well. Actually, in terms of very, very terms of movie dialogue about vagina
Vaginoplasty. That's probably up there. I don't know. The only other representation
in media of a Vaginoplasty is
Mr Garrison. Yeah, yeah. That I can think of.
And also, I guess that's the better one. And also, my very not accurate
educational video I tried to make a couple of years ago, where I did a 3D
model that just does this of the penis, just pushes it, pushes it in,
and then a green check mark, ding! Like a WarioWare minigame. You took a 3D
got on like dad's three D and hit the extrude, but yeah on the P is it
pulls it back to basically we start with the
we pull it back negative a hundred and then I'm done
okay. Here's my technology week. I pulled this from a bunch of different
websites, a bunch of different technology blogs and we're going to talk
about not by do we be it's by me and we're going to talk about go by that.
No, I don't want to go by that. I hate that name. I think it's a we be oh
it's different from dubia. I'm going to start it now. Here's from a bunch of
different websites. Here's ten future technologies that will change the world
first. Technology has made man easy to work and has changed the way of
thinking. Now, scientist has much more ideas for change this world. Here are
the top ten unbelievable technologies that can easily change our world
completely. I'm just gonna be jumping around here. That's fun, but number
nine is virtual reality. VR is not just a technology. This is a best proof
of being doing everything in this world. Nobody had dream about this
technology, but now it seems like reality. Our destiny is to become what
we think, to have our thoughts become our bodies and our bodies become our
thoughts when we looking towards the future is lot of talking about virtual
reality. The first traces of virtual reality came from the world of science
fiction. Now future can be totally chained through this unbelievable
technology. Ultimately, you can enter a virtual world in the cupboard in your
living room.
They're gonna have a virtual reality cupboard. You know, we are I was singing
about this. VR is such a funny technology because you think it's going
to be this future amazing change your life kind of thing, and it is for ten
ten minutes, but then for seventy five percent of people you instantly
vomit. If you play for more than yeah, and it's also that you're you're
entering another world, the cyber world, so you can play egg catch yeah look. I
can move my I can move. Oh my God, it's so realistic. I can move two fingers.
Yeah, wow, wow, whoa yeah, you just do most of the time in VR. You're doing
this now. Finally, in VR, you can experience being born as a baby with a
birth defect where you have no legs or hands,
and if you move, you're going to yank, you're going to yank a cable out and
like your computer, you can step on your experience being born as literally
belial from basket case.
That is exactly the body that you have in vr. You have two arms and a head
and that's completely it
being carried around by your brother. This is what it would be like if
belial from from basket case could look at a beach. Yes, oh my God, it looks so
realistic. Number one is autonomous robots. Now this is totally that
technology about which we can say that what a technology this a very dangerous
technology as soon as twenty thirty, a technological dollar sign angularity
will emerge with the leading theory being that artificial intelligence in
the form of autonomous and we're seeing a lot of dollar signs. Yeah, this is
written by a hacker or some kind of technologist. Robots might rival humans
in independent thinking and creativity. So to say it plainly, robots will
surpass humans in intelligence. This is very hard to believe that one day our
friend will be a robot and give us advises and make jokes with us. We have
friend user robot to be oh yeah to be oh three here's the next blog. I found this
one is called tech informative. It says tech informative is a professional
technical information platform here. We will provide you only interesting
content, which will you will like very much. We're dedicated to providing you
the best of technical information with a focus on dependability and information.
We're working to turn our passion for technical information into a booming
online website. Well, it seems nice. It's a great website. Here's the menu bar. So
we have tech informative. It's here's the different things we have home future
the world, electronics and reborts. What is rebord? So I saw rebords and I
thought, oh, maybe this is supposed to be reports. What is a report? So let's
click to the next slide here and I'll read you what it is rebord, a
vehicle,
rebord, a car and robotic vehicle technology.
This is not rebords. This is rebords as like a babe. I'm a rebord. I see,
and this is a picture of a rebord vehicle. It's a car that's standing up
kind of a standing car. So report means a standard right report was making me
laugh so hard when I found this when I discovered that report
I my reboard
here's some other reports they have on their website and they report road meet
Mars cat robotic cats, AI robotic cat naughty, very little pet lucky dug, not
all cats have fur and also the same holds true for cats of the robotic
persuasion. The lucky dug naughty, very little pet incorporates a cartoonish
look is created of onerous plastic and includes a toy bottle of milk and a
little blue basket to take a seat in. It says it says not all cats have for and
also the same holds true for cats of the robotic persuasion, but some do that
means that some robotic can re boarded cats have do have her. There are some
re board cats with first. You guys ever feel like really like the biggest
technological boom to me was the year where I was a kid and I saw the robot
dogs that do back flips and the purple catch up. I was like yes, that is this
is like an only I live in the future yeah speaking of robotic dogs. Here's a
rebord dog picture here for us this next one here and this caption says a
four lawful robot can learn to walk in an hour like an a like a invigorated
full
and there's a picture of a robotic dog and then here's what we have about this.
The Boston Dynamics has developed a four legged golem for analysis comes agency
DARPA agency, federal agency, government agency, bureau office, authority,
defense, advanced research projects, agency referred to as big dog that they
claim is the most advanced quadruped golem on earth. Huge dog will run at
four miles per hour, climb thirty five degree slopes and that's not thirty
five. That's thirty five five degrees without getting tired. Yeah, it's an
endurance thing and carry three hundred and forty pounds. However, the four
most spectacular feature is its dynamic walking. Huge dog will endure
slithering and even being pushed, so it's not scared of snakes. Its behavior is
specified. It approaches the disreputable uncanny valley. I don't think that those
things are in the uncanny valley. No, there's no they yeah, because they're
just as they look like normal. I mean look at that. I've always it looks like
an invigorated full yeah to me a quadruped. I always say that stuff looks
like an invigorate like when I see like my when my nephew first started crawling
and said, oh he looks like an invigorated full. I can even with stand
slithering. Oh yeah and pushing
during slithering. Wow, this invigorated full and dirt slithering so well.
All right, here's our next tech blog top ten high tech inventions, maybe in
twenty thirty vision of the future ten high tech inventions will hopefully be
using in twenty thirty. Here's the first one number four immortal immortality and
body sharing. While computers get smarter, the brain it link will also get
better. So you'll use external it more until most of your mind is outside your
brain. When your body dies, you'll only lose the bits still based in the brain.
Most of your mind will carry on. You'll go to your funeral, buy an android body
and carry on. Death won't be a career problem. If you don't want to use an
android, maybe you'll link into your friend's bodies and share them just as
students hang out on friends sofas. Life really begins after death. Would you guys
link into your friend's body just as if you would link into their sofa? Seems
relationship, believe sexual yeah. I don't think that I would upload my brain to a
computer. I don't think I would do it. I would not do it to my friend's body.
Wouldn't it be so scary to upload my myself to my friend's body? I would
upload myself to my friend's body against their will. I feel like it was
here's the right. I think the first hour that you're a robot is probably similar
to coming out of wisdom tooth surgery, where you kind of are saying anything
definitely, you know you're just like oh zero zero yeah things are still getting
Yeah, and then people are putting that together and it turns out you're telling
secrets, 'Oh, what happened at camp back in the day?' So, I wouldn't want to do
that. That's the laughing gas, right? I've been awake every single time I got
my wisdom teeth out. You've never been put under? No, it's way cheaper. You've
never done a surgery where you're put under? I got this taken out,
it took them five minutes, they pulled it out and then I took the train home.
The only two times I was put under is I had my tonsils out and then they
exploded and I had to get them,
your sutures exploded and I had to go get it redone. Does laughing gas count as
going under? I think so. I don't know. No. I think I was, I was awake the whole
time. Yeah, I was awake for- That's the only time I ever got anesthesia was-
You never done general anesthesia? No. It's scary, 'cause you're just- I did
local. I was terrified of it. You don't dream- I'm completely terrified of it.
It's a complete pause. The scary thing is when you, those people who are
allergic to it- I know, that's, you just die. Yeah, yeah. That's why I'm
terrified of it. Well, you don't die. I never- You die. You can, you can die,
even there's also a row who on anesthesia. You also can choke on your
there's people who take on a under there's people who go under general
general to not do it and then they
they
are fully paralyzed, but they feel everything. Oh yeah, I heard about that
on guard. Any this is a technology we need to eliminate. Get rid of
anesthesia, whatever happened to a coconut over the head right
to do that.
Why was that my I don't know I tried to say Boeing bonk, but it went
my kind of the a little bit bunk. That's what I meant to say yeah, and then you
do the surgery. Yeah, remove a leg. Here's the next technology we're going to talk
about is smart yogurt.
Smart you a quad core PC has for processors all sharing the same chip
instead of the single one there used to be. This will increase until computers
have millions of processors. These might be suspended in jail to keep them cool
and allow to allow them to be wired together via light beams in separate
developments, bacteria are being genetically modified to let them make
electronic components. Putting these together smart yogurt could be the basis
of future computing with potentially vastly superhuman intelligence. One day
your best friend could be a yogurt wow that's a pretty good rap lyric yeah me
like about used to be broke me and my my family was quad core all sharing a chip
damn my best friend was a yogurt and now he's a
well yeah you got to make it gangsta yeah. I guess what I like about this is
this is kind of to tech to crazy technological advances, where one
computers become a yogurt and second of all that a computer would ever be your
best friend. What do you exactly this person and one by a yogurt? They I
think it's pretty fucking clear a smart yoga. You think it's you think it's
bacterial cultures is basically yogurt
and they're saying it could be a computer gel and bacteria equals.
They're saying that's doodle God recipe for
for yogurt is bacteria plus gel exactly well, not only that a computer would be
my best friend that some yogurt would be yeah. They're kind of three things. I
think that in twenty thirty are my best friend could be a yogurt, whether or not
it's computerized. That's what I want. Absolutely yogurt friend. Yes, my do
like like oh, I say yo yogurt yeah yogurt. Gurt is a name. Gurt is his
name's Gurt, so the ad is like you say yogurt and he wakes up like Alexa and it
would be
well, he doesn't say anything he's he's today is strawberries. You're going to
eat today. You will eat strawberry over today. Yeah, you can change the way
just tell you off part. It's a it's an AI, but that tells you what type of
yogurt you have to eat that I'm not going to eat based on your diet. This is
stupid. I would eat my friend peach on the bottom yogurt.
There's a play crunch peach on his stuff like that. Don't say his bottom. What's
this? It's your robot friend. It's Gert to Gert. It's just Gert. I'm out on
yogurt all right all right we're going to make a billion dollars. Go ahead
you're out man, whatever as long as I'm not part of any yogurt company,
and I'm fine all right here's our here's our last tech blog here. Okay, this is
top ten future electronic devices for next decades origami DVD player or it
got me DVD player. This is a cool picture of a little thing where a bunch
of apps are coming out of it. It's made by apple and it's an apple thing. Do you
Do you guys remember that one thing that was the wrist phone? Yeah, it was the
light the watch that shot a light onto your projected a phone screen onto your
I remember that. That sounds cool. Well, they did like a GoFundMe for it where they
had like like concept art and stuff and then they raised millions of dollars and
then they started trying to make it and they realized it was completely impossible
to do it. Of course. It was awesome. Yeah. So this kind of reminds me of that. What
do you think they did with all that money? Just ran away with it? I mean they
they didn't run away. Probably still around. They didn't run away. They
didn't like pull up to get a stick and a bandana. They probably spent it all on
trying to do the thing. Yeah, they were like okay, got the money time to run
away from home.
Okay, I would do if I had a go fund me that big. Here's a here's a piece of
technology. I'm not making shit. No, here's a piece of technology guys,
self cleaning auto ordering refrigerator. There are already the so called smart
refrigerators in the market. Well, this refrigerator takes the technology to all
new level. This fridge is equipped with nano articulated technology with this
technology to the independent tiles present in the fridge, move the food
that needs to be consumed early to the top. The fridge consists of the LCD
screen, which displays content present in the fridge. This intelligent thing
also suggests recipe with the available items. It orders the things you need and
also thrashes the wastage or expired food by itself and for guys for the video
and for the audio listeners, this auto ordering refrigerator, the picture is of
us an oven, yes,
with a stove top yeah. So this is maybe one of the most genius inventions. I've
kind of makes me a refrigerator that looks exactly like an oven or top this
hobber cooks. We're hungry. Robert comes in trying to steal your food. He's not
going to look in the oven, a hot refrigerator yeah yeah. That's also a
good. That's a really good to stay on living animals yeah
like lizards yeah, well, a lobster yeah
lot of water. Yeah, okay, a water. A lizard really is the water. It is a good idea.
A lizard. You just take the crisper drawer, but you could also fill it with
water. It doesn't go bad if it stays hot, right? Food doesn't go bad ever. You
can eat all food. Well, then never mind. Oh yeah, I guess if it stays hot like at
a buffet. Yeah, so we should go to a buffet this week. I really want to go to
Golden Corral, but you have to find a good one. Well, fine. Let's find a good
one. We'll look at reviews. Okay, there's a good Golden Corral. Shut the fuck up.
I think we got to go back to this golden crowd. We get a prime rib. Oh, we do have
to go back to Fogo de Chao. Can we go to Fogo de Chao? Dude, you're bleeding me
dry. You're bleeding me fucking dry. Wait, I can think of a really fucking
week. I can think of a really good opportunity to go to Fogo de Chao in two
weeks. Yeah, I can't say it.
Why? Oh my God, yes.
Whisper and they have a conference room there.
he said you're wearing headphones. I can't really tell okay here. I'll mute
everybody and say it really fast. Okay,
oh yeah and by the way, bad lip reading turn off the actual bad lip reading,
good lip reading, try your try your worst
doing bad lip reading with
bad lip reading, getting getting hired by the on guys to do all the the White
house like press conferences thing where they're talking off my all right.
Here's the next
food. Here's the next technology. This is a future technology that we will be
using for the next decade. Firewire, Firewire, Firewire cable transfers data
between digital devices, also called as I e e thirteen ninety four. This device
is transfer rate can be as fast as eight hundred megabytes per second. Firewire
was fast and fire. It is expected to increase up to nearly three point two
gigabytes per second in the future. Usually FireWire is a hub where nearly 63 devices
can be connected and the data can be transferred between the devices. This is supported by
all operating systems like Windows 98 and above, Mac 8.6 and above. Guys, this is a
cable of the future. FireWire. We miss you so much. We miss you. You did not have your
day in the sun. Way better. FireWire. They should have changed USB-C to FireWire. We
should start calling USB FireWire. Blazing fast speed. Alright guys, I have one more
future technology. All right, I'm excited world, the most futuristic technology of
all time. I have two slides on it. Go to it now.
Big wheel bicycle
and go to the next pick. It's a tractor tire. Oh my God, guys, this is big
wheel bicycle. I actually didn't even realize how big the wheel was till I
saw it next to a normal bike. Look at the fucking car. This wheel is bigger
than a truck than a van. Yeah, you seems like a large tractor. Oh my God,
bicycle. You could go anywhere on that. This has no caption. It speaks for
itself. Guys, big wheel bicycle 2030. Yeah. There used to be a guy in my
hometown in Wilmington who would ride around on all the busiest roads on a
double decker bike. Oh, yeah. What? Like two bike frames on top of each
other. There's somebody around here that does that. And it was so clear.
It was this one bike. It was green on the bottom, red on the top. It was
the same bike every single time, and it was the same guy every single time.
And then one day, it was a different guy riding the bike, which means that
I sold that bike to someone.
Someone bought it. That's crazy.
And then that guy kept riding that bike.
There's somebody around in this neighborhood.
I've seen his bike.
He has a double decker bike and it's chained up in front of his apartment.
(laughs)
It's like, "Dude, no one's fucking stealing that."
Here's my other story of a double decker bike.
Maybe the guy died riding the bike and in his will, he's like to his friend,
"I leave my double decker bike to my friend and I pray that he can carry on my memory."
That he can also die on this bike.
Well, yeah, imagine how pissed off you'd be if you get that bike gets left to you.
And you have to imagine you get hit on that thing.
Imagine a car like bumps you in the back.
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
It doubles. You go faster.
You get left that bike and in somebody's will.
First of all, you can't sell it because someone left it to you in the will.
Second of all, you can't sell it because who is buying a double decker bike?
Yeah, nobody is buying that clown.
A short, a double guy.
Yeah, a guy, Robert Wadlow, Siamese twin.
Yeah, they might buy it, but they might buy it.
Side to Siamese twins that are connected foot to shoulder to
Siamese twins who have two separate accounts on Facebook on Facebook.
They're messaging you on Facebook marketplace from two different chats.
You think they're competing with each other, but they're the same
until you realize that they're a tennis.
Do you see half of their head?
You see half of their heads at each photo, each profile photo.
So I think these might be $500 for this.
But you can tell somebody else.
The hell this guy has a very high shoulder.
Oh, that's his brother.
That's his brother's whole body.
That's his brother's entire body.
And he's just that.
That's all he has control over.
They're connected, like he has no feet because it's his brother's shoulder blades.
And they're connected foot to shoulder and they live in a house that like one of them
is sitting at their desk and the other one is like a desk wave.
That's awesome.
Is there any Siamese twins where maybe one of the, because one of them's always got it
worse.
The one who's got it worse is like on the bottom of the foot or on the ass cheek.
I think so, yeah. I don't think I've ever seen one.
I'm sure, I think that it may, it does make it to TV.
Basket cases.
Yeah, that's a parasitic twin, that happens too.
Well, that's also.
It's like a coato, maybe would be another reference point for someone who doesn't.
Coato.
From Total Recall.
Oh, right, right.
And also.
Malignant.
Malignant is another one.
Back of the head.
Professor Quirrell from Harry Potter.
Yes, well that's less of a, that's more of a spirit.
Yeah.
But it's on the back of his head.
Yeah, but it's more of a spirit.
It's still the same concept.
Conjoined twin and you're a fan of the show. It's not
Professor Quirrell was not like Voldemort my twin for real
He didn't think that
Well, if you're a conjoined twin, can we get them like a bike them something? I don't know
Why is there conjoined they have enough fucking stuff going they get free shit all the time
You think they get free refills? Yes
Yes
Exactly
Half Price movie tickets.
Imagine, imagine, imagine.
A conjoined twin walks into a restaurant and the guy's like, "Uh-uh, you're both paying, you're not sharing sodas. You're both paying for a soda."
It's only one stomach, but you taste it twice.
That's really tickling you.
I don't know why that's so funny to me. That's not that funny at all, but a guy being like, "You guys are not sharing anything here."
Kind of ableist.
Problematic.
You know that a lot of times it's conjoined twins.
I already told you 2024 is my fuck it year.
The parents have to make the choice to kill one of them basically.
And that's what you're joking about.
I already said just a second ago.
And they pass on very early in life.
Fuck all the bullshit.
And if one twin passes the other twin often passes as well shortly thereafter.
And you might think that it's some kind of physical reaction.
It's heartbreak. It's despair.
Guess what?
It's my fuck it year.
really sound it. I mean, yeah, it was very insensitive. So I'm being
insensitive. I was fuck it. I'm being insensitive. What do you think? What do
you think? When I can join join twin there, there are young can join twin
pair. One of them has finally one of them has hit the mental maturity age
where for Halloween they would like to dress as something funny, but the other
one still wants to or scary someone else. The other one still wants to dress as a
superhero that is and they're going to be reading and one of them has the flash
costume and the other one is dressed as a skeleton. Yeah, and they open it. Oh
good cause
that's really good. Yeah, that's really scary. You scared me for this is a good
costume. The flash getting chased by a skeleton. Oh wow
damn the Halloween costume game for being a conjoined twin would actually be
insane. Yeah, what why I mean you just get so I mean you think about how fun.
Oh yeah, just costume. Yeah, you could be the guys from stuff. You could there's
so many things you could do. I like conjoined twins. I like to play with
them. Yeah, I mean, if you are a conjoined twin fan of the show, Patrick
already said, we'll get we'll make a shirt for you. No, we'll make a shirt.
We'll make a shirt. You go ahead and try to make a shirt for them.
Come on, we will make a special. You cannot have picked a worse thing to
prom. What are you talking about? There's
something specifically for you. We'll make one shirt, but you have to share
it again. I'm not making too much.
You're not doing good with that. Okay.
I'm not doing good with that. What do you mean by that?
Guys, you're being offensive, man.
Any shows? Do you guys have shows coming up?
Yes, but I don't remember when or where.
That's fine. Just check Caleb's social media.
Either you're going to see a show plug or you're going to see some funny ass shit.
I'm somewhere in Florida.
I guess we should just plug all of our social medias individually.
I don't think so.
it's 1997 is my new to Instagram. That's not true. That's mine. I guess you're
fuck it. Shit man. Fuck you subscribe to the Patreon. I think I did a whole
that's not my last time, but guys at this year, it's going to pop off. It's
incredible. There's an incredible backlog. We got moving Mondays on there.
We got beers. We drank is back. I predicted that it would not come back,
but it has come back and
Patrick said he's going to do something. I recorded something new. New DND
campaign has just started as of Monday. It's a door back to the fantasy DND
Trebuchet votes on the $10 tier.
And the shareholders meeting will be this month as well,
that we didn't pick a date.
Do we want to pick a date right now, this very second?
We will pick a date and it will be January.
Don't say a date right now.
I don't say a date right now.
The.
I have to figure out when I'm actually going to do it.
January the.
All right.
Well, I think that's that's really all we got.
Thanks, everybody.
Happy technology.
That is one more thing to say.
And follow @Nibirutruth on Instagram.
*heavy breathing*
*boing*
*static*
If you were- if you existed back in the Neolithic times,
they would cast you out of the community and you would be eaten by a panther.
Because you would need to learn to think like the group.
Conformity is how you survive. It's part of human evolution.
And then there would never have been crust on pizza if I invented it,
so then it would be the best food ever.
They only had crust back then. They didn't invent the pizza part yet.
It was just circles of crust.
They had the wheel, they said "let's make this out of bread."
They mostly had crust.
And crust comes from the earth.
It comes from the grains, and they smash them up so that you can bake it with water.
Exactly. Crust comes from the earth. Cheese does not come from the earth.
Have you guys ever noticed how crust is wheel shaped and cheese comes in a wheel shape,
but the sauce doesn't? What's up with that?
Sauce comes in a wheel shape. Tomato is a wheel shape.
Tomato is a wheel shape.
Tomato is a wheel shape and so is the tomato sauce can.
And pepperonis, too.
And so is the can that the tomato sauce is in.
Will you guys let Caleb talk?
I just want to make a point. I'm not raising my hand.
Oh, you can't even see it.
Can I just drop it? Hold on.
Do you see this tiny little o-ring, Charles?
I want to talk to you about food waste.
Do you see this?
No, I don't.
This is the size of a pizza
in Africa.
And this can feed 30 families
for 30 nights.
And you're throwing away probably 50 of these
a worth of crust
Every single time that you don't need to go.
I'll ship my crust to them.
To Africa? That's insulting.
So now you're insulting Africa.
Ship your shit to Africa?
That's not even legal.
That's not okay.
Imagine you're a starving African child.
You said, Caleb said that there are people starving in Africa.
You said, okay, I'll send them my shit?
Yeah, crust.
I meant crust.
Imagine the crust he's eating.
Not even the whole shit? Just the crust of it?
No, just the pizza crust. You guys are so juvenile and immature on this show.
You want to insult a starving African child, the stendid belly, who opens up the only thing they've ever...
the only package of mail they've ever had, they open it up, it's not only your shit, it's just part of it?
They can tell it's scooped out.
This is... I've been so misrepresented here.
And also, like, your shit's gonna be crazy 'cause you don't eat the...
all you're eating is cheese and pepperonis. Your shit's gonna be all... it's gonna be liquid when they get there.
when they get there.
[MUSIC PLAYING]