(upbeat music)
- Lyle, Lyle, Crocodile.
The Crocodile himself is here in the building.
- What's up boys, how's it going?
How's life? - What's up you killer croc?
How are you?
- I'm doing good, man.
I love this set, I love this fish.
You guys have a really cool operation here.
- It used to be Christmas around here.
- You do all everything.
- It used to be Christmas everywhere, Patrick.
- Well, on the set.
That is true as well. On the set, it used to be Christmassy. You do a digital set.
Yeah, I do. Well, it's crazy that you guys have like three cameras and five. It's
just me and a camera that sometimes works. And you're 40 times more successful.
Well, I don't know. That's tough for us to hear. Maybe don't tell us about how
bare-boned. Oh yeah, I'm nothing. Yeah, no, don't do that to us, man. No, this is
really cool. I love that you have a guy who sounds like Jigsaw that's...
Jigsaw out there in Mexico doing his thing, man. Say hello, Julio. You don't have a producer?
Hello, Julio.
I have somebody who helps me edit the podcast after the fact.
But nobody live doing all this.
You don't have a Jamie.
No, like when somebody...
We need a Jamie.
Everybody needs a Jamie.
The Jamie was a giant change for us.
Really?
Yeah, because now we can say if we don't remember something or we don't remember what somebody
it looks like Google pig in the farm. You know something like that, like oh,
here's a pig in the farm. We need oh, we need a photo. What does a pig in a farm
look like? Well, why does this hold your horses pig in the far cry for the far
cry?
He pulls up our cry for pig hunting where to find pigs for upgrade. So you
actually quiver more in the game. He's not all that good at the job. I would
say, well, I mean, there's the pigs. He did it. He did find he's an expert. How
How are you liking New York City so far?
New York is awesome, man. I was really stoked and happy the first week I came here because
I sold my car and stuff. The honeymoon phase has kind of ended.
It's over.
Yeah, it's like this is my life now.
Have people started being mean to you?
First question, do you walk around wearing this?
Not yet. I want to. It's too cold.
Do you think about going to Times Square hanging out with Elmo in the gecko costume?
I walked around... You could be Geico. Oh, snap. I walked around Las Vegas once in
the costume and this 12 year old kid came up to me and he showed me on his
phone that he had listened to all of my podcasts and then we took a picture
and then his mom came up behind him and tried to give me $5.
And I was like, "You don't have to do that." It's not one of those.
What a mark that lady is, Jesus Christ. We've never gotten a 12 year old.
No, I would say our audience on a Caleb goal.
We just need one. There's a one pick with a twelve year old because they'll
start going to school, spreading it around among all the other people
looking at different toilets or the toilet videos. What did you guys like?
Did you guys listen to podcasts when you were twelve or I'm sure you had like
YouTube or so you well with I used to be a big fan of you made it weird with
Pete home. Yeah, me too. Yeah, really yeah me too yeah, so I used to listen to
that when I was a kid and I would play Halo and I would do that was home
homeschooled, so I'd do that instead of learning. Really? Yeah, so I would do that pretty much
every day when I was a kid. And then I grew up and now it's not really my thing. How long
were you homeschooled for? Seventh grade all through high school. I have a friend who's
homeschooled and he mentioned... Now? Yeah. I'm friends with a... No, I have a friend
who, he was homeschooled. Okay. And he talks about how he feels too normal for the homeschooling
normal for the home schooled people, but to home schooled for the normal people
that you ever feel that I don't really at all blade. No, I was I was fully
homeschooled. I loved being in home school really. What was what you like
about it? No fucking school.
Did you were you not were you like were you lonely? Were you not? Hell no,
really? I had movies
and YouTube videos. Yeah, I guess this shit was amazing. That's cool, and then
I had to go to college. All of a sudden you're walking in and you have books. Oh
my God pencils. What are they? I really didn't know how to use them. I wasn't
even the kind of home school kid who gets good at something like I didn't. I
wasn't like
getting good at art, but that doesn't really ever happen. Well, the spelling
be there's one kid who was home schooled and destroyed the spelling instant
instantly. You've been proven wrong now. Nine percent of schooled kids and yes
schooled. I'm not because the home school is unschooled. Well, there's no.
That's a third thing are beating.
Well, the numbers don't matter, but the point is that it's smarter. What was
was your was it like a religious thing for you? Was it was it a teacher or was
it your your mom? I got in
with the thugs at my school and I was a I was I was what we call a future thug
really yeah. So I got pulled out because of the thug stuff that I was doing.
He ran over a teacher with a car. Yeah, it's not yeah. I did a lot of really
bad stuff and then my mom was I was getting suspended and I was on the verge
getting expelled and my mom was like we're taking you out of school. You got
I thought it was sick.
He was hanging out at a rival. I was hanging out at a rival. I was spreading.
I was like you don't even have lunch at our school. I was giving them the
football plays doing sort of very discreet handoffs, and so I just ended up
being taken out of school. You're given the sheet music for the and then I went
from this is a very rare. Well, I guess it's not that rare. I went from thug to
nerd
like
Today, do you still feel as though there's any thug remaining within you?
I pray for your sake, you don't find out.
I pray for you. I'm a de-escalation gecko now. Yeah, you don't wanna test
my gangster as it were, yeah, because it bites. Do you guys ever imagine
the situation? Well, I'm sure you do when you get mugged and what you would
do.
I think about this more than anything in the world. I had a new scenario
I came up with yesterday, okay, and this is if you're getting you're getting
mugged and you're just going next door to get some food. You didn't even bring
your wallet because you're going to pay with apple pay yeah and I was thinking
about this when I was going to get some food across the street. I thought well
someone comes up to me and tries to mug me because you know it's seven o'clock.
Yeah, the muggers are out. The muggers are out. They just I would just I would
be like charged. I would be like man seriously. I don't have my wallet on me.
I'm just getting food across the street with apple pay, but if you want I'll go
into my apartment and get my wallet
going, lock the door, all the police he would come into the apartment with you
I would be like I don't want you to come in because my girlfriend is home.
Have you guys ever gotten mugged before?
No, I've never been mugged and I know that because of that, it will be the end
of my life when it happens.
I have this like I've never been mugged before and I have this thing in my head
and I'm like there's no way I'm getting through life without the happening.
Because I've never been mugged, I'm building it up so much in my head with
all these scenarios and strategies that I will get stabbed.
Yeah, I will say there will be one word out of my mouth. They'll be like
give me your wall like well and then you'll be cycling through the dialogue
branch. Where do I go from here? I
this guy's already dying. Obviously, he's having so you'll actually you'll die
of natural causes thinking of what to do. Yeah, just trying to just trying to
do every every strategy at the same time of like just going like like a
deaf. Well, I have cancer and also I'm gay and then trying to make myself
throw up.
I've had I've had the fantasy that I would like appeal to the mugger
emotionally. I would look at him and I'd be like, Hey man, that's what I always
think. You know, what's going on? You don't need to do this. Yeah, but that's
not what would happen a lot. The way I would actually get stabbed is that
they would mug me and I'd have like two ten dollar bills in my wallet and I'd
try to give them one
getting mugged.
What I would do
immediately looking at the guy and just going.
I also think if I asked for my phone, I would probably go really, really man.
that's the one thing that like they really can't take anymore, because you
can just like
they have programmed the phones to be mug proof. You can know if you're not
your eye. There is a there is a bushwick bandit who really going around on a
bicycle or a motorized one bicycle, a bushwick bicycle band. It's been going
to people showing them a gun and saying give me your money when they don't have
money. He says come with me. He goes into stores will go into like dispensaries or
GameStop, he'll buy an X box with their Apple pay or they will and then he'll
leave and he does not kill. Why not just tell the one I just stop it? Yeah,
kill that's nice. Why don't you just stop him? That's my that's a good. See
that's what this is exactly the scenario. I need to be theory crafting
for yeah. This is what because I'm I'm you know still stuck on a guy shows me
a knife and says give me your money, but what do I do when he asked me to buy an
X box? Yeah, I know man. I don't game each. I don't have time. I would go in
to the game stop, I would be in there for about split it five seconds. I'd walk
out and I said they don't have x box man.
Well, I'm going to go
three sixty. Well, here's what you do. You spend the amount of money
you didn't want stick of truth.
I don't get it. That is a really good game. I would I hope you want it. I
think the thing that you're supposed to do is you're supposed to look at them
and say I've been waiting for this for a long time and then, when they say,
what do you mean you run away? I also think that's another confusion. I
one hundred percent someone tries to bug me, there's a good chance I will just
try and sprint away. I think there's a good chance I would do something really
offensive to get out of it, and so I just don't want to be put in that
situation. When I was a kid, I used to think like if I just like acted crazy,
yeah, I would be like, whoa, this guy's nuts. Yeah, I don't want his money. I
probably as crazy
as gonna
really is crazy.
It doesn't work in America. This guy's crazy. He probably only has coins on
it. Probably does a monopoly.
You walk around with the
walk around with a little bit of monopoly. Oh, you want to mug me?
Look how crazy I am. I have
it's all money that has your own face on it. Yeah, Caleb coin. Here you go.
You can only a hundred million dollars. You can only buy stuff at my house with
this. Yeah, I'm really gonna and then you have a little closet where you have
like red vines and skin. Oh, my God, I just thought
I just thought of an incredible satirical, idiocracy style thing to do.
oh, bloody hell, they come to muggy. You say sorry man, I don't have any cash.
You got a card reader. Oh, that would be the thing is with this current. They
probably world they probably would they would and you would have to tip yeah
exactly.
They say how much is it to be like I'm tipping a hundred percent of the
fucking mugging
and shits. Bullshit. Yeah, the mugging tip percents are a hundred percent, a
hundred fifty percent of two hundred. I've been falling into this trap a lot
recently. They mugged two fifty, two fifty for a cup of coffee. They flip the
thing, how much you want to tip? I don't know, $2. I'm paying five bucks for one
cup of coffee now just because this fucking piece of shit wants money.
What the hell is that?
It's fucking killing me. It is destroying this country. Yeah, we need to get rid
of tipping. Yeah, we need to get rid of tipping. How do they do that in the
other countries where they don't have tips? Yeah, I don't think that they
don't really have tipping in like Europe and Australia. Yeah, do you just make
everybody just poor? Isn't it like... Sounds like they actually pay the people
and the way yeah, okay, well that's definitely not the solution. We
can't be doing that. I think if they in German class, they told me that if
you do tip more than like 20% or something, if you don't leave just like
a dollar coin or something, they get like offended, which I think is not
true. This is invented because this can't be true. Mexico when I was in
Mexico and they don't they don't tip there really well, they do like but
it's well, maybe Julio could speak to this, I guess, but they don't really
normally tip, but it's just like you just weren't tipping. Well, no, I was
we were tip every time and every time we tipped, they would always be like
oh my God, thank you so much like it was like to the part like you have to
stop. This is not okay. I can't be much everyone is looking at us. Maybe it's
like nobody tips your son.
Probably did that's maybe why nobody tips there because they're too grateful
yeah and it's a little embarrassing. You get a little here's a cheat code.
You live in a country where they tipping is not the norm. All you have to do is
move to a tourist city where Americans are going to come and tip you true and
you're going to make twice as much money. That's and then you act all offended or
whatever. Yeah. These are money hacks. Money hacks. Have you traveled
internationally? Yeah, I did. I went to Mexico City, went to all over Australia
and Europe. Were you doing shows there? Yeah, I was doing shows. Not in Mexico.
I did one show in Japan, which was fun. Oh, that's... Wow. Yeah, there was
40 people there, maybe, but... That's pretty impressive for Japan. It was
pretty cool. Dude, there was like... Most of them were expats, but there
were four or five actual Japanese people there who just found the podcast
from the computer and stuff.
That is sick.
Have you guys done shows internationally?
No.
No, we're hoping to, but we gotta get passports.
Do a lot of international folks listen to this?
We don't know.
Millions and millions.
Dude, I get "come to Brazil" a lot.
That's a threat.
Well, no, I get "come to Brazil" and I'm like, "you guys are..." and then I'll see a comment
that says "come to Brazil" and I'll click the profile and it'll say that they live in
Brazil and I'm like, "fuck, maybe I should come to Brazil, they're not just fucking with
me."
is that you go to Brazil when people say that
and then they wanna be mean to you.
- Like chop up your body?
- Yeah, something like that.
Would you do a show in Brazil?
- Yeah, that'd be sick. - Would you do a show
if you knew they were gonna chop you up afterwards?
- Would I do a show if I knew
they were gonna chop me up afterwards?
I'm open to any and all new experiences.
- Okay, well, with that in mind,
what if they kept you alive as they chopped you up
so you felt every chop and you couldn't die?
- Well, I don't know.
I have certain status tendencies.
Well, let's just let's I mean let's strip the hypothetical question just down to
the bare essentials. Would you get chopped up? Would I get chopped up? That
sounds like a euphemism for something else.
Just into pieces, yeah, just little. Would you get chopped into pieces?
Chunks, chunks. Well, no, I actually, actually I would because there's
strength in numbers, and if there were more and more of you,
I could. If you're a gecko, you can. Oh, you're a gecko. Exactly, I'm a gecko.
So I could, they would all, like, just become their own little mini me's, and
and I could go and-- - A million little wiles
walking around.
- You know, I could be more productive.
- And then you can do all your tours,
you book a tour, you do the whole thing in one day.
- You do the whole thing in one day!
- The same time!
- One fucking day you do the tour,
'cause you have a bunch of mini-yous,
and each of them is--
- God, that's such a funny idea to book a tour
where every show's on the same day at the same time.
- Wait, actually, you know how like MF Doom
used to do that thing where they get imposters?
That would be kinda sick to put on,
a bunch of shows have an imposter doing a show.
- It's a roulette.
- One of them's gonna be real.
we the real one. I just invented guys what Mormonism God damn it. That's what
they do in Mormon temple. God fucking all do the same thing at the same is
that true? I think so. I was told that before maybe it's not true. I was told
they do every church do it at the same time. Well, I think they have to like
the same day at the same like script yeah. Oh really, well again I someone
told me that I could be where are you from from Baltimore? You're from
Baltimore.
I'm from New Hampshire.
Oh, okay.
From Massachusetts.
Okay.
North Carolina, man.
East Coast boys.
All East Coast.
All East Coast all the time.
All East Coast all the way down the line.
Have you guys been to Baltimore?
Yeah.
Yes, I have been to Baltimore.
What'd you do?
I was on the news there.
I drove around on it.
What were you on the news for?
I was on the news with our friends Girl God and they were asking me about a viral carrot
hack.
Yep.
And he said one of the most legendary lines in all of news history.
That's worthy of being pulled up.
Yeah, I don't know if we can find this line, but Patrick says and I quote, I
can't eat carrots. I'm allergic to carrots. This is the one line that I'm
not in. Okay, this is the one. We're not gonna be able to find this clip.
Yeah, they used my high school photo as a headshot. He says it like this.
Yeah, I can't eat carrots. I'm allergic to carrots. The only line I think I
said on the news. And that was the first TV appearance from anybody on the
podcast, and that is probably gonna be the only one. Yeah. And so it's gonna
a lasting legacy for us.
Oh, it's relatable. There's somebody else who has an allergy to carrots who's like, "I can
see myself in this man."
Yeah, exactly. Maybe I'll check out his podcast.
Representation.
How do you like Baltimore?
Baltimore's fine. It's not like... I enjoyed growing up there, but I wouldn't want to live
there.
Okay. Did you eat crabs every day?
I love the crab chip.
That's a good one.
It's a good chip.
It's a little bit kind of Old Bay.
Yeah, Old Bay is good. I love Old Bay.
Drug trade.
- For a drug trade? - Drug trade from the shows.
- Oh, hey man, I can't give out too much information
about my involvement in the Baltimore City drug trade.
- Don't worry about it, there's plenty of flyer up.
- Yeah, well, we'll do that.
I hate soliciting so much that I really,
we need to get a gun for the office
'cause this can't stand any longer.
- You guys ever shot a gun before?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, when you were 13.
- Come on, yeah, I think the last time I shot a gun,
I was like 14 and it was like a,
I think it was an MP5 and it was not a legal type of gun.
And we would just, we would go to the,
my brother worked at a paintball field
and we would wait till everybody left
and then we would just shoot guns
into all the like trees and shit.
And it was fun.
- My friends and I used to play with Airsoft a lot
and we found out that the Airsoft gun hurt enough
that you could kind of use it like a real gun
in that you could use it to force people to do things.
- Yes, that is true.
- Like you could point your fucking Airsoft gun at somebody
and be like, get on the ground right now
and they'll do it because they don't want you to.
- It does, it works good.
- It works the same way as a real gun.
yeah, I never liked any that was a thing everybody. I knew like paintball
growing up and I would play it and you go home, you're covered in bruises.
Even if you win, you have bruises on you, it should be the loser who gets
bruises right. They line them all up. Yeah, exactly the winner. You shouldn't
have. Oh yeah, you shouldn't be walking home feeling like physically bad. I
should never feel bad. That's what I'm saying. Have you guys ever got shot
with like an like a like a red rider BB gun? Oh no, I got shot by an airsoft
though. Yeah, like a metal BB. No, I don't think so. They can get stuck in you.
Do you guys remember when the AR-15, like I associated it with Call of Duty
instead of mass shootings? Yes, that was... Well, there was one in the game
though.
Which one? There was a mass shooting in the game. Oh, there was a mass
shooting, oh, like Call of Duty 4. Yeah, so even when I felt that it was
a Call of Duty gun, I saw the tide kind of creeping up.
right history yeah and so if you guys don't know Lyle Lyle does a show called
therapy gecko be gecko where you are live taking live taking calls from
anonymous strangers on the phone here's my yeah I have I don't know if anyone's
ever asked you this is anyone ever called and made like a fart sound into
the thing yeah people called and made fart sounds and clean sounds and we've
so how do you do it for a year I mean you gotta have a trained ear yeah so
You've gotten so many of these calls.
(laughing)
- Gets all the farts in the kid.
- Even from the first millisecond.
- I have two folders in my Google Drive.
- So you save them.
So what are you saving all these sounds for?
- What am I saving the fart and cleef sounds for?
I'm gonna make a cool song with them.
- Oh, okay, that sounds good.
- Put them on a sampler keyboard.
- What's the worst thing that anyone's ever called
and said into your show?
Prank style. - The worst thing.
Oh, prank style?
Jesus, man, I don't know.
Well, I had a guy very since,
He very earnestly called me to tell me about how he had a small penis.
And so for about 15 minutes, I was really...
Keeping it together.
Really, really earnestly, like trying to talk him through his
low self-esteem as a result of having a small penis.
And I really felt like we kind of connected in this way,
not saying that I have a small penis, but we just connected...
That there was something.
Right.
In this way.
And then at the very end, he goes, "I'm just kidding.
My dick is huge and you're a dumbass."
And then he called it.
and that
that just really hurt my feelings, 'cause yeah, so first of all, you got
destroyed.
I took the, no, no, I took the bait, but
well, here's the thing, as like, if I had told him he was fucking with
me,
then what if he really did it? What if he really did have a small
penis? He would have killed himself. And then he leaves feeling sad. I'd
rather I leave feeling like I... His life's already so bad. Yeah, can you
imagine you call, you're like, "God, I've struggled with this self esteem
based on my small penis my entire life. I don't know where to turn anymore.
I'm going to try calling my favorite pot.
That sounds fucking stupid and fake.
I guess that would be bad. Most people like I get calls about a lot of like
weird stuff and most people in the comments are like this is fake and
stupid, but I, I, I might, I think like a smaller percent of stuff is fake and
stupid. I generally believe I say I go into a believing thing. Has anyone ever
called and you recognize the voice and it's a celebrity?
Gilbert Gottfried or somebody like this. Yeah. Somebody with a really
recognizable voice. Yeah, I had someone who was doing a Scooby-Doo impression.
You had Scooby-Doo? Scooby-Doo. You assume it's an impression, but I'm
sure it could have been Scooby. I mean, no, Scooby-Doo's seen some shit.
Yeah. He's seen ghosts. He literally knows ghosts are real. He's also really
a food addict. Wait, hold on. Okay, wait. Actually, so in Scooby-Doo, isn't
the whole thing that ghosts are not real? 'Cause at the end, they like...
the original, whatever any kind of supernatural element is then revealed
to just be like a mailman. At least aliens are 100% real. Aliens are 100%
real. That's the last episode of Scooby Doo is that Scooby Doo takes off his
mask.
A really bad dog impression. Dogs can talk.
Doing a very bad dog impression. You guys believe dogs can talk?
So you like what you do? Sometimes, sometimes. This documentary just came
about me on Vice that were, and I went into it wanting to like, be honest about like my own,
like, mental health struggles and whatnot. But I watched it and I was like, Oh, fuck,
is my is my life sad? And I do like what I do sometimes, but sometimes like, like, like what
you guys are doing, like, this is like a just a light hearted riff. roast is fun. Like, do you
Do you walk out of this being like energized?
- Well, sometimes we hurt each other's feeling.
- It gets really, really rough sometimes.
- We get nasty at each other.
- Sometimes we will realize that we said something
that we've already said before, which really...
(laughing)
- How long have you all been friends?
- It's basically the exact same time as we've done the podcast.
(laughing)
- So tell me if the podcast is over,
you guys are just never gonna see each other again.
- No question. - No, definitely.
- No. - Yeah.
- Wait, are you trying to psychoanalyze me, you bastard?
I'm just asking questions. What kind of fucking droid witchcraft are you doing in this gecko suit?
Oh my God, this is the way people... I'll be talking to people... This happens to me in my real life.
I'll just be talking to somebody and I just ask them something and they'll be like,
"Are you doing your therapy thing on me right now?"
Are you a classically trained psychoanalyst?
No, I'm a crazy person.
What'd you go to... Oh, okay.
I went to film school in Philadelphia.
Oh, okay.
The same type of thing always happens to us. We'll be talking to people in our personal lives
and they're always like, "Are you trying to make a list out of me?"
Yeah, you're trying to listen to me right now. Do you guys like what you do?
Yeah, yeah, I mean I do so many things.
Yeah, I definitely do a lot of other stuff. Yeah, it's not my only thing. I
don't know what things do you do? I'm a future artist. Just kind of bond
Vivant stuff. Cool. Yeah, all types of bond Vivant type of things. Three times
a day. I cook a lot times a day. One time a day. Yeah, cook cooking. Yeah,
I actually do cook a lot.
I am.
I'm on, I'm going to give a free shout out to the Factor Meal Plan.
I'm on those meal plans.
I hate fucking cooking.
Don't tell me you have a code.
I'm not giving out a code.
Do not give out a code right now.
No, no, no, no, it's not a code.
I don't even sponsor the fucking thing.
You do the meal plans?
That's what you're trying to do.
I do the meal plans.
Here's my question about this.
You're going to hear this give you a code?
What happens when you get these meal plans and then you're like, "Oh, I'm in the mood
for spaghetti."
And then they give it to you and it's some bullshit fucking stupid ass salad.
If you're a good enough chef, you can literally turn the ingredients of salad
into spaghetti. But
you break it down to all the molecules and you put them back together. I guess
if you are really good at cooking, you could do that. You could do that. That's
a YouTube video right there. I made spaghetti out of salad. Yeah, isn't it?
You will see that on your YouTube page. Isn't that all
molecular gastronomy is? It's like, "Oh yeah, we turn this tomato into an apple."
That's alchemy. Yeah. You're thinking about it. No. You guys know so many
things. Yeah, molecular gastronomy. This is the kind of stuff that we talk about here
a lot. So you like this factor meal plan thing? I do. I'm trying to... Alright, so part of
this... I watched this documentary about me being sad. Is that what we're so sad about?
Is that you're eating out of these plastic bins? No, it's been a happy thing of my life
because normally I'm like... I've been on a crazy binge this... I was like... That's
my thing is binge eating. And so I was waking up at 3 AM and going to the bodega and drinking
a Yoo-Hoo, but I was romanticizing it like I was doing heroin in the rain.
The Yoo-Hoo.
That felt good, yeah.
No, well, it felt good, I guess, in the way that heroin feels good.
So very good.
So great.
Yeah, extremely, extremely good.
It's the number one thing.
By the way, just to, like, because this is something I want to debunk, a lot of people
think the Yoo-Hoo is chocolate milk.
It's not.
It's a chocolate drink.
It's water.
It's water, yeah.
Chocolate water.
Although there is milk in it as a...
Yeah, you gotta get the milk.
Yeah, there's milk allergen.
You gotta get the milk to get the chocolate.
Or the other way around.
Chocolate from a bean, my friend.
There's a cookies and cream Yoohoo that I'm hesitant
to try because I think it'll ruin my life.
Like, you'll get hooked to this new
Yoohoo. Yeah.
You're in good company, we've all had
some level of candy addiction.
What's your guys' stuff?
Him is everything.
All candy. He loses all his teeth everyday
because he eats so much candy.
He's cracked his teeth on candy.
tooth on a, it was either a gummy worm or some kind of hard gum.
How do you crack your tooth on a gummy worm? It was bad, it was bad,
it was one of those hard gum. It was like on the bottom of a,
it was like on a car's carpet on the ground. He normally has a candy
problem 'cause he gets the types of candies that have like four adjectives
in the name. Yeah. He's like, he's not satisfied with gummy worms.
He's gotta get the very, very super sour crawlers. Yeah. Have you had the
crunchy crawlers? No. Have you guys ever had Nerds Gummy Clusters? Oh,
yeah. I've never liked the little Nerds Gummy Clusters. You guys ever seen
Jimmy Neutron. They're like, it's the candy from Jimmy Neutron.
It's so fucking good.
They're really good. I had to stop eating candy.
So I'm pretty much off of candy, except for the other day.
I had the new Churros Kit Kat.
I just remembered this.
He says new. He knows when they come out.
That's what I mean.
Well, you read the trades.
What it was is I saw the Kit Kat there and I was like, well,
that is a new flavor. I have to try it.
And it was churro and it was, I'm going to be honest, not even worth it.
Every morning, it was not worth breaking edge on candy. Every morning you take
the newspaper, you like unfurl and you go to the candy.
Let's see what is horrible doing. So the factor has gotten you off the you who
somewhat. Some somewhat just like having a routine of some kind. That's my new
thing. I'm trying to figure out how to
well see. This is the thing about therapy. Gecko is that ultimately it is
the story of Polly. Achi the clown where I'm like, how do I'm trying to figure
out how to be happy and exist as a person. And so I'm like, "All right, maybe the
first step is to not drink Yoo-Hoo's at 3 a.m." And then I'm like, "How do I...
Now I'm trying to get into that, you know, so...
The sugar rush.
Yeah, so I'm on a bit of a spiritual journey.
These days, that...
Well, these days, the sugar makes you happy, though.
Yeah.
These days, that whole clown nonsense...
They do.
That's the premise of Willy Wonka.
Well, that's true.
Did you guys see the Wonka movie?
Not yet.
No, my wife did.
Okay, it sucked.
Yeah, I heard it was really good.
It's terrible. I re-watched the 2006 Willy Wonka movie, It Rocks.
With Depp.
Yeah, with Depp.
I mean, also, by the way, they don't give a fuck about it.
I like that Willy Wonka because he, like the new Willy Wonka is kind of like a dope, but
this, the Johnny Depp one, he hates children.
And he's mean to all the kids.
And it's way funnier.
This is his origin.
I hear the new one is Woker.
Oh, shit.
No way.
Willy Woka or something.
Oh, my God.
They drop a slur in the fucking, in the 2006 one.
Oh, yeah, sure.
They were cussing about it.
It's so funny.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
Yeah, sure. They were it's so funny. They when they're they're
woke fying the the new Willy Wonka. Then they're like, how do we how do we fix
how do we fix the Oompa Loompas? How do we make this not Willy Wonka having a
bunch of jungle slaves? Yeah. And then it's that they put you grant small and
he's like, my God, I can't believe you've
just that they still as a slave. But now it's a quippy
Isn't it? Well, he has multiples of there's a lot of stuff. I don't know,
man. I didn't see it. Do we have a Wonka expert that can call it?
Trailer that he catches Hugh Grant in a glass thing like a cockroach.
He catches him. Yeah, he catches him. There's only one of them. That's,
I think the thing about the Willy, the Oompa Loompas as cool as that.
They're a bunch of little guys. I don't care that there's just one.
He only had one Oompa Loompa in the new one.
Only one Oompa Loompa. Sometime between the prequel and the,
and the original he's the Hugh Grant Oompa Loompa is fucking.
Yeah, he's a sexually reproducing. Yeah, a pipe. What is it like when a person is
a sexually laying pipe on them?
Isn't it strange that
they're all guys? Yeah. How do they make new ones? Well, again, that's the
wokeness of the thing. Let me tell you, they don't show you the girl Oompa
Loompas because it's a kid's movie. True, and they'd be bad as fuck.
crazy. It's something I could only dream of and orange as well. Yeah, wait is
you orange in the movie? Yeah, orange with green on top. He has his orange
hue. He looks like an orange hue. Yeah, so there we go. That's why. That's why
they got him. Hue green. Yeah, hue green and orange.
They could have made a million different types of hue. They did. It's called
Oompa Loompas. No, no, in different hues. In different hues, they could have
made a movie of Hugh Grant as different colors. Oh my God, it could be called
Seven Hughes. It could be called the Seven Hughes, exactly. And it's Hugh Grant,
Purple Hugh Grant, Red Hugh Grant. But they all have different powers and
abilities. But what if you don't know anything in a movie, they have to do
something. What are you doing with just a bunch of people saving your colors?
Somebody's stealing colors from the world. Exactly. We were gonna watch a
movie exactly that was the plot of this. Nobody does anything, right? Really.
Well, there's... You know what I just watch? I just watch this movie sideways.
I'd never seen this movie before. Oh, that's... Oh, wait, I keep confusing
sideways with the one about heroin. There's one about wine is one about
heroin. This is really good guys. This movie is about wine and I went home and
I had a glass of wine well and I did I put my nose in it and I just smelled
like piss to me. Yeah, I still drink it always smells bad. It did. I didn't like
it. I don't think I can get into wine. I think wine is going away. I've yeah, I
heard wine is declined. It feels ancient.
It feels so ancient to drink wine. You feel it's kind of does week. It's desert
you drink it out of a some organ. I like beer. Wine is going to go the way of
mead and flagons. Yes, it'll be gone very, very. We're not going to see someone
will see a wine glass and think, oh, what am I in a castle? Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Do you like drinking? I do.
It's not my it's not my main vice, though. It's not my name, but yeah, you
who
I like to drink. I'm trying to I drink an entire by I got my latest like I
think
big binge was I drank an entire bottle of like it was a chocolatey liquor. Oh,
yeah, don't tell me you just drank Bailey's by itself. I drank Bailey's by
itself. Yeah, you mix it with you. Yeah, dude. No,
I drank a whole fucking bottle of Bailey's the next morning. I'm like, I
gotta get on the factor meal plan.
That's like my, that's, that knocks two things out of the way right at once. It
gets your chocolate and your liquor. Yeah, yeah, it's ultimate sin. It's much
better than, you know, drinking a handle of vodka and then eating a chocolate
bar.
That also sounds pretty awesome. Yeah. That sounds amazing. Do you like, do you
like... Actually, no, it was horchata. Oh, rum chata. Rum chata. Rum chata.
Rum chata. Rum chata. Yeah. That's better than Bailey's, I think. Yeah. Yeah.
'Cause Bailey's is like a... It's a thick syrup. Bailey's is a cream. Yeah.
Drinking a whole can of Bailey's. Just add the bottle. Really funny. In a
paper bag on the stoop, drinking the Bailey's. When I was a kid, I used
I used to think, because they have those little Irish Bailey's chocolates, I used to think
you could get drunk from just eating the fucking chocolates.
We were trying to figure out if there were alcohol edibles and then we tried to make
an alcoholic beef stew on this show.
Yeah, and it was a fail.
It was really bad.
You guys have had vodka gummy bears?
No.
That was something from high school.
Oh, wait a minute, yeah, where you put them in the thing of vodka and then they absorb
everything.
Yeah.
I remember those, yeah.
I never had one that was done right.
I always had them when they were still sitting in the pool, the ratio was off, and then the
gummy bears just became this sticky goo. It never worked. But I tried one and it didn't
even get me drunk.
I've had a chocolate ball that had whiskey inside of the ball.
Infused?
No, like a liquid whiskey in the ball.
Like a Wonderball with whiskey.
Yeah, and it was disgusting.
I can imagine.
It was fucking disgusting. It was like $10 for three of them. It was not a good candy.
I think that alcohol... I love alcohol.
- You should not mix. - Keep it in a cup, man.
- Yeah. - What's your ultimate vice?
What gets you?
- My ultimate vice thus far has been every single one
at different points in time.
- Yeah. - Really?
- Yeah, so now I'm kind of on the nicotine pouch.
- Oh, the zincs?
- Very close, the zen.
- The zen, I took one of those and it made me,
I feel like the buzz goes away after a while.
- Oh, yeah. - And that's why
you just do more of it.
And this is kind of how you form a dependency on it.
Yeah, so it's really amazing. Now my wife got on and now she's trying to quit.
Do you really have a wife?
Yeah, I'm really married.
Okay, cool.
She's trying to quit and now she's saying she can't see the tin in the fucking house.
And so now I'm hiding it. Now I feel dirty.
You gotta get the rewards.
Yeah, and she's like, "Well, you could just quit."
The hiding of it, doesn't that give you even a bigger rush?
Bigger thrill, yeah.
Well, now that I've recontextualized it, perhaps it will.
Now that I'm hiding, but then she's always going to be like, "What are you hiding?"
drinking and then I'm going to have to make up of some kind of
it's all to its hours. I have
I have a I have them still yeah and I'm going to have to develop a real drug
problem so that I can hide the sin in the make it. I've been having to come to
terms recently that I feel I've had I've had my vices in the past of TV and
eating candy and gaming and wasting what time and whatever way, but I think truly
right now my vice is literally actually simply sitting on the couch and doing
nothing. This is my main my biggest struggle right now. That's not a vice.
That's meditation. It's not the way
no zero nothing behind the eyes. Yeah, full becoming a piece of furniture.
Yes, can't move. That sounds like good. That sounds like how you do
meditation. Well, no, because are you watching? I've seen him. He's too lazy
to get the remote. You're really actually really doing nothing. Maybe
sometimes I'm on my phone, but sometimes I am just sitting there man. That's
Yeah, that's, actually I do think that's good.
I have a vice that I have been doing only in the winter.
What is that?
Where it gets so cold in my apartment that I will take my wife's hair dryer and I'll
sit in the bed and I'll just blow my entire body.
And she comes in and she says, "What the fuck are you doing?
You're bald."
And I say, "Shut up."
I'm growing one hair.
Yeah, I'm growing one, my hair got wet.
My one hair got wet, my big baby hair.
I think all my vices are normal stuff.
Candy and skateboarding.
alcohol, tobacco, gambling. Dude, I'm trying so hard to have an alcohol vice.
I just can't do it, man. Yeah. Fall asleep. You have to go and get stuff.
I wanna have a margarita every night of my life for the rest of my
life. But then you fall asleep when you do it. It makes me fall
asleep. Yeah. This is where you need to... 'Cause there's so much effort
that's put into making it that once you have... It's easy to make. Just
power through, man. Why are you being such a bitch? Yeah. Just power through,
drink 10 in one night and then you'll be able to drink five every night.
Come on Cameron, you can do it.
I'm going to do it.
Drink 15 tequila sodas in one night.
Cameron, I think you should do what feels right to you.
It feels so right to me.
Here you come with this bullshit again.
That's all I can do.
God damn it man.
How about you sit, look him in the eye and say, I know you meathead.
You know what feels right to me?
It's the current US government.
There we go.
Thank you.
Do you get political on your show?
All the time.
We always talk about, you know.
Are you sick of this bull crap up in Washington or what?
What you mean?
The down in Washington with the swamp?
The public transportation issues?
Well basically the whole damn thing.
Here's my one question.
Nuclear bomb Washington DC, yes or no?
Blow the whole thing up.
Start over.
That wouldn't be like a...
You know how people are upset about global warming and how the Earth's gonna die?
I guess they're upset.
Is it that...
Well the Earth's gonna be fine but humans are gonna die but is that that bad that everyone
dies?
I think it's everything dies.
Yeah, well, no, I don't think it's everything.
Oh, my God,
life evolves. I've learned this even though I was homeschooled, right? And I
wasn't allowed to learn this, but now I've learned this. And so what we're
just gonna get the world's gonna get hotter, we will get. Do you know what?
You know, it's crazy. I was reading. I was reading about well, I was really
getting interested in trying to go to the place where they did the Castle
Bravo nuclear test because you can go there. Yes, it's in the it's the bikini
at all a toll at all a toll bottom a toll. You can go there, you can fully go
there and you can go scuba diving and you can look at like wrecks of ships from
the nuclear test and stuff yeah and it's crazy and the crazy thing is I don't
understand how this can be possible that they say it's it's safe to go there. You
can go there, but do not eat anything from there. How can that be okay? If
there's a place where you can't eat anything that's there, how can you be
staying there. How did that stuff?
It was there
swimming there yeah, their fish, they're going to keep swimming. They could go
anywhere in the ocean. Well, that's true that scares me. That's horrifying yeah,
it's not that scary to me. I don't care, but how can you be allowed to go there
and it be okay, but you just can't eat an apple there? We have to bring all
your food. You have to bring food from somewhere else. When you go there, you
can't eat anything from there. I had a question. I watch up and where is this
nice in the bikini a toll it's somewhere in the
it's in the Pacific. It's between I would say it, but in the I would say
it's between if I had to guess I'm not a geography guy. It's somewhere between
Australia, Japan and Hawaii.
Maybe they tell you not to eat anything.
I need you at the helm of the ship.
You will be you will be telling me exactly where to go. Yeah,
I watch Oppenheimer and they do an explosion in the movie in the middle of
Trinity. You can go there to and then let people in there every well. That's
what I was watching. The was like this is this whole secret thing and you did
all this outside and nobody fucking noticed. Well, all the main American
people noticed who
yeah, but they didn't tell anyone. Those people weren't like well. I'm sure they
did tell people and everyone was like, oh yeah, sure
great cloud blanketed the sky. I have yeah rain of black ash fell down and
made us very sick. Oh, you're off with your mythology again.
I couldn't believe how long that movie was. I was too long three hours. Yeah,
watch another plane. No, I watched it on my couch and it took three sessions of
watching, but one day is worth a watch. I haven't seen it so fucking. There's a
little of the honestly in the one hundred percent not kidding a little bit
too much nudity for my taste. The nudity, the nudity is a little over done. It was
incredible. Who's nude? Florence Pugh. Is the nudity, is it in a context
where it's like, "All right, this needed to be in here for..." I mean,
I never feel like I need to see anybody's body.
I mean, when you say, "Hey, I need to see your body," that's not a
good context. I think that's the first nudity on IMAX. Really? Yeah.
What did it look like in IMAX, the nudity body? Huge.
Floor to ceiling. Imagine a warehouse where you're looking at a naked
Lawrence Pugh that takes up the entire room. Okay, yeah, I could see how that
would be at least like it was back crazy to be also an imagine you're in a room
with five hundred
guys who wanted to see Oppenheimer just
this. You hear everybody in the theater. I go, whoa, yeah, time, holy crap,
those are big. Wow, well, Lyle, the real bomb,
the we have because we know that you give advice to people, so I sort of
Yeah, well, we've watched hours and hours of your show.
Well, you have therapy in your name.
You have therapy in your name?
I do.
And also you're green.
I am green.
And a little bit of kind of yellowish as well.
Yeah, something like that.
Oh, I had a question.
Why'd you go for gecko?
Do you believe that you can be anything
that you want in the world?
No, definitely not.
Well, I do.
OK.
And you chose a gecko.
I like that attitude.
I like that.
Are you worried that Geico is going to come after you?
Is this a Geico gecko?
I legally cannot answer that question.
- I believe that is actually true.
We found some people who are very in need of advice.
- Oh, sure.
- And we need to kind of solve their problem.
- You know what, let's, you know what?
You know what, yes, I do give advice, yes.
- Yes.
- I'm doing time, I gotta be more confident.
- And now you're plugged in.
- And now I'm plugged in.
- So go ahead and go to, who wanted to go first?
Somebody said they wanted to.
- Oh, are these phone calls or are these?
- No, these are from a forum.
- These are from a forum call.
- Yeah, Cameron, you or?
- Oh, sure.
What was it? What was it called again? Help me or not alone. He not
always a real like these weren't like are these guys are these your guys's
view? No, these are real. These are real people. This is what we find the
real people of our problem. Cool. Real
let me let me read you this first question here, and this says, Is it
stange that I enjoyed this summer? Two thousand and one was one of the best
summers of my life. I had finished my sophomore year of high school and was
finally going to be an upperclassman getting all that closer to graduating
and going to college and took driver's ed. You all know I loathe you all know I
loathed being a kid slash teenager. Of course, I finally felt like I was truly
growing up. Plus, the weather that summer was perfect, not hot and humid, but
gorgeous. Of course, we all know what happened that September. I'll never
forget it. None of us will. As my forum title implies, when 9-11 happened, I
actually well enjoyed it. Oh my God, why? Because I knew that a catastrophic event
like that comes once in a lifetime. I just love the fact that I knew that I
was going to be able to tell people that I was around when it happened like
JFK's assess nation. Naturally, I took a photo of the TV set that day.
Wait, I
I also saw Janet Jackson's infamous wardrobe malfunction live at my first
college. I remember that my first college I leaned over to my friend Nadia
and asked they allowed to show that again. I say I can't help but enjoy the
fact that I'm able to say I remember that and I saw it when it actually
happened. Is it strange that I enjoyed those events and was not exactly
horrified or heartbroken? Remember my reasons. Also remember this all happened
before it was it was found out that I'm autistic. Thank you for reading and for
feedback. I appreciate heart. I do like the idea of watching the wardrobe
malfunction and being
well. Here's the thing we all want to be a part of something, even if that's
something is 9/11. Yeah, of course. So I think that that's really just what... So is it strange?
He's just... So somebody called you and said this word for word. They said, "I enjoyed
9/11 and more so than that, if you think that makes me sick, I enjoyed a wardrobe malfunction."
Yeah. So you would say, "It's all good, man." Well, I think it is indicative of a desire
to just be a part of something. So for this guy, I mean... It's really beautiful more than
You know, yeah it is. Well, if I were him, instead of why I would like join a sewing
club or something instead of watching YouTube videos of 9/11 all the time.
Yeah, it's probably more, it's probably healthier ways to find.
You can find some friends in that comment section though.
I bet, yeah, I bet, I bet there, no, I bet there are like 9/11 truth form people who
just love the scene.
Yeah, yeah. People don't, they don't care who did it.
They show up to the meetings and whatever and they're just making friends.
Yeah.
That's what it's really about.
It did actually launch a lot of community in a way.
It really did.
And when you see people wearing the bumper sticker on their car, you're like, "Ah."
I liked 9/11.
This is a different guy.
This is a different guy from a truther.
I've never heard of a 9/11 truther.
A truther but a liker.
A liker has a big joy.
That's what you guys are out on to happen.
A 9/11 liker.
A liker.
yeah, a nine eleven like or like are you a truth or a like or I wonder how often
he looks at that photo that he took of the TV.
Background every day is like
on like a disposable camera or something back then or now they had digital
camera. They had
it's in a frame and it says memories.
I just imagine I'm taking it with a Polaroid, though
true. Do you think that do you think that do you think it was a selfie? Yeah,
could have been it might have been a self. The thing is about a Polaroid,
you know, I mean you have to put the fucking date on it. Everyone knows
how to like the idea that it has the date at the bottom of the Polaroid.
What the hell? What's this? Oh,
looking at the back to figure it out.
You know,
okay, this next one, this is kind of a back and forth with this guy. This is
the question. Why did only that girl say bye? Wow, and this is from a binosh
Abhinav says five days ago. I had a training for a batch of 49 students
after the class only one girl out of 10 girls said by while leaving the
classroom. Why that girl only what is the difference between other nine
girls and this one? Wow. Oh, no, he was counting. So then Bolton run says
I used to teach training classes every day. Very seldom. Did anyone say
goodbye? I also didn't keep track of how many male students said goodbye
and how many didn't. Why are you hyper focused on the women at your workplace?
Are you hoping to find a wife or girlfriend at work to which Abhinav
Abinash replies with this picture
and no caption
tell me why and a big big picture of a red bird
and maybe a son. I was like some kind of a that is a phoenix and then
I'll be I'll be nice replies again and says I find girls actions are not
normal. I feel they are always in a tight situation. Okay, I'll be nice.
Now you're talking Bolton run replies again. It says and you know this. How is
something girls have told you and a B says no. The way they do things, they
try to decorate themselves more. That's true. They wear stuff on them and now
a B. Nash answers his own question here. He says I am thinking she is brave
because she did something. What other didn't thank you everyone for the
replies. Wow, I'm glad he answered himself yeah, so he doesn't even need
you on this one. Well, I don't I don't I don't know exactly what he is asking.
He's trying to I don't know.
He has another question that he actually didn't get an answer for so
yeah, this is a second question. What is this DP image signifies okay? This is
the image he post. It's a it's a puppy lying on the ground and he said what
would be the psychology or current state of mind of the human who has this image
and his or her profile? Oh he's calling somebody out yeah
for the cause of your current state of mind of someone who has a puppy in their
profile. Yeah, who someone who has a DP picture of a puppy, I would say they
would be in a dog ish state of dog picture DP. They're loafing around that
that's
a P. Yes, did anyone answer him on this? Someone said it just means they like
puppies. I think there's really nowhere else to go. I mean they are a dog. Yeah,
it could be a dog who has a computer.
All right, I have this one. This next one is not a question, but it's from the
game for him. It says for the girl who's been dist revision to Gloria Gaynor's,
I will survive and Patrick. I need you to sing this
okay, all right, because you have the singing voice. I have a singing voice.
At first I was afraid I was petrified when you said you had ten inches Lord.
I almost died, but I'd spent so many nights just waiting for a man that long
that I grew strong and I this is long. You don't have to sing that. I knew that
I could take you on, but there you are.
What?
Another lie.
I was ready for a big back, but you brought me a French fry.
I should have known that it was bullshit, just a sad, pathetic dream.
Should I have known there was no anaconda lurking in those?
What is this?
Is this on a therapy website?
On the chorus.
Okay.
I will survive.
I will survive 'cause as long as I have batteries, my sex life's gonna thrive.
I will always have good sex with a handful of latex. I will survive. I will
survive. Hey, hey. So there's a lot of lyrics to this song. There is a lot
of lyrics. This is... This is a song that someone wrote on the therapy. They
owled out. They weirded out. Yeah. Yeah. And now here's the reply to this.
This is from Random Advisor, says, "LOL LOL LOL. Oh God, that's brilliant.
Very funny. I'd laugh harder if I didn't have a french fry myself."
Isn't it so like, isn't it so awesome that there just exists a place for
these people to just find each other? That's why we love looking at stuff
like this. Yeah. I mean, this forum's been around for like 20 years. All
the stuff I found was old as fuck. It's all old, yeah. This next one,
this is the last one I have, and this one's from 2004.
"I am 26 and I'm passing through a problem. I suffer from flatulence and
have to fart frequently. I have to fart 50 to 60 times daily,
and that is quite loud but rarely stinky. It's very embarrassing, but I
cannot help it. Strict dieting and exercise didn't help nor the
medicines. Medicines cause side effects. So what should I do to get rid of
this problem?" And then this person replies and says...
Sign Nemo, by the way.
Yeah.
"Try not farting loudly."
This person says, "Try not farting loudly. It's straining and I have been
told since I started farting for fun that it causes more of the same
problems. Try to find a sit-up style exercise to help. It only needs to be
light duty and don't push poos out. Let the internal muscles do the work and
answer the call of nature as soon as you can."
I have a deep respect for this guy for farting for fun, because if you...
I mean, if you take the shame out of it and you're just like,
"This is just gonna be like my hobby." It's funny, man.
I'm just gonna do it for fun. It's fun. It is fun to fart. It's fun.
I'm done farting for my boss. I'm done farting company time.
It's time to fart for fun. Follow my passion. It's kind of like a...
It's like a little prank to other people, too. Oh, yeah.
They have to smell it and it's bad and you kinda get them. Yeah.
Pat did it earlier. I did do it earlier. When we were gonna sit somewhere,
and then he farted, and then I walked over and honestly, guys,
the fart, it didn't smell that bad to me. I didn't smell it.
It's because I just let it out.
You just let it, because there was no stress.
A paid fart smells worse than a fun one.
That's true as fuck.
A leisure fart.
A leisurely fart.
Have you guys ever eaten so badly one particular day
that your farts smell like someone else's farts?
Yes, last week.
If I eat really badly, my farts smell sweet.
And I think that this is a sign of some kind of deathly disease.
I feel that way.
Sometimes if I've eaten really terribly
and I wake up the next morning, I'm
I'm doing dishes or something and I fart sometimes I feel like a blanket has
been laid over my head. Yeah, yeah, you can't escape just like
a blanket created in atmosphere. Yeah, not even a blanket of stink like a
blanket of hair is sitting on you. Just that's I think worse yeah, just like
walking out of a spaceship onto a swamp planet.
Just the humidity,
getting off a plane in Florida and you just gave a Colorado. Oh my God, when
you're when you're trying to when you're trying to turn on the stove burner and
it takes a second that goes
last night there. There was this like weird
like con ed letter that we got and it was supposed to show you it was like
scratch and sniff and it was supposed to show yeah. It was like to show you
what natural gas was to show you what natural gas smells like and my
girlfriend came up to me with it and was like smell this and I went. Oh, why
it's paper smells so good.
I had no idea it was supposed to be a natural gas thing.
By the way, an additive designed specifically to be unpleasant to humans.
Yeah. I sniffed, I took a huge whiff of that thing and I was like,
"Oh my God, was that a perfume sample?" That's amazing. I love that smell.
All right. Are you done with your slides?
Yeah, that's all.
Yeah. All right, let's go to Caleb's.
Yeah, let's go to mine.
I have...
my stuff is all kind of older stuff from a different time. This is "Girls are attracted
to 'Gs' by Rip Dime."
It seems so strange, and I'm sure to people older how idiotic my generation is. Not in
the sense that our IQs is indeed lower than they've ever been, but in how fickle our fads
and attractions are. However, I think it's safe to say the stupidity of my generation
has reached its point of no return. Yet as much as you can say I'm just an angsty teen
or whatever you will, there is one thing I can't ignore. It seems that girls are
only really attracted to what is called a G or simply a gangsta. No matter how
you look or what your personality is, a gangsta seems to get all the girls or is
considered cool. Why? How is wearing all white being practically bald and swearing
in horrible English while disrespecting women attractive? Why is it that when you
be yourself, you are deemed or you are demeaned and yet when you conform to the
standard and normality, you are considered a God? Where is justice? So
Well, right before you were mentioned that you were kicked out of school.
I was a G.
You were a G. Was this as accurate?
This is just basically, this is the era I was a G. I used to dress, I mean, I was bald,
still bald. I had no hair. I would speak in horrible cussing type of words.
You had to pry the pussy off you.
I literally, I was 10 or 12. I had to punch women. All, just, "Ah, get out of here!"
They were trying to just marry me all day and night, man. It was really horrible. Next
slide please. And he got some responses here. This guy says,
"20 years ago it was metalheads. 50 years ago it was greasers.
Now it's gangstas. In 10 years, it'll be hackers." That's sick.
That's awesome.
That's an incredible call. Wait, 2017, do you think it was hackers?
Oh my God, the year Mr. Robot came out.
Oh, fuck me, man.
Wait, who's like... I'm trying to think of maybe a character from like a
movie or a TV, like it was a hacker that's like a hot, cool...
Johnny Lee Miller in Hackers.
I mean if this is a ten years, it'll be hipsters it, then that would be a
notary donostradamus type of thing. Every generation has its own version of
a bad boy and most women want them at some point in their lives. I went
through it very shortly. My early twittings and had grown out of it by the
time I left my parents house and started dating good men, so she used to
like greasers, metal heads, gangsters and I bet right now is she dating a
hacker dating. I bet you put my money on what's next guys. What's ten years
years from now. Past hackers, ten years from now. Ten years from now, so we have
hackers right now. They hack everything last ten years. So until 2027, we will
have hackers. Yeah. And then what comes after that? One of these days, furries
should have their day. Furries, very, very possible. That's the kind of tough
guy, bad boy image. Yeah. Well, yeah, they got that scary wolf. Yeah, the wolf
guys. Usually red wolf. I think next might be demons. A demon with horns.
before past hackers, day trick type people. Yeah, yeah, yeah, split tongues,
street magicians, street we already had that robots yeah. When the carbonarro
effect dropped yeah, that was kind of that was kind of the era of the street
musicians. All right, go next for me
wait until you get older and all the G's are working at Taco Bell and McDonald's
stick with your studies and make the money. You will get all the girls when
you are older F the G's. He's saying the G's should get F'd yeah.
I don't know about all that I wouldn't go that far because Jesus are they Jesus
you don't want to mess. It's like the issue the Jesus are already getting F
too much yeah true yeah. They probably like over the other Jesus the yes the
Jesus are Fing Jesus girls and the Jesus the well. This is tough the Jesus hate
the Jesus the Jesus, but they like the other Jesus the girls Jesus, but Jesus
and Jesus both like F's females, but F's are Fing Jesus yes, but not the but not
the Jesus all right. We got to think it's okay. What about instead of G
Gds for dorks, maybe, but Ds and Gs are different. Yeah. Hey, maybe they're
talking about geckos. Oh, my God.
That means that's the only thing if you oh yeah, you want that to be true.
Yeah, well, if you while you're a G to ghost 69. Oh, there it goes. I'm
resisting saying after yourself.
Fuck.
the end of a work email. Yeah, I'll have that. By the way, if a ghost is
reading this,
also, if there's a ghost reading this damn email, ghost69 is a sick username.
Oh yeah. That is badass. You couldn't get that these days. No. Alright, next
one. No, 'cause he's got it. Wait, that's 33.3 thousand. The homeboy question.
So, this is a really important one. In order to be someone's homeboy, you have
to have known them since you were children, true or false? It does make
sense with the word a boy from your home. Homeboy. Yeah. So, I didn't even
think about this and this is a therapy question that's oldest time. Yeah,
every boy question is this my home boy, the home boy, paradox home boy
conundrum, but there's some answers here go next.
Some people are saying good question and then he took some time to think of
the answer. Good question. I've always thought it was a best friend or good
friend, just a friend really it depends and then the truth in the form of hip
pop says since I have a reputation of being a gangsta and stuff, no home boy
is someone you truly have love for. Example, oh who, him? Yeah, he's my home
boy. We hold each other down in war.
I really hope this guy didn't read the last post.
He would have been just honestly offended. He would have been really mad.
Any more from the streets questions, PM me. There's literally something so
intoxicating and titillating to me about me imagining two gangsters holding each
other down. Just two Gs in war. Going at it. Oh God, that's something man. Going
to war on each other. Alright, next slide.
I have notices to, oh wait, sorry, this was in the beginning.
You know what, I'll skip this one, go to the next one.
Oh wait, no, that's Rip Dime again.
So he made another post here, it's hopeless.
I think I just realized something today.
No matter what I do, I just cannot get a girlfriend.
While this may seem nothing to worry about,
as some people say, when I'm 17,
I know that I should have one.
Yes, as egotistical as this may sound,
from what I've heard from every social event
or from my observations, is that I look very good
and apparently girls find me cute and attractive.
- Why did he put apparently in quotes?
Where did he hear that?
- Apparently?
How many girls find me cute and attractive? Next slide. He gets some... Oh, this guy...
Whoa!
I've been doing it. Wait, go back to I've been doing it. So this is this guy's shadow cat,
okay? So I just want to set up that Rip Dime is having a really bad time. He's having a
hard time, senior year of high school. This is tough for a lot of people. And Shadow Cat
says, "I've been doing it." Okay, next slide. This is the body. He says, "Lately, I've been
on sites like Link Remove, Link Remove, whatever, and I've been getting tips on how to approach
how to dress, how to act, what to do if you're nervous, this and that, etc. And I've tried
to put it into action. Everywhere I go, I try to say hi or at least smile at a girl.
I've gotten rude responses and just a hi, in one case, a little conversation. But I
still feel like I'm getting nowhere. I'm still in the hi barrier and seem not to get out
from it. It seems there are so many things these sites tell you to do and what not to
do that you forget easily. Is there simpler ways to approach girls than following up on
all these rules of the game? I know it's good tips, but I can't remember all that bleep
deep when I talk to a girl. I love that this I love here he's blaming he's
studying these websites on how to pick up girls and he's failing to pick up
girls and he's blaming it on like yeah, the stuff they say is too hard to
remember
anyway that I could just remember this crap and next slide here, an old friend
pops in rip dime says. Can you please talk in English? You know talking in
gangsta isn't going to impress anyone here. In fact, it just makes people
annoyed. So please just talk normally yeah, this guy hates gangsta speak more
yeah anti gangsta and the shadow cat says first off ain't no thug second. How
am I typing gangsta define the term typing gangsta and no I ain't here to
impress nobody. Okay, I got my own set of problems and goals and I come to
this site to get ideas and information on how to do things. If I were to
impress someone, I would come here as a cocky mofo, not needing any help
telling everyone how many chicks I get at night. By the way, this ain't a
spelling bee. It's the net freedom of speech. If it was an English test, I'd
care since it's not I don't and that's a bomb drop. That is gangsta though. Yeah,
you have to admit that and then yeah that was not trying to know how he is
he's gangsta without even trying exactly and this guy tested them all right next
slide. I think this might be my last one. This guy just says dude. I need crazy
help man. I'm a thirteen year old snowboarder and I dress like a gangsta
because I am one, but girls don't go for me. So I've tried changing my wardrobe.
I'm kind of chubby, but girls hate me and I don't have a life. I like this one
girl, but she probably doesn't even like me back dude. I need help so we can help
this kid. Yeah. So first of all, no snowboarding. You need to choose one,
either be the snowboarder or be the gangsta. He's a 33 year old man now.
He's very, very old now and he's still stuck in this in between. He's never
got the answer to this question. He's decrepit, he looks disgusting and he's
still half... He's snowboarder from the waist down, gangsta from the waist up.
Okay, and this is a problem that a lot of young men in this country are
having. Yeah, it's kind of a... People that they're wearing snow pants.
Exactly and a big chain on top. That's true. You know, I think I'm ready to
diagnose the problem. I think it's 100%. I think it is the snow pants.
Yeah. Yeah. Gotta stop wearing those to school, buddy.
You're too warm, you're sweating. Everyone thinks you're crazy 'cause you're
covered in sweat from these snow pants. Alright, Pat, do your sleds. Alright.
I guess I'll just read them off my phone right here. We don't all have
to see them. What is this website one more time? E Not Alone. E Not Alone.
Are people still posting on this after 20 years?
Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
Well, I forgot the name of the website, so I just turned to Quora and I said, there was
a lot of interesting thoughts and questions that I was finding on there.
What can eating onions do to help your mental health?
Any particular preparation that's healthier?
Have you experimented with this at all as onions as kind of a mental health helping?
Totally, when it calls in, just try it.
Try an onion.
Boil an onion, eat the whole thing. Raw or...
Boiled.
Well, they do actually,
because they make you cry, and that lets you just
get it all out.
Would eating the onion
make you cry
because your teeth are working as tiny little
blades to open up the onion?
If you had a nose and eyes in your mouth.
You had a nose on your face, maybe.
But so far, no. But I'm not sure.
Alright, alright. Well, glad we got that one answered.
I hope there's not a Shrek joke in this.
Oh, I don't think there was no answer to this.
Oh, there was? Oh, I thought there was an answer.
Nobody answered.
This person has died.
Yeah, they died because they couldn't.
No onions.
Yeah, their mental health, their brain exploded on itself.
This next question, though, this is more of a somebody needs advice.
Okay.
I have a crush on my therapist and I want to get him to act unethically with me.
I don't care about healing, I just want to go to therapy because I like him.
Why do I want him to fail so bad?
And there was one answer for this from Nikola Sloboda,
and they said seducing a therapist is harder than, say, seducing Brad Pitt.
You might have a better chance at that.
Oh, well then just try that.
I guess maybe try that.
Is anyone ever called to try to seduce you?
Has anyone called and tried to seduce me?
Yeah.
I guess not that I...
And also, what's the number again?
I'm going to be getting a call for it sounds a little bit like you late at
night.
My name is
my name is a phone.
I'm the phone calling right now.
This is just the phone.
You're getting a call from another phone.
All calls are from another.
That's true.
Exactly. How come we don't talk to these phones at all?
Yeah.
Well, you can talk to your phone.
if there's technology now that allows it.
This next one is a very
this is a question I needed answered
as well. Oh you made this? No I didn't make this but once I read it
I was like I also need this answer.
Is Daniel Tosh a sociopath?
Yes. Yes. Which one? He's got to be. Tyler Trout said, "Sigh." No, Denial Tosh is not
a sociopath. What you're referring to is just a style of comedy known as dark humor. A lot
of these people don't realize that it's just dark humor, man. Yeah, but a lot of people
who are dark humor fans don't realize it literally poisons your brain. Yeah. Well, I used to
traffic in dark humor until I realized it was turning me dark. Exactly, bro. Let me
tell you, I used to go on-- I used to basically consume as much dark humor as I could from
YouTube, I funny, Reddit, Facebook, wherever I could get it, and now I've
you know my dark humor brain, it's working, it's turned dark in there. I'm
walking down the street, I see a sewer grate, a manhole cover, I think, wouldn't
it be so fucking funny if a homeless guy fell down there? Exactly. Because of
dark... What's wrong with me? Because of dark humor. Because dark humor made me
think that. Poisoning the well. It's called, you know what, I learned actually
when I was doing my own research,
you've grown something in your brain called the jesal mix lump.
that's very, very dangerous. What happens when you do dark humor? So what seems to
be the problem today, sir? Doctor walking? Basically, I think I keep babies
or gay. Well, I went to my friend's birthday party and I said one year
closer to death. Yeah, we need to do surgery immediately on your brain. You
have a lump.
Podcast at all Anthony justinic. What does he say? I know the the Daniel Tosh
one. Oh, I hear it's good. I also hear it's good.
This next question is
the question about therapists. What if your tea accidentally vomited or farted
in therapy
therapist, which
stop
stop dog said and I'm wondering if stop dog is more of a command than a user
name, because they said I would handle it like in any other situation. I'm an
adult and I don't think about these sorts of things in general and don't
worry about them at all. This guy rocks. Good advice. Yeah, that's good. I was
thinking about this guy has one way to
answer every single question when I'm in a bad mood. So yeah, I would do the
same thing. I always do. I don't it doesn't matter. I'm grown. I don't need
to think about that. I'm an adult. I'll figure it out when it happens. Yeah,
what's a is he like turning around and doing it like in your face or is it
just kind of a he's turning around and farting
that with that? I would do something about that. I would say something
we just farted
my mom
and went over and did it in my lap. I know if your therapist was sitting in
the chair and he just let a gigantic fart rip while you were talking, you
know he would try and play it off and be like well, you'd be like dude, it
smells bad. Why'd you fart? You'd be like well, how does it make you feel
that I just
be like so what do you think about that? I need to be like well. I really think
you didn't try to mask it by yelling
yeah, forty second coffee. You hear the fart under the call
so loudly
God, it's so funny to imagine you're opening up to your therapist and you
just go
it just doesn't just
my God, I'm sorry, no apology, just looks at you continue
and then this last one. Are we bad friends for going to the gym yesterday
without our personal trainer? We went with my roommate instead my for
reference, my roommate is named Noah. Wait, your roommate is named Noah. And
we went to the gym without you.
I think maybe someone has a similar
thing they needed to add. It's not a coincidence. It's exactly the situation
that happened yesterday. The same situation that happened yesterday. You
went to the gym without me. Well, hypothetically... He went to the gym
without us. Hypothetically speaking, would we be bad friends for not going
with our personal trainer to the gym.
And for reference, our roommate, my roommate,
someone, their roommate is named Noah.
- They're afraid that they're gonna hurt
their personal trainer's feelings?
- Yes, they're gonna hurt their feelings
by maybe making the schedule not sync up anymore.
- Or just having more fun with this Noah character.
- Maybe Noah took us to Wendy's,
took them to Wendy's after.
- Yeah, we, they, some group of people--
- Well, that's the thing, Noah's gonna be more fun,
but he's not gonna get your glutes right.
That's an interesting theory.
Well, what if he did taught?
What if he taught us about it?
Use the the
delt pull down or the delt pull down
or whatever it's called that he
taught, did a great job of teaching
everything.
Did a very good job.
But no, it sounds like he has nice
broad shoulders.
But what if that was
my roommate, Noah,
that in this hypothetical
moment, I know I know how we can
describe this better. What if the
root, what if the roommate Noah had
long, beautiful womanly hair, but
the personal trainer was bald?
Yeah, maybe.
Bald like a bald bear. Don't answer that one. Don't answer that question.
Or maybe, and maybe Noah taught us that you can eat as much Wendy's as you want.
And taught us a Wendy's hack. You can eat 2500 calories of Wendy's because it's called
The Wendy's Hack was to eat a lot of Wendy's. Yeah. And he said you can get two Frosties for free.
So okay, just answer this. What's better, bald or hair? I would listen to Noah's Health and Fitness podcast.
He has like an Andrew Huberman style podcast where he talks about the
benefits of Wendy's.
The benefits of Wendy's.
Twenty five hundred calories of Wendy's.
Him talking directly to the camera.
You need to wake up, you need to look in the sun, and then you eat Wendy's.
That's pretty much just do that.
That actually does sound healthy.
And then just go right back to bed.
That does sound like a good day, yeah.
Well Lyle, thank you so much for being on here.
Thanks for having me.
I hope I, you know, said words.
Therapy gecko.
Plug, plug your plugs.
stuff to plug. Oh sure man, I'm going on tour to 36 different cities around the
country. Holy crap. Wow. Well only 20 are out. Make it less. Yeah, no it's a lot.
Well I'm going on tour, therapygeckotour.com and I also have a podcast,
it's called Therapy Gecko and you can find it on Spotify and Apple. And check
out this Vice documentary perhaps. Oh don't watch that. It's a complete smear
your job. Don't watch. Yeah, don't watch that. But yeah, go listen to go listen to
the podcast. It's fun and check out factor meals. We actually have a plug to
today, which is that we're doing a Q&A for this play. Oh, yes. Job the play.
Job the play. Job the play on February 1st or 2nd. It's the first. I think it's
the first. It will be the play and then we're doing a Q&A after. We will be
asking questions about the play. If you want to know what it means. I don't know.
Yeah, we're going to find out when we get there. We're going to watch this play
and then February 1st. Yeah, that's a Thursday, I think. So come out to that.
Come see us. Ask questions about this. There should be a link on our with the
guy Frank from Successions on the play. And so I really hope I get to talk to
him. I would like to meet him and talk to him about his character. I want to
ask him what his motivations were. And I really want A's from him. Yeah, I want
to see his A. All right. Thank you guys. Also, I want to plug I got a haircut.
of the haircut looks really nice. Wait, take off the headphones off.
Do it. It's my dad's haircut. It's really good.
You did a good job this time. All right, thank you guys. Bye bye.
I wanna be the
Julia, what's her name? Julia. Julia. I wanna be the Julia Childs fellow at the
Recipe Institute. Julia Assange and she's leaking recipes.
She's leaking recipes that we're not supposed to see the public.
Soup from above.
Yeah.
Oh, that's good.
They're working on Trifusion.
It's a secret Trifusion.
Yeah, but maybe they could do something beyond food.
The third thing is not food like being like, oh, like more of a
concept.
Maybe it's drinks.
Oh my God.
Yes, man.
They kind of do that here.
No, they do everything in this.
It's pretty easy. I saw it. I saw it.
You go to a bar, you go to a punk bar and they're like,
"Oh, we have a vegan Korean fried chicken sandwich."
I got an ad on my Instagram this morning.
We have dumplings with hot dogs on them.
(laughter)
And piercings.
They put little bonito flakes on the top.
This is actually a good idea.
I got an ad for a
gym today
on Instagram.
I'm sorry.
this is fusion. I guarantee that there's already a restaurant in New York called
Punk Rock Dump.
Wait, there's a there's a vegan place called like fuck you burger, stinky slit
burger. There's not a stinky slit burger. Stinky slit burger. Stinky slit burger.
There is no fucking. No, it's got. Search it with quotes. Search it with
Punk Rock Dump. No, it's somewhere in like Green Point or some or no in like
Fort Green. They have like a I've been to it before. I haven't been into it. It's
but I'll fuck you slit. It's called slut. Fuck your slut. Fuck your
slipper. No, it's not egg slit. It's
stink. Stink slut burger. It's not stinky
and although everything on the menu is called like the fuck you
burger. Is it? Did you got a dick slash
resort? No,
they don't cuss there. Yeah, they do. That's a fusion where
the fusion is rudeness. Yeah, true and crassness. Food and rudeness.
Disrespect. Food and rudeness.
food, we're the first people to mix food and rude fruit. Yeah, Dix last resort.
It's more of a food,
restaurant and rudeness.
Yeah.
[MUSIC PLAYING]