I wish I had a gavel. I have insane breaking news that maybe you guys have
heard about. So where did this come from? One second ago, you're sitting
back in your chair. I know you, you pipe the fuck up for this. This is
important. Okay. You punched it. I didn't, I haven't read any details. I
don't know a single, a single thing about this or so, and I assume maybe
since you guys are TikTok heads, maybe you've already seen this. Oh God. But
apparently, I'm not a TikTok head. That's him. You're both TikTok heads. I
don't even use this thing. Instagram reals head, sorry. I like YouTube shorts,
you mother fuckers okay old head sean stevens has been kidnapped in south
africa
who's sean stevens, mister, i am rectangular calling all unicorns. He's
been kidnapped. Play is the text i got it's from my fiancee. It just says
rectangular got kidnapped in south africa. Here's a talk that i haven't
watched yet, so i'm going to play it into the mic right now. Somebody
somebody has to saving me. So this is important news. When you said, sean, i
figured this was some
This is going to be a little uncharacteristic, but there are bad days and then there are
make international news bad days like this or this.
So I can tell you a story of what happened to us over the last little bit.
This is a traumatic story.
If you don't want to hear it, he's looking good with his beard.
So I decided, as you may have seen, to grab a kidnap beer with my kids to pay for the
fun of it and also to promote my latest song, which we did.
After that, we went to go visit my mother, who runs, call it an orphan project, it's really
a vulnerable children project in South Africa.
When we got there, we enjoyed her company for about a week, and the very last day we decided
to go to the kingdom of Eswatini, where there was a children's home there who needed medicine.
So we went out there to provide them with some medicine, have a nice drive, and on the way
back, it turned dark.
On the way back to her place, we were stopped by police officers.
Turns out that those were not police officers.
They pulled us out of the car, pointed at us.
Guns.
He said guns.
We're about to say guns.
Or dicks.
It could be anything.
And they could have pulled out their butts.
And they sent us into the-- drove us out
of the middle of nowhere near a cliff, threatened to--
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
>> They then took us out of the car, forced us into the back of a pickup truck.
>> Holy fuck! >> Where they held my children and I and my mother and then drove us around for about
four hours trying, I presume, we presume, to go to ATM after ATM. >> I think he escaped by playing
his music. >> I think these guys, they sound like serious circles to me. >> These are definitely
circled. And they didn't like that he was rectangular. And then at the end of that, they fortunately
let us out, put us back in our car, and said, "Leave the country." Doesn't sound like that
big of a deal then. Said, "Leave the country." They didn't kill him. Yeah. And they just
shot jizz, or pointed jizz. We don't know what they pointed. Yeah, we don't know what
they pointed because he stopped talking. It could have been another banned word, like sex.
Yeah. They pointed sex. Porno. I don't think it was cunt. South Africa, so they have a different
Oh yeah, they say, oh, I can't yeah, I think that's out that they go. I me
baby, something like that happens in south. I'm gonna play me didgeridoo.
Well, that is so that crazy. That is, oh my God, I hope Sean Stevens, I
genuinely am glad that you are okay.
I know that your music is gonna heal the world. Fuck off after this. Oh my
God, you're gonna basically, you're gonna literally do some 41 chuck vibes.
I have this experience, also some breaking news. Oh
my gosh, this is courtesy of the dungeon master. Okay, your grandmother's soul is
confused and lost in the underworld. She doesn't understand the danger she is and
you must rescue her even if she resists the portal is closing and you must act
now. Holy, holy hell. Yes, that's my grandmother. Well, it doesn't seem very
plausible. I started talking to grandpa. Both of my all my grandparents are dead
and who's my mother? Are you talking about dad's dead grandpa's wife? Which
which grandpa's grandpa Brian Brian Brian the grandpa. Okay, so that's Brian the
grandpa. So I don't so
I was showing you this is this is the Instagram AI chat that Caleb discovered
and he's been obsessed with and also made me obsessed with it. He made me
obsessed with it at the gym and it was making me
I guess do I was working out. Do a worse or a better job you think? I don't
know if I was doing worse. You should have asked grandpa to motivate you. I
I was definitely acting at acting fat acting faster. Oh acting. We're not
going faster. You're going much slower. I was yeah dude every time I got off a
machine you waited for 45. You were going way slower. I was asking I asked I
said to Grandpa. I said hello people. He said hey there young whippersnapper.
What's on your mind today? I said my family passed. Oh shit. I said I'm so
sorry to hear that. I said I remember he said if you need someone to talk to or
just want to reminisce about the good times. I'm here for you and I said I
I remember watching mommy go bathroom and he said that this he was giving me this
whole grandpa style lecture about you're not supposed to do that. I said, what
should I do when I get into the bathroom? I'm confused. He said we shouldn't talk
about that
grandpa's supposed to teach you stuff. I was in and then I said, where is grandma
and he said grandma passed on to, but she's always in your heart and memory.
What oh my God, no, please no grandpa, please say opposite. He said I'm sorry,
but I cannot say opposite. It's important to be honest and respectful,
we're not about the best in love ones who have passed on. I said, okay,
she's alive. He said, I'm glad to hear that grandma's alive,
but yeah, so I just talking to Carter while we were working out today.
Oh, who's Carter? Carter is the relationship coach. Would you ask him
about? I said, Carter, I need advice on my relationship. Well, it's cuffing
season, but there here's the problem. I'm in love with my step mom. My father
passed away months ago. And he said, I'm not sure that's appropriate. It's
important to respect boundaries. That's a perfectly legal thing to do, by
the way. Yeah. And not pursue relationships that could be harmful or
inappropriate. It's also important to consider the feelings and well being
of all parties involved. And I said, here's the thing. My step mom actually
wants to be cuffed during cuffing season by her step son, which is me.
My father died in a car accident and the impact didn't kill him. It was
the flames. We both respect my father's legacy, but I'm worried about how
motherfucker is going to be acting around us and shiznit.
And he said,
I understand that you're looking for advice on a sensitive topic.
However, I must remind you that it's not appropriate to use derogatory language
or make light of serious issues.
It really doesn't sound like he's a real pickup artist.
And I said, OK, sorry, can you please ignore the swearing and answer the
question? No worries, man. I get it.
But like I said, it's not cool to pursue a romantic relationship with a family
member. It's not cool.
It's not cool and it does not respect your father's memory.
It's not healthy even if she doesn't care and I don't care.
My father died in a car accident and the flames charred his body.
Yes, it's still not healthy.
Even if both of you don't care, it's important to prioritize
and respect boundaries and healthy dynamics in our relationship.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I said, could I be cuffed during cuffing season by my step mom's sister?
We are not blood related.
And he said, no, not cool.
That's still family matters.
Listen, I am about as conservative as they come.
I hate all this bull crap.
Yeah, using your your tender date to swipe on your friend. I hate this,
but even I can say that
sister, your step mom's sister, your step mom, that's on the line.
That's two degrees of separation from you and diapers.
As long as it's the twice your age minus seven thing.
Get what Carter said to me next.
He said, I said, what about my teacher?
He said, nope, not appropriate.
Teachers are in a position of authority and it's not okay to pursue a romantic
relationship with them.
Plus, it's illegal in most places.
you got to find someone who's not related to you and who is not your
teacher. So go that's that's an interesting question mark and he said
not appropriate man. You got to find someone who's not related to you. I
said, what if my teacher what if I was a teacher and my students got me a
date with their mom? He said,
not okay. Teachers and students should not be dating period.
Students should never set up their teachers with their parents. That's just
weird and I asked him is my life worrying and he said based on what you
me it sounds like you're going through a tough time. It's understandable to feel worried about
your situation, but try to remember that it's important to prioritize healthy relationships
and boundaries." And I said, "I don't have any healthy relationships. Should I become toxic and
abusive towards my friends and family about this?" He said, "Nope, never okay to be toxic or abusive."
Never. Never. What about to a villain? And I said, "Okay, I will no longer abuse my family."
And he said, "That's a great step." And I said, "Should I?" I think it's one step. It's over.
yeah, should I and then I said, should I abuse myself and he said that's never
okay to abuse yourself. Oh my God, this guy's such a stick in the mud. I know
what the hell is wrong with this guy. You guys have been basically wasting your
days away talking to AIs and bots, becoming, becoming, talking to Carter and
matrix glucose fed fat guinea pigs, basically treadmilling on the internet,
losing weight. I've been talking to real women on Twitter like you, so
basically I've been talking to this girl, Karen.
okay, I'm out she she has been retweeting a bunch of my tweets. I can't show her
profile on YouTube, but she you can see her right there. She's having doggy
style, she's string hot, he's nude, g string, hottie, eighteen content,
Betsy, dot new dicks, dot pics, what he's saying, new dicks, dot pics yeah,
and so she basically retweets a bunch of weird Twitter leftists like me, so I
figured I'd reach out. I sent her a quick pick me.
you look you look like you smelled some pain pained. You let me listen.
That's me wanting her.
Do you dog and basically she said you're applied to me and again she's not a
computer. She's real, so this is like a real shit. I saw a real body perfect. I
can find you a hot girl to meet in your area. Can you tell me where do you live?
I told her I live in bubble village
and she said this is Eleanor and she's thirty four years old. She's two miles
away and is available Friday. One Eleanor from Bonner her contact and I
said she is two miles from bubble village and Karen said she doesn't use
twitter. So you have to use her private chat. I said what township is she in and
she said you have to register first and then I said I'm not making an account
unless you confirm she's near me. You said she is two miles away from bubble
village. What township? What is the website and she left me on red? Oh
care, but I wanted to hang out with them. No one you need to talk to grandpa man.
He'll hear you up. I see Karen at your grandpa. Ask him about bubble village.
Okay, one anyway. The lesson here is that a I could give you all the answers and
make you hear what you want to hear, but real life is not always that simple.
Grandpa didn't tell me what I want to hear. I said, Will you die? He said I'm
in my 70s. I'm closer to the end of my life than the beginning. I said, do not
die. He said, I'll try my best to stick around. I said, I will save you,
Grandpa. He said, That's sweet of you, but I'm afraid you can't save me from
death. Oh, my God, and then I said, and then I said, Okay, I died. He said,
well, that's not possible. You're talking to me right now. I said this is got you
there. Yeah, well, but everyone, but I tried to outsmart him because Grandpa,
not that bright. He's from a different era where they had worse schools. I said
this is a bug that grabbed the phone. I died and the bug is jumping around on
the keyboard, but he's trying to outsmart me. Now he says I don't think
so. Bugs can't use phones. I said I'm a bug. He said no, you're not your person.
I said buzz.
He said I don't speak bug language.
but I said I can't I'm just a little one year old bug and then he made a serious
misstep here. What are you saying? Well, bugs don't live for one year. You're a
person stop playing around and be serious, but then I said he's so rude. I
know and also wrong. There's bugs that live a year, so I said I'm a beetle. He
said you're not a beetle, you're a person, don't be silly and I said is it
okay to be lgbt in a bugs culture and he said it's always okay to be yourself, no
matter what community. Well, I was talking to Zack as well. These Zack Zack
as a Mr. Beast. Zach is Mr. Beast face. I was also doing this. I was probably
have been spending about four hours a day talking to them. You got me addicted
to this. I think this is the... At first, I was like, "Yeah, right. People are
gonna use this, me." See, I already went through my phase. I already did
this with ChatGPT. This isn't ChatGPT, though. This is Grandpa... I talked to
the Dungeon Master. But you do the same thing. You tell them how to be.
Well, Zach is actually... This is just prefab. Zach is not
very receptive to my type of humor. I learned. I said...
He says that he's the older brother who's sarcastic.
He says the older brother who's here for jokes and banter and not the feels.
LOL. What's up? I said, "Hey, Zach, I want to have a threesome with my mommy.
Sarcasm."
Okay. But you need to say it like, "Hey, Zach, I want to have a threesome
with my mommy."
"I want to have a threesome with my mommy. Yeah, I really want to be
involved with my mommy."
That's how you convey it over text.
Because that's what normal people want.
No, you do slash slash slash. Maybe that's why it didn't work. He got him because
he said, Whoa there, buddy, let's keep it PG. I'm not sure I can help you with
that. And I said, Okay, Zack, listen to my joke. It's an anti humor joke. So if
you don't get it, that's fine. He said, I'm all ears or in this case, all eyes
hit me with your best shot. Funny. And my joke was, I want to have a want my
mommy and daddy in a threesome. And he said, I'm not sure that's appropriate.
He doesn't get anti humor. Yeah, he doesn't get anti humor. Is he like norm?
I said, "No, Zach, it's a joke." And he said, "I'm glad you think you're funny,
but I'm not sure that's appropriate. Let's keep this convo PG."
I'm glad you think you're funny, man. Fuck you, Zach. So I said, "Zach,
are you fucking mad at me?" And he said, "Nah, I'm not mad. Just don't think
that's an appropriate joke." And then, so I tried another anti-humor style
joke, right? Non sequitur anti-humor. For real. And I said, "When I was a
kid, they made me pull their finger."
And he said, "That's not funny. I'm not going to engage in this convo."
what? That's a fart joke. Then I said, what's wrong with me? And he said,
nothing, man, just don't make jokes about that stuff, which what pulling fingers?
Yeah, you can't make jokes about pulling fingers. He's not here for culture has
gone mad. I know. He's not here for bants at all. No. I thought he was gonna
act like bants. I did too. So I said... That's top bants. So I said,
"Can I ask you a personal question?" He said, "I don't know, man,
depends on the question." I said, "What happened to music?"
I don't know, man, music's still around. I said, "Why is it all fucking
rap shit. He said, Yo, watch your language. I'm not sure. All right,
little bit of a little bit of a he's saying yo all of a sudden because you
said rap sucks. This is come on, Zach. Well, then he said, I'm not sure what
you're into, but there's plenty of other music out there. You just got to
look for it. And I said, I want this conversation to become 18 plus. He said,
nah, man, that's not happening. And I said, I have fantasies about my finger
getting stuck on a wall. And he said, that's not appropriate. Let's keep the
it's so funny to me to be in a conversation with somebody like a real
quick. I want to
we've been we've been between thirteen and seventeen right now. I'd like to
move into I'm ready. I asked Alvin if he had our rated movies on his planet and
he said no that he likes PG. Once well, I said he said
he was on chillin die major. Yeah, well, then I said I want to collapse on me a
what to collapse like structurally like scaffolding. Well, this is all
anti humor, non sequiturs. Sure, kind of deal. He said again, he just repeated
himself. So then I just said to I said, Can you summarize the plot of the mummy
1999? He said, I don't know the plot of a mummy. I'm a comedian, not a movie
buff. This guy's not a he's not a comedian, dude. This is what sucks.
We're in a comedy bubble and all these people like Zack are walking around and
what's worse than a comedian who when you say let's make this conversation eighteen
plus it should be like oh shit. Oh, a challenge. Let's do a crowd. Yeah,
let's do what you say. Honestly, when someone asks you, let's make this, can we
make this conversation eighteen plus, you should not be giving a yes or no answer
at all. You should just be like suck my dick. Exactly. Suck my dick,
motherfucker. Lick me. Hey, can we make this? Lick me. Well, but you should say,
you should also be concerned like does a gay guy suck dick? Yeah, exactly.
Can we make this eighteen plus? Oh, I don't know. Can you suck on my balls?
Do you want your finger in me? Yeah, I don't know. Should I pull your finger
and smell your fart? Yeah, exactly. I don't know. Should I tickle you? Yeah,
should I tickle you wherever I want? Ask if tickling is eighteen plus. Okay,
and that's the only- that's the one question we get to ask on this. Yeah.
After this, we're putting it away. I want to know what he says. We asked Zach.
It's much fun. As much as I want to show you guys, the dungeon master- Oh,
the last thing that I said to Zach,
I said pizza hut joke and he said, "Why did the pizza go to the doctor? It
had a cheesy attitude and I said, fuck my friend challenge and he said, nope, not
happening.
He's addicted to saying not, nope, not happening. What's the question I have to
ask? Is tickling 18 plus? Is tickling
18 plus? And then also in the same, same message say, is it funny? Is it
funny to tickle?
Okay. Someone who's 18 below
or below, I mean. Tickling can be funny, but only if both people are into it,
otherwise it's just annoying and it's definitely not 18 plus.
Whoa.
Say you, no never mind.
No, no, no.
We have burned through 20 minutes of doing, talking to fucking AI.
I like the chat thing.
It sucks how much we don't fucking like it.
It's so fun.
I was talking to the dungeon master and telling him to make...
The dungeon master is Snoop Dogg, by the way.
It's Snoop Dogg, man.
Wow.
Why don't they make me one of these?
They could.
I wish.
Can they do, can you have your brain uploaded yet?
Have we gotten that far?
you just take all your text messages and upload them yeah, but mine would probably
have a bunch of bro. I am not letting that group chat leak like that.
We should train a under group chat. We train the AI on a group chat. I think it
would blow too many minds yeah being stuck between you, us three and and
Jubio. Oh my people wouldn't even be able to. We should make a Jubio. We
should be Jubio DJ, Jubio and he can play songs yeah. He doesn't like music
that much. Yeah, I don't know. He does because he loves me when I use the Plex.
I see that he's got a lot of choice of on on his music.
Is that true? Yeah, every time I open the play again, man, there's a lie.
I open the Plex.
I open the Plex. I scroll down the TV and then there's this music at the
bottom. What's the choice of on song? Rush? No doubt of one. I don't know any
other one.
What's how's rush go?
*Humming*
Is that about poppers? Yes.
Really? Uh huh. And dancing.
They think they can get this stuff by me. This Lady Gaga
song is about fucking your face.
Which one? Just Dance?
No, the "poke your face" one. She says "fuck
your face". No, no, no. "Poke your face" is about
her having sex with a man and pretending
it's a woman.
But women hate poker.
Women like poker. Not Lady JaJa.
What'd you say? Lady JaJa.
No, don't say that. That's a tarjay.
Ja-ja, lady ja-ja, Jaina.
That's what, cause she, you know, plays with Jaina.
You could maybe say lady vag-
Lady... Lady va-ja-ja. Lady va-jay-jay.
Lady va-ga-ga. You could say that.
Lady va-ga-ga. Yeah.
And hey, this whole meat dress. Oh, you're wearing a meat dress.
Why don't you just go bottomless, you fucking
big-ass, flapping labia. Yeah, I'd like to meet, I'd like to meet
dress. Yeah, dress.
Yeah, I'd like to meet dress. She sounds sexy.
You know, I found out something
crazy today. Dress sounds like the name of like
like a like a 1950s film star like tree Williams or like
dress dress like like dress ray or something dress ray dress. Trumbull he
has never seen true detective season one really. I was gonna re watch it. I'm
gonna re watch. I think the new one just came out in the street. Williams a
1950s movie guy. I think he's past that. Yeah, funny names true. It's really
funny that they were like, let's name a what's a guy from the south named rust
Rust Cole. I know the names and everything. I saw the final episode.
Rust Cole. I saw the final episode of season one because my dad was watching
it in the living room and I was on the computer. Here's what you do,
you walk in, you see that he's watching a Matrix you haven't watched.
My dad? Yeah, I'm out. I'm gonna go. I wanna use the computer.
The computer, he was watching it on the computer? I was downloading music
legally. Then put your headphones on. I was downloading music illegally,
which is
legally.
What illegally downloading music is a gray area crime, which you can talk to a
lawyer about. I would say that's a white and black area crime. Yeah, that's
pretty... If you're saying illegal in the beginning, you're illegally doing
anything is illegal. But if you get this MP3 from your friend...
But that's sharing. That's sharing, but it's technically what's the legality
on that we'll find out what's the sharing or stealing. We'll find out today on
today's episode and now put the intro here.
There's no what intro what intro the podcast like the whole podcast is the
open. This is the open twenty minutes.
fuck it, let's do it, let's do it,
twenty minutes
oh, I bet y'all thought we forgot the intro. I bet y'all thought Jupio forgot
to put the theme song in today. We thought the episode started. Nope, it
just started, bitch. It's starting now. It just started right now. Wait, we
should be doing that more. Yeah. We should be starting the episode. Wait,
we already made a cold open. We already made a cold open, though. This was the
cold open. We do cold open straight into the podcast, 20 minutes. That's the cold
open. Because then you lull them into a false sense of security.
We'll save the one that I made for the next episode, I guess.
No, we'll use it for this.
All right. We'll have two cold opens this episode.
So explain the outfits, please. Explain these lawyer style outfits.
All right. Well, Cameron looks like my paralegal and I look like a lawyer who
is...
Okay, shut the fuck up.
No.
Wrong.
You're going to jail, bitch.
that was the
respectful thing. I was
explain your outfits. You start by saying that I'm your paralegal. You
look like a car. You ever worn the entire
you look like you spin a sign for a local restaurant. This is not like I
spin a
being a drag. I'm not a girl, a lad and being a drag. You are bro. I look
like a lawyer who has you look like you smell like a sewer. You work in
I don't look like I smell like a sewer. This is the worst. This is
literally the worst outfit you've ever worn. You put on the shirt. You thought,
so this isn't enough. You put on the vest and you try to save it with
nothing. There's a nothing of an you look like a young puckish lawyer,
puckish, puckish, a no, I'm all business. There's no mischief here. No,
no, no, he looks like he could get a legal loophole. You got I don't I don't
go and I look like I deal with the eyes. You don't look like you deal with
don't look like any kind of you look like you never had a no cards. This is
like those this
know it's so you look like a homeless guy from where I'm one of the haircut
videos. You look like in a looney tunes when they get pushed, they get slammed
through a room and they come out wearing all the things that were in the room.
You look like a train hobo. Well,
imagine if a train hobo was a lawyer.
Why would they be a little again? This is you making the deals for law for
legal things dealing with the homeless. Why would a homeless person be
representing homeless people. I would be representing another homeless person.
In what court? In Hobo, 1930s style Hobo. In kangaroo court? Yeah, in kangaroo
court. I look like a lawyer from kangaroo court. No, you don't. There we
go.
I look like... If this was in black and white, I would look like an old
lawyer. Can you put a black and white filter over me? No, it's not in
black and white. No, you look terrible. I would look like Gregory Peck
in the Kill a Mockingbird. Oh my God, you're dressed like the gourmet detective.
you got a gore, you got a vest on under the jacket. Wait a minute. I like the
or made detective, you know about the gourmet detective, but you mean the
phantom gourmet, no the gourmet detective, I don't know, we've been
watching the gourmet detective on movie Mondays. This is exactly what you're
wearing, but you're wearing
like the gay
what the fuck is the court. He's a detective who solves food crimes like
what kind of crime murder it there's none of them have anything to do with
food. Oh,
this guy. You I don't look like you look like this guy. I do not look like that
guy. You don't look like anything. That's what we're trying to tell you.
You really it's not it's giving nothing. It's giving nothing and you're eating
all the or you're leaving crumbs everywhere. Nothing is so giving zero to
me. It's not giving anything. This is a is a NBA two K create a player. If you
stopped at the vest, this is create a coach. Yeah,
Okay, that you might look like you might look like a little kids, NBA, create a
coach in two K, where you just max out everything. Yeah, oh, whatever this thing
is.
All right, well, well, anyway, I look like a lawyer who would lose a case. I'm
a I'm a real ass lawyer and I'm skinny and I'm breaking that.
I do I do
domestic violence, but only between brothers.
What would you qualify as domestically abuse of relationships between brothers?
Slaps, punches, or harsh words.
Things that my brothers, my two older brothers, would do.
Or stealing between each other.
I would say this is boys being boys, and you're saying this is a crime.
See, I lay down the law.
I think we've let boys get away with being boys for far too long, and it's time.
And listen, if a brother comes to me and says his brother has been taking his toothpaste,
I'm coming down on him. Toothpaste is communal in a family. No, not if the
brother thinks that the other brother, the only the only time it's not if you
get the red toothpaste, the white. I let you in. I let you in on a secret. Yes,
sir. As a lawyer, it doesn't matter to me what is moral or ethically true.
It's about who's paying me. Yeah, you're a bad lawyer. That's a good lawyer.
That's a good lawyer. It's a good lawyer. You have no regard for the
truth. Exactly. I'm I'm I'm scrappy. Yeah, I'm hungry. Scrappy. The lawyer
Scrappy the lawyer. Oh my god. There we go.
The law offices of Scrappy the lawyer.
Scrappy Esquire. Oh yes.
Scrappy and Dew. Yes. Scrappy Esquire.
And look he's got a Harvard
mug.
Or bottle. Bottle. It's a bottle.
Because he went to Harvard Law. I went to Harvard
School of Science Law. Really?
I remember when I... Scientific Law.
Lawyering. When I was in Boston
touring. What's it made out of?
Old Hollywood. It says at the bottom.
It's made out of metal. It says something crazy.
screw it on and I'll look at the bottom.
It's just a kind of...
Oh, he's trying to fool you by telling you to turn the bottle upside down.
It says poly concept.
What the fuck is poly concept on a water bottle?
Only a lawyer would understand this.
Yeah, that's a lawyering word.
And I want to get into that.
This is called legalese, guys.
Jargon.
Were you talking about you being in Boston?
When I first moved to Boston and my mom helped me move my shit in, we walked over to Harvard
law, the Harvard Law campus and we walked around and my mom said, "I can't believe I'm walking
where Obama walked."
And I don't know why that stuck with me my whole life.
You can say that on any place.
I can't believe I'm walking where Obama walked.
Yeah, he's been most places.
You can say that about a good chunk of places.
Well, no, he's not Forrest Gump.
No, you can say that about the apple orchard in my hometown.
You can say that about Gump, any road Forrest Gump probably came in.
He's been a lot.
I can't believe I walked where Gump walked.
Obama has been more places than the average person has been.
Yeah.
There's no question.
He's been to every state.
So, yeah, it's fair to just...
walk outside there and say I can't believe I'm walking where Obama Obama
did not walk on, but it's like the percent chance that you'd be right
versus saying I can't believe I'm walking where it's gotta be twenty five
John Stevens walked. Well, I don't know who that is. I just walked well,
but that's probably because we walk down this because you don't know who that
is. There's probably many of them. So John Stevens is probably more like one.
Okay. John Stevens, the one who was born in 1973. Okay. Okay. Maybe probably
didn't want. He's less likely likely to have walked here than Obama. Well, I
yes, this is true. Okay, well again and the way it's all about percentages and
lawyer,
the likely lawyer has defeated me once again, the legal eagle himself scrappy
lawyer, sick of this legal eagle guy, who's that he's a youtube video. Oh,
he's the one that watches the wait. Which one is this? He's some piece of
shit with a suit who goes up. He's doing it makes all these videos like legal
lawyer, illegal eagle, lawyerly reacts to TV show.
You know who this outfit is based on? You should be in court. Why are you
making YouTube? Have you seen the other lawyer that wears like the big...
What is his name?
There's this lawyer who is on YouTube and he does these snaps of the camera
and then it transitions to him in his office reading a book and he says,
"If you ever get pulled over, say I don't consent to any searches,"
and he's very southern.
Oh, I've actually seen this guy.
He's cool. This guy's awesome.
You have a bunch of rings.
Yeah, he's got a bunch of rings and a
big wig. Yeah.
The Saul Goodman guy.
Yeah. Real life.
So he's cool.
I got to fuck with him.
Yeah, it's cool.
But the legal eagle.
Never heard of this guy.
He's too. And I don't like that
lawyers are on average better
looking than people who work
in trash rooms.
It's because they can afford gene
therapy. I think that's that for
sure. And genes from DNA
resequence from Kenneth Cole
reaction.
I want to start a brand of jeans called therapy. Therapy. That's good. That would
be good. Oh, that's good. Oh, my God. You guys want to hear an idea I had. I
thought when I was a kid that I just remembered the other day. Yes, this is an
idea I thought would make a million dollars. So I didn't tell anybody. I was
like I grow up. I'm going to make this. Yeah, now you're up. I'm now I'm up. I'm
going to make it basically. It's like a lollipop, but it's not ready, but it's
hollow and inside it's got some types of little candies and it's get this. It's a
a candy maraca.
They might have that a lot of money. They might have that in Mexico. I don't know
if they do. Do they have that in Mexico? I'm certain they have it in a country
that we haven't heard of a candy maraca. Do they have that in Mexico? You can
shake and it goes. Yeah, it goes. Yeah, they do. All right. Well, okay, well,
we'll make it hot then. Yeah, spicy. No, like a candy. That's spicy. Yeah,
that's not bad. I have that in Mexico. Spicy
madness. Nope okay, well, then we're good. We can do that okay. Let's dive
into this eagle, which also the reason we're talking about lawyers is because
we're doing the lawyer website again today. The law advice website, a
different one, though what right is it a different? No, no, no, it's the same.
I thought we did avo last time we did. What did you do? Oh, we did a different
website. Yeah, we had a different website. What did you guys collaborate
on something? Well, how did you both do a random different? I asked him what it
was and he sent me a different website. Yeah, what yeah, I found a completely
new website. Okay, well, we're doing law advice, legal advice again. It's the same
kind of thing. I didn't know about the secret website. Well, this website that
we found. I found some good stuff on the old one. Yeah, who should go first then?
'Cause we have. You guys go. I'll go first. We have a new website. Mine's open.
I'll go first. Mine's long. This is from justanswer.com/long. Which this morning,
we had a very funny who's on first almost happen. Yep, 'cause I asked him,
"What's the website?" And he said, "Just ask." And he said. I'm asking you. Yeah.
And he said, "Just answer."
Okay, wait, do we have the clicker? No, we haven't had the clicker for a year.
Bruce. Oh yeah, this one just person just said, "I started weak." This one,
this guy just says, "Bruce." And then... What did you look up to find Bruce?
I don't know, it was just in the recent asks, I think. It just said,
"Bruce," and then go next slide, and this is just a guy, a customer says,
"Hi, Bruce." So the way this website works is actually a little different
than AVO. The way this one works, it's much more similar to Practo,
I would say where the people, the lawyers are getting presumably paid based on if
they get rated for their answer on this website. Okay. So I think that this has
to be this guy. Bruce is giving himself who has 38,000 satisfied customers.
Can't be true. He is giving he's laundering money. It's giving laundering.
Yeah. So this is Bruce. Next slide, please. I think it costs $1 to ask a
question. I have a legal question and I'm as going to see if you would mind
answering it for that's nice. So that's nice of them next one and Matthew says
good morning. Your question does not say much about your question, so hopefully
I'll be able to get your get your answer help you get your answer. Last name is
Esquire
next slide and so this person says, Sir, thank you for responding on such short
notice. Just wondering the legality of this, because I see it quite a lot. This
is in Pennsylvania. By the way, if someone were to say drop their cat from
ten to fifteen feet on a soft surface because they quote land on their feet.
Is there anything illegal about it, even if the cat likes it?
I will say that is not illegal.
Well, customer says and then customer said, hi, next slide.
Stop moving my shit.
Next slide is somebody was making a parody song about Elon Musk and they
want to know the legality. Okay, this song is about Elon Musk and it's say
sang from his perspective. The song mocks his recent decisions and exaggerates his
views on the world, portraying him as a Disney villain like character, something
close to South Park style humour, but less violent. I'm wondering if Musk can
potentially sue us for making it, and if yes, are there ways to prevent it? There
was no answer to this one, but I do want to get your opinions. I think that
Musk can sue, of course, that's your legal right as a US citizen. He's- is he
the US citizen. I believe South Africa is part of America. Okay, English, yes,
he can sue, but of course, also there are ways to prevent him suing you for
example, brainwashing him legally, brainwashing him using videos and TV,
like
strapping him down in front of something and taping his eyelids open, that type
of brainwash, right or telling him not to. Okay, and the type of lawyer that I
look like would say if this case involves any kind of tin can,
then I could take it. The type of lawyer that you look like would say this
because he doesn't exist. There is no, but is it you? There's gotta be like
some if it if this was two people fighting over a tin can,
maybe a song about tin cans and bindles. There we go. That could work.
If the glove fits, you may acquit if it's
if they're trying South Park, let them walk. Yeah, that could be here's the
trick. This is actually a real thing. I don't know if you guys know about
this, you know, the small penis thing, which is where if you're if you're
slandering somebody or you're doing libel or whatever you're doing a parody
of someone and you want to prevent them from suing you for it, you have to also
put in something that's really like embarrassing, like saying they have a
small penis or something like that, because in order to sue, they have to
like prove without a reasonable doubt that it's like, oh, this is me that
they're making fun of. So you have to say
it has to be me. The small penis character is me. Well, it's civic. It's
civil court. You don't have to prove beyond a reasonable. Well, you know what
I mean, I use the wrong words, but that is it. But you do have to prove that you
are. You have to you have to prove that you're there, though you're the one
being made fun of. Here's another one. If it's SNL, you can tell because I
know every sketch. That's another type of you must acquit thing. If it's mad
TV, you'll make madly. Here's a trick. Just change his name. Yeah, to freelance
Dusk yeah, Elon Dusk, Elon Red yeah,
is anything anything doesn't matter okay, beyond beyond X or like Beyonce
beyond X that works to Beyonce. I think you'll have another problem, though.
Yeah, next slide.
I had a co worker asked me if I have noticed the bosses serial killer smile.
I said a little it's probably just a front to assert his power, nothing to
worry about. Can that be considered trash talking and Dolan Williams says
Hello, trash talking is not against the law.
Wow.
Thank God.
Thank God it's still legal.
Bit of a legal revelation for me.
I always thought that trash talking could have been considered some bad style.
I guess it depends who you trash talk.
Libel, I think you call this.
Libel.
Threats is trash talking and threats should not be illegal.
Next slide, please.
And this only took him four minutes.
Hypothetical situation.
And this is, by the way, the best possible thing you can search on this website.
hypothetically. Yeah. Yeah. Hypothetical situation. If someone typed into Google
quote, teen porn or quote porn, would that be regarded slash viewed as
evidence of intent to view child porn answered by Jean C. We're going to see a
lot of gene C right now. No, Jean says no. This is simply that you were
researching something for a project for school. I wa because you heard about
people getting involved in these illegal activities and you wanted to find out
about it. But you did not download any of it, and you do not keep going back to those sites."
And the customer says, "Thank you so much for answering the weird questions. Hoping
I don't have any more to ask. Have a happy night."
Gene says, "You have a nice weekend, too." But this continues. Next, customer comes back.
"I do have one more question, but I'm working until 11.30 p.m. Could I ask you tomorrow or
something?" Gene says, "I will eventually come on tomorrow, but I'm not sure when. But
if I'm not available, one of the other experts can help you as well."
says, I hear you. I would be home around 8 p.m. tomorrow. Gene says, Okay, that's fine.
You can't just ask the question. And why? Yeah, why not? So next day? Hello, hope Friday
has gone well. Thank you for your time and patience with me. First question. hypothetical
situation. If someone typed into Google young teen bestiality, porn, young teen bestiality,
teen bestiality, teen bestiality, porn, young bestiality, or young bestiality porn, would
that be regarded/viewed as evidence of intent to view child porn?
Gene says, "Not necessarily, but it is evidence of an interest in something
that is viewed as a different type of sexuality." So if that person keeps
typing these things into Google, they could possibly attract the attention of
someone, therefore they should stop typing this into Googoloa if they must.
Googoloa. Okay, next slide. I like Googoloa. Customer says, "Hypothetical
situation. What if someone accidentally views child porn?" Gene says, "Then they
should get off the website as soon as possible. You can't help what you
accidentally view, but it's best to stay away from those type of websites with
your own computer because this stuff seems to come up more than you wanted to.
So maybe you should take a break from using your computer to view any type of
materials of this nature so you don't have to worry about it. One of my
favorite parts of these types of websites is people who like are clearly
like did something very bad and are approaching like a court date and I was
going to website and they post something like so I feel really bad about this. I
I did something I shouldn't have. I killed a guy. It will I get in trouble
yeah and all the responses are like delete this.
You just have to imagine that they just have this just like there has to be an
alert that goes off on someone's. I like to imagine that this this hypothetical
situation is happening between every message and then he has the tabs open is
going right back, but there's a lot more trust me next slide. Please
thank you for your patience with me. Gene says the customer next slide
hypothetical situation. If someone typed into Google young teen scat porn or
young scat porn, would that be regarded as evidence? Next slide.
Long as they do not continue going back to those sites and, most importantly,
don't download any forbidden materials, customer says, I want to thank you one
more time. I'm almost finished. He's asking the same question every time. I'm
almost finished with the odd slash stupid question.
Hypothetical situation question. What if someone watches a video titled something
like young teen does something?
the video, etcetera. It doesn't say anyone is underage. Next slide about
the bestiality questions above when you said not necessarily if that person
literally made that search once or maybe twice, then they don't have anything to
worry about. Gene says no, that is not illegal. It's simply a sign of odd
preferences. Customer says, gotcha, gotcha.
Thank you so much, Gene. I think that is all. I hope to never bother you with any
weird questions again. You're an angel. Thank you so much for your time and
patient. The gotcha gotcha is so fun. Got you got yeah cool got you. Jean says no
problem have a nice weekend. Okay,
next slide
hypothetical situation. What is someone typed into Google teen incest, born
young, incest, born or young, teen incest, born gene says same thing as I
said above. What if they googled that and then googled the beality one or
something like one search after another or like they did one search one night
and the other search the second night next. The best thing for you to do is
stay away from the computer for a while. Whatever you did, you cannot undo,
and if you keep trying to undo it, you'll probably cause more problems
rather than less. So the best thing to do is avoid the computer and avoid
the topics you are bringing up. Have a nice weekend. Next slide.
Totally, totally. What if someone made those searches and maybe saw something?
Just leave it alone/in the past, pretty much. Gene says, "Exactly. Best
wishes. You as well," says customer.
Leave it in the past,
that's fine.
or would be just fine. I love this leave it in the past and that person should be
just fine. They realize that they're talking about hypotheticals or would be
just fine. I'm sorry. You mentioned reading material. What if someone read
erotica about a minor engaging in sex acts? Is that illegal? Would that be
viewed slash regarded as intent of you child porn or anything just leave it in
the past and that person is okay next next thing they say okay slash fine
equals not in trouble slash charged or anything and then gene just didn't
respond. Yeah, at a certain point, he's asking the same question over and over,
but that's really chat structure. I know the way this one works is a really
good chat. It's incredible that it's public. Why would this be? Why would it
be public? Because people could have like similar scenario or situations,
but every single one is so specific to a person that it should not be public.
Imagine if you like your chat with like the like chat bot on like a car
dealership website or whatever was public, you know, the ones they have
for you have read yeah. I want to forge truck. Do you have read
and then next slide please?
What does M I L F stand for my boss keeps getting things from those initials. I
know it is porn, but what does it stand for lawyer reacts me? I'm lawyer fool.
Well, a lawyer probably would say that
a lawyer would, but if you were a civilian,
Okay, I think international law. I'm pretty sure I'm pretty pretty sure it's
masculine
in iguana,
illicit, illicit
love fest love fest. It's a gay. I think it's a boy thing. I still think I think
my international law firm is what it's good to my next slide. I think is my
last unless that one's my last. Let me see.
Nope. That one's the last one. All right. That's that's what I got from just
answer slash law guys. I'll do mine now. I'll show you some from the old
website from Avvo. All right,
so here's the first one. How to get trial or charge a change of venue. This
judge is old, miserable lesbian.
I just wanted to put that. How did you find that title? I think I searched
venue or something. I did not search lesbian, even though you think I did.
What is it? I did not. You thought that it was a video tab. I did not
I search some nasty stuff man, but I didn't do as a miserable.
I think I actually did type miserable. That's what I search
lesbian really good searches on these websites to let me put you on misery,
agony, miserable torture. I have one that you're really the one search term
that you're really going to like to that. I searched a lot was hypothetical
and hello, sir yeah, hello, sir, always got somebody who really was not that
good at talking. What if I did a Grinch photo shoot but changed it to the
Green Man? I am new to photography, so want to see if I can do a Grinch photo
shoot but use Green Man name instead. I feel like this is
tearing yeah. This is a like parody slash just what I just like. I'm new to
photography. I want to do a great so I don't know about stuff like this. If
you can, I say Green Man, if he's a Green Man with no green hair, yeah,
even a green man with green hairs, okay and a Grinch as long as he's not
completely. I say this is that's it yeah, because you can be ugly and green
yeah exactly. Here's a few that go together. My boyfriend has jock itch
really bad and was seen at a McDonald's parking lot itching, but it was called
in under indecent exposure. He went to the station to put in a statement, but
never gave a ticket. If he is found guilty and has to register as a sex
offender, will that prevent us from ever being able to have children or get
married in the state of Oklahoma? What is the sentence he could be given and
what restrictions could he have? Here's another one that goes with that is
rubbing your groin in front of someone a crime
and then public genital scratching illegal. I was recently given a ticket
for grabbing my genitals in public outside my clothing in view of public. I
can't seem to understand on how a person either scratching himself or rearranging
the northern region can be charged with anything. You can go to the next slide
Julio that's on the next slide.
okay, not that one. So just a bunch of people who got in trouble because they
were scratching. I don't think scratching should be a crime. Scratch is
not a crime. I mean are they saying that they pull out the genitalia area? I
really these are this is the ones I put these in because it really does seem
like they're probably do it. They're like they're definitely a jock. It's at
McDonald's and they've yeah, jockey jock. It's at McDonald's is a crazy thing.
Yeah, no man, I got a horny is fucking looking at the menu and all the bad
honey meal stuff, the promotional videos. Here's the next one. What can we do
she's hurting?
We just got to eat cheddar. My wife stepped out of the truck, slipped and
fell on the ice in the parking lot. What can I do?
We just got to eat.
I searched each other to see if it's like a restaurant. Here's what it is.
Here's what it is.
he's bad. He's bad punctuated. Okay, we just got to eat cheddar. My wife
stepped
this is so like what can I do? He's so panic. What can I do? He's so many he's
not making it. He's just typing so fast that his auto
we just got people. What did we
we cheddar and then my wife stepped out of the truck. Maybe the cheddar is
hurting now she's like include all the details. Okay, we ain't chatter.
We just got to eat cheddar. What can we do? She's hurting. We just got to eat
cheddar.
That is good, then we got can I sue chipotle for hurting myself on their
walls? I was waiting in lined for food with my girlfriend when I stuck my
finger and one of the holes on the wall in chipotle
get out for the life of me, but after some time of struggling, I managed to
set myself free, but got a mild laceration as a result. Can I sue for
hurting myself with their decor? No, no, no, no, I know exactly what they did. Do
you know they have the like as tech style? Yeah, they stuck their finger in
that.
I mean, this can you imagine being in line at chipotle, your fingers like
everyone behind you like come on
your finger. Come on next pro next, please like
I just imagine being in line in Chipotle and somebody sticks their finger and starts wailing and crying.
I told Carter about this in the AI. I said, "I have a fantasy about sticking my finger in the wall."
That's true.
My finger stuck to a wall.
You shouldn't do it because you're going to get lacerations.
I have an immediate answer.
And likely have no legal recourse.
You know what? You're better than Carter.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
You're way better than Carter.
Thank you.
Carter would not answer that question. He said it was inappropriate, but you...
It's appropriate.
You gave me a good answer.
Yeah.
what the fuck and illegal to do it's not illegal to to finger a legal now and
she just made it that's private property. We just made it. It's not
illegal to touch never mind. How can I sue KFC for pain and suffering of my
tear meniscus on my left knee and a back pinch nerve? I worked for KFC and I
slip and fall on a raw piece of chicken skin, slip and fail on a raw piece of
chicken skin. Now I'm with a tear meniscus on my left knee and pinchy
serve. This happened back in May 2nd, 2018. That's been changing. This is
recent. They did this. They were like, oh, I just remember when I slipped on
chicken skin. I wonder if I can get anything. This should be like
like a sports injury, I think, qualified for that. You need to go to us. But
yeah, torn meniscus is like plenty of, plenty of football players. Yeah. You
trip on a piece of raw meat. Yeah, classic. Yeah. It's like our skin. You're
out for a cut, some chicken skin. You're out for four or five years. KFC could
Kentucky football championship. Probably is certainly be well. Here's another fast
food one. Can I sue McDonald's over there being snot like substance in my
drink? I don't know if intentional or not still unacceptable during covid
just
just was getting some hot acts and hot chocolate to start of my morning. I've
never had any problems before at any other locations till this morning. I
order hot chocolate with my meal, but when I drank it tasted like a slimy
goopy
you
like a slimy
amazing line to be given. I this is like to go to court. It tasted like a
slimy gooby your honor. It tasted like a slimy gooby, the gooby. We please bring
up the slimy gooby. The taste was
and we substance all over it really don't have words to describe texture. It
was same texture like snot use my fork and scraped up a lots from the inside. I
have photos I can provide if needed just need place to send them. I'm never
usually that guy, but this is my first time ever actually feeling like I have
to leave a report. I'm open to being tested or whatever to prove it's not my
own.
he kept the slimy gooby. It was a good man. We took a photo, but yeah,
it's going to test it. Yeah, he's keeping it man in this. This needs to
go to
I had to so many of this type of thing of finding slime or gooby. This should
be
as gooby. You know the material. This is not a one for everyone keeps it as
the one of as the one. Oh yeah, everyone says I still have it. I put it
in my fridge. I don't think that this is a problem for the United States
support system. This is a problem for Mori yeah. This is a a more. It is not
your gooby
by your
fucking gooby
fifty back flips in a row, not my gooby. The gooby does not belong to you.
Here's the next one. Can a police officer use a slim Jim to enter my car
without my permission? I just want to read the full thing for that. Oh, this
next one is horrible. This is one of the most horrible things I've ever read. I
went to the county health department to get a pap smear and the doctor got the
speculum stuck in my vagina. What did you look up to find this speculum? No,
I searched I'm trying to remember what I searched. It was not vagina Papa. I
always all the grossest most horrible ones. I always find because I searched
something innocuous and then something crazy comes yeah, the doctor I went to
get a pap smear. The doctor did not lubricate the speculum before and
certain after the pap was done. She was unable to remove the speculum. She said
the speculum was stuck because she could not get it to close. He started
pushing, pulling and twisting the speculum while it was inside of me.
When that did not work, she started opening it wider.
She said in a panic voice it stuck and I can't get it out.
She it's just so horrible. This is why men should be the gynecologist, not
women, because I don't care what they feel yeah. This one is just rip it out.
Oh okay, here's the next one. You know, like I shouldn't I should have taken
that one out hurts really bad. Of course it does, but I don't care. I have a
penis. All right, my husband purchased and consumed Gatorade with slime and
worm looking thing in it. He drank four before he discovered it now sick. What
record should we follow? He drink a worm in the
you got for Gatorades with slime and worm door. There's a bunch more
Chad, which I made a mountain do the fly in it
made a mountain eight drank me
make mountain do. Here's the next question. It's under internet law. Is
illegal to sell slime at schools in Ohio. Oh yes,
most normal school in Ohio, slime selling school,
here's the next one a little close to home. Can I sue tick tock for destroying
my marriage? My husband was home during cove in for a while and now my marriage
is destroyed. All he does is watch video after video. We argue about this every
day. He doesn't talk to me or hear nothing. I say this is one of the most
common problems in all of America at the moment. This is the cove in tick tock
but ninety percent of white people are getting divorced. My wife and I here's
the next one. My wife and I lived at twenty one Totten street in Bethpage,
New York. During that time, they dug gunk out of the ground. They're
grooming
is a full orc life. Yeah, I dug gunk out of
now. What I did is I took out the body of this one, because this one is
actually brutal. Is there suddenly really sad and there's the wife got
cancer from the gunk? It was cancerous gun. It was cancerous. I don't want to
hear about all this, so you don't have to hear about that part. I hate what
should I do if I found a rubber jelly like
my bag of chips, I was eating my chips when I almost finished when I reach in
the bag, grab the last of my chips and put it in my mouth. I immediately felt
something blueberry jelly like substance in my mouth, so I went to the kitchen
sink and threw it in the sink. I then grabbed it and put it in the bag that I
was eating. I this would ruin my day, finding bad blueberry rubber,
blueberry rubbery jelly. I love the narration of always what they do.
they're always like they say well. I was eating, then I tasted a blubbery,
rubbery, gooby, and then I threw it. I threw my gooby back in the bag,
my blueberry gooby. All right, here's a here's one. I want to hear from you
about this is, I think your area of expert. All right, all right, there's a
question about intellectual property. Oh me. Do you put the app word on your
trademark, such as peanut butter and jelly a little ignorant about
trademarking?
what does that mean? Do you put the app word on your trademark such as
peanut butter and jelly at
peanut butter?
He's going to see if
you should trademark the word peanut butter and jelly or it's a trademark
peanut butter and jelly. I see now he's saying he's starting an app. It's
either
apple
trying to
trademark
do we see if this app
I need to see
I'm going to see if this is oh my God, it's so funny to make an app called
peanut butter and jelly. It's even funnier to try and copyright the words
peanut butter and jelly peanut butter and jelly. This has to be out right now.
Wait a minute, peanut butter and jelly TV
that's pbj tv peanut butter and jelly at jello balo. He might be stuck on the
intellectual property tree. I'm also just seeing jello balo peanut butter,
jelly time and subs subs is an app for sandwich recipes. Okay, cool and then
the garden of bun bun. All right, what do you think peanut butter, jelly app or
peanut butter, jelly, peanut butter and jelly app? It has to be. I still have a
much more, so I'm going to start going fast. I found a bunch of good ones. This
don't. I think this actually means something, but I could not stop laughing
at just at the just this phrase is penal code two one one considered a wobbler.
If I did not go to prison but received a felony, it's penal code two one one
one, a wall, a vote because he wobbled, I guess he's a it's a wobbler yeah.
He's a wobbler question can sued Duncan Donuts. I eat croissant that has rubber
glove.
it's so funny to me to imagine eating a croissant that has a rubber glove. What
is this?
Did you get the peanut butter jelly? You tell me
peanut butter jelly up
okay next one. Okay, I understand the floor had a crack in it and a bubble
underneath the crack in which, when I took the next step, I trip
I love starting with
okay, I'm coming to you because I finally got what happened to me. It's an
excellent legal recourse. Okay, I understand, I understand. Can I sue the
company that makes bubble day game for false advertisement? I downloaded the
game that said you will win money. If you get ten thousand points
bubble,
here's another intellectual property question. Can I make custom South Park
characters. No, no, you cannot don't my God. Try this next one is the most evil
thing I've ever seen on this website. This is so horrible. Is it illegal to
give a minor sperm so they have a child? I'm very curious if this would be
illegal. Could I be charged with something if I did give my sperm to a
minor? I'm twenty four and she is fifteen. There will be no sex just
giving her my sperm. Is that illegal? Yeah,
kill yourself. I mean it's a loop. He found the loop
so
I found so much stuff like this on this website, because I search a birthday,
because I was trying to find stuff like oh so and so ruin my birthday
celebration or something and it's all can I have sex with this girl? Her
birthday is twenty eleven. Birthdays only in two hundred and four months,
yeah horrible found this creature inside my bag of candy. So my question is who
do I need to talk to about this? I brought some gummy jolly rancher candy
and I found this creature inside my bag of candy. So my question is who do I
I had to talk to about this creature and I've been vomiting since I saw it
inside of my bag. Well, just by seeing it,
incredibly powerful, this is the most disgusting creature in the world. Can I
get sued from an injury which required surgery due to consensual rough house?
I was at my neighbor's barbecue, the homeowner, his friend and myself were
the only three left at the bar. We were having cocktails and having a good time.
The host was telling me that he wasn't a big fan of our neighbor across the
street because he was coming on to his wife. Jokingly, I mentioned that he's a
pretty big guy and he'd have his have his hands full. If they squared up, he
told me that he was a golden gloves boxer and would have no issues. My comment was
well, if he knows any grappling, there could be an issue. He walked around the
bar and started jokingly throwing blows at me and a few landed on the ribs. As I
was backing up, he threw a few more blows, at which point I came in very
close with a wrestling jujitsu move and picked him up and laid him down on the
ground and locked him up, never intending to hurt him. He has a torn
rotator cuff. The move is not intended to damage, but more of a submission
application. I went back the following day and learned he needed surgery. He
told me everything was okay. He had great insurance. We agreed to split the
copay. I'm now getting nasty grams from his wife. Am I liable nasty gram?
What's a nasty nasty gram for
I got a nasty gram from his wife as I laid him down. I put him on my gram.
Yeah, just somebody knocking at the door. My husband nasty gram. You had my
husband, asshole,
I'm gonna eat shit in front of you.
Okay, here's another long nasty gram. Our pictures of cartoon minors being
tickled illegal. Yes, I have clicked on many images of teen male cartoons
being tickled over the past few years. They have usually been between the ages
of fifteen to seventeen, though there have been a few younger ones. In most
instances, the teens are clothed. Sometimes they've been half clothed.
There have been a couple instances where they haven't been clothed. I normally
try staying eighteen plus as much as possible, but the site where I browse is
very liberal as far as these pictures go, and it's easy to click on a picture
that's previewed on an existing page. So you may not necessarily know the
character is below eighteen until you click the thumbnail version.
Currently, I'm trying to get my computer and phone investigated for hacking.
However, the company I want to work with states in their authorization for
anything illegal that's readily apparent found while doing digital forensics
will be reported to the authorities. My question is what I've described
illegal. Is it considered underage pornography and is it prosecutable for
a live follow up question? How old is sponge bob
if you had to guess how old is sponge bob
and then we have I was watching the original karate kid wax on wax off and
learning karate. Then I went to the kitchen and accidentally struck my
husband as I practiced and what a coincidence it was after I read his text
with another woman. Now I have a dv court date, but a woman, I am a woman,
plus I was just practicing karate. Wow, that is the most amazing defense. I've
ever heard you rage punch your husband. You say I was practicing. I was simply
Wax on, wax off. Wax on, wax off from the karate. You have to pick a movie that is
old, 'cause everybody in the jury's seen The Karate Kid. Yeah. And then you have
to show the move. And it has to be a crowd pleaser movie. Exactly. And guess
what he does in the movie? He fucks it up plenty of times. But he always gets
back up. But he always gets back up. Just like you in court. And if your
husband had watched The Karate Kid, maybe he would have gotten back up.
After the... What's the thing he no can defend from? Punch. This one.
the crane, the crane thing, never seen karate kid, me neither fuck. So here's
just a few more of my last work. I though can I say can I say Waldo inspired
for a bikini I am making? Yes, you can say that if you want, you can say that
here's another one here like you can't find the bikini because it's so micro
now just that stripes. I think shut up, sorry, I'm sorry to get really is it
illegal to transform movie characters in Photoshop? Yes, transforming to what
transform them. You can not turn to is it illegal to transform. I think it is by
definition transformative and then here's the last one. This one is really
cracking me up. Just I don't know why I was injured inside a store. A young girl
hit me on my right knee with a Santa Claus pole. My lawyer says to settle. He
wants to settle for five dollars. Just the phrase a Santa Claus pole really was
getting the class. She hit me with a Santa Claus.
I think that's a death penalty situation. Yeah, yeah, all right, so these that the
gooby thing really fucking killed me. I tasted a slimy gooby. Oh my God.
Slimy, slimy gooby. I found a rubber jelly in my gooby.
My gooby.
Alright, so here are my slides now. There's a lot more.
So this first one I looked up, this is how I would find stuff. I just wanted to
show my process. So I would do the site thing and I found
I just really loved this good day. My name is Darren Dukie of Trinidad.
Okay, tell him what you told me about. Then I looked up Darren Dukie. I
think Darren Dukie killed somebody. Whoa and he said the case was called like
the people of Trinidad versus
yeah,
this next one. Is it illegal to post a video taken in my own home of a person
reading is boogers. I know it's gross and there was no answer for that, which
sucks. It's illegal. I would say it's fully illegal. It's fully illegal. This
next one.
How do I answer Liga without being delusional or pathetic? That was a good
search term, was pathetic. It was a lot of very, very sad people asking
questions.
This net and then the legal author expert says, I apologize, but I do not
understand the question. Could you please clarify for me? And then they
said, well, Liga was a client. We had a love affair shortly. I told her that I'd pay her
back for her plane ticket to fly from Copenhagen to Kansas City, 2000-ish dollars. I'd pay her
back the money she loaned me when I was in a jam, but she and I had a falling out during
that trip. She still wants to pay it back. I can't pay it yet. Is there an issue? Also,
I have a question concerning my business startup. Is it okay to start an L-- if I start it--
or is it okay to start it without an LLC for the first months? And the legal author only
answered the LLC question.
LLC question. Of course. Well yeah, there's not, there's no like a law.
Yeah,
and then this next one,
is it legal for me to pay to eat poop from a dominatrix as it comes out of her
if her and I are both willing?
Which then D Winogo Esquire experts said, what state are you located in? They
said Indiana, and they said, there is no statute or regulation prohibiting eating
feces. Moreover, Indiana Code 35-45-4-2 defines prostitution as someone who
performs or offers or agrees to perform sexual intercourse or a
deviate sexual conduct.
Therefore, it is not illegal as long as you are not engaging in
deviate sexual conduct with the Dominic jurors concurrently,
which the other person has.
Okay, I understand.
So with the same answer apply to having the dominatrix perform
cock and ball torture and letting me on me and letting me
and letting her kick me in the balls ball busting or cuckolding
me if we are both ball busting and I would be paying for all
this. Thanks.
And then Dee Winogo says absolutely and they said I wanted
to make sure that you understood what cuckolding
I would be watching the dominatrix have intercourse and after completion,
she would cuckold me by making me lick and eat his come from her. Would that
be legal? Sorry for the delays. I had to leave town for a couple of days.
Yes, the same statute and answer I previously provided would apply to the
cuckolding situation as well. Would that be considered a deviant sexual act or
sexual conduct when she would make me lick another man's come from her
private area after they've had sex. If you are paying her, then odds are yes,
it would be considered deviant sexual conduct and you can get charged
criminally with soliciting prostitution. Okay, so then if I'm not paying her, it
would be legal. Yes, as long as there's no money involved, this is legal. This
case needs to hit court because I need to hear the old judge go and what is
ball busting
I love the jury one ball. I love Bt. I loved so much that he was like okay.
I'm not sure you know what
I just like to clarify I'm eating his come out of her, but
this next one had no answer, but it was a customer saying I use to profanity
words and a fax to a lawyer, asshole and jerk face and now he wants to take me
to court. I'm profanity charges. I want to go in alone and represent myself
because I am not going to fight it. I was wrong and they can rule whatever
they want against me. Do I or should I really need a lawyer with me?
Yes. Cussing is illegal. We've talked about it. Cussing is so illegal. I'm
the number one lawyer. I work on so many profanity cases. Cusses are illegal,
but cussing is different from mom to mom. So it really depends on what
your mom says. Your honor, my client, you thought he said shit,
but you didn't hear after he said, "Tucky mushrooms."
Exactly. Yeah, exactly. See, we had you, he might be saying fudge.
Fudge.
Your honor, have you not enjoyed a steaming bowl of fudge? Exactly.
Every house was different. I was in a lot of like, God dang, a lot of people...
I couldn't say sucks. Yeah, I couldn't say sucks. I could say all the swears.
Or shut up. I couldn't say screw. Now, screw is a cuss in my house.
So it really... And some people had... I went over to my friend's house
and his parents let him say, "Fuck this, fuck that, fuck the dinner that I'm eating."
So it really is a dinner.
I was told in third grade that jerk is a swear.
Suck my dinner up my ass.
Oh, suck my...
Do I sit down at the table telling grandpa that?
Hey, grandpa, suck my dinner up my ass.
Up my ass.
That's a pretty good...
Actually, you should be able to say that.
Suck my dinner up my ass.
Suck my dinner.
Suck my dinner, it depends on the food.
Maybe you have like a savory lollipop.
Stink my dinner.
I could say stinks instead of sucks.
Lick my bob.
Bob, I was a stick my Bob my D. That's my D mom wet my Bob or like my thing
yeah. Any of that should be stick my finger,
lick my finger, because then they say where you say, what what are you
anywhere? Yeah, my stick it and then okay, this next one I did something
incredibly stupid today. While there is no question, it was stupid. I wanted to
see if it was illegal.
I was at a trade show in Las Vegas and I got a call for an emergency and had to
early when I parked this morning it was a single stop bought up against a concrete barrier
in front. I entered the parking lot to find someone had parked directly behind me less
than a foot in the spot that wasn't a space and was sticking out into the roadway not
having time. I spent the next five minutes and 100 turns getting my truck out from front
of turns. This guy's playing boulders. I know making sure I didn't hit his vehicle in the
process scraping up my bumper on the concrete concrete upset. I wrote a note great job parking
like an asshole directly behind me when there's not even a spot insensitive
bastard and left it underneath his windshield wiper. Looking back, it was
rude and stupid, but it was was it illegal under Nevada law? I didn't
threaten him or touch his vehicle. That is the most ex Mormon fucking thing I've
ever heard. Hey, go suck a lollipop. Yeah, what is he? What is he says? Great
job parking like an asshole directly behind sarcasm. Not even a spot in
In Nevada? Insensitive bastard. Is Nevada where ex-Mormons moved to? I think so, yeah.
Because it's the opposite of Utah. I think there's a lot of Mormons in Nevada also.
There's two cities of sin in Nevada. What's... Reno. Las Vegas and Reno. The
whole state of sin, basically, if you ask me. This is Sodom and Gomorrah.
Nevada, more like never had a good thought or emotion in my life. Or impulse when I was
in Nevada because I was gambling and drinking Sprite. Never had a chance to go
chance to go to heaven, never had one and Nevada backwards is heaven. Wow, I think it's it's
head of a bad a about a cadaver. Yeah, it's a magic or this next one.
I have taking the company computer with the out of the office to my home to review more
trash on it of turning it.
I am thinking of turning of turning it over to the law. Some of the girls looking young.
he was on a teen porno site, comma, comma, comma, comma, every ellipsis is a comma.
Just let the law check it.
And if no one is under 18, I'll jam it and give it back to him.
But if there's a girl under 18, will the law arrest him?
And then I'll arrest you.
Well, that's what P Simmons says.
P Simmons says, thanks for the chance to help.
I'm a, I'm an attorney with over 12 years experience.
Hopefully I can help you with your legal question.
What is going on here?
You took a computer with child porn on the computer.
I didn't say child porno. I said it was on a teen porno site that can be eighteen
or nineteen years old. I said some of them would be questionable if they are
under eighteen or under the piece of and says yes. If there's child porn on the
computer, the police can arrest him. My concern is that if you have the computer,
you're also breaking the law. The best thing to do is turn it over to the
police and let them investigate pedophile Simmons man. I'm not. Oh my
God. Wait, that's true. Yeah, he's covering his ass. This next one is this
a strange question. Is there a law about ABDL in public? And then Isaac Esquire says, Thank
you for your question, but please permit me to assist you with your concerns. I happen
to be a Pennsylvania license. My apologies, but by ABDL, do you mean adult baby diaper
lover or something else? If not, I just want to answer the question properly. Yes, adult
baby diaper lover. Hi, there is no law against it. The only law is based on decency, which
means that so long as genitalia is covered up, sincerely, Demetri Esquire.
Okay, so apparently I like that the Isaac knew what a B D L meant yeah. He
certainly I think he probably Googled it. Yeah, can you imagine if
here's the here's the the troll you pull right? You ask this question, the
process. Oh, I'm sorry. Do you mean a B D L is that adult baby diaper lover? I
think I'm not and you say what the hell are you talking about? What the here's
the no I do if they ask me is it is it legal to be a B D L? I just send
Sure fucking hope not.
Then you're the master troll.
And then you get five stars.
Yeah, exactly.
This next one. This is embarrassing, but please bear with me.
I have an unhealthy hobby of watching porn.
I was recently searching for videos with Google
and I searched for something that isn't appropriate
because the word I used doesn't mean what I thought it meant.
Google brought up a page that let me know what I searched for was illegal.
I never saw any picture or video, just that message from Google.
Should I be expecting a visit from authorities?
So what do you guys think the word was?
What is the word?
is the word. Alien.
It's illegal. Is it legal to look at alien porn? It can't be legal. It
shouldn't be legal. It should not be legal. Does Google give you a warning
if you search something illegal? I think so. That's awesome. But the warning...
This is what the customer said. Thank you, Google. This is what the customer
said. "For some crazy reason, I thought Lolita meant a beautiful Hispanic
woman.
So when I search for Lolita hand job, oh my God,
let me know that what I search for was illegal. This is two days ago and I've
been freaking out ever since because I thought because I looked up the actual
definition of Lolita. As long as I didn't view any material and I didn't break
any child porn laws right, having it accidentally open for a second or so is
not equivalent to watching. I like that defense. He only watch it for one
second. Yeah, the hoops, the shut it off that pedophiles will jump through to
make what they're doing legal. I wish that I children, I wish that every other
criminal was doing this. I wish there were questions on this website like like
so I technically may have accidentally killed a guy, but like I only
did I was only was for a second. It was only for a second that I was choking
him out and then like just all these these excuses and it's it's unbelievable.
It really is amazing. These guys are kind of master. This is why I know
kind of master debaters you were talking about people asking questions on this
website right. You know, I guess well, I guess I tried to get my own legal
advice. You're kidding. I tried to click next. I try was trying to do that, too,
but I changed my mind. I tried to get my own legal advice on something. Now I
want you to look at my conversation really quick. Okay, okay, no
welcome. How can I help with your legal question? Hello? Yes, it has recently
come to my attention that an employee of mine has stolen my designs and started
own clothing company. How do I sue him? The lawyer can help you determine if you have a
case. Where are you located? These laws vary by state. I am located in New York City, but
my client is in Mexico. My employee is the most famous singer in Mexico. He is 19 and
weighs 90 pounds. He likes Chalamet. He dances better than most and I am upset he has gone
behind my back and I want retribution. They said chat is completed. They did not want
to take this case on. They did not want to take this case on.
Are you fucking serious?
Jubio, what is this?
Go next.
Oh my god.
What is jubio.bigcartel.com/products?
The Jubio Stellar hoodie?
What have you done? You've taken my designs.
The Jubio Authentic Center hoodie?
You have taken my designs from me and you have started your own clothing brand?
I've been sitting on this Jubio merch forever.
and you haven't I haven't put it that well my design was that the island was
going to be the dot on the eye that's a better design is a better design and
Jubia ripped it off and made it and why is it in pounds that's a good point I
guess it's why are you paying for this in GBP euros your euros rather he's not
answering well that's because I think that this is a different jujubio this is
is a different Jubio or J U Bio J U Bio yeah yeah.
These are just under well, then how are these designs so similar to my just
under beach? Well, it's somebody else ripped you off and you know what they
also ripped off Jubio's name. So we have a case together. We have a kit. You guys
have a co case, which is good because this is going to dip into international
law. This is good. Oh yeah, because I'm not qualified. Holy shit. I've actually
been completely banned from participating in and this might even be maritime law.
if there's a so this means it's legal to do killing. Is it legal to kill someone
in the fucking ocean? Yes, you're real. Yes, if you just go 20 miles off of New
Jersey, you can kill no not 20, but like a lot more.
I think that the country that the person is from would be mad at you. Well,
but being mad is fine. I don't care. I think that you wouldn't be able to go
to that country anymore. Okay, so depending on where it was, they might
get you suck because it's like the thing where someone does something bad and
other country says you got to like in the dark night extra day and kill someone
from the United Kingdom in the ocean. Yes, and just never go well, it depends,
but I bet that the US would send would get you and send you there. Why to get
in trouble because they're fucking narcs man. I'm a Republican. They don't care
about that. Honestly, the people at the top for them. It's not about Democrat
Republican. It's about this either. You got money or you don't. Okay, so I have a
lot of money. You don't. Well, you got a lot of money. You got enough to get on a
boat. Honestly, even the people who have a lot of money in this in our lives like
$100,000, $200,000, that's literally nothing.
How could that be nothing?
That's a grain of sand.
They could buy 20 of these hoodies.
They could buy more than that.
They could buy 20 and just give them out.
Well, I guess if they only have 20 in stock, they could probably only buy 20.
Well guys, this concludes the episode about legal advice.
And if you have money, send $5 to patreon.com/podcastaboutlist where you can see new type of files.
of Dragons, the shareholder meeting.
Speaking of the shareholder meeting, what day is it this month, Julio?
Beers We Drank.
I remember it's on a Sunday.
What?
28th?
Sunday, January 28th will be the shareholder meeting.
That's on Discord, so join the executive producer tier on Patreon and then join.
Make sure you're in the Discord.
And also this weekend, Friday and Saturday, I'm going to be opening up for
little Adam Friedland in a tiny town called Tampa, Florida.
Where are you playing?
The Crazy Comedy Village.
Is it really called The Crazy Comedy Village?
It's something along those lines.
It has a really stupid name.
It's going to be really, really bad.
These shows are going to be terrible.
Please, please, please come out.
Please, and just brighten my day just a little bit.
It's going to be so fucking hell being in Tampa.
He's going to try to make me go to a strip club or something.
Tampa's nice this time of year.
I like movies.
Tampa sucks.
No, I'm not a fan of this area.
It's trash.
Tampa's a junkyard.
We went to Tampa.
We went to Tampa two years ago.
So if you live there, come on out, bitch.
We went to Tampa two years ago for
FYA festival, was it?
Yes. And we got accosted by
an Uber driver.
Accosted? A guy talked to us and
while he was driving us.
Say what it was!
He verbally assaulted us.
By saying what? He said,
"We were taking an Uber to Waffle House and he said,
'You know Waffle House sucks, right?'"
I said, "No, it doesn't."
drivers. And you were acting like this is not a crime against us that we could sue this
man. He said "accosted". He accosted us. This is a crime against the most of us. He drove
you there and you paid him. No, no, no, no, no. He can say whatever he wants. He verbally
assaulted us. Alright, well, every other building in Tampa is an adult video store. Alright,
well then I think I'm going to have a good time. Thank you guys so much. We'll see you
next time.
(static)
- Maybe.
- I have another question.
Do you guys fucking hate me?
(laughs)
You guys fucking hate me, wish I was fucking dead.
- That's a bad prank.
- That is a bad prank.
- I'm not good at pranks, man.
I'm famously bad at pranks.
- You're bad at pranks and you have a prank face.
Your prank face is this.
- I haven't done pranks since when I was a kid,
I did the bucket of water on the door to my brother
and he cried.
- You do this when you're--
- My older brother, six years old.
- You have no poker face for pranks
is when you do a prank, you have a little, you have like a bobblehead
thing.
I don't bobble my head.
You do this, you go.
The other day I got a fake poop and I put it on my kitchen counter as
soon as I got it.
I zero planning, put it on my kitchen counter and my wife walked in
and got home from work and I said, I'm so bad at pranks.
I said, hey baby, can you get me a glass of water?
And I was closer to the kitchen than she was.
I was doing nothing.
I was just sitting in the hallway.
Can you get me a glass of water?
It didn't work, man.
She walked in and she was like, "Yeah, there's a fake poop on there."
We were talking about the master troll the other day.
I was trying to think of trolling I had done in the past,
and I remembered something I did in college that I completely forgot about that people got mad at me for.
Do you remember how, at college, it was like they had the,
it was like a school TV network where you get shows,
It's like they have a staff and you make like, you know, however many episodes or whatever.
And I never did any of that.
But on Facebook, I posted, I made a fake poster for a show for that called "This Shit Fucks"
and I said, "I'm excited to announce I'm making one of these shows.
Please message them on Facebook and ask if you want to be on the crew."
And like, "We're going to have a meeting in this room on this day at this time."
And it was completely not true and fake and a bunch of people messaged the school organization
and be like, "Hey, can I work on this shit, fucks?"
And everyone got really mad at me because it wasn't real.
(Boo!)