That's good, I think. I think so. I did not see very much. Yeah, that might kind of complicate
it, but maybe not. I don't know. I gave one big one. I drink a Celsius this morning and
then because I wanted I went like NPC walk cycle and went to the coffee shop and ordered
a ham and cheese croissant and a cold brew because I thought that I needed to get it,
even though I didn't. I fully grabbed it and then got back here and was like, "Oh yeah,
this is going to be too much caffeine. At some point, I'm going to get scared that somebody
knows my address in the middle of the episode." I can't see anything. Bro, that is so NPC
of you. It's crazy to get a normal ass thing from a store. No, you know what I'm saying?
I'm saying like I get this with the ham and cheese, Chris on every single time I
come here and I'm saying Chris Scott for some reason.
I don't know what the hell is have well guys. It's the new year twenty twenty
four and we've decided to make a permanent change to the lineup of the
podcast
guys. I'm just happy to be here. I like that your glasses say two hundred yeah
two hundred with a I couldn't exclamation point or maybe a one two thousand one
two hundred year two hundred. I'm pretty excited about two hundred. This two
hundred is going to be big. I couldn't find any other ones yeah, but I'm happy
be here. I mean, I wish Caleb the best in his. So the story what happened is what
happened is Caleb last night, our friend Brian, who has been on beers, we drank
and stuff. Brian comes home from Texas and he's like, oh, I've got a bunch of
freeze dried, like
Texas barbecue,
and I want you all to come over and eat it and we're gonna gamble and stuff.
And so Noah is also, Noah comes home last night, also sick as a dog from this
food. I think he said that he threw up and then he was in my bathroom all night.
I like that you led with also
yeah okay,
Caleb got food poisoning for meeting five year old barbecue that was a day old
barb that was in space orbit yeah for two days. So he's sick, he's sick, he's
got diarrhea and throwing up and Noah came home last night, but the thing is
Okay, he's saying Caleb saying he's got food poisoning, but that's because he
always get he thinks he's sick right now from that Noah told me that they drank
they they drank a shit ton of like Noah came home with like six bottles of
booze.
I think that he's maybe just hung over and also a little bit sick from the
food, but I think that he's completely exaggerating how sick the food made.
He told me he slept two hours last night.
He said his phone is broken and he's been communicating with multiple people
all through only me so far today. Wow, I feel like I've been the conduit for him.
That's a thing that a drunken mistake person does a person who's made a drunk
mistake. I feel like he's like a mistake, an Olympian, you know, like I feel like
he just eats the same thing every single day and if his flow gets disrupted, he's
just going to like shit guys. I don't think any of this matters. I think we
need to be excited about twenty twenty four. We should be I'm excited, excited
about twenty twenty four of the year. I have to take these off yeah. Those are
It's so funny that like blindfold for so many years. We had a perfect place to put
the eyes right and now
two. Oh, we had a perfect place for the eyes. We fucking you can't keep we got
to get rid of these. The eyes are twenty years gone. It's four years. No, it's
no, it's not. It's a twenty because twenty twenty had two zeros, but yeah,
but but twenty the twenty tens were not good. I years either. Well, the two
thousands were the last time that these really made sense, but every now and
way of a digit that has a proper hole in it yeah every now and again yeah two
thousand and eight two thousand and twenty two thousand and four
two thousand four. You had two holes. It's the O's yeah
two thousand and twenty five will make a little bit of sense because you could
put the the hole on that five hole. The hole is never going to make sense again.
No now last time the one nine hundred and ninety s were good because you had
the two holes in the nines. Twenty twenty six distant yeah two thousand
were great. Twenty twenty six will be back. Twenty twenty twenty thirty twenty
forty twenty fifty. You know those these are all great. I can't I can't wait man
so the twenty yeah there's listen it's, but we have to give it up for twenty
twenty eight. Twenty twenty eight will be okay.
Twenty twenty eight that will be a
sideways. You can put just to use the two holes in the eight. There's going to
be interesting glasses. There's going to be a little renaissance twenty eight
twenty nine twenty thirty twenty thirty is going to be some exciting stuff, but
they're not twenty twenty four. We're not going to stop. They're not going to
stop making the glasses. No, they're going to push a square peg into a
circular hole every year from now on, just because we had those golden years
the two thousand look at how bad this is. Look at how bad the glasses start.
Did they start in the how long it had to have been two thousand, but I guess
that yeah, that's the only way you would think of doing that. She does this
one where it's the most exciting like one thousand nine hundred and ninety
two. That would be a good year because you can get put in the nines, but you
wouldn't see these people have one thousand nine hundred and ninety one.
Oh, they were patented in one thousand nine hundred and ninety two. That's
exactly what I said. One thousand nine hundred and ninety two would be a good
year. Yeah, yeah, the one thousand nine hundred and ninety two makes sense, but
it makes this is this is this is complicated. This is fussy like this is
pretty much go. You know what here's my thing. I think the night these these
one thousand nine hundred and ninety two glasses wait. They said they were
invented in one thousand nine hundred and ninety two. This woman's wearing
one thousand nine hundred and ninety one that woman is a time traveler that
is she would believe that that is a butterfly effect, but here's what I'm
saying the one thousand nine hundred and ninety two glasses. These have had
to have been invented by either a time traveler or a schizophrenic person
because who looks at the number one thousand nine hundred and ninety two
and says oh glasses yeah. I want to make two thousand you're like oh glasses
glasses or handcuffs or bubble wrap would be great to merge this off of but
nineteen ninety two is a psycho number to look at him. Look at this guy.
We're in the one thousand nine hundred and ninety eight.
That's Jerry Lewis
right there. That's Jerry Lewis, but look at this. It's two twenty, twenty
four. This is like when you like you're like like you know somebody that's got
a dog that should be dead. You know it's like it's like oh yeah that dog to live
in our stolen hours. Yeah, that dog is like it's like oh yeah. This is my
thirty four year old dog. Yeah, that's what these glasses are. We got to put
them down. It's time to put them down until it's time for them to come back to
we're going to feed. We're going to feed the dog a Big Mac with the we're going
to feed these glasses a Big Mac and then they're going to where they're going to
pass away. Why is there liquid all over? Don't worry about it. What the fuck
happened? Nothing happened. What did you guys do? Come on man? Nothing. It's
disgusting. Nothing bad happened
And we're back with amazing Brandon Wardell from Los Angeles, California, man.
All the way from LA.
Let's see, what is Los Angeles?
Holly, Holly, weird.
You hear a lot of this over there in Los Angeles, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
We got a little bit of soundboard today.
I'm on the soundboard. I always do it loud and proud.
And if you're near the... Oh my God.
Yep. Jesus Christ.
Still the entire...
Oh no.
Let's see.
I got to turn this off.
Nothing bad happened.
Were you not here for?
not here. I was not here for whatever happened here. Patrick, what happened? I
there don't worry. We did it. It was you did it didn't you Patrick could have
been Caleb, this famous spiller. Clearly you know, I think it's sticky on the
I spilled in an accident because you want to this. That's crazy. How do you
do that? What did you spill? Tell me what you spilled. Caleb was drinking
Coca Cola. It was Coca Cola and I was going to press the button for I'll
he admitted a flop joke you would you were made a joke and you went to press a
soundboard button and he got that's what happened. That's what happened. I'm
sorry. Well, we're going to forget that in the new year. That's how the last
year ended. That's how last year and we're and I'm forgiving. It was that was
three weeks ago. Yeah, that's the other thing that we were back in the stew.
It's been a minute. It's been since before. It's been a long. I there's a
lot of changes that happened in my life that I don't want to get in. Look at my
new hat. I got for Christmas
Wow for everyone who's listening audio, it's a sour patch kids hat that's
on yellow wow and green wow and it's squishy. What else did he get or was it
just a hat? It's just a hat. I got a family. I'll pitch
charlie bucket style. We're here with Joe today because Caleb is completely
sick. We've gone over this. I guess we're starting off the new year one
member down a new year, new team, me or new team member and I'm wearing. I
I realized just now, I forgot when I put this on, that this hat has reflective stuff woven
into it.
Oh, this is one of those cool hats.
My head is completely shiny on this camera.
That's pretty cool.
That actually does look dope.
We actually both have cool neon vibes.
We have neon hats today.
And Joe kind of didn't get the memo, did he?
Yeah, no, my hats aren't special enough.
No, it's a New Year's hat.
It does look special.
So how did 2024 end for you, or 2023 end for you guys?
Well, we hung out together on New Year's Eve and I had a delightful new
experience. Yeah, it's changed me forever. What was it? It was smelling salts.
Oh, yes, we were doing a lot of smelling salts and it unbelievable.
Patrick told me in his new video, Patrick told me that he smelled about
20 of them. I did. I was a fiend. They were awesome. Have you ever smelled
smelling salts? I don't think so. So basically, it smells so bad that you go
like this, but it wakes you up. It keeps you you hyped and wired ammonia. Yeah,
it's ammonia. It was like so bring me up. It was called like like wild insanity or
something. It had like a you know the joker on the on the bottle or something
like that, and I was like looking at it because I didn't. I was like, oh, I
wonder if just like what it says like is in this or the side effects or anything
on the bottle. It says nothing. There's it's just it's just like yeah, evil,
evil serial killer bottle. If the joker's on it, there's pretty good chance. I was
Oh, I it was it was his own. They're the brand's own character. Yeah, joker, but
you know what I mean? The type of vibe, the pre workout vibe and I was kind of
powdered insanity, right? So yeah, something like that something insanity
and I was thinking, wow, this is incredible. The smell is so bad. I need
to get a bottle of this for myself so I can make myself do things and get hyped
up, but because it says nothing on this bottle, I have to assume this is going
to kill me if I do it multiple times. So I get home. I google it on my computer.
I Google smelling salts, long term effects, adverse side effects. I Google
all these keywords. Guess what guys nothing yeah, really not bad for you at
all. Isn't that unbelievable government websites dot gov dot gov dot gov. They
want you to do smell. They say it's dangerous to breathe in ammonia. If
you're in a room full of ammonia, but smelling salts, guess what it doesn't do
anything. It doesn't even do anything good. You just play with chemicals bro.
it's just chemicals. You just it's just a smell. It's so funny. It's a smell
that's so crazy that it makes something happen in your brain. Jack put out that
video today and it's like
he has a bit in the video for the smelling salts
and it's so funny the realization like, "Oh yeah, Jack just bought these for
like a three second
clinic video. I want them. I'm gonna buy them for myself. It's such a genius
idea. It's so good. I literally think I literally would like to do them before
every single episode from now on. I think right before hitting record, I
think it will power everything up. It really I was
yeah, I think your boards in his room. I was going. I would smell do the
smelling salts and then I would do like finger board tricks on his like little
bench thing. It was so sick, really productive with the smelling. Dude, I
need them right now. I think it's the same thing where you just build up a
tolerance to it and then you're filling your room up with ammonia and then
you're dying. Yeah, you're not filling your room up with ammonia. That's not
that leading, but I was that's what I was saying, though, when we were doing it,
I was like can you like I was talking about how I wanted to get some to to to
pop me up for when I need to be pumped up like when I'm going to kill somebody
or something yeah and chase something exactly a chase scene yeah and
well you smell it and it's so strong and it's so affecting and it feels like a
laser is going into your face and you go
oh my God, and I was thinking, can you imagine the moment in your life to like
it's like after you've done it the first time, then you have the montage of your
whole life after buying it and then the one sniff, the one that where you get it,
you sniff it and you just it's nothing. You don't react at all. You sniff it, you
go
right. You have such a because you built up such a tolerance to it. Wouldn't that
be so horrible? You're supposed to hold them like really low to yeah, we were
not doing that. No, I was straight up to the nose. Dude, Thomas did. Yeah, he put
this nose like on it and he sniffed in so much that he had the salts on his nose,
literally stone face, no reaction, terrifying yeah, scary yeah, no Thomas
was like a like a statue when he was going to get you on these yeah. I wish I
could try them right now. I wish I
really badly yeah. Didn't Caleb buy them and he was supposed to bring them with
him? I don't think he bought them. Maybe that's why he's sick. Yeah, he ate them.
He ate the smell. He thought they were for seasonings. Yeah, he put them on the
steak. That's probably what happened knowing him
yeah. I mean it's the same thing with neti pot. Have you guys used neti pot?
Oh yeah. I'm a big fan of a neti pot.
How is it the same as a neti pot?
Because it goes in your nose, man.
I guess it's the only similarity.
You use the saline solution
and the more you use it, the more of a
tolerance you build up to the saline
solution and then you need to just put a shit load of salt
in your nose to do it and then it doesn't work.
Got it. Okay. You boil your water?
You gotta. Yeah.
I'm not getting brainwashed.
No, I learned about it in my high school class.
It says it on the moral too.
There's an episode of A Thousand Ways to Die where a person got like almost the same as like candy roo, but like for your nose and your fucking brain.
They got meningitis probably. That's what you can get from it.
No, they got a bug.
You can get flesh eating bacteria or meningitis or stuff.
They got a bug in their brain.
A bug?
According to A Thousand Ways to Die.
That's definitely the TV version.
A reputable source. A very, very reputable source, A Thousand Ways to Die.
why I've been watching. Oh my God, wait, you just reminded me I've been watching
the best TV show of all time. Have you guys heard of this show Kung Fu from the
seventies? Yeah, you ever watch this? My gym teacher would quoted at me fucking
fire. My dad was talking about how he and his brother used to be obsessed with it
back in the seventies when they were kids and I've been watching it. So it's
David Carradine. Yeah, he plays a character named Kwai Chang Kane. Wow, he
they Chinese man cool and he how much do they do they? They give a lot. They
don't do it a lot. Here's what they do. They do they do it tastefully. They
blacken his hair. Okay, they make they straighten it and they give them to
give it that kind of spiky type of look, but that's and then they put him. They
put him in in in loose fitting clothing robes. That's a lot he's that's a lot.
No there's no makeup, there's no makeup. It's not a comparatively listen to the
the seventies it's not okay. It's obviously not great no matter what,
but it's not it's not. I've I'm watching the show. It's not it's not it's no
fucking you know, make you runny. Yeah, exactly it's a far cry from that, but
the thing that he he does really play it up he's acting. He doesn't do an accent
or anything, but he kind of he speaks in Proverbs and he speaks slowly and like
is anyway he's a he's a Chinese. He's a he's a what's it called
cow in monk and he knows kung fu. He was trained by Master Po, who's blind and he
basically has to grab a pebble out of the master's hand, and when he can grab the
pebble, it's time for him to leave. But he then he
he graduates from the monastery and he goes and now he's in the Wild West and
he's wandering around and he uses his Chinese ways and wisdoms to basically
solve these problems between cowboys and outlaws who are fighting each other, who
for example, stealing things or being racist or raping women or stuff like
that. And then he comes in and he kind of says like, oh, is not the way of
peace more whatever. Wow. And it's incredible. It's the best show of all
time. You know, David Carradine's brother is the dad on Lizzie McGuire.
Wow. Fun fact of the day.
I think his brother is in Revenge of the Nerds also.
but I'm a guy the guy from revenge of the nerds, we're talking Keith or Robert,
the one with the black hair goes
that one. I haven't seen revenge of the nerds. I just not good my show corner
Joe's, but I can I add one thing about Kung Fu before we go to Joe shows yeah,
I'm ninety nine percent sure that Kung Fu is what Xavier Renegade Angel was
based on. Oh, okay, it's all him wandering through the desert and going
to towns and there's people fighting and he go. He says some kind of wisdom
adage. I don't know what that is either. Well, you'll get alt enough to be
watching a show like that.
My show, my show is also takes place in the s. The seventeen s. Well, so mine
was not doesn't take place in the seven is from the wild west. It's from the
seventy. It's from the seven
seventeen s. John Adams on a you have been watching that since I lived with
you. That's not true. I only want you one episode in in your move. You're only
watched one episode back then. I really I really dove in deep yeah and I'm doing
corresponding Wikipedia articles before they even pass the
the like alien and sedition acts. I'm like there's aliens in this show yeah
John Adams did well. I got a way better show idea than regular as John Adams
now. Well, I mean yeah, so it's really John Adams didn't seem to really be so
gung ho about the alien and sedition acts, but he left George Washington's
cabinet in
you know, he kept their jobs and they're kind of Hamilton's guys and Hamilton,
not as cool as we all think he is because I don't think he's that cool
because of because of the song yeah is the reason I don't think he's. I think
that every single one of these American history figures is fucking stupid
compared to like Willie Santos or like was that Keith, Kurt Heath, Kurchard or
any probably skateboarders. These are guys that are way cooler than the
founding fathers. It's just the thing I think about this John Adams guy. It's
just him and his wife. He absolutely loves her. He's she's his number one
confidant and he's just alive during the absolute craziest yeah man. I was to be
alive back in the day. There's basically there's no time period that I can see in
a movie that I won't as long as they show a house in a movie that's set in a
different time period. I think God I would love to be alive in that I couldn't
I wish I honestly now that I say that, even if they don't show a house, yeah,
it's old long enough ago that there's only jungles. I would really like to be
whenever I found fathers. You guys would be. Do you think I think you would be in
like a founding fathers? No, I would have I would have the ear of one of the
founding fathers. I would be like a worm tongue like yeah
I would I would be one of those people that dies from eating mud back then yeah.
I would I would eat a mud soaked pig or something and then I would get a
disease that like we've cured so many times over. You would you would eat mud
and then get sick and then they would like cut your stomach. Oh yeah, they
would cut my stomach open and take it out. You know,
why is it
what the fuck? What the incredible if you're around back in the in the
founding fathers days when they're starting the country and they're
writing the constitution, the declaration of independence and all this stuff and
you're like say you're like you're like a bandit or you're like a murderer. I'm
like a highway man. I'm a thief, I'm stopping people on the road and I'm
grabbing them and I'm killing them and they're in the they're in the room and
they're writing the constitution and they're like all right. We'll start
with like
let's see human rights and I'm like well. You should probably make robbing legal
and murder should be good and being right there in the room begin. Oh,
there's one guy. Yes,
I decree murder legal yeah. You should write one line in there. The guys are
the last name Smith get extra money from their job yeah and make sure it's
yeah the Smith. Yes, Smith gets money and he's writing it so fast, of course,
he's right by hand, yeah, they don't have a racers, but exactly it's ink.
They'd have to start
fucking, I can't believe Smith, because back then I mean nowadays, you know,
back nowadays people are like oh every crew they got the one manipulator. They
got the one bad guy back then every crew had the one serial killer. Once
serial killers weren't invented yet, the guy who's killed five hundred and
fifty five people, and so no way to track that and some not even a war. He
he just goes into the force and he kills people. Yeah, he finds people who are
camping in between towns and they're making coffee in their little pot and he
just kills them. It is a little crazy how easy crime was. Oh yeah, but the
thing I was really about the yeah, no, it's just like saying in the houses. I
don't know.
No, I didn't do that.
The first instinct when you kill somebody, it's like I guess I'll just
move yeah yeah, I'm going to leave this body here. I'm just going to go away
from it. There were no one will know there's somebody in my family tree. I
did like ancestry during cove it and I found that there is like somebody I'm a
distant, distant relative of in the seventeen hundreds murdered his wife and
then tried to like weekend at Bernie's her
there's like like an article or some shit where it's like something something
door in like like like this wife over the head with like a
and then props her up in the house. When, like the tech guy,
it's like I got also find the article. I feel like women got such like a low
dude, the funny level of respect that they're probably just like hello man.
Yeah,
she's very well behaved yeah, yeah, that's a good wife. The funniest part
of that is that, like back that like you like trying to weaken and burns your
wife is you could literally bury her in your front yard yeah and they would not
it would not be would be like yeah. She left well, you could also be like okay,
okay, she she caught like the bird disease yeah and now she's gone. She's
on her period, so she went to the woods yeah. She fell down the stairs and she
landed on my lacrosse stick yeah. I also I invented I invented a new sport and I
call it lacrosse. Yes, well stole it well yeah, yeah, I'm an eight American.
That's why I said lacrosse, because it would have been around back then, but
you were talking about how any time you see a house in a movie, you're like oh,
I wish that I lived back then. Anytime I see somebody cooking over like a fire,
yeah, that's where I like like the scene in Star Wars where he's eating that
fucking like chicken nugget over the
over the little ass lamp. Like man, I wish I could fucking eat that in the
woods man. Oh my God for me, you know what it is, it's more than a house, it's
showing a main street and I'm not showing main street. I'm like fuck John
Adams. They have a need to be a full scale old state house in Boston. Oh my
And I was like, that's fucking cool. How far into it are you? I finished it. Oh,
nice. How many seasons is one? It's one. It's seven episodes. We watched some of
that in eighth grade. They showed it. It was one of those TV days. They showed us
that part of that. They showed us the Patriot. Mel Gibson's the Patriot in my
eighth grade class. And there's a scene in that movie where a man gets his head
destroyed by a cannonball. And I was like, this is fucking yeah. What's Oh,
is it called? What's it called? Glory. Is that the one? Yeah, we watched that too.
Matthew Broderick and then no it's not Denzel is it don't know don't remember
all I remember is Matthew Broderick. No it's Morgan Freeman, but then there's
another one. There's another one of those kind of movies with Denzel in it
right or am I? I don't know. I don't usually watch movies that are set in
that time period, but then whenever I do I'm like oh. What John Adams is all John
Adams is like a hundred percent they shoot every conversation and just like a
super crazy Dutch angle and then you're like oh that's like a real guy like it
it makes it takes away all the like weird, boring shit. It's Paul Giamatti
right yeah. He fucking crashes it. My thing I gotta sign this fucking
declaration of independence. Damn it, I gotta fucking sign it. Oh Jesus Christ,
I'm going to fucking kill myself. I can't sign this thing. Any show with a
mug, a warm mug and a blanket
and you're saying anything over a fire doing that or I want to watch it. You
watch somebody drink a mug. Well, sometimes I'll do it simultaneously, but
it's like I'm, but your show
Yeah, I'm John Adams.
It's me John Adams.
Yeah, every day it's always for me. I'm watching something said in the old
West and I'm like and to my fiance. I'm like wow, wouldn't you like to live
back then? She's like no yeah, I don't care you're coming back. You're coming
back. I think if I get the time machine you fucking come and you're coming and
you're the furthest. I'm not doing this alone. Yeah crazy, the furthest back in
time I always want to go is like like nine hundred and seventy five something
like that. I don't want to be back in time any time after that. Well, we must
acknowledge our privilege and going back in time exactly. That was kind of my
joke with why my fiance doesn't want to go is because she's a woman in the old
west. You would probably be her body would be filled with mud yeah by a
person who grabbed her.
It's a horrible. I would want to go and me. I see it. I'm like wow. I would get
to eat lunch next to a cowboy.
I wouldn't necessarily be a cowboy, but I get to see the sheriff. You get to eat
like that's the thing you probably become a sheriff. If you just yeah,
talk smart enough, I was thinking about a guy who's like
who gets like pulled over by the cops and he's like like fuck the cops. Fuck
you like I'm not like I get out of my face and the guy's like I'm the sheriff
and he's like, Oh, my God,
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
The thing about like all that, like old when you see like the old food in like
seventeen. I'm so like this. The only thing I'm focused on, but like think
about just like eating like anything in like the seventeen hundreds or like the
cowboys and stuff. It's like all that probably tasted like shit. Yeah, it's
all bad. It's all like like food until like the eighties was all like bland as
fuck. Food was bad until twenty twenty one food is honestly for you. I know you
didn't. You just bad sandwiches. You would eat a turkey sandwich. That was
just bread. It's one slice of turkey slice of bread. Not true at all roast
way. First of all, Cameron is the type of
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
between the you think I like bread, bread, make you a throw perfectly to
shape the bread.
Now, if you think if you think I'm cutting or preparing any of my food in
any way, yeah, you've got the wrong. I always like well. I think that was what
Patrick was saying with your one. So I think cutting it to fit the bread. I
would never do that. No, okay, so no, it's free. It's pre cut. You brought
you bought the bread shaped like the turkey slice a
bread
bread shaped
turkey, but yeah yeah it's called turkey bread. It's a little turkey bread and
it's for you.
They made it for you. I sell it at the store this year. I'm going to start
making some putting some stuff in my sandwiches. Yeah, can you imagine a can
of beans you've been riding for two days? You need a hot can of coffee man.
it's always the coffee and the beans and it's just coffee with just coffee
grounds at the bottom of it and you're just drinking it's all it dude. It's
beans bread, but the bacon, though, but you gotta imagine you gotta imagine the
bacon is good yeah. Well, they're like the ham and shit. Well, you just have to
cut it up the cured like you got to make it all that stuff. I think that all like
all these delicious meats exist just because it's like it's not safe to eat
this shit. So we're just going to put it in a barrel of salt forever. Yeah,
yeah, it's going to be okay. It's like what's that shit called
ham hocks ham hocks is the hocks is the hocks. The part of the leg
ham. I think
it'd be so awesome to be like ham right now. What is it? What's a ham hock?
It's a hawk of ham yeah, but what I feel I think it looks like a cartoon.
It's the cartoon style with a circle in the middle. Yeah, I think so up. I'm
pretty sure I would love to try one smelling so you see what a ham hock look
like he's searching ham hock, H, O, C, K,
Amber,
what is a ham hock? Oh, it's a port. Let's go to images.
Okay, so it's a pig's knuckle. Oh well, it does yeah. It is the cartoon. It is a
yeah, yeah, but I didn't know it was the knuckle.
I would eat that actually. Of course you would. It's part of the pig. I would
eat it. If it tastes good, I would eat. If there's a big fat chunk of meat on
I was thinking about the fucking stupidest hypothetical we ever came up with the other
day. It was the one... Oh, fuck. I forget what it was, but I forget what the first part of
it was. But you said, "Would you rather do this or get a massage from an expert?"
I was just thinking about that.
Would you rather eat a food that's bad or get a massage from an expert?
this is I was on my way somewhere. I just started laughing. I'm not me. Would
you rather would you rather eat food made by an expert or get a massage from
an ex food? A thousand percent food. Wait is it the same expert? It's an
expert in both. Both I want food man, no matter what, but we don't matter what
the expert, no matter what in no matter what he is an expert, but we don't know
what he's an expert of no matter what he's you choose. He's doing the other
everything first okay. Here's what I don't know. We don't know what the
expert hands and he's massaging. Here's what we can reduce the question down to
using the using the power of mathematics. If we assume that so it could the best
cases that he's an expert in food, I see a
wait, wait, wait, expert expert equals x, but we don't know okay, but if he's an
x in something else, x the worst, the worst we can assume is would you rather
get a massage from somebody who's terrible at massages or food by someone
bad at making food easily the food, but he's an expert in something he's an
expert in something right.
He's a math
worst case thing. We got it with the thing we got to think about here is that
he is an expert in one thing. Well, how committed is the massage?
It's like sensual, but is it like is it a
well someone who's bad at giving a massage is just going to not really give
a massage. They can hurt you. I've been hurt by massage before me too. I've
my nerve was pinched by a massage in high school and it was excruciating the
worst pain of some of the worst pain I've ever experienced in my life. I
did she pinched your warm. She pinched my worm man and my shoulder
she pitched your work and your shoulder at the same time. Oh,
it hurts so bad. I literally think it's the worst pain I have ever experienced.
Only gotten one or now now to you know what the word I got one massage when I
was a kid because I hurt my arm or my back or something. My mom was trying to
for my depression and I massage. I was really nervous. I was really nervous for
me. I'm bright and happy on the new year. Well, I was nervous and then I just
immediately fell asleep. I didn't feel anything during the massage. You were
asleep. I just wasted it man. Yeah, I know. Well, you probably did you take
did you take your clothes off?
You don't okay. You remember you remember you remember. I don't remember
than a big smile. You had you had your winky out at full mass. I think I was
wearing shorts or like I leave on my leave on my undies. I haven't got a
massage since since that time that they killed me too scared yeah. That was a
good. That was an expert. I was pain bro. It's his worst any time and when I got
my I got my wisdom tooth out over the like the break that we were on and
the there's something called the sympathetic pain that you will get in
your mouth. Once a wisdom tooth is removed is what my doctor was telling me
and for some reason it was this tooth and the night before I was coming back here.
I could not sleep because there is a pain in the nerve in this to God and I was
just up all night just going.
Yeah, that's taking these codeine pills. They gave me a pain is the worst. Oh my
God. I couldn't feel shit after that, but that's a little book. It's like a
tree. All right, guys, let's get some one New Year's resolution for him.
Everybody. Oh, I already said mine, but I'm going to get my money up and I'm
going to become strong. Okay.
I would say I want to do everything I do, but a little bit better and a little
bit more yeah, and for me it's year of the grind. Yeah, it seems like we're all
kind of in the same. Yeah, we're all what's what's it's a year of what
what yeah, what animal is this year? Well, I'm saying let's let's think of
one. I was making up a new animal year of the ham, you're of the scorpion.
Well, no, just like what is a year of what you know, like I just got chills
saying year of the score. The scorpion is too scary, but I don't want to live
the year of the score. I see no no no no, it's the year of this. It's the year of
the scorpion. We're going to take this frog out. I have no connection to a
scorpion.
No, now you do because it's the year of the scorpion. You subscribe to the
fable of the scorpion and the frog. Okay, we are the scorpion. I'm going to
need everybody. I need everybody to to google the scorpion and the frog right
now. The frog is all of you and we are the evil scorpion and we're going to
make all of you out. We're to get nowhere
we're not getting we're not mate. We're not making it across his river halfway
through the year. We're going to fall off or fall off the scorpions going to
fall off the frog. So the front the score is not skin stinging the frog.
We'll just all in the frog, the frog dies and the frog dies and the frozen
also dies. Why the hell did you do that? We're both going across the river
together. You guys see the I'm evil mother nature, because I'm a bastard.
Did you guys see the video of the ant like fucking people? Yeah,
it's pretty crazy yeah you're the okay. I guess it's not year of the scorpion
year of the aunt. You're the aunt, you're the aunt, I guess it could be
year of the aunt. We get into fine chardonnay, you're the baby,
you're the baby, fud, you're a baby fud, you're the baby. I mean it's like
obviously there's you have the hunted for us. The obvious answer here, the
year of the frog. You're the hunted is kind of cool year of Sullivan. You're
the frog. I guess wow I didn't even think about the scorpion and we need to
have a scorpion mascot. We need to have an enemy for Sullivan. That is a
scorpion. It's not a bad idea. That is a really good idea. I think it might be
year of the guy year of man, your boys, your human kind of human enough of
these fucking animals. Who is the who is your pick for twenty twenty four
person of the time person of the year. Okay, after that a little too early to
decide, but you just have to make a call. It's a yeah, it's a it's a
prediction. I'm going to say this year they're going to pick Travis Kelts.
Okay, I'm going to try and get like a long shot. I want to think of like like
for example, like a see who's a CEO of a company right now. That's not important
at all, but who like someone who's going to be who do you think is going to win
the presidency this year. That's an easy that's an easy winner of that, like
that's probably the odds on favor. It's just trump by yeah, but I want to get I
want to get like a long shot. You know, yeah, no, no, no, you want to make a big
yeah. I'm trying to thank here like I guess maybe like
maybe like somebody the ceo of a car company or something so like a ravion
what's that ravion? It's the crazy looking trucks and you know the new
Amazon trucks. No, let's see who the ceo of Rivian is RJ scaring
RJ scaring is probably my
times person of the year. RJ
reapers jeepers scaring. Oh my God, who does he looks exactly like somebody that
I can't put my finger on it. I don't know. He kind of looks like one of the
like face yeah. I know he looks like a I generated person. I'm going to say it's
the new I'm going to say it's the new guy who's now in charge of Argentina. Oh
yeah, that guy yeah, that's not a bad pick. I think he's going to do
something crazy yeah. He could do something crazy here's my here's here's
the next thing we have to decide on for twenty four. It's celebrity death pool.
Oh yes, yes, yes, I've been thinking about that. I'm getting a little. I
think Justin Bieber I've been
another car crash could go down yeah, that's true.
So
somebody's trying to get in. I'm going to go with a little grim pick. I'm going
so Brendan Fraser. Wow, that's not a bad pick. I saw that movie, the whale and he
was so monstrously fat. He looked close to death. I also just think there's a
thing of like his whole narrative had this thing of like great peaking Valley
and then now kind of back on this top and I do it's a like I don't want it to
be true. I don't yeah. What if him and I don't know how to pronounce the name
key
very key, can he hit Queen? Yeah, yeah, I feel bad. They both they put if they
both die at the same time buddy holly plain yeah or they do like who's the
third person that you don't really think of on the plane, because it's always
the big bopper who's there big bop
boppers flying to play a big bopper is the one the third guy yeah yeah hello
baby.
They're like
big boppers back from the day and then they're like
crash. They go wait. If you're here,
and you know it's funny as fuck when they say it because of their acting skills.
Yeah, it's a scene from a movie yeah yeah okay, who else under the age of
under the age of sixty who else
Helen Mirin, she's older than older than sixty Merrill Streep will die this year.
I have to actually you can't you can't have me say anything because there's
been two times where a celebrity has died who and a week before I have said
something who Betty White and Henry Kissinger, okay, but so don't read
twenty year old people. Don't know it over. Don't know. Do not everyone says
is going to die every single week yeah, but the timing that when I say it is
crazy,
Gus and I happened it happened. No, I you know what happens is I say that I'm
going to kill them and then they die within like a week. Why would you want
to kill Betty? What I don't know why I said it I was being random. Okay, say
one right now. Oh, it's not a young. Who are you going to kill? Who are you
going to kill? That's what I was going to say. It can't be an old person. I'm
saying
old person boring for celebrity death pool. Yeah, Ryan Reynolds Deadpool,
that's too much. That's that's way
is on a stunt. I could see TJ Miller who does their own stunts and movies right
Tom Cruise. Tom Cruise could have a stunt go wrong. That would be one of the
most incredible ways for him to die of all time. Oh, you know who does you know
he does his own stunts. I think the guy from I think Homelander from the boys
does his own stunts some of the time. What if Harrison for over sixty,
over sixty Harrison Ford passes away, that'd be a crazy celebrity. I have it
all the
Elgort. Okay, that's where we draw the line, because I don't want to talk about
celebrity deaths anymore. Okay, we should talk about celebrities being born.
Who's the there will be a new singer born this year? I think Amelia Amelia,
singer will be born this year. I'm going to say, you know what? There's going to
be a new teen actor who has amazing chops. When he gets older, they're going
to be like he used to be in like a Disney show, but now he's like a 20
2044. Amelia's first album will be drawn dropping and 2024 beautiful flower
2044 44 20 year old. Her first album will be dropping and it's called
beautiful flowers in the sky. I'm also keep an eye out for that. I'm getting
like a feeling about a world leader whose last name is Gonzalvez. You know
know that spelling of Gonzalez with a V yeah it's that's going to come up.
That's going to be born born this year. Okay, okay, guys, we got some
predictions here, but I've pulled together some predictions from the
internet from for us as well. Here we go. Can we pull up what the before we go
any further? Can we pull up what animal this year is yeah search zodiac year?
Yeah, I do want to know everyone guess everyone guess
rabbit rabbit. Oh, it's like rabbit year. I'm going to get all dragon. Oh
Wow, actually this year, wait, twenty, twenty four will be the year of the
wood dragon. Whoa, that's the lamest possible dragon. No, no, no, what dragon
could look cool? You know the thing about dragon is bad because it implies
the dragon is artificial. Anything else air dragon, fire dragon, water, no,
it's like it's like a dragon that it's like it's a dragon that
breathes out grass. It's like an end to dragon. It's a dragon that has grass
breathing ability. It's imagine a way to picture this. Imagine going into an
old forest and old Chinese forest and you see a massive tree and then you look
away and then you hear something move and then you look back.
I think eyes open up and it's going. Have you ever seen like a tree that like
one of those trees that like like has a curve that goes up like it's like a pine
tree that grew wrong and then like yeah and it's a way nerves and then you're
like you're like oh this tree kind of looks like a dragon and then you sit on
it and it fucking gets up and flies away. There's like a big branch. I got big
fucking dragon's dick and it fucks you
but it fucking fucks you. Can you isn't it funny that dragons are just dinosaur
bones?
You're not always you ever think on that you see on that mind blowing. Can you
imagine apparently that's why Thomas back to bring back to the
apparently that's why Thomas Jefferson sent
Lewis and Clark West was because he on his giant property on in Monticello. He
found dinosaur bones and he just assumed that those creatures still existed yeah
in like the unexplored you would
like you it's way harder to be like oh, this was a millions and millions of
millions of years ago. Yeah, it just bone exist. It's so amazing how stupid
everybody was back then, because they didn't have the phone to look up and
correct themselves.
I would give Thomas Jefferson a phone. I go back in time. I give Thomas Jefferson
a phone. I would show him squirt off work videos. I would squirt and I'd show him
world star immediately. I would get back in time talking to Thomas Jefferson. I
be like all right first off buddy Thomas Jefferson it's out from now on
you're TJ yeah TJ, TJ Malone
and you're a singer.
This is called a microphone yeah. I would I would I would sit I would sit
him down and go TJ Malone and then I'll just press play on a beat.
I play him. I play him like I play him. I play him the instrumental of mint
condition, pretty brown eyes and I'd say you have to sing over this right the
fuck back then in those times they would have been the most incredible
freestylers ever, because this is the age of people saying stuff like in dubit
ably and the pursuit of happiness, so they would be going fucking crazy. Oh
my God guys, it will be unreal. I was thinking of Thomas Jefferson more like
slow R and B style singing type of thing, because I think we just invented
epic rap battles.
They don't do that on epic rap battle of history, though they modernize it,
I say and what's more I fucked your bitch and it's like they wouldn't say that
back down. They would say I per I engaged in adultery with your woman. I aged in
adultery. Now we had you writing for epic rap. I see adultery, got a
poltice
these burns. You can't hold this
hot like a coal is I shot you off in a catapult. This yeah show catapult is
exactly show Thomas Jefferson a pogging would change his life. I would show him
pogs. I would show him pogs and the paper and also the white women. I
would show him like none of it. Nothing will get done yeah
America
ten seconds in the time travel.
You go back, you go back and it's like America. You go to the future, you go
like to twenty twenty four and there's literally dinosaurs again.
All society has completely crumbled
it's plan of the a three hundred years yeah you're like you have ten seconds
you're outside of the room. You open the door from across the room. You show
them your phone.
You look in your wallet and all of the all of the money. All the president's
faces are gone. They just have squirrels and
I
don't know what happened.
You go back to the future. There's like a like a primitive style and a planet of
the apes type man. He says I don't know what somebody went back with a device
and showed him what women could do with their butts in the future.
Change the courts of history. He lost to try to invent all the humans invented a
time machine. They went way too far in the future. He lost his mind trying to
replicate the squirt
he's it he's up in the like in the in his attic like in like nightmare before
Christmas when he's trying to re engineer Christmas, but he's like you
show it in Howard Stern, so they just compilation everyone everyone in the in
the town is like down on the ground level, like looking up like what's he
doing up there? There's like flashing lights and liquid squirt got to the
way
stockboard is like
what's this yeah
it's exactly nightmare before Christmas, but instead of Halloween and Christmas,
it's Thomas Jefferson Thomas Jefferson and squirting yeah Jefferson,
making squirt, a gang squirt
women squirting. It's hers this time okay. Twenty twenty four predictions. I
got these for a bunch of different websites and blogs. I pulled them all
together. I kind of got just a wide range of all these possible different things
that people say might happen in twenty twenty four. So
I'm going to
go ahead and go through these and read this out to you guys and we'll see what
we think. If we think that these things are likely to happen in twenty twenty
four, okay, wait, wait, wait, so okay,
just a bunch of different stuff. All right, so let's let's check it out here.
This is not this is not by this is by Cameron. Let's go ahead here. So first
yourself. We have this blog called Stout Standards. You can say they are place
you'd think it would be, but you can see here they have their different. They
have their different sections on the website, like welcome the Malamute
Saloon,
coin Saloon as beer coin hunting, wet articles, brain farts, treasure, Expo
photos, how to use a shovel, etcetera. Now let's go to the next slide here and
you'll see that this is actually musings from an old beeper
is the header of this blog, and so I bet you're wondering what a beeper is. Oh
my God, here's his article. He says twenty twenty four what to expect and
here's a picture of him holding a crystal ball with a picture of him in
it yeah and here's what
in January Garrett issues press release stating that will it will indeed
introduce a metal detector. He's a beeper. He's a metal to
that will be capable of joining the never ending bitching bash with mine
lab and nocta and John Hallen goes off the wagon two days after getting on it.
I don't know who John
must be another be. I think it's just another
this guy does not like or is like good friends with and it's making a funny
yeah more likely, but it's funnier to imagine he's he hates him. He's trying
to ruin his he's trying to tarnish his name and then in October, the
manufacturers start refining their holiday ads by finding new synonyms for
words like deeper, amazing, visual, lightweight, multiple savings, etcetera,
but then realize the average techie, which I guess what they call detectors
won't know what they mean and go back to using deeper, amazing, lightweight,
et cetera. This is a beautiful painting of a community that I had no idea was
so yeah and here's the second thing that happens in October hottest new item
for techies in October, O D, olive green t shirts for privy diggers with
sayings like show me your shit and I love to think
did he
so this guy's the beep. This old beeper predicts that in October, twenty
twenty four, we will see a lot of people wearing shirts that say show me
your shit and I love to stink.
did he go is this in order or did he skip I'm skipping around yeah there's a full
it's all there's twelve different months. I'm not taking everything from all
those websites, just like that he had like three prediction yeah and we had
like twenty four twenty four predictions for twenty twenty four. I just realized
that two for each month. This guy's pretty smart yeah yeah and then in in
December he says detector sales soar as many newcomers enter the fray after
seeing how quickly you can become financially independent digging in the
dirt and dick stout. That's this guy's name stout stout, whatever it whatever it
if he is still around yeah, Dick Stout, he's like eighty something years old. I
found on his website Dick Stout. If he is still around, we'll put up his Christmas
tree, put a wreath on the door, pour a glass of red, celebrate making it through
another year and start working on his predictions for twenty twenty five.
Isn't that so cute? And then here's what he puts at the end of his article. I
love Dick Stout. Happy New Year and cheers and it's a glass of red. It looks
Dick Stout Dick. You are the man. I love you. What do we think about Dick's
predictions? Dick? I hope every single one of them comes true. I will personally
refund and olive green t shirt that says I love I love to show me your shit and I
love to
that's an incredible from an eighty something year old guy coming up with
the idea for an olive green t shirt that says show me your shit is unreal. It's
incredible all right, the next blog we're going to look at here. He does
call you know what I should say okay. It says show me your shit and then on the
back it says copyright dick.
Good idea, I would say she should also be a metal. The I should be a metal. The
is a good idea because it's funny because it's for privy diggers, which I
guess there's what people who go into the septic tanks and stuff, but yeah,
who would think that who would not even I don't even want to say privy diggers.
No, I just does it sound does not it sounds like a it sounds like a slur
from like one thousand and thirty. It really does it could be this guy's old.
We don't know back out. We have no yeah there's no sign of how yeah, nice of a
few born and born in what one thousand and forty yeah, some one to for he looks
like a face at he really does. I thought he was at first. The next blog we're
looking at is it ain't holy water,
and this is what what this blog says here. Chief knows wetter, but he says
what many are predicting for twenty twenty four. We have an image
in
twenty twenty one. It shows a bunch of people who just got their vaccines in
twenty twenty four. It shows the same amount of gravestones. Are we rocking
with this prediction for twenty twenty four? I don't know. I don't think so. I
I hope not because I got fucking I got tricked into that.
I'm going to say no. No, we're not rocking with this one with with it ain't
holy water. No, I mean I would say because also you know I would say graves
are less and less popular to yeah. People are getting put up into space on
hot air balloons taxidermy days burnt to Chris. People are getting stewed. Can
you go back one slide? I just want to read what this says. Oh yeah. Chief
nose wetter sarcasm derived through the bottom of a glass. It's a picture of I
think whiskey. Okay, so this is an alcoholics blog. Yeah, it ain't holy
water. If you understand the man, it looks like he created his web page on a
power point. Yeah, it really does doesn't all right. What's the next? What's the
next? What's the next prediction here? This is this is I'm just going through
random stuff here. It's I'm not that was his only prediction. Okay, this was a
news article. It says time will tell I'm a time traveler from twenty six two
thousand six hundred and seventy one. My seven wildest twenty twenty four
predictions from UFO discoveries to whole countries disappearing. I love I
love a time traveler coming back from sixteen from twenty six seventy one and
writing a like shitty little article. This is an even better than this. This
article is not written by the time traveler. It's written by someone who
saw the time travelers predictions, which are all on tick tock.
This is a very audacious time traveler to who has some very interesting things
to say about twenty twenty four. We'll see if these happen. The self
proclaimed time traveler first predicted that on May twenty first,
twenty four, a cloud would be made self aware by an alien species. He said the
cloud would turn hostile and attack random cities around the globe, so
specifically San Francisco, Berlin and London, followed by quote terrible
thunderstorms and flooding. He says there's going to be a living cloud on
May. Twenty first okay, this that's
we think that might happen. I feel like that's like not out of the realm of
possibility, a self aware cloud yeah. I mean I feel like who are we to judge
whether or not it is self aware right exactly, but I can imagine that this I
could see it. I can imagine these things happening and I can imagine a large
faction of people believing that this cloud has been angered by something
definitely. I would say that it's a it's not a sentient cloud. I think I would
think that it was that the aliens have a cloud shaped ship or like a cloud gun
that shoots a cloud around or just global dorm to go global dorming. Yeah,
visible dorming. What's all right? What's next here?
The last prediction a lyric made is that a species of bird previously thought as
extinct would reappear and begin to hum a scary melody. He said people who hear
the sound would lose control of themselves and hundreds would begin
passing away every single day. I think that's true. I think I what bird
didn't they didn't they clone the dodo bird and bring it back. I don't know if
that's something that I saw that was fake and then it just didn't didn't care
enough and just believe they haven't brought them back, but I'm sure they've
either synthesized their meat or they're capable of bringing them back. They
synthesized woolly mammoth me yeah, but I think they also did dodo maybe
I was anyway, though, after eating that shit, I don't know what the hell my
body go back, go back the dodo, I think is the obvious choice, but there have
been a lot of birds, but don't those are history. Don't those bird don't those
famously some type of moa. What about the you know the what's it called the
like gigantic crazy albatross thing that's like a fifty foot wing. What's
it called a terra torn or a fucking
there's some kind of New Zealand eagle that's like gigantic. That would be a
good gigantic bird and also you go the like King Kong skull face thing yeah on
yeah,
that's not a bird. There's a sharp shin hawk on my in my tree in my backyard. I
saw a hawk pick up a mouse from the median. We take on the highway. Oh yeah,
we both were texting each other about hawk stuff. I remember this yeah, it's
cool to see hawks all right. Here's the next prediction. That one's fucking
scary. This one I don't like this scary one to in March. Twenty twenty four, an
ancient artifact is found known as Pandora's box. It is opened and releases
many unknown mysteries. I hope not the intrigue of these things went out the
window with that one yeah that this one we know where you got this idea yeah
you're not cool yet. Not original
this ain't cool. Listen, we all read these these Greek myth books. Back when
we were kids, we all read Percy Jackson, an ancient artifact. I don't know,
maybe Pandora's box and something like that. It's opened, I guess, and what
happens when it's open something I guess many unknown. I know you should
be released. I hate it when an unknown mystery is released. Let show me a
known one, like although I will say maybe we don't know about Pandora's box
happening, but I can't imagine some unknown mysteries happening. Yeah,
here's the next prediction. Every day is an unknown mystery. Despicable me for
makes a billion
all right yeah. I can see it is that coming is that is that confirmed coming?
I don't know maybe
so this is kind of could be a shot in the dark yeah
yeah. I mean I would say they I don't I don't think they would do despicable me
for they, unless it would make a bill. I'm saying it unless it would make a
bill right. You trust them. They are going to be so that dream works that is
Illumination Illumination. Well, they just did Mario. Did Mario make a bill?
Not maybe Mario made a band almost a hundred percent. Mario definitely made
one band. Yeah, it made a band at least it at least made at least made one
band. Yeah, yeah, one point three six bill Jesus Christ. If you look in every
movie, it makes so much money. Mario's like all anything will despicable me.
Anything animated is going to be like every single country is going to have
the most famous actors doing the voices in it on the press. Before is definitely
making a bill yeah I'm all in lock it in like yeah. Do you have like a good
sound effect for lard? What's it called going draft kings put this in lock it
in? I might have a better one, but anyway
pickable me makes a bill yeah. Oh, I don't have a better one. These buttons
are so sticky. They are they're just like sticking in when I press the no
it's fine to the one again.
like it yeah. Well there we go to sound of action. There's two sound of eggs.
Now Julio, you have to use the audio, so this is the lock in sound and then when
we don't like a prediction
okay here, wait, let's go back and do all no we're not going to
and guys we need at the end of the year. We're going to come back. We're going
to see what came true. That's another creation, including the trend cheddar
chops. Some people don't know anything about cheese in twenty twenty four.
Other people will have hashtag cheddar chops. They're just charming and good
ground cheese talking about it, tasting it, sharing it this one. I do I
actually do think that this will happen because
I think Cheddar Chops. I don't think it will go by this name, but I do think
that a like what was it all out? What was it last year? What was it last
year? Everyone got into really into Cheddar Chops is going to be the big
cheddar. I don't think people got into church. People got into charcuterie, so
I think the next logical step did that. Yeah, well, yeah, but you're learning
you're learning the basics of meat and cheese that go, but I feel yeah, I guess,
that wouldn't cheddar chops already wouldn't they have already have burned
the cheddar chops with the charcuterie like when it moved to some people, some
people, I guess well there's two fact in twenty twenty four. Some people will
know about cheese that's going to be true. This is
I would I'm debating the opposite. This is hinging on this going viral and be
right. Okay, a viral cheese, there's no fucking way. You don't know that there's
absolutely the by and the impetus for the viral trend is not that anything
happens. It's just that the viral trend right now is that some people have
hashtag cheddar chops yeah and there's yeah also. I feel like viral shit hinges
on the ability for people to just copy it and do it right, whereas getting into
like well, maybe people are going to be posting pictures of cheese and say
hashtag cheddar shops. I mean this is a you guys,
if you want this to happen, you guys have to twenty twenty four, flex your
influence as much as possible. A new set of drops. Okay, everyone post a picture
of your cheese that you're eating and do hashtag
god post a picture of what has to be cheddar. All right, it has to be cheddar
in the well, cheddar chops is speaking for cheeses and for all, then it should
be cheese chops. Next prediction
a mysterious plague will spread all over the world, which will cause people to
sleep and hence will bring a halt to the entire world. Lock it in, lock it in
right now. Happened in twenty twenty yep, it's going to happen again. I
actually know I have been saying I think a new disease is on its way. I've been
saying this a lot. That's maybe my prophecy. I think that there's something
is going to
it's going to have been around for a minute. They're going to be we just
we've been seeing. We didn't know what to test for, but now we've seen that
this has been taking over. I don't know about the sleeping part, but I really
like the picture, too. I think that's supposed to be Nostradamus. Oh,
definitely an AI photo. Yeah, I mean I think I think if twenty twenty proved
anything, I think it's that we are definitely susceptible to sleeping to
sleep to a major halt of the earth via the sleep. What do you think? Are we
locking it in or are we boning it? I think we're boning it. I would say
because it's not original. It feels at this point like whatever I say you're
just going to do the opposite. So
what do you want? What are you talking about? I said no cheese chops and then
we it was cheddar chops, cheddar cheddar chops. You already forgot cheddar jobs.
yeah there was no she's. It was cheddar chops. I like cheddar chops now,
because this one okay, mysterious plague, yes or no, no,
it's a bone, it's a bone, it's a bone, cheddar chops. I want to hit
the good. The good one, a popular talk show host is rumored to be considering a
career change that could shock their loyal. This already happened. This
already happened with drew Barrymore's breaking the strike,
but she's not that there was no career change.
there was a well. There was a mean, that's not a it's a career change.
What's the word I'm looking for here a
people a people, she can change right, but this says a career, so do they need
to be a sitting talk show host now because Conan's new show is going to
come out.
Maybe that's what they mean is the career change like into back into being
a talk show host. Well, his new show is just him doing the remotes yeah, okay,
well, then that, but I will say I do think I can see Kimmel and I can still
Jimmy Fallon switching it up, Kimmel Action Star, Kimmel Action Star,
Kimmel, Tom Cruise dies in a stunt in dead reckoning to he's. He gets the
bends from a submarine stunt. Jimmy Kimmel takes his place as his care as
Ethan Hunt's son or or Jimmy Fallon returns to musical comedy. Yes, only
found back to stand up, drops the show and goes a full stand up. Yeah,
do you remember he had an album of songs? No, I two thousand and three. He
albums, music, he goes, he's full rap, comedy, rap,
what I wouldn't give to see Jimmy Fallon drop some some bars. Yeah, oh, I
couldn't imagine it. I couldn't buddy there. There's a segment on the tonight
show that you need to see. I don't watch it very often. I'm on the I'm on the
tonight show. Everybody shut up bro. I was I was on the tonight show.
There's a at the you can see me in the crowd at the end. That does not count.
Yeah, it was it was all right. I mean wait, wait, look at look it up, look it
no one last look at it. I got a one. I it's not Kevin Bacon and Greta Gerwig
episode and what's his name? We have to get through Nickoon did stand up and
I'm in the credits and I high five Jimmy Fallon that okay. You're disgusting
you're a bug. No one's going to look
okay. Popular talk show host changing career. We did not even think about
Colbert leaving to become a minister or president yeah or or president as his
character
oh
we're locking it in next one. This is a series of
stuff from a form. I found I did a reading yesterday about the state of
female rap and what events will be taking place in quarter one January,
February, March, the chair car. There's a tarot reading for the state of female
rap. Okay, the chair card implies a departure or vacancy. There might be a
notable figure or influence leaving the female rap community during this period
that creates a shift in the dynamics. When did they predict this? When was
that, because remember Doja Cat said that she was leaving for twenty twenty four
for the first quarter. Okay, can you maybe have a swap between late night
host and female rap star? Not a bad idea. There's more though. I'd keep going
here post to a female rapper changes her image. A female rapper will be taking
chances when it comes to her image and exploring news, aesthetics or themes in
her music career. This new image could be risky, indicating a departure from
their previous image or works, but I'm seeing them willing to try new things
for this female rapper. I think that she is taking a lot of initiative when it
times to creativity and projects, and she is confident in what the future holds
for the outcomes of these projects. This will come with a lot of like having to
defend her choices, but I'm seeing her have a bold demeanor. Who is the female
fucking lame prediction? Just be like yeah, someone's going to change all the
stuff and I'm so proud of her. There's one more female rat prediction. We can
do these all as a group where we can decide whether to lock these in or not.
Number three, cardi B's overall twenty twenty four career prediction. There
will be discord or issues within cardi B's social or professional circles.
there might be challenges related to relationships that could impact the
trajectory of her career. She will be experiencing feelings of depression,
anxiety or a sense that someone might be working against her. There is
potential emotional challenges that could affect her well being and
professional outlook. Cardi B may find opportunities to take breaks or enjoy
moments of leisure. This could be important for maintaining balance and
rejuvenating her creative energy. I'm seeing she's going to step back and take
a vacation of some sort. Let's lock that one in. Let's lock that one in.
so I'm pretty happy with that. I think the first two such a good prediction.
Yeah, I think
party B will go in twenty to Miami for vacation will go on a vacation and I
think she will shake her butt. Yeah, I think she'll probably take a break and
go on vacation. I think she will isn't this. This is like didn't her and her
husband just divorce offset yeah, I don't know her husband is still offset.
Did they divorce they divorce? They have not been together for a while and she
she announced in a I think it was a definitely that did not happen in the
she announced in an X space
or no. It was an instagram live. We haven't been together for weeks is what
I saw, but and also she announced in a twitter space. You were like
commenting on it as it was happening.
Cardi no card, I'm so sorry this happened to you
party. I hope this is not affect your musical career to go on vacation. I
swear to God. If you don't, I take some time for you. Enjoy some moments of
pleasure card, I'm going to do a tarot reading for you yeah. So what but what
I'm thinking from that is that isn't because she just got divorced from
offset, which you could call him now off off off the picture out of the
picture could be his new name. Yeah, maybe there's someone in her circle
who's still working for him and that could be the discourse. She's going to
experience. She's trying to hide all her income because he's going to try and
take her money in the divorce. They were in the baby shark. Move the most like
schizophrenic thing just like party. There's someone is working for offset in
your in your crew. Some one in your crew is a mole. There's a mole out now.
You need to go to my
to go to go. You need to take moments of leisure. Cardi drink some tea, shake
your butt
card. I know that card relaxes you card. I know I know that this is your. I know
you can't go back. You can't go back. It's I know that you're going to be
Cardi, I know you love the game. You will be completely you will be
completely swayed by
your appearance in the baby shark movie. You will think that you'll have to get
back with him because he and I are in the baby shark movie together. You need
to stay the fuck away. You need this by the way, Cardi. I also heard that in
female rap there will be one female rapper who is getting a departure from
her image. Do you know who that could be? It got to be you and you could start
doing death metal and heavy rock. Let us know. Do you like heavy rock? Do you
like heavy rock? Do you like Metallica style music? Yeah, do you like I don't
know? Maybe you could start singing like instead of doing rapping, you could
start doing like a kind of like
rap meets rock type of music. There's there's a there is a mole in your in
your crew. By the way, like rock and roll, do you like rock and roll? Do you
like rock and roll? Cardi? I saw your divorce, please for the love of God,
hold off the proceedings for at least six to eight years, because I am going
to law school right now.
I've just enrolled in law school. I will win this case. We help you. I will save
you. I'm the type of lawyer who will kill offset for you. I am a great
lawyer. I am going to be the greatest lawyer on the I'm a great or I'm a
great lawyer. I pass the bar. I will be so I am the rock and roll lawyer.
Trust me,
I know I know I know I am a lawyer
and
this and then like after yelling seven thousand text messages, finally
response and it's like hey man. This is not car.
if you are please stop texting, just trying every number until you get one
all right, let's look at the next prediction here. Let's see this here a
few. These are a few pop culture predictions. Okay, Taylor Swift will
finally come out as a lesbian slash by director. Brian Singer will be exposed.
Lizzo will have a massive weight loss. Chucky, the killer doll tv show will
come out of the closet and fat people will disappear. People disappear. These
are some pop culture ones that I found. I don't know if I think about the doll
Chucky the doll announced that he has a non non binary son that it was years ago
child. I was twenty years ago. Have you seen that one clip of Chucky
announcing that the the the Chucky's non binary son is from two thousand and
four nine non binary child, but they they confirmed on the show last year
that Chucky respects the Chucky Chucky respects the non binary and stuff. He's
a killer, but he's not an asshole. He's not a monster. Yeah, he's not a monster.
He's a living doll. Yeah,
I can't speak for the Chucky one, but I don't think he'll come out of the
closet. It feels like Brian Singer is kind of already been. Yeah, I know
singer's been exposed for a while. Yeah, I don't maybe they mean exposed in a
different way, exposes being innocent.
There'll be a dirt on the line here and let's quickly. I would say the Taylor
Swift one could happen if her and Travis don't make it. Yeah, maybe is Travis. If
Patrick's man of the year prediction comes true. Maybe something has happened
man time person of the year, the man who turned Taylor Swift gay
yeah
Brian singer, that's a lot yeah,
because it just happened already. He'll just get exposed by one more okay,
fair enough. The list of thing I'm Luke warm on. I don't know. I don't think
she'll know. I can't lose weight. Okay, Pat says she can't lose. He thinks he's
incapable. No, it's not that she's incapable. It's that she's not allowed
to. I think Chuckie is also I'm also not letting
Lizzo. Don't you dare? Don't you dare lose any weight texting two phones,
texting, cardi B and
oh wait a minute, wait a minute. What that's the image change? Whoa damn, oh
my God, I didn't even think actually you know what Lizzo because we already
locked in the other one. Get on that fucking treadmill right now and wait
maybe also for tying them together. Maybe Brian Singer will be exposed to
the mysterious things that come out of Pandora's box. He's exposed to the new
disease
you will not come out of the
to yeah, that's definitely
people would disappear, but his wife too much not feeling that one. So my
feels like it, maybe it's like a commentary on the Osempic rage, right? I
still don't think that's going to happen. The six hundred past this I don't
or no longer six hundred. All right, we got a few more predictions here. Let's
see what else we got
here's a three a triple water disaster. Let me read these out already. One is
these are what these are going to get specifically because there's a big
bulging thing. It's also there's a an earthquake and tsunami in Japan yesterday.
Oh my God, okay, so this is let me read these out. Then water disasters, fires
at homes and businesses. So those waters and fires and occultic practices could
increase because of hardships.
all of them lock yeah easy. These are easily I could see these so easily.
There is a pending water disaster over there yeah. There's something really bad
happening, but there's a water does and every now and then it happened. There's
the earth. There are noises from that water over there. It's going to burst
and I think I saw somebody's house on fire on the news. Yeah, I saw there was
a volcano last year at the end of the year in that country,
volcano country, volcano world, okay, not down
yeah volcano topia. All right, what's the next? What do you guys think about a
occultic practices could yeah. What are you talking about if I can everyone's
about everyone's a fucking witch now? I guess you're right. Everyone's got these
Betty page bangs and all doing which stuff they got a whole witch story and
over in damn Bush. Everyone's got these shirts that say let's summon a demon
yeah. Let's play with this. We do you say that my neighbor, you know,
practices could increase because of
Joe wearing by a full set of shirts wearing only those shirts of like a fun
graphic tea. Yeah, I don't really wear graphic. I know you wouldn't actually do
it, but I could imagine you doing that in a day back in the day. I was a big
graphic tea guy yeah, then I realize I just can't keep living that way. No, no
there's an age you get to it's time where it becomes time and you can't wear
a tom and jerry hood is sweatshirt anymore. Yeah, you can't wear be walking
around wearing a sour patch kids hat. There's an age you get to and it just
you look like a dope yeah, look like a dunce yeah.
some of us you have to graduate to yeah yeah, you have to graduate your style.
You got to start wearing sports merch for teams. You don't know anything about
yeah,
it's what I do
one shot where one shot two kills yeah
Hiroshima carp,
they're the carp. That's a good name. Yeah, that's cool. Sometimes you could
like you turn twenty six and you decide I'm not going to wear. Are you twenty
six? Yeah, you turn twenty six and you're like I'm going to wear
here. I hear your old as I'm going to wear loafers. Okay, wait, I'm changing
my celebrity death pool for
about how old old as Patrick is old Patrick. That's scary. I hope you don't
die. You start wearing loafers every day instead of normal shoes. For some
reason, I'll never understand a loafer. Oh, I just thought of something really
run for twenty twenty four, but I were in their late twenties in twenty twenty
four. They're not on today. Get get with the loafers and stop with the stoffers.
it's good. It's good right. I would say I would say don't wear loafers, so no,
I just think loafers are kind of clown con shoes. Well, the ones that I have
have tassels and killed their kilt loaf. Oh yeah, that's way cooler. Stop wearing
the hokas and start eating the poke. Have you seen the hokas that look like
they're like
like a backpack? Yeah, they're kind of cool. What do you mean they're like
weird? It looks like a kind of look like a squishy backpack, a squishy backpack,
a shoe that looks like a back pack. They look cool in what way
all right, one last prediction here. What is the final prediction? This is
from Pastor Enoch at a okay. The general overseer of the redeemed Christian
Church of God, RCCG has delivered prophecies for the year. Twenty twenty
four here are his a few of his prophecies are different than predictions.
Yeah, they're basically prophecies are will have prophecies. Okay,
here's his prophecies that I want to read to you guys.
Let's get to the prophecies, please. I'm ready to. Hello. I need to get to the next slide,
please. He did something any minute now. I would never go. Okay. On individuals, he said
there are some people who would start the year as nobody but become significant before
the end of the year. Joe ready to grab many opportunities this year. Guys, Matt Reif,
Ark, he's going to blow up on Tick Tock. We're all going to blow up. Everybody is eating
thing this year. I thought that you were just talking. I thought I was going to
just say only Joe is going to become a mat right type figure. You've been
nobody's. I'm glad you're glad you pointed me as a nobody in your life
but
well, I thought that we were all nobody's at this table completely, but I
thought that only one of us would thrive really a nobody yeah
no man it's this is the this is the year all of our friends who are complete
nobody's. Let's be honest, yeah, everybody we know is a we're nobody's
I'm a nobody, but we're going to become nobody lose a cant. Look at us at us
person of the year, the friend group. Well, the first friend, wow, the first
friend group to get person of the year, the gang, the first friend grouping to
get person of the year besides essential workers. You know they do have a group
chat. The essential workers damn wait the group
first time
the group chats, not a bad get like that's a good one hundred and one odds.
you might time person of the year is a group chat group chat. The cover is
like whatever message got the most react that yeah, the most thumbs up the
funniest joke. Oh my God, wow, we a group chat yeah, that's amazing,
that's an amazing that would be get but get ready. Everybody we have twenty
twenty four. It's time to grab opportunities, grab them. It's the year
of the scorpion. It's the year of the frog is the year of the grind. It's
your money, the frog and the scorpion. It's the year of the group chat. It's
the year of the seventeen hundreds. Wait a minute. If you combine a frog and a
scorpion together doesn't it look like a wood dragon?
I guess if you covered in wood,
if you think about it, yeah, well, I grits frog and a scorpion is kind of a
dragon ask
if you look maybe you had a dragon flight here of the laugh. It's year of
the it's not the year of the scorpion. It's near the scorpion and the frog
you yeah. I don't know about that. I don't know about the scorpion and
frogging yeah. It's got some implications that we're I'm not so keen
scorpion. Okay, then it's the year of the frog on top of the scorpion. Oh wow,
the scorpion gives the frog a right across the desert year of the desert
year, the year of the desert is imagine trying to live your life by the phrase
the year of the desert and try and figure out what that could possibly
entail means you not get a
water
dry
as a bone. Yeah, it's year of eczema. Y'all this year is going to be dry as a
bone.
All right, your bones going to be dry as a bone. We'll be back to regularly
scheduled programming. That's the last of the predictions. A lot of that was
yeah, grab opportunities. It's positive. It's a prophecy. Here's an opportunity
nobody's going to be. Honestly, I think the last prediction should be that got
dick stouts making a twenty twenty five prediction. Without standard, that
standard. Here's an opportunity that you can grab
Patreon dot com offers a podcast about list style subscription that you can
get. Yep, it's only five dollars a month, ten dollars a month. It's style,
yeah. Go podcast about list style. You can go to Patreon dot com slash
podcast about list. You could go to twitch dot tv slash podcast about list.
You could go to Twitter. You join the join the Patreon at five dollars a
month. You're gonna get not only are you gonna get an extra episode every
week, you're also going to get an episode every week of movie Mondays,
where we watch movies on Twitch. The VOD is only uploaded to Patreon. You're
also going to get an episode every week. What we'll see we'll see if it comes
back of beers. We drank who was a six missed killed them. It did them in.
They couldn't do it at ten dollars a month. You're going to get a theme song
for them that they didn't use. You're going to be getting ten. You're going to
be getting D and D episodes every other week. If you pay two orders of five
dollars a month, fifteen dollars a month is a shareholder meeting. Three orders
of five dollars, which is a
live live video call where we do presentations that have a Q and a I
and it's going to be zero dollars a month. You can watch
my videos home plan on YouTube and Instagram and and yeah, there may be
another
Patreon show added to the podcast about list Patreon this year, but I don't know
if I want to do it is an incredible value guys. There's over to you're
going to do one over to
Patrick is going to do a show. Patrick's thoughts may be coming back monthly.
It's going to happen. I promise,
but I don't know if I want to do it yet. That's going to happen. I think that I
have to change the format and restructure to us on you to follow us on
every social media platform. Send all the episodes to your friends and your
family. You just saw them for Christmas. You saw that uncle you hadn't seen a
while. Let's keep a connection. Let's send him this episode. Let's see what he
thinks and and we're going to have a poll that says should should Patrick's
thoughts come back as a music style show and Patrick's got a poll. Patrick has
been killing it in the stew. He's been going crazy in the stew. That's true.
He's every time I see him now he's touching a piano.
Well, I guess that's about all the housekeeping we got to do for twenty
twenty four. Happy New Year, everybody, and get ready to become significant.
Thank you. Goodbye.
This is my first ever post on that website. OK, OK. TuneZone.net. I was
thirteen years old and this is
Subject line, "I went to the carnival recently."
Dot dot dot.
Wow.
I like it already.
So, family guy does come up.
Uh, "Yesterday, I went to the carnival.
While I was looking at- walking around, I saw plenty of games.
At those games, many character-based stuffed toys were there,
including cartoon characters such as Spongebob, Superman, Nemo, Batman, and a few of the Simpsons.
But the character with the most toys was..."
Dot dot dot.
Stewie Griffin!
Oh my god.
That's an adult animation!
Yeah.
Stewie says "bitch!"
I was really concerned about this.
They ranged from massive to very small.
Brian, Peter, Meg, Chris, and Lois also had toys.
I even saw plenty of toddlers with Brian dolls, which there's no way.
No.
You lied.
There's no way.
I had to have been lying.
Yeah.
I've never seen a Lois doll.
I've seen one.
I understand that.
He makes them.
I've seen one. I've seen quite a few.
I understand that many adults and teens go to the carnival too, so I was not very surprised.
However, many of the games with the Griffin clan...
[Laughter]
The Griffin clan is crazy!
The Griffin clan!
I love when, like, it still gets me every single time when somebody talks about the Family Guy characters
as if they're like, like family friends, you know?
You're an amazing writer as a child.
Oh, because I also wanted people to think I was older than I was.
That comes across.
So, I had a sign saying "12 and under."
I was somewhat surprised by this.
I also recently saw an action figure featuring Jasper, which I forgot about Jasper.
Who the hell is that?
Oh, yes, yes.
The replacement Brian.
With the message on the package "8 and up," I know that Family Guy gets wonderful ratings
from the 9 to 14 demographic,
but wouldn't Fox want to hide that fact
rather than embracing it?
- Oh my God.
- That's crazy.
- It's so funny.
- No, I like--
- It's so funny you're trying to sound older in those posts.
- But your subject matter is giving.
- You accidentally, you were trying to sound
like 10 years older,
but you accidentally like sounded 30 years older.
You sound like a Christian mom.
- No, it's--
(upbeat music)