I
guys, New York City is no longer safe. There was a complete like there was a
brawl in front of the studio crazy situation. There was a male brawl by the
way, well, male and the whole situation is genuinely completely very sad, seems
pretty evil. You don't know the details. Maybe there's a fight over candy. I
I could hear, no, because I was the only one that went.
It seemed like there was a candy dealer.
I could hear everything through the other door.
Okay.
And yeah, it's really fucked up.
But somebody has been arrested.
Big hugs to the NYPD.
Thank you, NYPD.
Our boys in blue, you did it again.
Another sicko off the street.
Are they still fighting?
Yeah.
Well, that's good news.
The guy looked exactly like Matthew Golden.
The guy looked like Matthew Golden.
It looked like Matthew Golden was getting arrested.
had a woman got her face completely busted and then they started attacking
a motorcycle for no reason. They were doing a street fighter bonus stage to a
motorcycle.
Four innocent motorcycle. Firstly, knocked it over and then the guy walked
over and he started stomping on it. Just stomped the fuck out of it. Yeah. So
somebody
had their motorcycle with no engine completely destroyed for the motor.
That's the weirdest part is the motorcycle has no engine. It doesn't have
an engine. Maybe somebody already stole the engine. I think we slipped into a
backwards world. I think we did. This is like, it feels like... Motorcycles have no
engines like it feels like Twin Peaks season three. Wow. It's
genuinely and it feels like we just saw. No, it's like that
fucking scene where the lady he walks up to the car and the
lady is just screaming. I've never been. That's how that
I've never seen that's how it felt. I haven't seen the fight.
I only watch. I watched the first episode probably five
times. The first episode is so good. It's so long good dude.
It's a movie basically. I know and I'm like I can't do this
four times. I watched Twin Peaks a while ago and me and me and the fiance just
start restarted it like the other day and the pilot blew my mind. I couldn't,
I thought I was, I was gonna be like, well, it'd be nice to go, it'll be
nostalgic to watch this again, but I couldn't believe how much I like the
pilot. It's still very good. It's crazy, man. But anyway, that felt to me like
Grand Theft Auto.
David Lynch, I don't know. It was much closer to Grand Theft Auto, the video
game. Am I the only leftist that loves Twin Peaks? You might be. I like the
restaurant to when they put the guy into the car, he started like smashing the
door from the inside. I thought we're going to see a full escape. He looked
like he was halfway through, like Zazz make up from like Batman Arkham Knight.
Yeah, yeah, he looked like he had like a bunch of markings all over the back of
his head and very sad scenario. I'm going to say yeah, well, the saddest part is
it scared. I think it was so sad. He's peering through the front door. I was
trying to make I was making. I thought that someone was going to die, but you
you're going to stop it. I thought somebody was a tragedy. Hey, Mr. Cop
leave the guy alone, Mr. leave that guy alone. Okay, he didn't do it. All he did
was break a woman's face in half. Oh yeah, and then stop a motorcycle. What
made me what that's illegal. I thought that this was like a you thought it was
a cat fight. You thought it was hot, but then I didn't think it was hot. I just
yeah. When a man punches a woman, it's immediately a dog, a cat thing, dog
fighting. That's not fun. No, that's scary. That's not fun. A dog chasing a
cat around there's no cartoons. We all we all became three became the three
little Karen's in here looking out the window like oh my God, it was
only of course happening. What are you?
My life is so boring. That's literally all I do twenty four seven is look at
my window. Yeah, oh my God, I hope so. This is to be an old. That's literally
I look out the wind. I do exactly what we just did, but for when someone is
talking on the phone, I go yeah. What are you talking about guy? What's
and on and the maybe the one or two times a year when someone gets into a
traffic fight. Oh, my God, this is what we live for. Come here look yeah, well,
that's what they're arguing. We we live like the our neighborhood is pretty
quiet, but when I was living at that that place in Bushwick, where like the
ceiling was constantly like falling apart and there's black mold, there was
on Thanksgiving night
or the night before Thanksgiving, Thanksgiving Eve, I saw this this whole
family brawl. They were only speaking Spanish, so I couldn't understand what was happening,
but I saw one dude coming down the street with a cinder block, and I was like, "Oh,
shit. Oh, no." But the worst part was the windows in my room. It was an illegal, like
Alex's room should not have been built. It was not built on top of the code. It was just
on top. So my window, I wasn't able to see everything, so I had to go up to Alex's room
room because he went home. Alex, I went in your room when you weren't home to
watch a fight.
But yeah, it was just this family just with cinder blocks and beer bottles
being tossed at each other, and that street was so fucking crazy. You gotta
see one thing like that a year. Yeah. It's always like around this time. Last
year we saw in Portland the guy telling us he was gonna kill the guy with a
machete. Did we talk about that on the show? I don't think so. Yeah, I saw a
guy dragging a chain. Yeah, the chain dragger, the scary Resident Evil zombie
a laser gun. I saw a laser gun guy who there was a homeless guy with a laser
gun. I don't remember that I remember it was it in the future or now it was
must have been it was in the past for us. You're kidding. It was when we were
there a laser gun in the past. Yeah, that's even scarier. Yeah, it was
important because he brought that technology from another time. Yeah,
dimension I do. I did realize the other day, like when I lived on that street
where there was like constantly like a fighter, like somebody like throwing
like glass around or like somebody a couple of guys, someone collecting cans.
Someone's got no. There's a couple of guys who decided to have some fun one
night and slashed the bike tires on my folding bike. That's right. You remember
that the one that I ever tell you about that I won't. I gave you that one. Yeah,
I woke up at five in the morning. I heard a bunch of guys going. No, don't do
that. Oh, no. That could have been heard. Then the next day, both of my tires
slashed completely. It was a fun like that would say yes. Do that. I had a
group. There's a group of teenage just pieces of crap walking by me the other
day and I was walking Phil and they said, look at that dog stupid ass dog.
Fuck that dog and I was and I just literally I mean it was eight people. So
I just looked down and just ignored it. Yeah, the other day my neighbor rang the
doorbell. She's like I forgot my keys.
That's not crazy. Get out of my house. You crazy bitch. I like you crazy.
I was walking with my girlfriend somewhere and I cut through that big, that park where
we shot the Underworld's Biggest Mummy thing. We were taking a short cut through there and
this group of teenagers pointed at me and said, "Yo, don't he look like Mario?"
Way! You got cooked, man.
The worst part was I was wearing the poop hat.
You were wearing the pee hat.
there in the be and you guys,
if that happens to you, your girlfriend is not gonna look at you the same that
no, no, no, no, no, you have to you. I honestly I should have just broke off
and went into just like a bodega and just hid there and I don't I think a
lot of a lot of these teenagers are very well aware of the fact that they can
ruin any relationship. If there's three or more of them, they can ruin every
relationship. Yeah, it's like fucking
nocturnal animals that that movie with Jake Gyllenhaal.
It's like utopia, utopia. Are you talking about zootopia? No bit of a
documentary. It's a movie that I saw probably ten years ago. That is about
Jake Gyllenhaal being such a loser that his wife and daughter get murdered.
So, but it's the same kind of scenario. He's getting roasted yeah where he's
like just going along with stuff. The bartender roasted me last night. You're
kidding. What happened? You were there. He called me mustache. Oh, dude, this guy
was on one. He was on one. I tried to hand him a drink ticket and he was, I
was like, 'Hey, does this cover a June shine?' Okay, and before you say gay,
be honest, that's my stomach. Oh, the bartender, the bartender at the
bell house. Yeah. Oh, that guy likes me. He, I think he likes, he likes
everybody. He like, he must like like me and Cameron because he was bullying
us. Yeah. But I handed him a shot. Well, I said, 'Can I have a June
shot? Can, can this get a June shine?' And he said, 'I don't know. Can it?'
and I just said, Please tell me if I can buy
and he realized that he called me mustache. I said, What yeah, and they
started laughing and I said, Did you roast me man? Did you roast me? He said,
No, I said, Did you really just roast me must? Well, the other thing, the thing
that we're leaving out is that all three of us were in elf costumes, which I
wasn't in an elf. Not at this point. At this point, okay, well, I was in my
elf costume. He was normal. He said that he gave me a shot and said, Bro,
you better than will ferrell. He said that ask your ask your wife. She can
confirm she defended will ferrell. He said you better than she defended will
ferrell. His wife defended will ferrell. Why did you let her do that? Because
he's not better than will ferrell.
You kidding me? You don't have to you don't have to get into a debate about
it in front of the bartender. The bartender said that's a crazy ass thing
to say. Yeah, you're better than will ferrell. The bartender said that and
that you're smarter than albert einstein. She said, I don't think that's
She's right. You're not better than Will Ferrell. I don't know. You're good. You're a nice guy.
You're my friend. According to the bartender. You're better than Will Ferrell. You think
he's better than Will Ferrell? Maybe as an elf. Talladega nights. As an elf, maybe. I
don't like Talladega nights. Oh, that's what he was referring. Oh, I thought he was saying
your whole body of work was better than... I forgot you were dressed like an elf. No,
no, I'm dressed like an elf. He's not saying I'm better than Will Ferrell in all walks
of life. He's saying I'm probably a better elf. Okay, well, you're definitely not better
than Will Ferrell as an elf. I don't know. We can't talk too much about Will Ferrell as
an elf because that's part of my presentation. Okay. So we have to move on from this topic.
We'll move on. Well, I did. You know what? I would like to come clean and admit to a,
I guess a party foul. One that was an honest mistake. No. You guys, I accidentally stole
the spotlight of a karaoke song.
It was the one. You didn't steal spotlight. You accidentally stole somebody's spot
in line. You cut in line. Well, it's disputed because we both picked the same
song. But they clearly picked it before you. We don't know. The jury's still
out. Well, then you didn't do anything. But they looked upset and I want to
apologize formally. I didn't realize until after. Even if you did, you sniped
their song. I didn't realize until after when the song came up later in the
you you have to assume anybody at karaoke. If they pick one song, you have to assume
that's the only song they know how to sing. Yeah, so wouldn't the priority
saying, do they have a person you're handing the request to? Yeah, you tell it
to them or is it like you have a right to sound you're writing down the
question. Okay, and those are you writing down and then you go to the cop
car. That's over girl. That's sad. That's the saddest part. It's over. I
hope they're doing a raid right now in that building. Me too. So far, they're
doing the movie. The rate building right now, rappelling down the sides of
to the building, but I would like clearing out every floor hitting every
corner like this. I've never seen the raid. That movie is sick, bro. I
think we have you seen the raid? No, but I can imagine what you guys gotta
watch. I think every single time we would go to
not Gus's apartment, but anywhere with Gus in college, he would try to get us
to watch the raid. It's a good movie. Is it beast? It's beast. Is it a
Boston movie? No, it's like a
or something like that. That's only like Boston movies. It's
some time really just watches like the town black mass and the departed.
That's all he watches and movies that are like that. He
I hate hanging out with Gus. He always puts on fucking mystic river. I need to
get the I need to bring this book, but he gave me a book when I was in
L.A. that he has this detective series that he's been reading since he was
like ten years old that he still reads and there's like two hundred of these
books and it's about like a fat old detective and it's the picture of the
tech of the detective is a picture of the author and it's called like
mcbarney or some shit and he just solves mysteries every single time. It's the
only book he reads yeah and he gave me one and he was like yeah. You should
read this book. It'll like change your life. It's like a worse version of the
john grisham novel and it takes place in boss and that's why you like oh yeah
that makes sense. This one's completely in asia
The Raid, yeah. It's not an American movie. I don't remember what country it is. I said
Thai, could be Thai, Thai, could be Thailand. Don't know, so I'm not going to make a strong...
Is there an outland? Might be Indonesian, actually, now that I think about it. Oh, they
have the curvy letters. Thai has curvy letters. You know, I learned why they have the curvy
letters. The guys from The Raid, they put them in every action movie now. Okay. So if
if you ever see a guy or the guys don't need them, they usually are bad guys.
They were in some of the Star Wars movies. I think they were good guys
first. Well, they're in real life. They're actors, okay, and
athletes, yeah, martial artists. I wouldn't say athlete. I would say artist.
I think I would say, you know what that is? Artists is in the name of the
thing I was going to say. I would say that they are athletes, but then you
bring up the point that they are called art to add the acting is the art
art, but the the the Marshall, I would say the Marshall is the art part. No,
this is a beautiful dance between the wind and the man. Yeah, I will say an
escape artist is not an artist. You don't think so? No. Houdini, that is a
stunt. That is a stunt man or what's a stunt artist stunt. Yeah, I think it's a
martial artist is an athlete. One hundred percent. I guess they have
tournaments bro. There's no art your turn. There are
that's what are you talking about? That's
that's not a beautiful art. They play using art after they're done. There's
an art like a back to Paul and it's the game and former
art of the month. There's that that's an art tournament. What are you saying
the game and former art of the month? I don't know where they have the things
in the game and former. I have to do that's an art contest. There's that's
there's one example. I didn't say contest as a tournament, but that has nothing.
Of course, those people are artists yeah, but it's a that's they're not
martial. I think I'm I think I think I've lost the plot mate. I think you
honestly you bloody have I you feel completely you feel death for what you've
done bollocks. I've got gone bloody. I've been driven mad by this horrible
world that you saw just a sliver of I know recently
this violence is driving you out of your mind. You would not let one second.
I love the junction. I've I've completely gone around the band. You're around the
bend. You're over the hill mate.
You hit the wall. You hit the wall. I've hit a wall.
I've hit the wall. You've hit the wall. I've hit the wall. Yeah, I'm completely
washed. I'm mid now. You're not mad. Which Liberty women you should be a
baddie, but now I'm mid Susan Sarandon. Susan Sarandon hit the wall.
Helen Mirren Helen Mirren hit the wall
be Arthur.
Uma B. Thurman,
P. Arthur hit the wall,
Betty White, your way, Betty White, a long and passed away because you hit it
so hard yeah. Oh, the cops are still here. What the hell now they're going to
come get it. We're going to have to give a fucking statement. I'm going to go
statement on
dude. We'll just we'll just hand them the first thirty minutes of that. I will
give a statement. I'm willing to give a statement if it is on recorded yeah
yeah, because for my own protection, we have that's what we say to
I think that's a good idea. I will not talk to them. Pound that out. Yeah, that's a good
ass. I'm leftist as hell today. I'm talking about twin peaks, not talking to cops. What's
next for you, man? What's next for me? Right wing. I'm going to completely turn. I'm going
to become post left. I'm going to go talk to those cops. Go talk to him, man. I'm going
to go out there. I'm going to ask for an application. The thing is, cops are so different in New
New York versus North Carolina. Yeah in North Carolina, every cop is a super
soldier. There's bread from birth to be a police. Same with my home. Well, my
hometown, we have the SWAT team in New York. They're just like normal, like
five, four, they go to the store here. Yeah, they go to the store. They walk
around down in North Carolina. They go, they have, they do, they walk as an army.
It is a literal army. People always say the NYPD is militarized. This is not
none of these people could be in the military. No, no, they could be they
could. I mean they could be drone operators for sure. They could be drones
like yeah, like it could maybe be part of the BTS army,
perhaps a BTS army, maybe the BTS army, the only cops that the US army, the
only no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
white people of the white people are in the I thought that they were called the
BTS Army, because I thought that you thought they were called Army, because
they were a group. No, I thought the group was called BTS Army called BTS.
What I thought BTS was short for BTS Army and then BTS was short for
something else. BTS is short for something, but I don't remember behind
behind the scenes. Oh yeah, boys, the singers, boys, the singers, boys, the
singer, but BTS has to go into the Army. They broke up because they got pressed
the military service. This keeps happening to guys. Korean pop stars, they have to go
fight in the army. That's insane. You have to do one year of mandatory service. Whenever
a country has a mandatory army, that's fucked up. They have to do it. This has been taking
down a lot of eSports athletes. Speaking of athletes. Yeah. Which those are the only real
athletes nowadays. PRX Jing just had to take a year off because he got put into the army.
me. Oh my God. Yeah, and then he came back and he was even better at using his gun
in the games. Yeah, because now he knows how to reload it and now he has the
the thrill of the kill means nothing to him anymore. He's doing this is my
rifle. This is my gun exactly. It's completely been brainwashed and so this
makes you better. I don't know how it would make you better at music and
dancing and rap which BTS involves himself in rap, but I couldn't believe
when they wrapped. They also involve themselves in McDonald's. They involve
themselves in a new meal.
We're being distracted by the car is beeping at the cops. Yeah, yeah. So this
is another that's a classic of the work moment. Yeah, helping conflict. Yeah,
that you I feel like you'd only get that in New York where like they like if you
honked at a cop that for blocking the road at all, they would draw their
weapons immediately and switch. She's your car in North Carolina. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. You'd be you can't do that kind of thing. No, here to be respectful and
you have to cry or else you dead. Yeah, here you pc. I mean, there's so many
videos of people fist fighting police in New York City.
Oh yeah.
And the cops are just doing it.
Yeah, they go for it.
Yeah, the cops are handsome but literally like that video where the guy is fighting the dude
in the park and he like slips out the gun and hands it to his friend.
It's exactly like that with all the cops.
They take off all their shit and they're like, "Let's box.
Let's do this shit."
Yeah.
I like that.
That's a thing.
That's a respect thing.
Yeah, that's fucking honor.
Could you imagine somebody coming, like moving to New York to become a New York police officer?
it's got to be the most psychotic person in the world. Can they do that? Can you
do that? Do you have to be a resident of the place that you lived? No, because
all the all the traffic cops in my neighbourhood are all from India, like
every single one of them. Do they ever do the thing that they do in movies
where they're like, "Listen, buddy, you're too crazy. We're forcing you to
move to a village. You can't be-" Like Hot Fuzz? Like Hot Fuzz, exactly. Yeah,
they do that. Is that real? Do they do that? If somebody gets in a police
involved shooting and gets whatever you have to the sticks yeah, but you have
to that's funny yeah, yeah, is that it's it's your cops and the sticks are
evil or I know well, that's because they're all from yeah, they're all
because they all shot somebody yeah, they all got sent away yeah, I got sent
to boarding school by their bosses. Imagine the reverse, though, like a cop
that's like too shitty. So they send them to New York yeah, they should do
that. We need to toughen you up well, it's cop here. I heard there's a cop
here who shot a couple people. They sent him to Christmas City in the North
hole. Really? Yeah. Doing what? Cop? Being a police officer. Being a police officer? Yeah.
Imagine the police there. In PPD? Yeah. Wow. They don't have guns. They have a candy cane
in their holster. They have slingshots. They have slingshots that shoot bullets. Yeah. That
shoots bubbles. A slingshot that shoots bubbles. That's a good invention. That's actually an
amazing invention, man. Yeah. I like that. You might be back. You might have gained the
plot back. They might have jelly marbles kind of bubbles. Kind of bubble like that. Jelly
Marbles kind of marbles. Look at this or be yeah, you lost it again or be you're
back to being completely when I was just a bubble. Yep, a slay that with an alarm
system or a siren. That's pretty good. Yeah, I don't mind that at all. I mean
wait, what other vehicles are there in the North Pole is the only one with a
country car cross country skis. No, you have to like walk everywhere or ski
everywhere. They definitely got snowmobiles, man. Snow shoes, snowmobiles. I mean, that's
walking. Remember snow shoes? S-N-E-A-U-X? No. Oh, that was like Steve-O's shoe company.
You ever see snow shoes when you were a kid on movies and TV and say, "I want to walk
on those, man." Have you ever been snowshoeing? So it spreads out your weight so you don't
sink into the snow as much. Oh, that makes sense. But they're just tennis rackets, right?
Yeah. Well, I mean, a cartoon one is. I've jumped tennis rackets to my feet when I was
like it probably does about the same thing. My mom, I used to go snowshoeing
with my mom. They're like metal and like I mean they're kind of like, like yeah,
they're like metal and they're your feet lock in like skis. Have there been
advance? Yeah, I was gonna ask, has there been advancements in snowshoe
technology? Yeah, probably. Do you think they have a snowshoe that looks like a
Jordan four? No, well, so you could, you wear your shoes. Oh, okay. Still, so you
could wear, you could just wear your, but that would be fire, dude. Yeah, you
just wear your shoes and you strap into the snowshoes, but it's fun. It's a, it's
the fun thing. Imagine the Balenciaga snowshoe.
Pulling up at your Inuit village with the Balenciaga snowshoe. Free idea,
Valenciaga, if you're listening. People losing their fucking mind. The fun part
is when you get the poles, like the cross country ski type poles. You don't
really need them at all. I've been watching this woman on the phone who
is from... Oh, ambulance. Ambulance. Oh my God. Oh, dude, it just keeps...
What, what, what, the fucking mailman's gonna show up next? What the hell?
come on. The mailman did show up in the middle of it. The mailman, the pizza
guy, everybody just
when I was
the other door. When I was in the other doorway, the mailman poked his head
over and then threw a package in and then started walking. That sucks if
you're a mailman and something happens like that and it happens like at the
place you have to deliver. It's illegal for you to not deliver that mail. You
have to deliver it. You have a literal honors bound system. Yeah, you have a
code that you must have mailman's code is one that is punishable by death. I've
trying to get a break it I'm trying to get car insurance and every single time
I go for a quote it always asks is anybody in your family in the military
the police officer or a postal officer so apparently you get all the same
benefits yeah you get crazy crazy but from just being a fucking man yeah my
uncle's a man or was a mailman this is an amazing surgery anybody should do
this job so it takes a long time to get to where it's really good like that's
very heavy seniority based. Yeah, that's what my uncle said. You have to like work for a
long time before you get all the... He's like the samurai. I think it's one of those things
where they kind of initiate you. They kind of fuck with you a little bit. You get hazed.
Well, you get hazed in getting the worst hours. Well, you definitely get... The new kid, the
new guy definitely gets the Santa letters. And they're like, "Go ahead, bring him to
the North Pole, you dickhead." I used to give my uncle my letters to Santa. They have a
training academy. My buddy's a mailman. Shout out to Emmett. He's telling me that he has
to go to like a full academy. You go to like for like two weeks or whatever and you go
take different classes about different types of mailman things. Isn't that awesome? Do
you spin the bag like the gun? You have to learn how to spin the bag. There's reading
bad handwriting on letters, on the addresses. Oh my God. Oh, I thought that was true. There
There is a whole section of there's like a I thought you actually think you're
telling the truth. Well, the academy is real, but that's not a real class.
There's a big
like center where all the mail where they can't read the hand writing goes and
they all they use some computer to try to put it and then some of those letters
have just been there and they can't throw them away. So some of those
letters have just been sitting there for like forty years. It's crazy. I just
have no idea where it's supposed to go. Have you ever thrown mail away that
wasn't yours. My wife threw away a giant box of mail that was sitting in our
apartment for a while this week and I said that's illegal you're gonna go to
jail. You just admitted to your wife's crimes. Yeah well like double jeopardy
can't be held responsible. Okay. I always I always throw it cry I always return
them. Yeah. You return every last piece? So if it's a former tenant and it
doesn't say or current resident, I cross out the barcode and say not at this
address I sent to put it back. Is that what you're supposed to do? Yeah but it
it doesn't work. I just put you're supposed you're supposed to do that and
then supposedly the mail carrying service is supposed to take like the
post office to take it and like well, they take it, but they're supposed to
take it and be like oh, we won't deliver this to me to this person anymore here
because they're really not some, but they still send them, but I take it away.
I get like every single apartment that I've lived in
now my first apartment, every apartment, but after my first apartment, I've
in three places, they have never ever once given me a mail key.
Really? So you have no access?
My last apartment, before I moved out, I talked to my mail lady and I said, "Is there any
way that you can open this up for me? I have not been given a mail key. Do I go to your
office to get a mail key or what? That looks awesome. Wait, talk into it?"
Cam put a Santa hat on his microphone.
I think it's dampening it too much.
I don't think it's dampening it at all.
You do sound cool though.
I don't think it's dampening it enough.
You sound like Santa.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Whoa.
Wait, you really do.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I was a little Dracula now.
Yeah.
But yeah, she said, "Oh shit, that makes so much sense," and then opened it up and there
was just crammed mail, like the slot, like just had so much shit in there.
It looked like a real thinly cut turkey sandwich.
Yeah.
And they folded it over a million times.
That's what it looked like.
And she was like, "Yeah, I just thought nobody lived here."
Wow.
I thought you were nobody, man.
Yeah. I thought you were a complete ghost.
I thought you just didn't matter at all.
Yeah.
Well, Cameron...
We're not a stack of mail that tall.
You putting that hat on your microphone...
Reminded me of Christmas.
...got me well into the Christmas spirit.
Yeah.
Guys, it's week two of the... or is it?
Four weeks of Christmas.
I guess. I think so.
It's week two of the four weeks of Christmas.
On the second week of Christmas...
I wish we had a sleigh bells on there.
Watch this. I think you're going to be surprised in one second.
That's the bell shaking.
It's if you hit them really hard.
That's a different, they changed the bell.
That's a Jaws harp.
It's not a Jaws harp.
It's a Jews harp.
Why do you say Jaws harp?
Because it goes in your jaws.
Are you afraid to say Jews harp?
It goes in between the jaws.
That's closer to a jingle bell.
That's Christmassy.
Chimes. Chimes. Hmm. No, it's chimes. It's fully chimes. It has been declared chimes
by the sound association. Open up the power points and go. And we're off on
another amazing journey to guys. Mystic investigation. We're back on mystic
investigations y'all. I think untitled presentation is mine. Yeah. And mine is
Kaki webby Baba Kaki.
All right, who's going who wants to go first? I can go first. Let Mr. Patrick
go first. All right. So we are back talking about mystic investigations.
You guys, you're back talking me, but no, I'm talking about you're doing it
right now. You bitch. I'm not back talking. You're not a bitch. You're
not. I'm not sassy. You start. Can you give it like an applause? Because it's
Mystic Investigations. This is one that the fans love.
Why doesn't it get an applause?
I love Mystic Investigations. I got lost looking through all this stuff today.
We were investigating a mystical event over there, of a fight, that I feel like we did
not give Mystic Investigations a big enough applause when we mentioned it.
All right, well, if you're going to be such a... Again, back-talking me, but...
Mystic Investigations, yo!
All right, you get a couple of claps from me.
I was concerned that we weren't going to talk about what Christmas is really
about, which obviously, as you know...
Presents.
No, that's exactly what I was going to talk against.
I thought it was commercialism.
Yeah.
I think that maybe you're forgetting the true meaning of Christmas.
No, it's about...
What's the true meaning, Pat?
Well, the true meaning...
It's about corporations having...
No, it is about...
Green and red.
It is about...
And their logos.
respecting the birthday of our Lord and Savior, Jesus Christ.
Now, Julio, click next on the slide.
Did Santa Claus ever meet Jesus? Oh my, okay, here's my theory. Posted December
7th, 2023. My theory based on this picture is yes. By the Christmas spirit.
Wait, the Christmas spirit wrote this? My theory is no, because Santa came,
Santa had no reason to be Santa until Jesus had passed away. Well, let's
You're going to love this, what you're about to hear.
You're sure?
From the Christmas spirit.
More back talk.
And as an Amazon associate, we earn from qualifying purchases.
Yes, Santa Claus has indeed met Jesus Christ, the first son of the Omniverse God, on several
occasions.
This includes the one time Santa was in heaven upon his death at the hands of the anti-claws
on December 6, 343 A.D.
While in heaven, he was able to witness Christ in his complete, magnificent, metaphysical
form, although that wasn't the first time he met the most famous demigod and vice lord
of the omniverse.
Despite being born almost 235 years after the death of Christ, Santa was able to meet Jesus
via time travel.
As a demi-angel, Santa, or Nicholas at the time, accidentally stumbled upon his developing
Chrono kinetic powers at age 16. Wow. He spontaneously traveled 15 minutes back in time to meet himself.
Naturally 15 minutes before that happened. He was shocked to meet his future self. After
that Santa began practicing time travel, but he found the further back he traveled, the
more energy was drained from him. He also found himself greatly weakened and need and
in need of ever longer, ever longer recovery times at age 19. He finally traveled back
to the year one AD to meet baby Jesus Santa at age. Nineteen, I bet you I
wish they had a photo rippling muscle bulging through a red pinstripe suit
because he had the suit because he had this, you know, he has a suit, no
beard. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Of young Santa Claus. That is an amazing
make the movie. Got to make that movie adventures of young Santa like young
Indiana Jones. Yeah, he could fight a piece of young Sheldon, young,
whatever young, any young. Yeah, people love when old stuff is young.
and adventures of young little Wayne. We can make that to young Scooby Doo.
They made that at age nineteen. He finally traveled back to the year one
eighty to meet baby Jesus and officially became part of the first Christmas. The
three wise men magi sensed his holy nature and he was allowed to approach the
Christ child. He technically gave Jesus the first Christmas gift when he
presented a rattle that he made, although it was actually the fourth gift after
the three wise men's presence. When Santa was twenty four, he visited Jesus in his
thirtieth year of life. Jesus had complete knowledge of Saint Nicholas's
importance in the future. They discussed the state of reality and the destiny of
humankind. I do feel like that's a little bit of a flop gift for the son of God.
Yeah, that's a rattle. A rattle. After gold, gold, frankincense, myrrh, myrrh. I
love myrrh. Frankincense, I do. While we're speaking about movie ideas,
is a kind of a my dinner with Andre, Santa and Jesus sitting down to chop it up
about the state of reality and the destiny of humankind. Isn't that an
incredible idea? My dinner with Santa and Jesus.
Santa's dinner with Jesus. Santa's dinner with Jesus,
coming 2025. 'Cause the thing is, Jesus has... He's not ascended yet,
but he has some knowledge that Santa will be
an important figure. Of course. Santa will be one of the most important figures
of Christmas. Yeah, which I think it's hard to argue that Santa's not maybe
the most important. Imagine, imagine meeting somebody like somebody who is
like I have time traveled to meet you.
Please, please
let me be the God of your birthday. Let me be the God. I want to be in control
of your birthday after your death. Once you die, once you die, I want to keep
it going. I'm from the future and I am in charge of your birthday. I'm from
your future, you're gonna die in three years. Here's a rattle. Do you remember
What is a rattle I gave you? I think that I just would be I'd be a little skeptical
of him being the son of God. If as a baby, he was playing with a rattle. Yeah,
it's a bad gift. It's a bad, bad, the frankincense. He's going to smell that
the murder and that stuff is going to use that that stuff has spiritual
significance. It's in the Bible. Yeah. Well, I guess rattles kind of
have a spiritual significance. How so it maybe the sound of maybe it's a sound
you could if you're dead, if you're dead, you could get your death. Oh my God,
Santa delivered his death rattle back with the sarcasm. Holy crap, the sarcasm.
He's being sarcastic. No, I'm not being sarcastic. Tell based on the way you're
talking. No, no, no. Okay. Well, speaking of death rattles, Santa Claus witnesses
the death of Jesus Christ and I need you to see this photo of Santa kneeling at
Christ's cross. Holy shit. The unmistakable silhouettes of Santa. One of
the most artistic photos I've ever seen in my life. It is so beautiful. This
photo of Santa and Christ. Well, it's Christ isn't there. It's just the cross.
Well, it's the cross of Christ.
This is the cross.
Is it your cross to wear or cross to bear?
Cross to bear. But he wears it.
He bears it. It's on his body, he wears it.
He bears it, man.
Finally, at age 32, Santa went back to witness
the crucifixion of the Lord's Son.
When speaking of this, he begins to weep
and says it's the most horrific thing he ever saw.
Santa openly admits he went back a bit earlier
in an effort to save Jesus from the Romans.
However, Jesus himself implored Santa to let history take its place at its predestined course.
In reality, Christ knew the Romans weren't the real threat, but a mysterious force from beyond the omniverse
who had a vendetta with his father.
They are the ones who weakened Jesus so that the Romans could murder him.
Had Santa tried to intervene, he might have been wiped from the very face of the earth before Christmas ever truly got started.
This can't be the worst thing Santa's ever seen.
No.
How many times has Santa gone down a chimney and it's that one episode from
Breaking Bad with the ATM? Yeah. You know, it's like a little dirty kid who's
like in shackles, but he's been really good. He's got a
how many child slaves has Santa not saved? Probably a million. I think like
60% of the children on earth are slaves. Yeah, and he's and they're what,
so they're naughty because they're slaves? Yeah, no, they're nice. Yeah,
they're nice. Go give them a present and while you're there, slip them a
key. Yeah. Give them a birthday. All they want for Christmas is a skeleton
Yeah, just get out of that.
Alright, this next one is just a photo, but it was, I picked it because I liked that it
was a paid ad.
Wow.
And it's a photo of Santa feeding baby Jesus.
Breastfeeding.
Breastfeeding him.
Yeah.
And it says, "Paid Ad" at the bottom.
I wonder who paid for this figurine.
Well, I think it's some kind of auto.
It must be.
way, the coolest thing about Santa and Jesus's relationship is that Santa's
prayers are directly answered by Jesus.
Wow.
Santa Claus is one of the few people on earth who can pray to Jesus Christ and
actually get a spoken reply. That's unbelievable. Although he keeps the
direct prayers to Jesus minimal so as not to annoy him. Plausibly, the vice lord
Christ gets trillions of prayers from parallel universes and multiverses within
the greater omniverse. Most of Saint Nicholas's prayers are the equivalent
of a rhetorical question, so no direct reply is required. Santa also gets the
treat of Jesus being his Santa on Christmas.
Whoa!
The Holy Christ leaves a gift for Santa underneath his Christmas tree in Claus
Manor. Santa's perpetually young kids, Nicholas and Mary, always try to wait up
to see Jesus coming down the tree. Unfortunately, they always mysteriously
fall asleep.
I bet he gives him a rattle.
I have got to be some so I had a mention of his perpetually young kids and mine
to and I was like what who are they? What's their story? I googled them. I
googled like site, mystic investigations, Nicholas, Jr, which is the kid's name,
and I never explained they just always there's a bunch of different things
where he is and Santa and his perpetually young
Mary
Santa eagerly awaits the return of Jesus Christ at the conclusion of Armageddon,
Although he makes a point of inviting him to Christmas and Easter dinners every so
often in the hopes of him taking biological form, in his eyes it would be
the highest honor and most beloved guest to have, second only to God himself. It
is rumored Jesus Christ will appear at Santa's Christmas dinner in a spiritual
forum not long before the final battle of Armageddon.
OMG, that's unbelievable.
Before all shit turns south, Santa's gonna, Jesus will be like, "All right,
why you know you've been inviting me for a while. I can now finally show in
spiritual form, though I'm busy, so I'll show up and show up. I'll have a
we'll see me at the end of the table in a force ghost and I'll just wave,
but that's all I have to say about Santa and Jesus, but I did find one
more interesting thing that I think we need to we need to learn. Okay, we need
to discuss what is it
even Santa poops not
Unlike the imposter in the video, the real Santa Claus does not poop, nor does he produce
noxious gases.
As a demi-angel/angel-human hybrid, Saint Nicholas does not require food to survive,
although his human half does crave it.
His digestive system is supernatural and 100% perfect.
Everything he ingests is utilized by the human half of his body or transferred into angelic
energy, the same angelic energy that allows his human components to survive without sustenance.
more or less he could theoretically eat anything without any negative side
effects. This is includes insane things such as a chunk of steel, some uranium
or even a cup of hot lava. If you're one of the unfortunate beings on this
planet that must endure the indignity of defecation, then you probably need the
product in the video above to mask the hell of your smell. L. O. L. Poopery
before you go. Toilet spray is the perfect stocking stucco suffer for
humans for most humans, a K animal God hybrids on your Christmas list. So why
is he as fat as a fucking melon? Because he doesn't poop. He's all in there.
Yeah, every time he eats, he doesn't need to eat. He's right, but he craves
it because he's like
anyway. He has two thousand years of shit. Yeah, that's why he's very much,
but okay, this is all kind of surprise that even makes him jolly. It would
make me fucking if I was that impacted. I didn't add as far. Oh yeah, I would
become the anti clause. Yeah, that's that's all my slides. All right, I'll go
next here. I haven't this is more. This is a story time. Okay, I have for you
guys,
and this is this is apparently true. The movie Elf with Will Ferrell we were
talking about earlier is based on a true story. Guys,
Mg, so I'm going to tell you guys about what actually happened. Tell me the true
story of Elf, because it's become so commercialized. Yeah, it's been basically
interrupted and the real story is as you know. I'm just all I'm going to say
reality is sometimes stranger than fiction. That's my reference to this.
That's an amazing saying. Thank you. I never heard that the movie elf starring
will ferrell is the story of an orphaned human baby who was raised as one of
Santa's elves at the magical North Pole, capital of Christmas and unnamed
celebrity in the paranormal community, who was a regular guest of North Pole
City, learned of the true elf story and then gave the idea to elf screenplay
writer, David Barenbaum. David then built his own buddy, the human elf story
around the real one, because the rights to the original story are held by Santa
Claus and the human elf. However, Santa does give people permission to create
similar stories around the true ones. To some extent, the supernatural secrecy
pact could be in play, but realistically, nobody would believe such stories are
real anyway. So, Santa is the copyright holder of this story, and he said, "You
can't use this story, but you can do one that's almost exactly the same." So,
David Barenbaum has a direct line to Santa.
Yeah, he had to talk.
Through an unnamed celebrity.
Who do you think it is?
That's North Pole, yeah.
Is it like Burrow Eyes?
In the paranormal community.
Yeah, it's got to be.
It's got to be.
Okay, who is a celebrity that is also involved with paranormal community?
Zach Bagans.
No, that's too involved.
I feel like it's got to be someone who maybe knows Will Ferrell or rolled with Will Ferrell.
It's probably, it's definitely not Zach Bagan.
Rob Schneider.
Could be Sacha Baron Cohen.
Could be.
I wouldn't be surprised.
It's definitely not Zach Bagan.
It's like that video of the guy standing outside of ice Poseidon's bus. I don't
know that don't know it off. Okay, Mrs. Claus come along for the Christmas Eve
flying sleigh ride in truth. The real elf was technically Santa and Mrs.
Claus first child, although be it an adopted one on Christmas Eve of 1888. So
this is an old story. Mrs. Holly Claus wanted to come along during Santa's
present deliveries that included the usual three sleigh managing elves who
assist Santa. There are certain dangers with her coming along as she was merely
human at the time who had to be magically protected against the stresses of flying a light-speed
teleportation sleigh. There are also potential attacks from various dark supernatural beings.
Even in her current status as an immortal human, these supernatural stresses would still
be an issue. The magical protections required things to be slowed down, which can also make
Santa more vulnerable to the Anticlaws, Krampus, or other destroyers of Christmas. Since most
of these dark Christmas entities were beaten back sufficiently in 1888, it was somewhat
it's safe for Mrs. Claus to have that year. Yeah, okay, Mrs. Claus only came
down the chimneys of select places with Santa. That included a religious
orphanage in New York City. Sounds familiar, right? I'm sure you remember
sounds like where she greeted some of the babies in their cribs as Santa
delivered gifts. The priest who ran it actually knew Saint Nicholas, so there
was no violation of the supernatural secrecy pact. Mrs. Claus took an
automatic liking to one baby in particular, and she rocked him gently in
her arms. When it was time to go, she asked Santa if they could take the child
back to the North Pole to raise as their own. This was before the
angelic heavenly hierarchy intervened to grant them children of their own
immortals, such as Santa can't have children naturally, despite an angel
being able to have one immortal child with a human. It's nature's way of
preventing the earth from being overrun with the mortals, thereby overshadowing
the predestined story of humanity. Wow, the priest had no objection to the
adoption, but Santa regretfully said he was forbidden from bringing a human to
North Pole City, who did not find their way there on their own. This was
another amendment of the supernatural secrecy pact. She was quite melancholy
over leaving the child behind in his crib. Her sobbing in the back of the
sleigh made the rest of the delivery schedule a real downer. Santa and the
elves tried to console her, but she just couldn't forget the adorable little
baby boy. However, she eventually kept a stiff upper lip and fell silent so as
not to hinder Christmas in any way. So Santa ruined Mrs Claus Christmas hard
well where they had to have gotten the kid at some point, but then a little
Isabella invades North Pole City later on during Christmas morning. Santa was
enjoying his first post delivery meal. So here we see that he doesn't need to be
he does eat a behemoth of a breakfast fit only for a powerful human angel
hybrid like Saint Nicholas. Mrs Claus barely touched her hot cakes laden and
peppermint syrup and butter made from reindeer milk. Yeah, actually it's
probably fine nearby. A plethora of elves shattered and chowed down with
glee. Suddenly everyone fell silent and stopped inhaling their sugary food as
subtle sounds of a baby cooing could be heard. Santa uttered, "What in the seventh heaven
is that?" Everyone walked over to Santa's giant red velvet sack that should have been
empty after being drained of all Christmas toys. The bag was moving and suddenly a baby
came crawling out, smiling at everyone. It was Mrs. Claus' baby boy from the orphanage.
The child had somehow miraculously left his crib and entered the bag in the short span
of a minute. He managed to stay hidden in the bag throughout the rest of Santa's deliveries
due to it being a four dimensional bag. It had virtually unlimited space within,
so the child was probably crawling about what appeared to be warmly lit corridors
for hours before finding his way. Imagine it didn't find it. Maybe it was
in the back in there yeah
inside of the back rooms man. He could have been in there. They could have
never found him yeah. He could have died. He could have died of starvation
and water lack. Men of Candid Santa killed the baby on Christmas. I know
Mother Christmas scooped the cute baby up in her warm loving arms as she cried
tears of joy. She looked at Santa and asked, he found his way here on his own.
Can we keep him dear? He grinned widely and told her, yes, my dear.
From that moment onward,
she raised him as their own child and named him Sandy in honor of Santa's
father, the archangel Sarandio.
Although he spent a great deal of time with Santa's elves,
normally people age extremely slow at North pole city, including Mrs. Claus.
However, no human baby had ever lived there for any long length of time.
something caused him to rapidly age physically to adulthood. By the time he
was twelve years old in the year one thousand and one hundred, although he
was still mentally a child, since his friends were all childlike elves, it was
later revealed that his constant inhaling of elf dust acted as a
supernatural stimuli to accelerate his elf does come off of an elf. So here's
a little sidebar on what is elf does this is I pulled up this article just to
so we know here
more off. Most often elf dust is a byproduct of their respiration process.
when exhaled, it's invisible most of the time. However, it accumulates in the
surrounding environment at North Pole City. Much of the glitter in the snow is
actually elf dust. The majority of elves, including Santa Claus, enchanted elves,
only breathe the helium in our atmosphere. This partly explains their
comical low pitched voices, but I think they mean high pen. Helium composes a
mere point O O O five to four percent of our air, as opposed to the oxygen we
breathe, which makes up twenty point nine four six percent. Elfin cells
paranormal process the helium and Mac manufacture an argon neon compound of
a r2 any three that is exhaled from their lungs scientifically such a compound
could never exist, but this is the world of the supernatural we're talking about
here that being said the second this rare gas hits the air and immediately
breaks down to argon and neon these gases famous for causing the glow of
neon lamps emit a brief glow from the elves nose and mouth if viewed in
complete darkness in addition the exhaled elf dust will visibly shimmer in
that moment as well.
I'm always so fucking amazing how in depth all this is, but beware. Oh my
God, that some glittering and glowing substances can in fact be radioactive
rather than supernatural, although in some cases supernatural substances are
radioactive. Thankfully, true elf dust is harmless to humans, so if you see
something glittering and sparking sparkling, it's either don't touch it
because it could be radioactive. Well, it could be else us could be which
could make you your body get bigger. That's true, so I could make you age
kind of a gamble. So back to the story here, Sandy confronted his adoptive
father, Santa. He and Mrs. Claus sat down with Sandy to give him the news he
was adopted and was originally a human. Despite that Santa made it clear he was
their real son brought to them by the spirit of Christmas, he had also grown
into a true elf and should no longer consider himself human. Sandy was content
for a time until 1909 when Santa and Holy Claus saw the birth of their first
biological son, Nicholas Jr. The archangels allowed them to have kids after
understanding how positive it was for the clauses to raise Sandy. Sandy
became somewhat disenchanted and jealous of the arrival of the new child. He
decided to return to the human world in one thousand nine hundred and eleven to
find his real parents as a demi angel. Santa could look into anyone's mind and
see who their parents were. So now we're getting to the movie plot here. Okay,
Sandy's mother, Ellen Hemingsworth, was part of an affluent New York City
family who arranged a marriage to for her to another wealthy clan. Her husband,
Percy Hemingsworth, was a horrible cad. No cheated on her and was only in the
marriage to increase his family's power and position in life. Sandy's
heartbroken father, Patrick Forrester, was disowned by his own working class
family and run out of town so they wouldn't be blacklisted from working at
local faster factories. He headed out west and became a cowboy who never
married because he was still hopelessly in love with Sandy's mother. Sandy was
given a mystical snow globe by Santa that allowed him to open various portals
in a flash. He was out west in a small Colorado town called Woodland Springs,
current home of mystic investigation, the creators of this website. He found
his father on a cattle ranch. That's almost amazing, yeah, and now we'll see
more similarities with the movie here. Without blood and DNA tests, it took
some time to convince Pat Forrester he was his son. Thankfully, his mystical
elf powers aided him and they bonded for some years. Sandy didn't reveal where
he had been raised, as per the supernatural secrecy pact, along with
being told by Santa he would be branded a nut burger without proof he wasn't
allowed to produce. Although in defense of life, one can reveal their paranormal
powers. This happened when a violent gang of psychopathic cattle rustlers
attacked the ranch in the winter of one thousand and thirteen. Everyone would
have surely died if Sandy had not single handedly repelled them, mostly via dense,
high speed snowball throwing happens in the movie happens in the movie being
beamed with a one hundred mile per hour wet packed snowball can mess a person up
real good. Sandy was also forced to display other elephant abilities, such as
super strength when he talked a few rustlers around this caused the
formation of glittering elf dust to emanate from him. He finally told his
dad he was an elf, knowing such magic existed, inspired him to take a son back
east to reclaim his true love. They traveled there instantly via Santa's
paranormal portal activated by the magical snow globe. Then, in New York
City, Christmas, one thousand nine hundred and thirteen was approaching
that's Christmas one thousand nine hundred and thirteen. It's a different
holiday as Sandy finally convinced his mother he was her son. She demanded a
divorce from Percy Hemingsworth as she fell in love with Pat Forrester all
over again. However, the abusive cat of a husband sent thugs not dogs after
father and Elfin son, the thugs that were then dispatched Christmas style by
Sandy. A divorce was denied by everyone as his mother Ellen was whisked away to
England in the dead of night. Father and son managed to find out where she was,
but the magical snow globe portal was only programmed to go to Woodland
Springs, Colorado, New York City and back to North Pole City. Sandy was going to
return to the North Pole with his father to ask Santa for help, but it was
Christmas Eve and they spotted him in the skies above bellowing. Ho, ho, ho,
Merry Christmas, Santa sensed Sandy's presence below and landed in some woods
nearby. That happens in the movie to landing in woods. After hearing what
happened, Santa told Sandy and his father to hop in the sainted red sleigh. They
immediately flew away to England in a flash. Sandy kicked in the door and his
father got into an epic fist fight with the abusive CAD Percy Hemingsworth. I
with this cad as how do you I'm sorry how did they get to England so quick?
It's a it's a slay you ass. No, no, no, no, no, not I know how Santa got there.
How the hell they'd Percy Hemingsworth and his wife man in the rich abusive
cad yeah, but when they have been on it would have made more sense if they got
on a boat. Yeah, I got a private boat. All right, all right, he's rich.
His father got an epic fist fight with abusive cad Percy Hemingsworth as Sandy
hugged his mother. He said, let me floor dad. I don't it's weird after healing
the other two guards and putting them into a deep sleep. Old Saint Nick
strolled in with an uneasy smile. He then easily pulled the two brawling men
apart with his titanic angel strength. The supernatural voice bellowed loudly
enough of this insane violence. This is Christmas Eve for the love of God.
Sandy pleaded with Santa that his parents should be together as the wealthy
cad said he had every right to keep his wife and demand everyone leave his
property. Now this is an insane power of Santa that I never knew he had here.
listen to this. Sandra reluctantly agreed, but then recited some important
words. I say Nicholas in my holy capacity of heavenly ambassador hereby
make this unholy marriage null and void in the eyes of the Holy Lord and savior
of the universe. Amen, he can dissolve marriages. I would piss me off. I
would
like you. There's legal stuff. We have to do
walks in is like you're not married anymore. What if you're yeah? What if
that what if that's what your wife wanted for Christmas and you and
talking that's how you get a limone thing you're just done. Percy Hemingsworth
angrily attempted to punch Santa and the kisser as he exclaimed. Those words
meant nothing because he had marriage papers. Santa restrain him and said all
papers and records of this marriage have been supernaturally disintegrated. You
are no longer married and you will continue to be on my naughty list for
the rest of your life. No doubt, Santa placed the pathetic Percy into a deep
sleep as Sandy's parents embraced and kissed the joyous family, use the
Blue Globe to travel to North Pole City with Santa's blessing. That is amazing.
This is something they don't show in the movie. See Sandy's parents,
consummate the marriage, finally get married.
Well, because I think his mom's dead. Yeah, right. So yeah, they didn't want
to deal with Percy Hemingsworth. Yeah, the movie, they don't want to put a cat.
Yeah, the cat is a scary. Who would have been the perfect cat in that movie?
John Favreau himself, the director. Yeah, Sandy's parents finally get married.
Santa finishes Christmas deliveries and had Mrs Claus make plans with Sandy's
biological mom for a wedding. While doing so, the women bonded as Ellen showed
great gratitude toward Holly Claus for raising her son. All the elves approached
Sandy and welcomed him back with open little arms. They officially declared he
was a real elf. Sandy also made an effort to bond with his little brother, Nick Jr.
At about 7 p.m. on Christmas Day, everyone gathered at St. Nicholas Church. In the
witness of several elves, Sandy's parents were married by St. Nicholas himself.
Naturally, Sandy was the best man, while Mrs. Claus was the maid of honour. To this
very day. Sandy and his parents still reside in North Pole City. Often the
clauses and the foresters get together for dinner and other activities. Sandy's
full name is Sandy Claus Forrester,
still just called Sand last name's l. Now this is the most insane part, but
so this is like a move. It's like milk. That's the movie. It's his last name.
Yeah, yeah, wow. Now this is the craziest part. This part they'd need to
have put this in the movie, and I think that they should release a version with
this alternate ending. Okay, on Christmas, one thousand and fourteen,
Santa gave the Forrester family a unique gift. Sandy and his parents opened a
gift box and were transported into a mystical realm drenched in the spirit of
Christmas. Sandy was made into a baby again and his parents got to raise him
until eighteen with it a dream world. They simultaneously believe it was real
while knowing it wasn't a supernatural state that is hard to explain at the end
of what seemed to be eighteen years. Their bubble reality ended and they
exited to find only one month had passed. Sandy and his parents now had the
a memory of a happy childhood together. Sandy got the gift of two childhoods,
both of which he remembers. What did he have a say in being turned? No, no, my
guy is a fucking twilight zone episode and then here's the epilogue. If they
also didn't cover this in the in the movie epilogue, way more cops after the
orphanage priest died, he spiritually visited Saint Nicholas from the great
beyond. He confessed to secretly placing the baby Sandy in his toy sack. After
seeing how much Mrs Claus loved the child, Santa forgave him and both agreed
and never tell a soul for fear of the repercussions of a super natural
secrecy pact violation, angels, demons or any other entities who signed off on
the ssp could possibly go back in time to prevent the event. The sandy would
never become an elf, nor would his parents ever find you don't want that
shit yeah, and that's the story on like I said reality. It's stranger than
fiction. Sometimes it really is. They have so many different magical things.
I got turned into a baby for almost no reason at the end of it. Wow, that's
amazing. Okay, I have I was looking so I know it's a Christmas episode. We're
supposed to do all Christmas stuff, but I did get I just found something that I
liked a lot that it was not it's holiday related, but not so much Christmas. So I
have to apologise for that. That's okay, but
I do want to really quickly look at the have you ever looked at the disclaimer
for this website? I don't think so. We might have it. It has a no. I don't
think so. I mean maybe we looked at it for a second, but at first you think
it's just like a normal like copyright policy or something, but it says this
the following text below may be required under the supernatural secrecy pact of
thirty three AD. The characters places organizations at events on this site
mystic investigations dot com are completely fictitious. Wait. I know what
happened in thirty three AD. Yeah, whoa yeah, that's crazy. Any similarity to
any person living or dead is merely coincidental. Any similarity to any
place organization event or anything else for that matter is also purely
coincidental. Despite this site being a total work of fiction, we have no way of
knowing for sure if the various supernatural beings and folklore mentioned
actually exist on this planet, another planet, or a parallel universe. In fact,
they very might well- they might very well exist. If you believe the religion
of Godhoodism, which states that everyone who's good eventually ascends to Godhood
and creates their own universes, which we should do a deep dive on Godhoodism at
some point. Godhoodism might be the most important part of this entire thing. The
guy who made missing investigations has his own religion called Godhood ism,
which he takes very seriously as an entire blog about it, but basically you
become a God at the end of your life. Okay, next slide.
Who knows if we're required to say all of this under the alleged supernatural
secrecy pact of 33 A. D.
Blah, blah, blah. The information on this site is not intended to or implied to
be a substitute for professional medical advice and then this big medical
disclaimer, but you you might see this and say, Oh man, it's all fake, but
they seeded these little things about the the supernatural secrecy pact of
thirty three AD, and if you go to the next slide, there's a photo of this
thing. Look at that. Oh my God, that's the pact. It's a golden tablet with a
bunch of crazy writing on it, and so this was signed. I'm guessing that
these are all signatures of different gods, God, angels, all that sort of
and this is a very, very important pact. Okay, I want to move on from this though. But I just
like that they have this disclaimer, but then they tell us the truth in the disclaimer.
Okay, so the story I'm covering is what are the digital demonic dangers of Cyber Monday?
This is by Xavier Remington. Here you have a photo if well, yeah, so you have a photo
of some kind of hacker hacking into a MacBook, something that says 60%. And that's in Mordor.
It's like door and then there's a bunch of stairs up to heaven. It looks like heaven and
hell almost. All right, next slide. So maybe you skipped the frightening shopping frenzy
of Black Friday to avoid the dangers of being injured by hordes of human shoppers, zombies,
vampires, and the demon god of greed, Mammon. A lot of bad things can happen in a chaotic
crowd. There's also the potential for demon possession when it comes to those with weak
minds. Those suffering from the unfortunate and mental condition of greed and a lust for
material items they don't really need. These misguided individuals with monetary malevolence
in their hearts are compelled to injure innocent people who get in the way of their supposedly
sweet shopping deals." There's a lot of alliteration on this website.
It seems sitting in the safety of your home and shopping the dynamic deals of Cyber Monday
-- that's an ad, it's a built-in ad -- on the Internet is the way to go. Sure, it's a lot
safer, but there are still risks as you furiously click away, adding items to your virtual shopping
cards while whipping out your credit card. And there's a photo of a melted
computer guys and a scary set of yellow beady eyes behind a black. Oh shit. I
didn't even notice the eyes. Yeah. So this can get scared. I thought that that
was just a modem. Next slide. You may think that cyber monday safe. The risk
of cyber monday includes the aforementioned demonic possession for
the simple minded overwhelmed by a lust of luxury items. There are indeed cyber
demons within cyber space. Those dark spirits who can't quite make it into our
reality completely end up as paranormal binary data forms on the internet. This
makes sense when you consider that everything in our physical reality is
ultimately composed of non-corporeal energy, which is in essence a dynamic
form of data. Often they become trapped in the unfamiliar reality. They are bound
by the limits of the World Wide Web, hardware, and various software platforms.
However, they can still be diabolically dangerous. Even more alarming is a new
form of magic, which dark practitioners of magic or even demons themselves are
writing intricate AI code that they can breathe life into. In essence, creating
new cyber demonic life, their own private minions ready to dominate and corrupt
the future virtual reality holographic internet. Oh my god. So and this is a
Monday problem. This is a big problem on Cyber Monday. Jesus. Next slide.
Demons who merely haunt the web while still existing in the metaphysical world will simply
use their cyber form to brainwash your mind. Once weakened enough, they will perform a
standard direct possession. True cyberdemons will sometimes have the assistance of a real
world demon to pass the possession off to." So they will possess somebody through their
computer and then say, "Hey, Beagleborg, come get this bitch."
Yeah.
Scary.
The Beagleborgs?
Beagle.
Beelzebub.
It's considered a living sacrifice and the cyberdemon is rewarded with power and a promise to be released from the computerized prison someday.
If it is merely a lone virtual demon, then on-screen hypnosis and Wi-Fi connections are their entry into your mind, body, and soul.
The high-frequency electromagnetic waves of Wi-Fi act as a conduit for higher-dimensional cyber entities to enter your subconscious.
That is where perplexing possession begins.
not perplexing. I do not fuck with perplexing per person. The demonic
possession is particularly high while sleeping as your subconscious manages
your greedy material possessed thoughts of the day. Be sure to sleep far away
from the wifi or turn it off. Listen closely. Ethernet connections are best.
We already knew that shit. Certainly use of mobile devices is a risk on this
malevolent monday. Oh just on cyber just on cyber money. Cyber monday is
probably the highest demonic attack day. Next slide. How to repel cyber demons of darkness.
And this is a pair of green eyes shoot in a green hoodie, shouting out ones and zeros.
So Jawa Cyber Monday is the number one day for calamitous cyber entities to rear their
blasphemous binary heads forth to plague people with their hellish horror. If you want to
avoid the hazards that range from computer issues to being eaten alive, then be extra
cautious on Cyber Monday. Just think happy thoughts or realize there's plenty of trinkets
for everyone on the Internet. So don't obsess over your trinkets, guys.
Yeah. There's plenty to go around.
You'll get your shopping deal, another ad, but even if you do, even if you don't, it's
no big deal. Don't obsess over material items and keep a cool head along with a calm heart.
If you see your computer starting to wig out, then immediately shut it down and leave the
room because it could be a demon entering your domain. Blessing the computer with holy
holy water
to put water on your computer or merely cleaning the screen off with it can
help placing religious artifacts around your computer can also help using a
Bible as a mouse pad is a major moral measure of security as you serve
through perilous virtual waves. I never considered that use the Bible as a
mouth mouse bed. Have you as you serve the perilous virtual waves of cyber
monday's ocean swimming thick with sinister shopping sharks. If all else
deals, try praying to the Holy Cyber God, Cyber God, yeah, Cyber God man, Amen.
Next slide.
Cyber Monday, at Mystic Investigation. So they're taking measures at Mystic
Investigation, and there's an ad on either side of those ones for an LG OLED
Evo that says it's time to upgrade your television. Our employees are given
fifteen minutes every two hours to personally pursue the Internet for Cyber
Monday deals. All our computers are cyber vaccinated with the latest magical
anti-demonic software, along with being blessed by a priest.
There are also protection spells in place.
Employees may also take turns on cyber patrol duty
and shop on websites as they officially look
for signs of trouble.
Some are also assigned to our cyber phone center
on this dangerous day.
While waiting for calls, they are allowed to shop as well.
Generally, we get information on the type of entity
inhabiting one's computer,
and then we design an antiviral-type program
to deal with the supernatural scourge.
tougher cases require us or our partners and other communities to make a house
call to exercise the cyber demon, which could be a reboot of the exorcist.
Yeah, is that your computer or your phone is completely has a demon in it,
man? Get that thing out of here. The computer cyst interesting note. This to
me is the most interesting part of this whole thing. I persist because we've
been talking about so cyst the exorcite exorcist. Oh my God, it was right under
the exorcist, the webser site or like the web source, the webs or site
interesting. Now, cyber genies are usually far less nefarious and think
akinator,
akinator, akinator far less nefarious than their real life genie in a bottle
counterpart. Their mind is oddly altered in a positive manner by becoming
digital me too man. Then there's the awesome freedom. They feel not being
confined to a bottle or lamp, nor are they bound by the three wishes rule.
however, it's best to exercise caution. If you come across one,
they can still get quite vindictive if you offend them. So cyber genies are
nothing like real genies at all. They don't grant wishes. They just live in
the computer. They just guess to see what, oh, you're talking about Hassan
Abhi, right? So that's interesting. I think maybe there's another slide, but
that might be it.
Now, that's it. That is it. So that's the I know that Cyber Monday is already
over. I want to know what cyber God. I'm really yeah. Me too. I forgot to
include something about cyber God, but maybe we can look at it real quick.
Just search cyber God, mystic investigations. I'm sure it'll come up
because I do. I am interested to see I want to see a photo cyber gods. This
has got to be him right? Yeah.
Whoa, my God, he looks like a tool music video. Way crazy. Does the fabled
cyber God exist? It is a five minute scroll down. There are those who claim
to have contact with a so called cyber God. However, most of the time they are
cyber demons, cyber gen, cyber genies, cyber ghosts, and other enchanted
electronic entities, more or less real life, higher dimension and dimensional
entities or souls that either purposely or accidentally are transmuted into
digital data within one computer, a network, or on the greater world wide
web internet. In the future, complex computer vices,
complex computer viruses may form an artificial intelligence and become cyber
demon like entities. He predicted chat GPT back in 2017. Oh my God. It's scary
fuck man and look a metabolism secret has been revealed
try this bizarre five-second hack let's just see if there's any more photos of
him false cyber
future yeah just keep going yeah then man
cyber god afterlife weird science wait a g a genie possessing a computerized
site creation created lisa the weird science cyber genie
wow the cyber god's mission what does he want whoa
he kind of looks like the helps and he's oh he's stopping. He stops the AI. As it
says, he fights against the AIs on the God. We have a thanks cyber God, this
cyber God fighting for us again. Genies well, thank God for the Lg Oled Evo.
Yep, and that's actually an amazing deal. That is a great deal. That's a great
check this out. If you have money and Alexis built into that guy for a
Christmas present, that's a gift guide. All right, you guys, that is the episode.
It looks like we might be getting arrested pretty soon.
Yeah, I think there's a paddy wagon that's pulled up in front of the office.
The full paddy wagon is in front of the office.
They have been here for an hour or so.
Something crazy must have happened while we were recording.
So, if you don't mind, we're gonna go talk to some police officers.
Bye guys!
Guys, I've made a terrible mistake.
What happened?
Maybe a marriage destroying mistake.
Oh no. Yeah, last night.
Me and my wife have decided to start doing a budget.
doing a budget, right? To do, take care of our money.
It's that season, man. I've been on the budget too, and it's been ruining my life.
Not good, dude. It's not good.
What happened?
It's not good to look...
Dude, the moment you realize how much money you actually have...
And your wife makes double the amount of money and it's still not that much money.
Exactly the same experience.
And then she's like, "Is this really how much money you make?" And I go, "Yeah, bitch. We
have an office."
I'm seeing the exact number of money I'm putting into savings every month.
Yes.
Sorry, more than two digits sometimes.
Only sometimes.
Yeah, but I last night we did we went over his budget spent hours to yeah,
we set up a joint bank account took us weeks. We finally got it.
We're doing got to put together had to go to had to go to Bank of America,
set up the joint bank account, how to do it took days. I'm going to need your
advice on this because we have no idea how to do. He said that this is marriage
ending I don't think you need his advice. I know he's getting he's working up to
the mistake. I'm making them I made the mistake okay so last night so we set up
the entire thing right and then and and in my checking account not that much
money but we agreed that like our joint checking account is gonna be groceries
and yeah like yeah stuff that we'll both do right so last night she goes to bed
and I stay up so I can do the dishes like a good guy right yeah and I'm
sitting there and I'm watching YouTube videos and I get this ad man. I get this
ad for something called Alpine Butcher that sells A5. Oh no, I know, I know, you were saying you were gonna buy it last night after the gym.
You, oh my god, did you put it on the fucking joint bank account? I
accidentally bought it with the joint bank account card A5, marbling score 12,
*laughing*