Go ahead, say some woke shit right now. I'll blow your fucking head off. I
what is this a sex toy
for me? It is yeah for me. It is I point this in the mirror and I jack off
no. I pointed a mirror. I think nobody should have access to guns, even
soldiers. I don't think anyone okay, that's interesting, that's
interesting. So
go ahead and tell me how you think we should fight a war.
How are we supposed to kill millions of people without a gun using? I feel
statements
so give me an example. You take my territory
or when you ethnically cleanse my country or terror or area, ethnically
clans. It makes me feel unheard on the world stage.
so maybe we can work towards a solution where I can validate you for you,
wanting my brace to
no longer walk the earth. Okay, and I can validate you and say and then I walk
into the meeting
and I see every single person kill. I see both sides of this. I see completely
both sides of this guys are back to debating. If you can tell we're doing
the debate on Christmas to a cross. We just ate six enchiladas between the
three of us and about four pounds of beans, so to each six until I will see
you'll see how this goes. What the debate because there's a lot of inch a
lot of me, you tell me you don't even have a position. Yeah, you ask what your
nothing is you say. I don't even want one yeah. Exactly true. You always
complete centrist. Anytime we do these debates, which anytime meaning one time
and now yeah you we did a different debate, but it wasn't between us. We had
hot dog and hamburger, but that's more of a boxing. That was a battle. That was
a battle. I thought we were going to do a battle.
battle, but it's a different thing. It's a word battle, a debate, a battle, but
basically I am I mean this is last time we did a debate. We did all sorts of
topics right. We did every topic under the sun. Go ahead and do the voice or
Pat, whoever you are. What voice? The voice of the intro. Oh, we did stuff
looks like. I don't remember it. Well, just say stuff man. It's improvise
Christmas. Well, we didn't do that. Well, we actually didn't talk about
Christmas, but this time this time it's only Christmas. It's only Christmas and
it's the it's a we're having a debate on the role of wokeness in the holiday
season and whether or not it should be allowed or dis this obviously it should
be disallowed, whether it should be obviously allowed and we're all I don't
even remember what the second option was and we're all elves because we ordered
these elf costumes and forgot to use them in any time. It would make sense.
We did the girl God show. I
fell in love with the elf. We had we had a
love with them. I asked for him afterwards. They said no yeah, which
first of all, I also I'll take a listen. I'll take credit. I masterminded this. I
sent Caleb. I said Caleb, you have to go agent. You have to go be like the face
character for our party, like in Baldur's Gate. You have to go and finesse these
elf costumes. Charisma is to steal them from girl. God charisma was way too low.
You rolled at one. I rolled a critical failure yeah, and then I said I said,
let me buy them off you and she was like, oh well, you know you don't need
it. Yeah, I'll send you the Amazon. Yeah, I'll send you Amazon like I was
like, well, just give them to me then and she said no yeah. I came back to
you hat elf hat in hand and I said we have to buy them ourselves. Elves are
stronger together. Elves are today. We're divided
funny noise. I guess like tomatoes.
I do not look like tomatoes to talk today. Are you kidding me? So how's
your day today? But I would see what you look like. Turn your camera on Buster.
You mother Buster. He can't turn his camera on a gun. You bastard say
something, say something, defend yourself. You sound like a tomato bitch.
Say something other than tomatoes. Fucking Christ, you're tomato brothers.
I'm not
we're not the mother fucker. We look like one were elves to today. We're not
brothers at all. We're brothers and arms on opposite sides. We're sisters
because sisters are always arguing sisters fight. They say you fight like
an old married couple of sisters. Yeah, old married
sisters do fight all the time. What's that about? Brothers? I talked to my
brothers once a year. If I had brothers,
then this
then you wouldn't be like how you are. No, I wouldn't be so damn woke of
your brothers. I grew up with brothers. I grew up in a household of women and
men. I grew up with two brothers and a sister.
I grew up, I grew up with a I grew up with
purple furry monster. You're kidding. Yeah, that's a flat, a bald faced lie.
Maybe let me guess in my lived experience, because you're from where
arrest. You're from woke Disneyland, where they have gay night. Yeah, I'm
from walk stir you from walk stir walk stir mass
I really need Worcester to become a center of of a liberality and what
yes of people's can call it already. Walks that would be isn't it already
now
okay, so now you're kind of coming over to my center of Massachusetts. I would
say that Boston bridge, bro lame bridge, a lens of fruits and nuts, summer
summer fill up your welfare bag, summerville is there. You're trying to
day shut up yeah. I'm not really good at I don't even talk shit about
some of
because you're from there. Don't even don't you even dare talk shit about
you look like a tomato for real. I don't look like you dress. He's dressed up
like a tomato. You are dressed up like a tomato. I'm an elf bitch. You look at
the glow. Yeah, I bet he's from red pronoun, Vidence, Rhode Island
so that's literally what it is there bang him main. Oh yeah, that's more scary
Stephen King territory. Oh well man's chest, New Hampshire, just her her
New Hampshire, a man with a chest, who's a herd, New Hampshire, damn that woke
Konya, New Hampshire, Well Konya, let's see Wilmington, Drillington Kilmington.
That's what it really is
Earlford, New Hampshire, that's good like Guilford, yeah,
Milford Mills. I like that would be the
what's up yeah, what's up? I'm a hot over there or instead of a man,
instead of acting, it could be like action
like an action movie, but that would be anti woke. Well, you got to put I'm
just thinking of some action. Okay, so now you got to put some woke cities
and some un woke cities action. Glax, burrow, I want you to know this today.
Cameron P town, you are now that you are my gym brother. Yeah, my brother in
arms, chest, legs and feet back or back. We don't do a feet day. Why don't we do
it? Why we do kind of there's that motorcycle one where you do this, but I
guess it's a cab phrase, but you use your feet for toes. Use your feet to
walk to the toes. You have to be a dancer if you want to work out your
toes, but because point because we know all about ballet because I did it my
my whole life, because I'm woke. That's I do that. Instead of having a job, you do
ballet yeah, that's how I got blue ass hair. You eight hours a day.
Clock in nine to five ballet and I guess what I teach children ballet and
drag. Oh my God, all that is drag. If you ask me what the crap are you doing
guys like you think ballet is a drag, but I see it for what it is an art form.
My wife asked me to go to a ballet recently. She's a a belly like to watch
to watch one watch one yeah and I said it's better to watch a video of it
where they have perfected it. You have to go see a random time. It's like if
why do they I don't ask her to come to the Korean Gaming Cafe. This is why
okay, here's the thing. This is I guess outside of the debate, but this is why
I don't like plays man. Okay, it's like going you go. Would you like to go see a
movie, but they're just trying it? They're trying to do it. You want to see
all the actors try to do the movie, a one take movie. Would you rather see the
movie that they worked for two years on yeah right. That has effects that they
finish. They did the best try. That's exactly on the screen man. They can be
like a giant dinosaur in it. You can't have a giant dinosaur in a play unless
you do that. I would actually I would actually watch that. Do you want to see
a do you want to go see a movie that could be completely different every
single time, every time you want to see a movie where somebody might just
forget their lines? Yeah, exactly that they just they tried it. It's an do you
want to see an attempt at a movie? I don't like plays man. No, it's not for
really know. I don't like plays, but I also don't like bellies because of my,
but I think theater fosters important community in high school.
It shows boobs to as a guy's I've heard
says who did my friend live it. He was in a friend's name is Levitt. Well, his
real name is Jesse, but his middle name was Levitt. He went by Levitt. He told
me that he saw boobs when he was working when he was in theater. When we were
twelve years old, he saw boobs. I did never see boobs. I didn't see boobs
theater. Well, he wants to go. He said he was seeing him like every day. I
wasn't in theater. Was he doing like was he in a burlesque show?
He's in a burlap. He was in a child burlesque show, which is something you
probably want. You sicko bang bang. I don't want it because I already have it.
I have all I need.
I'm woke man. Oh God, so tell me what your plans for Christmas would be okay.
we'll do it. I guess we want to introduce our position. Let's introduce our
you mean X. We'll start we'll start. Let's start with Caleb. I guess we'll
show Caleb's me position on the debate.
We'll start at that end of the table.
So
all right, read out your your your list card. I am a Christmas traditionalist.
Obviously, I think that Christmas season starts on December one and no earlier.
I'm sick. I am sick of the day after Thanksgiving waking up and there's
garland everywhere, garlic, garlic, no that's Halloween garland everywhere,
disgusting green parts of Christmas trees. Leave that out of my shit man
remember the reason for the season
hmm. Look at that presence now on no long wrong wrong wrong wrong Christ
commercialism. It's about Christ birthday. It is not about commercialism.
That's the complete opposite. Actually, okay, it is not about unless you're
buying black right. I company anti capital, my discount code. No, none of
that. And then Mrs Claus is white.
I'm sick and tired of all these different races of Mrs Claus.
It's just not... I mean, listen, I'm fine with people being from all sorts of
worst countries than the one that we're in, but I'm not fine with rewriting
history. And it says in ancient texts going back to Mesopotamia, in the
hanging gardens of Babylon, there was tablets that read, "Mrs Claus, white as
the snow on which she walks right. It's just the truth. You know she was
Egyptian right so it's African. What is this clause was not fucking Egyptian?
I didn't know that bullshit. It's true. That's but that is we had out history,
but that is not true or bulls. It's not true. Don't listen to don't be swayed
Mr. Middle. I don't know who to believe in. Well, that's what I mean. Let's see
let's see Mr. Middle position. All right, let's see what I believe,
which is
I am a Christmas fan. I'm a supporter of Santa Claus, but also commercialism.
I like the presents and the stockings and I don't care who brings the gifts
as long as they
are
fun.
I just like Christmas. I just like Christmas. I couldn't see that TV is
too far away. You simply just are a fan of everything Christmas. Oh, yeah.
I don't care what happens with I just like the music in the pageantry. Do
you like keep the politics out of it on either side? You know what if you
want to put politics into Christmas and
if you want to put if you want to change anything that Santa has willed into
existence. F you I'll say that much. Well that's
both of us. So we're going to push you. We're going to push you so into the middle that you'll become
nothing. You'll be you'll disappear. We're going to compress you. Yeah. Well if that
that's it and so be it and here's my position for the debate. I am of course
woke and I am a I'm a woke iconoclast, so I want to destroy the icons of
Christmas. I believe Jesus Christ belongs in jail. Well, not in Christmas,
you shut your fucking mouth. He's only a baby. Oh man, he literally manipulated a
group of twelve people to do his bidding. He was a cult leader to hang out with
I'm what are you manipulating me and can't mean Patrick. I think that on
Cameron, why am I saying your camera know so many times a sorry continue. I
believe on Christmas Eve, we should be leaving out gluten free cookies and
oat milk. Shut your trap, you bastard, and if my kid asks for Harry Potter
books for Christmas, I'm hitting them. Did you just say them? I said that I'm
going to shoot you to death with my fucking gun and then punch the hole.
Okay, we have one more position to look at to that. I don't know if there's we
I have one more member of the debate. If someone wants to read this, it says
Jubio, he's a white Mexican, which I've been dreaming of. It says I'm a lot
now. He died. I'm a me Papa. I'm a me Mama. I'm a Papa Noel. So he likes
Christmas. He likes his mom. He loves Christmas. He loves loves Christmas,
loves his dad, loves his mom, loves Santa Claus, Father Christmas, Santa
Claus. Yeah, that's cute. That is nice. That's actually very sweet. I'm curious
to see where he ends up by the end of the debate. I'm guessing that he will have a
strong stance on my end, probably no, we'll see bro. He's from Mexico. I'm
going to say walk is fucked up there. No, they're not. It's literally an entire
country full of Latinx people, Latinx, but they also have they have the cartel,
which I think is kind of cool. They should have the cartoons instead. Well,
that's a rude point. Rudolph, which is here without a Santa Claus, a crazy
nights, Santa's beginning. Wait, no, not a crazy nights. I hate that movie.
Well, yeah.
Oh my God. So what's our first topic here? I guess I'll put forth that I
think that
Christmas is a time to basically promote anti racism.
And how do you suppose we do that? Well, through gifts, I hope. Yeah, through
gifts, I'll be giving my white uncles,
I'll be giving them gifts on like what I am. I can't deal with this. This God
did look at the world and and and activity books work books with anti
racist word searches and because they've done studies, they do studies and and
this is what besides therapy. This is one of the best ways to learn and where
intelligence is word searches and match the difference or find match box cars
is what I'd rather. What are your sources on these studies and was it in
Berkeley. This was a study that was done by me with my feelings.
You're okay and jokes, no logic yeah that doesn't involve logic at all.
That's just as I suspected. I don't know if you know this you're committing what
we call a fallacy. I'm the lying, you're committing what we call a felony,
which felony wielding that gun without a permit. I have tons of permits yeah,
yeah right here and right here. My two
permits are my hand and my gun doesn't food called chicken participation sound
so good.
That does sound really good at a restaurant. Did you say earlier chicken
salutation chicken salutations? I would order that was another one to I can't
remember, but also we talked about this very briefly because I did want to say,
but no chicken on Christmas meat, any Christmas meat out day. Oh well, that's
really good. That's actually that's great news for you. I think a Christmas. We
should get take our meat out. That's great because chicken isn't meat man.
No meat man. We should take our meat out. We're not eating steak. We're not
eating chicken. We're not even eating eggs, which I think is meat because it
comes with different colors. You're making me want to throw up chicken is
not meat. Eggs are not meat chicken is not meat. It is a chicken is a person
you're making me want to throw up. Shut the fuck up to right now that it walks
it's a person. A chicken has two genders that it has style. A human has two hundred
and fifty two genders in every strand of DNA. You walk fucking piece of dog crap.
I will blow your head off all over the Christmas man. It could get a different
gender every year. Oh, yeah, for Christmas. That's a terrible gift. And that's a great
gift. It changes your outlook on that's a terrible gift. There's no commercialism in that.
I'd like to there's no there's no physical object that you spend money on
that
it gives back to the world wrapping paper. You're putting
like rocking rolling paper. I bet you instead of having I bet you don't even
know how to start a damn fire and I bet you pull up the crunchy roll fire
simulator and you put that on the TV at Christmas. You fucking bastard. I don't
and I bet you that's so I do not pull. I do not actually use crunchy roll at all.
now that's cultural appropriation. I have my Japanese friend. He pulls up crunchy
roll at his house in Japan. I have him call me in the middle of the night when
he's awake and he tells me what's happening in the animes. Oh, so I only
watch on emas where the characters have different colored hair. I think I'm
completely going to throw up and I think I need to go. You're going to throw up
yeah. I don't feel good right now from my I'm worried that I caught Noah's
sickness right now. He doesn't throw up. That's not a throwing up sickness. I'm
that I caught whatever Noah has. Well you can throw up if you need to. I think I
might have to go. I think I just left in the middle of the fucking episode to go puke. We were
having a really heated debate I guess. We were really getting into it. Maybe we need
to slow it down. Let's get it slow and sensual like sex between two men.
I think sex between a man and woman should be over quick. I think I actually
I actually agree with that to even though I'm I'm conservatively. It should be
right way fast and jerky yeah because you don't good.
So we're agreeing on something here. Yeah, is that time is money time is
money and this what I'm supposed to pay this bitch ten dollars of time.
There's a finite amount of sex to be had in the world. Anyone given moment
that is true and it's better for a black guy to have it with a white guy.
you're kidding
and I and I suppose you think that white guys can get black guys pregnant and
vice. Okay, let's get let's get right into it. Let's dive into the issue of
black guys versus
in the bedroom who who would get pregnant and who would be the
inseminator. I am
wish I could get pregnant. I bet you fucking do. I bet you probably walk
around with one of those period cramps out of all of our friends. Who do you
think is the man most likely to get pregnant through a freak incident, Joe
joke could definitely be already has and he's hidden the baby. He could
definitely
he's had an abortion.
I think he could definitely get pregnant. I think men should have
abortions. I think men should go have monthly abortion, so they know what it's
like for women to get abortions and what they take out their their nutsack. I
think they should get a board. I think if a man eats too much, he should go
I was taken out of his stomach. You're kidding me and it's I think I should pay
for as a I think that and I also support those M pick. I do not support as epic.
If you are going to get skinny, you have to go work for that. Yeah, you have to
go to the gym every single day and you have to run for four minutes and then
you have to get so winded that you have to leave and think you're having a part
of part attack, a heart attack, a stroke, yeah, a part attack, a part of your
body, your body, your body is attacking. It is or it's being attacked.
I think that we should. I don't think that anybody should have a gym membership
and instead I think they should have a public pool membership.
Oh, and I think that everyone should wear their shirts in the pool
to hide their shameful bodies. You think that's okay in case to normalize it in
case there are people who are ashamed, but I don't think anybody should be
ashamed of their body, even if they're like two hundred pounds, two hundred
pounds, even if they're a fat guy is like two hundred pounds, two hundred
six. That's disgustingly fat. I don't even want to imagine this person.
Okay,
you won't be the shit. I think that Mel mentioned where the shirts in the pool.
So if a woman who's 120 pounds wants to wear a shirt in their pool to hide her
body, she can't her big fat body. Yeah, yeah, no, I just disagree with you. I
think that women should be wearing bikinis and men should be wearing suits
at the pool other way around.
You think that women should wear pants? I think that man, how are they gonna
give access to their bush easily, which is shaved
or should be. Are you serious? I don't think anybody should shave
any part,
but you think that photos of Marilyn Monroe, where her dress is being blown
up by a guy with a straw or whatever you think that there should be hairy
black pubes crawling like spider legs out of the side of a like. I don't like
photos of Marilyn Monroe. I like photos of Marilyn Manson.
you he's my sex icon. You think that's a he yeah what the hell is wrong with I
bet you look I bet you jack off the photos of Lena Dunham eating food.
You fucking woke piece of dog crap. We're getting a little away from
Christmas. I think it's mostly just
talking about fat
all right back to Chris. I think the girls should be by Lena Dunham should
have been called boys and girls, so it's all inclusive. So you agree that boys
your girls includes everybody yeah. If you keep if you have an ampersand in
there, a weird squiggly symbol, you bastard okay, here's what I want to
know yeah walk me through what you think
the Christmas story is the original don't be going. Oh, I shot my eye out
with a red writer BB gun. I'm right, which is amazing an amazing movie. I'm
talking about okay, the one that happened two thousand years ago. Okay,
let me let me through that what you think happened in that manger.
So
basically a straight
middle eastern male was born through in vitro fertilization, which should be the
norm. No, as well as surrogacy. I hate surrogacy or maybe if I'm woke, I'm
supposed to not like surrogacy.
It's kind of one of those things where to me it seems evil in real life
surrogacy. Yeah, I think I agree. I think that I think it gives me a kind of
existential horrification, not a baby, but I do support horror for the
the horrification of America anyway. A young baby is born okay. First of all,
it's that well that's probably the last part of the story scientific freak
accident. No, that's where it all begins. So you don't think it was you think
that they had a thousand two thousand and twenty three years later.
Basically, capitalism has taken this mystical occultic story. That's a
perverse
and it's they've perverted it. You think and I think that commercialism has taken
over, which is good, but I or well, I like when so it's good if people if you
spend money on pink presents,
where the hell even by pay you let me guess you do your Christmas shopping at
target yeah and the croc store and you do it a month. I do I do it. I do it
three months in advance and I do it and target in the electronics aisle. Oh God,
phone. I get my I get my I get my nephew. I get him cooking mama. Shut the fuck
for the don't you dare switch that man to switch the best console ever. At least
no, I don't tell me you got the Oled version. No, I don't have the Oled
version because we don't have a TV. We read books instead. So when my nephew
places switch, he uses the built in stand that comes on the back of the
switch. Do you know the one that no one's ever used? Yes, he uses that he
puts it on the on the kitchen counter because we have no chairs in our house.
it goes and he sits on the floor of the other into the kitchen and he holds the
joy cons. Why don't you have chair? Oh,
I believe in standing desks. You're kidding me. I had a beat your fucking
fruity ass for that and he has a he has the pink model of the switch dude. No,
here's what Christmas is about okay, okay, Robert Earl keen, okay, Christmas
sounds like a presidential assassin to me. Happy Chris, Merry Christmas from
family. That's a great song Motley crew. I want t shirts from them every single
Christmas. I want a different Motley crew t shirt. Okay, I want studs on my
belt. I want to get every single Christmas. I want the same three things
as a conservative father. Yeah, I want
golf balls. I want a twelve pack of golf balls. I want a brown wallet. Yeah,
and I want some kind of gift card right anything more than that anything less.
it's going to be a no for me. I'm going to cancel Christmas next year. Let me
let me walk you through what I'm getting for me and maybe this is my Ridge
wallet. I would like a special edition Blu Ray of Black Panther to Wakanda
forever. The one where they fight underwater Mexico.
Don't tell me you have Blu Ray in your house. Okay, first of all,
I have a Blu Ray optical drive that I plug into my Mac book.
Whatever happened and we don't we watch it and the screen is smudged to shit
because I think it's a touch screen and when I go on Etsy, I try and
grab all the heart shaped necklaces out of it. I like heart shaped necklaces,
then I wear jewelry.
I think all jury and I like Etsy for buying jewelry for myself. I think all
jewelry should be edible and what else do I get, but I get and then I get a
master class. No yeah, I get a
master class. I get I get I always ask every year, ask for the errands work in
master class. I ask for a cooking master class and how to make macaroni and
cheese
and I okay, so you eat cheese that's good. Well, don't tell me it's die.
Cashew, oh God, cashew cheese, you fucker and I ask for a master class on
how to correctly address the homeless population.
I got a good thing to do you fucking turn them into a hamburger, no
address, unlike whether you're supposed to say, sir or ma'am, oh not the
problem of homeless people who are camping. You mean the blessing it's
it's no blessing man, the blessing of diversity and income brackets,
thousand,
thousand, listen people every day are murdered by fentanyl crazed hobos
walking around to know who think that I think that you should get fentanyl. If
you have a headache
and there was something else I was going to ask for for Christmas that I can't
I'm having trouble remembering
probably. Oh, I remember what it was, and this is the most important one. I
I want this is my favorite gift. I want this every year, a hand drawn gift
certificate for one free hug.
That is a bullshit nonsense Lala gift from a fucking dumb ass kid, and I want
one that says one free item from the grocery store. Well, that's just a
normal gift card, and I don't think I think you'd be hard pressed to find a
normal gift card that says one free item from the crush. Well, how much is the
most expensive, not a bad idea for a good well. Some grocery store, self
grills and like well yeah, whatever the most expensive thing you need to buy the
gift certificate. That's such a good idea for a well yeah. I guess it kind of or
it's there we go again capitalism ruining Christmas. We can't have a free
item because everyone's going to abuse it and get the George Foreman grill. I'm
fine with capital. I like George Foreman because he he did what God said to do. He
went forth and multiplied. He has eleven children. I like big families as well,
and I think so, like molest each other yeah. What
I even woke
it's woke to
well, no, it's not guess. It's not well. It's not woke at all. You're just saying
yes to things yes, and I believe in improv you fucker piece of shit. Let me
guess you're happy that second city and you see beer coming back to New York
city, not you see be why not because I'm against sex slavery.
Well, I guess I'm pro you see be then
I guess I'm completely pro I'm super woke. I'm against sex slavery. I don't
believe in sexual assault. Here's what I don't believe it should be done to
okay. All right, that was tricky for a second there. I here's what I would get
you for Christmas. Okay,
let me get you want a
well, a helmet probably because you probably ride your bike with a helmet.
Oh, a bike, you mean a stationary bike.
That's how I get it right. You don't tell me you put on a helmet and ride the
peloton
and
pellets on and I play and I go on my phone and I open up Google Maps and I
and I do little craps. I use ways I actually use ways also well, then I use
ways is across the aisle. I use Yahoo. I still I still print out the map quest
directions every single day to get to work. Never memorized it. I go on
street view and I and I right I go on a new type of street with it goes inside
of buildings and I ride the peloton with my helmet on and I ride around the
library. I think that you and me right now, we would do an amazing round of
Geo guesser together yeah, you'd be guessing everything in San Francisco. I
don't
Mexico. This has to be Compton. I think yeah.
I think I saw somebody of his Hispanic Latin next descent. I think this is
probably shy rack. They call it.
What do you think about the North Pole?
I think it exists yeah, because I think it's a settler colonial state.
What could you think the elves aren't happy? They get to make toys all day.
The elves are the colonizers men who was there before in you at people, I
maybe
I guess I didn't really think it through the I just think that I was a
call those elves for being up there where they work hard for you every day
let's build your your bad dragon triple XL size dildos that you're fitting in
your mouth all day. Sure, sure, you realize that they're alienated from
their labor right.
Do they get do elves get paid? I don't care, but do they get paid? I guess
they're bored room and board. Is that enough to be making billions of toys
every year? Our elves
are they native to the North Pole or are they from some kind of dimension of
light. I think it probably is wonka status where they were in the jungle.
They were from the jungle and Santa went in and he was like he was slashing all
the lines of the machete and then he slashed one big group of vines and he
looked out and there was just a bunch of a bunch of a looked up at him and ran
away in a river basin. Yeah, they let him to like it was like and it's like a
waterfall and they have like kind of like a city built vertically into the
side. Yeah, I think it was probably that kind of thing. He met with the chieftain
of the elf tribe and the elf said we will come for you. We will come to your
north pole, your age, your great pole. Thank you, you saved us,
you saved us from being in this. You saved us from yeah. I don't know what
well we have an elf natural predator in the jungle. So let's just me jaguars
yeah
jaguars, panthers, anacondas eating elves all day in the Amazon. We need a
place where nothing can live.
that's what they said. You probably want you and let me guess
you probably think that Elon Musk is some kind of dumb a beat bastard.
Yeah, are you kidding? The only reason the greatest genius, the only reason
he's famous is because he's handsome.
Okay, you think he's handsome? Yeah, we don't live in a meritocracy at all. I
think he's an ugly piece of crap. He was ugly. He'd never be on he'd never be
buying twitter doing all this stuff, which by the way, my social media
network of choices, Pinterest,
what so you can look at pictures of flowers and all sorts of dumb gay yeah
here my here. I'll list off my Pinterest boards. I go ahead. You bet flowers
okay
birth stones.
Okay, I don't even know what mine is
live birth footage
miracle the because I think it's a miracle. Okay, we can so the miracle it
was a miracle when Jesus was born immaculate conception. It was a maculate
understand anti Christian
rhetoric.
They have a rhetoric, a rhetoric section where people post rhetoric. You can
find basically anything on Pinterest. Can you find pornography? There's some
pornography, but you know what pornography is to me, probably you
erotic literature.
So you're saying that every piece of media you call you think it's called
text yeah, and this is an erotic literature. So you think that let's say
Lana Rodes getting double. I prefer Lana Del Rey you
back to fat. She's big and fat. Now
I think she looks good. Let me guess you your favorite porn stars are probably
Buck Angel and
what's the other guy?
Oh yeah, Steve, I wish I knew some names of male porn stars right now to drop
that big funny fuck. There's a list of twenty of
God, I watch straight porn, but I look it up by the man's name. He's like how he
does it
yeah
okay, expect that Christmas
yeah bitch yeah. What's what's Christmas dinner Christmas dinner? Let me guess.
Well, I don't know additional a roast beast. Yeah, we've had rose. I mean I
don't know my wife and my daughters and their friends all make it. Okay, we have
every woman in the town come over all the guys. I have a forty person
love seat that we sit on and
traditional love seat and we sit there and we watch football game after football
game after. Well, let me tell you what I'm having for Christmas dinner as a
woke iconic. Let me can I guess take a you actually nailed mine a tofurkey roast.
Did I get that we don't we don't do roasts? First of all, we only have an
the fryer. We have no oven, a tofurkey roast. You probably have chow mein. No,
I got I have a roast. I have a Christmas. Can I tell you right now what I eat for
Christmas dinner? Wait, okay, the middle guy's back. Sorry, continue you a
Grinch, motherfucker
boy
breakfast for dinner,
scrambled eggs. That's a good thing to come back. Nickel toast. That's a good
come back and I do that yeah. Pumpernickel breakfast is a breakfast is
purely a breakfast. Breakfast belongs at night. I don't even do breakfast and I
I do dinner for breakfast. I do one meal a day man. I do. I believe that people
should eat ten to fifteen meals a day. No, you think they should do tiny meals
throughout the day. No, no, I even eat don't. That's a pizza. No one should eat
at all. That's your opinion. That's your take is no one should. No one should eat
at all, and I don't know what this debate has been about yeah, because
you've been gone. I had a sickness attack. Did you ralph throw? I didn't
throw up. Did you, but I had to I had to come down. You had to
I did let my I did let my I think maybe eating a bunch of enchiladas before we
recorded was not a good idea. I'm fine. I feel great. I feel better than I felt
in
two hours yeah
my body's full of carbs. My brain is firing at a rate. I my body's full of
cars, because I think that people should be transformers and should transform
their gender and their book also become machines, bro and I'm a transhumanist as
as a transgenderist. I don't even know what the God damn hell are you on about
with men shouldn't become women shouldn't even know what a car is. First
of all, okay, men shouldn't drive or shouldn't be cars. They should drive
cars. No, no, no, no, we need to get rid of roads. No, don't tell me you like
public transportation. You like bastard public transportation and I like
swimming. Bring back the public pool. Let's talk about the public pool again.
You think we should? I think it should be summer weather in Christmas time.
where has this debate gone? Wokeness versus Caleb and this is just this is
it's nothing to do with Christmas anymore. We're trying. You know what
trying? You know what you could you moderate it, man. You have lost the
plot completely. Okay, then you moderate. You have you two have completely lost
the plot. He thinks he should swim to work talking about the pool. You don't
get a pool for Christmas. You don't even get actually you don't get a man.
Someone's never had Christmas in L. A. The great city on earth. Oh my God,
the greatest city on Earth. You're making me go on to his side. Sorry, second
greatest Portland. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Even
the greatest Portland, Maine. Shut up right now. Shut the hell up. Portland,
Oregon, Portland, Maine, Los Angeles. You shut the F up. The greatest city in
the world. You, San Antonio, Texas.
The greatest city. What is that? Oh, now you're mocking me, 'cause that's what
I look like. My tongue's out all the time.
Fucking idiot. I'm about... That just made me sick again. Moderate, man. That
he just made me bring us to Christmas, some Christmas questions. Okay, well
what okay, if I have to give the topics, maybe that's what we should have been
doing from the beginning.
What do you think about the role of
the of movies? I hate rolls and I like rolls Royce, but keep going. What do you
think of the role of Christmas movies in society? Are they promoting?
are they promoting woke enough or have they become too woke or are they not
being woke enough? Of course, they are. They are. They not only is die hard a
Christmas movie, shut up,
but so is John Wick four. No, how so you're making me hate violence in it.
You're making me hate and despise.
And I bet you like these sacrilegious movies, such as violent night with David
Harbor. Is that camera all blurried up? Which one? The one that oh, it's gone.
Caleb's just went away. No mine. Well, I accidentally knocked into Caleb's camera
when I was coming back. Well, now I look sharp as a tack. Well, let me guess what
your favorite Christmas movie is. Go ahead,
probably
Rudolph.
You got it
yeah, you nailed it. Yeah, I like Rudolph. I think every reindeer should have
gotten a red nose to be equal. No, no, no, no, no, no. There's something called
hierarchy of I don't believe in individual. Peterson talks about this
the hierarchy of needs hierarchy. No, not hierarchy of needs hierarchy. I
think the hierarchy of needs is starts off a diverse community. Now,
second of all starts off Christmas gift. Second of all, second of all,
missile cognitive behavioral therapy at the top. It's a love third of all
being a girl. No. And then after that, it's shelter food and all the rest
to the stuff. No, you fucking it's Christmas gifts, mistletoe, Santa's love.
Let's talk mistletoe. What do you think about mistletoe? I think upper thumbs up
thumb does down. I think thumb up. Yeah, thumb up or fucking pussy. If she
catches me under that mistletoe. Oh my God, we're getting down and dirty. Okay,
fuck under the mistletoe. Yeah, you don't have sex under the mistletoe. You give
a kiss. No, I'm actually, if I this is something that we my wife under the
mistletoe. I thought you were the traditionalist. Yeah, and that's
traditional that's that's why there's nothing more traditional and sex with
your wife. Yeah, but I there's nothing traditional about sex with your wife. I
believe sex should be in front of everybody. Jesus, my God, I think you
get under the mistletoe with a somebody you don't know, a stranger at a holiday
office party. You think that's you think that's what should hook up at EDM
festivals. I like sluts. I like hipsters and I like
pirates.
I don't know what pirates fit into that. I like pirates are cool. I like pirates
because they
seize control of ships. I just like presents. I don't like any of this
stuff. I like presents and I like Christmas. We know you're the Christmas
fan. Okay, give us Santa could be Chinese. No, he couldn't. He could know
he couldn't. We actually don't we actually don't know evidence pointing.
We actually don't again. There is right and if even if we had gotten some DNA
from Santa like his beard hair when tested it, the results we would still
not be able to know whether he was Chinese or not, because that is not
biologically in your DNA. It's a mindset
what
that you're so anybody that Chinese is a mindset. You can think all races, just a
mind race is a mind mind told mental construct. I think wokeness is a mind
virus that you seem to be verily infected. Okay, that's fine. I like
viruses. I like Cove in one thousand and nineteen. I hope it stays around forever
because I like wearing masks because I can put my favorite Steven Universe
characters on them.
it's a new fashion accessory for me. It's basically jewelry. I have a
bedazzled coven mask as much as I hate that I've worn since twenty seven. I
have one that says my wife makes me wear this shit as much as I hate that. I
do think that if somebody were to get you that as a gift, you would enjoy it a
lot, so I'm conflicted now right. Give us another topic, then
gifts
have gifts become woke in the past year?
Yeah, and that's good. Since the COVID-19 pandemic. Oh, we already talked about
gifts a little bit, but I would say that gifts, since COVID-19, what do you get
now? A PCR test for Christmas now? Yes. Because of it's people are trying to...
Well, I get that every day of the year. You get a PCR test every day? Yeah.
I've never had one. I think that that shit stands for
prison. Photograph, catch, release. Exactly. Exactly. Thank you very much. My
entire camera roll on my phone. There's one picture of me and my gender
neutral partner and every other picture is a picture of my of a negative
covid test that I took that day that I sent to my boss at work.
You scroll through it. It's for and time. I read it yeah. I read it still
clean the paper I'm holding in front of my face,
still wearing lipstick in the pick. Oh, what the hell and I wait was it a gift
what the lipstick? No, I bought it myself using my unemployment check.
You're on fucking unemployment, even though you're employed. That's a gift
from the government. That's a gift from the government. I accept that. That's a
good thing. If there was a if there was a Christmas election to decide on who
was Santa, how many times would you vote? I would vote as many times as I could.
I don't even vote once. Okay, that's how traditional I am. I guess actually,
maybe I wouldn't vote either, but I would I would give my no. You know,
here's what I would do. I would give my
my ID card to someone like Julio
Mexican person who's white enough to pass for me in the picture, and I'd let
him vote for me. You know what I would do if there was a Christmas election?
What I would
vote for myself, because I'm running for Christmas comptroller really. What is
it? I think I don't believe that we should have comptrollers anymore. I think
they're fascist. Oh my God, you don't think that I think boards of select men
are inherently
right wing. You are a fuck ass, so you want a if you think that I can't be
Christmas, and I think our government should be a paramilitary woke death
squad who kills white chuds
on Christmas on Christmas, Merry Christmas, white every year. We should
have a chud purge now, and that would be the greatest gift I could ever get
would be if all these fat fucks
that's not that's not body. We're alive and body posi. They have blue lives
matter shirts on okay, buddy, they got blue lives matter shirts on their
walking around. I'm like is that flag waving in the wind? You okay, you're
getting sidetracked right now from what the the original thing was supposed to
be about, but you were talking about gifts actually, but let's transition
making gifts into stocking stuffers okay stocking. I think that stockings should
be normal socks for people that are fat. You probably
like you bring it up fat people all the time. I'm woke he's woke. He's obsessed
with the number one thing that woke people think about. You probably think
that stockings are something that that you wear whenever your boyfriend gets
it's what I wear when I get fucked. Oh
yeah sure I in my house. We hang we hang those those same stockings that I wore
up by the chimney. Yeah, we also hang up my mesh basketball shorts that I wear
when I
you are mesh basketball. Yeah, they slide down easier on the stockings.
Well, that makes some sense and my and my and my fish and my vision at tuxedo
shirt. Do you hang all that up on the fire so that the smell emanates around
the house to dry them off? They're soaking wet. If you were at my house, I
smell like chicken.
If you were at my house, I'd hang the stockings up, but I'd also hang you up
by your nipple piercing right on the man that would get me off. I meant to
come and I stuff your mouth with
is
he probably likes that. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
let me guess you don't even make jizz anymore. Yeah, I'd probably just give
you a candy cane or gingerbread man. I have I got a special. I got a special
type of a sect to me where they snipped my my tubes and they connected them into
my esophagus. So I constantly am tasting my own j
wait. Do you even have to climb out inside my entire body so constantly
there's this and they do the thing where like a so they're siphoning gasoline
where they go and they sucked it a little bit and they plugged it into my
into my throat. So if I constantly whatever my balls generate a new sperm,
immediately get sucked up and you get my and you feel it back your throat and I
go and I lick my lips like this. A new sperm, you generate them one at a time.
Do you have what you're gonna need you generate? Yeah, what are you talking
about? I thought it was like you have a million sperms. Yeah, but you still make
a you. Do you think you start with all your sperms? Yes, no man. That's women.
You're a girl.
No, girls. Stop trying to trick him like that. True girls start with all their
eggs. No, I don't know how big is an egg. It's about the size of a grain of sand.
I think there's no way they start with all of them, but the egg is huge
compared to the sperm.
How many and I think that should be the relationship of size between women and
men. You think women should be big women should be big and strong and men should
be a size of a pin. No, no, no, no, look
every single time that we bring up something
you say some crazy as shit and it has nothing to do with Christmas.
least it's your job yeah. That's what I'm doing right now. I'm doing I got
man you're not you're you're you're you're you're complaining. You're not
even bringing a question. You say I don't want to talk about sperms and eggs.
That's all I want to talk about at any given moment. What you should be talking
about day in day out. How big is an egg compared to a spur? How many eggs does a
woman have? How many sperms do I make at a time? How many sperms can I fit my
mouth? What's a new surgery I can do it myself to access more sperms? You should
be talking about shirts and or bikes with pegs instead of we talked about
guns and eggs. You're talking about bikes already? How much did I miss?
When was that? About 20 minutes? He said he wears a helmet to ride a
Peloton.
He missed that completely. You would have loved that. I would have loved
that. I just had a sick attack out of nowhere. Okay, mall Santa. Mall Santa.
Okay, mall Santa. Winter Wonderland. It should be, I think that every single
store should have a mall Santa. Yes. I think every single store should have a
you to be walking into you probably like game stop and not even the xbox parts of
game stop. I don't like malls. Why first of all, because they're like a is
basically a modern day coliseum, a roman coliseum. What we watch amazing people
spend the fruits of their labor. Okay, you realize you're referring to a blood
sport right now. What's a blood sport? It's a sport where blood is spilled. I
do not like hockey, the roman football, which I also do not support. You don't
support football? No, because I think the ball is not circular. You are if you
don't support like a long shape of the ball. No, I want everything to be the
same. I want every ball and every sport to be the same. If you don't support
if you don't support football, then you are supporting taking away a specific
gift from a specific child. That's true, that's true, but
again, I think that football and baseball and sports like golf are
inherently violent, and so we shouldn't be giving these golf. I wish off is
finally literally it's a club. It's fine. When I play, I aim for the birds,
bro yeah, you join a call and trap. So what do you think we call it a trap?
It's because it sucks your life away. You probably like the trap.
I actually live in the trap.
Well, yeah, which trap
I don't know. I've never been outside
you haven't even seen the sign a second house in the hood. Wow, oh my God, you
like living in the hood. I bet you like I bet you are opening a muffin store
there and do type of muffin store that's going to be out of business. I know
what you're talking well. No, I don't know what you're talking about. You
muffin store is that is this a reference to something or just like an
example of an example of a woke type of business. Okay, so I did get what
you're saying. Your second with the second part of what you said. I thought
you might there might be some movie about a muffin store that opens in the
would know, but that'd be no, but
put that past that being a movie that both of you guys have seen and I've
never
that's fair
but mall Santa.
He I think that anybody should be allowed to dress up as Santa. I'm with
him on that. I think that I think that Santa is the perfect representation of
Christmas. You probably think that the kids shouldn't sit on the Santa's lap. I
think that they should sit on like well. I'm not going to say what I was going to
say
okay, that's good. Yeah, we can yeah all right next time anyway. Okay, next
topic is
the fruit cake wait. No, I'm one I'm teeing you on no that can't that's not
can a good face fruit cake. I can't in good face. I working dessert ever. It
has fruit in it, which is my favorite food. We have cheesecake or actually I
should say my favorite food is fruit flavor.
I like Laffy Taffy. I Laffy Taffy and salad and soylent salad and soylent. I
have soylent salad instead of salad dressing
I dress up like a salad yeah.
Why was the ketchup red? Why saw the salad dressing?
Okay, that I like I like that. That's a good joke. I'm going to remember that
forever.
I've never heard I was maybe the tomato supposed to be the one that why did the
tomato. I don't think ketchup would be in this. Why did the way turn red or why
was this tomato red? Why was the
ketchup?
That's not it.
That's not the catch. I catch up. That's the calming sound. I bet I bet out of
the bottom. I bet for I like when ketchup makes the fart noise when it
comes out of the bottle. You nasty, I respect to the body and all its
functions. You nasty as hell. I don't think farts are funny. I think they
should be revered. What let me guess, I think that the only time of fart should
be heard as if it's in a gag gift. I think it should be heard, smelled and
seen. You want green flow, gas and tasted.
I had a dream last night that somebody had a green fart cloud.
Who was it was you? It's probably me. You prophesized my sickness. Did I oh
yeah, because you had a green stinky fart.
that's not like prop prophecy. I think that's a prophet doesn't make you. You
probably don't even believe in prophecy. You probably don't know. I bet you think
that you know a prophecy. I believe and I bet you don't even believe in profits.
See Christmas is about commercialism boy. I don't I like buying stuff from small
businesses from local artisans and from farmers. Wait a minute, not a market. I
actually like them. You like gifts, so here's the examples of gifts that I
bought this year for my family. Okay, now I'm now I need to okay gifts you
to list all of your gifts that you bought. Okay, so for we'll go we're
gonna go gift for gift. We're gonna go back and forth or say a family member
and we'll say what we got on wild turkey one oh one seven fifty mil. I got
my aunt a new dress because I think she'd look really, really, really pretty
and and it's low cut. Shut up uncle
video of me playing the no Russian mission on DVD, got my uncle perfume,
not cologne, but perfume, nephew, nephew. I got him some stilt so that he could be
the same height as all of his family members. I got him a barbie video game
shut up nice nice. I got her a football or no. I got her a barbie ball.
it's a part. It's a pink ball, a pink football, got your knees, a barbie ball.
I got my knees a barbell to start working out and become buff and
brother. I got my brother some flowers for his grave. He passed away.
He passed away. He passed away. He didn't have a seat belt on. I got my
brother a witchcraft one on one candle kit. Okay, come wicked
no
you run your other brother, my other brother, older brother, my older brother.
I got him a letter from Thomas Jefferson authenticated. I got my older
brother estrogen shots. What Thomas estrogen?
I think that's a letter from
well, that's all the older sister doesn't have to. Why are you doing
siblings. There's so many possible members of the family, cousin, second
cousin, great dad and your best cousin. Here's what I got my dad. I got my dad.
I wrote him a note that says you are no longer the man of the family. I don't
because I don't believe in patriarchy and I think you have no claim over this
family leave now every single fucking holiday. Me and all my brothers and
cousins and dads. We I mean dad only have one. We have wrestle on the front
lawn to see who's going to be the man of the family. I do that with all the
women members of my family to see who's going to be the woman or the man to see
who I'm going to wrestle.
You just wrestle women, you're sounding a lot less like a woky and a lot more
like a pervert who yeah
what's the difference. Thank you, thank you, thank you. At least you're a
little bit self a facing. I like that
he's a super agent for your side. Anybody ever gone too far in the woke
direction for you?
know. I don't think I've ever met anybody who's been more woke than me,
because every time I do,
I either
kind of shatter their mind with an argument tactic, okay, and make it so
that they don't ever are enabled to hold a conversation anymore,
or I just get more woke.
Just get more woke. That's disgusting and you're on mastodon. Yeah, I'm on
mastodon and blue sky. I played half of the new Spider Man to game. Oh my God, I
don't think you can guess which half I played like only the miles Morales
missions. Is there more than miles Morales? Yeah, they also white Spider
Man, which is what I think his name is
there. Spider Man and white Spider Man. Yeah, okay, let's get down to
one more Christmas thing. What do you Spider Man? No, no, you can think of one
Christmas topic. Yeah, you were making such a big stink carols. Oh, that's a
good one here. I am burner rock me like a hurricane. I think I think it doesn't
matter man. It's fucking here's my hot take or should I say cold take when it
comes to Christmas or hot when it comes to the Christmas fireplace on Christmas
carols. I think that Carol of the Bells should be banned because it's too scary
for people with sensory overload. I
you can't cater the entire world. It's too many notes. If I want to blast that
out of my Ford Maverick with the subwoofers, I should have every fucking
right. That's on my side. That song came on Pandora, which is the music streaming
service that I use. You don't even have a choice on Pandora. There's no freedom
of market. It's radio. My little brother, who is four years old and we just
diagnosed him with autism because he likes playing with blocks, died.
the my God killed him. Well, he might have actually had something wrong with
him. If he can die from a song yeah, the and the autopsy, they lied on the
autopsy. No, they said it was because he did not have enough nutrients in his
diet. What were you feeding him? We were feeding him paper.
We were
tofu wrapped in paper, the paper that the tofu comes in yeah comes in paper.
I think I'm supposed to be. We weren't pressing the tofu either. I think I'm
supposed to be the worst guy on this and somehow you have killed a child and you
I killed it was my little brother since what oh so now you think the eldest
sibling is responsible for raising the younger sibling. Yes, because the mom
should be on quaaludes and the dad should be at work. No, no, no, no, do
you know what to take a to raise a child? It takes a village fuck a village. It
takes a village in any country, a village, fuck a city, fuck all that. I
demand we get back to talking about Christmas carols. What do you want me to
today man. I already told you my we talked about the Carols. What okay?
I
okay. I think our parents are good. Our Carol's becoming woke.
You just have this the same question for every yes or no question. I
come. I shouldn't be here. So stop shoehorning all this fucking. I just
need to I need to speak about Christmas because I love Christmas so much.
I think I'm trying to stay here. Carol is a beautiful name for a baby boy
born in twenty twenty three
that you're for real, like carol spinny, who played dead, which is how I say for
real. What the hell is dead? Your ass is about to be dead. If you keep talking
about all this bullshit to me, the female ass is dead as a as a
erogenous zone. I don't go anywhere near it. You're not you're not. That is a
it's a no man's land, no man's sky. I think that game is bull that the woman's
at the woman's ass is a no man's land because it is for women only. No women
should not be anywhere near another girl's ass. Women should be called on
watching each other's at except in different videos, except for videos
on line videos on line. Women should be touching each other's. I guess I like
videos. I guess we could find some common ground there. Why what are you
doing building a silencer? That's my gift to you. Of course, you would have a
silencer silencing the voices of everybody around the world. All these all
these minorities that live in other countries over the sea.
Yeah, I guess I would like to silence them. All these minorities that live in,
for example, Asia, the other minorities, the only silencing I do honestly,
because I like my guns loud and my t shirts proud. The only silencing I do is
silencing the night when I play the song really, really loudly
oh silent night, holy night and pay attention. These lyrics all is calm. All
is right yeah. I likes the song silent night to the cover by the dickies, but
what the hell? Yeah, you like the vaginies, punk music that had that has
irreverent references to sexual anatomy. Listen, I like rock and roll all day.
I like Elvis Costello. I like I like the red hot chili peppers, but as soon
as you bleed over into this punk BS, dude, I like punk music man. I'm a fan
of Phoebe Bridgers. I'm a fan. The hell is that the other her sister,
Phoebe Bridger, in her boy band? Is this an animal crossing character? I like
Brockhampton. What the hell's Brockhampton? It's basically a hundred
guys who are in a what we call a polycule. You're kidding. What the
fuck's a polycule? That better be a bug. I like bugs. You like bugs. Their
skeletons are on the wrong sides.
It's on the outside. It's on the outside. Okay, one more Christmas. I
need you to come up with one. Let's go to Christmas Banger one Christmas
thing, because we are getting off topic talking about Brockhampton and bugs.
What should be on the top of the tree?
That's a good question.
That's a very good question.
Not an angel.
A MAGA hat.
A big red MAGA hat that says, "Make this tree green again."
Because you probably want a white Christmas tree, because I've seen those.
I want a green Christmas tree that has lights around it that are every color of the rainbow.
I think on top of the Christmas tree, I think that it should be a high achieving female who's
worked hard this year and is on display for everyone to see and appreciate. You want them
to put Sydney Sweeney on top of the Christmas tree? Sydney Sweeney would be a good choice.
She worked hard this year. I bet you want -- I bet she did. She got all her fucking
rolls because of her boobs. That's what I think. And I bet you want the top of the Christmas
tree -- I didn't even notice she had boobs. I bet you want the top of the Christmas tree
going to be that demonic statue they put up in the financial district of all the
all the tentacles coming out of the woman's head.
What the bowl and in the financial district, you're talking about the
fearless girl, are you talking about Starbucks? You're thinking of hair? No,
I bet he would want the Starbucks logo on top of his train somewhere. I saw
there's a golden thing and I got so mad at it that I shot everybody in my house.
I
it's a golden statue and I bet you like the little girl more than the bull. Yeah,
course. Yeah, it's a defiant piece of art work. All right. Well, it doesn't seem like we've
come to any sort of resolution. Well, we have to ask the undecided. We have to ask. I mean,
Julio, who convinced you who won this debate? Are you pro woke, anti woke, or do you just
like Christmas?
I'm pro woke.
Pro woke.
Oh, my God. Of course, you would be. Oh, my God. Well, I mean, you got to think this is
the guy all is fair in
oh, so far
that is not as a Christmas horn.
That is a Christmas horn.
I think this belongs to Christmas. No,
keep that out of all right. Well, I guess that that is the debate. I'm
sorry that I became completely ill in the middle of it and it won't happen
again.
Alright, Merry Christmas everybody. Bye! Join us next year.
PODCAST ABOUT LIST
*Avatar Pussy*
I am just finna say it, Avatar pussy probably tastes so good.
DOOOOODAY!
You can't start the episode like that!
Ha ha ha!
What's up y'all, welcome back to Potabout List.
We're here recording in the library at our college.
Yup, our college located at 120 Boyles.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not gonna dox us.
Dude, do you know what I saw today?
I saw the fattest guy riding a skateboard around campus.
He was like, and I'm not even kidding,
he had to be like 200,000,000,000,000 pounds,
but he was taller than me,
and he had a Mario mustache.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, yeah, I saw him too. Honestly, dude. I wish that I was him. He looked so awesome. I hope I see that guy again
I want to make him jiggle like a jello bowl. He was really good at skateboarding though, especially given his height and weight
God, it made me so jealous. You have no idea how jealous I am of that guy
I want to sniff his stinky shoes after he skates. I want to turn him into a bubble and make him squirt bubbles God
I'm feeling so sexual. I wish the bubble was my boyfriend. I would take the bubble out to dinner and drink wine with him
Oh, I love wine. I love red wine and white wine.
Yeah, and I wish I had to make the bubble squirt every day as my job.
Oh, and the bubble looks like Mario.
Dude, me too.
I wish I could make love to a bubble and achieve mutual orgasm.
I wish the bubble I am imagining was the third host of this podcast.
I hope one day he becomes the third host of the podcast.
I bet he would be the funniest podcast host of all time.
Aight, motherfuckers, this honky finna sing.
I'm in love with your suit.
I'm gonna sing too.
In a few years, I will bring a Mexican on as our producer.
You would not believe your eyes
Ten million fireflies
lit up the world as I fell asleep
'Cause they fill the open air
and leave keyer drops everywhere
You'd think me rude, but I would just stand and stare
I'd like to make myself believe
That planet Earth turns slowly
It's hard to say that I'd rather stay awake when I'm asleep
'Cause everything is never as it seems
*Skype call*