Take your hat off right now and put these on and wear a red shirt. Number
one, number one, number one, Nigel Uno. Nigel Uno from Codenames Cazen. Where
was he from? England. Oh, what did he talk about? I don't. Can you play? I'm
you're going to get them all my name say like I have a new invention. I have a
new two by four technology. You're okay, Australian a little. I thought he was
us. You know that's the blonde one. Yeah, kind of ruined it. Yeah, it wasn't
that good. You also weren't wearing a red shirt. If you had a red, you do
that yeah, but you should be able to think on your feet. I know I didn't like
you give me these sunglasses. If he had put these on me, I like I would just be
like this
surfs up to
see, but that's not Patrick laugh. That's not night Nigel uno, but it's
like I'm thinking my feet. I'm improvising. You know I'm rolling with
the punches. I'm doing something that's funny. He became a surfer. I can do
that, too.
Well, do you so different prop now? This has been used? Yeah, I got another. Oh,
I'm completely blind. No, you're not. Who said that me? Who's you?
Don't laugh at that. That's not funny. It's funnier to be blind.
Being a surfer is funnier than being... First of all, laughing at blindness is
punching down. Yeah, that's punching down as a disability. Laughing at surfers
are punching... That's a disability. Surfing is not a disability. If you're
stupid enough to fucking hang out with sharks, you have a mental disability.
You're not hanging out with sharks, you're hanging out with waves. You have
a mental deficit if you are hanging out with waves and sharks and fish.
And you think that those are friends. They said I had a mental deficit and I
still got into college, so...
You got into college more than any of us. I got into three colleges. Yeah,
that's actually pretty impressive. Three colleges dropped out of each one. Toby
motherfucking Keith is dead man. I know. Fuck dude! It actually was, I was
listening to a, I was listening to a lot of Toby Keith in the past couple of
weeks on its, genuinely. I ain't as, Toby Keith and Tim McGraw I've been
listening to.
I ain't as alive as I once was. But I'm as dead once. Well, you know what guys?
I'm covered in dirt and worms on me now. All these people, all these people.
there was a time back in my prime when I got up and walked around. I love this
great. I love my great it's my kind of great.
It's all dirt and stuff and grass. Yeah, they buried me up my
on my face on my ass. They said Toby,
you passed away, Toby, Toby, you have passed away man and I'm sorry. I was the
another one. I was for my grave yeah and flesh for my worms. Well, that could
work to a good flower, flowers for my grave flesh for my worm horse,
worm horse, my wormies
because these are my wormies
dude. Oh my God, that'll be a great thing for an edgy guy like Marilyn
Manson to do to be like raisin, take care of a bunch of worms and be like
yeah. When I die, release these into my grave, that's actually so fucking
marry me with my worms, because like if you did because the the supreme edgy
thing to do would be like I let my dog eat me after I die, but you can't do
that. No, the dogs are interested in the or you get a pig farm anyway. Pig farm
go snatch style yeah, but like people, people get mad at that. They won't let
the pigs do it, but worms it's like you're already dead and you just put a
yeah. The worms are going to eat you anyway. Exactly that's true, but anyway
ever all these people saying rest in peace, Toby keep this rest in peace till
I'll keep that well guys rest in piss Toby Keith, because I actually think it
was a piece of shit. Watch your fucking now watch it. He wasn't watch it. He
was an SJW wait really yeah. What's he you Toby Keith? Was he an S? Hey Toby
Keith fuck you man. You see that I know that you were an SJW and now that I
realize this your dog shit to me and I'm glad you're dead. There was a there's
this like fake story that goes around about how Chris Christopherson
made fun of or it said like you the hell's that Chris Christo you don't know
he was in the highwayman I think with Willie Nelson and Johnny Cash.
Oh, Stars Born.
SNL.
Stars Born.
He was in SNL.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
But there's like this fake story that goes around like I think they were like buddies
and everyone was like yeah Chris Christofferson told him that he didn't serve this country,
he's pretending to be a patriot or whatever.
And that's going around again now that he's dead.
Toby Keith is responsible for probably half of the deaths in the Iraq war.
Oh, absolutely.
This guy can't, you can't, this guy deserves every medal on earth.
You can't write the Taliban song and not get a purple heart.
Dude, how many fucking people listen to a Toby Keith song?
American soldier.
Literally, there are...
I'm an American.
Toby Keith songs led to the loss of so many legs.
So many guys who were like so good at football.
Toby Keith is the as has legs on his on his head. Yeah, you know how they paint
how they they paint planes on like a plane when they shoot him down. He was on
his guitar. He was painting legs, just tons of white legs,
bones all over his guitar, just a bunch of femur bone and not even you know
sitting on a throne made of bones, white bones and fucking shin bones. We're
thinking about his cousin leg. We're thinking about cousin legs right, but
we're not considering how many
the
whiskey related alcohol deaths for these women. Oh, that was something I wanted
to talk about, man. I think that this might be... There's no question in my
mind that this was an alcohol related passing away.
I think... Oh, 'cause he loves bars? 'Cause he loves bars and he's spending
all his... He loves at least one bar. Yeah, he loves one bar. I guess that's
true. I guess that's true, but he says, "Red Solo Cup, I fill you up." So he
also likes parties. Yeah. And what do you do at parties with a red solo? That
a picnic. He likes a whiskey girl. And so many women were trying to do him and they started
getting into whiskey. Women can't, that's a man's drink. You can't drink whiskey if you're
a girl. That's the point of the song. You don't actually put hair on your chest and
then nobody wants to date you. Yeah, then Toby Keith won't want to date you. You think
he's telling the truth and that's how he's lying? I think this is, I hate saying this,
I hate even thinking about this, I think that the tide is turning on alcohol in America.
Yeah, absolutely. I think that Toby Keith, this death is going to be the first of many
alcohol related deaths that we see probably me and Patrick soonly following.
And the younger generation are not.
They're all addicted to vapes and zins.
They don't even want to drink alcohol anymore.
I saw something like Gen Z is the least alcohol drinking generation ever.
They don't like it.
How?
It's because they're fruits.
They'll grow into it.
No, they won't.
We're technically Gen Z.
I think it's because they're...
We're Gen Z on the technicality, you know?
Well, wait, yeah.
Gen Z isn't Gen Z like they've been legal to drink for what, four or five years?
Yes, and they haven't started in 97. I'm a day walker for the Z lineal. I'm I can navigate
millennial spaces as well as Gen Z. Stalker. Yeah, I'm not a gay stalker. You're also we're
all day walkers here. I don't know what that we can navigate millennial space. We can say
stuff about Matt Kim, but also he told millennial man. They if they put they say I'm a zoomer,
I don't care, but I have you want to claim that say doggo right now. That's
well. That's what I mean, dude. I've I can I'm so much more likely to connect
with somebody who says doggo than somebody. Yeah, that's true.
True. There's no can you imagine being in a like? Yeah, I don't know if I'm
gonna party full of millennials only. Yeah, I'm gonna do okay. I'm fine. I'm
in. I'm with my my home turf. You might bring a slice of pizza. Now touch my
button. Give me a millennial right there. That's yeah zoomers. They do not eat
pizza. What house are you? They don't eat. They don't like. I'm definitely
Ravenclaw. See he knew immediately what I meant. It's we're all millennial.
They were not zoom. You might be zoomer. You're zoomer. You're actually full
zoomer. No, I'm day walker bro. No, you're not man. You're full zoom. No,
I'm day walker. No, I'm not a full zoomer because I like alcohol and I hate
weed. I got a
I can go to the hookah bar. I can go to the regular bar.
they accept me. Why don't they have hookah bar? Why is there a hookah bar,
but there's no cigarette bar? We can just smoke cigarettes and smoke.
They got it in Pittsburgh, dude. They have some of those. Hookah,
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Why the hell did we do a show there? You saying a
city made me remember. I wanna do the plug at the top, but I'll do it.
We'll do it eight minutes in. Guys, we're adding some shows to the tour.
Oh my God. Holy fuck. These guys, these are not your typical... And Julio,
I'm gonna send this picture to you right now so you can pull it
up on screen. I'm so strong from the new shows. We're doing the sketch. We're doing the sketch
tour of course that you guys all already know about and bought tickets for. He's been obsessed
with my strength. I have been touching Patrick a lot just trying to get him to flex. You
tried to fully molest me earlier. He doesn't care about my strength at all. You saw that
too. I did see it. I wasn't trying to molest you man. You're being dramatic. He was touching
up on me. You never had a good friend before who touches you. I felt what felt like a piece
piece of wood touching the back of the chair. I had some and you know what I'm
saying. I'm construction less station vibes got a car station unless he asked
you to touch it.
By the way, we have
some shows here. We're doing the sketch shows with with home plate. It appears
these ones are just us, just a trio, some podcast shows for you guys. We're
hitting the major cities on this one that we haven't been to yet. Guys, we are
going to Minneapolis on March 30th at Sisyphus Brewing. We're hitting Detroit
April 3rd at Loving Touch and of course the Jewel of America. We're going to Carborough,
North Carolina on 4/26. Caleb tried to give me a Loving Touch earlier. So go ahead. I
tried to give you a Jewel of Me. These ticket links are supposed to be up by the time this
comes out. It's just a fissy in how much you try to fuck me. They might not be up on the
website yet, so if you go to the website, try to buy it and you don't see them, just
keep hitting F5 for the next few days. But they're supposed to be up tomorrow. We'll
I know at least Minneapolis is already up. Well, you and me have had so much
tension over the years about our bodies being close to each other. You guys have a real will
they won't they? I feel like for me with both you guys, it's like it's a will. They will.
And that's how I feel about you and Jubio. You can't feel that way about some about two other
people. This is like if Fleetwood Mac, if they were all boned. Are you feeling will they won't
they about me and Jubio? You're saying that you think me and him have done it. If Fleetwood Mac
Jack was all doing it and they got along after they were all doing it.
That's what this podcast I got an argument, some kind of fear between you
about I gotten it. Well, I got I have no fear. He can touch me a little bit
like I got into an argument with somebody yesterday about how they were
like yeah. I'm zero percent gay. Somebody has to have talked about this
before they said I'm zero percent gay and I said, but you would probably like
it if it was the best one ever
yeah,
the hottest guy, but not even like the best, the best experience, anything that
you think you don't like the best ever of that thing. I've definitely like right
no yeah, it's like you get up in the you get up in the plane to go skydiving
you're like take me back down. I can't do it. Please they go. No, you're doing
it. You got your parachute on they push you up. Oh, my God, yeah, oh, my God, I
feel alive for the first time in my life. I feel alive. This is exactly
about it for months after we've had this conversation. We've had this
I need to go again. The wife walks in and you close your phone quick. You're
looking at skydiving
jumping off of the bureau in your bedroom is never the same. Never, never
you have to go all the way. I'm saying man, I videos of people skydiving
doesn't cut it. No, I feel like everybody's so saying I'm straight and I
or I'm gay, but you've never had the best version of the other yeah, because
I think I think I used to think I didn't like sushi and then I had very
expensive nice sushi one time and now I'm like kind of thinking about sushi more
we've and then also a conversation about food. Once you have the bet really yeah,
well, I think that it also comes to sex experiences. Once you've had the best of
that, once I've had the best different kind of sex, now I'm looking of course
it's going to feel good. It's sex, it's going to feel amazing. It's in the it's
in the name and then once I start raising, say amazing sex is in the name.
once I have the most amazing sex, I'm sure it would be amazing, but then I'm
going to start it's the it's just like the sushi. Now I'm getting grocery store
sushi. Yeah, right now you're like now, which is the best form of sushi. No, not
well. It's crazy to me that you didn't like sushi before. Yeah, that is fucked.
It's weird. I didn't not like it. I just said you didn't like I didn't opt for. I
got some this weekend. I got grocery store sushi this weekend. Well, no, it
was the triangle. I got grocery store groceries this this week.
pray tell about this grocery store groceries. What's your haul? Flatbread,
mozzarella, and pizza sauce. Guess what I was making with that? He's getting,
he's getting a pizza sandwich. Flatbread pizza, y'all. He's getting, he's getting
gigantic, this guy. I thought you were gonna make pizza soup. I got cereal as
well. Pizza soup. Pizza soup. That's leftovers, dude. When you make homemade
pizza and you get to eat pizza soup for the rest of the week. Oh my god,
that's so good. It's like a Thanksgiving sandwich. Making pepperoni stock for
your pizza soup. It's so good. Pepperoni stock is great. Dude, on my pizza I had
some arugula. I had some prosciutto. Not a pizza man. Yeah, that's a flatbread.
Yeah, what was a flatbread pizza? Well, yeah, you already said you got a
flatbread. Yeah, so I don't really understand. Did you do pizza sauce?
Yeah, that's I said pizza sauce. Wait, you did pizza sauce, arugula and
pepperonis? Not pepperonis, prosciutto. Prosciutto. Okay, this sounds like a
pretty good pizza. It was okay. I think it would be better the second time
I made it if you put it in a wood fired oven, it would probably be amazing.
Yeah, definitely wood fired oven. Yeah, I was thinking of that when I was
making it.
You can get one for the home. There's cost $300. Well, I was thinking just
maybe putting wood into my gas powered oven.
Oh, my oven has started smelling like gas again. I think it's happening once
more.
Well, you know that you know the burst of gas smell when you turn on your
oven, when you start preheating your oven, that always gets me. I'm always
like, "Whoa, whoa!" And then it goes like a few minutes go by and it's
we were having that meeting earlier about those shows and Alex was like do we
have a co two monitor in the house? I want to get one because it's starting
to smell like gas and
a monitor yeah that's what he said, which I didn't want to call him out, but I
don't think that funny yeah, but
do we have a nitrogen monitor? The air is seventy five percent nitrogen in
your house. You need to leave, but the air his room is next to the kitchen and
the air smelled like that because I
accident. I was making a cream sauce type thing and I needed to simmer and
then forgot to turn the way
wait. Let me stop you right there. You're telling me you were creaming and
your roommate smelled it.
That's nasty. What what the fuck? It's actually kind of you're creaming out in
the kitchen. Yeah, and I left in the runner on. I left the burner on for
probably an hour and a half. It was fire. What's the
burned for an hour?
how long is X men origins Wolverine stop talking about X men, bitch no shut the
fuck up. I'm sick of this. I'm done with you. The other day we get on a meeting
and he's we just came from the gym and he's like look what I found on the way
back from the gym to giant X men comic books. Fuck you man. You I've been
watching now you're now you're changing the universe. You're changing reality to
give you free X men. So that's my power. You're not yes, you're not an Omega level
I am an omega level. You can bend reality to my will. You are not an omega level
mutant. I had a really thought that was really at first it kind of tickled me
pink and then it started to-, I can't tell if this is a cogent thought at all,
but I want to tell you guys this thought I had about the Simpsons. I was watching
the Simpsons. I've been re-watching it. Were you watching the X-Men episode? I
can tell you're watching the Simpsons because you wore a Simpsons skin shirt.
Oh my God. I would have killed a Simpson, one of the less important ones, so that
nobody cares. You skinned a Simpson alive and you made a shirt with him. Hans
small man, but can you imagine living in the Simpsons universe living in
Springfield, along with the Simpsons and every time you watch TV, it's like
someone else from your town. It's always like oh they're interviewing my doctor.
Oh, that's crusting the cloud.
No, there's my neighbor. Oh, that's my son.
Somebody else, you know, you only have public access at that point. It's just
so funny that it's like their interview. They interview like oh, this is dr nick
of year and they're like oh that's that doctor. I see like
twenty times before yeah. Oh these are all oh they're oh a poos on TV. Now
yeah, it would be so incredible to watch TV and every time it's a different
person from yeah. I haven't seen I haven't seen too much of the Simpsons.
I've seen enough, but that's great. That is crazy, which I would have that's a
reveal. I was watching well when I was a kid. I did you not seeing girl. I
didn't see the Simpsons until I was in the girls either middle school girls. I
I watch I watch family guy in South Park, we good, then I think it you can tell
did you twisted mind you are not. That means that you're not like like me and
Cameron people see us and they smell Harvard right because we grew up with
the pedigree. Yes, exactly. You see me, a serbic. They look at you, you're
thinking, you're thinking Plymouth State University, maybe maybe Keene State
University. Isn't it ironic these kind of universities that have parties, the
community probably goes to a professional writing school rather than a community
college. Interesting. That's right. That's right. And I've been to two. I've been to
two community colleges. And you watched community? I never watched it. There you go. You made
community be very, very different. Yeah. It's clear watching that show that
these people have never been to a community college. No, they don't know about the Rubik's
Cube. They're like, "Oh, it happens at a community college. Probably a blanket for it." There is always, in
every single, every community college I went to, every community college I went to,
to kid walking around the school who is practicing rubix cube speed thing with
one let me say also smarter than anybody. Why is he there? Here's a roast for
their tv show community. Yeah, that's a boring ass name for a tv show. Yeah,
mit blam yeah blam laughter. Yeah, that's a better name community. It's a
boring word. You have to open the thesaurus to find that one. There was a
show called kablam. I don't know if you knew this really yeah, Nickelodeon.
why is it said blam laughter? He's a blam, blam, blam, blam, blam, blam,
laughter, it's not a blam exclamation point colon, laughter, laughter, it's
also do blam sorrow and it's clear to me that the people who information the
office never works in an office either yeah. Well, they worked at Harvard
University. Can you imagine how amazing you should write a show called writer's
room? Yeah, nothing like an actual writer. Yes, because we've never been in
one of them. Here's the thing, Paul Provenza, you're not in the green room,
you're on a stage. There's thousands of people around you in the middle of the
not for last festival. You idiot. He's so dumb Paul Provenza, but one of the best
standups of all time. Yeah, everyone talks about his standup. Everyone says,
dude, you should have seen Paul Provenza back in the day. He has a, is it, have
you seen that one episode of Green Room where he's wearing that t-shirt? No. It
says, we are all African. I want that t-shirt so bad. That's a Richard Dawkins
t-shirt really yeah. Richard Dawkins is I think in his Twitter picture is wearing
that shirt. That's badass. Yeah, so it's like it was like an early or late 2000s
like atheist thing. Yeah, being African. Yeah, because of the we are all
origin of the human race, but a land bridge, but you know they say maybe that
there that some Native American people were here. They were in America even
but they didn't emigrate from Africa. What was the first where who was the first
guy who transformed from a I mean imagine how weird that was being born and you're
a man and you have two monkey parents. Well, even more than that man, they the
Neanderthals and the Homo sapiens, they coexisted, they were around at the same
time and Neanderthals probably died out because Homo sapiens just like out
competed them for natural resources. So it'll be like you and your Neanderthal
bros, you'd like get up and like all right time to go hunting, let's go kill a
woolly mammoth. We got our our rock with a vine around it that we swing around our
and they were at the man, they're just using their hands. Literally, it's like
it's like it's like the movie where it's like a movie where the big company
comes in and and and fucks up the like little, a little bit small business.
The humans show up to the mammoth hunt. There's a bunch of homo sapiens and
they got swords and shit yeah and they're they're full night. You're
fucked. They're not killing you, but they're they're getting all the stuff
they definitely killed. They killed. They also interbred, I think. Oh, they
were interbred. Can you imagine having can you imagine
damn
crate
into bread. That was a really fucking good one. Can you imagine having a
situation where it's like it's possible and I won't say acceptable, but it's
possible for you to be like damn, I'm a fuck someone of a different speed.
I'm just be like sitting around with your boys at the bar and be like damn
like I'm really into
yeah, what's your type man? I hate to bring it back to our other species. I
hate to bring it back to explain. No, I don't, but you love to that is
definitely there's definitely a mutant chaser type of guy. Well, where is the
where is the the family like where's the family comedy or something right homo
superior, where is the family comedy about the the homo sapien bringing in
their Neanderthal Christmas dinner is that in crude? No, but it could be
crude five. They carry in the Henderson. Oh, that's a big foot. Yeah,
yeah, that's a good idea. That's a great idea. I think yes, who's come
guess
yes,
to dimper.
It's a great idea.
That's a really, really good
subtitles. Yeah,
well, no, the homo sapien speaks just english. He's just like a guy with the
like my favorite vest on my favorite neanderthal fact is back when they first
were discovering neanderthals. The early scientific name for them was homo
stupidus
and they changed it. They were like all you stupid homo.
I didn't know science had
I didn't know science had a name for you.
Homo stupidus
the academic papers. We discovered homo stupidus yep and they're like now he's
right next to me.
That's an amazing yeah. Homos stupid is is awesome. Is that one of those things
where I mean that's clearly latin, but maybe a guy was named homo stupidus and
they named him after that guy yeah stupidus john stupidus yeah or the guy's
name was not homo stupidus and they were like this name named after you.
I know they
he's really named after they were the old scientific names. They got to bring that
style back man nowadays, it's all naming them after people, but back in the day,
fuck all that, like grizzly bears, their name is ursus something horribilis. I
like that, that's great, it should all be like that horribilis, horribilis,
which I think that of bears is extremely cute, yeah, but not grizzlies man, I've
been seeing these even grizzly, they have hunchbacks like quasimodo, my grandma
a hunchback like Quasimodo? I saw that bear. That bear video. What bear? Where the lady
gets a, the bear has like a deli cup stuck on its head and she takes the deli cup off
of the bear's head and then the bear brings his mom to her house and keeps trying to like,
like, just like showing, the cub is showing his mom just like, this lady's, this is my
OG right here. This lady took the cup off my head? This lady took the cup off my head.
change my number. Well, what is the prayer mom? I want her to be my new mom.
What if it was a punishment? Maybe yeah and the moms coming over, let
I'd be pretty pissed if I was the mama yeah, they're taking my kid ever take a
cup off of that. I can imagine some I can imagine a Karen in a restaurant
saying that like she's sitting down. She goes to the bathroom. She leaves her
her toddler at the table and with a cup on his head, a waiter comes over and
takes the cup. I know it's
how
that'd be a bad punishment.
I
hate that we need to bring back cool punishments for kids, because like what
will like glue your hands to your head or yeah, it needs to be more. I don't
know it needs to be more. You do something you borrow soap as a classic
bar. It's a good example. It should be, you know, things stuff. I had to borrow
soap as a kid. I got that. I would swear. I think I got the bar soap. Maybe
once. I had to use Listerine because my mom knew that I hated Listerine so
badly.
That's weird. Well, it burns my
my most
means it's working. The punishment kid memory I have the most is that my dad, I
forget what I even did, but my dad was like I'm gonna, I had a bunch of little
like Pokemon figurines of different Pokemon. I like a bunch of them that I
would play with and my dad was like, oh, like you did this whatever I'm gonna
take away your favourite Pokemon toy and I would be like I was like, oh, my
my favorites a meow
the lamest one
or
fucking
doing the worst, the worst lie of all time and him completely knowing which
one is my favorite. Yeah, I try to pass it up like no. This one's my
favorite
please yeah. I feel like I'm going to be probably seeing right through that with
my kid yeah sure yeah as a kid. You always think you're a genius and then I
feel like you think back and you're like, oh yeah, yeah, I used to think that I'd
be able to hide myself in the love seat. Like I would, I would, that's different.
I would, I would think I thought that I was so, so
and you're like, I thought I could fit inside the
I thought that I could, I would position my body so that it, I thought that I
would looked like a cushion when I did this and I would like you'd go under the
cushion. No, I would be in the middle of the chair and I would try to see how
if I could cover the whole
cushion of the love seat, it was like it's not a love. See, it's more like a
chair. You thought you were a salamander. I thought that I could look like a
cushion and every single time my mom would walk in and say, what the fuck are
you doing? You thought you were doing the scene from Lord of the Rings where
they become a rock. Yes. What are you talking about? I still don't understand.
You thought you could look like a cushion. He just explained it. He thought
he was like covering himself up or did you cover yourself up with a blanket or
anything? I think so, yeah. Yeah, you know, like you've seen Lord of the Rings
how they become a rock. You thought you had active camo? Yes. I could imagine
be thinking that as a kid. I'm sure I thought something similar. I was probably
five or six. Sixteen, seventeen? That's not... Yeah, five or sixteen.
That's not... Anywhere between five to sixteen, I tried this. You were a quite
dumb child. I was very dumb. I mean, I told you before I got my head stuck
in a reclining chair.
Get the hell away from these chairs, bitch. You are not allowed to touch the
chairs anymore. I don't think there's any chair. There is a chair in my
house and I do sit in it now because I think I've got a chair. I was going to
say there's no like sofa type chairs. I used to think I definitely conquered the
chair. My grandpa had a lazy boy. You do your damn chores. He's not his grandpa's
boy. I'm his grand boy. What's this Listerine? Don't even after I say that I
was after I say that I was tortured with Listerine as a child. You pull out a
Listerine thing you want one. I'll take one after we're unless I do something
bad coffee. Okay. If I say something bad, then you can give me some. I'll have
these on reserve. Okay. Thank you. My dad has my dad smells like those all day.
Yeah. Yeah. Because he pops them like like they're nothing. That's what I've
been doing. Yeah. I bought these in this one. I don't got I had to I had to I got
my blood drawn this morning and I had to and guys I'm going back to the doctor to
get my results and I'm planning to scream at her for no reason. Just so you
you know what I mean just I want to be mad at her. All right, let's do that. Oh
thank you. Hey, Mr. Fetter, thank you so much for coming. No, I can't I can't I
have to pent it's pent up. I'm really let it loose. You gotta get like a
pot. So I'm just I'm just letting you know so I can report on it again next
week because I'm seeing her next but like what are you gonna scream at her
about just everything I can my blood, whatever my blood results are any
upcoming appointments. I have I'm just I'm gonna I'm ready to take my war to
the next level, but anyway, I had to fast for it and I could part of the
fast is you can't even chew gum. I'm supposed to chew gum. I don't know
heavens, but that's what it says. It says no, you know, no, no eating, no
drinking anything other than water, no drinking alcohol, no smoking. Can you
have a strenuous exercise? Yeah, wine is good for you. Wine is alcohol, by the
way,
and no chewing gum, even if you made me it gave me the most clear moment of
lucidity in my life that guys right now I'm completely addicted to chewing gum.
You are I remember addicted to chewing gum so badly, so hopelessly addicted. I
went. I full guy quitting cigarettes reached for a piece of gum and had to
say no ten times yeah like over the like you know this is like in the fast. The
fast is like probably total like three hours of being awake time. I mean like
it's not like I'm like all day. It's like right before I go to bed, I'm
reach for the goat. No, we're going to pierce a show and I was at your house
and your fiance was asking you about the gum and you said this is the last two
pieces and then you pulled out another big thirty six. You have the briefcase.
he has the briefcase. It's not a briefcase. It's a cylinder. Yeah,
that's so he is the
they make briefcase. You've never seen the
really long ones. You can get a Costco. I'm going to get that. Yeah,
I got to say, do we have the other day? Julio? I joined a discord call with
Julio and he said I said I was chewing. I forgot. I was said something about
gum and he said you don't like gum and I made me so mad. I turned on my
camera and I had like four
in front of me. I was showing them all to him that I saw your gum desk,
Dude, I saw it.
That is a 12-year-old's addiction.
I'm hopelessly...
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad I'm not addicted to Zen.
You need to get addicted to something even better than that.
No, I like gum, man.
You're going to like my thumb.
I like your thumb already.
Really?
Chew on it.
It's fine.
But it's so ugly.
It's not that bad.
Chew on his thumb.
Look at this thumb.
It's not that bad.
Look at this one.
Look at my slender thumb.
Oh, my God.
You have a slim thumb.
I have a cut from my cat.
Slim thumb, mother-thumber.
car and it's making an X stop crazy stop. Don't even say what I think you will
say
you're not going to say it right. Charles Xavier would not fuck with you. By the
way, in real life, he would literally listen to the last episode and hear
what you said about people in wheelchairs. He would call you. I say
about which that's behind paywall. So if you're not subscribe, no, you can't give
any detail. You won't know what he said. No, no, no, no, no, that it was bad. I
said okay, let me clear the air. I Caleb said that people in wheelchairs have
Ganondorf powers for some reason, and I said I'm crazy. I don't know. I don't
remember why reason. I don't remember why, but Caleb said they have some
hidden Ganondorf power and then they become Ganon and I said yes, stay a pig.
You said go back to be. You said you would see someone in a wheelchair stand
up and say go back to being a pig because I got I got confused. I forgot
that when Ganondorf becomes Ganon, he becomes a pig.
Nobody knows what you're talking about. Ganon is a...
They will know what I'm talking about. Ganondorf is from Super Smash Brothers.
Yeah, and Ganondorf is the man. Ganondorf is a super punch. Ganondorf is the man.
Ganon is the pig creature. I don't know what the fuck you're talking...
Ganon... Shut the hell up. Ganon is a pig creature. No. You've become a nerd.
You've become a full nerd. I have become... You're talking about X-Men and
Ganondorf, man. That's hardly a pig. That's a pig. Okay, a hog. What kind of...
he's got who I'll give you that he's kind of hogs got hooves and hands. He's a
hog. Nobody has hands and hooves. Oh, well, you said he has hooves like that
was a disqualifier, but he's type of pig. That's not a pig man. That's a
fucking limb monster type of he has a cheese sword in this picture. Yeah,
that sort is made of cheese. None of them. What goes good with him? I don't
want to look at any more pictures. No, I was a holy cheese. We're moving on to
episode now. All right, we're done. We're done with you. All right, we can jump
right in the pig stuff. We can jump right in to today's episode, which is
okay. Go ahead and enter.
Welcome to our new our new game show that is actually adopted from an old
game show. The price is just right. The price is just right. Right is right.
my pride is ride. My pride is ride. My pride is right guys. Today we found some
funny ass
listings for items to buy on the internet, but we're hiding the prices
from each other and we're gonna see if we can guess the price. Oh my God, this
is an amazing idea. I'm pretty excited for this. I found some good stuff. I
mean, I could go first. If you guys do this, let's just go into order of tabs.
Okay. All right, I'll go first guys. And today I made a title slide by
I wish I did that as Julio always tells me or he always passive aggressively wants
me to make a title slide.
That's Nickelodeon.
That's the Price is Right.
So I don't actually, I never actually watch the Price is Right or know any details about
it.
It's amazingly fucking awesome.
If I'm doing anything wrong, you guys have to tell me.
Who is Price is Right?
That was Bob Barker, not Pat Sajak.
Pat Sajak, I believe, became.
No he's Wheel of Fortune.
Drew Carey became.
Drew Carey.
On this one you have to make sure that only go to the next slide when I say next slide because you can't you're going to be
Giving away spoilers. We can't spoil nothing on this.
So let's start with our first item that you guys need to guess the price on. Can I say one thing real quick?
You can say some stuff. You can say as much as you want.
If in the world Kayla if Cameron is Drew Carey then Julio would be his Mimi.
Who's Mimi? Okay, well that if you watch the Drew Carey show. What the hell is that?
You'll just look up Mimi Drew Carey show and you'll know. No. No.
so okay, let's take a look at our first item from ebay guys all right. This
next slide, please. This is an item called slime types, fluffy foam and
normal. Okay, so brand new or best offer with free shipping, and I got multiple
I mean you can analyze this as much as you want, but I got multiple slides
people listening. This is a I just want to say what this what this item is.
It's a rubber made Tupperware with it looks like some kind of white
oobleck type thing. Right. It is mostly... And let's hit next slide here,
so you can see some more pictures that are included with this listing,
and you can describe these to the listeners. Let's see the next slime.
Oh, wait, this is multiple. So this is slime types, fluffy, foam,
and normal. So they have many of these. I think... Okay, so these are
all... It looks like they ate Chinese food and then used the Tupperware to
put slime into it.
And they're all white, they kind of... Some of them have sort of a...
Yeah, well, one is pink, but they all
are plain, except for one has sort of a fruit cake style. Yeah, jelly bean
mix in
jelly bean mode, jelly bean mode. I would say for that one, and then next
slide here. These are the last details about this item. It's brand new,
unused, unopened, undamaged item in its original packaging. The brand is slime
and the type is fluffy slime.
Now guys, based on these details, what do you think the price is without going
over all together?
it doesn't say every slime. I think that it's for every slime. I'm going to say
package. I think it's a package. Yeah, okay, wait. What are they? Call that
prices right?
You're saying what forty dollars forty dollars for the locking in locking in
locking in at forty. I should have got some some sound effects for this damn.
I'm going to just make one up. We have plenty of them.
That's a good sound effect. Yeah, you can keep that one for that. So that was
I'm going to say well, I'm not I'm not revealing anything and I'm just finding
sound effects and then this is if you're right. Okay, so he said forty yeah,
I'm going to say
man, I'm going to go a hundred. I'm going to change my answer to fifty and
they're ten dollars each. You can't change it. You already said locked.
Okay, well, I unlock my lock. Okay, I'll let you change it to fifty. I'll
let you change it because Patrick
next slide. Please, Caleb, the price of these slimes
two hundred and ten dollars one point Caleb one point Caleb. The slimes are
expensive you guys. I could have guessed that I wish we had a ticker that we
could put the points on yeah. I'll take you have thought about this through
maybe that's flick. All right guys realize let me get to let me get to my
next item here. This is an item. Okay, thank you trick. This is an item on the
next slide here. That is called line dog mating
this is on Timo and I have to censor some stuff on this. I just censor some
on the picture and so this wow I've never thought of this. I'm going to buy one
of these. This is a it's a stuffed dog that looks like it has a pussy hole.
Yes,
it's a dog sex toy. It's so this is called. This is an item called sleep
estrous dog toy simulation, mating toy, plush poodle, vent fire, estrous partner,
mating, sexual companion, venting, fidget dog toy, okay, and now it's
something to know about this. Here's a detail. This is an item that is on sale,
and this is for so where this is about the sale price, an active dog, a dog
that is
wanting to mate, yeah, but is locked up and you let it fuck this. Let's look at
some more pictures here. Okay, next slide,
the features it has are
simulate appearance, which is again censored. That is a
flesh light hole for a dog, pussy
simulated rabbit hair and a suction cup base. This is known as a mating sexual
companion. Okay, so this is for like a dog breeder. Yeah, which is crazy.
It's about it's not for a dog breeder. This is for your dog who is frustrated
and tries to legs all the time. This feels to me like maybe a cover up yeah
now let's go to the next slide here. Let me read you the description. Here's
some more pictures
of it in use. Here's the description. No lubricants is not included. One dogs
with estrous behavior at home, holding legs, riding over dolls, making love to
the air, etcetera. Only chasing female dogs outside and not estrous behavior at
home are not recommended to buy to dog. Cannot be too stupid if your dog belongs
to what cannot teach a few years will not be fixed to the kind of toilet. Do
not recommend to buy okay three. The host needs to be patient. Dogs are
emotional creatures, too, and mating doesn't happen all the time. It may not
be used on the spot, but dogs with estrous behavior will use it sooner or
later under the patient guidance of their owners. And now to the thing you
we spoke about about a cover up. I'd like to this next slide is like to read a
review from this four stars color khaki. The one in the photo looks bigger than
the one I got might be a little too small for my dog as he is bigger than
this.
This is really, truly so guys, I'm going to tell you also this is this. I'm
going to tell you what the it's on sale. It's on sale sixty eight percent off,
so you're you're looking for the current the sale price. I think that this also
one thing on this is I think this might be a new leader for number one worst
thing to be reincarnated as
in your next life. If you wake up and you're you can't move and you have four
limbs and their suction cup to the ground, you're in for a very rough one.
This is going to be this is a ten dollar item on sale from seventy dollars.
I'm going to say the original dollars locked in. I'm going to say the original
price. You don't have to guess the original well, but if it's sixty eight
well if it's sixty eight percent off, I might as well get twelve. Ninety I'm
going to get the original price twelve ninety eight okay. Original price was
two hundred current prices, eighty four or no thirty. You said sixty eight off
yeah okay, then thirty four sixty four
choosing you guys choose a number four dollars that's locked in okay, all
right, Patrick,
you were not that close, but you did not go over. Oh Caleb, you've gone over
the price. It was forty eight fifty one, the original price one hundred and
fifty five dollars and fifty three cents. God man, I had a better guess
and that's pretty cheap. If anyone wants to buy one of these to use for their
dog,
that's I guarantee that's what that review that is so bad, pretty terrible.
All right, let's go to a more normal one. Okay, next slide, please eyes on
men's salt water stretch, flat front, chino pants color cadet navy straight
size thirty with thirty two length condition new with tags next slide
please easy transaction. Thank you is on ebay. This is on ebay. Why is this in
here? This is this is just a pair of yeah, this is a regular pair of khakis
they're not khakis they're navies. Well, this is a pair of navy chino pants. I
guess the price I saw that's a that's like a department store brand. I'm going
to say this is
forty five ninety nine. These are and I'm going to use my clothing brain. These
are probably
twenty five ninety nine okay,
let's reveal the price
one hundred and seventy six thousand two hundred and three dollars and five
cents. So Caleb you were closer, but you're a little off. I'll take the
point. Listen, I was playing to win not playing the exact right. I knew that
again. These are still up on eBay. Anybody wants to go by these? It's an
busy transaction. So you know does it come with the guy? I think it must come
with the guy to come with a guy for that price yeah of new friend all right
here's the here's the next ebay item. This is talky ball. Okay, wait, this is
an ebay bid. This is a talky ball and this is next slide. Please item
description from the seller. I was opening a bag of talkies and found this.
I was thinking of eating it, but I thought I could auction it. So yeah,
some ideas for it, you can put it in a grinder and have Taki seasoning or
whatever you want. This is $10 starting bid. Yeah, we're guessing starting
starting bid. Oh man, I'm gonna say I will say $20. I think that this is a
novelty spice. Okay,
Caleb
shit,
Patrick. Oh,
it was $4. It was $4. That's a good deal. I would have
a talky ball, a talky ball. He's right. You could grind that. Okay, but what
about this one?
Black talky chip rare guys. This is a black talky chip that looks like poop.
Yeah, it looks like it looks like goose poop. How did you find this? I search
talky
here's the item description for this one guys black talky chip rare condition is
new shipped with USPS ground advantage, not new. I'm going to guess ten dollars
again. What would it be in a pose? I mean like he's like used to put it in his
mouth
I'm
it's basically new. It just looks like a burnt chip. Yeah. How much do you think
it's worth? It's rare ten dollars
starting to like you're trying to lead me astray by saying it's rare because
anything that's rare should be over a hundred dollars. I don't think that
somebody's paying a hundred bucks or even thinking that somebody will pay a
hundred dollars for a black chip. So I am going to say
seventy five dollars seventy five dollars. Yeah, okay, Caleb,
you are the closest. It is three hundred dollars guys. This is a rare black chip.
It's three hundred dollars. What do you do with that? You just eat it. You put
it in frame
in a black plastic bag. Yeah, I would want to know you know what I would cover
it in resin. You know what I would do is I would take this and I would take it to
a testing facility to find out what was in this chip. Yeah, because that is not
pure talky seasoning. I can tell by the color. So this next one moving on from
dockies. We have another ebay listing manipulation demon ring mind control
power wealth, dark demonic magic satanic and here's the description. This is
zero tia. Can you feel her strength? Do you feel her magic calling to you a
special conjure epic energies of power burst from zero tia and the next slide
here.
She is a godlike powerful psychic being with telekinetic abilities for exceeding
that of your average psychic spirits, dark power and sacred forces awakened.
let her share her powerful psychic abilities with you mind reading mind
control will manipulation force manipulation future site psychic visions
ancestral knowledge, ancient secrets revealed telekinetic force and creation
and destruction of spirits through telekinetics. This is four hundred and
fifty dollars. Okay,
I am going to make a tactical move. Okay, all right, because I know where
this came from. This is on eBay. They have a section called metaphysical. Yes, and
which is an amazing discovery. I had no idea that they had a metaphysical
section and I scrolled through the metaphysical section and they were
exorbitantly priced, I would say. A lot of items like this. So you already said
four fifty. I'm off. I don't know exactly what the price was. I know it's going to
be high. I will say four hundred and fifty one dollars. Wow, okay. And we need
to we need to take turns with first bids because this is I'm I'm tricking you
every time yeah yeah, I pretty much I'm winning for so Caleb, your cheating
strategy has paid off. Yes, this price is fourteen hundred dollars, yes for
basically every power available in the world. It seems like an amazing deal
also so guys, this is my last item. This next one, okay, this is a domain name
mister dapper dot com premium domain name from my things to sale twenty four
seven, you can buy the domain name MrDapper.com. What do you think it is
worth to have a website called MrDapper.com? Okay, so I have to guess
first this time. I will say MrDapper.com is going to be
$7,000. Okay. Okay. Well,
I'm gonna say 7,001 because of free local pickup.
Okay, it has free local pickup, so it's definitely around there or this could be
you know what I'm going to say actually
I'm locking in at one million really okay, Patrick
eleven million dollars,
eleven million three hundred and twenty nine thousand two hundred dollars.
My God,
you won with a million dollar guess.
Wow, it's too good of a sight. You guys think Mr. Dapper dot com is worth
eleven point three million. Absolutely. You create a streaming service with
for sure, with all kinds of just movies for dapper men. Make your money back
that one. Every Hitchcock movie on Mr. Dapper, every James Bond on Mr. Dapper. Oh my god.
Or it could be like Mr. Skin and it's a website of just guys looking good in movies. Yeah.
Guys looking smart. Every time that an actor wore a suit in a movie. It tells you what
suit they're wearing. Yeah, I think that's a good idea. Okay, so Mr. Dapper.com was much
much more expensive than I thought. All right. Well, here is my oh my God, I'm
being past the what is this?
Okay, all right. I have the I have them out now. I had no which one is which now
my first item is from Timu. Okay, and this is a political item
brother for a Trump 2024 hat
a trump 2024 had a truck. Trump Trump Trump America back. Okay, who's guessing
first? Well, okay, this is the lowest price ever. Okay, I want to let you know
that already the lowest price ever
and it is on sale. If it's on Timu, I'm gonna say
August first three twenty nine. Okay, three twenty nine. Really? Three dollars
twenty nine cents.
you know I'm going to go. I know that Miss Prince can often fetch a huge
price tag on the reason on the secondary market. I'm going to go four dollars
Cameron,
okay,
it is two dollars. Seventy nine. Oh, so Caleb also, why didn't you give me a
buzz? Oh, you both get a buzz. I don't know the rules really. I think it's
line going over yeah, but I went over over yes. So Cameron loses,
because he went more over.
Get a point, neither of you get a point, but you can also pay six six
sixty nine cents and for yes,
what I almost did
after pay on the trip. I'm at and again, this is I mean this is a good
deal. This is going to make a lot of money. Why the fuck have you not
bought this two dollars? It's still up. Okay, you're buying this. All right,
I'll buy it. Trump 2024. All right. What else? Yeah. All right. This next one.
This is a shirt from the same website. Whoa, wait, this is a swag out. This is a
very, very cool shirt.
Now, I want you guys to guess based on this. This is the title of the item.
Funny Golden Chain Monkey 3D graphic print men's novelty shirt, sleeve shirt,
crew neck T shirt, summer outdoor.
and this is the photo of the item is this guy. This is a guy. Yeah,
it's kind of rich. He does seem to bracelets. He's got those are those
are
those are that bracelet on the right is a seasick one. Yeah, so he probably
owns a yacht. Oh, yeah, good point. You know, I'm gonna go with
is it on sale? Can we know that it's not on sale? It's not on sale.
I'm gonna go with 6 49 6 49 6 dollars for it's a team. Oh yeah,
yeah six forty nine okay. I'm gonna go
one dollar
one dollar. That is a really safe guess for Timu. I guess if I line dollar
Caleb
my God
wait. I was closer. Oh,
it is seven fifty nine. Wow God damn it, man. That's it. I might buy this. I
so yeah. My next item was from an auction website of Hollywood memorabilia.
Okay, cool. This is I am Sam
Dawson, Sean Penn, Red with Target name tag on the front uniform where it's the
target
Dawson War in I am Sam. That's an incredible being a member. Is this
auction over this auction? I will say is over. Oh, God, can you imagine hanging
this in your house like a jersey
and I do want to say one. They should retire at a target. They
should you can't have
that's retired.
You have to be careful when you're saying that
Sam for my Sam is retired.
What
I will I will give you this piece of information. Okay,
it was not sold and the bidding is over, so we can still contact this
private seller. You can contact this private seller. Yes, and this is we're
guessing the starting bid or the because it was not sold me. There was there was
one high. You're guessing the highest bid. Okay, how was it not? Yeah, how was
it? Not? I don't know. I don't know. They probably the reserve price. Yeah,
probably. Okay. Okay. Does it say what the reserve price is? Yeah, it says it
says what the high bid was. So guess the high bid. So he doesn't know what a
reserve price is. No, I don't know. We shouldn't hear the reserve price. I feel
like no. Okay, the highest bid for this.
It's going to be kind of low. I feel like if it's if it didn't meet the
reserve. So I'm going to say three hundred and fifty dollars. Okay, three fifty and locking
in and twenty five cents. Okay. Damn, you know, I'm going to try and undercut here.
I'm going to go two hundred dollars. I'm feeling I'm feeling the two hundred two hundred. You
want to lock in. I want to I would like to lock in two hundred dollars. You're both locked
in target. I'm locked in three hundred and twenty five cents, two hundred
dollars and one cent. Well, you guys
to both to both of you. No way. Both of you. It was one hundred dollars.
No one really wanted this. No one wanted this bad enough. I bet three. I bet
two hundred was the reserve. I mean, I would have paid that. No question. Yeah,
that's crazy. But this is that's the other thing. You could just get this
anywhere. What no, not one that you want on one body. That's true yeah and has
a stink. Well, all right, well, we'll just move on to the next one. He's been
all over the world. He smells like every food. That's true. He was in Iraq.
Yeah, during the war, he him aware of some reason it's walking around. You're
smelling all sorts of amazing spices. Exactly. Had in your kitchen, I mean you
also you wear this out out and about to go. Oh my God, from I am Sam, you don't
you don't have it on the shirt. Well, yeah, I have that at home.
I am Sam. Yes. Oh, what a great costume.
All right, this next one is from ebay. This is life size jack sparrow bus
statue, johnny depp prop pirates movie amber one to one. Now, why does it say
amber ready?
Thirteen thousand thirteen thousand no three thousand three thousand. That's a
huge swing. That is a huge swing. That's a massive. Let's split the difference
eight thousand okay.
I this looks really good. If I just saw this picture, if I didn't get the
description,
I would go crazy high on this and the reason is because it looks like a
mission impossible to mask yeah yeah that maybe I could put it on and I could
walk around and people might think I'm depp, but
I can't. I have a head already. I can't put this on top of my head and walk
around and be a depp. I mean I get, but then I have it all depp, but then
people know his body. I know he's tall. He's not that tall. He doesn't have a
long neck, long head, head, thickness, torso. I am gonna say
I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say $1800 and $75 as well. 1800 and you were
I feel like there's no way I'm right. What was your 8000? 8000, 1500, 1700.
I think I have to have gone over, I think.
Oh my God, it was ten thousand nine hundred thirteen thousand would have
been too much. Yeah, I felt it course through me. I felt Johnny Depp spirit
that in my body, the curse of the black Pearl. Oh my God, went to
have this from Zinga. You had this from Zinga worldwide. Yeah, I see. Yeah.
All right, this next, this is another thing from eBay. This is
Bill Cosby signed Academy Awards, eleven by fourteen photo JSA. Okay, I bid
first right yeah here's what I would pay for this zero. My guess is zero you're
gonna lock in a zero zero okay one cent okay. I do one cent one cent and two
cents. You know what I'm standing on my principles, so I'm fine with losing. I'm
sitting on business. Okay, well, Cameron was closest
the serial rapist
but some people I mean some people are in stuff like that Jeffrey Dahmer and
Kemper Bill,
Cosby
yeah, they're all one in the same nowadays. I think he's trying to think
of the other guy. I can't remember his name. Well, while you're thinking about
that, the people have tons of Freddy, Freddy Krueger hand and so people buy
this shit all the time. Ted Bundy. Oh yeah, all right, while you're thinking
of the or will you already so I can plankton this next item
seven and one sixteenths inches mega monster. That's a record size museum
fossil teeth. Is it is it confirmed to be? Yeah, do we know if it's a replica?
I will say right now that this is from New York Island fossils. Okay, so
probably probably real. I mean these are expensive. I'm well, it's your guess
first. Yeah, okay, well, why don't you just say what yours is first just to
okay one dollar. Oh, okay, you know I'll probably go two hundred and fifty
thousand dollars and half of a cent two hundred two hundred fifty. Really? It's
big man. It's a fossil. I mean, I
yeah, you know what? I already said it. I guess you alright to fifty. I'm going to
go eleven hundred dollars eleven. Oh really? Yeah, I'm going to go eleven
hundred. Wow. Well,
Caleb,
you were closer. It is twenty thousand dollars.
That makes sense. Yeah, very expensive. That does make sense. I guess I was
thinking you have no respect for ancient things. Well, you know what I'm thinking
because I'm thinking of a great white shark tooth, but you know what the thing
about that is it's not extinct. There's a lot of those around. That was kind of
my reference point in my head, but I guess it makes a lot more sense for
something that you did seventy five million years.
Well, speaking of ancient things, your mom
well, speaking of ancient things, you ask
should I go with
Should I go with the bid or the buy it now for this one?
Let's do buy it now.
This is worn very smelly shoes comfy brown so soft.
Okay, I would like to say this is a pair of UGG slippers it looks like that have a
fully matted back where they've been worn.
Very smelly comfy brown so soft.
These are dads.
Yes, these are daddies.
These are dads that he got for Christmas twelve years ago.
And he's been stinking them up every time he gets them.
These are the football shoes.
But these are puffy brown so soft.
Yeah, and I bet they are soft because they're very worn in.
I'm going to say
very smelly.
Why would they add that?
And so here's my question.
It's a bid too. It's a bid. It's an auction.
Yeah. Are we doing buy it now?
Oh yeah, we're doing buy it now.
So the very smelly makes me wonder, is that
does that make the price lower or is it making it higher?
I think it makes it higher.
Yeah, makes it higher.
Because they wouldn't. You're right.
Because they're trying to get their money.
Money's worth.
They're not going to add to something like that if it devalues it.
Right.
So very smelly. I'm going to say that this is $75. And wait, is it just one
shoot? No, it's two shoes. Well, from the picture, I'm guessing it's one
shoe. But it's a shoes. Okay, I'm gonna go. You did
75. You're locked in. I'm locking. I'm gonna go $30. $30.
That's your final. No, you know what? I'm gonna I'm gonna gamble that you
are just gonna blow out and go over. I'm gonna fuck. I'm gonna go $10 and
just try and get under $10. Yeah,
one dollar. Cameron, you already locked in ten ten dollars.
It is twenty dollars. Buy it now. Yep. By Gamer sixty nine.
And what can you just send me the link for this one? Just like a very early
because I feel like you. Yeah, just to make sure. I mean, it is a pretty
reasonable price. Four dollars and twenty eight cents. You can clean the
smell off. Yeah. Well, I don't somehow I feel like the people buying this are not
buying it and I can clean the smell off and they'll be like new.
it saves the money buying already smelly shoes, very, very smelly. These are
comfy brown shoes. They're comfy brown. So soft. Yeah, yeah, yeah, comfy brown.
So soft. Yeah, they're trying to flip shoes. Yeah, I have
oh this one. I can just get rid of okay. So
skip that. Yeah, we'll skip it when we get to it, but I'll just show it to you
because I liked it. How many items do you have? You I have you tell me how I
I knew the shopaholic was going to have the most items.
I have four items.
Okay, this next item I went to Facebook Marketplace to find.
Oh, good.
This is men's jockstrap.
Oh, a leather one.
And you can tell from the photos that this has been worn and washed.
Used men's jockstrap.
$35.12.7.
Now, remember this is on Marketplace where people like to use round figures.
Okay, free.
interesting men jock strap free is actually a strong guess. It is. I will
say I mean if are you locking in for you all looking for okay, then I do one
cent.
Well, it's just more likely to be free than one cent, but it is probably right.
Well, I think it's fifty fifty. I don't I don't I don't it would be a nice
trick, but I don't think it's trying to I don't think it was. No, I'm not
trying to trick because this cost money. Well, yeah, I mean, I'll give you a hint.
It cost money.
I probably shouldn't guess free then no, but it's too late. You already did.
I mean, I respect the honor of the game. I like that and you did one cent.
Caleb
fifteen dollars and available to deliver if local. Fifth size. Small to medium.
That's what you're really paying for. That's not even necessarily what you're
paying for. That is what the actual item that you're buying is. This guy shows up
with it. Oh crap. I wore it to come deliver it. Well, it's like I got to take
this thing off.
this next one. I'll try to like burn through. We'll just kind of burn
through lightning around lightning around. No, because these are cleaning
be good. Okay. I don't have these are cleaning burns through it and I'm
like no,
that means go. Yeah, we'll do it. We'll do it. Well, this is beans cleaning
beans. These blessed beans are used to clean energy and given to Mother Earth
cleaning bit. This is bird seed. This is fully bird. Okay, I'm seeing so this
I this is a bowl of dried beans. I'm seeing Lima. Yeah, I'm seeing kidney.
I'm seeing black eyed pea and I'm seeing some black beans
and you're seeing some hands blessing the beans. It looks like which is that's
worth a lot. I would say this is this can't be more than than a dollar fifty
worth of beans that are okay. A dollar fifty worth of beans. You're going to
lock in at a dollar. I'm going to say a dollar fifty of beans. Okay, no,
Cameron, what about you? You're forgetting the blessing. Yeah, they're
lessen part of the list. I'm atheistic. I don't believe in this kind of blit. I
don't believe in anything good. Five dollars
because I think it's going to be more than that, but I don't want to put you
were closer at these are ten dollars. I was going to guess ten dollars and I was
like I don't want to go over. So I guess five and said because you went so well.
We need to see a bullseye. I could have gotten a bullseye right there man. Ten
dollars was in my head, but I wouldn't I would have only done. I would have done
ten dollars. You had done five. Yeah, all right, well, this next listing will
just we'll skip it, but my wife says no more. My wife says you are your guitars
must go to different
yeah. How much is the price? One of them I was going to have you guess the price
of each of them and a jubilee. Can you just get rid of the text boxes over the
prices here
because they are different for an interview? You can all right well, then
this next one I need to see this next. We'll go to the next one
next one. Whoa! This is podcast about list world domination t shirt from Wendy
premium. Okay. And Wendy premium says and I don't know if this is a
review or if this is the description of the item.
A total of 45 prosecution witnesses were called to present evidence
against Kelly with many of his victims including the podcast about
list world domination shirt.
Moreover, I love this singer Aaliyah who married Kelly in 1994 when
he was 27 and she was 15 identified as Jane does accusations of
engaging in sex acts with women under the age of consent followed
R Kelly for decades, but it took the meet to revolution in the broadcast of
the twenty nineteen documentary say surviving R Kelly for Kelly's long
standing wow blah blah blah blah blah. So the description of the podcast
about list world domination t shirt on Wendy premium speaks about our
Kelly. It's the area.
It's the nearly our tour shirt from two years ago is one of the many
called to that was was one of the victims of our Kelly was called to the
witness stand. How much do you think
I do you think that that would raise or lower the price of this? I mean this
has to be a collector's that well, first of all, it's out of print. We don't
make this anymore. I don't think we actually ever made it as a hoodie. Yeah,
so
I'm first. I think I'm first. Yeah, you're first. Yeah, I mean you can go
first if you want though. No, I'm gonna, I will say it is on sale and it's
a hoodie and it's on sale. Yeah, okay, twenty bucks,
twenty bucks. Even I say eleven ninety nine. Okay, Caleb, you are closer.
It is twenty two ninety nine.
so he said, so I'm closer Cameron's close.
He said you looked at me, looked away from me, looked at cameras at Caleb,
you are close. I got your names mixed up also. I love the Wendy logo right
there. That's a beautiful logo. I wish we could zoom in on that. It reminds me
of it's the Wendy's logo without an S guys. It completely is well. Now this
is my final item okay, and these are called jelly boy.
Jelly Boy G.
And these are all over print jeans.
All over print jeans.
Can you describe them to me?
Yeah.
Now they have- can you go ahead for one slide?
So there is an Oliver on the waistband.
It says Jelly Boy.
On the waistband it says Jelly Boy.
On the front of the pants on the left leg, it is a photo of a very
handsome young man holding a flute of wine, champagne, and Cameron Fetter and
on the butt it says jelly on one
now. I
also they were found these also yeah they were designed in Italy.
Shelly
jeans designs in Italy. Okay, and I want you to guess how I mean Italy should
tell you that you know the I just saw Bowser walk by, by the way, guys, don't
tell me that one hundred percent to saw a person walk by with a Bowser show on
their back. Oh, my God,
well, just remember Italy Milan, the capital of fashion. These are high
high fashion pants, so just think about that.
Also, the
wait the jelly boy design, the jelly boy design these yes and think also about
the licensing fee that went into these for the appearance of
celebrities, celebrities on the jeans, so that will have to be baked into the
price and the fact to make jeans, make them jeans that look exactly like
sweatpants. That is very
yes, look and feel exactly like sweatpants yeah. Okay, so for the jelly
boy jeans. I'm
a
God, this one's tough because whoever posted this really could have put in.
I will say
a thousand dollars, a thousand dollars, okay, okay, I'm going to met a game you
here. I'm looking at this listing. I'm looking at the length of the block
that's covering the dollar. I don't think a thousand dollars is fitting there.
I'm going to put in a hundred dollars as my guess.
because I think that this could be. I think this is three digits of decimal
point. Well,
Cameron,
no way hundred and fifty dollars. I thought that it was going to be. I
thought you were. He got him on the no. They're moderately priced for what they
are. I mean, these are jelly boy jeans. What website are these on? He's on
Seaspring.com. So these are available to buy. Jelly Boy jeans. Okay. Oh, you can
buy those. You can buy Jelly Boy jeans.
I could have had you in it, man. All right.
Well, that's a different product altogether. That's Ass Jelly, the
t-shirt.
Ass Jelly and Seaspring. All right, pull up Caleb's slides here. All right,
here's mine. Do we want to slide this all the way over here? Yeah, you can
slide this over for Caleb. Okay. Okay, so this is the ding. This is the
All right, all right, I'm ready. This is dirty. Okay, this first one is on
offer up. Have you ever used? Yeah, yeah, this is dirty sock. Okay, so some
things that this is a picture of a sock that's being held against a subway tile
like bathroom. Yeah, condition is new, even though it is a dirty sock and this
is in Queens, New York City. So we can buy this supposed to buy Angel Rodriguez.
the brand is quick silver size. A point five. How much do you think the dirty
sock is? Who's first?
I can go first and I'm gonna say that this is
I'm gonna say like fifteen dollars is one sock. If it was two socks, it is one
sock. If it was two socks, I would have said twenty five. Okay, you lock that in
for me? Yes, I'm gonna lock that in. It's three dollar bill y'all. Okay. Three
dollar bill. Cameron, you.
you
you got close.
Nine hundred ninety nine thousand nine hundred and ninety nine dollars.
You didn't tell us it was on sale. That would have chased my whole
answer.
Guys, the description, the price has dropped from one mil to nine hundred
ninety nine thousand nine hundred and ninety nine dollars.
That's a big deal.
Okay, this next one is
the awesome. Go to the next one, please. All right, so I'm just going to
show this to you a couple slides.
I know what this is.
No, you don't.
there's no way you know what this is. I can tell it's a suit.
Okay, so wait, I just wanna get guesses about what this is and I
will slowly reveal what this is, and I'll explain this. This is a
some kind of image of... It looks almost computerized image of Dwayne
Wade wearing a Miami Heat jersey, okay? And it doesn't really look like
him, his neck is a little too skinny. Yeah, it doesn't look like Dwayne
Wade at all. It does a little... Or no, sorry, Ray Allen. Oh,
Okay, yeah. So this is like a Ray Allen Miami Heat era corner three crazy shot
to win the championship era. Ray Allen. He's got a basketball. He's sitting
there. Yeah, he looks a little, a little computer. Now, I have to say,
I think, I think, I think Patrick kind of poison the well a little bit and
I'm looking at this and I really am just seeing latex, latex covering latex
covering latex. Alright, can you go to the next slide?
so now this is an action. Okay, no, this is this is an action. Okay, this is a
real doll. Could be also this could be a real doll or this could be a three D
model.
That's a good point. I could see that because I saw a couple of those people
selling those all right. I would like you to go to the next slide.
Okay, guys, he's naked and he's showing his butt. It's the same guy that he's
looking back still holding the basketball naked and showing his butt
cheeks. Okay, so now next slide. It was on YouTube. So this is, of course,
Iron Tech Sex Dolls, gay male realistic TPE full body life size love toy for
women. I don't think that a woman is buying this. Well, it says gay male.
Well, there is it in both. Yeah, 13 people are watching this item. This is
in high demand. Okay, well, you kind of also screwed up here by showing six
months for 99. No, it says that on every eBay. Oh, okay, never mind. It's on
ninety nine, so we know it's more than ninety nine dollars, but we could
assume that yeah, I think I think it's all right.
I'm gonna hit this with I'm just and I kind of just trying to let these fly
from the hip nine thousand dollars. I think nine thousand USD okay, I'm gonna
go lower. I'm gonna say twelve hundred USD really
Patrick. You are pretty damn close. This is it's almost like you've looked at
this before. This is
this is thirteen hundred and ninety nine. You are two hundred bucks off man.
that is you see very familiar with this world
that is impressive. Okay, I need to see this thing and I need to see it in
action. This is clearly a
rendering of it. Yeah, I don't think it's got to be a real photos like that
can't be real. Okay, I'm willing to bet this is made to order and nobody has
bought one yet. Yeah,
let's do it.
Next slide do it. Okay, so this is a doll. This is a doll with it has very
legs and very short arm. And this is a haunted one. You went on metaphysical. I
did go on metaphysical. Okay next slide item description from seller. Next slide.
The doll has been in my family its whole life. I brought it back from Germany when
my Oma passed. And the next one. Thanks for looking there is a trap soul inside.
Okay so this is a haunted doll, active, possessed, brought from
Germany, Hildegard. That's her name.
Maybe go to the next slide. So how much do you guys think this one is?
$450.
Okay, I'm going to go $13,000.
$13,000.
$12,000.
$1,000.
What did you say?
$450.
And you said what?
$700.
Cameron?
You won, but you are far off. This is $11,000.
Oh my God, that's almost the exact same price as the Johnny Depp one.
so you have a you have two choices you can make on this ebay yeah is do i want
a haunted doll right right with a trap so okay i got i got my christmas bonus
i've got twelve thousand dollars eleven thousand dollars to spend on one item
yeah what do i want well i got i got an ebay gift card yeah okay this is a very
thousand where it is a very different thing now go to the next one i went all
kind of dolls and stuff and figures and all this shit yeah you have an
interesting doll so say what this is elmo it's it's a tickle me elmo doll
Okay, so next slide. This is actually a authentic haunted doll, extremely
active, real Elmo demon Astaroth attachment. Oh, the demon Astaroth is
attached. Astaroth has been attached. Astaroth is a powerful demon. There's a
video on this where the guy talks to the Elmo doll. I forgot to add it, but
on the listing, he has a YouTube short where he talks to the Elmo doll, makes
the Elmo turn on a light bulb. Whoa! Tell me that isn't freaking your brain.
it's extremely power. That is scary. So guess is on this haunted Elmo.
Check this out six hundred and sixty six dollars and sixty six cents. That's a
strong. Yeah, that is a strong guess. Well, I'm gonna go nine hundred and
ninety nine dollars and ninety nine cents.
Patrick
Cameron
this is a deal for ninety nine.
That's kind of a good deal. Yeah, I mean, Asterod is one of the major
demons. You get the whole demon, you get the whole thing. It's trapped. It's
attached. I mean that's a demon that I feel like that's like that's a
celebrity. Most of the demons that get attached to stuff. I feel like
typically you want they don't have a name you or you wouldn't know their
names. It's like you know it's like oh, I hung out with Jeff at a party
exactly as a real, but I hung out with miles teller at a party the other
night.
How much of the party cost and I have one last one guys. This is again. I
kind of want you to guess what this is. This is a text from Jesus Christ that
is I'm coming soon. Are you ready on an iPhone and it's noon o'clock and the
phone is charged and it's being held by a woman? Yeah, there's an iPhone three or
four, by the way, but it's not actually a phone. It is an image. It's an image of
well, yeah, it's on the TV, by the way, and this is a this is a book.
I think that this could be
text from Jesus Christ, like you're like paying to first Jesus Christ to text
somebody. You think it's a service? Yeah, I think it could be a service, like kind
like a face time with Santa service slide guys. This is Christian NFT digital
art. Oh
what the fuck oh the employee anti Christ, oh my God,
oh my God,
as soon as I say I'm coming soon. Are you ready? A picture of me fell off the
wall
right after we're talking about Astor on. Oh my God, my God, that is scary.
last. I wish we had that on tape. I wish we had that was that in the corner.
It is not here anymore man. That is I do not like that's crazy. It was me
something bad is going to my to me. I do know this blood results or these are
going to be bad. Oh, my God, you're going to have different blood. I don't
want to say Jesus anymore. Yeah, why please Jesus? No, you want to say his
name to cast out the demon. Yeah, Jesus save
Okay, so save how much you think this Christian digital NFT art is
1 million dollars, 2 million.
That's a little over guys.
A little bit over. I didn't lock in. I'm gonna say 1,000. No, you already said,
you already said a million, you already said 2 million. Okay. You're both.
So wrong. This is a steal, $10,000 for this photo. You could have that in
your Solana wallet today for $10,000 guys. And that's gonna be worth a lot
lot of money in the future when Jesus comes when he actually comes back,
people are going to say I he actually texted me. He actually texted me an
nft, but I think that's an amazing art and this guy has a bunch of different
Christian nfts. If you want to go check those out yeah, well, I don't remember
who won Julio. Were you keeping track? You had to have yes, okay, who wanted
wait, wait, wait, do this score. Let's say third place here. Let me let me give
me a second. I was in third place.
All right, give it give it to me. Let's fly up like Mario party third. Who is
third place. Third place, with five points, Patrick.
Bruh. Okay.
And second place, with six points, Mr. Caleb.
And our winner. Who's the winner?
Our winner, with eight points.
Oh, that's a massive leap.
Cameron Fetter.
Congratulations,
well played. I can't turn this off.
Congratulations, Jelly Boy. All right,
so
go get the Jelly Boy pants on T spring. Wait, did you do that on your personal
T spring? I think so, yes. Okay, just search Jelly Boy jeans, but don't buy
them, just look at them. Just look at them. Unless you really want Jelly Boy
Swag poop dot com slash shows guys. We're coming to Boston to Atlanta to
Philadelphia to Toronto to Chicago to Minneapolis to Detroit and to Carborough
North Carolina guys. We're doing sketch comedy. We're showing videos. We're
doing a live podcast in Detroit. We're going to do a full eight mile thing of
some kind everybody in the two one three put your mother fucking three one
three put your everyone in the two one three put your motherfucking hands up
and three one three and then that's three one three. Yeah. Yeah. Where's
three two one three. I have no idea that's got a series. Where's the three
one there two one three. Where's the three one two one three that doesn't
but guys buy your tickets. It's going to be incredible. It's going to be so
much fun and the shareholder meeting this month. If you are subscribed to the
page around at the executive producer tier, you can join the shareholder
meeting on three our telephone area codes in the North American three twenty
three. We don't care about three. This is nothing. You did it wrong. You did
it. This is nothing. It's two north north nor Cal. Okay, patreon.com slash
podcast about list. You can subscribe and you can join the shareholder meetings on
the $15 tier on discord and this month's shareholder meeting is on leap day itself
February 29th and I think at 6 PM. I don't think we decided a time, but I
think usually 6 PM. I think that's a Thursday. I'm pretty sure so go sub to
that and you can of course get premium episodes on there for only $5 a month.
There's a huge backlog and it's fucking fire and swag and I think I'm probably
going to have lunch pretty soon. Yeah, I'm very hungry. You're getting a call.
All right, let's do some lunch. All right. Happy birthday later to anyone
whose birthday it is.
Anything is on the tape. You had a dinner conversation. Oh, yeah, I'll
talk about it. O's steak. Well, besides the foodie asparagus, spare
side of the food, Sam. Well, not the lemon, not just like candles and
the all that kind of lemon.
Lemon, then you don't eat a lemon at dinner. You put lemon on. I call
lemon limb. Well that's what you call lime. Must be a regional thing. Really? You call
lime lime? You're not even saving a syllable there. What about salt? Sal. Pepper is pep?
Pep. Okay. I've heard pep before. What do you call ketchup? Chup. Chup is good. I like
What do you call mayonnaise?
Mayo.
He came up with that one.
That's universal.
What do you call mustard?
Don't say it.
I know what you're going for.
I actually call it M.T.
Two syllables.
Yo, pass the M.T.
What do you call sauerkraut?
Oh, that's tough because I can't call it sour
because that's what I call sour candy.
is
has passed though that they're like that it's like all right we've had our fun
with Germans yeah I think you're saying it's time to forgive and forget the
whole no no no no again it is a confusion situation but even enough time
has passed not to forgive and forget but to stop calling the crowd time has passed
is a crazy thing this not even a hundred years man all right well once we hit the
hundred years I guess we can stop calling them crowds and stuff.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[no audio]