you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
you're a crap monster
I started recording it, say it again
I didn't catch the first half of what you said, say it again
I'm doing the new theme song
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Friendship will win ♪
- All right, okay.
- That's it?
- And then the English version is like,
♪ When you know that you're alone ♪
♪ And there is nowhere left to hide ♪
♪ Then you have to call your friends ♪
and you guys will always ride and rhymes in English. It doesn't rhyme in Japanese, it
only rhymes in English. And you have two friends and yourself and you look at lists, podcasts
about lists, friendship will prevail.
So when translates to prevail?
Yeah, I'm Japanese. Yeah, so it's easy for me to translate stuff like that. Okay, so
To be Japanese, I tweeted this, but I have to just get it out another way, too. But there's
the art gallery I work at today. There was like a bald, older white dude with a very young Asian
woman as his date. It was clearly like a first date. And he just was dragging her around all the
stuff in the art gallery and then went up to a photo of a horseshoe crab and just pointed it out
and he was like, "Do you like cooking these?" And she was like, "I don't know. I don't know what you..."
And he was like, "Cooking? Like a restaurant? Restaurant!" And then he like started like
pretending to eat something with his hand and he's like, "Restaurant!" And then they just gave up and
they left. Damn. Yeah, man. What museum do you work at? The Museum of Patrick's Mom.
I keep trying to get you to reveal it on the show.
I don't care. I work at the MIT Art Gallery.
Okay.
Doesn't mean anything to me.
Dom was asking today.
Oh, yeah.
If you want to go.
That's the answer.
She's like, "Oh, what museum does he work at?"
Yeah, well, let's go beat him up.
Somebody come visit me while I'm there.
I will not.
There's a guy who walks around the art gallery and he comes a lot apparently and he just he'll
spend like two hours there. It's a very small gallery.
Does he wear a brown suit?
no oh there's this guy when i i worked it when i worked no no no no no there's a reason i asked
no there was a guy when i worked at the clover in m.i.t uh-huh there was a guy who wore a brown suit
and gucci shoe like gucci sneakers and he had like a really bad comb over and i thought it must have
been him no no but he was a guy he would come in he would stand there in line and just go like
like coughing up shit. He ate a Neal hamburger in Vancouver? Yeah, basically, basically he was like
Neal hamburger but he was very clearly just like an MIT professor and he would he kept all of his
coins and his money like everything he ever owned in a plastic bag in like his breast pocket.
Breast? Mm-hmm. He had boobs? Yeah. Oh my god. That's why I was asking did you see his big
brown titties? Yeah, they're good. It must have been that guy. This guy, I don't know who else
He just walks around with a note, like a notepad, and he looks at every piece of text in the
gallery, like all the little plaques that say the name and like the artist and stuff, and
he just looks for typos.
See, that's why I thought this guy would be that guy.
And then he comes back.
What do you mean that's why?
He didn't say that yet.
Yeah, I know, but that, I mean, just shit.
Weird shit.
Yeah.
But he just apparently comes like once every couple weeks and tries to find all the typos
in the museum and then when he does he traps whatever the nearest woman working
is and just like just so you know there's a typo where you meant to say Chicago
but it says Chicago anyway what was your name my name's Paul and they'll just
talk for a while and then so his name was Paul huh the guy's name was Paul this
guy's not actually named Paul I was just guessing okay his name is Patrick no
yeah yeah my brother's name is Paul that's why I was saying now I'm gonna
bring the suit is my brother I don't like you lounging like this dude you
like fucking Julius he's in the trash dude you left the trash open the cats
are performing a heist on the trash from now on whenever someone starts to tell
me a story I'd be like oh shit did he wore a brown suit who's a guy wait wait
wait oh my god was it Paul with a brown suit who came into my work and he goes
And he was like, and wait, he had a plastic bag and he had a brown suit on and he had
big fat tits.
So was it that guy?
I'm trying to tell you the story of how I survived 9/11.
So okay, but he was in 9/11.
Yes, he was.
That's why I asked.
He was in both.
Oh my God, the cats are going absolutely insane.
This is the craziest thing.
Oh my God.
They're going insane.
Stay right there.
so cool going so great right now what did you did you give them cat nip no I don't
know what they've been do I think they got scared cuz I let you guys into the
house before me ah now they have like a bunch of adrenaline
andreana there was a guy on on doomsday preppers who said I who said I just got
a pulse of adrenaline pushing through me I mean I need to I need to get into that
show dig in.
It's so fucking funny dude.
I was watching it last night.
This whole episode is just going to be Patrick running around trying to stop his piss.
Yeah it's just me running to fucking make sure my cats don't do stupid shit.
Just put them in the cat room.
I don't want, no, they'll sit there and like ruin the carpet.
Alright, yeah right.
That's a fair point.
*gibberish*
Um.
*laughter*
Oh my god.
Patrick.
Fucking christ dude.
(laughter)
- Oh my God.
Patrick--
- Smoking, Christ, dude.
- Patrick threw a crumpled up McDonald's bag
and the cat jumped and knocked over a pile of books
into their water fountain.
- Yeah, Patrick has a giant water fountain,
a giant Roman water fountain in the middle of his house.
- I live in luxury.
- Yeah, you do.
Yeah, unemployed Patrick with a giant marble fountain.
- I can't sell it.
- I made enough to get the fountain
and then that's all I needed.
- Yeah, so I quit.
- So I quit my job.
I would get a baller ass fountain and give all those like little cherub kids big fat dicks on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, because it'd be like they're not babies now. They're just-
Well, they are a thousand years old.
They're little people. That would be the big change. I would change the proportions.
I'd give all the kids beards so once you see their huge penises, it's not weird.
Exactly. It's not a kid with a huge penis. It's clearly a man.
In some culture, it's like good luck to have like those little cherubs like peeing.
It's good luck to suck a small penis of a child.
To have them like peeing, right?
I have no idea.
Because there's one restaurant that I would go to in Harvard Square that had this like a shit ton of like little cherub fountain statues.
Like everywhere in the store, just like every service and they're all holding their dick peeing.
Was this place very lucky?
No, it was the waffle place.
The Waffle Place had a bunch of Babies Wieners?
Yeah, pretty crazy.
Probably some kind of signal.
To the other Waffle fans.
It's a pedophile cabal thing.
Yeah, pedophile Waffle.
Patrick and I had a fun experience on the train today.
We got on the train and a guy was blasting music out of his speaker.
He was playing an IDM remix of Gucci Gang.
It was awesome.
When you say speaker was it like a giant like a JBL, JBL kill.
Gotcha.
But it was extremely loud and when we got on this old Asian guy was sitting next to him
on his phone and then we sat down and like the train started moving and the guy like
leaned over to the old Asian guy and went, "Who the fuck are you texting?
Who the fuck are you texting?"
And then the guy just got up and walked like to another car.
It's funny that-
and started running up and down the train car and swinging on the poles and then
he was like dancing around he went I am having a shit ton of fun right now and
then he got off the train. It's funny that that people like train people have
figured out that they can just do stuff like that with impunity because and
nobody wants to deal with it. Yeah nobody will ever say anything to you. People just like people just
want to just get home so bad that they will take so much abuse on it on public
transportation before they snap. Yeah, before they even do anything. Yeah, they'll
just ignore it. Yeah, they won't even look. Yeah, yeah. I would say when shit and piss gets
involved. Yeah, once you see like... That's a line. Once the guy starts
jacking off like... But see, jacking off I think I still, I think I probably just
move. I would kick the penis out of his hand. Yeah, kick it onto the floor.
And it turns into a snake and it slides away. It slides. Yeah, snakes slide.
That's it. Snakes always have to be going downhill or else they can't move.
That's so true. Because they're so slippery. This episode is just us
corralling these cats. Yeah, trying to block the cat from jumping onto the recorder and
stopping the episode. Just put them in the fucking oven. Just yeah, just do something to them.
Honestly. Well Yoda's fine right now. Yoda's chilling. He'd like to be boiled to death.
He's being a good guy. Can you give them a bath tonight? Sucks. You have to give them a
bath? Yeah. Look how fucking dirty they are. Do they get disgusting and stinky because they're
Look at them right now. They're fucking gross.
I mean, they don't look any more disgusting than they always look.
They always fucking look like aliens.
Yeah, but sometimes they look clean.
No, they don't.
He's sneaking around the other way trying to jump on the recorder.
You're not allowed to be my friend. I will never love you.
Why not?
Because he fucked up all the episodes, and apparently he's dirty.
Yeah, I can't be friends with something that's dirty.
Yeah, you suck, man.
He does not suck.
He does, dude.
No.
I'm gonna get him a present for Christmas, and then I'm gonna hand it over to him,
and then I'm gonna take it away at the last second.
Why? Because I just told you I hate them. You couldn't do that to Yoda. Look at him. I could.
I could do it to both of them at once. No. I could do anything. I'll take, I'll give the
present to one of them, take it away and give it to the other. Oh my god. Back off, cat.
Halt. Halt. And now you lick your penis? That's his leg. Damn. Oh, he went for it. Oh, there he
goes. Oh, he's trying. He's not flexible enough. Yeah, go over there. There's tons of, there's
dogs are right they went to play with the dog bring my dog over here and have them
eat your cats I'm gonna have you eat him in one bite and then and then I'm gonna
pull their skeletons out of his mouth don't don't do that I'm gonna bring my
tarantula over and it will scare your cats out of their skin yeah I'm gonna
bring Duke Nukem over here and I'm gonna sick him on your cats don't he's gonna
go Duke Nukem forever on your cats he's gonna throw a poop at my cats yeah he
seriously will yeah remember that and hit and they'll say I got a cat scratch
fever I'm throwing shit at a cat I'm gonna kill these two little cats don't
kill and then I'm gonna watch TV I love the Duke Nukem yeah I'm gonna vote for
Gary Johnson yeah they Duke Nukem is a big libertarian I'm learning he is yeah
Yeah dude, he's a real guy and he voted for Gary Johnson.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
You see, they're thumping from the other side.
I think it's the litter box, but I don't know what's going on.
They're playing in the litter box.
Abortion is a human right.
That's nice.
Wow, Duke.
Yeah.
Great.
Duke poop 'em.
Women make 77 cents for every dollar a man makes.
Black women make 63 cents for every dollar a man makes.
telling me that this country is just I like Duke Nukem now yeah he's super going
to keep yeah um aliens are real I put an alien in a bikini and I did he fucked it
yeah I'm in any and he's like if you order a flying Dutchman at in-n-out they
give you a burger without the bun. Thanks Duke Newcomb. There's a secret menu at
Chipotle you have to unlock. It's okay to be gay. Not. Duke you're confusing us. Taco
Bell has new vegetarian options. Taco Bell has a black bean gordita now. He's just doing ads in
between everyone like secret sauce is just mayonnaise and ketchup mixed
together fuck you you can ask the McDonald's employee to give you your
fillet of fish fresh you can yeah if you say yeah you say can I have it if you
say can I have it fresh off the boat mm-hmm yeah and they'll give it to you
well no cuz they leave them on the in the heat under the heat lamp all day uh-huh
The stars are out tonight for the Academy Awards.
Jennifer Lopez looks dazzling on the red carpet. Adam Sandler was robbed of a
nomination for Best Actor. The cast of Parasite is here. The cast of Parasite is
is Chinese. Duke, no! What? Am I wrong? Yes, they're Korean. What does that mean? Is that a kind of
Chinese? Well, yeah, I guess. But yeah. When it comes to condoms, put two on. Never fall asleep
There's your shoes on always watch your drink
Man I love college and I love drinking a
Milly a milly a
Million here a million there
He's doing the Asher Roth version because he can't say the day and night
the lonely
Seems to free his mind at night
He's all alone. Some things will never change
I need a Winn-Dixie grocery bag full of money right now to the VIP section.
Duke Nukem, you're surprising us in so many ways tonight, dude.
Baby girl, what's your name?
Let me let me talk to you. Let me buy you a drink. R. Kelly is innocent.
Just boys being boys.
Duke stop. Duke, that's enough.
You're telling me... Harvey Weinstein had a giant penis.
You're telling me Bill Cosby, America's dad, raped over 50 women over the course of 40 years?
Oscar Pastorius did nothing wrong.
Dylan and Eric will-
Yeah, I've never heard of Dylan.
Dylan and Eric will be at the E3 Awards this year.
Dylan and Eric are booth babes for Ubisoft.
Dylan and Eric Klebold are booth babes for Newegg.com.
Buy a trench coat to put on your computer.
There's a demon wearing my stepdad's skin and I'm going to strangle him at dinner.
There are reptilians who live.
My mom is a reptilian.
I saw her pussy and it was covered in scales.
I saw my mom's pussy.
Awesome.
That's my grade.
Aziz Ansari.
Your book about modern romance touched me in a way that I can't describe.
O.C. Zansari is Chinese.
Duke, no!
What?
Was he not in Parasite?
He has a sort of Chinese name.
I thought we were talking about Star Wars.
You're kind of going into like a Walter Cronkite thing.
Yeah?
Yeah, you sound good.
JFK has just been assassinated.
No he hasn't.
that was a long time ago. Did Walter Cronkite say that?
uh... no, Walter Cronkite said uh...
Jackie Kennedy
now that your husband is gone my number is.
Jackie Kennedy damn you have some big ass flappy titties.
You got some big ass sixties titties. When you bent over to grab the back of your
husband's skull off the back of the trunk of that car
by god we saw everything.
get out of your cat he's going to a station okay let's do this all right
dot ten reasons porn should be big it's just too fun to do do you know i can do
that
into that for a year
uh... so this is my here as duke nukem this is by inferno top ten years here
read this and read the description for this list of duke nukem voice
race uh...
porn is a video dot patrick
shot up
born is a video and movie of recorded sex many people will get addicted soon but
here is why porn is bad for you. I have addiction about porn, but I want to quit because how
I feel is that they hurt women and they don't respect them kindly.
This user is InfernoTopTenors. Damn. Nice anime, Avi. Yeah. RIP this account. Damn, the account
was dead. Duh, account gone. The account got dead. They made lists to cure their crippling
porn addiction. Yeah, yeah. And they lapsed. It's not an addiction to porn, it's an
addiction about porn. Yeah. So it's just reading about porn and thinking about it. I'm addicted about porn too.
Yeah. Number one is it's a disgrace to women. It's really women's fault. Yeah. The
whole thing, you know. They're the ones who are signing the contracts and saying
yes to all this bullshit, you know. So I blame them. They write it, they wrote all
of the the contracts in wingdings so the women couldn't read it. And girls are, and women
don't read things anyway. So they just looked, they saw that they, they're like,
"Okay, yeah, I'll sign this." Yeah, at the beginning they wrote, "And this is how a
sports car works." And then the women stopped reading it. And the carburetor goes, "Oh, geez."
Yeah, when you're using a charcoal grill and then that's how they started the
contract and just women just didn't read the rest. Yeah. Yeah. We should
write porn. Yeah, oh, that'd be a good thing to put on it, just a porn screenplay.
okay let's do that let's call it let's call it the fucking of Patrick yeah the
fucking the fucking and sucking of Patrick fucking his guy of all time no
it's like super Patrick the fucking really dramatic it's like a it's like a
pick a black and white picture of Patrick like looking up at the sky the
poster and you gotta get fucked cuz man it's obvious dude no it's obvious you
You're the baddest bee of all of us.
You're scaring him, stop.
I'm petting him.
He's scared of you.
Look, he's scared of you.
Why is he jumping on his penis then?
Why is he crawling over me and sitting on me and loving me like a father and friend?
Because he's scared of you.
I'm scared of you.
You're not scared of me.
I'm scared Cameron's going to blow up.
Do something rash.
I'll blow up.
Cameron's going to blow up.
Yeah, he's going to blow up.
He's going to press self-destruct on his penis.
He's going to blow up you like a blow up fuck doll in the porno that we're making.
And then he's gonna fuck you in your blow-up doll ass.
Do people like having sex with blow-up dolls?
Do they like fucking a balloon?
Yeah, or like an inflatable raft.
Or like a... I feel like it would be like less soft than a balloon even.
Yeah, it's like fucking a life jacket.
No, 'cause you know like the ends of like...
Like if you get like a floaty or something and then they have like the sealed part that's all like spiky.
You touch that with your butt?
Wouldn't that be inside of the vagina part of the inflatable doll?
No, they just put it somewhere else.
They just put water in there.
engineering. Yeah, but what if they forget? Samsung. I'm sure in the
expensive inflatable dolls, but I mean the $20 ones, you're finding
at Spencer's. I feel like you're better off like fucking like a
hole in a piece of furniture. Yeah. Let's be
real, the women that they paint on those dolls don't even look like... they don't
look very good. You know, they don't look beautiful. Yeah. So you might as well...
fuck the couch, which is infinitely more beautiful. I would rather fuck a couch
than a blow-up doll. Yeah. Now one of those really expensive... What about a blow-up couch?
A blow-up... Oh. Like an inflatable couch that you put in the pool. That's tough. Yeah, I wouldn't have
sex with that. You wouldn't have sex with that? No, because also there's no hole. And if you do
put a hole in it, then all of a sudden now you got a leak. What if it's an inflatable
couch that has a pussy. Uh yeah like it has a human pussy. You just float in the pool and lie on it
face down. It teaches you how to swim and fuck. Caleb you've been in the pool for like three hours
just face down on that floaty. Yeah your swim trunks pulled halfway down. What about it mom?
So I'm panning. Fuck you, maybe some Totino's. Put the pizza rolls in the pool. Put them on the
Put them in the pool, float them out to me.
Put them on the edge of the pool and turn around.
I'll get them.
But it is a girl's fault and it is a disgrace to women.
There are comments on here.
There are 20 comments on it.
You can click on the comments.
Men don't force women to do porn.
That's all up to the women.
Pork can also be a disgrace to men.
I don't think so.
If you're a man and you're in porn,
that means you usually have a big penis
or a really small penis. Yeah. You'd be like the Minion. Do you know about the Minion? No.
The Minion was this like series of videos that came out in like 2000 whatever. I think Dane Cook
had a bit about it. About the Minion? Yeah, the Minion was a very fat guy with a small penis who
would throw food in girls' faces. Whoa. It was big on e-fucked. That's sick. Yeah. E-fucked used to
be so good. Yeah, e-fucked sucks now. It does suck now. It got way worse. It's all just like... PC
culture ruined EFUX. It actually it went the other way kind of yeah I looked at it
maybe a couple months ago just goes like what's going on with this website.
That's the only place that has the Chuck Berry sex tape. Exactly yeah I actually think
that is why I was on EFUX. Yeah that's why I looked at it too. Yeah it's so funny but
all the videos are like dumb bitch gets fucked in the face and then beaten into
shit yeah and then sent back to Europe.
And I'm like that's not funny it used to be like guy guy accidentally farts while
having sex yeah and dressed as Bart Simpson yeah that's funny
it's like girl bleeds out her ass yeah yeah girl gets her pussy caved in with a
wrecking ball hmm okay wreck-it Ralph destroys Hulk smash fisting vagina
butthole Hulk hand up the butt yeah full stuff foam Hulk hand in a lady's ass
sound on she's just making Hulk sounds yeah this comment says porn she be ban
it's harms women from men and it keeps kid from porn here's a good comment
from Doro Explorer 13 it says and men you sexist I like this comment there is
something called porna - you know what is that oh that's porn for girls yeah
Yeah, porna.
Porna.
slut with big-ass boomies yeah damn she got big she has big boobs big booms big
boom slut boom what about boom what about do what about boob noob Kuhlman
boob Kuhlman and yeah any boob Kuhlman boob Kuhlman I like to have said I'm
I'm addicted to online poker.
I'm-
Big boom sluts.
[laughter]
He just does all the same things from before.
I'm-
I'm ten thousand dollars in debt to partypoker.net.
Amy Schumer is Chinese.
[laughter]
Dude, what are you talking about?
I've never seen a picture of her.
[laughter]
Duke Nukem doesn't know-
I just guessed, based on her voice.
Based on her voice and her name.
[laughter]
A-me.
I thought it was Amy Shumai. Duke Nukem is Chinese. Duke that's you. I am. I'm Boob
Koomin. I'm Boob Koomin. Isn't it Boom Koomin? No now it's Boob Koomin.
He likes to koom on some booms. He likes to koom on booms. He likes to kooms on some booms.
I like the cumen boobs.
That's boob cumen.
That's boob cumen like the spice.
Yeah.
Yeah, cumen.
Cumen.
That's how British people say it.
Really?
That makes sense they would say it that way.
They call it asparagus rocket.
They call it arugula rocket.
Arugula.
It's because it's too hard for them to say.
Oi.
Arugula.
a bunch of people are they are named arugula so yeah yeah and and we tell you
something about people in Britain they may not like arugula but they'll be a
rude to you if you ask where the where the closest American restaurant you ask
where Big Ben's yeah where's Big Bang put me in Big Bang put me in the fake
Big Ben is Chinese. It's a giant gong. I'm talking about Big Ben my cousin. He's Chinese.
My cousin married into the family. Yeah. He married my aunt as his mom. You're so stupid!
God damn you dude. Yeah marrying someone and be like can I become like your family's
cousin? Instead of being the brother-in-law can I be the cousin? Sure I don't think
there's any laws against that. Is there look can you just legally make somebody
like your cousin or your uncle? If you can adopt somebody can you also just like adopt
them as your cousin or uncle? Yeah yeah. Let's go down to the orphanage and try to see if we
we could all become cousins. Just walking up to some kid, "Hey, you're gonna be my uncle."
We should do it. I kinda wanna be a kid. Kid, you're my dad now and you have to go to work.
You have to feed me. Otherwise they put you in jail. We should do a nephew circle. Yeah.
We should go legally become each other. I don't wanna do a nephew circle. Yeah, we're gonna
do a nephew circle. I know exactly what I'm doing. The only nephew circle I wanna be in
is me my two closest friends and Snoop Dogg and he'd be calling yeah he says
what I do nephew what it do nephew mm-hmm and I go huh that's pretty cool
that's gangster Snoop Snoop dogs you are such a gangster Snoop that that is
gangsta Snoop at his gangster Snoop at gangsta Snoop Dogg and parody account
mmm ghetto Snoop Dogg yeah all right number two pop-ups might give a virus to
your computer. Well then, well that's the closest to a good reason we can get to
the on this list. Okay so I was looking up a car here listen okay so I was
looking up a cartoon image it had like no skin color in it so I thought it
wouldn't be dirty so I unblurred it only only that but now I keep seeing yeah
now I keep seeing porn on all the images I look up and I don't even look up
anything to do with the dirty stuff and I'm only 10 years old. It's in capital
with in there. What do you think that means? It had no skin color in it so I
didn't so I thought it wouldn't be dirty so I unblurred it. Probably they went on
rule 34 or something. Yeah. Ten-year-old and they're trying not to it.
They wanted their comment just so you guys know. Mom, look at what I said on the
top tens that's why it's in the history yeah on porn i like i keep seeing porn
on all the images i look up like everything you look at porn comes up
yeah there's a comment here another one from soldier of fortune
he keeps my man up and it says best reason
yes yeah pop-ups are uh i feel like pop-ups are kind of a relic of a time
that oh yeah you know everybody has ad
blocker now. I miss pop ups. I miss the congratulations. You won. I don't miss pop ups. Congratulations.
You won. They were fun though. Sometimes you get ones like. The ones with the games. Fuck
this horny fat guy. Slap the monkey. Oh slap the monkey was good. Warthog flip. Warthog
flip. Yeah. I've never seen that one. You never played warthog flip? Warthog flip. That
was one where. Oh where you tried to flip. Yeah. You tried to flip the halo warthog.
Yeah. With a grenade. Yes. I do know that one. I was thinking of like the animal. I was like
what could that possibly be? I played that too. That's a North Carolina classic game.
The warthog. Do you have warthogs in North Carolina?
Um, 30 to 50 feral hogs in North Carolina. Yes, dude. Yes! Woo!
No, there's um... Yeah! I think there is, there's wild boar, I think. Yeah, probably. Yeah. I don't
know. I don't, I don't even, is a warthog even a real thing? I think, I don't even know. It's the
one with the crazy nose. It's the one with the horns. Oh, the one with the big long nose. It's
It's Pumba.
It's an alligator.
Wait, then I don't know if it's real.
If it's Pumba.
That's true.
Pumba's a cartoon.
If I saw Pumba in real life, I'd shoot him in the face.
Warthogs are the most disgusting, creepy looking animals.
Why are you looking...
Warthog removal.
I'm gonna show you what they look like.
Damn, they do have a big fucked up nose.
They're really crazy looking.
They look like the Power Rangers villain.
Yeah, they do.
Yeah, they're pretty crazy.
They're like donkeys more than pigs.
Look at that.
The baby ones are pretty cute though.
Fucking skull looks disgusting.
Look at that. That's pretty cute.
Any baby is good.
Except baby Hitler.
And that's the only bad one?
If you think of someone really bad.
Baby shit.
Baby shit? Looks like Caleb likes baby shit.
Baby Hitler.
Hitler made out of poop.
Now that is the epicocity of what you just said is blowing my mind right now.
The idea that there would be a poop Hitler. Poopoo Hitler?
Mmmmm. I mean no. Ugh.
I don't want to sit here and make out with a version of Hitler made out of crap.
What are you talking about?
I have so much better stuff to do with my time.
I don't want to sit there and go to a movie with a kind of Hitler who's just made out of a bunch of just poop
and he has like a life and he has a mind and he can kiss me.
I don't want to kiss him in the middle of a movie.
I don't want to fuck a hole inside of like that I burrowed with my penis inside of a guy
made out of poop who looks like Adolf Hitler and has a little mustache.
You think poop Hitler poops skin?
I don't want to get all the skin, I don't want to be fucking poop Hitler in the ass.
And then he puts skin on my penis with his butthole and then I use that to wipe him down
after.
I don't want to do that man.
I think he does.
I don't.
I think he does want to do that.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to have two poo pitlers that I bring with me when I travel and they stay
in the hotel room and then I order them room service and then they, when I get back they
give me a freaking double blow job hand job.
I don't want to do that.
All right, number three, your brain could get a disorder.
I think that happened to me.
I think I watched too much porn when I was a kid and now I can't, I mean, Mario is crazy
to me.
There's a comment from Caleb on here.
What is it?
Caleb9000.
Oh my God, what?
It says, "This is Caleb from the future."
Yeah, no, your brain only gets disorders from birth, they aren't contagious.
So it goes against everything Caleb just said about his Mario disease.
future he learns that you can't you have to get it's Caleb 9000 years old yeah
the idea of me being 9000 years old is making me so sad that I can't even think
hmm yeah yeah I would not I wouldn't be able to do any of my favorite activities
and I would never yeah none of my favorite activities like number four you
will learn to hurt women no well I don't like hurting women you'd
skipped ahead I was about to read a comment okay I'd opened the comments I
I didn't see that.
If you want to watch too many plus, how is that a porn problem?
You should use a safe search and block it from enabling safe search for six months so problem
solved.
Did you guys ever have like a filter on your computer?
My uncle tried to set up one for my mom, but then I went on a website where I had to enter
in like my mom would have to come over and make sure that when I was really young, I
I was like 10 years old and she had to come over and like type in the password
every time I went to a new website but then like every time I think I went on
aim and every time that I went to send someone a message I was like mom come
here you need to you need to type in the password again so I had my mom do that
like ten times which is all your damn messages she would yeah she would read
what I was saying and then I did it so many times in one night that she shut it
off. So she let you just go free. Kids one, mom zero. Fuck you mom. Anytime I hear a story
with kids winning, I sing. I sing a song. I really hope that Howard Zinn writes a kids
history of the United States. That's from the perspective of the kids beating the parents.
Because you know history is so often written by the parents. We really need to get it from
perspective. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And he's going to town on his leg. The kid's guide to survival.
The kid's guide to survival. Yeah. Hide under a table. World War Kids. That's what the Nubo
Kids War 3. People think the new, well there's two other kids wars? Yeah, when did those
happen? Yeah, yeah. It was, they skipped the three. It was grounding and spanking for the
first two. That was what started those two. And then the third one, yeah you guessed it,
snack time. I thought snack time is good. Well, the kids war three was to make sure that we
get snack time. Oh yeah. The inalienable right of all kids, every kid to snack time. Exactly.
Yeah I heard if you don't bring snack you can get a graham cracker or an apple. I, have
I told you about my first grade teacher? Oh yeah, I got yelled at once for, because I
didn't know whether or not I had a snack in class. Damn. She had like a whole, she had
shit fit she like stood there in front of in front of the whole class was standing
there screaming at me do you have a snack yes or no do you have a snack and I was
like crying because I thought I was gonna get in trouble if I said no but I
didn't want to check my backpack because I was too scared to get up yeah
indecision mm-hmm indecision 2020 mm-hmm the Daily Show they should bring that
back they should dude they should bring back the Daily Show it's been gone yeah
- Yeah.
- No one, it's not there anymore.
- It's not.
- Yeah, number four, you will learn to hurt women.
- From watching porn?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, not the porn I watch.
The porn I watch is all about just watch, you know.
- Caleb 9000's back on here and says,
"That's not something you have to watch to figure out.
"Violence is a natural instinct."
(laughing)
- Though a bad one.
- Yeah.
- Damn, that's sick.
- You just know everything.
- Violence against women is a natural instinct.
It's natural.
Says Caleb.
Guys, it's a release.
Come on.
No, I do think it's wrong to beat up on a girl.
And I've never punched a woman in the face.
And that's the honest, the God honest truth.
Never once have I turned around when I got pushed in a bar fight in Santa Clarita and
the thought that a big fat lesbian was a guy and punched her in the face only to later
realize that I had maybe broken a woman's nose.
never happened to me and I never would do that yeah number five porn can cause
relationship problem yeah relationship problem is my hand and my penis got too
close to each other now I'm married and they're stuck together as an imprint
yeah
It feels like a penis. Do you have a penis tattoo? No. I have an embossed penis tattoo
on my hand. I got a dermal implant of a penis. Yeah. Which one is a dermal implant? It's when
they put like a tiny star in your skin. So it's like a bump. Oh yeah, okay. Yeah. Those
things are... It's like the piercing that sits on the bone or whatever. I don't know what that is.
Okay. I think it's just a bump under your skin that they usually make designs with.
Oh, I don't know. They put a thingy, they put basically the back end of a stud
in your body. Can you look, can you show me a picture? I have no idea what the hell you're
talking about. It's a bump on your skin that looks like a shape. Wait, look up penis dermal.
It's these things. Oh, oh that is a penis dermal. But people also get, they'll get like, you know,
shapes and stuff. Yeah. Disgusting, dude. They're awful. Ugh. Those are gross. That is, whoa.
Oh that one's pretty cool. That one's tough. Yeah. They put skulls in the fist. Yeah. Look at that
shirt. Who's that? Who is it? Is that Rob Zombie? That's Bob Zombert. Bob Zombert.
Dab dab. Somebody got the one-up mushroom and the invincibility star on their hands.
You will never die. Yeah. You always have a one. You will never die rock and roll.
infinity signs. Ugh. Yeah, they're really gross. I would probably get, I would get, uh, I would get,
I would get Pac-Man given the finger. Yeah. I would get Squidward's name. I would get, I would,
Squidward tentacles. Those are dermal implants, like, you barely read them.
It's the lyrics. It's the lyrics of your- Just like swollen two bumps.
What is that? Oh, that's Squidward's name. That's, that's the lyrics to your mean one.
That's my favorite character.
I'm a huge Spob Bob fan.
I love Spog Bob.
I love Spodge Bodge.
Yeah, so I got Squidward animals on my...
Yeah, Squidward's animal.
I got Squidward animals on my leg.
Yeah, I got fat...
Whoops.
Pussy.
Fat pussy.
I got a fat pussy implanted in one of my legs.
Oh my God, that's the move for jacking off and jerking off.
Get a dermal implant of a woman's vagina.
a porn star somebody like you know Remy LaCroix or like Lisa Ann or like Lana
Rhodes and you get their pussy installed in your hand and then you sit
there and you sit there and you're jacking off your fucking your hand.
It was a Kumgo? The Kumgo is in your hand and then you dump it into the into the sink.
Is he doing something? The cat? Yeah. No. Where is Yoda? He's not... I don't know.
Is all you think about these cats all the time? I'm trying to tell you
about how I'm where my new invention of jacking off. I was asking where my cat is.
What about a movie that's like Ricky Gervais invention of lying but it's the
invention of jacking off mm-hmm and he's like oh it's not real so I can check off.
In here I fuck my hand yeah in here yeah. Oh you're God now. I closed my eyes
and I pretended that my hand was a pussy and I rubbed it back and forth. Yeah.
But that would be a good movie. Mm-hmm. I don't think that would be a good movie.
Ricky Gervais the invention of getting sucked in fuck. What about Ricky Bobby?
Bobby Gervais Ricky Bobby
Yeah, I'm gonna drive a car in it yeah, I'm gonna drive a car if you ain't first you last yeah, I'm John C
Riley come here. I'm gonna tell you about I theism
Atheist Ricky Bobby yeah, I'm gonna have a nightmare mm-hmm actually you know what we can actually just start dinner. We don't have to do grace
That scene is just completely ruined. They just sit in silence. All the kids still have
southern accents. Everybody except Ricky Bobby Travis. But where are we going to make that
movie? He's not sponsored by Wonder Bread, he's sponsored by Tesco. Number six, it can
destroy families. That's true because if your dad is jacking off to porn and your
mom is jacking off to porn when are they gonna go to work? It can also destroy
families because say you're sitting down on the couch right but then in walks
your banging hot stepsister and she says why'd you spill all my you spell this
money on the ground and you'd be like no I mean you'd pick it up she bends over
boom fat pussy ass ball sack right in your face man and you're sucking on it
and and and your mom walks in and she goes you fucking my daughter
Tim Allen's head with the breasts of the Pamela and Anderson and and in the legs
of Tam Allen and she walks in and she's like what are you doing with your sister
you say I'm fucking her in the ass are you blind and then she says no no this
is how you tell you yeah and then the neighbor over the fence and the wheels
over yeah do you Wilson glory hole
Glory hole my god
Xxx yeah, this is bone improvement
Now we're not destroying the family now we're improving well, I'm that at the end everyone dies
Yeah, and then at the end everybody dies because an asteroid hit
Yeah a comment on it can destroy family says if your dad watch porn your dad sucks
My dad didn't suck. I've never caught anybody
I caught my dad after he did. Yeah, because he didn't know how to delete the history. Ah
So I think I told you this story but my dad
So me and my two brothers fought for like
Like a week. Mm-hmm. They were like who the fuck looked up fake taxi, and then we realized it was my dad. Damn
I'm realizing that one time I got like something kind of close to that.
Oh, we taught my dad how to private browse.
Smart.
I got on the computer and there was like a porn pop-up was on the computer and I was
like, "Oh, I'm gonna get in trouble for this."
So I was like maybe nine or ten.
And so I found my dad and I was like, "Dad, there's like something like, you know, there's
like porn on the computer."
And he's like, "What?"
And he went and he sat down and he just looked at it and looked at me and he's like, "What
"What is this garbage?"
(laughter)
And then he closed out of it and he was like
"You know, who knows, you tell me if that ever happens again, cause that...
that was weird.
That was really weird."
And then he just went back to
just, you know, watching the wire.
"What the hell is this crap? What the crap is on this TV?"
"They're naked? What the heck?"
"She's... what are they doing to each other?"
"God, Caleb,
I think I see her thing, dude.
I think her thing and her what's are called.
We need to throw out the monitor right now.
We gotta take this computer back to Best Buy because obviously the Geek Squad needs to put
a couple hours in on this machine.
This thing.
Does this come with the computer?
What?
Wait.
Okay.
I told them not to install any crazy porn boobs and vaginas on here, but it seems like
they did.
Great.
Leave it to Dell.
It's so hard to get through.
It's so hard to get a good firewall these days.
I think we're being hacked.
I think some of them are being hacked by naked people having sex.
I think beautiful women are hacking my computer.
In like, I was in like fifth grade, my little brother tried to download, like he tried to
get Halo 2 for PC.
Impossible, until the Master Chief collection came out.
So he, yeah, he downloaded Halo 2 for PC.exe and then there was a, like a bunch of desktop
icons that popped up and one of them, the only one I remember was an icon that said
gay dungeon poor. That's so funny because it's like what do you gain from
uploading that virus right that puts gay done. It's like it's like when people
sell their CDs on the street. They're just trying to get it out there. Yeah,
you know, they're just trying to get distribution. Sometimes it's hard when
you're an independent gay dungeon porn content creator. The icon is Freddy the
fish no the icon was like an M for some reason it was like a stone M for mr.
Patrick mr. Patrick's alter ego mr. Patrick mm-hmm have you seen mr. steel
yo damn cat recently see around we saw him remember mr. steel yo damn remember
he was out to grab your damn cat mr. he was outside yeah he go I don't remember
if we were talked about on a premium or not yeah you don't know mr. the guy who
I
my money can sleep at some point in the iron i might be sleeping or didn't get
go
yeah
mister yeah i go get go
really no
now that is his name
who who's got to get the guy i don't like a little street never sleeps
what's that
the wall street the movie
was that i was just a movie about a guy on wall street his name is gordon get
go
now it's funny and doesn't he get a lot to me at the enderson larry lizard and
i'm the king of wall street on the king of all the money on the street
my name is mister monkey i'm saying this
that's the best thing
i am sam the snake and i'm actually in a a much fun manager funny frog
on the funny frog i guess what the funny i don't think it's a giraffe and i'm
in jam the president of the of my neck it seems i said my dick yeah i'm the
lion king
does need a lot of the lion king two-and-a-half what's up my name is the
on the bees knees
and i'm uh... and i a bsus amnesia's business and i'm
managed kid cody and i'm good
and one of the wall street guys
missus israeli introducing himself on the line
which i have
things are going to be easy
it's beautiful
you can't really get
mhm
moving on the air
on bob wall street
now bob wall street and bob wall street let me teach you a thing or two he's
sitting in a cardboard box at the bottom of the head
I always wanted the biggest--
Hop into my machine.
I wanna show you what my empire once was.
They should do a version of Wall Street,
but like where all the porn companies are,
and call it Balls Street.
They should do a version of Wall Street
where there's a wolf that's there.
They should let a wolf have some money.
(laughing)
Let's see what happens.
Yep.
What was that laugh?
He went.
I'm excited about this wolf.
You look like a damn Keebler elf right now, player.
I'ma keep it all the way one million with you.
you said that here you posted on the media employees in your day and tree
you're in my tree but i'm not in your treat is my this is my a tree are
where's the cookies and mister kepler i do have a thing a cookie dough yeah i
bet cookie dough
yeah always got cookie dough he's gonna be keebler on the night
dot com sister dot
i think the cookie dough and you know what i'm gonna tell you here's why you
keep their health man because you small you're annoying as a marriage because
your irish actually same height as you mother fucker you're not
You're half an inch shorter and you know it.
I am the same height as you.
How tall is that?
That's 5'10".
You think you're 5'10"?
I think we're both 5'10".
We're not.
Why not?
I'm like 5'8" and a half and you're 5'1".
No. I'm 5'1" plus 8".
5'9"? So you admit you're not 5'10".
It seems as if you've been bested by me,
who is sort of a Sheldon for Big Bang Theory.
And you're like the girl from Big Bang Theory
loses to the smart guy.
Says it right here.
Yeah, you can lie.
It says it right here.
They don't measure you on a license.
It says 69.
They just ask.
I'm going to read off Patrick's license number.
Okay.
No.
Let's see, what can we read off here?
1111.
Can we read off your address, your home address?
No, I don't live there anymore.
Alright, his hair color is brown.
If anyone wants to hack his hair, listen to his brown.
If you try to change my hair color to any other color, I will flip my shit.
It's funny that you look like 20 years older in this photo.
I do? You do look way older in this picture. How?
You do. You do. We'll post it. We're going to scan Patrick's ID and post it.
I am freshly 18 in that picture. Freshly. Barely League.
I was 17 the day before. Oh my god. You look older. You look like you're
18. Height 69 inches. You look 180 years old in that photo. You look
like shit. Oh, I got to get this renewed this year. Shit.
I think I got to get mine renewed too. That's going to be one of the ultimate license
to license before and after. That'll be good. You might have to frame those.
It is disgusting. Number seven. Yeah, porn is gross. Yeah. But it's sexist.
They shit and they fart and stuff. They're making porn now where
people shit into tortillas and wrap it up in like a burrito. I'm serious.
I haven't seen it but I know that it exists. I'm gonna show it to you later.
I'm gonna send you a link or a should send me
Miss you as it file you should send me greatest freakout ever
Yeah, I've been rewatching the one where he puts the people throw his ass. It's so funny. No one could tell that was fake
Yeah, I mean you were it people are so gullible back in the day
Just like every every viral video was you you had to you had to get hardened by greatest freakout ever one you have to get
Hardened I you get hard and hard as you see the remote
They actually show full penetration.
In the remake.
Yeah, in the porn parody of Greatest Freak Out.
Greatest Sex Out Ever.
Greatest Dig Out.
Yeah, and he digs out that little asshole.
He digs out the bread in the sandwich
like they do at Jimmy John's
and he fucks the shit out of it.
Did they do that at Jimmy John's?
Yeah, I saw them do it today.
Number 34 is boobs are annoying.
Boobs are so annoying.
That's a common comment.
anonymous buddy talking reckless like that. They contain elements of violence. I
hate elements of violence. It's a disgrace to couples wanting a child. Do
you think porn should be rated TVMA? Oh absolutely. It should be rated NC-17.
They should rate porn M. Why don't they rate? They don't rate because that's what I
actually watch it sometimes cuz there's no rating on it so if it's M
like I don't watch an M rated thing. You should rate it P for porn. Yeah but then
that make me maybe I'll look at it for preschool about xxx they rate it xxx I
think don't watch it I would think that music is like three X's because I was
classically educated so I actually have an advanced understanding of Roman
numerals and so you can't watch it until you're 30 that's a pretty good rule
that's why it says xxx I think you're I think everybody would be better off if
it was your it was impossible to watch porn until you were 30 years old yeah
you know biometric tests yeah bio you have to type in your social security to go
into any porn site you have to last three you have to take a we have to take a
photo mm-hmm and send it of your penis and then they age they they do a
dating on your penis to find out do face at young and if it changes they know
you're old true because it doesn't change if you do face up I've done the
face up young on a baby and it does not change anything. Yeah it says error
already young. Yeah this is this this is baby. Yeah it says this is a baby. It's a Russian.
Is it a Russian app? Yeah. It's part of the collusion. Part of Donald? Yeah
that's they actually did all the they made Trump look cool and all the
pictures they were part of. Oh my god. I really liked that new picture of Trump.
Oh yeah that's so funny. I didn't I didn't think it would you know you think
looks kind of cool yeah it looks fine his hair looks good his skin looks cool mm-hmm
I don't really get why all these people are speaks of me no shiny should be is
that a problem no no people like when people are shiny that's a whole category
of porn that is like shiny like bubble buddy from Spongebob people like you when
people are shiny that's why there's a guy who dresses up in silver and does a
robot moves. Yeah the Bicentennial Man Robin Williams. Yep. People there are
Bicentennial Man on every street corner in LA doing the robot. And they love to do the robot.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. You go up to them see that's the secret. It's a tribute to Rob. People think
people think you have to go up to them and give them a dollar. No you go up to
them and say Bicentennial Man and then they will reveal that they are Robin
Williams to you yeah they're all Robin Williams over guy comes up he goes oh
the robot the robot whoo it's all I got hmm who is it is it Robin Williams or is
it monkey Williams who is just a regular monkey has no relation to Rob Williams
just has a last name like anybody should monkey Williams monkey Williams oh my
god Johnny Carson I have the worst news you know how Robin Williams was supposed
come on the show. Yes, yes I do. We accidentally booked a Monkey Williams.
Luckily he can do the "ooh" exactly the same. Luckily he does basically the same exact act
but I don't know how to pay him because we ran out of bananas two days ago. We
have a great Monkey Williams he is the lead singer of a band called the
Gorillas. Oh my god I used to watch Gorillas music videos and get so scared.
yeah the one where the funky homo sapien gets really big finally someone
sunshine in the bag
I loved that song
I got sunshine and it's bad
I'm useless
but not for long
the monkey
the monkey part is about to happen
that's when I would turn it off
That's when I would turn it off when he says that.
I'm the monkey!
I also would get scared.
I would get scared at the other one with De La Soul.
Is that Feel Good Inc?
Yeah, they draw everybody so scary.
What are you talking about?
You weren't scared of the windmill in my video?
You weren't scared of the gorillas?
No. I loved them, they were my friends.
You didn't think the album cover was scary?
You loved them dude, that big guy with the drums?
I loved him the most.
I was scared of the lead singer and the girl because he had no eyes
That's what was scared what scared me about him was that he had no eyes and he sang like a little fucking
Other guy was the Satanist you aren't scared of him. I didn't know some yeah Murdoch. You know the nest yeah
By Mark Hamill, I don't know no you think of the Joker. That's right. Okay, you think of Luke Skywalker
I don't know what you're talking about at all the gorillas. Yeah, you don't
You knew the name of the guy.
I thought we were talking about the Batman.
The Gorilla...oh, oh, you thought...
We thought we were talking about Gorilla Grodd.
From Batman, yeah.
Who makes an appearance in Batman.
Is he from The Flash or from Superman?
He's from all of them.
He's from the zoo.
Boom.
I don't know that he is from the zoo. He might not be.
I think he's from Monkey Planet.
Zoo is Monkey Jail.
No, it's Monkey...
Oh my god, the zoo is just a jail for monkeys and elephants and bees.
You enter the zoo, you walk out of the gift shop and you're just swarmed by bees.
Yeah, every other monkey is out of season.
All we have is bees right now.
Yeah, we lost federal funding for them.
The only thing we could afford was bees.
These are the only animals people don't protest for us having in a cage.
Yeah, mosquitoes.
The guy next door to us just kind of had beekeeping shit, so.
Yeah, so we just decided, "Eh, fuck it."
We cut him a deal.
He gets to keep all of his bees here.
Yeah, and we charge you $50.
We charge you money and we don't give it to him.
There's a...
Do you guys want to go in the snake pool?
Do you guys want to go in the ant room?
What's that?
It's a bug zoo.
A bug zoo.
for bugs. Yeah, welcome to my bug zoo. We have ants, there's bees everywhere. There's just
like a cage that has a pile of shit in it. Yeah, that's the fly exhibit. Yeah, that's
where all of them eat. It's like a lawn, there's the worms, the worms live under there. Sharks,
I'm asking for a 40% stake and 50 million dollars in my bug zoo. You're gonna do what? I'm gonna
put a million bees and a hundred ants in the same room and I'm gonna charge
Chinese tourists $150 to walk in and they're not allowed to leave until they
say uncle yeah and then just instantly closes cuz all the bees just fly away
yeah it's but it like bars up like a cage yeah then we had to get then we had to
get the fake bees on sticks yeah just like stuck in the ground the guy just
like you know how they have like people like paint like the Warhammer
characters but he's painting a fly it's a bee colors yeah I have to paint like a
million more of these fucking things every time unless they don't stop moving
we have to move them every day every time he lets go of it it just flies away
shit I didn't put things only got two stripes on it luckily no B yeah luckily
this spider will never leave us mm-hmm and it's dead and and it's the web says
Charlotte's Web a spy Ross over anybody with Charlotte's Web Charlotte's Web the
CBD company this what Charlotte's Web is a big CBD they should not have done it
- It stands for crawling big tarantula.
- Durantula.
- Like Kevin Durant.
- Yeah, Kevin Durantula.
- Okay, Dogel, show me a bug zoo.
- Build a bug zoo in my house.
- Okay, Dogel, build me a bug zoo
for my friends to hang out at.
I don't like ant farms, unless they're alien.
Honey, are you okay?
Okay, Google.
- Dogel.
Okay, Dogel, play Alien Ant Farm, Smooth Criminal.
Okay, Google.
Smooth Criminal, what's this about a burglar
with alopecia?
That's loud.
Nice, all right, well, let's, yeah,
we can read the Patreon to this.
Oh, yeah, okay, Google.
No, keep it--
Okay, Dogel.
Volume seven.
(laughs)
No, keep it loud, you can't hear it.
Yeah, seven's still loud.
No, put it back up.
Okay, Dogel, maximum volume.
Maximum volume.
You can see she was a name...
Wait.
Okay, don't put it there. Now that's too loud.
Just keep it in the background.
Yeah.
Alright, it starts where?
Oh yeah, we got a lot this week.
Was it here?
Yeah, that was the last one.
Alright, cool.
Shout out to Nick Bailey.
Ryan Corvello.
Shout out to Michelle Larney.
Michelle Larney.
Chandler Albers.
Shout out to Rayashi who makes really cool music.
Shout out Mr. Business.
Shout out my big bitch Mr. Business.
Mr. Business, what's up?
We love you baby.
We love all of the patrons.
I love every single one of you.
If you could tell two friends, we can get to 200 bucks a month.
Do you tell two friends?
We can get an Xbox One S.
This is the Podcast About List Challenge.
You tell two friends to subscribe to the Patreon.
And we get the money.
And we get some serious money.
And we're going to challenge your wallets.
Uh huh.
This is the Podcast About List Challenge.
You give two friends our money.
15 episodes, one book, one Caleb.
One Caleb.
couple videos of me on his videos there's a zip file I filled with a bunch of
pictures Caleb's real phone number my real phone number is on there and a
listed video and you're absolutely welcome to to call me or text me I don't
I'm not worried about it you know I'm the thing is you pay me and I'm your
slave so do whatever you want to sound like you're a slave if you're getting
paid I'm not paid feel bad that we did all the patreon shout outs while alien
and
suck each other's dicks.
Oh, you watch that a lot.
No, I'm saying it's like this. No, no, I like to look the other way
when you're doing it is what I'm saying.
You like to watch a baby suck a dick on you.
I don't like doing that.
The other way into a mirror so you can see it.
So I can do my makeup.
You like to watch the other way into a funhouse mirror
because your view of society is so skewed.
I think you guys are missing the point that you are two babies
and you're sucking each other's penises.
No, we're not. No. I'm watching it happen.
So why are you watching it?
on a on a on a browser so it's okay
Bye guys!