You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(explosion)
- Woo!
- Yeah.
- Back at it, back in the lab.
- Ba ba ba ba ba.
- I feel, I don't know what about this thumb thing
walking around like this.
- It's so you can hitchhike better.
- Well I have to be giving a thumbs up all the time
or else blood will pool in it 'cause it's still bleeding.
But it makes, I feel like a pirate.
- Yeah. - Kinda, yeah.
- 'Cause you have skirts.
- I feel like I have a hook hand.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Oh God, I feel like fucking shit right now.
- You feel like a pirate.
Your body feels like a pirate.
- I woke up too early, I went to bed at like four.
- Nice.
- I got home, I had all those white,
or truly hard seltzers left over from the show.
- You gotta go crazy with the seltzers.
- So I was like, yeah, I'm just gonna drink
like most of these.
- Just alone.
- Yeah, well no, I was drinking with Dom.
We had dinner, I made a meal,
and then we were like drinking.
And then I just realized, I just,
every time that I drink, I just keep drinking.
It's so easy with the seltzers,
'cause I'm just like, oh, I'm not drunk.
And then it hits me, and then I got too high,
and I went to bed at like four.
- Four?
- I went to bed at four, got up at nine,
because I had to clean up the apartment.
- And by the way, you did a bang up job.
Yeah. Spotless. I gave up halfway through. But yeah, I just feel like I've been farting all day
and it's been like just high octane just shit coming out of me. Just like nitrous, the energy
drink? Oh, they feel too hot coming out. I know that, yeah. I think it's, I ate a bunch of tzatziki
sauce last night. I ate a bunch of pita and tzatziki. Sometimes I walk around the art gallery
and I'm farting so constantly it's like I'm holding like a bowl of hot soup
and just steam is coming off of it. Yeah. Oh, I hate when it like you can feel it leave your pants.
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Your tight leather pants. Yeah. You see the bubble.
Yeah, dude. Man, the best is the still the fucking the infrared video and it's just the
the guy standing there and he farts, you just see the cloud of smoke come out.
It's so classic, too.
Yeah.
It still, it makes me laugh every time.
I would say my farts run abnormally hot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I feel like sometimes they burn me.
Do you get like that when you eat garlic?
I eat a lot of raw garlic.
My entire diet for like two weeks has just been lentils and broccoli, which has been
just fucking me up.
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
And kidney beans.
I did have, I put a bunch of garlic.
I made like a vegan alfredo thing.
I think you're allergic to garlic. I've never heard of garlic makes you fart.
Yeah, maybe I am. I don't know.
Don't tell Patrick he's allergic to something.
Yeah, do not tell me I'm fucking allergic to something.
That's not going to go over well.
Yeah, what am I thinking? That's such a bad idea.
Yeah, you're going to come in tomorrow, he's going to have locked himself in the bedroom.
There's garlic everywhere.
Garlic has gone airborne.
I can't go outside.
I'll start farting if I go outside.
Yeah, there's garlic in the sauce I made.
garlic in the sauce I made and then there's I mean tzatziki is just mostly
garlic and yogurt. No it's mostly tzatziki. That's true. Yeah I didn't think about it like that.
It has to have tzatziki. Oh shit. I made a vegan tzatziki that's been in my fridge.
I had a different thing of tzatziki that I was eating. I have like a thing that big.
You're obsessed with that shit dude. It's so fucking good. It's just tangy. It's
is garlic yogurt. Yeah, but they don't have... There's no garlic flavored yogurt. Yeah, there's
no garlic flavored yogurt. Yeah, that's a very good point. It's the perfect sauce. What are
you putting it on? Pita chips, french fries. You just use it as a dip? Yeah. Oh, yeah,
that's good. Yeah, it's a good choice. It's better than hummus. I disagree. I replace
tzatziki with hummus all the time. Hummus is the bomb, dude. I don't know. A little sabra.
I think I...
Yeah, I say I like Sabra.
The best hummus I've had is...
I don't like their hummus, but I like everything else about them.
I don't care.
Yeah.
I just support them as a brand.
Yeah, I buy all the hummus and I put it straight in the trash can.
I don't eat it, but I just want to make sure they get my money so they can do whatever
they want with it.
I donate straight to Sabra.
I have an active blue recurring donation for Sabra.
Yeah, $100 a week.
Yeah.
I've just been...
Last night I smoked weed, I didn't freak out.
Oh, that's good.
- No, it was very nice.
- What was the context?
- I smoked weed and I didn't freak out.
- Where?
- In my room.
- By yourself?
- Yeah.
- When?
- Last night.
- No, when?
That's a when.
- Oh yeah, I can't tell 'cause of you.
- When?
- Accent.
- They're the same, yeah, I get made fun of.
Yeah, I always have.
- Rightfully so.
- No, it's a normal way to talk.
- No, it's not.
- It's normal to be from the South.
A lot of people are.
Most of the world is from the South.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
Global South. - That's not true.
what
no yeah no yeah no yeah no some of the no some right now
what side of my own you're on my side okay
no I'm not I'm not on camera to find you
you're on my someone Caleb side no yeah you are correct now I should be on your
own side
Patrick Patrick come to my said we've cookies oh yeah well we have cookies and
more cookies in him Patrick we have cookies that we have a massage chair
uh-huh like one of the ones that you put on an office chair
And we have a penis sucker.
I need both of those.
We have a paintball course inside the middle school.
And you can hit the teachers with the paintball.
Really?
Yeah.
His side has homework.
Yeah, you get to burn it.
We got homework and a homework bonfire.
Burn after reading it and doing it.
And you have to do all the homework and make all the problems.
I get to play paintball and watch it burn after reading.
On my side, we just finished filming Jackass 4.
Whoa!
We have a preview copy of it.
If you go to Caleb's side, all your hair will fall out.
Oh no.
That's fine.
We have hair.
And Caleb thinks it's fine.
It is fine.
Caleb doesn't care if your hair falls out.
Yeah.
He doesn't care about you.
We have a cool wig selection.
Really?
Yeah.
You can get a big afro.
And nobody even gets weird about it.
No one will make fun of me for it?
Nobody will make fun of you.
my side you can say whatever word you want. Whoa! Same thing here with one
exception. Okay, well that doesn't sound too good. Yeah, mine's better. Oh, so you want to
say it? What? What? What word are you talking about? The N word. Which one is that?
What are you talking about? No, that you said you could say. Caleb doesn't even know what word he's talking about.
He said you could say any word on your side. He don't even know what word I can say.
Yeah, here you can you can say every word except that one. And I'm
I'm drawing a hard line in the sand.
I do like rules.
This sounds like a lot of rules, Caleb.
We have a nude beach and kids are allowed.
(Laughter)
Not, you can't be naked.
I'm not going to go there.
If you're a kid, you can come and you can watch.
I'm not a kid.
Yeah, you are.
I don't feel comfortable going to a nude beach.
That was my dream when I was a teenage boy.
I was just like, "Please, a nude beach."
It's like 13 and up.
up. Never found it. We have a teen club where adult men are allowed in. Whoa! I don't want
to be on either of your side. You got a weird side, man. I didn't open it, we just have
it on the side. We have an original GameCube. I have a modded Wii. We have a Kinect. If
anyone wants to just send me the Wii component cables, we will give you... We will pay you
for them we will let you choose a side choose a side pick a side stupid we'll
let you choose a side of your own yeah and you get to choose anything you want
french fries a salad mm-hmm or some or onion ring kettle cook chip mm-hmm you
ever have a frip? A frip? It's a thick chip, fry chip. Robert Fripp? No. Oh yeah, Robert
Fripp. I don't know who that is man. Yeah, Caleb doesn't know who that is. I don't care
about your music. He invented new standard tuning. I don't know what that means. He invented
power by Kanye West. Yeah, that's true. What the heck? I'm serious. He's the guy that goes
dun dun dun dun dun dun. He's the one that goes la la la la la la. No, Swizz Beatz did
Oh, Swizz Beatz did that, okay.
Yeah.
Man.
You fucking idiot.
I just gotta stop drinking for a while.
Yeah?
I'm like...
Let's unpack it.
I'm so hungover.
What's going on?
No, it's just this whole weekend, like Saturday and then Sunday.
Nice.
Or yesterday, and now I'm just like, I'm shooting hot gas out of me.
It'll make you, it'll fuck up your, your stump.
Yeah, I don't feel good right now.
Feels, it'll fuck you up, man.
Yeah.
- I've been, I've just been getting home.
All my roommates all go to bed at like 9 p.m.
and I just like wander into my apartment
at like 3 a.m. every night, just fart all over the place.
- Nice.
- And just like leave like a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich in the sink.
- Nice.
- And then fall asleep with the door open and I'm naked.
- Hell yeah.
- Yeah.
- Nice.
- That's how we do!
- I think I just got bad heartburn.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I just ate that cookie.
No, I'm just disintegrating.
- He ate a cookie in front of me.
- You have cookie?
cookie out of his fridge and ate it right in front of me.
And didn't even offer you one?
It was one of those, um...
You had a fridge cookie?
Well, it was only a quarter of it left.
It was really weird that it was in the fridge.
It was only a quarter of it left.
It wasn't mine either.
Dom's gonna be pissed when she finds out I ate it.
Oh my god, she better not listen to this.
She's gonna, yeah, she listens.
You're gonna be in the dog house tonight, buddy.
I'll be in the freaking dog house when she finds out I ate her damn cookie.
I eat my dad when...
You ate your dad?
I ate my dad.
When my dad and my mom were like about to get divorced, that my dad would just sleep on
the couch like every single night, right?
Bollard.
And I would wake him up every day in the morning and I'd be like, "What happened?"
And he was like, "I just fell asleep watching Seinfeld."
And that's why he convinced me, they had a TV in the room, but they convinced me that
my dad liked Seinfeld so much that he had to sleep on the couch.
Yeah.
Yeah, because he would just watch it well into the night.
Nice.
It's pretty awesome.
I was a pretty gullible kid.
Yeah, when they when they first got to like separated my dad
I just didn't see my dad for like a month and my mom was like I was like hey
Where the fuck's dad and she was like he's just cleaning the old house. Just getting it ready for the next person
I was like damn
Dad sucks at cleaning that's taking a long time
Get off your phone Patrick. Sorry my sister texted. I don't care
I went so I it was my nephew's brunch yesterday. Nephew's brunch. Nephew's brunch. I showed up there
three hours too late I
Showed up. I had that I still had that fucked up mullet. I gave myself. Yeah, I looked I didn't even I didn't notice it at all
It didn't look weird. It didn't look weird. I
Didn't even know you cut your hair since then. Oh, well, yeah
I just I came home Saturday and just cut both like I took the scissors and just cut I think one of them
I think there's a part on this side where I cut too close.
There's either this side or this side, but there's one where I cut way too close.
And then I showed up at my house and my cousin Ryan, who I barely see, was there and everyone
was like, "Yeah, look who it is."
They were all waiting for me to be like, "Oh shit, what's up dude?"
And I just went, and I just walked past him and just got a shit ton of water.
Damn dude, Ryan, damn, you got a shit ton of water too?
I got a shit ton of water.
Holy crap.
probably why you're farting so much dude. You're drinking so much water.
Yeah. Where did you find this list Patrick? I found this list. He was looking this up for himself.
Yeah. He was going, he was going to use this on... No there was a thing I
specifically looked up. You're going to use this on your Xbox girlfriend.
What did I eat for breakfast? What did you eat for breakfast?
probably breakfast it's in that is fucking psychotic yeah say you're say
your meal ranking just so everyone can laugh at you the meal ranking is lunch
dinner breakfast you are in so saying the dudes that is not is like just
completely ass backwards there's not ass backwards breakfast dinner lunch
breakfast is awesome lunch is fine lunch for me lunch is like be anything I eat a
a for lunch I'll have like a protein bar yeah yeah I usually just get lunch lunch
is just a fuck hold up okay I'm trying to get dinner no cuz there so it's like
lunch dinner brunch breakfast they're not counting you are psyched you were sick
in the head dude how am I fucking in the head you were there's something mentally
wrong with you no yeah you come home you guys like eating I just like eating
sandwiches you like eating so you have you ever heard of a breakfast sandwich I
I don't like breakfast sandwiches.
Why?
They're too heavy.
Too heavy?
You can't lift them off his plate.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I don't like eating breakfast.
If I eat breakfast in the morning, I'll throw up.
What?
I don't know why.
You'll throw up if you eat breakfast?
Dude, I think you're pregnant.
Yeah.
Think you have morning sickness?
That sounds...
I don't know.
I just...
You'll vomit if you eat breakfast?
I don't know.
I can't hold down food in the morning.
That's insane.
You should go to the doctor.
I've never had breakfast sandwiches.
I don't know.
I just...
I can't.
You should go to the doctor.
Yeah, probably.
You have GERD or something.
You know what it probably is? I think that I can't eat breakfast
because I think that I'll throw up.
That's what it is. It's because you're doing
your hypochondriac thing with breakfast.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, either way.
You're going to do what you did with weed and one day you're going to be like
"Guys, I love breakfast now."
Breakfast. I actually had
breakfast and it was fine.
It didn't even kill me.
I totally could. I don't know.
Just come get some breakfast with us sometimes.
No, I, I, every time I eat breakfast I feel like shit.
No, you know what it is? It's that I have to wake up in the morning to get breakfast.
Oh, see that's what, for me, I like, like today-
You're always awake at like eight though.
Yeah, 'cause the fucking, the cats wake me up.
Okay, then go to breakfast.
I don't know, I don't want to-
You're, you, I-
I like to stay in bed 'til like eleven.
Get up at eight and stay in bed 'til eleven.
You can get breakfast at eleven.
Eleven is a perfectly normal - I got breakfast at like 10 30 today.
10 30 is when breakfast ends.
At McDonald's.
Yeah, exactly.
Now they go to -
That is the perfect time to stop serving breakfast.
No, I like a late breakfast.
Well, it's all day breakfast now.
Because I also - I completely skip lunch most days. I'll eat a late breakfast.
How do you skip -
Like a snack.
Yeah, I'll skip lunch sometimes.
Skip lunch, eat an apple.
But a good lunch.
Good lunch. What do you - what to use like a good lunch though?
A good lunch is like a sandwich.
What kind of sandwich?
Like roast beef.
But breakfast is too heavy.
But I can do a french dip which needs a jus to make it fucking go down.
Like you're doing a hot dog eating contest.
So? French dips are great.
Breakfast sandwiches are great, dude.
Yeah, I like a lox bagel sandwich. I'll eat that.
I don't like breakfast if it tastes like lunch.
You're a monster, dude.
a monster. You're like Michael Jackson. No. Yeah, you're a monster. No. He was a breakfast
monster. He was never technically proven guilty. Yeah, you know who else hated
breakfast? Who? Mr. Pedophile. Yeah. And Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Jimmy Savile.
Dr. Rapist, he hated breakfast. Now I'm not saying anything about you, but
Professor Racism thought breakfast was... he thought breakfast was for them.
Yeah. Yeah, so I just want that to... Wait, why would breakfast being for them be a
bad thing? Well, I mean, I'm saying that's what he thought. That's why he didn't eat
breakfast. I'm not saying that that's what you think. Yeah, but that's
someone who doesn't eat breakfast often. They might be racist, they might be
pedophile, they might be... I heard Hitler never ate breakfast. Hitler ate breakfast so much.
No, he didn't. Yeah, he ate fucking German. He ate little streusels. No, he didn't. No, he didn't. He tried to he actually banned streusels.
That's why there are no...
Okay, hold up. Try to find a streusel. Try to find a streusel. Hold up. Yeah. If I had like
Toaster streusel, I would eat toaster streusel for breakfast. So you like dessert?
Dessert? So I knew it goes... it goes lunch, dinner, dessert, breakfast.
I ate dessert. You ate dessert? I just ate a cookie right in front of me.
This is like the first time watching The Matrix. It wasn't even your cookie. You stole a cookie to eat it.
So now we're introducing a new category which is just food and then there's food that is around.
So where does food that is around rank in your ranking? Oh I don't care. Is that number one? No.
No? Food that is around does not count. What? That's still food. It's food, yeah. That's a meal.
It's not lunch or dinner or anything. It's just like getting you... It's snacks. Yeah, it's snacks.
Okay, so where do you rank snacks? Snacks is better than lunch. Oh my god. So you rather...
If I called you up in the morning and I say, "Hey, do you want to get breakfast?" You say,
"No, sorry. I hate breakfast." I say, "Do you want to get some snacks?" You'd say, "Yeah."
That's the best.
You would jump, you would leap out of bed like fucking...
Snacks can be anything too.
It's just like lunch.
Lunch can't be anything.
Lunch can be anything.
You can get breakfast for lunch.
You cannot eat oatmeal for lunch.
Yeah, you can.
No, you can't.
No, you could.
Yeah, that's just...
You could.
It's not a good decision, but you could.
Oatmeal for lunch, that's fucking insane.
Okay, then you can eat anything for breakfast too.
You could eat anything at any time of the day.
You could eat a tuna sandwich for breakfast.
Yeah, you could.
You probably do.
But you wouldn't like that, because it's in the morning.
Because it's breakfast, yeah.
Do you like eggs?
wouldn't like that because it's in the morning. Because it's breakfast, yeah. Do you like eggs?
No, I barely like eggs. Okay, all right. I only like scrambled eggs. Okay, never mind. I was
gonna say this absolves you. Or the McRiddle eggs. Okay, so that's two kind of eggs that
you're fine with. Do you like bacon? If it's in a sandwich. I'm gonna leave, dude. This is
completely insane. I feel like you dosed me with something. This is so crazy to talk to
to you about breakfast. What? It's not. I just don't like breakfast. You're an alien dude.
You're not from planet earth. You're from planet lunch dude. You're an alien from planet lunch.
So. And that's not good. That's good. It's not dude. Lunch is good. Hot dog? Hot dog
is. Hot dog hamburger. God you like a fucking wet hot dog? No. You like boiled hot dogs?
If I could eat a Chicago style dog every day for lunch, that would be the dream.
That's insane dude.
Your breath would smell so bad.
It would, but I would be full of good shit.
If I could eat breakfast for every meal, I probably would.
I would too.
The cheapest meal.
Cheapest.
And just like, I like it.
I can eat eggs every meal.
If I could eat, okay.
If I could eat pussy every meal.
Just sandwiches.
Just like, just good sandwiches.
Just a sandwich.
Your whole diet is different sandwiches.
So what's the opening sandwich?
The best sandwich?
The opening sandwich.
Like you wake up, you go, you head to the fridge, you take out your sourdough loaf.
What do you put in between those pieces?
Probably just cheese.
Probably just gonna make a grilled cheese.
Grilled cheese for breakfast.
What's that?
You literally, you live the life of fucking Tom Hanks in Big.
You just wake up and you eat grilled cheese and you play with your toy cars.
What is wrong with that?
Grilled cheese for breakfast, what's wrong with that?
Yeah, it's like cheese and toast.
It's a baby meal.
No.
Grilled cheese is a child's meal.
No, not if you use like different cheeses.
So you think if you do more than one cheese, that's an adult meal?
Yeah, but if you do one slice of American cheese, that's a baby meal.
If you are eating whole wheat with American cheese in the middle.
Mac and cheese or grilled cheese, both baby meals.
No, not if you bake the mac and cheese.
Baked mac and cheese is not a baby meal.
I'll go with baked mac and cheese.
Baked mac and cheese is a side.
That is not a main dish.
What?
No, you could have it for a main dish.
I wouldn't have it.
You could just throw some pulled pork or bacon in it and then it's a fucking meal.
No, that's a fucking experiment.
That's an epic mealtime.
Lobster mac and cheese?
Lobster mac and cheese I will never eat in my life because--
It's good, but I hate it as a concept.
It smells so bad.
Yeah.
It's cheese and fish.
It's disgusting, but I like it.
Cheese and fish are-- there's a reason God put those two things on opposite ends of the
like opposite elevations.
Yeah.
You know, they should never meet.
Cheese comes from the tops of mountains.
Cheese comes from goats which live on top of mountains
and fish actually come from the bottom of the earth.
Bottom of the mountain.
Yeah, the bottom of the mountain.
Inside of the earth.
Yeah.
I don't like...
Filet of fish, what about that?
What do you...
Because cheese and fish should meet,
but sometimes a filet of fish do be hidden.
The filet of fish...
They have the perfect amount of cheese on it.
One piece.
it's it's half a slight yeah yeah it doesn't even cover the corners yeah
yeah
uh...
playfish issues is the exception
i really wake up you need real cheese what's the lunch sam about goldfish
goldfish
called this season fish and i don't think it's she's i don't think that can
use that with real goldfish to make it
well they use it the use of goldfish mold with a three-year-old real goldfish
it was a little bit of a cut they put real goldfish inside it and i hope not
They do.
Yeah, me too.
I hope not.
They do.
The second, okay.
The second launch.
The second Italian job from 7-Eleven.
Solid choice.
That's your choice though?
I mean, an Italian sandwich.
Your ideal sandwich.
No, no, okay, you couldn't eat sandwiches all day.
That's what you said you could do!
I said if I could.
I'm just thinking.
I'm saying you can.
Oh, okay.
So now I have the ability to eat sandwiches.
So your choice is the Italian job.
Okay, then I'm changing it from grilled cheese.
I thought I was I was trying to time everything out not so that I don't feel sick
Sandwiches make you sick. So you're no I just
Sick, it doesn't you know, you know, you know
Breakfast I feel like
Breakfast gives me heartburn the worst just because of how greasy everything is like a good breakfast
Just has a shit ton of grease in it like hash browns. That's true. Oh, yeah, I think it's a grease problem for me. Mmm
So like it's bacon and like eggs and it's all cut in the same grease.
That's him dipping fries in tzatziki sauce.
What? What is wrong with that?
I don't know, but grease just fucking makes you feel bad.
That's a pretty greasy meal I would say.
Oh yeah, but that's at the end of the day.
I can take fucking heartburn medication.
You can't do that in the morning.
No, I could, but it's just annoying
because then I have to spend the rest of my day with heartburn.
One day when you die,
in like a car accident,
or like a sandwich accident,
sandwich accident. They're going to cut your brain open and all of our questions will be
answered. There will be some growth in like some part of your brain and the doctors will
explain it to me and Cameron and we'll be like, "Oh, that was why he was completely
crazy."
Hold up. I got to get a fucking... I got to get a Tums.
Damn, just having the conversation. You said grilled cheese for breakfast and that did
make me feel bad.
My body started slowing down.
I feel like I'm in bullet time right now.
Patrick picked a list from the Odyssey Online today.
For those who are unaware of the Odyssey, do you guys know about it?
It's like Medium.
It's like Medium, but if your thing gets to the top of the page, you get like 20 bucks.
post your writing. It's articles website. It's articles website. I love articles
website. Yeah. Medium, Reddit. I knew someone in high school who said that they were like
yeah you know I just got this writing gig and it was the fucking Odyssey. Oh my
god. That's sick dude. So that's like who is on here? This is a this is a list that
Patrick found when he was googling actually the exact title of this list. 20
pick up lines for the college gentleman for online and in person.
another thing about the odyssey
it's like for college kids so these are college students writing it like a lot
of the articles will have like the author's name and then like what
university they go to you know gotcha uh... this is a reminder water a little
the subtitle of uh... of this list of his cameron's water my water is empty
isn't it
now you have a little bit of water
i'd
the subtitle of the list is thank you all my e gods of tender i am not worthy
and it's a picture of a guy and a girl holding on a beach in the guy has one
but the girls but
what
and girl
are you right
the what are you talking about how do you set a guy and a girl i just was
was surprised
so right on the i_d_ fucking talking about what i was going to go out shut the
fuck are you reading
i wasn't reading anything i was talking about a picture no
as it is a picture of a guy and a girl he missed a lot of that i said i said he
has a glass of wine anyway i don't like to do it he missed it there's a good one
and then what i was gonna say after that america is that the girls holding like a
tumbleweed or something that we shut up about your cat he's in pieces drinking
water
it's true you know that's fine
duties as okay
that's uh... he is head fits
yeah all you want to describe the picture
uh... it's a good thing that i was saying what patrick in new york and
beautiful Italian couple drinking a nice pinot grigio. Nice and cheap. She's feeling on his pinot grigio
you know what I'm saying and he has a hair, his hair poking out of the back. He has like a bush.
Yeah it's like a tumbleweed. Yeah he's holding wine and she's holding a tumbleweed. She's got
that Jordi Vero thing. She's a cowboy. She touched a meteorite. Now she's growing grafts on her.
I don't know what you're talking about. It's like that. Have you guys seen Creepshow? Yeah no I
Okay, I knew you fucking knew that Cameron. Yeah, well, I didn't know I didn't know it the way you said it
Once you said creep show I knew what it was, but you were like it's like
Jordy, vero the name of the fucking thing. I think the whole breakfast conversation got us heated up and we need to relax
Yeah, I think we're all
I think we're all a little prickly about the breakfast stuff still so let's
Let's focus on the job at hand, right?
Um, it's a typical saturday night and you're going out on the town to grab some food and maybe some drinks
So you start walking into Kilroys or Chili's to make your tummy happy.
And the moment you get in you see this gorgeous specimen sitting at the bar alone.
That sounds-
*laughs*
Some specimen.
Yeah, like some-
Yeah, a giant booger.
*laughs*
Specimen.
Damn, what's up specimen?
Damn, you want fine ass specimen.
There are other girls in the room, but you feel this special force that attracts you to her that
you've never felt before. You just feel like you gotta make a move or you're gonna regret it for
for the rest of your life,
but you don't know what to say and you're hesitating.
The time is ticking and you see other dudes
getting ready to make their move
to make an impression on the lady.
It's now or never.
Yeah, the fucking, the guys at Chili's,
they're like hyenas, dude.
They just circle specimens.
- If you're a guy and you're at Chili's,
it's like you get sprayed with horny juice
as soon as you walk through the door.
You're going in there, you're barking at women like a dog.
- I'm at Chili's looking for specimens.
- You're sitting there, I'm barking at some specimens.
Yeah, after this I'm gonna go to Chili's and find that specimen.
Hey!
Yeah.
Hey, what's up specimen?
I'mma experiment on you.
And then she starts to walk away and you go, "Hey!
Right!
Right!"
One.
Margaritas!
Two.
When I get to five!
Two and a half.
Well, in simpler times, brute force, wealth, or just plain physical attributes may have
helped others score some points.
Yeah, that's a weird inclusion, I'll say. And win their potential date's heart. However,
in today's sophisticated society, just having a cute face or good body doesn't cut it anymore.
Nowadays, you've got to be clever with your words and funny on top of other attributes.
Yeah, nowadays you have to be funny.
Yeah, Jim and Pam ruined that for every guy.
I know, dude. Guys used to be able to be so stupid and unfunny.
You used to be Roy, now you've got to be Jim.
Yeah, I and but then the true the real
Fuckers, they're Michael Scott. Mm-hmm. That's right. Yeah, the real ass players real players become become date Mike
Yeah, and for sign what did you drool on my computer?
Water droplet
And for science I've been compiling the best field tested up-to-date pickup lines that can help you pick up girls that you like
Instantly, so let's get to it. It starts with online dating pickup lines
Oh, we got to use these to pick each other up?
Yeah.
I'm going to pick up.
I'm going to pick you guys up right now.
Okay, number one, who wants to get picked up?
Just say it to one of us.
Patrick, you're the kind of person I would catch eye contact with on the bus and never
have the confidence to say hi to, so hi.
How's that?
Did I pick you up?
If someone said that to me, I would shoot them.
Can you imagine thinking that, can you imagine just anyone talking to anyone on the bus that
you don't know?
Right.
Like just like, so like introducing yourself to someone on the bus.
Also just like, "Nice to meet you, I'm Mr. Vanilla Penis."
My name's Gilroy Penis.
My name's Penis Penis and I am the bus driver.
My name's Penis Penis, I'm a comedian from Atlanta.
I'm taking y'all to January Middle School, let's go.
on the bus driver today the other bus driver sick bruce bruce is as i'm
middle school on this cousin jennery and you had a jennery yeah
nice are really good
status of school i know i don't know
but you know of a m a middle school to know what's up with that
they talk about that everybody is obsessed with the schools around here
yet been rankings of the school yeah it's a very serious and we had a good
one high rate my dad went there
i don't know i'm not from fucking brookline
Damn.
Um, alright, Caleb.
Caleb, I was so happy I matched you that I tried to tell a random lady at the bus stop
about it.
What is with this guy and the fucking bus?
Can you let me finish the fucking pickup line?
He's trying to pick me up!
I wanna have sex!
I wanna have sex so bad you're fucking it up.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for ruining it.
Are you done?
I just- And if you say something about what your cat
is doing while he's in the middle of picking me up, I'm gonna fuck you.
Okay.
Okay?
I'm just I was I was so happy I matched you that I tried to tell a random lady
at the bus stop about it she was not amused.
That's it?
Yeah, that's the...
Why?
He's obsessed with the fucking bus.
Why is he obsessed with the bus?
He's the bus driver.
Yeah, he's...
I thought of all these while I was driving the bus.
Bus to bus.
I was using Tinder on my phone on the bus.
He tried, as people like tried to put their money in the machine, he was throwing these
at him.
Yeah.
The second thing I was like, "Oh, I'm gonna have to get a new phone."
I was like, "Oh, I'm gonna have to get a new phone."
people like try to put their money in the machine he was throwing these at yeah
the second all right number three is what you're on I've had a crush on you for
two hours that is one of the most all-time pickup lines going up to
someone at a bar like right or right as they walk in I saw you at the bus stop
now I'm here say something cool say something cool and then in quotes
it's something cool. This guy's random as fucking shit. Wait, this next one's my
favorite one. Okay. All right, Patrick. You have matched with a weirdo. Please
press 1 to continue the weirdness and potentially get married. Press 2 to
adopt a snow leopard. That shit is weird. That is some weirdo random shit. Can you
imagine your first message on Tinder being like, "Hey, press 1 to maybe get
married to me. Yeah. There's like, just this type of guy is just so like...
A real Patrick.
No. Yeah.
No.
Yeah. Were these helpful, by the way, to pick up college-aged girls?
Are they helpful for you?
No, I didn't write this.
Oh, so what about younger girls? Do they work on them?
I don't know. You wrote the list.
I did not write the list.
I was asking. I asked you a yes or no question. Do these pickup lines work on high school-aged
girls? No.
No, they don't?
(laughter)
- Gotcha!
- Damn.
- Yeah, do your parents know you're a pedophile?
- What?
- You know that?
- Do you guys know you're gay?
- You guys are still mad at me over the breakfast thing,
but look at this, look what you're not getting.
- Oh my, please, please, please, please, please.
- Please, oh my God.
- You don't get this.
- Patrick pulled out his penis.
(laughter)
- Look what you're not getting.
- My pee pee.
- Please, please, please, please.
- Number six.
You must be a small amount of red phosphorus on a wooden stick because we're a match.
Fuck you.
Yeah, you match.
Shut up.
That's pretty good.
Please, I will do anything for it.
Take it, take the pedophile thing back.
Everything's back, you're not a pedophile.
I'm serious.
I can see you crossing your fingers.
My fingers are not crossed.
You're crossing your fingers behind your back.
They're not crossed.
Please, please, please.
He's crossing his eyelids, dude.
You have a drug that I'm addicted to.
Can I use it?
He blew a smoke cloud that said no.
When?
Oh, I caught it.
Go, Patrick, read number seven or something.
If I had a penny for every person that swiped right on me, I'd have 46.
Damn.
The most important thing is I'd spend it all on you.
You're worth 46 cents.
That's all I'm willing to-
Hey, bitch, you're a couple of pennies.
Yeah, bitch, yeah.
You're worth fucking, you're worth two Ed, Edd n Eddy jawbreakers.
Not even.
Yeah, you're worth like, what was it, they just wanted a quarter?
Yeah.
It's so funny, those kids did so much for a quarter.
Damn.
They would spend all episode trying to get a quarter.
And they never got even, the jawbreakers were too big too.
Let me just say.
Well that's the other thing.
If there's a jawbreaker that big, it would cost a thousand dollars.
You know?
But they gotta-
You'd be licking that thing until you die.
You might lick it until you die.
And how do they fit it in their mouths?
They couldn't die.
Because they are in purgatory.
Is that a fan theory?
I love those dude. The rugrats are all inside of Charles Manson's head or whatever.
Yeah.
Spongebob is the...
Spongebob's are actually germs on top of Hitler's mustache.
Well what I heard actually is Spongebob is...
He lives under the sea.
Bikini Bottom is like basically
like the atoll where they tried all the nuclear bombs out at yeah and it made
everything alive yeah yeah yeah it's actually that's sponge bob all the
characters are the seven deadly sins cuz you have sponge bob was gay mr. Krabs is
rich or yeah great Patrick is stupid squidward asshole yeah
Squidward's awesome.
Sandy Cheeks woman.
Most of them were, most of the characters on Spongebob were gay.
The only one who is confirmed not gay is Plankton because he has a computer wife.
Well no, that's pretty gay.
That's why my cousins weren't allowed to watch Spongebob because it was too gay.
I mean how many lovers and joysticks?
You think the computer has lovers and joysticks and you know what those are.
So does a guy.
Joystick look like a peepee.
Yeah, yeah, guys have leather, leathers. Guys have a really thin, guys have like a two-inch
lever on them. Two-inch lever with a big red circle at the top. Yeah, with a Rudolph nose. Yeah.
Yeah, sometimes, yeah, I watch, I watch TV and I get a red penis.
When it's after 11 p.m. and they play the Girls Gone Wild. When you go to channel 206. When I
accidentally flip to an extends commercial. Oh. And they show the hot girl. It's curtains for my
penis yeah it shoots off me like a Roman candle yeah ooh when I saw you specimen
it's curtains from my penis. The eighth part is thank you
almighty gods of tinder I am not worthy. Imagine being a woman and
getting these messages. Imagine being a woman and nevertheless she persists
You know what I mean? Even with all these freaks and creeps online.
Yeah.
Imagine being Spongebob on a dating website and what you'd... I mean, you probably wouldn't
get any swipes.
No, tons of... No. A lot of people would try to fuck him for the clout.
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, I fucked Spongebob.
Fuck Spongebob for the clout.
Yeah.
Yeah, a bunch of...
What'd you do? How was spring break? You'll never believe what happened.
I went to Bikini Bottom.
I fucked Spongebob. He's actually very down-to-earth when you meet him. Yeah he's
actually way cooler. He's a psycho on the show but when you meet him he's just
kind of chill. The money like never changed him. Yeah. He still lives in
that same pineapple. Now we're moving to IRL date pickup lines. I feel like these
ones are gonna be way worse. Oh they'll be so much worse. He's got a picture of
of Michael Cera right there yeah what Scott Scott Pilgrim yeah oof that's a
yikes from me yeah you know that awarded one yike don't they know that Scott
Pilgrim uh you're not supposed to idolize you're not supposed to idolize a
character because in the movie he he he lives with a gay guy he also does kung
fu and he does come through racist which is racist he plays dance dance
revolution yeah which is also racist yeah it's also racist I'm told by Patrick
Patrick tells me that pretty often.
Yeah.
Is that it's racist to play Dance Dance Revolution?
Yeah. I go to Dave and Buster's and I stand there and I protest Dance Dance Revolution.
Yeah.
I stand there with a sign.
Because there's no white avatars in the game.
Yeah.
It's great. Dance Dance Revolution is racist against white people because the characters are a
shadow.
There's not a guy who looks like me.
Yeah.
It looks like my shadow.
There's a - I knew a kid who lost like a hundred pounds playing Dance Dance Revolution.
Really?
Yeah.
That's racist.
It was very racist.
It's racist.
Wow, he is racist.
Yeah.
I'm gonna put him in jail.
He should go to jail for that. I just thought, I mean, just what a good - it's - that's like
the silliest way to lose weight.
Yeah.
Yeah, and it doesn't make you - like, it doesn't make you good at dancing. It just makes you
really good at Dance Dance Revolution.
Right.
You know what I mean?
You have to - if you want to go dance somewhere, you have to imagine the triangle.
the rose.
Like dancing to a revolution.
Walking into the club, like yeah, dressed like Night at the Roxbury.
Just fucking, just dancing in a perfect square.
Just putting your feet like.
Yeah, holding on to two bars, you bring a walker, then you just start beasting on the
ground.
Only moving your feet, just breathing super, super heavy in your date's face.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm going to do that.
That's my pickup line.
The first IRL pickup line is, "If you had to binge watch a show for a few days, what
would you go with?"
What?
That's it.
That's your opening line?
You're supposed to say something sexual.
Yeah.
You know?
If you had to binge suck my penis for a few days, would you want to suck my penis in balls?
That's true.
And then you hand her a note in class.
It's like circle yes or no.
You say that out loud, then hand her a note.
And then you walk away because you can't handle the rejection that might happen.
bartender says, "What's that note? Do you want to read the whole bar? What's on that note?"
The next one is...
He sees him slipping something into the girl's drink. He's like,
"Oh, oh, do you have enough to share with the rest of the bar?"
Number 10, what film can you quote all day, every day?
Probably Elf.
Yeah, Merry Christmas.
Santa.
Yeah, I know tons of elf quotes.
"We wish you a merry Christmas."
"Happy holidays."
"Dad!"
Yeah.
What else is an elf quote?
"I'm Will Ferrell."
"I'm elf."
"Hey."
"Hey, bitch."
"Hey, how you doing? I'm Will Ferrell."
"I'm a Will Ferrell."
"New York, the Big Apple."
"Oh, it's me, Jon Favreau!"
[laughter]
That's my elf quote.
"It's Jon Favreau!"
"Oh, how you doing? It's me, Jon Favreau!"
Forget he's in that movie, he's a doctor.
He's also the director, the doctor of the movie.
The doctor.
That is the doctor in film, the film doctor.
Number 11 is, "I wish I was cross-eyed so I could see you twice."
No.
But he is completely cross-eyed.
He doesn't realize it.
"Damn, I wish I had fucked up eyes."
Yeah.
His eyes are crossed outward.
He's looking at two different girls on either side of her.
I want to see the world one little bit at a time.
you think I should see next what's the magic says someone going up to you just
fucking saying yeah these all sound like they're like pitbull lines yeah yeah
I'm taking you worldwide Dolly I want to see the world which part should I see
next what do you want her do you want her to
sit the dream scenarios she's like my vagina my buddy oh yeah my whole yeah
bathroom you wanna see yeah my the bathroom of my boobs in it yeah they
have a bathroom with boobs. They should have a glory hole that's two cutouts for
boobs. So you put the boobs in the hole? And then guys can look. You're not allowed to touch it.
It's a sign that says no touching. There's like a six layer sheet of
bulletproof glass. Yeah so you can't shoot the boobs either. People go in
there they get scared of the boobs so scared that they try to shoot them
they're terrifying mm-hmm number 13 we should go out otherwise my friends will
never believe me what is that yeah what is that mean number 14 if I can guess
the first two digits of your mobile phone number you have to fill in the
rest deal hint this is it this hint is not you'll say this but he says hint
it's most likely going to be 0 1 7 what are you talking that just like the
area code where he lives yeah he thinks all phone numbers yeah all phone numbers
pretty much yeah he's just been stuck in Albany his whole life yeah yeah at the
Chili's yeah your mobile phone number that's it can you may also yeah like if
I have your mobile phone can I guess your mobile phone number you know what
shoot go for it. 9-1-0. 9-1-1. Number 15, let's meet up. Worst case scenario, you have a
laugh and a free drink. I don't know if that's the worst. I don't think that's the worst case scenario.
It is a much worse case scenario. My dad, I guess he said this to my mom once, he said, "Hey, do you
want to go to my place and fuck and have pizza?" and then he said,
"What's the matter? You don't like pizza?"
Because she said no.
She said no to that.
And now they're married.
Now they're married. They've been married a long time. They have a bunch of kids.
Yeah, well, because he said, "What's the matter? You don't like pizza?" And she was like, "Oh,
I guess that's a really good point." All right, I do like pizza.
Okay, I guess I do like pizza.
You have a point there.
And then he made her pregnant.
He filled her up with pizza.
Oh, come on.
That's your mom, dude.
Leave that to me, man.
I'm not supposed to say shit like that.
Don't ever say "fill your own mom up."
You're disgusting, dude.
What the fuck?
It's not gross.
It is gross.
It's objectively gross.
Jesus Christ.
No, it's a fake.
Unless she's your stepmom, then that's awesome.
Yeah.
Your Chinese stepmom.
You could never fill up a woman with pizza.
Not even your mom.
Fill her up like how much pizza could your girl hold?
this bitch full of a gallon of pizza. Yeah, my bitch can hold two tombstones
worth of pizza.
And I'll save it for later.
Yeah. Yeah.
The next one is
do you eat or drink?
Because I think we should do one of those things together soon.
Do you eat or drink?
do you have a slobbery do you eat or drink and you know where i can go to eat or drink
do you like lunch from space balls
i wonder what this guy looks like uh there's a picture of my there is let's yeah that was
michael it was at the beginning it's him and his new girlfriend that he got john f kim oh okay whoa
it downloaded you click on his name it downloads as an html page oh he's kind of what he looks like
He has two articles, two very big articles, it's this one and a very personal letter to
Donald Trump.
To Mr. Trump.
"Why guys sometimes prefer video games.
Why I would still wear my high school."
"Our society's impending doom."
"If you could share your mind with."
"Firearms are still a necessity despite the huge mistakes of Colin Kaepernick."
Oh my god.
the psychology of the high-tech all but i'd sexual
how climate change has affected
the simple product thought process that explains and there's a photo of a
minion so must be the minions yet this guy's cool is one follower
damn but f
ball is about to have four players once we're done with that that for fall
knows no that was a chance all fall god damn it man
uh... the world is literally begging for me and you to go conquer it how about
this weekend
that sounds like a psycho
do you want to conquer the world? I would like to conquer something with you
let's go be Genghis Khan, Kublai Khan
let's go put ourselves into the gene pool let's go be Wrath of Khan
yeah let's go be Ricardo Montalbán
you've clearly got great taste, know any good restaurants?
This just sounds like you're talking to your friend's mom.
Yeah.
You know?
I would not tell my friend's mom.
She has great taste.
Me neither.
You clearly have great taste in kids' friends.
Because I'm here, bitch.
Do you like any restaurants?
Oh, he has the disclaimer at the end.
You should have put this at the middle, at the beginning, dude.
The middle and the beginning.
It says, "In an IRL situation, just saying these lines would be weird.
Therefore, make sure you go up to them and introduce yourself first, then use these pickup
lines to start and carry on interesting conversations.
Okay, I want to point out that this next, the last two
have, both of them have the word "shall" in them. Yeah.
They both say "shall we". The first one is "I would love to be the reason you
delete dating apps forever". Oh my gosh. Shall we have a drink this
weekend? And then the next one is "shall we flip a coin? Heads you go out
with me, tails I go out with you". See that one's at least recognizable as
like a pickup line. Yeah. You know. Shall we? Shall we? The rest of these are... Just go
up to a girl and go, "Shall we?" Shall we? All of these read like a bat, like you took a pickup
line and translated it to Chinese and then translated it back. Yeah. Yeah. Is that the
end of them? I guess that's the end of them. Let's see what else this guy has on here. Oh,
well we already... Well, we should definitely look at... I just want to look at guns being a necessity.
yeah well
uh... me
to that
here is a happy page a camera has to go to
uh... hacker type reduct on
on the one i click on
student firearms are necessity despite this is just in the article
you know what is it's
despite what happened in los angeles
i
uh...
despite what happened las vegas
and he's not only is going to have a moment in our own has
firearm death stats
cool just a long article
so i don't know this was a huge mistakes of colin kaepernick
which ones that he would mistakes in the make
uh...
what do you have a i guess and that's what the article saying
however when he said the following he crossed the line
i have great respect for the men and women that fought for this country and
that's a sad day he crossed the fair line in the same buddy
the site i was a troops the psychology behind sexual assault uh...
shut up john
uh... i like him
he's cool i think he's a good guy what is what is his origin indiana country boy
who likes to write and share ideas what is his personal letter to trump
to mister trump
dear trump for this church this christmas and i would like
a sega game sir if you don't mind i'm going to cut to the chase we are
ruining the country we love in a door
well did he's taken down
Yeah, this article has a whole 163 views.
Badass.
I wonder if he's made any money off of this stuff.
Awesome.
Hopefully.
He deserves it for the other one.
Go to Odyssey, search meal rankings.
Okay.
Look up lunch.
I'm just gonna search meal rankings.
We're not gonna look up lunch.
Why?
Just look up lunch.
Because lunch would be like the...
It's skewed towards you.
No.
Yeah, exactly.
We're trying to be agnostic here.
Let's see.
Vegetarian meals ranked by my bacon loving dad.
Whoa.
I'm not seeing any meal rankings here.
45 Disney dogs ranked from the worst to the goodest.
No.
Yeah.
Breakfast is the most important meal of the day for students.
Click on it.
No, fuck you.
You guys said we couldn't look up lunch.
It's the most important meal of the day.
I didn't look up.
We couldn't look up lunch, but.
starts your day off on the right foot improves memory and concentration and
increases energy. That's why you're stupid. Three reasons. So give us the reasons why lunch is good.
Lunch is good because you can get a sandwich. You keep going back to the sandwich. You can get a burger.
A burger? It's a different kind of sandwich. It's just you can get a salad. Basically you could if
you if you want dinner for lunch go ahead. What's you want breakfast for lunch go ahead you can't
can't eat dinner for breakfast.
So it sounds like you just like, well first of all, you can't, boy you were saying, you
wanted to eat a grilled cheese for breakfast and you say you can't eat dinner for breakfast,
you just, you just like food and you think that you can only eat any food in the middle
of the day.
Yeah, you can.
Once you break out of society's cage and you realize that you can eat any food you want
at any time of day, you are going to love breakfast.
Patrick was trained his whole life to, because he had a feeding time of one o'clock when they
would fill up his trough with slop and big pink slop and slime. I did not eat big pink slop. You did man.
You would eat a chunky... I'd eat regular slop. No you'd eat... no you like pink slop which is girl slop.
No because once you blend all this shit together it becomes brown. No but you would get specifically
pink slop because you like to do girl stuff. No. And girls are a pink color and you like to eat
pink slop. No. Yeah I don't know what to tell you. Why would... how do they make the slop pink first
of all. It just comes out that way. Yeah, because they put it on the girls.
It's because girls make it and the pink comes off of their skin and goes on to...
The pink comes off of their makeup. Yeah. And it goes, it falls into the slop. And then you eat it at home.
And you eat it in a big, you eat it in a big bowl. And you put it on your face like it's makeup.
Right, you eat it in a trough. I don't eat slop in a trough. You eat slop in a trough like a urinal at a
NASCAR event. No. Yeah, and you pee in on the, you pee in the big, the big trough with the ice in it.
Yeah, when Patrick goes to a NASCAR event, he sees the trough and he goes, "Ooooh!"
He sticks his mouth in it and he eats up all the ice and all the water.
The ice?
Yeah.
Why did they do that?
That's funny.
I will admit, peeing on ice.
We should go to a NASCAR race.
Yeah?
We should go to the one?
Did you see Trump flying Air Force One over a NASCAR?
That's pimp.
That was sick.
Yeah.
It sucks that that's cool.
It's cool, dude.
So cool.
NASCAR, why don't they call it Fast Car?
By Tracy Chapman.
(singing)
Patrick likes music by people named Tracy.
Yeah, that's like the pink slop of music.
Do you guys know that's a black woman?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Tracy Chapman, Fast Car?
I had never heard that.
I thought it was a white guy until like three years ago.
Did you know Banana Pancakes, that's a black woman too.
No.
Yeah, it is.
I thought Tracy Chapman was a white guy.
No, did you know Ashton Kutcher is a black woman?
Yeah man.
Did you know Caleb is a black woman?
You did know that?
Yeah I did know that.
How did you know that?
Because it's not true.
Dude you just said yes to anything.
Oh but did you know that song Bobby Caldwell?
No.
What you don't do or what you do for love?
No music you have ever listened to or heard.
Yeah that's true.
No.
Yeah, well that guy, that's a white guy.
Well then it's like, I guess you wonder where I've been.
I bet you when you get into a bar with a touch tunes I bet you go fucking crazy.
Yeah, I did once.
I bet you fucking.
We did at that pool place in Sherman Oaks.
Yeah, you loaded up with like $15.
Yeah, you spent so much money on that.
That was $10, that wasn't that bad.
No, you spent more than $10.
You spent a lot of money.
No, I spent $10.
Yeah, you spent more than $10.
I remember that.
Dude, you spent $180.
No.
You spent $300 and then you had to buy your plane ticket back.
Yeah.
No.
You did.
by my plane ticket but you actually sold your plane ticket in order to spend more
money on the touch team i wanted to listen to you know i was there
because i felt like playing this pool and listening to black sabbath was very
cool it is not a bit it was cool it wasn't we listen to sweet leaf
it's a great song never i can tell you a single black sabbath some brick iron man
that's a movie time and move it robert denny junior they play the song in it
win
when he goes and he suits up
yes in the song then
See it's not a real song. I've already sang too much on the podcast. You're right. You're going
to give away your voice. Yeah. I need to practice. Patrick secretly has an unbelievable singing
voice but he has to save it because he's going on American Idol next week. Yep. That's right.
And let me tell you what buddy, you're going to Hollywood. I've been waiting for them to say that
to me for so long. I got you pre-vetted with the judges. Yeah. The new ones? Simon's not there
Simon's coming, he's coming this week. You know it's on ABC now. He's gonna look at you man. He's gonna look at you bad.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, he's gonna give you, he's gonna, he's gonna go Gordon Ramsay on those, on that ass. Yeah. Gonna go fucking
With his new like, botox. Yeah, with his big, with his chatterbox teeth. Yeah, his big chatterbox teeth and his eyes that go down.
His sunken in eyes. Yeah. Yeah, he looks like a corpse. Yeah, he looks like the Bye-Bye Man.
yeah cuz he's constantly saying bye-bye to bad contest exactly yeah bye-bye
goodbye bye-bye oh there was one I remember now you get off my fucking
stage now he fucking owns yeah Simon Bowles he was so mean compared to Randy
and Paula Paula was too nice Randy too cool mm-hmm Simon just right no Simon
too mean but when they would have like a guest judge like Christina Aguilera or Steven Tyler or
Steven Aguilera those two. Honestly if I had to get a blow job for one of them I don't know which one
I would choose. Christina Aguilera or Steven Tyler. Probably choose Randy just because he seems nice.
I would just imagine he was live. Do you guys know Tyler Stevens? No. I made him up. How is he doing?
I went to high school with a Tyler Stevens.
Really? I made a you didn't I made him up.
I just said I made him up so you couldn't have gone to high school with them.
Okay, so the the judges for the new American Idol is
Katy Perry, Luke Bryan and Lionel Richie and also some someone named Bobby Bones
is the in-house mentor.
Remember the fuck Bobby Bones?
It's a skeleton.
Yeah, Ren and Stimpy are the new judges.
That would be sick.
They would fuck it up so bad.
Oh my god, they would root they would they would make everyone sing happy happy joy joy. Yeah. Yeah, they would put the log on them
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I'd say a mummified bog man. I'm a fight. I'm a fight bog man. I'm a fight the bog man
All right, we ran out of the list so we're gonna go yeah, we have to read do we have any new patrons
We have a new one new on patreon
I listen to this today and you live in Boston me and Tom O'Shea are doing a
roast battle tomorrow at Laff. Tonight tech. No, it's tomorrow night. Yeah, so it's
tomorrow night the 20th. So is it tomorrow night today? No, no I know
what I just shut up. Tomorrow night. If you're listening to this the day it
comes out it is tomorrow night at Laff Boston.
Say the date. But if you're listening to it. It's the 20th. If you're listening to it the day after it comes out it's tonight.
sure yeah and if you're listening to it two days later it was yesterday and three
days later was two days ago then we could keep going forever yeah yeah it's called
the present because every day is a gift that's true yeah yeah but come see it
it'll be very fun former guest Tom O'Shea yeah we're just gonna rip into
each other and rail each other yeah and just fucking rail each other and do each
other we have one new patron John Duggan. John Duggan. Duggan? I think it's Duggan.
Duggan Nash and Ormald Nash have just subscribed. John Duggan Duggan. Josh Duggar.
Do you guys remember the movie Dougal? Yeah. Yeah. Thanks. John Stewart's in that movie.
Thanks for remembering it. John Stewart is in Dougal? Yeah he's Dougal. No he plays the
villain. John Stewart? Yeah. Dougal's the villain. He's the villain. He's my dad's
villain