You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Patrick Fallon's through the wall of list.
[Music]
You're a crap monster.
[Explosion]
Patrick is so penis starved that when he looks at anything it morphs into a penis in front of his eyes.
Like a starving...
Oh, the shark and the penis fish are friends.
I recorded so I could say that.
Oh man, that's rude.
Oh, it's a tiny shark. It's a tiny leopard shark.
Patrick is a baby.
it look like baby movies I'm actually it looks like what does the fish look like
this big guy looks like a penis yeah cuz you're gonna starve I'm not penis
star haha I am NOT you are did you oh you're not because you've actually been
eating you've been having a lot of penises no yeah yeah yeah you have a
surplus I don't have a surplus yeah you do you go on Facebook market and you
I look up surplus penis on Facebook marketplace.
Factory reject.
Yeah.
Factory misprint penis.
Mark it down.
Six dollar misprint coin penis.
You go to that shelf in the grocery store and you look for a really old penis.
My penis is red.
Thank you very much.
I need to return it.
Can I have a white penis?
Turn off this movie.
Please turn this movie off.
Turn the fucking movie off.
Turn the movie off or I'm going to turn you off. I know where your button is.
Yeah, only Caleb knows where Patrick's button is.
I do know where his button is and I could push it.
Turn off the TV, Patrick.
I might flick your button if you're not careful.
Do not touch my button.
I might do it, too.
I might rub your button up and down until you turn off halfway.
He made it into a weird thing.
That's what you do to a computer.
You don't rub a computer's button.
Yeah, you do.
I've never rubbed a computer.
No, yeah, he did there's a girl computer you find the button and you fucking you you're right here. Yeah, fuck that button
Cuz it's okay. It's a girl
Yeah
Not okay for Patrick. There is a reason he's not weighing in on this one. That's true Patrick the idea of
Fucking a girl computer is just a step to our metric
That's beyond the pale a girl computer. Oh my god, it would never exist
Why yeah cuz it's sexism they won't make one. Mm-hmm. Yeah
When Siri scared of how power Siri came out a bit. Well Siri is a computer, but it's your phone
It's a computer. It's a girl. It's a guy computer, but they put a girl voice on it. Yeah, it's true
It's actually just a guy. It's like it's a
Kestrel, you know, it's so it's so messed up that
Girls don't even get full computers. They just get smaller phones. I
Know yeah
Yeah, it's seriously fucked up that when boys get to go on every website girls can only go on BuzzFeed and Netflix
I've literally never seen a girl use a tower PC in my life
Really? Yeah, they don't do it. I've seen girls use tower PCs. Yeah on the websites you look at it's pictures
Calm yeah, I bet you on the dark web computer. Calm the closest I've seen is I saw a girl accidentally use an alienware laptop
one time
Yeah, she thought that it was a big makeup palette and she opened it up, but it was a
computer and she started screaming because there was video games on it.
Because she saw the letters on the keyboard.
She saw the alien and she thought she was getting abducted.
She still thought it was a makeup palette, she thought it was a mirror, saw the alien
and said, "Oh my God, I'm an alien."
At first she thought she was watching that movie Paul. She thought that was on the screen.
And then she when she got she got more confused when she realized that it was
some sort of big phone. What was that movie Paul about? It's about an alien that
smokes weed? It's basically Ted with Paul. It's Ted with Paul. Okay. And he's British.
Just I'm imagining that. Or he's not British. No he's Seth Rogen. Simon Pegg is British in the movie.
I'm just imagining the pitch for that movie is just a guy going in.
It's like Ted but Paul.
It's Ted but Paul.
But he's Paul.
We're in.
Say no more.
Ted was huge for us.
And Paul came out before Ted.
Well then Paul was Ted.
Paul is Ted but with a guy.
Ted was Paul.
Which came out?
Paul is Ted with a guy.
Ted is Paul.
Hey Dougal, which came out first, Ted or Paul?
You put Dougal in your bedroom?
Yeah, and needed an alarm.
I need an alarm.
use your phone and he's a rooster he's the one talking about get a real go to the
store a little clucker get a Rhode Island red yeah and put it in your room why
don't you just make a contraption to shake your bed and pour water on you and
make your toast in the morning when you wake up yeah you yeah that starts with
like a mouse that wakes up you stupid running the fat mouse from Cinderella
yeah he knocks over he knocks over a bunch of marbles and then my marbles
slowly some of the marbles go into different places and fall onto the
ground but one marble falls into another cup which falls over into like a banana
cream pie for some reason and then slaps you in the face. Sorry I was late for work this morning.
And then you wake up with my alarm clock back together.
Covered in pie. You have pie all over your face.
Pie all over your face and a huge boner.
Sorry my alarm clock was acting up.
The Viagra pie got in my mouth.
Paul came out one year before Ted.
Whoa.
That's what the guy.
Mark Walker walked into Paul and he said "One year from now"
Holy crap! I'm gonna make this my movie!
Oh my god!
I'm gonna make this a movie about a bear!
Ted is good.
Ted, yeah. I haven't seen Ted.
I liked it when I was like a younger.
When you were a younger.
Did you know that it was filmed around here?
Did you know they used an actual bear to film it?
And then they used CGI to turn it into a toy?
They actually killed the first Ted.
And then used a second Ted.
Yeah, and because they killed the first Ted
first
get married at I said I haven't seen Ted yeah I think so yeah there's like the
church in Cambridge giant old churches and yeah yeah I don't know if it's the
one in Cambridge or if it's the one like Arlington the one like in the
Arlington stop the church at the end of Ted well yeah I know that I know that
real-life church I don't I've never seen Ted well I said the third time I'm saying
I've seen Ted over. I know that you know that you know that church. No. I'm gonna
look up Ted's church. Near Copley. Oh it's that one. Oh yeah I know that. Yeah. Is it that one?
It might be that one. I don't know. I haven't seen Ted. That's the one next to the Arlington stop. Don't make me say it again.
Wait the one on the corner that's like the garden is right across. Yeah I think so.
That's the one. That's the one I'm thinking. That's the one next to the Arlington stop.
That might be the one from Ted. Whoa that's insane. So the church that we're thinking
about might be the one from Ted. Yeah. If you go there and you say show me Ted's church too.
If you say show me the Ted, they legally have to show it to you.
All right, I looked up Ted's church.
Nice. They're going to find some church in like Nashville.
I heard that Paul actually used the same church for the scene where Paul gets married to Ted.
In space, on a space church. But really, they didn't even use a real space church.
They just cropped it out.
Yeah, they used Ted's church.
They used Ted Paul.
Oh, there's like film location tours of Boston.
Of Ted?
let's yeah there's like a ted tour yeah let's go on a ted tour. Ted filming locations, Fenway Park,
the Hatch Shell, New England Aquarium, Public Garden. Guys if we work hard enough, that's just
one day tour of Boston that's not yeah I know. What is the landmark? Going on a New York City
tour, movie tour, the Empire State Building. You might recognize this from King Kong. Yeah you
might have seen in the uh Elf, it's an elf. Uh we're gonna skip this next stop uh something.
Yeah go get an elf tour. Something happened in 2001 uh we're gonna have to skip. Oh shit he's in
in the trash. He's in the trash. Double microphone. Yeah baby. I just went double
microphone. I just went double micro. It's not probably won't be able to tell.
But just so anybody was listening I had two microphones in my mouth and if
anybody's listening and it was really cool. Patrick always has to go fight his
cats in the middle of every episode and now he's walking towards me with his
with his cat's balls. Oh fuck I hate him dude. Why do you, you wonder why I hate him?
It's because you stick his nuts in his balls. That's not his fault, that's mine. He's a good guy.
Oh I hate you, that's what it is. Yeah but you're the, you know. Why do you hate Yoda? I don't
know who that is. He's a kind soul. Is that the one whose balls were just in my face? Yeah. I
should have slapped him out of your ass. If he was like one iota less human
looking I would have slapped the shit out of him. He's back in the trash. Oh my god he's in the recycling.
Just let him eat it. Why would you think he would? No! You didn't let him eat the recycling. It's funny. You didn't close it. Why would you think he would
he would just not go in? He was going to recycling because it was full of cans. Triple microphone.
I used Cameron's that time too.
Okay. Did you close it this time? He's gonna get in. It's closed. He's gonna get in. He's not gonna get in.
Let's start the list.
Three, two, no.
Let's talk more about Ted and Paul.
Yeah.
Ted and Paul.
What if they made a movie where Ted and Paul meet?
Like Alien.
Yeah.
Whoever wins.
Whoever wins wins.
And they become best friends because they both love smoking weed.
They both love smoking weed.
And then Mark Wahlberg and Simon Pegg have to also fight.
Yeah, but then that's like a daddy's home situation.
Yeah.
Yeah, but instead of Will Ferrell, Simon Pegg.
And instead of Mark-- no, he isn't.
Yeah, instead of Mark Wahlberg, Mark Wahlberg.
Yeah.
Instead of Mark Wahlberg, Mark L. Wahlberg from Antiques Roadshow.
Mark L. Wahlberg.
That's the host of Antiques Roadshow.
His name is Mark Wahlberg?
His name is Mark L. Wahlberg.
He's the Spanish version of Mark Wahlberg.
Mark the Wahlberg.
Yeah.
It'd be pretty funny if they recast for-- they made Ted 3 and they recast.
They're like, "Oh, Mark Wahlberg doesn't want to do Ted 3. We're gonna get Mark L. Wahlberg."
Yeah.
Now, that would be a laugh to me.
I don't think I've ever seen Antiques Roadshow.
Really?
Yeah.
It's pretty fun to watch.
Do they just look at old stuff?
It's really bright.
Oh, it's the church.
It's the church by the Prudential Center.
Okay.
Nice.
Yeah.
It's cool, man.
They just like, you know, they talk about like, "Oh, you can see in this painting.
Here's where you can tell how it's real."
It's pretty.
It's good just like spacing out TV.
I'm going to bring you on that.
Okay.
Yeah, and they're going to be like, "You can tell this is a girl because of the penis."
This is worth $3 million.
This is worth $3 gazillion.
They play Ted.
They play, uh...
They play mini-golf at the Route 1 mini-golf place with the big dinosaur.
Oh my god, no way!
Did you know in Patrick's life-
They go to the landmark mini-golf place?
The place with the dinosaur?
You've seen it.
Yeah, I know. That's why I-
I'm gonna fuck you up, man.
Why?
I just wanted to let you guys know about the filming location.
I haven't seen Ted!
Well, no, now once you watch it-
I would have recognized you can keep an eye out. Okay. Did you know they go to Pizza Planet and Toy Story?
Mm-hmm. I'm serious. Have you heard in the Spongebob movie? They open the Krusty Krab 2?
Fuck yeah, I do remember that. That doesn't happen. They do man. That's literally the opening scene.
Do you recognize? They go to the ocean in the Spongebob movie.
(laughter)
- Yeah, that's right.
They go to the bottom of the ocean.
You might recognize it.
We're doing a Spongebob tour.
- Dude, in Star Wars, they go to outer space.
- Yeah, it's fucked up.
- We're going on a Star Wars tour.
- Star Wars and Spongebob tour.
- Yeah.
- Ground to air.
- You go up in a rocket that goes up in his base
and just falls into the ocean.
- Get to the ocean.
- Well, in the middle.
- They actually, they filmed Spongebob here.
They also filmed Finding Nemo here.
- Yeah, it's a Spongebob.
- And Jaws.
- It's a Spongebob, Jaws.
only filmed half of Jaws. Yeah, it's true. And most of Finding Nemo. In Jaws they go to the beach.
The beach. So the way that this tour works is you start at the beach, you go
into the water, then you go up into the sky where Airplane was filmed, and
then you go to space. And planes. And Top Gun. This is where Top Gun was filmed.
and guardians of gahool part of this is where they film guardians of gahool
you know it's a sky I mean prove me wrong it'll be a hundred dollars and then well
they also filmed it in a tree yeah you go to the tree where the elves live and
then they go to the beach this is actually also the tree that bugs bunny
climbed in that one episode yeah I'm guessing there's an episode he climbed the tree
and then they go to the gym and the guys like yeah this is where I film my
I come here and I film the girl you might have seen my videos on live leak yeah
and this is also where they film dodgeball yeah yeah as well yeah this is
what's a globo gym what's it called glaze globo gym and the average Joe's
and average Joe's yeah what a terrible name for a gym mm-hmm yeah why would I
go to a gym called average Joe's you think you would I'm trying to get I'm
trying to get it swole yeah and also all the gym equipment is so crappy why they
want to keep that dump open why does that guy throw no wrench at them oh yeah
that would not be that movie would not fly today you couldn't throw a wrench in
adjust in long and also you couldn't have a guy in a wheelchair be funny I
wouldn't they wouldn't let that fly anymore this is actually the wheelchair
they filmed I would not you could not have you could not have ripped horn in a
movie nowadays.
It's true.
Nowadays they wouldn't let you do it.
This is actually the chair that they filmed.
Rip Torn's.
I don't know, just a chair.
What's the movie with a chair in it?
Men in Black.
This is the chair where they filmed Men in Black.
That one scene.
The white egg chair?
What?
The big white egg chair from Men in Black?
That thing's cool.
Yeah.
That's where Rip Torn sits.
I like those little...
A lot of sitting down.
I like the bug guy.
Yeah.
of the little guys yeah like a like Liz Warren posture yeah yeah yeah yeah
she's one of them she is she's tall alien oh fuck she's been lying about her
race and her species yeah what is he's an alien she's an alien mm-hmm yeah what
are those things called what the little bug aliens bug aliens men in black they
try to have sex with Rosario Dawson in Men in Black 2. Which would have been one of
the most all-time win. All-time best scenes. Yeah. This is my bedroom. What's weird about that scene is that
Will Smith makes Rosario Dawson stay at the apartment. They're called Neebles.
The Neebles apartment. He makes them stay there. Don't they look like Elizabeth Warren?
He makes them stay there and she like, and the whole time Will Smith is like, "Stay away from them."
This is from the Men in Black Wiki. "Neeble is a male worm and one of the four main
worms in the Men in Black series. Like the other worms, he is addicted to coffee and
is semi-perverted." Yeah, he said watch out for Neeble. So they're not Neebles,
they're just called worms. Oh, Neeble is one of the worms. Neeble is a worm.
Mm-hmm. Huh. There's an ad for online poker here. No need to hide your poker face. "The worms seem to love
coffee and are very energetic and even perverted." That's kind of a logical...
yeah coffee makes you perverted the worms are ruled by an emperor who is slightly
taller than the average one but is rather heavy set did they show that if
most if not all worms no I don't think so most if not all worms cannot drink any
coffee as it is considered a movie which is believed to be coffee cannot be grown
on their homeworld or coffee prices are extraordinarily high or exports of their
coffee are not that good worms tend to panic in times of crisis and are likely
to cry out rather than fight.
It's all that coffee. Makes you anxious.
The worms are not very good dressers, as when disguised as humans,
they show parts of their worm anatomy like toes or antennae
and can be a major issue
when on Earth and a headache for the men in black.
I feel like they do a pretty good job
if all you notice is the antennae
popping out of it.
I wouldn't be like, "There's a worm in you."
They get their...
The worms are fleshed out in Men in Black,
the animated series.
That's where they see their emperor and stuff.
they do that when they do an animated series and just pick like like the group
of four things that are the same guy yeah just make the entire series about that
like whoa look at the emperor worm damn this is just a guy from Futurama I know
yeah what's his name that looks like from Percy I oh my god what's his name
whatever Chris grob gris-grob gris-grob gris-grob Chris cross Chris cross
Chris Graub will make you jump, jump. Yeah. Daddy Mac will make you...
Junk. Junk, junk.
Junk, junk. What's the thing?
What if Futurama was live action? They could never.
I bet Leela would be even hotter in real life.
Okay. Who would you choose to play Leela?
I know who I would choose. Probably Leela.
I'd choose Leela. Probably choose Leela.
That's right.
How could I not find the name of this guy? And I got to his planet or whatever this is.
I got to this guy's planet and I couldn't even figure out his name.
It was Lurr. I hate when I get to a guy's planet and can't figure out the name of the guy.
Alright, let's do the list.
Wait, there's...
Let's read more about the Emperor Worm.
The Emperor Worm is the leader of the worms. Unlike the other worms, the Emperor is large and in charge.
It's so clear that this is written by like a middle school like this whole
wiki is written by a middle schooler. God damn it.
He is hugely fat and almost double the height of the worms.
Hugely fat.
He usually shows up unannounced to the men in black.
Here he usually brings two big cases which the agents always carry in.
The Emperor is careless and defenseless so the other worms must watch him.
He is also disappointed in the worms as coffee is only reserved for royalty.
He appears in the episode "The Big Bad Bug Syndrome" and "The Mine Mine Mine Syndrome".
he's a scenario like syndrome yeah i don't know
that'd be really if all of the
yeah it looks like it is every episode is something syndrome
let's look
because i just saw one second
because i clicked on this look
the doggy dog syndrome the jack-o-lantern syndrome
what the hell
that's smart you gotta add here for the goo goo dolls on tour
whoa we should go yeah we should go why is every because you're a baby
no yeah and you like goo goo gaga no i like iris no you're a bit you're a girl baby like the song
that no i like the songs i like the song iris no you don't every single episode is how many
fucking episodes i think that was only on for like one like 50 something what if it's not looks like
it was on for three seasons so if it's not called syndrome it's just whatever like little kid who's
like he's like editing the men in black wiki who has a syndrome they had an episode called the end
Game Syndrome and it was two parts. Looks like Avengers copied somebody.
Avengers, they were gonna call it End Game Syndrome. They were gonna call it Infinity Syndrome and End Game
Syndrome. But then they found out about the real Infinity Syndrome and thought it would be
insensitive. Yeah. So they took out, they took out all the syndrome. Yeah. So they
just called it Infinity. Oh my god. They were like, that's not, there's nothing to it like that. No, Syndrome from Incredibles.
He was gonna be in it. He was gonna be in it. He was gonna be in it. That's Thanos. Holy crap.
- Yeah, and he was gonna get, yeah,
and he was gonna fight Mr. Incredible.
- And the Emperor Worm was gonna be fat in the movie.
- The Emperor Worm was gonna be fat,
and he was gonna be twice the size.
- Oh my God, he was gonna be the Hulk.
- Yeah.
- SpongeBob was gonna be the Emperor Worm.
SpongeBob was gonna play Robert Downey Jr.
in Sherlock Holmes' Game of Shadows,
but Rocco, from Modern Life,
he ended up in Rocco's Modern Life instead.
- Yeah, it's super annoying whenever they do recasts.
I hate when they do reshoots of all my favorite movies
right before they come out and you see all the cool yeah cuz I was absolutely
certain that Sullivan the frog would have been in Avengers endgame I thought
apparently they cut out all the scenes right before it came out they cut I was
convinced you would have literally major story there is literally a part of a
majors in game where they went to planet hamster and they cut out food in your
jacket they cut out the entire thing no and what the hell's going on over there
Just leave him alone. Just think about something else.
He's eating a bag. He's holding on... oh it's because Dom's lunch box is in there.
These things have cat-like reflexes. They're cats. Oh now you're all shy.
Whenever I see a plot hole in a movie I'm like oh this is clear evidence
evidence they cut Planet Hamster out of this one too.
They cut out Planet Hamster.
One of the actors looked into the camera and tried to tell the public the truth about the
incoming hamster asteroid and Evil Hollywood cuts it out.
Evil Anti-Hamster Hollywood creates propaganda.
Yeah.
There was a whole scene, or a whole arc of the love story between Mary the marsupial
and the Hungry Hamster and they trashed it because they thought it wouldn't do well in China with the
whole Hong Kong protest going on. Yeah. They thought it wouldn't sell because Marcy the Marsupial is
Chinese. Yeah. And Taiwanese. And Hungry Hamster is Taiwanese, she's Chinese,
mainland Chinese and they thought that... They have a love story. Yeah, and they thought that
that it would just bomb overseas.
They thought it would end the conflict and they have a stake in chaos.
Yeah, exactly.
They thought that this scene would be so pure that the protest would end.
But they needed that because they're part of the prison industrial complex.
Which, yeah, it was strange because then the hungry hamster did become like a symbol of
revolution in the Hong Kong protests.
Exactly.
wearing hungry hamster masks and and throwing acorns at the cops.
Just big acorns. You may kill one of us but you will never defeat all of us. Yeah. We are
hamster, we are hungry. We are the hamsters. We are hungry. So the list today is the top
ten penis shapes on the top tens dot-com from user Holly Rolo. Before we get
started what shape penis do you guys have? Penis shape? No you don't know?
Probably have normal. Normal? Mine's penis shape. Normal is actually is actually
it's it's actually sitting on a washing machine. No. It is that's it is the shape
normal. Yeah. Yeah there's a shape called normal and it's a one inch it's a one
inch spike. It's a one inch line. Yeah it's a one inch line that has no mass.
my my penis looks like a line rider man. And the shape yeah the shape normally
there's a there's a little guy riding a sled on it or if you go to
hotrod.com/line rider. You remember that they had a hot rod themed line rider?
I'm gonna hawk my rod on you. All right Patrick's penis is like a lion's tail.
big piece of hair. Every once in a while it just like jumps for no reason. It just like
flies out for a second. What penis size do you have Cameron? Electric toothbrush. With
bristles? Yeah and battery pack. I have a toothed peenis. When I use it it plays Paralyzer by
finger. There's a rock and roll all night by Kiss when I have sex. Yeah, because that's
a different kind of rock and roll. You know that's what the song is actually about. It's
actually like. No. You know most rock songs are actually about sex. Name one. Name a rock
song. What the F? That's one. Song about sex. Song about sex. Yeah. Name a, you guys don't,
clearly don't know anything about rock. I'll name one. Bohemian Rhapsody. Isn't that one
about it's about fucking it's about having about singing no that one's a
note about singing and going la la la la la that's about having sex mm-hmm yeah
Caleb's penis is like a stack of moral moral technique dance with the dance of
the devil is one of the greatest rock songs of all time first of all second of
all it's definitely about sex that is the horniest song I've ever heard that
ending oh my god can't keep it in my 311 that's yeah that's that one's about sex
because amber amber is the name of a vagina mm-hmm that's a slang urban
dictionary word for what about um shake my sillies out shake my sillies out is
about having sex what about but crazy style baby beluga baby beluga is about
I mean is about fucking a big bitch the alphabet yeah song the alphabet song a
rock cover of the alphabet song about coconut it is a sex song yeah cuz you're
it's about getting an STD. It's like getting a cocoa nut. Getting an STD and curing it with
limes and coconuts. Yeah. Yeah. That's why the guy goes "Ooooh" because he has chlamydia.
Yeah, my penis is a stack of bottle caps. It's not a stack of bottle caps. 99 bottles of beer.
Yeah, that one's about about loosening up.
Yeah, it's gonna take 99 bottles of beer for me to have sex because I'm such a
For me to have sex without throwing up.
Yeah, I can't even think about sex unless I've had 99 bottles of beer.
Here's penis is like a nose bulb.
A nose bulb?
Squidward's nose.
You know the thing you squeeze to get snot.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I wish man.
No, that is kind of, I guess it is if you include my balls.
I have huge balls and if you squeeze them I squeeze pee.
He sucks snot.
I squeeze out some pee.
- Is your candy bar still there?
My candy bar? - Get out of here!
There we go.
- It's not a candy bar, it's a protein bar.
- No, you're eating candy. - I don't eat candy.
- You don't eat candy? - I don't eat candy.
- You take candy for dinner.
- You're off the pod, dude.
- Whoa, yeah. - Today, no, I do eat candy.
- You're on probation.
- I was thinking today, it's,
my teeth have been hurting a bunch recently,
and I realized that that is actually--
- That's 'cause you haven't been eating enough candy.
- Exactly, it's a sign that you need to eat,
that you have been eating not enough candy.
I have a bunch of Meganites at my house.
I might be getting on, having a really good sweet, sweet tart deal heading my way.
So you guys might want to get in on this.
We can split it three ways.
I have a guy who sells sweet tarts and we might be able to get like a huge shipment of them.
Damn, that sounds awesome.
Yeah.
Do you guys want in?
All right.
Yeah.
Okay, let's do it.
I could throw down.
Let's spend all the pot money on sweet tarts.
Like a hundred bucks.
A hundred bucks each.
A hundred dollars worth of candy.
It's like 600 sweet tarts.
there and also two gummy worms. Two? Two big ones. Whoa. Two jumbo XL gummy worms and also
one of those big fat gummy bears. Oh my god with the hollowed out belly and you can put
juice in it? Yeah you can put juice in the belly. Oh. Yeah and also. The one from the
song? Yeah and also. John Travolta the gummy bear? Yeah and also a chocolate bunny but it's
completely solid. Milk chocolate. What about a chocolate bunny full of peanut butter? Can
we get we swing that no that would be extra that would be a hundred dollars
extra a hundred dollars for a chocolate pie full of peanut butter. That's steep but yeah I will pay.
It's steep but yeah you got to mm-hmm cuz you I don't know how to make that shit I don't have a mold.
All right so number one penis shape is the dwarf. Not really a shape. Yeah I'm
kind of imagining a garden gnome. Yeah that's not a gnome. He has a garden gnome on his body.
there with his arms like on his side. A little gnomio and Juliet action. Yeah. Have you guys
seen the video? He's fully clothed. Fully clothed gnome. What video? The video of um... Of the
gnome? Of uh, who, what's his name? James McAvoy doing the interview, or like doing
like an advertisement for gnomio and Juliet. Oh he's like crying. He's like crying. He's
like yeah go see gnomio and Juliet and he just looks like tortured. It's called acting.
an actor they're holding him hostage fucking idiots and you guys ever see
split I think he's crazy I don't think he's an actor I thought he was called
spit mm-hmm cuz he spits on all the girls sure it's called spit yeah there's
a part where he spits on his hands and he says and gas rubs it together and he
says daddy hungry I named it spit after that come another person like pistachio
disguise and then he says keep saying it it morphs into a Arabian accent split
was a spit was actually it's just a reimagining M. Night Shyamalan's
reimagining of Master of Disguise. I've seen Master of Disguise so many times.
It's so good dude. I have it on DVD. You guys want to watch it? It's so funny. It's yeah.
It's awesome. I honestly being a little kid and seeing like that George Bush
impression in it. Yeah. That's why I made me understand politics. Yeah man. It made
me a communist. I said whoa this guy seems like a jerk. Yeah. I like the part where he's
an Indian guy. Yeah. And he feeds the Kraft single to a cobra. Yeah. That's funny. That's
a funny. And he gradually morphs his accent as he says become another person. The Turtle
Club. All time. You know the back story behind that right? Yeah. He saw a turtle and he said
there's a cigar there's a cigar then then they they're just trying to know
there they shot that scene there like while the plane hit the South Tower whoa
and there was a more in the South Tower there's a moment of silence on set while
Dana Carvey was in the turtle suit yeah and that's awesome like well 9/11 just
happened but I gotta go be it's her yeah he's trying to get his money man yeah you
got to he turtled out the scene is dedicated to the brave men and women who
lost their lives today. If only the World Trade Center had gone down into its
shell and then popped back up and bit off the plane's nose. Man that's
That's a crazy scene.
It's awesome.
Yeah, just like CGI out his nose.
I like the part where he's got shit on his head because he's like a cow patty.
Oh yeah, he's dressed as shit.
When I was a kid, I watched that scene and I was like, "You had to dig so far down to
pretend to be a pile of shit on the ground."
The ultimate disguise.
Yeah.
I like the one where he's like, "You got a tiny wiener and some little nuts?"
you got a tiny wiener and some little nuts.
Yeah.
And then he does the back flips.
Oh my God.
Let's just remember this movie.
It's so funny, dude.
So, the first scene in the movie is when James Brolin is disguised as--
His brother.
Yeah, he's-- no, it's his father.
That's his father?
Yeah, and he's disguised as Bo Derek.
It's either Bo-- yeah, it's Bo Derek and then he gets Brent Spiner caught when he's like
stealing.
like stealing something or making Brett Spiner, he's protecting it and then he
ends up working for Brett Spiner and then there's a Dylan and Cole Sprouser
in it and then they do a science experiment and then the mom from
Wizards of Waverly Place is in it too. Yeah. Yeah. And she and they call her the
Tush Queen and then she... Oh she's the big fat ass. I forgot about that. That's why they hire her.
They hire her because she's got a big ass and then she makes out with J.
Johnson from Mr. Show and then he's good doesn't doesn't first underwear yeah
first he puts the underwear on his head his parents parent he gets scared cuz his
parents are gone mm-hmm did that already had and then that and then he come okay
yeah so then his mom's there's a scene with the Exorcist yeah the Exorcist
scene okay so his parents get taken away by Brent Spiner. Okay let's stop. I just wanted to see how long it would go.
He would have just made it up. We could have just let him just keep going and then just like
slowly the episode gets quieter for like 40 minutes. We should we should have a
patreon thing where it's just me describing the entirety of the movie. Yeah that's the
patreon this week is I'll record it by myself and it's just me describing
everything that happens in Master of Disguise.
No.
Okay, alright, I guess you don't like what the fans...
You can do it, you do it, you can do it.
People seem, on this list, very disgusted.
Yeah, they do not like the dwarf.
People say, "What the hell? Report this."
"What the hell is this list?"
"Worst list ever. This was a total accident, by the way, coming into this list."
"/Girls shouldn't see this list."
[laughter]
RootbeerFan says, "Ew, what the hell is this list?"
Someone says, "This list is the most disgusting."
Yeah, that guy is weird 666. You must be weird to throw a 666 in there a reference to
Okay, wait, so it's on this on the penis size or shape dwarf yeah
Do you I thought you were gonna go?
I choosing for a coming from a Filipino family
I grew up with the sort of people around me who believe that Asians have small penises being an Asian
I used to think it was all rubbish. I know my penis is rubbish
I'm now 17 years old and I can confirm with not so much pride that my penis is really small.
It is only five centimeters.
We got him, dude. We got him.
I'm not ashamed.
Cut that clip out.
Oh yeah.
We got him.
No.
We got him, dude.
No, I was actually doing a different voice that whole time.
You were doing a Filipino voice.
Yeah.
Now keep reading it.
Can you go back?
All girls who like small dicks, please contact me.
Thanks.
Juge Despida. He's smoking the Juge right now.
I'm on the Juge right now.
The Juge Despida.
Juge Disputer.
Number two, the Eiffel Tower.
Oh, could you look at that?
It's when your penis gets zapped by a ray gun and it... Oh my god, stop skipping ahead.
I'm not skipping ahead, I'm just showing you.
Cameron went baby mode.
So when your penis gets zapped by a ray gun and it just starts to half
disintegrating that's the Eiffel Tower. Yeah. And just like the veins are left.
The beautiful veins. The beautiful nervous system.
The beautiful nervous system of a man's penis. I can only imagine what it would look like.
That disgusting picture of like the nervous system and all the weird.
Oh, yeah, like it's like the eyes and this that's so cool. I think it's awesome. I bet you do you freak
I think it's sexual to me. There's a comment here that says I love to suck on the Eiffel Tower
It says this is what my uncle has
Jim you're rocking a total Eiffel Tower
Uncle Jim dude damn fucking things looking nice things looking fucking French dog
I've always wanted to see belly. I want it because I want to kiss you on top of it. Yeah
Hey
Jim I saw I saw your I saw your fucking weird penis in ratatouille last night good work man
What do you do for that? I'd love to control your penis like ratatouille. Can I sit on top?
Can I straddle your penis and and pull on the puke?
Bitch go ratatouille on my penis
She'd be pulling my pubes, make that thing go cuckoo banana crazy.
Tangent, but I remember the thing we were doing.
It's like a cowboy showing up to your door and be like, "Can your nephew come over to play?"
I just moved in down the street and my mommy wants me to make new friends.
I reckon you have a nephew. I'd love to play catch with him in the backyard if that was okay.
Can we play cowboys and Indians?
I reckon your boy just got a shipment of play-doh in. I would like to make some spaghetti with him.
Like a Kurt Russell from Hateful Alien. Yeah. Spits in a spittoon.
We don't have a spittoon. Where did that sound come from? He spits onto your nephew.
Well, he'll do just fine. He'll do just fine.
Me and your nephew are gonna go downstairs and make some play-doh snakes.
Yeah.
Thank you for letting your nephew come over.
We love having him around the house.
He's just dripping with spit.
Yeah.
I just got an Easy-Bake Oven and I was wondering if you wanna come play with it for a while.
Me and your nephew are gonna watch a slinky go down the stairs.
I got a big stairwell in my house and I need a nephew to use it.
We're gonna use Diplo blocks to build a lifelike couch.
Diplo.
Diplo. Diplo's the EDM guy. Yeah, those blocks. That's what I'm talking about. Me and your grandson
are gonna run around in the living room for a little bit. I'd prefer if you would move the
couch out of the way. How many guys does your nephew have? We're gonna use super soakers and
we're gonna need fresh towels. We'll be very wet when we get back. Nah, I was wondering if you could
lay out some snacks and some Capri Suns for us. That would be just dandy. Now if you had a couple
fruit leathers yeah well get back yeah pretty nice oh no fruit all right we'll
take gushers if you have them it's fine the gushers you have any now I'm thinking
everything about the fish never mind what are you thinking about no just the
fucking just what the other I've said it before I think but just the Wall Street
guy trying to order a gusher at a restaurant it's a classic yeah it's a
classic to you that's a classic in my brain mm-hmm yeah classic my brain knows
Sopranos. In my brain it's classic. Even though everyone hates it.
Everyone hates the Sopranos. I know dude. Sopranos.
I only hang out with girls. Tony Soprano.
Number three, Marge his hair. Marge's hair.
Marge his hair. Marge's hair.
Marge's hair just says. Yeah just a bumpy fucking bee sting.
Blue. Blue. Blue.
Poisoned. Yeah. Stung by like an anti-bee that turns, your
stings turn blue instead of red. An anti-bee.
about it. I can't stop thinking about the ante. It's purple. He's purple? Oh my god.
And also he's friendly. Yeah and when he stings you he gets more powerful. Yeah.
He actually survives. And he's a hundred feet tall. And thirty years old. He's thirty years old.
And he wants to play with your nephew and he sounds like this. That's right I brought it
full circle guys. Can I play bees and children with your nephew? Can I sting your nephew?
nephew right on his cheek. Teach him a lesson. Your nephew's gonna dress up like bees and go
pollinate some flowers. I was wondering if me and your nephew could raid your closet
and dress up like mommy and daddy. Will you be my queen, my new queen? Nephew, will you
be my queen? I'm gonna turn you into a hive. That's a cow, that's our new character.
Cowboy B. Anti B. Anti B, that's a cowboy who likes to hang out with nephews. Okay, it's cowboy
Antibee I'm not a bee mm-hmm that's his line yeah now I'm not a bee but your
nephew uh he stabbed himself in the leg with a nappy pan when he was next to me
and he just started shaking I reckon your nephew might be allergic to my
sting me and you nephew wear a cowboy hat he wears a bee hat oh my god he's
dressed up. Yeah, he's in a bee outfit. Oh my god, a bee in a bee outfit? Wow. That's nuts.
And then, yeah, ugh, that's disgusting to me. Number four. The sausage. The sausage. Now
that's a, that to me is the, sort of the classic vanilla peanut shape. Yeah. Intestinal lining.
Mm-hmm. Intestinal lining and like a little, a little knot at the top. Yeah. You know? Yeah.
For me, I have that little knot at the top because it's like, you know, like Elmer's
glue at the top, just it'll build up.
Yeah.
That's what I've been doing with Piss and Cum.
And so I just have a little thing that every once in a while I have to clear out with a
scissor.
With a scissor.
What?
Yeah, I have to use his teeth.
I also use his teeth to sharpen my penis.
I do have sharp teeth.
Yeah, like a whetstone.
Only comment on the sausage is, "Ding dong, Tom Green, Freddie got fingered."
There's a whole song he sings in Freddie Got Fingered.
there's also ding dong there's ding dong but there's daddy would you like some
sausage I would have done ding dong doorbell yeah if there was a doorbell
sized penis yeah ding dong the witch is dead
ding dong the witch is dead which I'd that's what I sing when the witch dies
mm-hmm but not because I'm a munchkin you're much not the reason I sing it I
sing it because I respect the munchkin I'm much can dude you're like oh I enjoy
their culture. You're three-quarters munchkin. You're the munchkins king. You're the king
of the munchkins. If I get to be their king, I'll be a munchkin. Yeah? Did you know that
all of them are gay? Including the king. I'll be their king, dude. There are no female,
I don't remember it well, but I don't think there are any female munchkins. Oh, there's
female munchkins. Yeah, believe me. Okay. Yeah, I've drawn them. So, number five, the
tip of the iceberg. The tip is that? Oh, because most of your penis is in your ass. Yeah, yeah.
I've actually, my penis is way bigger than two inches. I'm hiding like nine more inches
in my ass. You just gotta pull. You just have to pull. You have to pull it out. Pull it
like a ripcord out of your butt. But also by the time that you get to see all of it
it'll probably be melted, so. Yeah. You have an ice penis. Yeah. When I was a kid I used
to measure my penis by pushing the ruler so far into my balls that it was like, it was
awesome and now I measure it normal I only measure it with the circumference
yeah every what to see if you're losing weight no yeah you do see if you can fit
your little tiny none of none of the weight I've gained has gone to my penis
you wish I wish cuz that'd be funny that would be funny imagine a fatty dick yeah
cuz it all when you when you get fat it all goes in your pubes when you get fat
- Yeah, your penis just gets slowly swallowed.
- Yeah, by your pube bone.
- Like if you see a real big fat guy
and they just got the head sticking out.
- Dude, that's a pimp move.
Being so fat that even if you have a huge dick,
it's just gone.
- Didn't we find a thing on here,
like during the pod we found somebody
measuring their penis next to an SD card?
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
That was like the best micro penis I've ever seen.
- Yeah, that was, yeah.
- Yeah, he put his penis next to an SD card.
- I forgot about that, oh my God.
- Yeah, for scale.
oh my god yeah and the XD card just the SD card like turn sideways yeah it just
looks like a line yeah I'm tired okay - I'm tired so I mix up the letters s and
X sometimes card s e XD card whoa what you're gonna kill Cameron so oh my god
you killed Cameron you bastard you bastards number six is the droop it's
just
to. I don't even wanna pee. You're a fly and you're trying to pull your penis but it keeps
like moving away from your hand. No, no. No, I don't even wanna pee. No, I don't wanna pee now.
I'll just pee in your pants. Just sit down and pee on the toilet. I don't wanna go through the fly.
Shut up, lazy penis. The zipper hurts my back.
Number seven, the old guy. The old guy. The old guy. That seems like the type of guy who has a penis.
A full old man sitting down there. It's like the dwarf. Yeah. He tells you some stuff about the
70s, about how weed used to be better in the 70s. Yeah, no, it used to be crazier in the 70s. It
wasn't better. Weed used to be crazier in the 70s, man. And he tells you- Women used to be free.
He says shit like "don't bogart it" Yeah, no he says "don't Humphrey bogart it"
Yeah, that's how old school he is.
"Don't Humphrey bogart that thing!"
He says "don't Marlon Brando that" Yeah, yeah.
"Hey Brando, don't Humphrey bogart the cigarette"
"Don't Judas Iscariot the marijuana cigarette"
"Cause I'm so old" That's how old I am.
Yeah, "don't ooga booga unga bunga woolly mammoth that"
Sorry, that's how old I am.
Yeah, don't dinosaur that thing.
Hey, don't- hey, don't-
You're seriously pleosaurus-ing the weed thing.
Hey, you're holding that thing-
Dude, pass the wheel!
You're- you're-
Pass the wheel, dude!
You are fucking- you're fucking- you're pterodactyling that wheel right now, dude.
Just pass it, dawg.
Dude, you're holding that thing like a stegosaurus.
You're a complete fucking-
You're totally bacteria-ing that thing right now.
You're a serious dodo, man.
Hey, man, you just grew some legs.
serious fish with your fish with legs that's how old I am you ever heard of
the Big Bang that's what I did the number eight the veiny that's not a shape
that's an attribute it could be a shape if it's veiny enough my penis is I'm
thinking the scene in scanners when they fight oh yeah the veins like explode out
of them yeah and they're that's what I'm yeah yeah that's what I'm imagining for
veiny do you know what I'm talking about can I've never seen so let me pull the
picture. Scanners is so good. Scanners is awesome. I prefer. I saw scanners. I had to see scanners
for uh. You had to? Yeah. You had to? I had to see it for film one. I had to go see it
on 35 millimeter. God I hate school. I hate film. I hate Emerson. So glad I'm done with
that shit. Yeah I don't think I'm going back. I'm working as a personal chef now. Look they
get their veins like this. Yeah. See this? That's what happens to their veins. That's
what the veiny shape would look like. I've seen some veiny penises man. I feel like there's
a there's a pretty direct like the bigger your penis is the more veiny it is.
And your penis's eyes go white.
And you have big white eyes on your penis.
I do think honestly it sucks.
I think if anything if you the thing that makes me laugh the most is seeing balls with googly
eyes on them.
Like that's funnier to me than like any written piece of comedy that anybody can ever produce
is if like a guy walks in
I don't even need to know him
a guy walks in
walks into your house
balls through his zipper
tears down the door
yeah, yeah, kicks it down like Hagrid
you're scared, you're sitting there fucking scared
cause you're like what the fuck is going on
actually now that I think about it, it is Hagrid from Harry Potter
it is Hagrid
it's Hagrid and he has two
he kicks it down, these are my balls Harry
and he shows you the balls with googly eyes
I put these googly eyes on with a spell Harry
yeah, cause I'm big
I glued them to my penis with a spell
These are my balls, Harry.
Is that what he sounds like?
No, I don't remember what he sounds like.
You're a wizard, Harry.
You're a wizard!
These are my balls, Harry. You're a wizard.
You're a wizard, Harry.
Excuse me, Harry Potter.
But Hagrid, I don't want to go to school.
Shut up!
These are my balls!
I didn't say anything about school!
Get on my motorcycle!
I'm Haggle.
dragon yeah make that face when you make the voice that's name the curved that's
the curve number nine on the curved penis and that the top caught one of the
comments here says taebanana I think a minion wrote that guys they like wait oh
my god the minions have figured out how to go online oh my god oh that's who's
been harassing people the minions the Russian minions the guy from e fucked
Yeah, that minion. Yeah. What's the next one? Oh shit, we're on like number 10. Oh my god.
Number 10, the one that requires a magnifying glass. Not a shape. There's a lot of...
Talk about, that sounds like a Harry Potter book. There's a... Harry Potter and the one
that requires a magnifying glass. Harry Potter and... My penis is small, Harry. This is a
comment right here. Coming from a tall Chinese boy, I am sad to say that I am one of those
few people whose height is not proportional to their length. I am following my idol's footsteps"
- oh, this is -
Yeah.
Yeah, why didn't you read ahead before you read that?
What does he say?
"Following in my idol's footsteps, Caitlyn Jenner, by coming out to the world,
telling everyone my biggest insecurity in life."
Pat can't read ahead of -
He can't read one word.
No, I can't.
He sees one word at a time. It's like -
Well, now I got to finish the comment.
Now you do. Go for it.
Yeah.
Ugh.
This is also definitely by the same person who said earlier that they're Filipino.
Make up your mind, kid.
Are you Chinese or are you Chinese?
I am hoping that I receive the same recognition in terms of bravery just like her.
Kendall Wu, New Zealand.
Let's let Patrick Stew and guilt for a minute here.
You read the trollolol comment.
Yeah, I read the trollolol comment.
every top 10s list there's a trollolol comment that you read you read the whole
thing and then you realize the first letter of everything spills out I'm I'm
piss man yeah yeah or suck my a Hitler yeah something like that
that's roll a little guy sitting at home guy did sitting at home doing the song
yeah right now he's sitting he's looking at a photo of me and he's doing this and
making the face yeah he's going yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait you might be the troll guy look at you man mm-hmm you know the whole song
Edward heel yeah yeah how do you know it cuz it's your name I I did when I was
like 12 I got into another song that he made there was one song that he another
song that he had and I was like I kind of like this that's like to be like a
story I would make up about you.
Oh my god.
To get into like internet memes and I feel like I wonder what this guy's other music
sounds like.
Yeah.
This is great.
The hits are great.
Let me check out his other work.
Yeah.
God you're weird.
There was one it sounds like he's saying buy Banilu Pork and I guess there's a brand called
Banilu Pork.
And they used it in their commercials I heard.
Yeah.
And now that guy's a millionaire.
He's dead.
Yeah he died in 2013.
Wow.
I don't care.
I don't even know that.
I don't know that.
I don't know.
Come on.
Dude, you're funny.
You never learned like math but you know this shit.
No, I don't know math but I can tell you like stupid shit like that.
Number 11 is the we dot.
We have another comment from that same guy.
Coming from a tender Filipino boy.
I'm not reading the rest of it.
Why did you read the first?
Why did you read the beginning of it?
I don't know.
Then, I don't know.
Read the rest of it.
You have to read the rest of it.
You literally, I said it was from the same guy.
still every time you start one you have to finish it's a podcast about this rule
coming from a dad well I can veto it if it no you can't we have we veto we can
be to your coming from a tender Filipino boy who has had many a good time
exploring various penis shapes I give my endorsement to the weed dot as that the
weed dot has a distinctly more fragrant and mellow flavor than the rest similar
to that of old underwear. That was pretty good. That was pretty funny. That one's funny. The
last one wasn't. Kendall Wu. Fuck you, Kendall Wu. You make me look like an asshole. Yeah,
Juge is our friend. Yeah, Juge. Juge, we'll take you to Jollibee. Juge, you're the cool guy of the
week. Yeah, we'll take you to Jollibee. I'll get you some Pala Bok surprise. Yeah, some happy go
chickens. We'll get the Halo Halo. Yeah, I'll get you the Mapo Mapo. I'll get you the tuna pie.
I'll get you the sir bucket.
I usually will give you a tuna pie and you can fuck it.
Wait, I earlier, I want to find the list earlier, before we started recording I did find a list
called the worst things that a Filipino can say to you.
Oh my god.
There was one.
There's one that I want to read.
Number three is "ha, hot dog."
The rest of them are just Filipino words.
And the last one is "bobo."
I just want to share that real quick.
Top ten annoying and most worst things Filipinos can say to you.
All right, back to the list. Number 12 is the inverted.
That's a vagina.
Yeah, that's called a vagina.
One comment.
I thought it was called a vagina when I was little. I thought it started with a B.
One comment with eight votes and it says, "Okay, that's it. I'm done."
Yeah, this is where I draw the line. Talk about Tic-Tac-Dicks and Eiffel Towers all you want,
but think about an invisible, invert-a-dible penis.
No.
Number 13. Well, you can't skip the classics.
Okay, go ahead. Read them.
the chode. Da chode. And the only comment says fat penis. Wow. Yeah. No, keep going. Read. You can't
skip the classics. I have a big one. That's it. Okay, keep going until I get to the one I wanted
to say. Well, there's only one classic. I wanted to say 16. So you say. Okay, say 16. How was he
supposed to know which one you wanted to say? Yeah. I sent it to him with my mind. No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did. You have no. Number 16 is the circular. And the comment says, whoever mad this
was probably high. Yeah. The circular is just a chode though. No. No, it's like a flat,
a two-dimensional chalk zone penis. It's not, it's yeah. I would rather have that. You'd
have a chalk zone penis? Because you can fold it up like an umbrella. No, no, it's like
Ken doll with a circle drawn on. Well, that's not, that's cheating. That's not cheating.
What do you mean that's cheating? I don't know. Are you guys not cheating? I don't know,
it just feels like cheating because I had a good solution and then you guys changed it.
- And then you guys changed it.
- He saw the really small penis and he said,
that's cheating.
- That's seriously cheating.
- Hey, you're not allowed to have one that looks like that.
- You don't get to have sex, that's cheating.
- No, I think I would take a circular chode
that I could bring up, bring into an umbrella shape.
- Number 18.
- And then fuck a guy with it.
- Number 18, I--
- No, I mean a girl.
- Whoa, wait a second.
- We got two good clips of Caleb in this episode.
- I would fuck a girl with her penis.
Fuck a guy in his vagina.
- I would fuck a girl's circle.
- I would have sex on a--
I would touch my circle to whatever.
I would put a magnet on my circle.
Honestly dude, I'd put my thingy anywhere that the fucking cows roam.
I'll just throw it anywhere.
Number 18 is the slinky coil.
But I first misread it as the stinky coil.
Now that's a terrifying thought.
The idea of a coiled pig tail penis that smells like sulfur.
Like a pig's ass.
smells like a pig's ass. It smells like a pig's ass and also it has a little sort of curly...
It smells like a pig's ass and it's covered in pig's shit.
Yeah. And it's a pig's penis. And who knows where it's been.
What does a pig's penis look like? It's like corkscrew.
Why don't you look down? Fatass.
AHHHHH! Gotcha you fucking...
GOD! You piggy, piggy oink oink.
You are the piggy oink oink. No you are.
What do we got on Patreon? I'm trying to pull it up.
We got Joe Mama. Joe Mama.
Joe Mama. So many emails I forgot to read. I was like for like 30
minutes this morning like I tweeted it but just like just imagining just a
professor who just like says every kid's voice name in like an offensive
Japanese voice. I was just saying just names that I knew in the Japanese
voice like like "Kyro Jojo" it's just Kyle Johnson. There's one, there's a
skateboarder named Gilbert Crockett. I just kept saying "Gilbertoo Crockaka".
I don't remember where we left off. Yeah. Was this the last one we did? I remember I'm smart. Maybe?
We'll do it again. Yeah well I do remember this because I remember arguing
over the pronunciation of this name. Okay. So we start here. Okay. Shout out to
"Name Goes Here". Making us look like fools like we forgot to fill in the
template no but they put they put their name down his name goes here and that's
legally their name legally your name if you put it on patreon I'm serious yeah
Greg Greg De Bruno shout out to Greg De Bruno yeah Carter Sutherland yeah to
Caleb nope Caleb pits for shout out to the spam slam for subscribing to us on
YouTube. Thank you Spam Slam. Ethan Davis. Ethan Davis. Ethan Davis you fucking you.
Ten dollar patron. He edited his patron to five dollars. We should say we are like
we're gonna do the Master Chief calls that we have to do. Yeah so we're gonna change the
ten dollar tier because it's just we're all very busy and we do not get to do the
Master Chief calls. If you're currently in the ten dollar tier you can you'll get
your Master Chief call, well... But we're gonna change it to something better. We're gonna
change it to something better soon. We just have busy lives. It's hard to get all three of us in a room.
And also you. Yeah. I mean we could theoretically do them after episodes. And Master Chief too. Master Chief is also...
Master Chief is incredibly good. The thing is that what people didn't realize is that there's been a new wave of
Covenant that have been fighting the Galaxy. That's why we have to change it. So we have to
change it yeah and then mr. 911 yeah we hope it's not one you know mr. 911
Ian Drake thank you thank you Embry Morrison thank you thank you Greg De
Bruno for editing your pledge to $10 whoa thanks Greg Greg you know all I guess
thank you Twitter new login to Twitter from Safari on iPhone
yeah pod bean for their new monetize your podcast webinar because we're trying to
make a million dollars on this thing. We're gonna have another book coming out.
Thank you Adobe Creative Cloud, video tips, live streams, and you can sell mine. Can one of you guys help me make a website?
Yeah I can. Cameron can. We need to make a website for this. Yeah.
We should do a link tree. It's been a long time coming. We should do a link tree.
Yeah we should get a link tree going because I'm sick of putting everywhere
you can find the episodes on the Twitter. Yeah. I'd rather just put one link tree
link a link tree uh-huh we should do a link tree we should get on we should try
we should do a box lock we should do a free we should where we should upload
Patrick into man space and lose I'm gonna probably tomorrow upload something
so no - I'm gonna upload the stinger knife-throwing video fuck yeah probably
no I haven't ripped it yet I'm not gonna do nice if you guys and I'm gonna okay
On the discord, if you just keep messaging me personally, I will do it.
Do it, please. It's easy.
I know it's easy, but I have to get my laptop out. I have to find my DVD burner.
I have to get the disc.
I have to open my eyes. I have to take the way insecutive press in my hands.
I'm unemployed. I have to get out of bed.
First of all, I wake up at lunchtime. I got to eat lunch.
You do. Because you wake up at lunchtime.
And then you have to throw up because you ate one extra bite of a sandwich that you didn't mean to.
Exactly.
That happened because I was sick.
I told you that in confidence, motherfucker.
I wasn't referring to that.
Oh.
You just--
I told you about that though.
Yeah, I couldn't eat lunch.
I tried to eat.
I think it might have just been the bread.
That was God's curse on you for talking ass about breakfast, dude.
Dude, I got--
The ham and egg God just fucking struck you down with fervor.
No, I got real good cold cuts and ham.
Sam from Green Eggs and Ham.
I got good cold cuts.
I got pancetta, I got salami, I got prosciutto.
I got provolone in there.
I made like a real good sandwich.
Real good cold cut combo.
And I just like...
Dude, I'm gonna go cold cut combo on your nuts right now.
If you don't stop talking.
Yeah, we're trying to finish that.
Cold cut combo on your nuts.
I'm gonna Ralph.