You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
You're a crap monster.
Hey everybody, it's me Griffin McElroy.
I'm here to announce I'm running for president.
Yeah, I'm actually Justin McElroy and I'm running for vice president and also his brother.
Yeah, now that Pete Buttigieg dropped out, we thought that somebody needed to run who was pretending to be gay for money.
Travis. Travis McElroy. Travis put it down. Travis. Travis put it down. Battery. Put it down.
Travis ate a battery and this is him now. Travis. We need the nine volts for the smoke detector.
The weed smoking McElroy Brothers. Yeah that's what they need the smoke detector
cuz they'd be smoking inside. Yeah. You know they turn it on so all the
neighbors know. Yeah. And then like you run into the hallway you're like yeah sorry I
know the smoke alarm keeps going off. You're still doing the voice. Cuz it's the McElroy's that do that.
to do that. They are smoking weed in their apartment. Fuck you man. Fine, never mind. You ruined
my life right then. I did not ruin your life. Keep going. Keep going. Okay, do you really
want me to? Ignore Justin. Can we have a vote? Who wants me to keep going? Me. Well, you
can't vote for the fans. That's half and half. And I am the deciding vote. Patrick's the
new guy, so he doesn't count. True. You are the new guy. You're the new guy. I'm not the
new guy. New guy on the pod. Fresh blood, that's what I call you. I can smell you. You
You smell one day old. You smell like a baby. You smell like a baby's little diaper. You
smell like a baby's diaper that Cameron likes to smell. Dude, I'm gonna spear you with my
ooey gooey laser beam. You're gonna melt. Okay. Yeah, you're gonna melt. And you're gonna
melt into human candy. That's fine. Patrick melts if he touches soda. That's not true.
That's true. He drank, was it Baja Blast? Yeah. He drank Baja Blast out of a jelly jar
with the straw. Whoa. It didn't have any jelly in the... That's insane. You know that cup
that I... From Taco Bell? You know that cup that I have? He poured it out of the bottle,
out of a plastic bottle into a little mason jar thing. I needed to drink it through a
straw because sugar hurts my teeth now. I gotta go to the dentist. Maybe you shouldn't
be eating sugar then. Yeah, no, I know. Yeah. I had a... Today, like two days ago I found
a pack of cigarettes on the ground that had clearly been run over by a car, so I picked
them up and I did not even have a single thought that that was maybe a bad idea
until today and I feel like-- How many did you smoke? Huh? How many did you smoke? Six.
Nice. Yeah, there's probably tire stuff on them. Yeah. You know and I'm just inhaling it.
Oh, you got like more dirt? There's more dirt than normal. You got more dirt.
There are more reds though, you know, they're like a nice cigarette. Extra dirt.
Yeah. Can I get the cigarettes with the extra dirt? Yeah. Can you give me the
dirtiest cigarette. It's okay, it has a filter on it, it doesn't matter what's in it.
It's true. I got that dirty juice. You know those filters that Hunter S. Thompson used?
You know what, no I don't. Like the ones from Fear and Loathing? The white ones? Yeah, like the
white filters that you put on the ends of cigarettes. I think that's Cruella DeVille. Oh yeah, the holder thing.
The Pink Panther one. It made me stop smoking cigarettes.
Because you thought, why? Because I watched all the tar build up in it.
wearing fishnets and lounging on the couch with a martini and holding a cigarette holder
in two fingers.
And he was like, "Maybe I should stop smoking cigarettes."
I don't like what cigarettes do to me.
They turn me into a sexy, sultry little bitch who hates Dalmatians.
Yeah.
They turn me into one of the most respected fashion designers in that book.
Cruella DeVille.
Yeah.
Yeah, actually, Cruella DeVille work.
She's getting her money.
That's what's up, bitch.
if she's killing puppies or dogs or whatever they are those little creatures
she's a boss AF she's a boss AF B I C T A mm-hmm she's a girl
she's a girl Bob she's a GIRL girl mm-hmm with a capital G that's yeah
capital I as well and all the letters are can you know what fuck it every
letters capital that's how much I appreciate yeah she's a girl yeah
yell it so that for the people in the back mm-hmm I use a girl a louder for
the yeah what you guys been up to today anything fun I went skateboarding for
like an hour and then I rolled my ankle and I didn't rolled my ankle didn't
realize it's so funny when a cat meows for you to say what the fuck is if you
forget that you have two crazy loud cats yeah yeah listen it catches you off
guard every time somehow. I don't know. Yeah I watched two Godzilla movies today.
That's all I did. Really? Yeah. Yeah I had to walk home with the bad ankle. I watched... I don't care
about that. Yeah we're talking about Godzilla. Can you just... Hey new guy will you hush?
Son of Godzilla and Destroy All Monsters. Destroy All Monsters? Yeah. Guess what
they do at the end? They don't destroy the monsters. You're correct. They don't destroy any of them.
Yeah. Which... Is that a Godzilla movie? Yeah. Keep up. Godzilla, Destroy All Monsters?
What's the turtle one? It's just called Destroy All Monsters.
Oh yeah, I've never watched Gamera.
That one's good, man. Gamera is awesome.
That's good. When does Baby Godzilla come in?
Baby Godzilla is in- Godzuki?
First appears in, no, Godzuki's from
Hanna-Barbera. That's the one I know.
Baby- Minilla- I know Godzuki.
Minilla is in Son of Godzilla.
But Baby Godzilla is a
different character that's from- I couldn't get
into Godzilla. Godzilla vs
Mechagodzilla 2 or something? I watched a
couple of them with, or just like a couple of
movies with Cam and Pierce and I really liked them. Not enough to watch them by
myself but they're really fun to watch. I don't think I could ever watch them by myself. I think I've tried.
We should watch them. Did you say you'd think you'd cry? No, yeah. I'd be too scared. The monsters are too big.
No, it's just they're destroying all the cities. They're even destroying schools in that.
That's kind of cool. But they destroy the people's houses too.
They destroy a big building that has a big elevator. Patrick just cries
when he sees more than five Japanese people in the same room. He starts crying and wailing.
Yeah.
So, there's all, they always have like one character who's just an old white guy whose
dialogue is very clearly dubbed into Japanese. He's like, "Why'd you cast that guy?"
Does he still do that?
Like Matthew Broderick?
No, it's just like he literally, he's, it's like in a dub, you know, where you see,
he just is saying other words. He's not speaking Japanese. It's like, "Why?" Nobody,
they probably didn't understand him on set. Why cast him? If he can't speak Japanese, why is he
there? I love - the fun - the best part of that - of those movies is hearing just every time Godzilla
comes on stage - on stage. On stage. On stage. All the scientists just like looking up.
It's Godzilla. I've not seen enough Godzilla movies.
That's just a - that's what happens in Japanese media. It happens in anime too.
Every time that they see a Godzilla.
Every time someone gets surprised they go, "Oh, yeah, oh, oh."
Yeah.
Just like that.
And when they come they go, "Ahhhh!"
They go, "Ee-oo-ee-oo-ee-oo-oo."
They reversed it.
Yeah.
Yeah, for Japanese.
They freaked it.
And they went and they mind freaked it.
Yeah.
Yeah, we were watching a lot of Criss Angel before we started recording.
easily one of the most sexual people who's ever walked this earth.
Yeah.
It's weird how like...
Just like you, it's... Magician's the only job that you can wear a vest with nothing under
it. Magician or Green Day, those are the two jobs.
It's true.
It's mostly Green Day.
Or the cool librarian.
Or the cool... That's true. That's true, the bad boy librarian.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was like, "Yeah, you can return the books a day late, I don't even care."
"Hey, you can be as loud as you fucking want in here, man, who cares?"
I took the safe search off the computer.
You can go on YouTube now.
That's right.
Yeah.
And if you see a funny video, you send that shit.
That's right.
No more Freddy the Fish.
We're playing Quake.
Quake on the computers.
All the computers are Alienware now.
It's pretty sick.
Yeah, that's right.
You know what the book, the only book we have here is?
Ron Swanson's book.
Tucker Max.
Tucker Max meets Ron Swanson, a book I wrote.
We just have all those Bill O'Reilly books about killing the presidents.
That's the only fucking book in this place.
strategy guide. Yeah and Matty Matheson's cookbook, Word. And the strategy guide to Spore.
Yeah. In case you want to play Spore. We preloaded the galactic edition of Spore onto all the computers.
And we have World War Z. You can cheat forward into the space stage instantly. We replaced
all the non-fiction books with DVDs and all the fiction books with computer games. Yeah.
And all the, and the floor. Pretty much is a GameStop now. Yeah, you have to pay. We're
have DVDs now yeah that's right GameStop MovieStop yeah we got computers in the
store we got guys who jack off on them mm-hmm yeah and a printer yeah we have
an Epson laser yeah and you get a card with the number on it mm-hmm that you
pay for stuff with yes we're also a bank we're also the bank that's right I'm the
bad boy librarian yeah I just do all that stuff yeah my name's Kratom.
Nice to meet you.
Kratom the bad boy librarian.
Dr. Kratom.
No relation to the drug.
No relation to the other Dr. Kratom.
No relation to Dr. Kratom but I am related to Dr. Sebi.
Yeah.
Yeah we have all Dr. Sebi's 5,000 books that he wrote.
That's pretty much the only thing in the library.
I don't know anything about Dr. Sebi.
I just assume he's like Dr. Bronner.
No, yeah.
Yeah, he was like if Dr. Bronner added like two more things to the soap, but the things were like it washes away HIV and it cures cancer.
That's kind of what he was.
So being a doctor is all about getting soap.
Yes, it's mostly a soap based job.
Do you think Dr. Sebi had...
That's why they do that thing with their hands.
Wash them.
there and they're like oh I'm sterile and they yeah they can't they can't have a
kid that's like while you're asleep I'm not gonna fuck you I can't have any
pregnant you I can't have any kids mm-hmm yeah yeah dr. Sebi I think his
thing was like I don't know horsing around I'm just around no I think we
talked about this he thought like he thought like yeah he felt like HIV could
be cured by the power of music or something oh really yeah our music good
vibes and good wine and good wine and so they killed Nipsey Hussle they put a
bullet through his brain because they thought he's gonna tell the world. We've talked about Dr. Sebi so much.
It's funny that we've talked about him so many times and never once have we gotten to look up.
We just think he's a funny name. He's probably just like a good guy. I don't think so.
I don't think he's like a good guy. I think any doctor that you know the name of is
probably not a good person. That's true yeah cuz then it's like Dr. Eugene Gu, Dr. Phil's good, Dr. Eugene Gu, Dr. Kravorkian, Dr. Mangala, Dr. Acula.
Dr. Acula is the worst one. Yeah he's scary.
Not the worst one. Dr. Who, Dr. Evil, Dr. Doom. Dr. Evil, you know that's a layup.
We knew from day one that was a bad guy. Well yeah but then he turns around and you say
Damn look at that fat ol' ass!
[Laughter]
Yeah.
Well yeah but now Scott Evil is the bad one so.
Oh.
Dr. Scott.
Dr. Scott Evil.
Terrifying.
Dr. Bronner is probably evil.
No, Dr. Bronner is good.
You can't put that many numbers into one number without having some kind of deal with a dark beast or a devil.
It's true.
- And that soap, I got that soap on my asshole once.
- Six, six, six, and one, you ever notice how it says
six, six, six, and one on the bottle?
- How about this, we start a new shampoo, soap, shampoo.
- Shampoo.
- One, three, three, seven, and one.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, those are shampoo for gamers.
You can clean your computer with this shampoo.
You just pour it all in.
- If you put enough water in it, it turns into goo,
and then you can do like a swipe of your keyboard
to get the cheeto- - And then you put goo
on your friend.
- Dr. Mario.
- You can put goo on your friend.
- Yeah, and if you drink it, it's a stim.
It's a stim pack.
Yeah.
And it makes you way better at gaming.
Your health bar goes up.
I wish that people had health bars.
You can overheal with a special goo.
That's true.
You can get super shield.
Yeah.
Overshield from Halo.
You can go uber charge medic TF2 mode.
Yeah.
You turn into a red crystal.
You turn into a red blood monster.
What is it supposed to look like?
I feel like it's super charge.
I think it's red super charge energy, but that's just the scientist in me speaking.
It's blood.
Who knows?
It's extra blood.
I think it's extra blood energy.
Yeah.
It's definitely some sort of energy shell machine.
Would you guys drink a bonk if it was real?
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
Would you?
Yeah, I would.
I would drink pretty much anything if it was real.
Would you fuck the flubber guys if they asked you to?
If they really wanted it?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Really?
If they helped me with basketball.
You notice I said guys.
help you with basketball? Anything to get me into the NBA. What do you think for all of
us, when do you think we would have had to start training to get into the NBA? For me?
I could start training tomorrow and get in in three days. Okay. Let's do it. I can probably.
If I train for 16 years, starting tomorrow, I could get into the G League. You think so?
I could play for the Maine Lobster Red Claws. The Maine Lobster Red Claws? Is that what
called the main Red Claws. That's not a G League team is it? Yeah it is. The Gatorade League?
The main Red Claws. It's a team. Is that the Boston G League? I think so. The main Red Claws?
Yeah. They have a lobster as their mascot? Yeah like a main lobster. That's funny. Yeah. It used
to be the D League. If I started training the second I was born I would be in the NBA by month
one. Month one of your life? Yeah. You have to graduate if to a year of college. I would have
done it already. Well, didn't Kobe. Kobe didn't do college. That was before they changed the rule.
They're going to change it back. It's called the Kobe rule.
128 online credits within a week of being born.
Wow. Yeah. That's impressive. Yeah, it's all rollover for my channel.
I just guess. It's all rollover, man. I just guess on all the multiple choice tests.
I have to go through a lot of reincarnations before this pans out for me.
It's like the monkey writing Shakespeare thing.
Yeah. Eventually, I can be a one-year-old in the NBA.
By one month old I mean. Yeah I guess you're right. Wow the Maine Red Claws what a terrible logo.
Yeah. Yeah it does look like a Freddy the Fish thing. I think that might be their updated logo.
That's still bad. He has basketballs for antennas. Yeah. That doesn't make sense.
It's because he loves to sense the basketball. Yeah the Celtics complete the purchase of the
Maine Red Claws. This is on Bangor News Daily. Oh that's huge. That's congrats Stephen King.
Stephen King's - Stephen King, that's huge, man.
Yeah, this is big for Stephen King.
The manager of the Red Claws.
Stephen King.
Or Joe Hill is the manager of the Red Claws.
Yeah, well, no, Joe Hill is on the team.
Joe Hill is the -
Yeah, I know.
The ref.
I'm the ref.
I know that.
You don't know that.
I knew that already.
I knew that before you were going to say it, because I have a premonition like
Stranger Things by Stephen King.
All right.
Who's Stephen King?
Steve and King.
Yeah.
I one time saw the coach of the Celtics, Brad Stevens, in the Boston Common Coffee Company
downtown and I was with Neil and he was like on his computer like two tables down and I told Neil,
I was like, "That's the coach of the Celtics." He was like, "Whoa." And we were like, "What do you
think he's doing?" And I was just like probably something like and then I started typing on my
computer, "Basketball, basketball, basketball, basketball," like really loudly and we just
just kept doing that and then he like stormed out of the coffee shop. It was so funny.
Yeah. Nice. Sorry Brad if you're listening. That was a really gross wall of water. Yeah
you want me to do it more? You can do it more. That's gonna sound good. That's gonna sound
good. Water makes Caleb burp. No it doesn't. Water makes me go crazy. I get too much water
in me I go wild I start spraying pee everywhere yeah I spray a clear your BP
stream I spray it clear like perfume mm-hmm I could dodge either of yours
piss no no I spy pee in a cloud yeah paper I dodge it no I see back I pee a
bit heat it up with a hairdryer while I walk towards it yeah I pee the mist from
the mist by Stephen King by stranger things but there's nothing in it it's
just mist no there's a thousand monsters that come out of my penis hole.
about Stephen King's The Pissed. And he's fucking mad. And he's really angry. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The Mist is the one. I'm Stephen King, I'm pissed. The Mist is the one with The Mist. Yeah, The Mist is in that.
Right. Stephen King's The Mask. The Mist is in what? The Mist. The Mist is in The Mist? Yeah, they
have The Mist in that movie. Yeah. Okay. Only role. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, never did another
movie. Well, they... I guess it did like... They did use The Mist for The Fog.
They also used The Mist for The Fog. They also used The Mist. The Mist appeared in... Is The Fog the one with Mark
- No. - No.
- That's the happening. - Think of the happening.
- The happening.
- The happening scared the fuck out of me as a kid.
- The fog is John Carpenter.
- I saw the happening when I was like--
- With the sea zombies.
- When I was like 10 years old
or whenever that movie came out.
And I was watching it and there's a scene
where like guys start like jumping
into wood chippers and shit.
- Mm-hmm.
- And--
- What is happening?
(laughing)
Oh my God, what is happening?
- I turned, I looked out of my window
like right as that scene was on
and somebody had just started a wood chipper.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, which is like terrible timing
for a kid to be watching that movie.
- Oh my God, what is happening?
- I turned, I looked out of my window
like right as that scene was on
and somebody had just started a wood chipper.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, which is like terrible timing
for a kid to be watching that movie.
Also, I shouldn't have been watching that movie,
I'll say it.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, mom.
- Isn't Zoe, does Zoe Deschanel play
Mark Wahlberg's wife in that?
- Zoe Deschanel plays Mark Wahlberg.
- Yeah, it's a bad role.
- Oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm from Dorchester.
- She's from Dorchester?
- Okay.
- No, Mark Wahlberg is.
- This is Zoe Deschanel as Mark Wahlberg.
- It took me a second, I had to process it.
I'm on a lag, I'm on lag today.
I'm lagging behind a little bit.
- Oh, I'm so sorry, Mr. Vietnamese Man.
(laughing)
Sorry, sorry I bumped into you.
- Yeah, she broke a--
- She just has a meet cute with a--
- She broke a ukulele on the back of his head.
(laughing)
Sorry, I'm--
- Oh, oh my God, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
- Sometimes I space out.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- What kind of list we fucking with today?
- This is the top 10-- - Yo mama.
- What the hell?
- Top 10 yo mama.
- You better take that back. - And that's the episode.
Thank you all, good night.
- I take it back.
- Thank you. - I'm sorry.
- This is the top 10 funny things
a Magic 8 Ball should say.
You just spilled that all over me.
- I suck at drinking water, dude.
I always have, I always spill it all over myself.
- Just get a straw.
- Like the last three times I've done like a paid spot,
before I go on stage I'll like have a glass of water and I will just spill some of it so I have
to be I'm on stage I have like water all over my shirt. It sucks dude. It's pretty good. I just I
fuck it up every single time almost. Anyways. The list. Yeah it's a funny ass bullshit list today.
Yeah. Oh really? This is some funny ass bullshit. You know what I love.
Oh wait I want to do a list shout out. Someone sent us a list that it doesn't have enough like
stuff on it to do, but I want to do is Mr. Say Uncle on Twitter sent us this list,
creepiest names to give a kid. And it's just kind of, it's like Satanic Lucifer,
Lucifer Demon, that kind of stuff. But the last one is Joker Clayface.
Yeah, number 13 is Sprite Coke. That is so creepy.
Yeah.
I need a kid named Sprite Coke.
Hey, Sprite.
Imagine, yeah.
Sprite Coke is the name of like a DIY scene rapist though, for sure.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I'm Sprite Coke.
But yeah, imagine like first you meet someone named Sprite and you're like, oh, that's weird.
And then just the absolute horror when you learn their last name is also Coke.
Yeah, when you see them sign for like the tip on the restaurant.
Yeah, it would be worse.
You see, so you learn that their last name--
It would be worse, Dr. Pepper Pepsi.
That would be worse.
You learn, so you go, you find out their name is Sprite Coke, right?
And then you look at the receipt and it says Sprite Coke Jr.
Oh my god.
That's terrifying.
A horror story in six words.
Sprite Coke Jr.
What about a guy named...
Fuck you, Ernest Hemingway.
I wrote a sadder story in three words.
Sprite Coke Jr.
Speaking of names, me and a friend were watching The Great British Bake Off.
Maybe I've said this before.
We were watching The Great British Bake Off.
Have you seen that show at all?
There's a guy on that show whose name is Paul Hollywood. Yeah. Right? And we were
like oh that's that's such a funny name I wonder what his real name is. So we
looked it up and his real name is Paul Hollywood. His real name is Paul
Hollywood. That's funny. The best part is his father's name is John F. Hollywood.
John F. Hollywood. John Fitzgerald Hollywood. So fucking crazy. And he's from like you know Leeds or whatever.
Anyway, let's go to the Magic 8 Ball list. I'm just thinking John F
Hollywood. John F Hollywood is such a good guy. Like just talking like JFK about
Hollywood. I mean that's just like the like if I... We need better parking at the
trade of Joe's. If that was like the first day of me as like a spy and like
someone asked me my name I would panic and say John F Hollywood. Sir what name are you
checking into the hotel under John F Hollywood. Caleb John F at Caleb Hollywood.
Mr. Spy. Yeah the spy who shagged me. I guess the name Johnny Depp used to sign
into hotels under was Mr. Donkey Penis. That's covert. Yeah. Do you have a Mr.
Donkey Penis staying at your hotel? Yes. Can you imagine that you're working at the
Marriott and Johnny Depp walks in and he's like, "Oh, you Johnny Depp?" He's like, "No,
I'm Mr. Donkey Penis." I have a reservation. I'm gonna need a hundred candy bars just
charging in the room. Yeah, and could you put some creepy lighting in there? Yeah, could you put
like a vampire? I want you to make the towel look like a functioning jack-o'-lantern.
please put a candle in the shower I'm serious yeah I need a bunch of makeup to
cover up and my wife hates me in the face yeah can I have 100 monsters living
under the bed yeah can I get a working gremlin I want
three thousand I get a workable gremlin I get a functional gremlin can I get a
ghost I can fuck sexual ghost it just it just can be just a boner under a sheet I
I don't care. Can I get a sheet with the holes in it so I can pretend to be a ghost?
Whoa.
So nobody knows who I really am. Mr. Donkey Penis, my real name.
My real identity, Mr. Donkey Penis.
Yeah.
You have to show ID, right?
Double incognito.
Yeah.
So that means you had to have some fake ID made that says Mr. Donkey Penis.
I'm sure that if you're famous, they'll just let you do that.
Yeah.
Whoa. Okay, Donald Trump.
I'm sure.
This is Cameron's gotcha moment.
Yeah, if you're famous they'll let you do it.
They'll let you be named Mr. Donkey Penis.
Yeah, they just let you do anything when you're famous.
Like be named Mr. Donkey Penis.
Yeah, they will dude, they will.
It's so funny that that happened and it was like fine for him.
Yeah.
Just unshakable dude.
Pretty great.
That video you sent of him when someone says he's a--
He's at, yeah, it's like--
Oh, the Diamond and Silk thing?
Yeah, Diamond and Silk.
- Yeah, it was like a Black History Month event,
and they were like, "Mr. Trump,
"you're the first black president."
And he was like, "Yeah, yeah."
(laughing)
And everybody's like, "Woo!"
- He does like finger guns at the guy.
- Yeah, yeah, so funny.
Yeah, that's what he thinks black people do,
is finger guns.
(laughing)
He's like, "What does a black guy do?
"This."
(laughing)
Yeah.
- I've seen the wire.
(laughing)
- All right, Top 10 Funny Things
Magic 8 Ball should say by Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga.
Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga. Puga.
Oh, that's a good let's look up that let's make that up right now. All right
Okay, that's one. Yeah, that's one. Yeah, he smokes weed
I need to borrow your car
That would I would not let job of the heart my car do this. He would ruin the suspension listen, buddy
I just need to sit in the passenger seat
That's okay, that's three that's three
He could say poop
We won't say that one. Yeah. Yeah, I don't want to be too strong sugar is low
Nice you have any crackers or juice because my blood sugar is low
It feels like we're avoiding doing this list
It feels like we're dancing around it. All right, you're fine. You don't want to finish the job a list
everyone's gonna be angry at you for cutting off the job list.
I'm sorry I said anything.
I just saw a magical phenomenon.
Okay, there we go, that's six.
Alright, I spoke too soon.
Here's number seven.
I just saw another one.
Okay, that's seven.
The charcuterie board was amazing, Debra.
You really outdid yourself this year.
You sound like Danny Trejo.
(laughing)
- I got the virus, guys.
- I just saw the loogie in your mouth when you talked.
I saw a big green jaba in you.
- That's the Jetsman jaba that's been talking.
- You just coughed the jaba,
that's why you can't do the voice anymore.
- I have two more.
- Two more?
- Two more jabas.
- Donald Trump, you can say Donald Trump.
- Donald Trump.
(laughing)
- I don't know how to do the voice.
- You need to reset the modem.
- Yeah, that's good.
- All right, that's pens.
nobody will be mad that we didn't finish that list. I'm glad we finished that one up.
Yeah. It was all worth it. In the end everything's worth it. Okay, so remember
when you had that crush and you turn - Patrick remembers when he had that crush.
Remember when you had that crush and you turned to your magic 8-ball to see
if he liked you back? What if it said one of these things? Yeah, so this is a list
for Patrick mostly. Yeah number one who is your guy crush?
Who's your man crush growing up? Non-exist. Who's that? He's a tall guy.
He's an elf. Non-exist. Who is your guy crush? Mike Condolences.
Mike Condolences? That's pretty good man. That's a Bart Simpson. Heywood Jablomi. Yeah mine was Sucka My Pino.
Suck on da... Suck on da my dog. Suck on da my dog's penis. Remember when Kevin Gates told that, did that thing where he made the woman suck his dog's penis?
Yeah. I remember you telling me about that. Dude that's a great video he's just he's just like talking to the camera and he's like I had this
bitch over here earlier right you heard me and I told her if you don't fucking suck
my dog dick you out of here. You think he just met his friend? No. He clarifies. He
says he says he said oh yeah I don't mean my friend I mean my dog's red rocket.
No no no he's he talking he's like that's man's best friend. Oh man. Yeah and then he has
another thing in his in his over-under for Pitchfork they they asked him about
like licking the inside of or his dog licking inside of his mouth and he's
like ain't no dick clean it in my dog mouth. I love him dude. Anyway his crush is his dog.
Yeah yeah yeah. Number one is I'm literally a ball filled with water and triangles in it.
What are you expecting? The answer to life? Get a job. Yeah we need sort of a sardonic
like Bill Maher. Yeah yeah. But you shake the ball and then it's just. Yeah the Republicans.
I'm here to smoke weed. Yeah.
Yeah, he shakes the ball and it says, "It's time to smoke weed."
Yeah, wow. I need that in my life. I need that. Imagine a world
where no, with no religion and everyone smokes weed.
Perfect.
Yeah, that's heaven to me.
That's heaven to this atheist.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Um...
uh...
blue
you know uh... we have a little bit of a job again and i really want to know
what do you think that's the sound like
as kind of a sound like next
besides the triangle part
isn't that what people's mom say when
that turned twenty
why are you talking to the white and slowly
can you not read
can refer missing you know i read you not really actually i was letting you
guys are you can always read all of you got approve approve you wrong patrick
went to go wash his eyes out.
Why?
Well, wait, I want to go back to that comment.
Beside the triangle part, isn't that what people's moms say when they turn 20 and still
live in their basement?
So without the triangle part, it's, "I'm literally a ball filled with water.
What are you expecting the answer to life?
Get a job."
That's what people's moms frequently say.
This comment is completely ridiculous and unprecedented, unwarranted.
I'd like the commenter of this comment to come forward, denounce the comment, remove themselves
from the website and come on the podcast for an order for us to do bukkake onto them.
You just proved him wrong atheist style dude. You just went Bill Maher.
You went TJ amazing atheist on him. You just went TJ Miller on him dude or you're
about to. You know what I'm saying? You went TJ whatever his last name is and you
poured hot oil on his penis. Oh jeez listen to this comment from Pet Sounds.
Whoa that album? Yeah well this is by Brian Wilson. Oh yeah I used the 8-ball and daisies
on so many crushes back in the day I wouldn't take no for an answer either
oh whoa no yeah well that's I mean that's not that bad I'm sure yeah I know
what he means yeah but take no for an answer from the eight ball yeah okay
yeah but it's pretty bad yeah I think you were too great you guys are
overreacting I don't he's fine I think we needed I wouldn't take yes for an
answer that's better yeah that is a better reason this made me nearly cram
my pants. Which one is that? I don't know if that's, it could be pee. I bet he meant crap
and he mistyped. Well that's so far away on the keyboard though. Maybe cram my pants.
Cream? Yeah is it cream or crap? But why would that make you, why would you cum from reading
(laughing)
- Just thinking about the eight ball.
- Yeah, well not even, yeah.
- The hole in the eight ball.
- Eight balls around like a boob.
- Water and triangle.
- Somebody took the glass off.
- 'Cause a boob's is water with triangles in it.
- Oh, that's why the moms say that.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, because they--
- And that's why you cram,
'cause you're thinking about your mom.
- Yeah, and her triangles.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
My mom is modeled like a RuneScape character.
- Cram a pants, maybe got a boner
and his pants got crammed.
got some cram in his pants. Maybe he meant to say cramp his pants. Yeah.
And he's trying to combine them. What about cream? Maybe he was trying to say
ramp my pants and he added the C at the beginning. He's trying to skate his pants.
Ram his pants crazy into his pants crabe
Yeah, what's crabe
Isn't it something he does. Yeah, it's probably something he knows. Maybe he was trying to say wash his pants. Oh
That's a really good. It could be that wash or rinse. He also didn't do it. He got but he got near he nearly nearly
He nearly crammed his
I nearly crammed my pants. Number two. You have a therapist for this. No, I don't. And then the
comments are there's one that says mind readers. A guy who takes a therapist is a mind reader.
Well, get out of my head. Well, well, well, what's the solution? What's wrong? Yeah, what's wrong
with me? You already know what's wrong. God, why am I even here? You already know everything. Yeah.
Yeah.
They're scary. They're too powerful.
Terrapists.
Number three, just play Charlie Charlie instead.
Yeah, let's play Charlie Charlie.
What is that?
Right, and that's a game where you summon a demon.
Oh, and the demon's name is Charlie Charlie.
Yeah, or like a ghost of a little boy.
Wait, you might need like paper and pencil. Let me do...
I don't need that.
Look up Charlie Charlie online.
Digital.
Charlie Charlie.
Digital Charlie.
Look up Charlie the Unicorn.
Let's watch that instead.
Yeah, let's watch FilmCow.
the Charlie Charlie challenge from the skeptical inquirer.org.
Oh, I bet this is this is going to have a slant to it.
Oh, you got to do this. You Charlie, can we play this simple question and two pencils put on a
cross drawn on a piece of paper should allow you to evoke the spirit of a child or even a demon.
This is the latest web craze known as the Charlie Charlie challenge,
perhaps dating back to an ancient Mexican tradition.
[Laughter]
Charlie, Charlie.
Nah, the goose of the Charlie.
The Charlie.
Yeah.
El pencil.
You do this and then the pencil moves.
Charlie, Charlie.
This is such a long article.
Can we play?
Yeah, I know.
You know?
This article is written by Massimo Polidoro, the investigator of the paranormal, author,
lecturer and co-founder and head of KICAP, the Italian Skeptics Group.
Whoa, I got to join that.
Oh, is that okay? I need that
Scare they have a game on congregate called Charlie Charlie jump scare challenge don't put jump scare in the name of the fucking
Yeah, I'm gonna know you dumbass. Let's go to maze game
But we're at area or kid Charlie Charlie pencil dot com pencil game from scary for kids calm
Yeah, you're scary for kids. Yeah, you are cuz you are closer to Charlie
No, but you you're you're surely it's a kid Chuck Pitts. Don't ever call me Chuck Chuck Pitts
it's my you guys can we start call me Mike whoa Charlie Charlie Michael we
might if you just start going by your middle name we're both going by our
middle names yeah we have the word yeah yeah all right Edward was rest of this
episode I can to Edward yeah morning zoo radio show her name for the show Mike
Mike Mike into Edwards you yeah Mike in the middle oh my Mike in the middle of
two Edwards. Yeah, Mike in the middle and then the parentheses of two Edwards.
Okay, I'll be in the middle. And it's Mike in the middle because it's
the middle names. Because we fuck. Whoa. Mike and the middles. Oh my god. Oh my god.
We're the middles. And we're both Edward middle. Yeah. Edward middle. We're all
changing our name to Edward middle. You know what? And you're just Mike. You know
what? Fuck it. I'm gonna change my middle name to Edward. No. And now the show's
called three Edwards no yeah three Edwards wait wait wait wait wait wait
you you're staying Mike okay okay two ads are better than one in the mid one in
the middle but I'm Mike but I'm Mike in the middle like to Michael in the middle
Mike love in the two heads are better than I'll combine Michael and Caleb to
Mike lip and then it sounds better wait wait no Michelob in the middle with two
heads which are better than one who are better than one then one is in the
middle then one is and it's because it's their middle names yeah what about the
name show what about the man show three guys yeah yeah guys in their middle
names yeah what about two and a half men right and I'm about two and a half Viet
men what about what about friends no that wouldn't make any sense all right
because I hate you guys yeah yeah yeah as a producer that shows it who's a
producer that show the Emerson guy Bill Cosby mm-hmm yeah he's a Bill Cosby is
he about chill Cosby rehabilitate him about real cause he's a SoundCloud
rapper. Yeah, he's maybe like a cool grill on. Yeah. Grill Cosby. Grill Cosby.
Grill Cosby. And he's white like Paul Wall. And he's got the meats.
Garbage. Yeah, Grill Cosby. Yeah. Yeah, and he's just cooking up some steak. Is Paul Wall white?
Huh? Is Paul Wall white? Yeah. Paul Wall? When I was a kid I thought he was Chinese.
I just saw yeah I mean kind of you know you can imagine why right I thought it
was like like I thought Paul Wall was a Chinese name. I guess that makes a little bit of sense.
That was like P-O-L-W-O-L or something. Okay imagine this right yeah Bill Cosby's in
prison okay someone throws a chicken sandwich at him. Nice.
his eye is it with his mouth his I it bounces off him ineffectually first of
all yeah his eyes turn red his white is his excuse me mr. Doran he's doing
something he's doing a word Ozby oh now I'm listening now we're Edwards now
Patrick Edward Doran do not speak when I am speaking to you what we're saying
about. His eyes turn red, his hand flips open to reveal a machine gun, laser gun,
ooey gooey laser gun blaster. His - I think that is what it is. - starts beeping. Okay.
Kill Cosby, the evil robot. Oh my god, what about pill Cosby and he takes an
ibuprofen? That's better. That's way better. Yeah. How about this, how about he gets out of jail, right?
And we take out his weird eye.
No, no, no, he gets out of jail, right?
He comes to us at this time where-
Does he have glaucoma?
Shut up.
Oh my god!
Shut the fuck up.
I just wanted to know.
Yes, he has glaucoma.
Is that bad?
Is that-
Oh, how funny was that?
No, I just wanted to know.
Yes, he has glaucoma.
You shut up.
I just wanted to know.
Okay.
You're in Edward mode right now and I don't like it.
[laughs]
Edward moment.
So, Bill Cosby gets out of jail, comes to us.
This is like, you know, ten years from now or whatever.
I don't know how long he's in jail for.
He should be in jail 10 years maximum in my opinion.
But anyway, he comes to us.
That's all he's got left.
Okay, he comes to us.
We're at the time, we will be producers at NBC.
Okay, all three of us.
You know, we'll be huge money making, money fucking money makers, right?
We produce the biggest shows on TV.
We produce toddlers in bikinis.
No, not that.
That's a different...
That was all you.
That was your idea.
That was all Caleb's show.
We produce women, women with huge cans too.
And the third one. And we produce a Spongebob reboot. Okay?
Yeah.
Spongebob meets Star Wars.
No Squidward.
No Squidward in the reboot.
Spongebob meets Harry Potter meets Battlestar Galactica.
And Halo TV.
Halo TV.
And Halo TV show. So they come to us, or he comes to us, right? And he's like, "Listen,
y'all. I've been..."
Why are you giving him that voice?
Because now he sounds like this because prison made him normal. He said, "Listen, y'all. I'm
different now okay I'm different but you know it but I'm but I'm still the same
bill yeah right so they so we said you know what man fine we'll give you a new
TV show it's called the call it's called the still Cosby show okay yeah and you
have to remain completely still yeah screen anyway he does he does like the
face at the beginning of the show but then he gets stuck like that for the
ready doesn't move in the rest of the show is 22 minutes of him just going like
No, the whole show is he gets put in a room, right, and he can't move, and we line up all
his victims and they come and do whatever they want, and he can't move.
So they can beat the shit out of him.
They can crap on him.
Well, it's a hypothetical, Patrick.
No, it's not.
It's happening.
I sent him a letter.
I sent him a letter from the-
He's going to be here in five seconds.
Not five seconds.
He's fucking old.
He's slow.
Wait, hold on.
There's somebody at the door.
I'll go get it.
You do not, do not let Dillkos be in my house.
If that's who I think it is-
I have to.
pizza. I didn't order a pizza. Have you ever never heard of the pizza prank you fucking
idiot? I'm gonna open the door. Don't open the door. Just open it a little bit. Don't
open it big enough for anyone to get in. Oh my god you gotta oil your door. Oh my god
you let six Bill Cosby's in here. I don't see anybody. Yeah nobody look what are you
seeing things again Patrick? Yeah. You should lie down for a while. Put your glasses, put
your glasses it's just one bill Cosby. It's just one, I'm wearing my six glasses. Yeah he has six vision.
Yeah. Oh my god he's making a sandwich. What kind of sandwich is he making? Don't touch my meats.
What was that? What was that? What the? That was a tuna sandwich. He's making a tuna sandwich.
You brought that from his house. He brought the ingredients. He brought the ingredients.
ingredients separately? Yes. Why? Hungry. I guess that's a fair reason. I'm hungry. Yeah, I got that.
What are you touching in there? The fridge. Are you giving me a tuna sandwich? Yeah, for later.
You're not even gonna eat it. I already ate. You already ate? You said you're hungry.
You said you were hungry earlier, what the hell?
I'm a famous liar.
I guess that is true, he's a famous liar.
He is a famous liar.
You're a deceitful guy.
You should probably get that guy out of your fridge.
I don't even, what if that's a can of chicken, not tuna? Is that chicken or tuna?
The same thing.
They're not the same thing.
This is the same thing.
It's the same meat.
It's not the same meat.
It's completely different.
It's on the sandwich now.
It's a good point, there's nothing you can do, it's on the sandwich.
What's on the sandwich?
The chicken and tuna.
What? You said the chicken.
I don't know.
Can you just read what does it say on the can?
Tuna.
Okay, okay.
I think he might be lying.
If it's a yellow can, tuna comes in a blue can.
Why is there a chicken on the can?
It's the chicken of the sea.
That's a good point.
He does have a good point there.
It's the chicken of the sea.
So are you just going to hang out there for the rest of the episode?
No.
Where are you gonna go?
Med school.
Why?
I don't know.
What school?
Temple University or Alma Mater?
University of Phoenix.
You're going to University of Phoenix?
For what?
That's on the computer.
Are you gonna stay on the computer in my kitchen?
Yes.
Alright.
I just don't, I don't touch money.
Yeah, stay off the files I guess.
Y'all have, y'all have fun.
Alright.
Yeah.
Let us know if we're being too loud.
We're not.
over being too loud if you need to study. Yeah, you're good boys. Oh thank you. Yeah. He's actually a pretty nice guy once you get to know him. Honestly, yeah he's probably, wait no.
He's like the worst guy ever right? Yeah. What's the next number on the list?
We're at 44 minutes. This is one of the most schizophrenic episodes we've ever done. Number four is you were expecting me to say yes or no
weren't you surprised you haven't I said Yoda was that Yoda what is that Yoda
magic Yoda ball the magic Yoda ball that says do or do not I am the Yoda ball
Yoda Cosby I'm just gonna leave it at that yeah yeah how about Yoda Kotb and
he hosts the today show like what about like those Cobb nope
- It's Hoda Kotb? - Hoda Kotb.
- Yoda Kotb, okay.
- Now you're catching up.
- Yeah.
- Sorry I'm a mile a minute faster than you guys.
- The fastest pace.
- I got fast today again.
- You got fast today?
- Yeah, I got really fast on the way here.
Kind of like last episode where I was super fast,
I got pretty fast on the way here.
- Yeah. - I'm slow.
- I'm pretty fast.
I had a Marlboro Red, a Coke Zero,
and a tuna salad sandwich.
- I hope we get to-- - You ate Bill Cosby's
tuna salad sandwich? He's gonna be pissed.
- No, I didn't eat his, dude.
- You ate Bill Cosby's sandwich.
Did he eat your sandwich?
Yes!
Shut the fuck... I will fuck it. I will fuck you.
I don't like it.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
The sparks are flying.
I'm gonna fuck you, bitch.
No!
[Laughter]
Yeah, will you watch out?
What? What do you mean? This is good, dude.
The people have been asking for this.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
We get a thousand DMs a day saying, "Will you do the Cosby thing again?"
"Will you please assault Bill Cosby?"
me. I say yeah no problem I'll do it I'm a hero. I'm gonna get sent to the same jail
as him and on day one I'm gonna throw another chicken patty at him. Yeah I'm
gonna eat the chicken patty off his face. They're gonna let me do that. Yeah yeah
I'm gonna go there and I'm gonna I'm gonna bring him a bunch of homework to do
as punishment. That's what he's doing right now. I'm gonna I'm gonna find his
secret stash and I'm gonna eat it. Whatever it is. Candy. I don't know what
it is. I bet he has the worst taste in candy. Yeah I bet he's eating. He's only eating candy he likes his
quaaludes he eats the spanish fly that's what he likes that's his favorite candy dust bunny
he eats dust bunnies like a chocolate bunny but it's dust yeah yeah damn his eye looks like that
a bug ball i know it's disgusting i don't know why he likes it the very idea of a bug ball is
making him want to hurl just imagine it rolling around i'm gonna ralph you better shut the hell
up getting pretty close to fucking spewing when you talk about a bug ball and not in the
way that that sounds.
Yeah, you're going to spew.
I'm not going to spew.
I'm not going to cram my pants because I think about a bug.
Dude, you're going to throw cram right out of your thing-a-lingy.
You like to fuck a bug.
No, well, I have been known.
He fucks a bug.
Yeah, he does.
To fuck a bug.
I mean, if it's a sexy ass little bug.
Yeah, you would eat any--
If it's a tight little thing.
A bug in a bikini?
Yeah.
Okay, you tell me, a bug in a bikini?
He likes the Bug's Life bug.
The Bug's Life bug did have a tiny little waist and a big fat ass.
Insects-a-saurus from Monsters vs. Aliens but really small.
The Monsters vs. Aliens, the big bitch, I'll say it, I would beat it.
That's a gunshot outside.
That did sound just like a gunshot outside.
Probably was, man. Yeah, it's pretty much the most dangerous neighborhood in America.
Yeah, I pretty much live in the hood.
Patrick lives in the favelas of Boston.
to triangulate your position because they know you live in the hood. Yo, hood
Patrick. Pat in the hood. That's an account. We're making that account. Somebody make the
account Hood Patrick. Please make it @HoodPatrick. @GhettoPatrick and the
display name is DatGangstaPatrick. Yeah. Just please do not say it. I can't.
I can't. I'm looking for jobs right now. Yeah, he can't have that said. I can't have my name associated with that. Yeah, the name Patrick.
yeah yeah every time you apply for a job they google Patrick yeah gangsta Patrick
a bunch of gangsta Patrick star like like big t-shirts this guy has a whole
nother life he's not telling us they pull up ghetto Patrick star is like why
did you tweet this?
number five is ask your mother lame yeah number six stop asking who let the dogs
out already I would never ask a Magic 8 Ball I would just listen to the song to find the
answer. This is one of the stupidest lists I've ever seen but it doesn't even
matter because we're having fun right? Yeah. It makes me dizzy how much fun we're
having. Me too. It makes me blast off into my mind. You should take a nap. I've been
telling you for a while I think you should nap. Yeah you've been, you've been. I wish we could
record earlier in the day. You've been throwing a temper tantrum all day. I have not been
throwing a temper tantrum all day. You've been walking around begging for candy like a mutt. I've been walking around
I'm bopping you guys on the head. He's been hitting his like he's been putting his arms straight and hitting his fist to his sides
And he's going I don't wanna do it. He's been chewing his sleeves
Mm-hmm. I used to chew my sleeves a ton when I was a kid. One of my cousins used to chew his neck of his shirt.
I will always remember the flavor of a sleeve.
What about the string on a hoodie?
Yeah, they weren't as salty. Sleeve is better. Sleeve you got a lot of good salt. I never ate a sleeve.
I ate a whole sleeve. Yeah, I turned I turned a jacket to a vest
That's the day to take it out of my stomach my belly button
One I thought you said shirt for some reason we said jacket
What I was thinking you had to you know what never mind
Cameron does not own a shirt Cameron doesn't even own a shirt. That's how cool. I am yeah
He came in here with pasties on his nipples
Pasties that were shaped like mr.. Krabs yeah
yeah mr. not sure I'm not not painted to look like mr. Krabs just shaped like it
yeah so it took us good silhouette yeah but it's the continents on it it looks
like an earth shaped like mr. Krabs people don't know that Pangea when you
put it all together looks like exactly mr. Krabs yeah that's what they based
spongebob off of was show you Pangea yeah they based it off the past I heard they
actually faced I heard they based a lot of these TV shows that are coming out
now about either the past, present, or future? That's terrifying. They base a
broad city on the future. They base broad city on the present because it's about me
and my best friends. The future where women can actually be on TV. Yeah. That was the first show to
feature women. Yeah, before that it was like old Greek plays where you just had
just guys playing girls but some of them were really hot. That's why some of them
could get it. Like Kids in the Hall and White as Kids You Know, those were the only shows on TV.
Yeah. They had guys dressed up like girls. Or when they had Chris Farley dress up like a
girl that was in fun buddies with Tom Hanks wasn't buddies white chicks mm-hmm
yeah I think that was the the straw that broke the camel's back that's when they're
like these women are getting too hot okay we got it we got to put real women in
now yeah yeah and then they did not make a movie for a girl until 2001
- Yeah, finally the phallus was destroyed.
It unlocks the female energy. - Two big penises in the sky?
- And the plane kinda looks like a pussy.
- Yeah, you know, now that I think about it,
the World Trade Center, two dicks, kinda gay,
good thing it was gone.
I don't want that shit in my New York City.
I want a big, two boob-shaped towers.
- They should do-- - That's what they should
replace the one big dome.
- That's why they wanna build a mosque there.
- One-- - Oh my God!
- That little-- - Ah!
(laughing)
- It's terrifying.
was like a dome but it was the height of the Twin Towers like both of them.
What if there's a box the size of the entire earth, the whole earth could fit inside of?
Yeah.
It would be night for a thousand years inside of the box.
What if there's a microwave that you could actually fit a whole bag of Totino's inside?
What if there was a microwave that made it cooked?
Did you know a bag of popcorn is larger when popped than it is smaller than when it is not
popped?
Yeah.
Uberfacts.com.
We should start a fact-based website.
Yeah, do you know that Mr. Bean actually...
Mr. Bean actually had a bean?
Mr. Bean has never eaten a bean.
He actually had a bean in his pocket.
Did you know Mr. Bean actually had a bean in his pocket the whole time?
It was there the whole time.
It was there the whole time. Things you missed.
A closer look.
A closer look. Mr. Bean actually had two beans in each of his pockets.
And you... Wait, and we're just learning this now?
this funny British character that you know and love actually had two magic
beans in the coat of his bottom hat. He actually had a bean ability the entire time. He just never used it. He just never used it because he thought it'd be bragging.
But he actually had a bean ability. They were gonna it was scrapped before they
could air it on the BBC but he was going to sprout at the end. Yeah. He was gonna
a sprout into it into a not into a big beam into mr. sprout yeah which is a
different a metamorphosis his wings is but mr. sprout can talk to whoa and he
has any has a voice he goes hello there hello yes whoa he's like did you know
the show home improvement did not actually feature any homes did you know
Or did it improve? And nobody was a licensed contractor on that entire set.
Did you know Tim Allen actually had to fight the producers to get Jonathan
Taylor Thomas on the show and he because he thought that he was a great kid.
What about Tim Owlen and he's an owl?
Who? Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. Yeah, they should come in there.
Fun fact. You look like David Koresh right now. Yeah, yeah you do. It looks, it's cool,
you look cool. Fun fact. Straight pimping like David Koresh. Yeah. Fun fact, The Family in Family
Matters actually did matter. They did. Fun fact, The Family in Family Matters was actually white
and they painted them before every episode.
They did.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was originally called Family Splattered because they were splattered with paint.
It was originally called Family Guy.
That was taken in the future by another name.
And they realized, but then, yeah.
Somebody was going to make a really good show called that.
They were like, "Ah, shit, that's already lined up. We can't take that."
Yeah.
Okay, so the SD card ran out and it stopped in the middle.
Yeah, we lost the--
We lost a bit about a dad going crazy over Mickey Mouse. We hit the funny maximum on this one.
We topped out the funny meters. Yeah, until we come back to... It ran the funny alarm.
Bring the funny with Jameela Jamil or whatever or no Chrissy Teigen and Jeff Foxworthy. We brought
the funny and Jeff Foxworthy went, "You might be bringing the funny if you got a fucking
shit."
These are the two new ones?
I don't know what's going on.
Hey, yeah, right?
Caleb, help me out here.
Patrick can't process numbers or words.
This was the last one last time, right?
This is the newest one?
Sure.
Yeah, I mean, well, no, I don't think we said that person's name last time, actually.
I think, okay.
Yeah.
We did all right. I don't know I do not know February 23rd. No we definitely did yeah, we definitely have some so okay
So I'm gonna God here right what?
26 okay, yeah, okay, so thank you to Christopher good and
Thank you Christopher good. Yeah, yeah, Christopher good. Oh wait fuck you Christopher bad before we do
Patreon names can I yeah, I know we already did one, but can I plug a show wait?
the picture. Oh yeah. But people who aren't don't have their names they won't listen
to the patreon name shoutouts. We have other news too. Do not log off yet.
Mm-hmm. Okay you can say the rest of the names then. Okay and then we have a
new $10 patron Ian Mitchell. Thank you Ian. We have news about the $10 tier but
first Caleb you want to do your show? Yes yeah so I'm on a show in New York I
know some people have asked me for if I'm coming to New York for anything I'm
and gonna be in New York today. I've been asking Caleb if he's gonna go to New York.
On Thursday. Please go to New York. Please get out of here. March 5th. And then so I'm
there for a show at the Pit. At the what? The Pit. Caleb that's a pit? At the Chuck Pit.
I knew this was coming. Chuck Testa. I knew this was coming. It's at 7 p.m. at the Pit.
It's me and some great comics. Ryan Shuh, Rachel Sinnott. It's an evening of
stand-up comedy apparently. And then I think I'm... Hosted by our good friend
Mary. Oh yeah, hosted by Mary, she's great. And I think I'm doing some other stuff
that weekend, just look at my Twitter to see. Anyway, if you come to a show
and you say that you listen to this podcast, I will buy you a drink. I really will.
I'll go T-Pain style on you. I'm gonna buy you a drink. Okay, well if you go T-Pain style,
you gotta wear the hat. I'm gonna be dressed like a ring leader from a
circus and I'm gonna be doing shouty snap and buy you a drink to
you if you say that you listen to the podcast. We're getting Caleb's voice to be auto-tuned.
They're gonna auto-tune me yeah they're gonna auto-tune me and I'm gonna dress
like a like a scary voodoo magician mm-hmm yeah so I think T-Pain looks cool
in like 2006 he started doing us a whole circus thing yeah yeah all right so
patrons we did we finish the page just joined T-Pain just subscribed for 1
million dollars an episode yeah crap her episode hey I don't know how that works
to thank you you know I'm saying you real real real life auto tune you auto
tune us at the end of you are doing this part he's going to he's gonna he just
he's saying no he's actually your mind is telling you no but your body's saying
yes I'll eat yeah and that's you oughta tune that he's gonna sound like R. Kelly
yeah no mm-hmm yeah no it's kind of crazy how that's a line in an R. Kelly
song and then all that shit came out huh? My mind is telling me no but my body my body
is telling me yes. Alright so you're gonna auto-tune that? Yeah. He's gonna make that
sound just like R. Telly. R. Telly? R. Telly. Ronald Television. That was his name. Well
that was his name don't wear it out. Yeah. Okay so. Oh $10 tier. Yeah update to the $10
a Master Chief Skype call just not do we're never in the room three of us are
only ever in a room to record this nowadays and then and then like it let
alone when other people are available over Skype yeah so it's just not doable
I'm trying yeah we are we're free this week I think so if if there's we have a
backlog of Master Chief Skype calls so we can hit you for those if you want but
you also were changed we just changed the $10 tier so now it's a personalized
video for Master Chief so basically you can request what you want Master Chief
to do within reason not to be safe. We can't dress up like Master Chief and put
things in our butt. We're not dressing up as Master Chief. We'll pass your request on to
Master Chief he'll film a video for you. But Master Chief will not put anything in his butt.
He can't put stuff in his butt. He doesn't have a hole. Let's talk about his
abilities. Number one he's pretty good at skateboarding right? He can skateboard
yeah decently well master chief he can play pool yeah right and he can make
music okay so those are those are a couple you know he can do a lot of stuff
though I know he cannot drink water through the helmet yeah or any not yeah
chief can play um but yeah you can you can also just ask him questions he's
available for Q&A he loves talking to the fans master chief can a shout out to
your girlfriend's master chief can attempt to play a lot of your boyfriend
on guitar okay master chief does not will not give
shoutouts to boyfriends only girlfriends it's a personal moral thing for him
yeah yeah John as we so if John Spartan John in parentheses if you subscribe to
$10 to you right now we'll send you a message and you can we'll try to get a
Skype calling with you this week if you'd rather that but it's I mean it's
just tough in general. Yeah. And also Patrick gets really scared and cries when
he sees a Skype window and he has to be in the room to chaperone the Master Chief call.
He thinks that the ringing sound is too loud. Yeah. Yeah. For some reason that makes him cry, we
don't know. We tried to solve it by screaming into his ears over and over. It's the bells.
He hates the bells. Boom, boom, boom. Don't even. He thinks he's getting married to
whoever's calling. Yeah. And he gets really excited. He crams his
pants when somebody calls him because he thinks he's finally getting married.
Yep, it's true. I'll say it. It's true. It's all true. We have fun stuff coming on
the Patreon. Yeah, we're gonna be making some videos this week I think hopefully
that you'll see eventually. We decided tonight that we're gonna have a special
themed episode coming up. Yeah, we do. We'll do that on the Patreon. You'll be excited for that.
We have a weird Jollibee documentary that'll come out. We're gonna be putting a
director's commentary on the Patreon. Yeah! We have access to the
Grinch movie I have that on... We're gonna be doing a watch along. We can do a watch along that
may or may not include some way to get the Grinch movie onto your computer for
free so you can watch along with it easily. Yeah. Actually, yeah, definitely not
now that I think about it. I don't know why I said may or may not. It doesn't, that
doesn't exist. There's no such thing as a Grinch movie online. There's no link
you can go to that downloads the Grinch movie for you on Google Drive or
anything similar. And if there is we would never post it. Absolutely not and it would not have
an audio track included already and it would not be covered under parody law
because of and I would I there would not be little rope like robot versions of us
at the corner of the screen yeah and I would I would not have one of the
smallest wieners my doctor said he ever saw and the episode Caleb's doctor is
dr. said and he is dr. seven he's seen tons of penises yeah that he is the
other thing was he wouldn't but he is. If you rearrange penis it spells sepi.
That's true. It spells nsepi which is pretty close to sepi. Yeah. So just
think about it. And also one last thing, I love you. Mm-hmm.
I love you. Caleb loves you. I love you. All right this is two Mike's and Michael
signing off. Two mics. Two mics and Michael, that's good!