You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the mindless.
Crap monster.
[SCREAMING]
This is the crazy frog.
Breakdown.
[HUMMING]
I just think that he was a phony.
I fucked a crazy frog!
Dun dun dun dun dun!
I thought he was a phony, then I found out he was just animated.
Wait, hold up. Let me go grab my crazy frog.
Your crazy frog? We already started recording. You can't leave now.
Alright, Patrick's gone.
Oh my gosh!
Alright, let's...
We need to figure out our exit plan for him.
Because he's been doing this every week.
He's been running and grabbing something.
He's had to go to the bathroom and grab some poop out of the toilet.
We need to figure out a way to get him off the podcast permanently.
We can pretend that he's sick.
Oh Patrick, you're too sick to be on the podcast.
Oh my god, Patrick.
Oh that is cool.
He has a backpack, which no, it's probably not, it probably can't hold anything.
Wait, no, keep it on.
I'm gonna take a picture of you.
It's a stuffed animal that goes on your back that looks like the crazy frog.
Alright.
Does it have the weenies?
They do not have crazy frog, wait.
There's no penis on him.
no penis on it they got no penis on the thing they got no what they do to my boy
I have to return this they got no penis on the I have to return this there is no
they do have a they do have a little puck I'm starting to understand where the
straps on it yeah but oh cuz I okay I think I took that you put a present
inside a crazy frog it used to be that you could I think I did what are you
doing to him? I think I did... That's his heart. I took... I did something to this. It doesn't matter.
I had to bring it... Nobody's gonna understand this. Yeah, this doesn't... Yeah, this is so...
this is so impossible to explain visually. There's a... we have a crazy frog here, which looks
life-size to me. Yeah, no, this looks like it would be the height of crazy frog if crazy frog was real.
Well, he doesn't... he rides... he rides an invisible motorcycle. I will say, they made his face
extremely fucked up. They did fuck the face. That's probably what it was. Yeah, they fucked the
face completely. They fucked the face a bunch of times. They fucked him blue. He became blue.
But it used to be you could squeeze his hand and then he would do his crazy frog sounds
but then I had to bring that to class with me because Ben gave it to me. He had to. Well Ben
gave it to me in the middle of the day and then I was like oh well I have to go to class with this
and I didn't want like crazy frog noises to happen in the middle of class. Just don't press the hand.
I pulled a wire out of it. He can't help himself from holding hands with him. He pulled the wire.
He knew that he wouldn't be able to.
He's like companionship.
Yeah, he was like I have to kill you before I can resist holding your hand.
Oh my god, you cut his veins.
I cut crazy frog's.
You sliced his nerves.
You cut his main artery, man.
Crazy frog's thing is broken.
You cut his main vein.
Yeah, man, I want to bring my friend to class, but I'm afraid he'll talk, so I have to take
out his wires.
So I had to kill him.
I had to kill my friend so I wouldn't hold his hand.
Yeah.
It's true.
And so I could hold his hand and he didn't go bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang,
It's like the end of American Beauty. He killed him so he wouldn't hold his hand.
I've never seen American Beauty either. At the end the dad, the gay military dad, he
kills Kevin Spacey because he tried to fuck Kevin Spacey and Kevin Spacey was like no
I'm a pedophile and the guy was like oh but I'm gay and so he killed him because he didn't
want to feel gay.
- It's the battle of intersectionality.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's the, the, the.
- Yeah, which one?
- The oppression Olympics.
- Yeah, battle of gay.
- Did Kevin Spacey win an Oscar for that movie?
- I'm pretty sure you won an Oscar for that movie.
- No.
- For being both characters.
- Yes, in real life.
- Yeah, you were like, this.
All events in this movie are based off
the life of Patrick Doran.
- I was two years old when that movie came out.
- It doesn't matter when it came out.
- I think it was 2001.
I think they time travel to find your story.
I watched this movie, The Return of the Living Dead, the other day and the beginning of the
movie it says, "Everything in this movie is true.
All names of companies and all names of people are real."
And I just thought that was funny.
The zombie movie.
Is that the one where the butterflies come to life?
Like the butterflies on the wall?
Yeah, yeah.
That's a good movie.
It's a really good movie.
But I thought it would be funny if they did that.
They're like, "Oh, this would be funny."
And they just get the fucksuit out of them.
I don't think there's any legal recourse for being fooled in a movie.
Yeah, but I'm saying it would be funny if that happened.
It would be funny.
I'll give you that much.
If then the movie had to get destroyed.
But like what if that?
What if they had to destroy the movie?
Every horror movie I feel like in the past ten years has had a thing at the beginning.
This is real.
Like the Exorcism of Emily Rose.
Well I feel like based on a true story is different.
They literally they're like...
The events of this are exactly true.
Yeah, they say like all the names of people and all the names of companies are exactly
as they are in real life.
We should just...
No, they always say they change the names.
Yeah, but they didn't say it.
what I'm saying. Yeah I know. That's exactly what I'm saying. Now I get what you're saying.
What movie is it that starts and it says like if you have a heart attack don't
watch this movie. No that's Frankenstein. Oh really? They do yeah that is true they do
say that the beginning of Frankenstein. Really? They say this movie isn't for the
faint of... yeah a guy comes out in front of a curtain he's like I have to warn you.
Oh yeah I remember that. You watch that movie with a curtain? Take the curtain off the damn screen.
damn screen fool no there's some movie that's like all all it's like if you I
don't know it doesn't we should upload a copy of Star Wars that has that at the
beginning mm-hmm this is like this is a true story but that's the only change
the entire movie yeah and people like is that that wasn't on the yeah George
Lucas will not stop editing his movies yeah the fact you will not stop adding
stuff yeah he made a mumble recently our Wars movie put Hillary Clinton in the
newest version of it yeah yeah she played Jabba the Hutt that no we wish you
better now she played princess Leia Hillary Clinton you fat as shit bitch
I'll say it you fat as shit that's why I didn't vote for you yeah I didn't vote
for you cuz you look like a bag of yogurt you look like a bag of piss you
fucking look like a bag of yogurt fat shitty old you look like a big rolling
ball down the hill you look like a what's it called a Tamuki but you look
You look like the Tanuki suit. Tanuki suit? You look like Mazuka Joe.
No, what's the name of the game where you're a big ball and you collect-
Oh, Katamari? Yeah, you look like a calamari, bitch.
She looks like a calamari because everything- You look like a whole calamari.
Anything that she comes in contact with sticks to her and she ruins it.
In Katamari they make it better.
We should start a political podcast. Yeah, wait, let's start-
It's just Patrick talking. Okay, here, wait. Let's start-
We put Patrick in a room and we say, "You have to talk about politics without using-
you can't like open up a tab on your laptop or anything you just have to say everything you
know about politics for an hour. So here's let's start let's do political stuff. Okay let's do
some political stuff. Elizabeth Warren is like a parasite on the mouth of a fish and the fish is
America because we love to we keep on swimming but Elizabeth Warren yeah she's like a little spider
that eats the fish alive from the inside. She's like an Anunnaki and she will transform into
whatever she wants including a Native American yeah yeah he's a Native
American cuz she was here way before anybody else
she's an alien you're a total Bowser jr. right with war and and you're like
Lemmy you're lit you know what it is you're Remy LaCroix and you got a big
fat ass and a humongous pussy Elizabeth Warren your praxis is trash and it
reminds me of of of reminds me very much of my balls it reminds me of what's it
called banjo-kazooie nuts and bolts that's how bad it looks like my nuts am
I bitch and you yeah and you look like a bear and a bird combined Joe Biden you
got a brain you good like you look like it blizz Warren you look like all the
fucking animals on the on your totem pole all combined into one you fucking
stupid fucking loser. You know what I bet you asked to be player two on GameCube
because you can't handle the responsibility of player one. Liz Warren's the kind of person who
turns off the GameCube when someone says you're not Native American. She hits the
reset button. Yeah. She hits the reset button. She plays Animal Crossing she
hits the reset button so Resetti will talk to her. I bet you lose on all the
luge maps on Spongebob Battle for Bikini Bottom because you can't handle the tongue.
No. Yeah. I bet she doesn't even like playing Mario. I bet she doesn't even
like playing. Liz Warren, you on Tetris you stack up all the blocks and you
never complete a line. Yeah, on Tetris. That's on Tetris. And that's on Tetris.
Liz Warren, you put on a movie and then you leave halfway through the movie
because you have to go to the bathroom and then you come back and make it and
you rewind it. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah, yeah, you bitch. And that's your, then that's your
policy. Joe Biden, you look like a giant ant from the Matrix, the Path of Neo. Joe Biden,
you have black eyes like a, like a, like a duck. Hey, Joe Biden, you look like Plank
from Ed, Edd n Eddy. He does? Yeah. Damn. Still, you look like someone drawing your
face on fool. It's true he does. Caleb had one sparkling rosé. I had a sparkling
rosé all day and now I'm going psycho. I'll go off on any candidate. That's right Joe Biden
you're like the you're like Psycho Mantis because you're trying to look into my cartridge.
You're a pedophile. You're searching through kids cartridges looking for your personal game.
You're trying to find the entrance. You're trying to play inside their cartridges you're trying to
blow on their cartridges and reset them if you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah and Amy Klobuchar too.
Yeah.
I'm not going to talk about her.
I'll talk about her.
Amy Klobuchar you're like a...
I have too much respect for her.
You're like a thwomp.
You're like a bitch playing Cooking Mama and trying to eat the food off the screen.
I'm serious.
She's a thwomp.
She did that.
Yeah.
You look like a whole thwomp.
You look like a thwomp combined with Patrick.
I will not say anything.
I bet your pussy did that.
Your pussy tastes like a mystery flavored dum-dum, you fucking stupid dum-dum bitch.
Yeah. Fucking fat ass bitch.
Yeah, more like Amy Ghostbustar.
[Laughter]
You think ghosts are real and you look like Slimer.
Yeah, you're trying to slime the country.
Yeah, more like Amy Go-to-the-Butch-ar.
Because she goes and she gets out fucking two pounds of Capicuolo, eats it in her sedan.
(laughter)
- In the parking lot.
- It's true.
- Yeah, Cory Booker.
- More like Cory Booker's show for kids
and he watches the show and he wishes
that he could be the child performer.
- Yeah, you stupid creep bitch.
- Yeah, Cory Booker, you look like a snapping turtle.
- Much respect to Rosario Dawson though.
Archer is an all time show.
- Oh, she's not in Archer.
- Yes she is.
- She's not in Archer.
- Oh no, that's that other lady.
- That's Aisha Tyler.
- They're the same in my head.
- Clerks 2 was five.
yeah he was fine kids saw that movie. I think Clerks 2 is the only Rosario Dawson flick I've seen.
She was in kids have you seen kids? I have not seen kids. The movie's effed up man. Yeah?
That's one of those movies that like someone's older brother shows you. That's like a dance
with the devil type movie. Yeah no that's the dance kids is the dance the immortal technique
dance with the devil adaptation of movies. They should they should do a film adaptation.
[Laughter]
Oh, Dan's at the table.
You just go to the Wikipedia page.
And it's just an hour that the song plays in the background.
It's like "Trash in the Closet."
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Yeah, because R. Kelly's in it.
He's the main guy.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
"Kids" is a fine movie, I guess.
And you know what?
While we're back on political stuff for a second, Bill Gates, you look like Steve Jobs.
Yep.
Hey-o!
Bill Gates, who's--
And Steve Jobs, you're dead.
Someone, there's someone that does look like Bill Gates and I'm trying to think of it.
It's someone we know.
It's you.
Yeah.
It's not me.
Dana Carvey is the turtle in master disguise.
Pete Buttigieg, you're like a point and click adventure game because I...
Pete Buttigieg, you look like a Bosmer.
You do.
You got a Bosmer radiation coming off of you, dude.
You look like a Bosmer.
But I feel, yeah, you're like a Bosmer in that you would be a cannibal.
I'm catching Bosmer waves with my detector off of Pete Buttigieg.
it's a Bosmer level over over 9000 exactly oh my god Buddha judge the
Bosmer Pete Bosmer judge and then beta or York you're just a loser
just a total char pad mm-hmm Amy Charizard Amy Clovis shart oh sorry
Can't just put a cat on Patrick's face. I'm sorry. I was trying to put him here
I don't the most vicious attacks in the in the I'm sorry man repertoire
Hmm you put a cat to your friend. I'm sorry as penis on your eyes
It wasn't his piece foot went out and hit Pat in the face wish that was his foot. Yeah, you wish
That was a cat's got a fit, yeah, that's my fifth leg
Yeah
You cats are not packing heat. I'll say it. No, they aren't they're like me. They're like you man. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I hit yesterday
I was at the skate park. I
Fucked up a backboard slide that guy I'd like I have a backflip
I fucked up doing a bit there was oh my god. This was the funniest thing
There was just like a dude who just kept going around
He had a longboard but his trucks were like so tight and he was trying to just carve around like the the bowls and stuff and
and he like just kept fucking up. Like he - the funniest thing I saw him do, because there's
like at Smith Park, there's like the park and then there's the basketball court, and he fucking hit,
he was on the basketball court riding around just like trying to like - you know like that thing
that longboarders do where they like put their foot on it and then they spin around and then
they keep going like while they're moving? Yeah. They put their foot on it. So, he was trying to
do one of those, hit a pebble and then fell like face first into the ground and then got up and was
like like dad who were playing basketball came over and like stretched his legs
for him oh but I fucked up a backboard slide I'd like never do that and then
it like went up and it hit my side taint and like you have you have hemispheres
to your taint that's how big it is no you do no the side taint it's the side
taint yeah there's the regular taint and then right here that's the side that's
your crotch buddy yeah yeah well okay then the side taint what are you talking
about? The side taint! The fuckin'-- You talking about the area between your pelvis and--
The area between your leg and your and your pube bone yeah that's yeah it's just
your crotch. That's the crotch? That's the crotch zone. I thought the crotch was the hole.
The hole. The crotchet, the hole is the urethra. No. No. I mean the whole W hole.
The whole W. The W hole. I got W shaped urethra. So the board went, it missed my nuts by an inch.
What could have been dude. I would have thrown up. But I got, I remember. You got thrown up from
getting hit in the fucking balls? I got hit in the side taint and then I got up. Stop saying that.
I got hit in the side tank, got up, walked around and then said I'm going home to somebody,
like somebody I don't know.
Just to make it known, just so you had it on paper.
Yeah.
Hey, where did that guy go? Just got hit in the side tank.
Oh, he went home.
He went home.
Yeah, oh, actually.
After a hit like that, after a catastrophic hit to the side tank, it just makes sense.
You know he got hit in the side tank.
Oh, I would go home too.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I would have told somebody.
Yeah, I would have told somebody.
You have to.
When everybody looks at you because you just hit yourself in the nuts.
That's maritime law.
I'm going home.
I'm going home everybody.
I can't do this anymore.
You have to tell them.
Me, I can skate.
I can skateboard.
I can kick flip a longboard.
I can board and kick every day.
I can kick flip with a longboard.
I can grind with a screen door.
I'm extremely good at skateboarding.
You cannot grind with a screen door.
I could.
You give me a screen door, I will be on a rail.
You would never do it.
I would probably do it before you did it.
No you wouldn't.
I could do a flip on a laser.
I could do a flip on a laser beam. Are you serious? No. I could do it. You could never do a laser beam.
We're gonna have to... I'm gonna put that to the test. Alright, make a laser beam.
Here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna do the Cameron Olympics. Yeah. Which is like the Special
Olympics. It's all the same stuff. Yeah. But you have to flip on a laser beam too and you're the
only competitor. Okay. And we're gonna video it. Oh, this sounds fun. Yeah, it's gonna be fun. We're
We're gonna make you dash.
Yes!
I know you love to dash.
We're gonna make you throw.
Cameron's dash.
We're gonna make you Cameron's dash.
I get to throw?
What can I throw?
Uh, javelin?
Spear?
No.
Uh, what do you want to throw?
I mean, I'll probably throw a ball.
A frisbee.
He's gonna throw a ball of crap.
Throw a ball.
Please don't throw a ball of crap, dude.
He'll do it.
He's a psycho.
Well, that, yeah.
He would also, he'll get first place no matter what he does.
does because he's not afraid to pick up his his mouth and when he's not afraid
to use his mouth like a like a like a like a pooping yeah that's like if it's
like the soft day yeah soft a poop a scooper yeah that's nice here yeah thank
you for using the soft day what kind of what kind of events we want to see in
Cameron Olympics. Yeah, I think Cameron skateboarding I'd have to see.
I could probably, with like an hour of practice, I could probably do a really shitty ollie.
Okay. I've never done an ollie in my life. I've gotten close to one before, but I've
never actually done one. I mean, I had a very good day at the skate park yesterday. I'm
like really the side thing to hit the side team when home that's even worse
the grown man like kid no yeah I think it was I think he might have told a grown
kid you might have is your thing like if you're at the skate park and you're the
oldest person there does that suck not really no if it's like you tell there
oh yes don't kids anything you move out of the way and they listen whoa yeah
it's like God mode. When I was in high school I kicked a kid out of the
skate park. You're still in high school? Yeah. What are you talking about? When I was
16 I kicked a scooter kid out for... A scooter kid? You're still 16? He poured water on
the box and I said we don't... I was like you can't do that. We do not like water boxes.
We do not make boxes wet here at the skate park. I was like what are you trying to ruin it?
Yeah we're all good. And then he got pretty scared. Whoa dude you scared
You scared? I scared a 14 year old at a skate park when I was 16.
Because he made the box wet. I've punched a 7 foot man in the face.
Yeah. Yeah. And also I killed a baby.
Yeah. I'm way tougher than you guys. Whoa, Anthony Jeselnik just walked in.
Whoa, Anthony, that was an awesome. Do another joke. That one was so good.
I don't know anything about Anthony Jeselnik. I've actually raped my mom.
Yeah. And people are like, "Woo! Dude, he's the funniest fucker in the world."
Because women are actually ugly.
Yeah, mass shootings are cool.
And I actually prefer a mass shooting if I'm at a restaurant.
Prefer one.
I go in, they say smoking or not smoking.
I say mass shooting.
I say put me in the mass shooting section.
Yeah.
And Joe Rogan's like, "Man, you're a genius. How do you come up with these fucking fucked up jokes?
You have such a crazy sick mind."
I've actually taken inspiration from Christopher Walken.
He does have a walk-in thing going. I forget about that.
I've seen an interview where he says that Christopher Walken is the
person he bases his like tone of voice.
The one Anthony Jeslinic thing that I really like is his Dane Cook impression.
Yeah, I've never heard of it.
It's so fucking funny.
I think there's some stuff that he says is funny, but it's like most of it is just like...
I mean, he's definitely like a good joke writer.
Yeah, he's a good joke writer. It's just like he's trying to be just like a - he
used to try to be just dirty Demetri Martin.
Oh, and he was dirty.
and we already have one of my favorite comedians, Dirty Dmitri Martin.
Dirty Dmitri. Yeah, I love him. Dirty Dmitri the comedian. He does like, he does a
version of the Aristocrats with a notebook pad. Yeah, and he's like... He draws everything.
Yeah, and then the sun started shitting everywhere. Yeah, and then the sun started
shitting and then... And he said, "The Aristocrats." That'd be cool. Yeah. What about Dirty George
Carlin. That wouldn't happen. What about clean George Carlin? He says fruit you. That's where you went to
college. Mm-hmm fruit University. Yeah because you're in it you're such a fruit.
Yeah. Remember when that was an insult? Yeah. That's like an insult your dad says. Yeah my dad
actually does say yeah he'll be like you're being a real fruit right now. What
are you a fruit? If I get one time I got a lemon drop at the bar in front of my
dad rookie mistake absolutely rookie mistake and he was like pretty fruity
drink he got there you're like yeah I love lemon my dad doesn't outright call
things my dad stopped calling things gay but he does do this thing with his
eyebrows now when you order something that's gay hmm he's like oh you're
getting that mmm for the listeners Patrick shaved his eyebrows off when he
said that I'd started pulling my eyebrows out with a thread shaved his
eyebrows into a picture a tiny picture of a guy fucking another guy. Into a tiny picture of my dad making the face.
yeah he does that with his eyebrows. He did he shaved his eyebrows into two
Hitler eyebrows. Hitler eyebrows. Yeah. That were just little squares. Yeah. I was
watching that whitest kid Hitler rap last night. You wanna try that again?
(mumbling)
- Somebody reverse that.
- Yeah, you'll be surprised and shocked.
You're never getting on SNL, buddy.
- And really angry.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to bring up from the Discord.
- Oh, a new person in the lore.
- We were asking, I'm designing like a
Hungry Hamstravaganza shirt and we were asking people in the discord like, "Oh, what characters
from the show should I put on it? What's funny?" And they said that, "I guess there's a discord
created character named Solution that we've never heard of."
We had never heard of Solution. We're still trying to figure out who Solution is.
What Solution? We just wanted to shout out Solution.
Solution and the head first walls. Yeah, Solution and the head first walls, something like that.
I tried to ask who Solution was, everyone just said you know.
Yeah they kind of iced us out. It's like we made you.
Yeah. But I want to shout out Solution. I think it's our fault for not paying attention.
Yeah. Yeah that's what it's like if you don't pay attention to your kid.
I'm not going to blame anybody that's at fault for Solution.
Yeah. I'm not mad about it. I think yeah I think Solution is a great addition.
Yeah. I'm welcome. I'm happy to welcome to the roster. Yeah this is our first
This is the first acceptance. This is Solution's acceptance.
They're going to mod Solution into the podcast.
We're patching in Solution soon.
Into all past episodes.
Yeah, so you go back. There will be tons of Solution material.
Just keep your ears out and your eyes out.
Would Solution as an Italian man?
We haven't done our research. I don't feel comfortable just making stuff up.
It's really not our thing.
Yeah, not our place.
We will become educated. Next week, you might hear me doing a funny Solution.
voice saying Solution, ramming my head into a wall and I'll kind of round it out you know.
They'll give us the baton and we'll run with it.
Yeah.
I mean yeah.
So shout out to I think it was
Shout out to Solution and only Solution.
Yeah no fuck whoever came up with Solution. Solution was bigger than you.
Solution is we're starting a new podcast called Solution
Solution Solutions.
Solution yeah.
Solution
Solution's business solutions.
Yeah, and he'll have tons of, you know, he'll be, it'll be think it, learn it,
solutio.
Solutio.
Solutio it.
Solutio it. Yeah, that'll be his catchphrase. See, again, we're getting too far.
Yeah, I don't want to, yeah.
Whatever, let's just hop on the list.
Yeah.
What time are we at?
Right now, we're at the clock.
Oh, damn.
Yeah.
The list today I found pretty quickly, so, but I think it's funny.
I'm doing.
This is on the top 10 signs you have a bad neighbor.
And it's by user New Metal Maniac.
>> Here's a number one sign.
>> Friend in the pod, New Metal Maniac.
>> Number one sign, his name is Patrick and he lives next door to you.
>> I feel like I am a pretty bad neighbor.
>> Yeah, you definitely are.
>> Yeah.
>> I just, no, I don't do much.
>> I feel like if you just stand in here and you go, yeah!
>> If you had a lawn, dude, I would never want to live next to you.
>> Yeah. >> If you had a backyard,
I can only imagine what you're doing back there, dude.
I do not want to smell Patrick's musty backyard air. You would build a
you'd build a half pipe. Yeah I'd build a mini, if I had a backyard I'd have a mini
ramp in there. And you'd have an above-ground pool that you would not clean. I would not
have an above-ground pool. I hate swimming. You love swimming. You would have it for your...
You hate swimming? No I don't hate swimming but I feel like a pool... Patrick can't swim.
I feel like a pool is just scary. I can swim. I don't know. No I had it, there was a pool in
the the condo you can swim literally right now okay 10 seconds all right I'll go in
the tub great go that's not deep enough sip I we have to go to the YMCA that's
fine there's only three one second one second all right Patrick cannot swim
it's been proven we had a pool in my name why you can't swim we had a
pool my shit it got rid of it they they shouldn't have had a pool and check
there's a lot of upkeep yeah that's why you that's why you'd be a terrible
neighbor yeah you know what I get you'd let it get like not even green you let it
get brown there yeah you just like a little it there was like an old there
was an old couple that was in charge of the pool in the neighborhood yeah your
mom and dad no my mom and dad were young just absolutely flaming and Fran Fran
one day did not clean the pool she didn't clean the pool for a week and
then the pool was green one day and it was warm and I was like oh I wonder why
it's warm and then I opened up one of the filters and there's a bunch of dead
frogs. So wait, I thought that frog's blood was in the pool and that's why it was green.
To clarify, you saw it was green and you felt it to see if it was warm? I went in.
You went in when it was green? I was swimming in the pool because Fran told us it was fine. And that's
where you got your frog abilities. Yeah, that's when I got my frog abilities. That's when you got a big leap.
That's when you have an extremely long tongue. Uh-huh. Yeah. But yeah, she was like, "Oh, it's fine. I just
used a new cleaner and then we opened the box it was a bunch of dead frogs in it
those are clean my mom was like we got to go home I don't know what the fuck is
going on damn clean when I was a kid there's a there's a hurricane in North
Carolina and they we like the like the hockey team there was one exact it was it
was the Carolina Hurricanes yeah they came to my town no people died Patrick
will you shut up there's a hurricane that came my own town cool they left
open my parents left open the back door like cracked and we like went to sleep
it's left open your back door crack now
that's my mom and dad you're talking about me what hurricane in your back
door crack he's mad now Caleb's doing that thing with his eye when he gets mad
he's good they got a whole hockey team yeah I'm doing on John's face yeah a
knife and a spoon please that's just for us no they they left the back door open
cracked not my now my ass crack not my baby butthole that nobody put anything
in my ass but they did leave the back door no and they left the back door of
the house kind of open, okay? And we went to sleep and we woke up and there was a thousand
frogs in our house and we had to chase them, we had to chase frogs out of our house. My
mom would, she like found frogs like in the--
In the cereal.
Like no, like in the--
In the cereal?
Yeah, like in the pantry for like weeks.
No, they were in the cereal.
Damn.
Yeah, well we were eating--
Do you guys notice my rash?
Your rash? I did notice your rash.
I did notice your rash.
I wanted to ask you if it was sexual.
I have a rash because I'm allergic to Prilosec OTC.
I love dude, halo, d-o-d-s-t, that's what you're allergic to.
If you want the rest of my Prilosec, you can have it.
I don't, is that a dick pill?
What's that?
It's a heartburn medication.
You take 14 pills in a week and then...
Oh, I've taken that before.
Yeah, you take 14 and then you don't have heartburn for like four months.
Yeah, I, when I was...
So I'm gonna have, not have heartburn for two months because I only took seven and then
I don't know if that's how that works.
When I was a big fat guy, I would get the most insane heartburn.
Me too.
I would get combination sleep paralysis and heartburn.
So, I would wake up and not be able to move and also be choking on my own vomit.
And then I died.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
That's what this list is about.
I died like the girl in Breaking Bad.
The description of this list is by New Middle Maniac.
Do you fear your neighbors or hate them?
This list talks about the signs of having a bad neighbor.
Not necessarily the worst types of people that can be neighbors or the most annoying
things overall just the signs the neighbor next door could be bad. Number one they
act like they own the street. That pisses me off. When Mr. Johnson puts up a sign
that says Johnson Boulevard. Yeah yeah. You're like what are you doing? He's like I
own the street. I mean is it? It is my street. You're just acting. Okay. Yeah you're an
actor. You can't be the mayor of the street. You can't. It doesn't
make any sense. You can be the king of the street but you better have a leather
jacket and some switchblades yeah street kings yeah and a crown yeah the Latin
kings of the street you can be the Latin kings mm-hmm that's true yeah you can be
the Latin Kings you can I just call him Kings mm-hmm I don't even I call them
the Latin X Kings yeah this the new metal maniac about this one says basically
King X basically the vigilantes the ones who like to think the whole street
belongs to them and should follow their rules. I hate when Mr. Johnson makes rules
for the street. I hate when my street has a vigilante. Yeah. Damn, my neighbor's a vigilante.
Oh man, we have the worst vigilante problem on our street. Yeah, we have a serious
vigilante problem. Parablam. Parablam. Sorry, I wasn't paying attention. Yeah. I tried to
jump back in and I fucked up the fucking landing. Number two, their home smells
awful. Does that mean you can smell it from outside? Yeah, their home has a dust
thing around it like pig pen from Charlie Brown. Yeah, it's got serious stink lines.
Yeah, it's got stink lines. Like flying spaghettis. It's got stink lines in Patra. And I'm not talking monsters.
I know I'm definitely a bad neighbor, but like I feel like I was lucky enough
growing up, because we were definitely bad neighbors, but I was lucky enough to
live next door to my aunt. So it's like I could be as bad of a neighbor as I want.
You could shoot those stink lines right at her damn face. She didn't care. Oh, and believe me, I
did. Yeah we were always bad neighbors growing up. We would have like, it's
because we would like encroach on people's properties. Like one time
there was this huge mud puddle in this in our neighbor's yard. It was like when we
were living like out in the country sort of. There was like a giant mud puddle.
Yeah. That you made with your butt. No I didn't I didn't shit it out with my ass.
You made a mud puddle with your butt. My older brother and his friend duct-taped me and Levi, my younger
brother, to like hand trucks for moving and we just they would, through the mud
they just like played chicken with us and just like smashed us into each other and
then the guy called the police. Wow. Yeah. We uh... what do we have? What do we have?
What do we have? We... oh um... there was one time... no I won't say it. Say it. I had
neighbors who would hit the... we lived upstairs and they would hit the floor
the ceiling or floor with their broom. Oh I've been there a million times man. Yeah.
When I lived in 35, there was a fucking, there was like a frat that lived below me,
and they would just like, they would start playing music like four in the morning
through like, it was like they had like an Acura owned by like an idiot that had like a giant
subwoofer in it. Yeah, yeah. It was just blasted. He had an Acura in his apartment? That's what it
sounded like, you know, you know like dumb people who get like, they just get like a 2003 like Acura
with like chipped paint and they put no money into the car and then just buy like $1800
worth of speakers.
Keep it in the trunk.
Yeah, and then they play like some song where you can't hear anything except just like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was like those kind of speakers.
Yeah.
And you hit them with a broom?
And I went down and I went hobo with a shotgun on them.
Nice.
You've seen that movie?
No.
It's a good movie.
But I could guess what happens.
That's got Ruger Hauer.
Yeah, if you were in it, you'd be called homo with a shotgun.
you were in a call be booger ouchie booger ouchie that's your name if you
were an actor no I wouldn't and you'd be dead just like I am an actor yeah what
do you act a fool you got that right yeah yeah you know you might have I'm an
actor you might have recognized me for my role as a damn fool all the time a
damn fool when I'm in the Walmart there was one time my mom I think I've said
this on the show before but we've we my mom showed us the scary maze game and we
couldn't sleep because of scary move dude yeah yeah we couldn't sleep because of
how scared we were and my aunt next door like came over and started scream like
trying to scream at us and my mom was like I'm trying to get them to bed
because like our room was adjacent to hers like so all she could hear was us
like fighting with my mom yeah that's a serious that's a dark mom move there was
like a shadow mom well there she just did it because it was a prank shadow the mom
don't shadow the mom hog yeah you do have a mom hog no I don't hog mom I don't
have a hot and you have an evil version - my aunt living next door to my aunt
sucked yeah cuz there was one time where we were like young and we were getting
babysat and we were like we had like a young babysitter and so like we were
trying to like make her laugh and stuff and I know I know we're trying to make
her laugh I tried to fuck every babysitter that's not that's not the
situation and I did that was she was a she was just like our family was ugly
she was ugly you can say it she's she's a family friend so she lived with us for
bit so that's why she had that thing. You should date that girl. No, she's a total family friend.
But she like was watching us, we were being too loud and my aunt called us and I thought
it was my mom on the phone because like she I guess my aunt, my aunt's a fucking bitch
and she... You won't call the family friend ugly. But I'll call my aunt a bitch. You'll
call your aunt a fucking bitch. So she called our house and then was like trying to like
she was like put one of them on the phone right now I need to talk to them and then
she gave us the phone and then I answered in a voice like I answered like a cowboy voice
like hi like no cowboy ever sounded like this like the sunset sarsaparilla cowboy from fallout
okay yeah let's see that's how I answered it and she literally I heard I put the phone down
because she hung up I heard the dial tone and within like a second of me being done with the
call my aunt opened our front door and just started screaming at us about how
she had to work the next day she does sound like and I have never I have never
liked her since she did that really yeah she does not respect cowboys she does
not respect the Sunset Sarsaparilla boy I'm at peace with each of my aunts
mmm I find all of them just great people I would if they were uncles different
story if I like my uncles but if my aunts weren't related to me I would hate
them if aunts and uncles had to fight who would win? Uncles win. Why? Here's why, because
uncles will give you a beer and listen to Bob Seger with you. Uncles have
beer, aunts have wine. Mm-hmm and cigarettes. And cigarettes. They have
barefoot Moscato and cigarettes and they smoke them they smoke half of a Misty
and then they throw it out and they drink too much Moscato and then you can
steal their cigarettes right out of their hands during the World Series in
2014 yeah I did and and also half of aunts in my experience are from Peru and
they're really small yeah so I feel like that would and it's 10 and it's 10 times
worse when your aunt is your neighbor yeah because they because number three
they steal your mail number three they steal your mail you guys ever have this
issue people what neighbors stealing your mail yeah no I've mostly like lived in
spots where like people can't touch my mail.
And that's a tactical choice. They can't even touch it.
They can't even look at it. Not even if they wanted to.
No, I've never...
I mean by accident before but they would give it back.
I used to do that all the time. I never stole mail. There's this house...
That's a federal offense, bud. I only did that when I was a kid. I didn't give a fuck about the mail.
I just thought it was...
I was like, I'm breaking a law. I respect the mail too much. We would walk around this
neighborhood called the North...
the North Chase, yeah, North Chase.
- Northside Long Beach.
- Northside Long Beach where I grew up,
and we would steal people's mail.
- Yeah.
- There's this house--
- The mail house.
- And they always leave their mail,
they left their mail on the yard always,
and I was like Amazon packages and stuff.
- Mail on the yard.
- I was like, damn.
- There was--
- But I never did it, I was like, that'd be mean.
- It is mean.
- My neighborhood growing up, we had just like one
like little shack where they put all the mail,
and uh... one of my cousins was like staying with my aunt he got a he got a
blowjob in the mail house
and they had to send him home
uh... in my town when i was growing up they had one piece of mail and we all had to
look at it and share it and just write different stuff over it
it was completely you couldn't read it at some point so much white out on it
and then uh...
kayla made it
did you guys ever do ding dong ditch? oh we did yeah in my we had like a small
apart we had a whole small complex so everyone knew who everyone was and like
we we had a neighbor who we called Geico because of those commercials through the
I always feel like somebody's watching me so we used to we used to ding-dong
ditch Geico's house because we called him a pedophile. It was just a bunch of ten year olds calling like a
fat old man a pedophile. We would ding-dong ditch this one army guy yeah we would do
it like at least twice a week and we never got caught there was a plate he
only had one eye. He was like pretty young. He only had one eye and we would like just
ding dong and then run across the street and there was like a bush. We were
completely invisible. We went, my uncle got drunk and took us out
ding dong ditching in the neighborhood where he was a member of like the board.
He's on the HOA. Yeah he was on like the homeowners association. The thing is it's such a fun thing to do.
Yeah, I would do that now. Yeah, no, she's making a long ditch vid. Yeah. Yeah, it's still funny
It's really funny, but the one time we went to we ding-dong ditch Geico's house
Oh, so we had like ding-dong ditching now is everyone has a video doorbell the ring is fucking creepy, dude
I walked down the street the other day
Yeah, no, it's it's so creepy though like the street. I was walking down the street. I grew up on
they always have video doorbells. I was like, damn. They're all watching me right now.
They're all jacking off. We had like, there was one night we went out, so the thing
about Geico was he tried to talk to me about comics once and that got my
friend scared. You were like, he's a pedophile. Yeah, I was like, yeah, he's trying to talk to a
kid, he's a pedophile. And then my friend one day he like drove by and then said
"Stranger Danger" and he stopped the car, pulled back, like he waved at us and then
he went "Stranger Danger" and he stopped his car, pulled back and he went "Which one
you said that was it the little one oh my god yeah then from there on out we were
like oh why would you do that unless you had something to hide damn and so we
just like found out his name through the phone book and then I go yeah it was
Steve Geico so we called him Geico or pedophile Steve and then we pretty good
pretty good name number one day he left his screen door open sorry to interrupt
one day he left the screen door open when we were ding-dong ditching him and
I don't remember who did it but they just went up to his door and went "HEY!" and then ran away.
And scared the shit out of him. It was awesome.
Number four is they have a pet which is obnoxiously loud.
That was me.
Yeah. That was probably me too.
I had a beagle Australian cattle dog mix.
Did not have a pet growing up.
I just had like, we had like outdoor dogs, which is something like people don't really have up here I feel like.
We had like outdoor dogs that were just like,
they weren't even, they weren't even,
like they were beasts.
Like they were, I had no control over them.
- Yeah, my dog feels like a fit.
- They lived in like a cage and we fed them slop.
- Yeah.
- You know, and they were just like,
we just had to, there's no point in having them
except just to like fucking make our neighbors despise us.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- They would just yell all,
the neighbor had like a little kid.
- Oh, yeah.
- And the dogs wanted to fucking eat this kid so bad.
They wanted to rip him to shreds.
- Dogs wanna eat kids.
Yeah, there was when I was a kid, there was a dog that lived like in the house next door
and there was like a little fence around like a chain link fence.
And there was like a big ass dog and whenever I went in the yard to play, it would just
like start freaking out and trying to jump over the fence and it scared the shit out
of me and I stopped going outside for a while.
Dogs are scary.
I was so scared of dogs for most of my life because of that dog.
One of my shitty neighbors like growing up like she was at the same age as me but she
was like I don't know she just sucked she has like a kid now and nice yeah she
accused like she did more than just suck
second fuck the pregnant guy she tried to accuse my uncle's dog of biting her
she went you sir have bitten me yeah no she like came up and then like showed us
just like it was like snowing out so her hands were a little red because she
wasn't wearing gloves and she's like yeah that red spot is where he bit me and
then my dad looked at her and went no and then shut the door.
Damn. That was awesome. Number five they spy on you. That sucks. You ever had this experience?
I just told you. The video doorbells. Yeah I guess you have that too. I'm thinking
I'm thinking Disturbia. Yeah. That movie with Shia LaBeouf. I haven't seen it. It's
like the rear window yeah remakes basically oh really it ends with that
Kings of Leon song oh well thanks for spoiling I just said I hadn't seen it he
watches like little kids jack off to porn in that movie yeah honey changes
the TV on them yeah yeah it's pretty awesome dude that sounds cool yeah and
then he won any watches he tries to watch a girl get naked which he ends up
being the good guy in the movie so yeah yeah that one does not pass the Bechdel
is it um is it which friday the 13th movie is it is it the fifth one uh where he kills the guy for
eating the chocolate bar no oh which one is it is the where the kid is uh the little kid is looking
is looking out the window at a girl getting changed and he sees her boobies and then but
then he starts freaking he starts jumping around his bed and like hitting pillows and going like
for like no reason it's really weird and he starts ramming his head into the wall
do you know what I'm talking about?
I don't remember that.
You build up rage because the testosterone is stuck in your peice.
Somebody find that scene and send it to Caleb.
No, send it to Cameron.
Caleb loves that scene.
My military roommate did believe that in community college.
He believed Disturbia was a real movie?
No, he believed that if you don't jack off you become an alpha male.
It changes your, dude it changes your um
it does change your balance.
hormones. Your balls get too filled up, you get change your center of balance,
lower center of gravity, you can tackle people easy, you're taking to the ground like
vertical leap. Two shots to the fucking head. I will say Muhammad Ali did not have
sex before fights. Yeah. You know, there's something to that.
Listen, if it worked for Muhammad Ali, it'll work for me. That's all I'm
saying. Cash is clay. Catch this clay. Catch this clay. Caleb Clay. I'm remembering a
neighbor that I had that because we had like one of the neighborhoods I lived I
moved I moved like 19 times before I moved to Boston. I just like moved every
year growing up and one of the places we lived-- Because you're 19 years old.
Because I'm 19 years old and one of the places we lived had like a tiny pool in
the middle of the thing and the people who lived there were so crazy about like
like making sure people who were using the pool belonged to the neighborhood.
Yeah, and because like half of it was just like a normal like shitty houses North Carolina neighborhood
But then the other had the back half was like these huge fucking houses. Yeah, it was like a brand new development
They were just like saving or they were sharing the pool with us
Yeah
and so these people like we would go and a lot of times people would like ask us like where we live and stuff and
There's this one guy who would always like kind of look at us when we were in the pool
He lived across the street and one time he came in and he was like
I know you kids don't fucking live in this neighborhood
and I was like yeah I do bitch and I was like 14 and just talked so much shit to
this guy just kept calling him a homo like just was fucking just ribbing him
just like making fun of her looking goofy he I was it was I was just it was
fun because I knew I had it in my back pocket like I live in this neighborhood
yeah and I kept telling him like please call the cops please call the cops he
was like he just like hassled us until I was like all right we're leaving man and
And he's like, "Good, I'm following you home."
And this dude followed us home, back to my house,
and he was like, "Oh, this is your house?"
And I was like, "Yep, it's my house."
And he's like, "Fine, walk in."
And then I walked up to it, and I used my key,
and I walked in, and I was like,
"Come here, man, I want you to meet my parents."
(laughing)
- Nice.
- And then he talked to my mom and dad for a long time,
and he was just like, "Yeah, man,
"I'm like the biggest asshole in the world, aren't I?"
It was so nice.
That's a good feeling.
It was the best feeling.
My aunt's, my other aunt who lived in the neighborhood, she was the person, she was that guy.
She was a guy?
You had an aunt that was a guy?
Yeah, my aunt was that guy.
No, my aunt would like, like if kids like in the neighborhood had their friends over,
she was like, "Yeah, you're only allowed to have like five guests per house."
My aunt was making up fucking rules?
Yeah, she's just making up five guests per house.
Yeah, she didn't even, yeah.
It was fucking stupid.
No, my aunts suck. I hate my aunts.
That rugs, dude.
What the hell?
Five, five, five.
Yeah, no, just some arbitrary rule that she would--
Dude, you cannot have friend groups bigger than three in this neighborhood.
Just some stupid arbitrary rule like that to pull out, like, when she doesn't like a neighbor.
Ah, ah, ah, no laughing on Tuesdays, guys.
You cannot bring sandwiches to the pool.
Sorry, it's what it says.
Yep. It says in my brain. I made a book-- I wrote a book in my mind.
of my brain is that you can't ever make me mad so yeah and yeah look hanging of
having more than five guests that makes me mad I'm seriously getting I'm hulking
out right now even thinking I'm bulking up I'm bulking up to kill you to be the
defender the bouncer of the neighborhood number six they throw too many parties
that was also my family yeah I used to live next to this guy I think his name
was Asher Roth and he would just throw these fucking buck wild parties. He loved
drinking, he loved women, and he loved college. Yeah yeah he went to the
University of North Carolina next door and he just got in love with college.
This is the description of this one. "This is a weird item and it seems like it
doesn't belong here. It makes the neighbors seem very popular but I tend to
avoid parties for good reasons and there could be some shady stuff going on in
them. Shady stuff at the party? They're playing with the pinata. They are having
too many guests in the house. Yeah, they have more than five guests at the pool.
I heard that people are taking turns in the bathroom.
They're all using the same bowl for chips. No more than five people in the bathroom at any point. Hey, no more than three chips in a bowl at one time.
Hey, one bite per minute. You can chew once per minute. You get three ounces of dip,
okay, and I'm measuring it. Yeah, one glass of water per night. Mm-hmm. You get one
glass of water on your bedside table. You get one glass of milk under your bed. One
kind of long poop every two days. That's fair. No black pants! Get out! She
cuts you from the neighborhood yeah he sends you home you're not wearing the
right thing yeah where do I go to work you have to live at work now and you get
there and your boss is like oh we already have father guess I work another
thing I just remembered it was either her or my mom kicked the ice cream man
out of the neighborhood oh damn that's that's cold I will say very popular mood
with move with kids I'm at no I was the fucking kid of the rid of the pariah
Yeah, I was a pariah because they would kick the fucking ice cream man out. I don't know
It's all you know that side no soliciting no square cars
No music outdoors. They kicked the good ice cream man out the one who would sell you poppers if you asked him not not like
So weird they kicked out the ice cream man who was selling all the kids poppers
pop its pop its yeah like he was like i got fireworks i can sell you it's on the low he'd
sell you the bad the little like the box he'd sell it to you for 75 cents cheaper than the ice cream
yeah you don't need it yeah it's gunpowder yeah but those are like those are like a dollar
or like they're probably more it's like three bucks a pack so you're telling me he would
say there's an ice cream man who sold you fireworks at a loss uh-huh that your mom kicked out of the
the neighbor well yeah he was selling cold food that's a good thing to have no cold
food in the neighborhood only
yeah warren idea yet you are meals no cold so you want to have a taco there
better be some trees and i don't know if she said she kicked him out and then also
said that he was a drug dealer and a pedophile
well yeah i see yeah and that's another good thing you will know drug dealers or
pedophiles in the neighborhood
yet equal police said can one of their community public five drug dealers
She did not say pedophile.
Sorry, we have five pedophiles already.
I'm going to have to ask you to get out of here.
She didn't say pedophile, she said kid catcher.
And then I told all the other kids that the ice cream man was a kid catcher.
But I thought he was your homie.
Now you're switching sides, dude.
Yeah, more like Patrick Tomo.
Well, you get brainwashed as a kid.
Yeah, you got brainwashed.
You're telling me you got brainwashed.
You got brain from that guy, alright.
more like you got brain-freezed by the next one's my favorite one on this list
they live completely alone yeah okay read it go ahead I did it was my
family have to actually say it number seven they live completely alone you may
not think that a neighbor is bad because of this but think about it the neighbor
in question does not have a spouse a kid or a pet and is completely alone
something is amiss with this kind of neighbor if they are alone all the time
What it is is anyone's guess. I think it's normal to be alone. I think it's not normal. It's terrifying and awful.
I don't remember if this guy lived alone, but his name was Dick and one day we had our screen door open.
Dick who is alone. Dick who is alone. Alone Dick.
And Dick came up to her, we had our screen door open and we were inside playing and we were playing too loud and
Dick came up and said he was gonna call the police on us for disturbing the peace and
I wasn't allowed to have a sleepover that night. And you're like, hey, listen up Dick
I'm gonna disturb your peace if you know what I'm talking about. I would have said you want to talk about peace buddy
You realize we've been in Iraq since 1999?
How about we disturb that peace? Dick died like two months later and when my mom told me I was like good
He ruined my playdate. I did that with my grandpa when I was a kid. I had like a mean old grandpa
I just like hated him growing up
up and I was maybe like six when he died and like my mom and my grandma they're
both like crying in my house and I went up to him and I was like what the hell
are you crying I thought we all hated that guy yeah damn I had great emotional
intelligence as a child oh I had a terror I when my great-aunt Kathy died
we were waiting on the stairs on Easter because she died on East the night
before Easter morning and I was like when do we get candy are we doing like a
moment of silence right now and my uncle Paul freaked the fuck out on me.
He did a Paul flip. Yeah he was living with us at the time.
All my uncles lived with us. Yeah he was living with us. I just want to skip to number nine.
We'll just do number nine as the last one. They play a lot of loud noises from
their home. Just monkey noises? Yeah just the intro to Head Like a Hole. Yeah yeah.
Yeah, so they play samples.
Why do you keep playing?
It's like white noise.
Yeah, stop playing noises.
It's how I sleep.
It's jungle noises.
They play loud jungle noises.
I'm from the jungle.
I'm a monkey.
I have to - this is like white noise to me.
This is my house.
This is what my house sounds like.
What about a monkey that goes -
What about a monkey that -
Think about that.
What about a monkey that can spell?
Well, they can do that I'm sure.
Nobody's asked them yet.
The thing is we haven't learned their language.
I'm gonna learn your language pal
if you don't shut the fuck up. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm gonna teach you some language.
I'm gonna teach you my personal
love language. F-U-C-K-P-U-S-S-Y
P-U-S-S-Y
C-K
I'm gonna, you know he's coming to Boston.
Pussy C-K. Yeah, Pussy C-K.
That would solve so much
if you just came up on stage in a pussy hat and he was like "ah my daughters are old now"
what if he got a pussy installed into his chest like Iron Man?
like Videodrome?
yeah that'd be kind of funny
and he keeps a gun in it
yeah
yeah see but now that no that would lose people again
okay but it's a pink gun
that's pretty nice
it's for breast it's pink for breast cancer
oh breast cancer Susan G Coleman that was perfect
Susan G Coleman and it's Susan Gary Coleman
[Laughter]
He's behind Save the Tata's
He wasn't even talking about breast cancer
He just said that one day
And then everyone was like, "Gary, you fucking genius!"
"Gary, what was your first name again?"
"Susan!"
[Laughter]
Susan Gary Coleman
She's in Postal 2
[Laughter]
that's so weird Gary Coleman is a big plot point of postal to the movie or the game
the game is there is it a movie - I've only ever played postal - to just run
around and shoot stuff you put the cat you put the cheats in to get all the
guns and then you put the cats on the end of the shotgun yeah I've never I've
never just like played it like a game they came out with the sequel to postal
- it's like postal like apocalypse weekend or something like that like they
came out with it like recently yeah I think Milo Yiannopoulos does a voice
yeah I'm gonna have to check this out I have it I didn't realize yeah I didn't
realize I had it when I bought postal - oh damn I was one of the first games I
ever torrented postal - yeah mmm it's a it's not a bad game that was when I was
like oh you can just pirate any game and don't have any DRM yeah but like
sometimes like ISPs will hit you I got a sniper elite v2 I got hit for Saints
- That's not a hit yet because I just downloaded like...
- They had it on Xbox, I didn't need it.
- Random shitty old movies and like Digimon and shit.
- Stuff that nobody's tracking.
- Exactly.
- Like a 700...
- Like I'm sure if you download, yeah, like the stuff that just came out, like if I download
Uncut Gems right now.
- Yeah, I downloaded like a 700 megabyte file of the abominable Dr. Fibes in middle school
and my mom like almost lost her shit on me.
for some reason my mom thought you couldn't get caught downloading music
but if you downloaded movies on LimeWire that's what got you
I don't think people got hit with LimeWire as much
No, you could download any mp3 you want
That was kind of before they knew how to
track it. Yeah, we got our final, the nail in the fucking coffin, the thing that we
weren't allowed to torrent anything ever again, like my parents were like we're
gonna check the computer
was my little brother downloaded
tyo cruise dynamite dot mp3 on utorrent
and that's what got us
Jesus Christ
you got all that for tyo cruise?
no i had such like a good like
library of torrented shit and it's all gone now
too because my parents made us delete some of it. I had every like David Bowie
and Sonic Youth's entire discography
I fucked up my parents computer which is downloading just full albums.
Fuck yeah.
That, like Primus' whole discography, the soundtrack to The Hangover.
I thought that song, the Primus song, My Name is Mud, I thought it was My Name is Butt for
so long.
We've talked about this.
Oh, okay.
I just wanted to double check.
My name is Butt.
Not to be confused with that son of a bitch.
Not to be confused with Mud.
My name is Butt.
What was the last one? We definitely did that last time. We did this.
Christopher Goode yeah. Yeah we did I mean we recorded. We did it. Alright so
there's this then. Alright. There's the last one. Yo shout out to Tom. Yeah thanks Tom.
Nathaniel. Shout out to Nathaniel Smith. Thank you. Drew Maschiarelli.
These are our patrons by the way that weren't shouting out. That subscribe to
us on patreon we say what's up to the real homies huh yeah you are drew master
mascarelli Sarah V Ramirez thank you Sarah very much thank you extremely um
Jack Philbin thank you Jack Philbin love your dad's work
rejace rejice rejects red rejice Philbin and it's one of the pokey with the
Reggie's yeah Reggie Philbin and he smokes at Reggie uh-huh he smokes that he's
smoking seed he smokes that Reggie shit Sam Davis
thank you Sam Davis Ryan mock Ryan mock thank you yeah I'm butchering your last
name Ryan Ryan mock and thank you to service at PayPal comm for your
transfer was sharing transfer was successful yeah we transferred our PayPal
Uh-huh, we got some money from PayPal. Let's take a look at the promotions folder. We got Sig Sauer ammo ammo ammo
45 auto we can buy in bulk on Sig Sauer ammunition and save we should just spend all the pod money on ammo
We should get it
Send it all to
Neal's place. Yeah, and then just
Just let the car let the fucking dice roll as they may yeah, let the cookies blow up cookies
All they will rumble let the cards drop it's a milk. Let's spin around let the cards fall in the milk. Yeah
Oh, uh-huh, and we're gonna throw. Yeah, you're in trouble, buddy
All right
One something's on my milk
Something's on my milk! Three something's on my milk! Let the guards go in my milk! Okay, bye.