You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- All right, and we're back in the mix.
- Look at that, that's how good we are at this.
Don't eat the shit.
- Yeah, what the fuck is your problem, dude?
You're so stupid.
- Is that the Chipotle that gave you food poisoning?
- No.
(laughing)
- Going back ever more.
He saved it.
back for seconds. That would be so fucking funny dude. I can't waste it. I can't put it past you.
I wish that I could put it past you. I'm unable to. What gave you food poisoning?
I think, so I have two theories. Okay. I did get Taco Bell in New Hampshire.
All right. And I also the next day got a pizza from Veggie Crust. Veggie Crust is good. I got
got a different pizza that I don't normally get.
I picked it up, it was kinda cold when I opened the box.
It was a Gobi Manchur.
Thinking about it right now makes me wanna puke,
so maybe that is the thing that gave me food poisoning.
- Yeah, the mind is what detects it.
- The mind is a powerful tool.
- And when was this Chipotle from?
- This is from yesterday.
- Before or after you had food poisoning?
- Yesterday you had food poisoning,
and you were like, I'm gonna go to Chipotle.
(laughing)
- Lunatic.
- Oh, I just got done shitting water in applesauce
for fucking 24 hours.
I'm gonna go get Chipotle.
- I needed rice, I needed protein.
I've not eaten all day.
I was done with all of the symptoms.
So, I decided I needed to treat myself.
- You're a monster.
- I'm not a monster.
- You should be put in a cage like a dog.
Oh yeah, something I, we already recorded one episode, this is the second in this marathon
streak. I forgot to mention on the first one, we're back to shitty microphones now because
my school where I rented the good mics from closed, so I'm sorry but the audio quality
on these is going to be worse. It probably will be worse for the foreseeable future because
I don't think we can afford buying nice microphones.
I think if we save up a couple Patreon checks, that should be a priority.
Yeah, but I mean, I need to live.
Or if we do enough begging online right now and say...
Sure, Cameron does too. Okay, so...
I'll be fine. Don't let him.
No, no, no, no, no.
That guy, Shay Serrano, he keeps giving out $250 to people.
Send it to us, man.
Mm-hmm. Shay Serrano and then Stavros from Stavros Halkias said he's gonna do it too.
He's gonna give us $250?
If we get Shay Serrano and Stavros Halkias to give us $250...
That's $500.
$500. That's at least one microphone.
That's cash money.
Yeah, no, but we are going through a rough time right now. Patrick, unemployed as he's always been.
Cameron got canned. I got canned from one of my jobs. So if you want the first, this is the second
part of an episode. If you want the first part, you should sub to the Patreon. Let's continue what
we were talking about before. Kangaroos. Yeah. We're talking about kangaroos punching. I was
talking about that video that's... is your cat hitting a speed bag in the other room?
What is that fucking sound? He can hear... I put him in the other room because I'm
trying to eat and Sphynx cats are notoriously very bad at trying to steal
your food. They're very bad at it so he has to put them away. They're very like any
Egyptian. Mm-hmm. Yeah. So that's him trying to get out of the bedroom. It's
such a funny noise. Yeah I should probably just put this away and let him out. Yeah
you well yeah why should you start eating immediately when we started recording I
don't know I'm very hungry right now you can finish eating yeah I would love to
eat a kangaroos pouch all right now you can tell your story yeah is the cat
getting is that getting picked up on the probably not I don't know are you asking
me cuz you you know you chewing into the microphone that's true yeah that video
with the kangaroo where the guy the kangaroo like puts the dog in a headlock
yeah yeah and then the guy like pulls up yeah punches him in the face. That video rocks.
The funny here's what I was thinking about that video so much yesterday
because the the kangaroo is in complete shock right when he gets punched he he
like he stumbles back and then just looks at him yeah and the reason is the
kangaroo he only understands kicking. Somebody he gets kicked in the face with
the hand. Yeah, he's like so confused and that opened up a new world for him.
It was just like it was a mind bug that was making me go crazy yesterday.
You know, you know, it's I was watching a shit ton of kangaroo videos recently.
Do you know they can stand on their tails?
That's how they kick is they literally their tails support their weight and
they do that in Spyro 3. Fucking insane.
They use it like if you watch them hopping they use their tail like in the
back. They're like a tripod.
They like balance on their tail and move their feet forward. Sheila does that
in Spyro 3.
Yeah, you do that in your mom's bedroom.
Kangaroos are close enough to humans that I feel like there is a different universe where
humans evolved from kangaroos.
Yeah, they're like horse rabbits.
They're like horse rabbit chimps.
Yeah, Australians evolved from kangaroos.
Yeah, they did.
Yeah.
That's why they talk like that.
Just eat your fucking chipotle.
Yeah.
I saw a bunch, there's a bunch of videos of kangaroos trying to jump through glass doors
are big windows because they can't like to see the reflection and they're trying
to like fight it so they just jump and it's like smash into it and the people
just have to go up and be like go away stop stop go it cuz I'll just break the
windows if they if you let them it's such a yeah and I love that they're like
despised in Australia yeah like everybody they kill them not even cuz I
want they make burgers down there it's a pretty good meat imagine looking at a
kangaroo though and being like I'm gonna turn that shit into a burger yeah I'm
I'm gonna put ketchup on you.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Have you seen that video of the deer
running through the salon?
- I think so.
- It's like a deer, it's like some security cam footage.
- Yeah, no, I did see it.
- I was watching that, Dom sent it to me
while we were playing Jackbox with the Discord.
Shout out to the Discord. - Oh yeah, people go
on the Discord, we're gonna have game nights.
- Yeah, we're all locked inside.
- It's fun. - Yeah.
- Game nights. - Shut up.
- We play Jackbox, we watch that guy play Session.
sometimes scribble scribble oh yeah scribble oh yeah we'll play uh yeah oh
but there's just I was watching that video I watched it like four times and
then I just watched like the people's reaction the dude getting his haircut
goes up and just hugs the cashier it's just so strange like like a fucking deer
just ran through why you like you're consoling you grab your gun you home
- Oh my. - Yeah.
- Yeah, strangle the deer. - This is the sheriff.
- Yeah. - Put the deer in a headlock.
- Dude, it's so fucking funny. - Dude, you look like a total deer
- in a headlock right now. - (laughter)
Yeah.
God, he's fucking just going...
I'm trying to eat it as fast as I can.
Shut up, man. Just eat it.
Just eat it!
You're not allowed to talk until you finish eating.
Content-- yeah, go.
go sometimes I imagine what if Patrick was in that movie holes yeah he would be
one of the holes yeah you'd be one of the holes yeah just just Shia LaBeouf
digging into his belly button. Shia LaBeouf fucking the shit out of him.
He dug into me with a shovel. Damn dude he said I'm gonna make a hole out of you yet.
He's like you guys have oat milk and I said no and he hit me with a
shovel. I like that he kind of became Southern at some point yeah what's that
about like now he's like yeah I don't know man like we yeah yeah honey boy no
he played he plays his dad Southern in that I would never watch a movie oh it's
pretty good I heard it's pretty good yeah never watch a movie I Amazon it's
like gone Amazon Prime it shut off on shit yeah it shut off in the middle like
towards the end of the movie so I haven't seen the ending of it yeah it
shut off yeah they turned we're having trouble because too many people are
quarantined. It said that? Mm-hmm. That's what happened to Discord the other day.
Yeah, I heard it happened to Minecraft and Xbox Live and stuff too. Really? Yeah.
Dude, I'm gonna be... There were QAnon people who were like... They're shutting down Minecraft!
One of the baddest of communication. There was a QAnon guy who was
like, "I can't believe it! I saw this earlier today! They shut down Xbox Live!"
How am I gonna talk to my friends? Yeah. How are we gonna organize? Finish eating
Patrick so you can let the cat out. Yeah, the cat is going crazy.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Oh shit, they gotta eat in ten minutes too.
They have to eat in ten minutes? Oh god. Or else what?
This is a disaster. This is horrible.
Cats have to eat in ten minutes.
I don't know what we're gonna do.
Probably feed them. Jesus Christ.
Every time Patrick stands up his fucking microphone falls.
I don't know how he does it. That's because Patrick's body acts like the heavy thing on the block.
on the block at a lake.
No, it's a, the microphone is in orbit of him, so he stands up and walks away and it tries
to follow him.
It's a leaf sword.
It shoots out of orbit.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
Yeah, and there he goes.
Anyway, yeah, I need to be, I'm going to watch a lot of kangaroo videos over the next couple
of days.
Yeah.
I think I might learn everything about them.
No.
Get this, there is a movie.
Anthony Anderson okay from scary movie and a kangaroo what mm-hmm what's it
called next time next thing you know kangaroo guy no it's a bit about a hip
hop kangaroo mm-hmm named kangaroo jack he's on there's kangaroo jack is only in
that movie for 10 minutes that's not true like jaws dude yeah if they show
for too long it looks fake. Exactly yeah or you lose the fear.
I think they did do a kangaroo jack cut like a horror movie.
Yeah like like the Shining one. I remember those. Those are great.
Now you know why I put them in the other room. Yeah I already knew why you
put them in the other room. They're just psychopaths.
They're walking on the table. It's funny that in like two weeks you're gonna be eating them.
Yeah. Yeah. Like you are, I hope you know that's where we're at. I would never eat Yoda.
They kind of look like rotisserie chickens. Oh they look like, yeah, they look like chickens.
Yeah, you will. I would never eat Yoda though, that's my boy. I don't know.
Yeah, you guys will be. Depends on how he's. He's in the trash. Oh, fucking god damn it.
Why do we record? Why does he throw down the microphone? I don't know.
Wash your hands.
I know you didn't consider it. And you're not considering that nobody can hear you right now
either. God damn you Patrick. Just hurry up, just walk over here. Get your cat.
Okay, let's start the list.
We're really, no, we're not gonna, the list is, I don't think the list is long enough.
We should, it's not long enough?
Banter more.
I love banter, dude.
Oh my god, the cats are eating the chips.
This is the worst day of my life, dude.
I hate your cats.
I hate everything about this place.
Look at the poop on his ass, dude.
He's shitting on the couch.
He's got poop all over him.
He's covered in poop.
He's not covered in poop.
in poop. You would see it if he was covered in poop. You can't see it?
This is the kind of poop only cool people can see.
Whoa. Yeah, like that's my sixth sense. Patrick's killing the cat by
wrapping the light cord around the neck. I hate them so much. Why? Why do you think?
They're making this a disaster. They're fine. They're doing cat stuff. I hate them.
Oh shit, it's in ten minutes that thing is gonna feed them. I know.
it's gonna be so loud yeah oh it's gonna be super loud we can go push through no
I'll push through it the spirit of the marathon yeah I don't know that's
straight-up not gonna be good no it's so loud yeah two o'clock we got it we got a
pause okay let's pause we'll pause now and then we'll jump back in after they
eat this is a mistake that's fine all right so the cats are fed now cats are
it's over it's all over. Yoda has figured out how to push the feeder so that food
comes out and they open the door so now so now he's back now he's back yeah now
he's just licking it. Just leave him just sit down yeah just relax for a minute
yeah yeah. God I just despise them more than anything. Why? Why do you? Because they ruin
everything. They don't ruin everything. They ruin everything. They do not ruin everything.
- It's head-butting the food machine.
- It's unbelievable how shitty they are.
- They are not shitty at all.
- They're terrible, dude.
- They're not terrible.
- I wish that you had a baby.
- They are babies.
- I know, there's way worse than a baby.
Yeah, you don't even get a diaper.
- No, you don't even get to look at the diaper
when you change it.
You gotta stop saying that about them.
- You should make them wear diapers.
- You should have diapers for them.
Oh, there he goes.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
when you're so cool to do that to a gumball machine
i'd do that if you don't know if you're listing one of the cases lifting their
feeder up and down getting little pellets to come out
yeah he's hacking you know if you go up to a a soda machine and you just click
zero zero p
i mean he's so loud is it a yeah he just picks up the feeder and slams it down
god damn it did i find it works
i hate them do not have another patches of the room
i hate them so much
Fuck again. I just can't wait for you to have to eat them
No, yeah, you're gonna you're gonna stuff them with with
Mozzarella energy can like a beer can chicken
Yeah, I'm just gonna put them inside of each other like turducken. I do not like that
Yeah, you're gonna put the small you're gonna have yo fucking
Fuck it. Oh my god
Yeah, my guy
I'm excited for these cuz we're just gonna like
schedule these to be posted and they're just gonna go on way past like when
everybody's dead. Yeah. Just in like three weeks but one of these will release to
nobody. Yeah. It's gonna be awesome man. Pretty excited. I'm gonna be very pimp.
Yeah but it's just a virus though it's not even like a... Yeah. You are exactly the
kind of person who will die. No. Yeah. You are. Yeah. You're just gonna stay here right?
If I get it, I'll die. I'm just gonna stay here. Yeah. Yeah, see that's why you
definitely already have it. I don't already have it. I'm going to the woods, player.
I can go, I can go to the woods. I can go live on my family. You can't. You can't drive.
When are you gonna go to the woods? She can drive. She's gonna abandon you and go to
Alaska by herself. No. Yeah. Yes, she will. She's gonna go to the Simpsons. We both live in
the woods. She's gonna go to the Simpsons. Both of our families live in the woods. She's gonna go to the
Simpsons couch. She would not. She's gonna leave you behind and sit on the Simpsons couch.
think about it when we record we're almost doing a Simpsons couch gag Simpsons
couch guy that's just an hour of them talking it's the Grinch yeah yeah and
then the TV turns on and it's the Grinch they're watching the Grinch - I love
Simpsons couch gags man yeah yeah there's funny as hell about Simpsons
casting couch gags okay right and that's all yeah all the Simpsons gagging on my
penis. How about the Simpsons ouch gag and they get hurt. How about the Simpsons crouch gag
and they're in stealth mode. Yeah. Yeah. Somebody explained that that form of
assault, stealthing, to me recently. Yeah. What a name. I think I thought
they were doing, I was like, what are we playing Metal Gear Solid over here? Is
that? That was my joke to them. Yeah. Yeah and they were like, no it's
It's called rape.
Yeah.
And I was like, "Oh, I thought it was a video game.
That's my fault."
Yeah?
Yeah, that's what I said.
Yeah, you said it in that voice to them?
I thought you were talking about me.
Shut up!
That's what you sound like.
I'm going to kick your cat out the window, dude.
Don't threaten my cats.
I'm going to put your cat into a meat grinder.
Don't do that.
I'm going to turn him into a hot dog.
I don't like that.
I'm going to turn him into a hot cat.
I do not like when you do that.
I'm going to.
I'm going to turn him into a slam burger.
I'm going to turn him into a smash burger.
I'm gonna turn him into a hot cat. I do not like when you do that. I'm going to. I'm gonna turn him into a slam burger.
I'm gonna turn him into a smash burger from Shake Shack. I'm gonna turn him into Super Smash Brothers.
I'm gonna put him inside the game and they get butt stomped by Bowser.
I'm gonna do, I'm gonna do the... Bowser's butt cheeks are gonna crush their heads up.
Oh, I'm gonna do that's a home run derby part of Super Smash Brothers where you hit the big the big...
What the fuck is that guy? Sorry.
Dude, since there's been like
Sell like the self isolation and shit and stuff like there has just been so many just insane people
Walking by my apartment and just just shouting. I don't know what's going on
But there's just people outside like I've heard so many more so much more fight on John said that he's noticed an uptick in crazies
Yeah, I think it's just because there's less
Normals, yeah, yeah, you know, I think also this is the time for the crazies to really go crazy. That's true
this is the time people who normally you would walk by and wouldn't be
talking to themselves this is when they will be talking to themselves. Give it two weeks it's gonna be the purge man.
Yeah. Yeah. And that's why you're gonna die Patrick. No I'll be fine. Because I'll be at home, I'll have a shotgun aimed at the door, my house is gonna be set up with
I can go to my house. I'm gonna have marbles on the staircase and hot tar and a nail and one of the. And a spider. I'll be fine. I'll go to my home in New Hampshire, I'll go to my parents house. I'm gonna go absolutely home alone on these fools.
I have a pellet gun. A pellet gun? And there's a real gun there too. Nice. It's in a safe.
I haven't found it yet. I haven't found it yet. I'm gonna find my gun. I'll just sit outside
with the pellet gun and I'll practice. You're gonna sit outside on a peloton? Yeah. Pat,
you should start riding a peloton. I might. I know someone who has one. I'm gonna start
rowing. I have a rowing machine in my room that I don't use very often. It'd be funny
if I like came back and you were just super buff. I don't have anything else to
do. Just get strong. Cameron's gonna get prison whipped. I probably will get strong. I'm just gonna try to. I'm gonna
say I'm gonna get strong. I'm gonna do it for two days then I'm just gonna stop.
You should just get extremely strong. I would love to. That would be so cool. But just huge arms.
Nothing different. Just like huge red arms. I'm worried I'm just gonna get fatter. Yeah. I mean
you just gotta start. You just have to do, the thing is yeah. Just like jump a bunch. I'm
I'm basically, nothing for me is changing other than I can't go outside.
Yeah, that's true.
Literally, I've been doing this, I've been prepared more than anyone.
I know what I'm doing here.
All you do is you just kind of sit in here and then you get up and go to--
Yeah, give us Patrick's quarantine tips.
What do you do?
You sit at home, you go to 7-Eleven a little bit.
You wake up, when do you wake up?
You wake up 2 a.m.
2 a.m.?
You stay up till 10 in the morning, you fall back asleep.
Wait, so when did you go to sleep to wake up at 2 a.m.?
I'm not I haven't gotten there yet. No you started at waking up at 2 a.m.
So what time did you go to sleep to wake up? I'm getting there.
Okay all right wake up at 2 a.m. You wake up at 2 a.m.
you stay up till 10 a.m. you fall back asleep
till 3 a.m. What? Till 3? It's already 24 hours. Yeah you already went to 3 p.m.
Okay. You get dinner, you get lunch which--
You wait in that order, dinner and then lunch.
You get lunch, which is breakfast.
Lunch is breakfast.
What time are you eating lunch/breakfast?
That's at 4.
4am or pm?
4pm.
Okay.
And then you go to bed at 2am.
What do you, what else?
So you wake up, you eat one meal and then you go to bed when you wake up.
At the same time.
Mmhmm.
And so that's the ubermensch sleep cycle.
If you can't understand this system, you're gonna die.
Okay.
Alright.
That's all I'm saying.
I'll die.
I'll die, yeah.
I don't want to try and understand that.
Yeah, that makes absolutely no sense.
That's too difficult.
Yeah.
Time is a-- Patrick understands better than anybody that time is a construct and he just
exists outside of it.
He's not worried about it.
You sleep 30 minutes of every hour.
Yeah.
That's 12 hours, baby.
None of it makes sense.
When I was-- at some point in high school, I was just like homeschooled and like I was
going crazy and just like I decided to try the the the uber minch sleep cycle yeah
where you sleep like you sleep 90 minutes every five hours yeah and yeah I was
like one of the worst weeks of my entire life I was like going I was so sleep
deprived that I was like hallucinating just it's it was terrible did the cat
fart again yeah no no he dropped a dookie in the bathroom for sure dude I
will say that is pretty cool yeah that a poop that a poop can cat in the bathroom
you should can teach them the flush yeah there's no he doesn't he doesn't poop in
the toilet you should teach him just close the door don't pick it up
that's gonna shovel it into his mouth Patrick comes back his poop all over his
mouth well I picked it up well it's all picked up it's all cleaned up it's all
picked up yeah and then he ties his he ties his lips together like a poop bag
and he could walks outside yeah I can still smell it it probably it smells
worse now. It smells really bad. It's because you just walked up to it. Yeah, that's true. Oh my god.
Yeah, it's so awful. Dude, they have the worst smelling shit in the world. I hate here so bad. Yeah. Why? Because it
smells like shit. There's two monsters that run around that are addicted to making noise and eating
my food and you refuse to wear shoes. It's my house. I don't have to wear shoes. I'm not saying
have to I'm saying it's part of the reason I hate it well when I move to the new
place in September true you won't their life will all be dead yeah yeah no we'll
be fine this isn't and this is like I feel like I'm on fear factor right now
this smells so bad yeah smells pretty bad yeah this is a challenge to record
something while Joe Rogan throws shit at my face. Record a one hour podcast when a cat has pooped in the bathroom
I'm
Stinky little fucker he is man. Yeah, he fucking sucks. All right. Let's do this. Let's isn't suck. All right. This list is from Pierce
Thank you. Thank you
Follow him at cringe underscore genius. Mm-hmm. You may have seen him. He's on truth point on the street a couple times
Yeah, he's been on here. If you live in LA, you've seen him on the street that close to the mic
You've seen a mom straight in LA. Mm-hmm
You've seen him in your house? Anywhere else? You've seen him on the block. Post it up.
Northside Long Beach. He's selling CDs. Northside Long Beach. He sells CDs of his episodes on this
podcast. He says this is a soul podcast. He says this is raw shit. This is that prom shit. This is
what we do. Don't tell your mom shit. Yeah, he says that to people. He sent us a list called
weirdest ice cream flavors on Top Towns. By user... what is it? Anthony Fantan...
Anthony... Becquerera. Becquerera831. Becquera. Anthony Becquera831. Some
Italian guy. Some Italian... some fucking shitty wop sitting in front of an old
old computer. A new machine. A Lenovo ThinkPad. Yeah, and he's like, "I'll write the weirdest
ice cream flavors." Yeah. What do you think of the weirdest thing I can? All right, before we start,
- I'm gonna start, if you had to come up with,
if you were in the first episode of Nathan For You,
and you're coming up with an ice cream flavor,
frozen, shut up.
- We're doing it our own.
- This is a different version.
- This is called Caleb For You.
- In this episode, in this version of the episode,
he's going to Cold Stone and not in--
- Oh, can we do mix-ins too?
- No, yes, oh my God, yes.
- Yes.
- Okay, with that in mind.
- All right, who's going first?
penis okay can I and the topping is Grinch balls yeah fried bacon I'm at now
imagine that that's not weird I would imagine how weird that would be okay wait
I would hate wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait and my
boyfriend licks it out um soap soap cuz you don't ride soap with and with the
top of a gun bacon make sense and
chicken wings vanilla. It's not
sounds about right
poop chocolate.
Can I get the poop chocolate? Yeah,
I would say you hit the sand fast
and I say to the other. Can I get
the poop chocolate diet chocolate
diet crap diet BD? What about large
ice cream? Yeah, I get a large and
they say, sir, what are you talking
about? We only have only have like
We only have like it and love it sizes.
Mm-hmm.
Like it, love it, and gotta have it.
Yeah.
Excuse me?
I gotta have it.
I gotta have it, poop chocolate.
I just remembered I have Hi-Chews.
Yeah.
Yeah, you want one?
No.
You don't like Hi-Chews?
I'll have one.
No, I love Hi-Chews, I just can't eat it right now.
Oh, 'cause it'll freak him out.
It'll freak him out.
I threw up so much yesterday, my teeth are soft.
And then you had Chipotle.
You can't eat a Hi-Chew.
Yeah, and then you were like, "These things can handle a sada."
I didn't get a sada, I got chicken.
side of there is like $9. I don't know. I think it's all the same. Chicken's like $8.
What are you talking about? It's not all the same price as Chipotle. It isn't but...
$7.50 for chicken, $7.50 for veggies, $8 for carnitas, $8.50 for steak, $8.50 for
barbacoa, $9.50 for carne asada. $9.50? Mm-hmm. That's too expensive. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I got it like twice. It's pretty good though. It was good. Oh no,
it's $7.50 for sofritas too. What about the weirdest Chipotle flavors? Yeah.
Vanilla. Vanilla would be, any ice cream flavor would be a terrible Chipotle flavor.
But what if it's like a fried ice cream at Chipotle? What is that? And you get a churro.
What? I'm saying like like something you put on a rice bowl. Yeah. We can put ice
cream on the bowl. Ice cream does go in bowls I guess. Yeah, no rice. Yeah what about a rice
flavor of ice cream? I'm sure that exists in Japan. I've had it. Why would it exist in Japan?
Probably in Taiwan. Yeah, why would it be in Japan? Yeah, why would they have it in Japan?
Are you saying Japanese people like rice? Yeah, what the fuck is your problem dude? You're
racist. No, I got confused. Now you're saying they don't like rice? No, Japanese people hate
rice I'm sending you to the news my friend well I got a station for you I
got a scoop for you daily ice cream it's a nice scoop and it's poop podcast host
first says Japanese people like rice and then says they hate it not only are you
racist you're a flip-flopper - yeah racist flip-flopper Patrick that's my
problem with a I used to be I should be a Nazi in prison and now I'm like help
stop people from being racist like stop flip-flopping yeah just take a side dude
yeah race race is wrong with it racist flip-flopper what am I in the beach in
Florida yeah racist flip-flops yeah what yeah what am I a beach in Florida or
South Carolina what am I a beach in Florida what am I on a beach funny
things I ever saw I was in South Carolina I saw a big fat black guy on a
Confederate flag floatie in the middle of the ocean it's pretty beach it's pretty
cool. I was just like that's really funny. It is funny. You should have taken a picture.
Yeah, that's the thing that like people from the north don't really get about the south though,
is like it's so just like something that you see so much that you're just like desensitized to it.
Yeah. You don't even really like that guy probably did never thought about that. He was just like
yeah, yeah, he's a floaty. He's like the only one at the whatever like surf shop I went to.
Yeah. The cat is on my hand.
No he doesn't. Caleb hit the cat. Stop hitting my cat. I'm not hitting him, I'm petting him.
Stop that. If I was hitting him he'd walk away.
He walked away. He just walked away because you were hitting him. I wasn't hitting him.
You were hitting him. You were absolutely hitting him. No. I don't hit cats. He's doing domestic abuse.
No. Yeah. And it's not even your own domestic, that's what's so fucked up about it. Yeah he just shit.
Yeah, of course he smells like shit.
Alright, weirdest ice cream flavors.
Number one, Horse Flesh.
That's pretty weird.
That's no different than bacon ice cream in my eyes.
That's like Taco Bell.
Yeah, Taco Bell actually has Horse Flesh ice cream.
Do they have ice cream there?
Uh, yeah, they do.
They should.
Yeah, they should have a horchata ice cream.
I'd eat that shit.
Yeah, Taco Bell horchata.
They should have horchata at Taco Bell.
They should have cheeseburgers at Taco Bell.
And pizza!
And video games!
oh my god and free drinks and a girlfriend yeah that you can rent out
yeah in the bathroom yeah they and they should have a bidet they have that water
side well cantina they should have you should be able to work there for free
mm-hmm if you want you should be able to hop behind the kitchen I can start
working the Taco Bell in downtown crossing 15 bucks an hour
for a baseline employee.
Dude, I would pay them to be able to use that sour cream cock gun that they use.
That thing is fucking sick.
I'm going to fill that with pee and use it into the toilet.
They shoot the beans and the cheese and the sour cream out of a fucking piping gun.
I wish I could go to Taco Bell right now.
You could.
I would say that's a huge danger zone right now.
go in a hazmat suit it's fine. I mean walking into a Taco Bell in a hazmat suit. Spray everything.
Yeah. Spray the person in front of you in their face like pepper spray. Yeah. The top comments.
You know we were making fun of that guy on the bus to New York but. That guy did deserve
to be made fun of. At that point in time yes. There was a guy dressed like he was in Fallout.
Yeah he was wearing like a gas mask. He was wearing a gas mask. There's no difference to
that versus just wearing like a mask. He's wearing a gas mask and a Kanye West
graduation hat. Yeah. No that guy absolutely deserved to be made fun of.
Yeah. He's one of our patrons. Yeah. Yeah. The number of top
comment on horse flesh is "Ew oh my god what would incline somebody so that they
would eat horse flesh?" Obviously some people can't spell or else they wouldn't
eat it. I'll tell you what would incline me. Ice cream. Yeah. I don't care what flavor it
is. As long as it's ice. As long as it's ice cream. I'm only eating horse flesh because
I can't spell. I thought this said delicious snack. Yeah, I thought it said horse. It was
a bucket full of just like red disgusting. I thought it said horchata. I thought it said
horse fresh. Yeah. And I was like, mmm, fresh. I thought it said candy. I just can't spell
at all. I don't even, I thought it was just a drawing. I thought it was a really bad drawing
that didn't look like anything, but it was words.
I just saw ice cream. I recognize ice cream.
With just little pieces of raw meat in it. I thought it said delicious, so I ate it.
I thought it said red delicious, apple flavored.
Somebody says, "What in the heck are the people putting in food now?"
Somebody says, "And this, my dear mortals," wait, Pat, reread this. This is your comment.
And this, my dear mortals, is when all hope of the human race regaining their dignity and sanity was lost.
That's what it was. It was saying horse, horse flesh.
We should have Lloyd on. I would love to have Lloyd on, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, he's a man. He would, he's, he would, he definitely knows this website.
I would bet he's ranked in the Spongebob characters on here before or something.
Yeah.
You poor horsies.
Imagine this is someone's favorite ice cream dot dot dot.
Yuck.
I'm getting so mad imagining this is someone's favorite ice cream.
This is your favorite ice cream?
What would the guy look like whose favorite ice cream this was?
Probably look exactly like Patrick.
Yeah, probably me with a hat.
Yeah, he's not wearing shoes at the ice cream place.
A cowboy hat.
It's Patrick with no shoes and a cowboy hat.
I think I'm going to pick up that.
We can make that happen.
I think we make that happen pretty quick. I'm gonna pick up a signature hat. I think
I'm gonna shave my head and just have a SIG hat. Back away from me. Why?
Because you definitely have the virus. I don't. You've been coughing. So? You've been
coughing. I've been coughing because I've been quitting vaping. Okay that's... I don't
know. I still don't want you coughing around me. That's what I would make up to.
I just got a Bands in Town artist alert. Ariel Pink sent me a message. Patrick just
got an alert that he has the virus on his phone. His phone said we
detected your connection. Patrick will die from it. No. And we will live
and we will carry on. I don't think I'll die from it. I think you'll get, I think
you will lose your legs. That's just from the diabetes. Yeah but you'll go to the
hospital because of the virus and they'll say you have it but you're
probably gonna be fine but while you're here we should get rid of these. You do
have diabetes in your labor and you just have you you have giant swollen purple
like rescue hero legs and you're like no I don't have diabetes I think I don't
know how this person I think it might have been my mom's grandpa huh but he
did get his leg removed somebody in my family I don't know who it was someone
in my mom's side of the family got their leg removed and then every year at
Christmas, like after they passed away, they would fill up the leg, like the
plastic leg, they would fill it up with like Christmas wreaths and they
would make us take pictures with the leg. Oh my god. Holy shit dude. Yeah. I thought
you're gonna say they filled it up with eggnog. No. No there's pictures of me like
really really young and I'm just... With a leg? With a leg filled with Christmas
stuff. Oh my god dude. Yeah. That rocks. My my my uncle had an eyepatch and... My uncle
had an eyepatch. My uncle... And we used to play on it. He had he showed me how to draw.
My uncle had an eyepatch or no my like second cousin some guy that I would see
like once every three years or whatever. Yeah your boyfriend. And my dad I always
would ask my dad I'd be like what is wrong with him and my dad would be like
he used to be a pirate and I believed that for so long. Yeah. He was just like a
got he worked as like I mean worked as a greeter at Walmart you should not if you
get hired at Walmart and you have an eyepatch they should not make you the
greeter that's the Walmart from escape from New York yeah yeah the Walmart that
Kurt Russell works yeah yeah welcome to Walmart motherfucker
number two weirdest ice cream flavor it's an oldie but it's a goodie it's
poop poop is honestly the number one oldie but goodie yeah poop is the number
one worst ice cream flavor I'm thinking of ice cream's tasted like this who
smells right now doesn't smell that bad it did yeah that's most bad right now
it's cuz we're used to it I think it's cuz I came back I think I sucked all the
poop in Caleb so you did yeah they got some stinky ass shits man I got to
figure out what's going on with them I think that maybe I think anything
anybody or thing that eats tiny beads of stuff is gonna have smelly shit. That's
true. Doesn't matter what kind of food it is. That's why you have such stinky shit.
Somebody comments on poop and says, "Now I can't stop laughing." And says, "What? Is
this an actual thing?" Yeah, I would again refer you to that episode of Nathan
Well that's frozen yogurt so that one doesn't have anything to do with this.
Yeah I guess you're right. Here's a weird ice cream flavor.
Well we got a...
What?
What is it?
Okay well here's mine.
Yeah.
Okay.
Charlie bit my finger flavored.
Oh my god. So does it taste like...
It tastes like...
Charlie's finger.
No yeah it tastes exactly like Charlie's finger. Charlie's finger flavored ice cream.
Just like kind of salty. It has a booger on it.
Yeah.
Oh boogers.
And it makes you laugh.
No not Charlie's finger.
No boogers is...
So if boogers isn't on this list, this is a bad list.
The top comment here is another Patrick comment.
This is a comment Patrick left on his philosophy alt.
I don't know why any of these are on the weirdest ice cream flavors.
I find them to be quite tasteful, especially human flesh.
We got a badass freaking Hannibal Jekyll or Hector over here.
Alright, alright Anthony Cheslinick.
Hannibal Jekyll over here.
The dark philosopher.
I like this comment also what drugs you use when making this list poop dude what
kind of freaking drug I'm on yeah Jacob yeah I'm high on poop right now yeah what
kind of we should do Jacob and do we should do a episode on Jankum dude yeah
yeah yeah we should all get fucked up on Jankum and toilet wine and then do an
episode yeah Bruno flavored ice cream Bruno flavored ice cream and it open it
opens its penis up and it says Bruno yeah yeah that's a funny scene in them
That motherfucking movie. The part where they make Paula Abdul sit on a person.
Yeah. It's so funny.
It's true.
Yeah. Anyway.
You can watch-
Why are you cracking onto the microphone? What are you doing?
I'm cracking my hand.
Why are you doing it on the microphone?
We got the electrical on. We're getting too much heat.
Yeah.
I just heard it in my headphones.
We're trying to kill my cats and shit.
We're trying to eat his cats. We're telling him that he sucks.
That's not even good.
What's not good?
I love my cats. You can't say that you're gonna eat them.
You love the cats.
I have said it so many times.
You can't say it.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to get upset about it and then I'm not going to say anything and then I'm just
going to be upset every time that you say it.
About eating a cat?
Yeah.
Okay.
That's fine with me.
Yeah, dude, if you say that I'll get so quietly mad at you.
If you say that I'll get upset and you'll never know.
You diabolical, you have a female brain, Pat.
Here's a comment from TrollsFan536.
says one time my brother said chocolate ice cream is poop. One time my brother said
chocolate ice cream is poop and I threw up. Do you guys think, do you guys subscribe to the idea
that two girls one cup it's just chocolate ice cream that they put up there?
You think it's real poop? No I saw the butt. Yeah but they shoot it up
there with like a piping bag. Nah. You don't think so? No. I think it is. It looked
like poop. He's right chocolate ice cream looks like poop. Chocolate ice cream
doesn't look at it I think it's too melty and no it's too green in that video to be
ice cream but I have never had a poop this man doesn't matter I ring in your
question is just whether it's real poop or not I don't think it has to be yeah
it could be icing or something I just mean I think that poop you like when I
poop I think that they when they went into that dust I mean closer to dust and
that shit when they went into that video there's no way that they could have
known exactly what okay maybe the poop was gonna look like maybe the because
sometimes I poop and it's like it's like a million little strings of crap you got
a problem you gotta go to the night you have a play-doh spaghetti yeah it's what
it looks like some Caleb yeah no cuz you have a thing of plastic stuck in your
butt
I have a triangle yeah shape poop sometime yeah he has a you got a salt
check your lid stuck in your asshole I don't know I just think I think that they
they had no idea what it was gonna come out like and it came out perfect I mean
that's a that's a picture-perfect poop nah yeah it looks good man good enough
to eat I will consider I will consider that they did poop into the cup and then
because there is a cut so I do think that maybe they pooped into the cut and
then changed it to ice cream they they examine the there's no one part where
she's opening up the asshole and licking the poop out.
- Okay, I forgot about that part.
- Yeah.
- So, no, it's definitely not ice cream.
- I think that you could,
I think I could recreate that video with zero poop.
- Do it.
- I think you could.
- That is the podcast about Liz challenge.
When you're in self-isolation.
- I'm gonna blast Patrick with an enema.
- No.
- Yeah, I'd blast Patrick with an enema.
- No, no, no, you said you would recreate it.
You gotta recreate it on your own, buddy.
- It's two girls!
- Uh-uh.
- Yeah, it's two girls, it's perfect.
You guys can recreate it.
- You, me, and Patrick.
Yeah, we'll put on wigs, I'll put on the dress I have to wear, and I'll suck chocolate ice
cream out of your asshole like there's no fucking tomorrow, baby.
I can't be in the video for a number of reasons.
You can be in the video.
No.
It'll just be your ass, okay?
They won't show your face.
It will just be your ass with a tattoo of your name on it.
I've got a hemorrhoid problem, I can't be in this video.
You have a hemorrhoid problem?
Mm-hmm.
That is better.
So you can suck the blood out?
Yeah.
It just sells it, you know?
Because you've got to one-up them.
It's true, yeah.
Two girls, one bloody cut.
girls I just I hear a big hairy with a hammer oh they got sued for that video
they did yeah I don't know they said too gross it was a Supreme Court they see
yeah yeah they're too gross guy don't my root bitter Ginsburg is trying to stay
alive just in case it goes back to the Supreme Court. Ruth Bader Ginsburg is trying to get
Two Girls One Cup shut down. Yeah. No, they got sued. I don't remember what for. Anyway,
let's go to number three. Too sexy. We got sued by the nasty police for eating shit on
camera. The nasty police, Ruth Bader Ginsburg. Yeah. Number three is Viagra. Now, this is
an ice cream flavor I think I eat. I feel like we were, if Extends had become... Wouldn't
just be a salt flavor in Viagra just salts what isn't it like like how the
Adderall is I've never looked into it honestly honestly honestly and there I
was a blue ice cream does look pretty tasty have you did I remember as a kid
eating dear eat blue cotton candy ice cream no there was this place mrs.
Moomoo's that had blue cut. I thought you went to Mrs. Moomoo's. Yeah I did and I sucked on her udders you fucking bitch.
Caleb sucked on Mr. Moomoo? No I didn't. One of my aunts used to call the short bus the Moomoo bus.
Huh. So that's where Caleb went. No I didn't. Yeah. No I went to regular, I went to regular school.
You went to the, you were on the Moomoo bus. No. No I went to regular school. You went to dome school
and gave dome. No I didn't. You were dome schooled. Caleb was dome schooled. You guys were comb schooled.
because your parents would comb in your mouth.
No, I went to a barber shop.
Beautiful hair.
Your dad would comb and he'd comb in your mouth.
No, he just couldn't have beautiful hair.
My dad taught me how to make a harmonica out of a comb and tissue paper.
Oh yeah, me too man.
That's a classic.
That's a white trash classic move.
Actually, no, Gordon from Sesame Street taught me that.
I can't credit my dad for that.
That was like science fair for me.
Yeah.
Yeah, my dad would just be like,
of like a bunch of things you can make with duct tape and I would just make like
wallets and shit yeah I had a duct tape wallet for a long time
my dad still makes duct tape wallets. They're sick dude.
Fucking, this boss. Lame. Dude I could make a trifold duct tape wallet. You'd make a triforce dude.
Yeah I can make a triforce duct tape. Yeah yeah no you couldn't no you
couldn't. Anyway I would eat blue cotton candy ice cream. Anyway I eat cotton candy all the time.
I'm not retarded. I would eat cotton candy all the time growing up and I would shit
blue shit and but then I would be like mom I think I think I'm an alien.
You ever have purple cow ice cream? Maybe. Stop making shit up. No it's a good flavor.
It's raspberry dark chocolate. Is that from Lizzie's or something? They have it at
different places I think it was like a Hershey's flavor yeah did you guys eat
because it's a really good you guys eat like hoodie cups growing up or whatever
the hoodsies yeah yeah we that's not a thing that we don't have hood milk yeah
that's like a local thing so weird everybody's brands are yeah yeah aren't
brand yeah that's true like we have like oakhurst and hood yeah yeah
okhurst weirds me out because they put an acorn on there and that should not be
be on normal milk. You should only put it on nut milks. Acorn milk. Exactly.
Acorn milk you can milk it like a nipple though. Yeah. It looks like a
breast. Yeah it does look like a humongous breast. A big wooden breast that a pirate woman would have.
A pirate woman with two giant acorn breasts. Yeah. Oh my gosh she's so beautiful.
A comment on Viagra says I fell out of my chair and died of laughter thinking
about Viagra ice cream. Yeah and then he landed on his rock-hard penis. Yeah and snapped it
in half. Yeah. Who is this? Xolthar? From Big. Xerathor. What are you saying? Says tastes
good. Xerathor. Number four is blood. That disgusts me. The very thought of this makes
me want to brush my pants. This run of four comments is really good. I kind of want to
try this for a weird reason. When I was a kid I tried my blood one day and I kind of
I found out what vampires like about it and the last one I like blood and I'm
not joking.
You ever do you have a vampire kid at your school? Absolutely yeah, yeah, man,
we had a kid who drank someone's blood in the bathroom. This comment way this
comes is so yummy. Jeffrey D. Mar
Jeffrey D. Marry D. Mar. So is this vampires favorite ice cream flavor and
then someone responds and says I'm dying with laughter.
well that's a scary comment yeah oh my god dying more like I'm left there with
laughter laughter is the name of a vampire yeah laughter the Dracula take
your mic away from your face when you chew you're literally the same as
Patrick don't ever say that I knew that would get you what's wrong with me it's
just Caleb doesn't like it I don't I don't know why he doesn't like about
them just with food you guys are both bad with food I never eat it is my first
some every yeah but when you do it you eat it right in the mic because you don't
think about it you guys need to be more conscientious you need to be more
respectful when we're going to be suck up suck up my balls you pussy I can't
wait to bury you dude I'm gonna what's next I'm gonna bury you dig into you
list your ass okay number five tickle my way up in you tickle me Cameron I'm gonna
tickle you to death because you ask for it no yeah I would not ask for that you
would you would you would walk around the mall asking people to tickle you till
you die I'm gonna wriggle up you like an eel no you won't and I'm gonna die in
there you know I'm gonna smell awful and you won't be able to get me out I'm too
big I'll get stumped you know hold on tight mm-hmm taller than you you're
gonna have to make some room for me yeah can you you're gonna have to make some
room for me inside of you because I'm a gun there and die yeah cuz tomorrow I'm
gonna call up in you and I'm gonna die I'm gonna crawl in your ass and die and
And that's facts.
And that's facts, B.
The next one is cabbage.
Cabbage flavored, I'd eat it.
I love cabbage.
Cabbage is pretty good.
I like that cabbage, when you leave it out, it smells like shit.
That is so fun.
It's such a funny vegetable.
Vegetables have various, like onions, they have the stick.
Oh, kale?
Kale smells like a dumpster.
Yeah.
You leave kale out, it smells like that dumpster out there.
From what I understand, that's like a defense mechanism that they have when they're being
like, like that's why onions make you cry.
Well, that's because you're breaking the cells.
Yeah, but it's like part of, it's that, it developed as like basically a defense mechanism.
That's why you have to cut it while it's attached like the root part.
And like cabbage, if it starts to get too warm or whatever, it just starts to smell
like dog shit.
Yeah, it's like Irish people boil it.
Yeah.
Because they love the smell.
Because they love that smell, dude.
Every corned beef and cabbage though, that's a combo that can't be beat.
You're so stupid.
We're talking about ice cream.
Did you guys get every ice cream place nearby emailed me and said, "We now have e-gift cards."
Like the exact same email.
What?
Why do you have so many ice cream places?
I don't know.
Why do they have your email?
It was like two or three, I think.
But it was like the same global ice cream.
You signed up for the Global Ice Cream Registry.
It was so weird because I don't know how.
Oh, you know, I bet I logged onto their Wi-Fi before.
That's probably what it is.
Oh.
- No, no, you were at an ice cream shop long enough
that you logged onto their wifi?
- Yeah.
- Cameron went to ice cream--
- You a baby for real, bro.
- Cameron went to icecream.com and put in his email.
(laughing)
- Stay up to date on the newest flavors.
- Cameron went to Moose Tracks.
- I like the newest flavors.
- MooseTracks.org.
- Yeah.
- Because he wanted to find out all the places
that had Moose Tracks.
Is that a local ice cream?
- Moose Tracks, I think that's a thing.
- No, I think that's just a flavor of ice cream.
- Yeah, no, that's like--
- I thought that was local to like New England.
or I thought it was like a New Hampshire flavor
'cause of all the mousse.
- No, I think it's just a thing.
- What about chocolate?
- Yeah, chocolate's a Texas thing.
- Yeah.
- No.
- What about Rocky Road?
That's only from that one Rocky Road.
- Okay, I feel like Rocky Road is what people,
like I thought for a long time
that Rocky Road was like a West Coast version of Moose Tracks.
- No, two different ice creams.
- Really?
What's in Rocky Road?
- Rocky Road is, wait, what's Moose Tracks?
Moose tracks is like peanut butter and like chocolate. Yeah, no, rocky road is like
chocolate ice cream with like vanilla like almost like
Like cream stuff in it and then like pecans or something filled with cream
It's like a there's a nut in it you pump cream into only knew about rocky road because of the weird out song
Is an owl so there's an owl song
Wait, I want to get to the next one is really good. I want to get to it. Next number six is breast milk
- They make, there's definitely--
- Well yeah, the comments say,
this flavor actually exists.
I would love to try this one day.
(laughing)
- From what I understand, it tastes like stinky shit.
- I really like this comment that says,
"What?
"That's crazy.
"The only people who like it is babies."
(laughing)
- Babies is capitalized.
- Yeah, and spelled B-A-B-Y-S.
- Babies.
- I wonder what breast milk tastes like.
I almost tasted it before.
- No, you tasted it before,
you just don't remember, bitch.
my friend tried it on france
at a state fair in wisconsin come get your ice cream made from breast milk from our
cows turns out he was saying fresh milk
i do understand that there is
that they do sell breast milk and breast milk ice cream i just wonder
how it is harvested and like how much of these women being paid is it like a
donation thing i think maybe they're making it
for their baby
no but yeah but what is the process like do they like put their their hat on from
the walk out the door with a suitcase and walk into like a factory and get
plugged up like a cow no they put their boob in the freezer they put they put
their boob and there's two holes cut into the freezer and they just have to
go and stand in it for a while in it for like an hour and then it freezes all the
breast milk and then they just kind of squish it like they squish it out like a
soft-serve machine. That's not a bad idea. Again it's a small hole so you got to
wait a long time. Yeah it takes so long. Half of it's already melted by the
time you're done. Yeah see I just don't I just am interested in the logistics of
oh my god Vice should do a video about that. Yeah. That would crush. It's like I'll do it.
These women are changing the breast milk ice cream industry. You know what if somebody has to be the
journalist who goes around to all the breast milk places and watches, I'll do it.
No you won't. I'll go and I'll watch all the breasts. No you won't. Yeah I will. All the hot
mommies. That's what's so hot about a pregnant woman is it's like a third boob.
It's like a third giant boob. A third boob with a guy in it. Oh my god. The only thing better than a
normal boob without a guy is a third one with no nipple and a hole instead and a
guy's inside yeah yeah guys inside the other ones and we just didn't know
little guys oh my god and when you and breast milk is there this is something
for their come and it's two milkmen yeah and they're pouring out a glass they're
pouring their come out of a glass into the tip it's not even come it's just no
it is man it's milk they get from the milkman factory how does it get into the
So yeah, how does it get into the girl?
Think about it.
When you make milk, the girls make milk because the guy made milk into the girl.
No, they get a shipment.
The same milk comes up and out of the breast.
They get a shipment every week from the magic school bus, which goes inside of the girls.
Which drops off the milkman, yeah, and he pours the milk out into the kid.
We have come up with one of what could be...
This is the system.
This could be a great Disney ride.
This would be the great system.
This is the new Pixar movie.
Yeah.
John Lasseter, you weird pervert. I know you want to jump on this right away.
Yeah, I would like to go into the Magic School Bus. Actually, I want to go into a cool Magic
School Bus style Ferrari and go and check out Ms. Frizzle's flaps down there. You know what
I mean? I want to drive around them like a Formula One track just over and over again,
you know? And then I want to get air on her giant clit.
I want to jump it like the Grand Canyon. I want to jump her pussy like the Grand Canyon
in the Magic School Bus.
Do a flip.
Yeah.
Oh no, I fell in. Oh no.
You have to get me with your fingers. If you can catch me.
And then I'm running around her vagina as she tries to catch me with her pinky.
Yeah, that's disgusting.
And she kills you by accident.
Yeah, and that kid, I'm Arnold right now.
That's who I am.
You're what, the one who isn't fun?
You are home, dude.
I'm the lizard.
Arnold says we should have stayed home today.
You are home.
You can't be Arnold.
Pick a different one.
Be seen.
Patrick is Carlos.
Mencia.
Yeah.
Do-da-da.
Remember that, when he would say that?
He would say do-da-da.
Do-da-da.
Remember the do-da-da song?
Oh, I remember every single case.
If you are a D, please don't marry a D. Follow the genetics and you'll see.
kids will be D to D's. Oh my god what a genius dude. That's so smart. Yeah he's
smart he's a smart guy dude. Yeah. Carlos Mencil. Yeah he's so smart he his brain
just couldn't think. What was his real name like Chuck? His name was Ned Arnell.
Ned Arnell. Whoa. Ned. That's awesome. I know I know so much about Carlos Mencil. He was my favorite comedian when I was 9.
The video where Joe Rogan goes on stage at the Comedy Store. That video broke my heart. He's so funny. That video broke my
- Have you seen that? - When I was 11 years old?
- Carlos Mencia was on stage and Joe Rogan,
in the middle of a show at the Comedy Store,
goes on stage because Carlos stole the joke.
And he's like, "You stole this joke!
"Like you stole this joke from a guy in the audience
"right over there!"
And Carlos is just like, "You're a loser, man!
"Everybody in the audience loves me, bro!"
And then like two weeks later his show got canceled.
- Yeah.
- Dude, that video--
- I remember the radio interview thing where he steals,
he, you know what I'm talking about?
the Bill Cosby bit? No, I don't know.
Oh no, that was in a WTF episode?
Where he like makes everything up?
No, there's a video where he calls into something
and he says a joke
and then he hangs up and the person
on the radio show or whatever is like, "That was my joke."
[laughter]
Maybe it wasn't Carl, there was some joke
one some joke stealing comedian who did that.
I'm pretty sure it was him. His episode of WTF
he goes on the first episode
and just tells like a bunch of lies
about like not stealing jokes
because Mark Maron asked him about it and then Mark Maron released another
episode like a week later that was like the guy who used to open for Carlos
Mencia who there and they just talked the entire time about how he's like a
pathological liar yeah and just like can't tell the truth and like is this
stole like jokes from him the entire time he was opening for him and then
Carlos Mencia comes on again and he's like yeah man I stole all the jokes it's
so funny we have a bunch of patrons yeah we save them like do you like for a woman
then like no they subscribe we should do it yeah no I know I know but we're
marathon recording today it's okay we just know that for the next couple of
episodes we probably won't say anybody's name well that's what I'm saying should
we just do well no yeah you know it doesn't really matter yeah all right all
right so our first patron shout out to Carlos Mencia oh no and net Arnell yeah
Alec Nannerb. Thank you. I think that sounds familiar. This is two pretty hard
names back-to-back. Yeah. Alec and Bowser.
Buldasar Peck. Buldasar Peck. Peck? Thank you. Owen Aldret. What's up, Owen?
thank you um matthias august anderson thank you uh thank you um madeline busby thank you madeline
um ben snape well he should not be mentioned yeah uh yeah you know what ben snape we can't say your
name i take that back thank you back um owen thank you dj i hope thank you dj the dj the dj
from the skating rink. DJ from the house it's full. Jack Cates. Shout out to Jack. Dennis Campbell.
Shout out to Dennis. Love Dennis. Matthew Bradley. Thank you. Oh Patches. Patches aloha.
Thank you. We shouted you out. Three friends here at the end. Yeah. Maraid. Maraid Ganley.
Never met you but you added me on Facebook. She's the boss. Shout out to Maraid. Yeah and Thomas.
We love Thomas. Thomas. We're gonna have Thomas back on soon. Yeah. Is that Thomas? Yeah.
Okay. Hey. I don't know his name without a zero in it. But it is. Yeah. If your name had a zero
in it, I would recognize it. Yeah. Sorry, bitch. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. All right. Thanks, guys.
Should we just continue the list? No. All right. Bye. That would be pretty fun.