You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- All right.
- It's actually been a couple minutes
since we stopped recording the last one,
so I did have to remember,
we're talking about VeggieTales.
- Yeah, we're talking about VeggieTales.
- Kick it off.
- We gotta talk about--
- If you listened to the last premium,
we ended on about VeggieTales.
And if you didn't listen to it, you should subscribe.
- Yeah, it really is like,
these four episodes we record today will...
- It's kind of a saga.
- You have to listen to them all in a row
or else you lose it.
- It's kind of like when you listen to the album version
of an Eminem song and then there's a skit before it
that cross-fades into the song.
And then you get the last couple seconds of the skit.
- Yeah, like Paul.
- Yeah, and then you're like, "Ngh!"
- And then the song starts.
- Yeah, and then you're like, "Oh, I wonder what that's from."
And then it makes sense when you listen to the skit.
- Basically, you're--
- That's what you gotta do
If you're not a Patreon subscriber, it's like watching the second and fourth Harry
Potters and not the first and third.
It's like watching Harry Potter.
You're going to be like, "What the hell?
Hermione got hot too fast."
It's like watching Harry Potter but with your one eye closed.
Yeah.
Impossible to understand.
So we were talking about VeggieTales.
There was a character in Jonah, a VeggieTales movie.
Did you guys watch just the movies or did you watch the show?
I've seen basically every thing. I've seen most of the episodes.
I think I saw all of it but didn't see the movies.
You didn't see the Jonah movie?
I don't think I saw the Jonah movie.
You didn't see the Pirates?
I saw the one with the walls of Jericho.
Pirates Who Don't Do Anything?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I saw that.
I heard the song for that one.
You didn't see the movie though?
I saw Larry Boy and the Pirates Who Don't Do Anything.
I had the Larry Boy car, the action figure.
You had a car?
Yeah.
Pirates Who Don't Do Anything was basically like the night at the Roxbury of Larry Boy.
or of VeggieTales where like it was a sketch on VeggieTales and then they
kicked it off into a movie yeah yeah oh then I saw the sketch yeah you've
definitely seen yeah I saw the sketch but the only movie I saw was Larry Boy and
the Big Fib. Pirates Who Don't Do Anything was the first the first
VeggieTales like thing that was not about God. Oh Larry Boy and the rumor weed.
Oh rumor weed is a really good one yeah and I had the action figure
of Larry boy he in his car yeah I wanted to fuck the girl squash mm-hmm every
movie that I ever watched growing up I wanted to have sex with something in the
movie yeah I brave little toaster the toast is toaster this might be the one
that I finding Nemo the Nemo oh shit I had this - no I wanted to fuck in finding
Nemo I wanted to fuck the head starfish this toy oh yeah I had that - yeah and
and pull up the character you're reading about ok hold i gotta find the car that i
had
yes if i miss car
there are a lot of people find it was good to have to do what i had nice
actually i had a lot of had a lot of edgy tales toys when i was a kid
i had no idea had anything to do with god
yeah i don't know is a god thing either when i was a kid yeah i thought it was
just like all these you know that i are you know some that's like keep walking
yeah but you want to know that's a little rock that's that's about them
finding... Yeah, that's the Walls of Jericho. Yeah. Oh yeah, yeah. And the peas are the...
Oh so... French peas. So, there was a character, I never saw it, I just remember seeing him
on the DVD cover, but there was a character named Khalil. Yeah. And Jonah. He's from Jonah,
yeah. He's the... He's a little blue worm with a turban. And a big thick mustache. I love
him, dude. And then he says, "Hello, my friend." Yeah, he says my friend a lot. It says his
appeared Khalil has an Indian accent he is a blue caterpillar just I love
something I love about that Jonah movie is like he finds Sodom and Gomorrah and
there like yeah that's the it's a story of Jonah so he finds Sodom and Gomorrah
and he goes and they're like like everybody there basically their analog
for like gay sex because that's the whole thing yeah the Bible is like
Sodom and Gomorrah, they love drinking slushies.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- They love slushies.
They love purple slushies and they suck on 'em.
And it's just a bunch of peas running around
sucking on slushies.
- God damn, dude.
- And so they get killed for that?
- Yeah, well I don't actually remember what he does,
I don't think they, oh no, yeah, the place explodes.
Yeah, God explodes it.
God fucking goes Nagasaki on the place
where they have too many slushies
and they like candy too much.
- Oh my God. - It rocks, dude.
- There's a piece of trivia here, though,
for Khalil from VeggieTales.
- Also, funny that he, that's like the only name
in that entire show that is not like--
- Yeah, it's not Larry. - Whatever the vegetable.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's like there's a worm-- - Khalil Da Worm.
- Yeah, Khalil, the only person with a vaguely--
- It's Jamal Da Worm's brother.
- A vaguely Middle Eastern name, they make a worm.
(all laughing)
Well so here's a piece of trivia. Oh my God. With a giant nose by the way.
Look at this fucking. Yeah. These JPEGs are awful. But.
He's a worm with a big giant. He looks like Big Dave. Let him read the tr...
Let him read the tr... Let him read the trivia. It says here due to his
ethnicity an online review for Jonah a VeggieTales movie went as far as
pointing out the fact that Khalil's involvement in the film was written
9/11. Just imagine his point. Because Khalil is the one who's like God, because he's, Jonah's like I
can't like I don't care about going to to Sodom and Gomorrah and Khalil's like no
God has to destroy it. And then he blows it up. Okay so there's there's a picture here of K.Lil. Yeah who's
rap Khalil. Yeah but then there is one of salesman Khalil which is somebody just
went into Microsoft Paint and made him orange. Damn. Also worms don't have legs.
Yeah. Caterpillar. But why is he a worm? He's a caterpillar. Oh. Khalil the worm.
Khalil the caterpillar and Jamal the worm. Yeah. Brothers and best friends. And
enemies. And best enemies. Yeah best enemies. Yeah. Rivals, competitors, and best
lovers and when your idols become your rivals when you fuck each other in a
circle greater than greater than greater than sign uh-huh when your brother is
also your rival when your brother is also your wife when your brother and
wife are the same person your brother is also this is how I'm trying to be your
brother's your wife your brother's your wife and your mom and you go to the
school and all your family members are one person in the carriage yeah yeah
when you get to sit in the racecar carriage and you get to fuck your
boyfriend this is how I'm trying to be spring break forever and your mom lets
you ride in shotgun in the car yep and you smoke a blunt with your dog no you
don't fucking you smoke a blunt with your dog you ever hang out with someone
who smoked weed at their dog my mom I think so but not not off the top of my
head I definitely remember seeing like that someone I hung out with and then
like yeah yeah yeah I remember seeing somebody who used to just blow weed smoke
in their dog's face and then I just stopped hanging out with what I the way
do it is you have to blow it perfectly into a bone and then they'll eat it.
Bone clout. And they can't help themselves, dude. They go cuckoo for bones.
Yeah. No, but it's just so funny like seeing that dog just how like I was like
oh this is like the calmest like chillest dog I've ever seen and then
like two weeks later seeing them just blow weed smoke in the dog's face.
It's like brain damage. To be like oh yeah no they're just
making them sick. Yeah. Yeah, weed is not good for dogs. No, it's not.
It makes dogs like depressed. Yeah, I feel like dogs are every dog. I know is depressed. That's true. My dog is not depressed
She's uh anxious. She's uh, yeah
My dog has been like fucking inbreeding
Animals forever and we're like surprised that they have like all the anxiety and cancer. No, i'm not surprised
My dog really is just a fucking idiot. My parents. Yeah, they're all I mean, they're all dude. He's awesome. He's a golden doodle
He's stupid as shit. He's the happiest dog in the world.
Golden Retrievers, they just built like the biggest stupidest dog they could.
It is funny, these dogs are just retarded wolves.
Yeah, a million percent.
They're like, yeah.
Yeah, they're just like not smart enough to kill us.
Yeah.
Like they never...
Except for Pitbulls.
Pitbulls are smart and strong. That's why they're dangerous.
Dude, I used to have a Pitbull.
I love Pitbulls. That's like my favorite kind of dog.
We had to give her away, but like she like...
The girl ones are horny.
Dude, yeah.
Yeah, man.
She used to like...
She was like a fucking meatball.
Yeah, I used to wake up and...
She was like a, like, she was so huge and like her leg, like...
She was a meatball?
Yeah.
I thought she was a doll.
She was, no, she was like...
She's bulbous.
Dude, she was buff as shit and it was just so hard because she was, every time she saw
me was like, she was too excited to see me.
Oh yeah.
You live with a female pit bull, you wake up every day, it's sitting on your face trying
to get you to eat its pussy.
That's how horny the dog is.
Yeah.
Some people wake up to their dog licking them.
you wake up to it and you're like a dog. It's a different pair of legs. Oh my god. Sorry. I had a dream. I was eating ravioli and I woke up.
I woke up and I was eating my dog's pussy.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
That's disgusting. That is disgusting.
It's cheesy.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
dream I was in the finest Italian restaurant. I woke up and it still tastes exactly like ravioli.
Fido, what are you doing? A girl dog. Fido. Come on. Fido's a, Fido's a gin. I can't,
what's a girl dog name? I don't even know. Rose? Sarah. Sarah. Mrs. Jennifer. Mrs. She's All That.
Mrs. Fido. This is my dog, Mrs. She's All That. Fidoette. A-L-L-Z-That. Fido. Fidecio. Fidecio.
- Medea. - Fidecio.
(laughing)
- Here's my pit bull named Medea.
I wake up every morning to her
sticking her giant pussy on my face.
- Jesus.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's how they kill you, dude.
That's how they're dangerous.
And their bred,
their male ones are fighters,
but the girl ones are fuckers, dude.
(laughing)
They'll get you.
- They will get you, dude.
That is always funny when like a female dog
will like hump you.
Mm-hmm. You're so you fucking idiot the girl ones have lesbian competitions and underground rings they do
Yeah, but you're like yeah, but like that's a boy lesbians
Dogs fuck each other. That's what Michael Vick thought he was doing. Yeah. Yeah, you know you just have my dog is the stinkiest
squanch
Drop it on your dog and kill it
What a way to start an episode.
Yeah, my dog and her poison pussy will
Will win. She's a prize fighter
I don't want to talk about this anymore. It's funny
Dude it's so gross. What dog pussy? Yeah, why? What's the problem with that? Pussy's pussy man
Like Snoop Dogg says, "Pussy is pussy, and baby, you're pussy for life."
He says that?
He says that in A-Kon, "I Wanna Fuck You."
That's the end of his verses.
He says, "Cause pussy is pussy, and baby, you're pussy for life."
It's so funny finding out that song was called "I Wanna Fuck You."
That is a song where it comes on the radio and you're like, "That sounds normal."
But then if you try to listen to it on Spotify or whatever, just the "I Wanna Fuck You" version
comes up and it sounds insane. It sounds like a Rucka Rucka Ali version.
Yeah, it sounds like a parody.
Yeah.
I wanna fuck you? What a terrible hook.
I wanna fuck you.
That's like when they changed Let's Get It Started.
I wanna love you.
That's like when they changed Let's Get Retarded to Let's Get It Started.
Yeah, it's like you go back.
Yeah, I remember hearing that the old version for the first time and just being like, what
the fuck?
Yeah, it was an SSX Tricky.
I remember it was on my parents.
Like the original.
the original version was on my parents iPod and I was like what are they
listening to? What is this? Dude it's so the fucking the line he says before "get stupid"
yeah that's so fucking crazy yeah get stupid wear a helmet live at home with your parents till
you're 50 die young damn yeah dude oh man it's so it's so funny the only reason
that they changed the lyrics was because the NBA wanted to use it in their
commercials yeah yeah they would if the NBA didn't want to use that song that's
the only version of the song. There would be no Shakira. Yeah. Or not Shakira. There'd be no Fergie.
Shakira O'Neal.
Basketball don't lie.
- Ball don't lie, Shakiro and you know.
- Oh, maybe when you hoop like that,
you make Will Chamberlain go mad.
- Whoa!
- And then it still has Wyclef on it,
but his name is Wyclef Basketball.
(laughing)
- Wyclef Basketball shorts instead of Wyclef jeans.
- Oh, that's good.
- Wow.
- You know, didn't Wyclef like steal all the money
from Haiti?
- Yeah.
- That's a fucking boss move, dude.
I'm gonna dunk a basketball into his asshole.
Who was the third guy in the Fugees?
It was Lauryn Hill, Wyclef, and then the other guy, and he had the song from Bullworth.
It's a song from Bullworth, and Old Dirty Bastard has a feature.
We've talked about Bullworth and just how fucking stupid that is.
Yeah, we did talk about Bullworth already.
Do you remember when Nas had The Firm?
No.
Which was like his version of the Fugees.
The Firm was a skateboard company.
That's all I know.
The firm was like, it was him and a girl and a guy, and another guy, and they were just
pretending to be the Fugees for a while.
Fugees rocks, man.
Yeah, Fugees are good.
Yeah, that one Fugees album is really good.
But yeah, I don't know who the other guy is that isn't Wyclef.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's probably Black Eyed Peas.
He had the song in the...
It's Apple D. App from the Black Eyed Peas.
Yeah.
But the whole song is about him being president and then ODB's verse is just like him just
being ODB.
I love that Black Eyed Peas is just, it's Fergie, what's his name?
Will.i.am.
Will.i.am and then like two robots.
Taboo and Apple the App.
Yeah, it's one of the twins from the Matrix.
It's the dark version of the Matrix.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fucking rocks man.
They make good music man.
I got a feeling, such a great music video.
The idea that time would stop.
I have to feeling.
I have to feel you.
That was the original one.
Yeah.
The original one was I am retarded.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, just every Black Eyed Peas song.
They bring it in every single time.
The record producer's like, can we just not--
Why do you guys keep writing that?
It's funny.
Look, we made parody songs before you put us in commercials,
all right?
(laughing)
- We just wanted, we wanted to have our own My Bologna.
We wanted to have our own Eat It.
That's why we're called the Black Eyed Peas.
We wanna write food-based parody songs.
(laughing)
- Yeah, they were like the Lonely Island at first,
but just all their stuff was, yeah.
- Gotta get that poop, poop, poop.
- Yeah.
- That poop, poop, crap.
- They had a--
- I got that down, Sandra.
(laughing)
Yeah, "Where is the love" was originally "Where is the bud" and it was a Smoker's Anthem.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That one's not true.
"Where is the cud" and it's about a cow's tongue.
Yeah, it's about a cow's tongue.
Yeah.
"Where is the cud, moo-oo-oo-oo."
That was how this song went.
That's such a funny idea.
Just every Black Eyed Peas song is just ableist before it hits the radio.
Yeah.
Mm.
Ooh.
Ah.
2000 and late my IQ is 8. You're so developmentally late. Oh that's good.
Yeah. There you go. I can't remember is this a, are we doing a list on this? Yeah we're
doing a list on this. Should I pull it up? Yeah. You just have Nickelback How You Remind Me
Up right now. Just play that. Let's listen to that for the rest of the episode.
♪ You remind me of who is under my house ♪
♪ You remind me of my cousin and my uncle ♪
♪ You remind me of all my best friends now ♪
- That's a song about you guys.
♪ All my best friends ♪
- Yeah.
- What was this one?
- Someone said this in the Discord, let me figure out.
- I'll say it, I've said it before, I'll say it again.
Join the Discord, come hang out.
We're doing, during, since everybody's locked in their house,
we're doing game nights, we're playing Jackbox.
'Cause Jackbox, it never gets old.
It gets only gets new. There's a Minecraft server where me and Cameron and Patrick have a tent.
I don't have Minecraft on my computer. There's a big Spongebob.
There's uh you know if whenever they just do a little bit of a cop it sounds it sounds like
the guns on that. Yeah it sounds like a laser beam. It sounds like the Naboo guns. You know the ones
the ones where she uh it shoots the balls. Padme pulls them out of the the chair that she has hidden.
Yeah, what a girl boss padman. What is it? Why did they shoot did they shoot boogers at the
No, they just had green bullets. No those big balls
Oh the the gun thing of job of the hut the gun gun guns. Yeah, the gun gun guns
They shot it was like an electro ball
It looked like a booger to me
This was list, but I have a dirty mind. This list was sent by mumble crap and the discord crap. What's up, baby?
Thanks mumble. Yeah, we do. We have a channel where you can just send lists and we'll send them to we're picking stuff from that
Yeah, you don't have to do the work anymore. You work for us you pigs. It's so hard to
find a list. We did use up a lot of stuff. We've been doing this for a while. Dude, I
wonder if we're going to hit 100 while we're in quarantine. Fuck, I hope not. Oh dude,
if we don't have anything planned. By the time this comes out it'll be 95. I don't think 95 yet.
Maybe. Yeah, I think our last one was 91. Yeah, our last one was 91. I'll fly up for the 100.
if this last one was 90, what happened to this one?
Don't fly up.
I'll fly up.
Drive up. Don't fly up.
It's way more expensive to drive.
Yeah, it's way more expensive to drive, but you have less risk of getting Corona.
I don't care. I'm badass.
I'm not gonna do it with you if you get on a plane.
I'm the Terminator.
I'm the Determinator. I determine who has Corona.
Yeah.
Corona. Corona. You guys both have it.
You just pointed behind me.
Yeah, there's a guy behind you who's about to infect you. Look out.
Oh, it's you. Oh, no.
This one is top 10 things to sell in school.
No, we don't.
You have a cat.
Get the fucking cat off the mic now.
He's got some stuff to say.
Oh, the cat's purring away.
He's purring into the mic.
He stopped.
You made him stop.
We should get a dog.
We should get a podcast dog that lives in the internet.
Let's get a virtual dog.
We could get one of those little ones that do backflips.
Oh, it's purring.
It. He has a name. Yeah, what's his name? Leonard.
Fucking bitch. I've not called him Leonard like since I got him. I like him more if I call him Leonard.
Yeah. The fact that you gave him like an eight-year-old's name for an animal. Well, no, because he's a fuck. Puts me off.
They're both fuckers.
I just, you know. An eight-year-old wouldn't be allowed to name its pet fucker. Call it the fudger.
Call him super my dog when we adopted her her original name was fudge
I feel like that I'd name a dog fudge. I'd laugh at it for a day, and then I'd be like yeah
Can you imagine a call foot yeah yelling that across the playground?
My dad when I like my childhood dog
I was named amigo and the way that he named the dog was like he was gonna open up. He's opened up like a
Dictionary to pay he opened up a Spanish to English dictionary and just like it was like I'm gonna do cuz that's how he named me
My name there's was he just opened up the Bible and like picked a random page. Oh my god
I landed on Caleb Josh and Levi and
He was like, I'm gonna do the same thing for the dog
But in Spanish, but the first one that he landed on was like Spanish for lunch
The Spanish word for pedophile
Yeah, yes, I have my dog's name is burrito. My dog's name is El pedophilio. Yeah
Yeah, it's really obvious - yeah
Yeah, it's just one of those words where they L kitty did one of those words were Spain Spanish people
They just didn't me try El Rapisto
Rapisto all right, so these are things to sell in school. Yeah, it's a number one knifes
Knifes yeah knives that shit. I'm
Called the freaking grammar police. I tried to be a knife kid for a little bit, but they're so
If you buy a knife you to bring your parent cuz like a pawn shop won't sell it to you
I had a listen to this comment real quick
If you haven't sold a knife or had one sold to you by your sophomore year
Then you're probably the same kind of person who wears overalls
You guys wear overalls in high school? No. You guys were overalls kids? You probably were, right? Oh, I did. I knew it.
Yeah, I didn't. Yeah, no, I would I wore like a
I wore like PacSun. All I wore. Yeah, I was like a New Balance. Yeah. All I wore was like
Converse and Dickies and overalls and shit. Yeah, I was just a whatever was at the top of my drawer and then New Balance sneakers.
I was like graphic tees and like and like skinny
chinos until me and Janice started dating and she made me dress like a like a gay
guy mm-hmm and here I am. I yeah I've praised I've dressed the same my whole
like since I turned 16. You have a good style going on though you know you you
like skating makes you like people like people care about like clothes
that's true like I just was like I care about pants more than I think I should
everyone that I knew just like runescape and so we I just would wear like a like
a vulcan t-shirt. I know a good pair of pants. What do you got? I like these ones. Oh these
Dickies, the Dickies double knee. They look like Shrek's pants. But you know, I like them.
You know the texture of Shrek's pants? You know he has like scales on his pants? It just
sticks in my head. It's like snake skin. Yeah when I imagine Shrek I just think about the
texture of his clothing. That's one of the first things that sticks out to me in my mind.
I'm going to stitch these back together. I'm going to stitch you back together. I'm going
stitch your asshole shut you're gonna try poop go up like a balloon pop yeah I'm
gonna see ever peeing a balloon and throw it at someone no no but I made homemade
stink bombs with my friend and we should put our shit in them and then piss in
them I did that I just like this is from now we're at it and then we threw him at
a school I did it with all we can not shit piss and not shit yeah they're
terrible stink bombs I don't I mean just like I mean it's just a gross liquid
yeah but like it won't it doesn't like make everything smell bad yeah we just
- He just threw it at the windows of his school one day,
like on a Sunday, 'cause he lived in like,
there's like a wood barrier of forest
between his school and his backyard.
So we just spent all day making these stinky stink bombs,
I mean just shit and piss in a bag.
- Yeah. - And just threw it
at his school.
- That's pretty sick.
- Yeah, man.
- I did that in Montana.
I don't remember what we did with it.
- Now he's a fisherman.
- I went to Montana, I'm in Montana.
I've been to Montana a lot. - He's a fisherman?
he's a fisherman i was a kid
fishing is fuckin sick right now that we should do it
yet did you guys should have come fishing with me and ryan was at work
so yeah
you're at work and that no excuse camera could've come camera hates and i don't
remember what i was doing that over your doing as it were and i would love to go
fishing
i'm not fishing in the carter park
didn't isn't what's his name good i think i i think i was just sick and i
think i'm feeling very sick
when you went fishing I think I rested.
Because I know we were...
Oh yeah, we were waiting for the Thanos copter to charge.
Because I remember that weekend we just ate like utter shit.
Oh yeah, I was on my food tour.
On my highway food tour.
Cameron has a weak body.
I do have a weak stomach.
Cameron eating Jollibee was the worst thing he could have ever done.
Yeah.
It did ruin me.
I mean I don't eat healthy but I don't eat like that crazy.
I don't eat fried chicken or anything.
I was prepared for that.
Yeah, yeah.
Patrick was eating lead for two weeks, just a stomach lining.
Yeah.
I mean, but also, again, as we said, I guess at this point, a week and a half ago or whatever,
that Patrick, you've eaten so much crazy shit in your life that you're just immune, dude.
Yeah, I feel like-
But when I do get sick, I fuck up.
I feel like if I shot a bullet at you, your body would absorb it like T2.
No, I should get killed by a bullet, but if you tried to poison my food, I would survive.
Yeah.
King.
Yep.
Like a king.
Like an unkillable king.
Kings, the whole point is they don't survive, that's why they have the poison tester.
No, the kings survive.
The poison tester is King Koopa.
King Koopa never got poisoned.
He did.
No, we should get that fat fuck.
What did he get poisoned by?
Mario's fists.
Pfft.
Not a poison.
And his fire.
Alright, we didn't even talk about knives.
I'm gonna go fuck about knives.
This is a great idea so we can kill the teacher or commit suicide.
side. Whoa. 31 upvotes. Yeah. Dude, I tried, I had a knife for a little bit but then it
got, you know like when a salt lamp gets sweaty? No. No. If it gets too humid in a
room a salt lamp start like. Melting sort of. Yeah, melting a little bit and my knife
was next to my salt lamp and it rusted shut. Oh damn. Yeah. That sucks. My knife
that said dad on it yeah I've had a I used to have a night you to buy a knife I
inspired yeah that was yeah make me buy a knife yeah do you still keep it on you
no no you saw I kept it on me for a while because there's a bottle opener -
true damn yeah that's up yeah then I stopped I couldn't I didn't like couldn't
bring it on a plane to LA or something yeah so I just it's in still my drawer
right now I should probably start carrying it again it's nice to have a
a knife on you. My older brother used to have, he had butterfly knives.
That's sick. That's dumb. I think Dom used to be able to do tricks with butterfly knives.
What? That shit's so awesome. It's funny that you just fucking chop your fingers off.
Yeah. Like Spy from TF2. Yeah exactly like Spy from TF2. I saw that in that game and
And then the next day I looked up butterfly knife prices.
Listen to this comment.
"I want knives so we can do whatever we want and threaten the teachers to do things for
us.
Also so we can bring protection from people who break into our school, but mainly the
first thing about threatening the teachers."
This is a horrible idea.
Please add real items since I would love to actually sell items.
Thank you.
Hi.
Hi, welcome to my item shop. It's just a locker that says items.
My school item shop. Would you like a potion?
I have a potion. It is equal parts.
We as a young nation need to overthrow the teachers.
God, every time you cough.
Yeah, it's putting me on edge.
I know that this episode will age poorly when you are dead or...
I don't have it. I literally have not left the house.
Dude, you have it. My boner is pointing directly towards you.
Because you're gay?
Because it senses danger.
Yeah.
"Lol at all these hate comments. My dad in high school actually sell knives."
I like to think his dad currently, like, goes to the high school.
His dad sells knives.
The high school selling knives. Is he on your shoulder?
Yes. This one I like.
Yeah, he's...
Awesome. It's great. My friend always asks for a knife, but I don't have one.
I want knives so I can slip my fist and rub my blood in my enemy's faces. We
should do blood brothers. Yeah yeah breaking news murder attack in a school
breaking news murder attack in a school and that's the whole commercial
coming up a great artichoke dip for super bowl.
Yeah, this just in, food and snacks at the TV.
This just in, the teacher's lounge has no apples.
This just in, the girls bathroom doesn't have any urinals.
What the fuck? The teacher's apple had a worm.
More at 11. Back to you Chris.
What are you doing? I thought we were doing school news tonight.
Derek with the weather tonight an investigative report. Does the girl's
bathroom really have a couch in it
yeah yeah and then to you Derek with the weather Derek with the weather and
weather and he's like there's going to be snow forever and we have no more
school. Thanks Chris win
sounds good to me sounds like an epic win.
We're going to kill the teachers with the
knives. Never a good idea says anonymous. Honestly, I wish I knew about this
earlier knife is for ending people life.
That's a good chance. We can kill those haters other kids could kill you
Sausage lover 99. Add me on Xbox Brazil nut 72. That's such a good Xbox username.
Brazil nut 72. What was your guys' game tag? Can't wait to kill history tech.
I shared it with my little brother. Mine? It's still the same one I have on the
It's E Doran1234. So if you want to add me on Xbox Live, E Doran1234.
I think my Minecraft name, which was the only like, or like Steam, was Tenebrae Omega.
My Steam name is still Wargers. It's still my YouTube poopname.
My Xbox name is SpamXHavoc. That's pretty sick. I think my PlayStation name is CamFedder.
I don't know, it might not be. But I made that like a year ago, so that's why.
That's your name.
Yeah, that's my name.
Yeah, when you grow up, you stop.
My RuneScape name was Penny Picker.
Oh, yeah, he told us about that.
That's cool.
Because you were going to make that documentary.
No, that was different. No, Penny Picker, that was like a... Back in the day, that was
like a something, like a moshing move was the Penny Picker, and I thought it was cool.
In a couple of weeks, we will, Caleb will be making Chump Change.
It's coming to theaters near you. It'll come to your local. Michael Moore has backed it. Yeah. Yeah, Michael
Yeah, as long as I film the whole thing in Flint, then he's agreed to do it. Here's a comment
This idea is very shocking. I do see this happening in the near future if students keep being like this
Good luck teachers slash haters regards
If students keep being like this damn students be doing this students be do be like this
What's number two? Wait, wait one more
more ye because I would really love to walk into school with a M9 bayonet and
kill my business teacher she is a massive bitch.
Dude, that fucking rules. God damn dude. A bayonet. That's jumping like a level.
That is how nowadays that's how you get away with a mass shooting. Bring in a
gun that people would just assume you're doing show and tell with. Yeah. Like a
- Yeah, I just be like, oh, he's just.
- Imagine a kid just pulling up with a musket at school,
though.
- Yeah, that'd be sick.
- There was a kid at my school who tried to walk around,
or he tried to get it approved,
but he wanted to do a Nerf war for the senior prank,
and he set up like a whole rule system
of how the senior prank would work,
and then I just remember everybody in this,
like the seniors 2015 group just being like,
yeah, we don't wanna do this.
I was just like, oh man, he--
- What was the senior prank when you were here?
- Senior prank was, we had a rave in a classroom.
- Whoa, dude, that's insane.
- Yeah, well, they had to, there was apparently
a prank so bad at our school that they had
to approve our pranks.
- That's pretty funny.
- Whoa.
- So--
- Wait, what do you want?
- Prank approved.
- Number two--
- We had to get our pranks approved,
and then after the rave thing happened,
me and my friends just ran around the school
running into classrooms and yelling.
so that fucking rocks yeah number two is gum oh the gum kid at school the kid who
sold the gum I didn't sell gum I was a free gum guy yeah I never gave away gum
for I never sold gum I was not not business savvy yeah oh one of the top
comments is always make sure this is above any kind of weapons we have to get
this to the top but the top is vote this to the please vote this one a number one
number one I'm having a reflux dude you have it no yeah one of those those
little spheres got stuck in your in yours yeah have gas yeah you know the
spiky virus yeah it's like what is it what's that ball called that gets big
ball cunt is a tumor no the ball you know I've been scared that this has been
one of those got stuck you think you have a soft vocal cancer I'm a
- I'm a hypochondriac, I can't--
- One of us will get cancer.
- Yeah, it's probably gonna be me.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, again, I think you're probably immune
to everything but cancer at this point.
- Yeah, I don't think any of my older--
- Well, you smoked cigarettes since you were like 11, right?
- 12.
- Yeah.
- How much, what was your peak?
- Most cigarettes?
- Like in a day, how many were you smoking?
- Oh, I was like, before I quit,
it was like almost two packs a day.
- Whoa!
- No, it was almost like--
- That's old man numbers.
- Two packs every two days.
- To a pack a day.
(laughing)
- He's thinking.
- No, he's thinking, hold on.
- He's doing the math.
- Wait, no, no, no, no.
- No, two packs every two days, not a pack a day.
No, I did seven packs a week, not a pack a day.
- There was a point where it was like
a pack every other day.
I think that might have been my most.
but there was a week where i did smoke it
to how did you get it did with someone is not card you
or do you steal it from people uh... no my mom spokesman
policy just
so until i turned to come on the way turned eighteen
that's when i got that
because there is any good ideas
you five dollars in new hampshire
and i'm eighteen
so what else you can do exactly what i was a
they just sit in my room and play lord of the rings on gamecube and smoke six
- True, so you could smoke inside.
- Yeah.
- You had a Cigs inside house.
That's crazy, man.
- Yeah, I had a Cigs inside house.
- Fucking insane.
- Twice as much cancer.
- Oh my God, dude, Cigs inside.
- Secondhand smoke and Cigs inside.
- Yeah, that rocks.
- But I would play, I would sleep on a mattress on the floor
and I only had like, I had just shelves
that I put all my clothes on.
- Yeah.
- And I would just smoke Cigs
and play GameCube all summer.
- Damn.
- I wanna go back, dude.
- Absolutely boss, dude.
- Dude, I wanna go back.
- Absolutely, boss.
- This comment says, "If your school doesn't allow gum,
"go for it.
"Just try not to get caught or you're dead."
- Oh yeah, that was a--
- Gum was illegal in your school?
- I, so I--
- Death penalty?
- I used to chew gum 'cause I had a 504 plan,
which was like for kids with ADHD.
- Oh yeah, dude, I had a 504 too.
- Yeah, so I had a 504 plan.
Part of my 504 was I could chew gum during tests,
but my math teacher, seventh grade,
Mr. McCarthy went on paternity leave
so he could watch his kid,
and we had this substitute named Mrs. Williams.
Mrs. Williams was one of the worst women
I've ever met in my life.
Mrs. Williams accused me of,
'cause if you didn't do your homework
you had to get your mom to sign it,
she accused me of ripping the page out of my book
when I did the homework.
Dude, she was a fucking nutcase.
And then Mrs. Smith.
- And you were like, you better not cross me
I'm gonna go get the bayonet from my backpack yeah for her and mrs. her and
mrs. Smith did just said horrible things about me to my mom apparently but yeah
your child is a pedophile your child fucks a kid no but she I was chewing gum
during a test and then she just straight-up just said she didn't believe
me that it was in my 504 plan and I had believe Patrick believe Patrick let's get
it trending we need to get it trending right now for an incident that happened to me when
I was 12 years old yeah no but I had to I had to fight I had to fight like the teacher
I'd like fight the teacher yeah like Celebrity Deathmatch you and the teacher I wish oh my
god dude I hope she gets freaking I would love to get in the ring with Miley Cyrus
I would love to I would love to me versus Mrs. Williams I would like to knock her block off
Mrs. Williams if I see you it's on site if I see you I'm gonna knock your block off you
your weird bitch your weird jerry curl you had I'm gonna clean your clock you
weird tall white yeah I'm gonna suck your dick yeah yeah I'm gonna milk your cock
milk your cock like the udder that God made it yeah bitch you wore too many
rings mrs. Williams that was weird you wore too many rings and you had a weird
jerry curl sounds like a gypsy and it was so weird when you would belly dance in
class and take all of our wallets yeah and you put a hex on my friend yeah yeah
he got dragged to hell yeah yeah you know white I yeah yeah it's our you made
someone eat an apple and the seven dwarves yeah that's not a gypsy she's
not I was a witch she's a queen
I'll say it go go bordello yeah Queens isn't it Romani I don't give a fuck
talk about if you're if you're European, I can I can call you anything I want. I
heard such a dude. I heard Kurt Metzger. I was listening to White Precious, which
is like one of the best stand up albums ever, but he there's a point where he
calls Greek people diner monkeys and I've had that stuck in my diner monkey is the
greatest European slur. Yeah, yeah, I'm holding out. I'm holding on to that one.
for the first time I ever meet a Greek person.
(laughing)
Hey, what's up, you're a diner monkey.
- Going to Steve's kitchen down the street.
- Yeah, can I have a spanakopita,
double time, diner monkey?
(laughing)
Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Our brains are getting poopy.
- Yeah, read the--
- Getting poopy liquid brain.
- You have poopy liquid brain.
- Read the last comment, Caleb.
- A keefy.
- Okay, thanks.
(laughing)
- Number three.
- That was a Caleb kind of comment.
- A keefy.
- Slime.
- Yeah, number three, slime.
We sell some slime.
Kids just have different problems than we do.
There was slime, I'll say it, when I was growing up, slime didn't exist, man.
Yeah, we didn't do slime, we did Oobleck.
Oobleck.
What the fuck, man?
You remember doing Oobleck?
We did Oobleck in science class with my weird...
The book, the Oobleck book scared the fucking shit out of me when I was a kid.
The part when the Oobleck goes in his mouth...
There's an Oobleck book?
Yeah, it's a Dr. Seuss book.
You never read Oobleck?
No, I didn't know it was based off a Dr. Seuss book.
Okay, so it's based off a Dr. Seuss book...
I thought they were just trying to teach us about non-nutrient food.
there's a kingdom where i thought they were just trying to do some on
newtonian fluid.
There's a you fast talking hog shut up.
There's a book and it's about like a kingdom where this mysterious slime
rains down that just ruins everything a touch. It's like super sticky. They
can't clean it off and like it like and nobody can't like everything gets stuck
everybody gets stuck in the oob like and there's a part where some day he
swallows an oobleck and it like sticks up his insides and he can't talk and he's
like gonna die it's crazy dude. They tell me about that's like the Shel Silverstein
poem about eating peanut butter you eat a peanut butter sandwich and your mouth is
stuck closed and you can't even breathe and your parents won't help. Scary stuff.
Dude every Shel Silverstein when I was a kid they scared the fuck out of me.
All of his, the concept for all of his poems are like,
what if I wrote a poem about a guy with no face?
- Yeah.
- What if a monster lived inside of a kid?
- Yeah, what if there was like--
- And then, yeah, all you have to do is read his poem
and then just imagine his face.
- What if the street stopped?
- Dude, that was like--
(laughing)
Dude, that was the, that's still such a funny part
of Diary of a Wimpy Kid.
Where they just have the drawing of him
and it's like he looks like a pirate.
It's so funny dude. Yeah, he's a crazy looking guy. I would not like the guy anywhere near
my kids. Oh, except to read. No, just Shel Silverstein. He's not just on the back of
the book. He only existed on the back of the book. No, but they just kept using the same
photo of him. Yeah, they used the same photo of him and he's wearing some big fur coat
and he's got a giant beard. Yeah, and crazy veneers. Crazy veneers, bald head, giant eyebrows.
Okay wait, these comments are, something's going on with slime here. Listen to these
comments. I'll just read them in a row. Everyone sells slime. What? My best
friend did and got a hundred dollars each semester. What the f- It's a good idea to
sell slime because a lot of kids like it. So slime, so okay, so my little
brother, no my little brother, the nine-year-old, he loves slime. Yeah, my
younger sibling loves slime. It's because of those Instagram videos. No, it's because kids are being made
autistic by the Internet. Yeah. And slime calms them down. And they just make colored slime now.
Yeah, yeah, it's like a five years younger than us. Yeah, it's like it's like how like like you remember those cubes that were like fidget
Yeah, it was it's like that but yeah for just like devolved. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, every kid is autistic nowadays. I don't say that it is
I would it is everyone or 80d
This is this this like the comments on this read like they're coming out of like an alternate universe
Like we just found like yeah, like listen, this is crazy
someone's pretending to like so they're trying to send a message like this
listen this everyone in my school like slime even me and literally everyone
wants it and sells it is like this stuff it's like yeah this is like this creepy
dude I slime is just a can't make slime because me and my sister made a mess one
day and got banned from it my god dude we got banned from slime is a really
good idea you can get a lot of money and everyone likes it I sold slime in
fourth grade I made like $100 a week I made $78 off of slime selling in two
weeks that's the only person I believe because that's a rain that's a normal
number yeah I will sell this tomorrow I have literally made about $14 and I
started five days great idea I love slime I like slime it's a good stress
reliever yes yep yes I want slime slime when can I start I like it but not
prefer it at school. I will just stick to the regular learning system or book fairs."
Kids should not be so stressed that the only thing that can calm them down is slime.
This is so insane, dude! "I am selling slime and I have made 100 pounds in two weeks. X.
Wow, you should try it out. X. I made 50 pounds starting a slime business in school."
God damn it, dude. Imagine going back in time and explaining this to Ronald Reagan.
"My friend sells slime in school and made $50 each week and by the end of the month she had 200 bucks."
One day in industry is going to be kids selling slime to each other in school.
That's how kids are like, that's like when the people in like Brazil like hack Minecraft
accounts and then they just kind of mine for gold and then sell the mine or the runescape accounts.
Yeah.
And then they mine or they get like all the gold and then they sell the runescape account for money.
There's like a concept of like a David Foster Wallace novel.
It's kids selling slime to provide for their family.
Kids have a slime economy.
Yeah.
They start slime businesses.
yeah those comments weirded me out yeah bizarre dude we look let's look at
number four cuz then this kind of reminds us of our this must have been
like how our parents felt like rap came out yeah everybody loves yeah we're like
rap yeah what is that rapping yeah they just have no clue number music number
four is weed mm-hmm top comment you went to high school I went to school high oh
Oh my god.
Because you guys, I knew in middle school when I was like in sixth grade, the seventh grader,
this kid Bob, he was like one of my closest friends.
Dude, if you're in the seventh grade, you're going by Bob, not Bobby?
No, he was Bob.
That's some fucked up shit.
He was Bob.
We were in a band together that we never made a song or played any music, but we were in
a band together.
He sold weed and the way that he would sell weed was, this is like such a sick like 2008
thing, he would bring weed to school in tiny bags and he would hide them in the tag of his
new era fitted hat. Nice. Because it was like a little pouch and then he would
come into math class every day and be like, "Caleb, smell my hat." And so he would
pass the hat around the class and all the kids would like smell the hat and
then someone would be like, "This hat's great," like in front of the teacher, "This hat's
great. I'll give you ten dollars for this hat." Damn. Yeah, man. Bob is a genius, dude.
Yeah. Yeah. I think he's dead. Yeah. Yeah. Nice. Damn. That was like my main drug
dealer friend in middle school. Yeah. The only drug, like the one drug dealer at my
school lived in my neighborhood and my mom hated him so I couldn't. So you
couldn't buy any drugs? No. When did you first smoke weed? I talked about it
before I first smoked weed when I was like 13. Oh yeah. At a basketball game. Yeah.
Yeah. No I was already smoking cigs so I was like let's go to the next level. Yeah.
I didn't drink until I was 15 though. Yeah I didn't drink for a long time. No I
I drank when I was 13. I think I was 16 when I was 13. I was 17 when I drank and smoked for the first
time. I had a pineapple soda mixed with a vodka. Whoa. At my sister's 16th birthday. My first time
ever drinking I stole, my mom had like, somebody gave her a bottle of Hennessy and they never drank
it. So me and my friend John, we stole a, we stole like just a bunch, and I didn't know how to drink.
I was just like this alcohol, so I poured Hennessy into a giant solo cup and then
is there something interesting happening outside? I was just standing out there. Yeah, I thought they were
looking in the window. I poured Hennessy into two solo cups, like all the way to
the top and it was like the most disgusting thing ever, but I was like I
guess this is what it's like and we both like blacked out and then I remember I
was like we went for a walk on the beach and we blacked out and then I woke up
and I was running in the rain. It was like pouring down rain. I was sprinting and
John was like ahead of me and he like fell over and I had to like drag him like
into my house and then I like got him like on my bed and I was like okay he's
asleep I'm gonna go vomit and then I went to the bathroom I was vomiting for
a little while and then I heard just like something outside just like I was
like what the fuck is that and I opened the door to the bathroom and John was
completely naked at my brother's electronic drum kit in the living room
just feasting on it and it was completely unplugged oh man just fucking
going yeah that's awesome just completely naked damn here's a comment
on weed it get my thing going damn we'd get my thing yeah I got a smoke weed so
I get my thingy going.
Maybe offer the principal a toke after school too.
Principal, you want some of this?
I would never share my weed with the principal.
Never dude, that's what cops do.
You're all wet, you have never touched weed and you won't sell it.
What about wet with PCP?
I think wet is maybe a new slang that we don't understand.
I love weed, a gum over the seven tree of a dog.
That's literally what being high does to your brain.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- I bought a pound of weed
and also ordered 100 pre-rolled cones,
stuffed them and sold them for $5 each.
Think of that.
1,600 pound, $5 each jay,
which is .3 of a gram.
That's killer profit.
That's if you don't smoke your supply.
Stay lifted, by the way.
There's 453 grams in a pound.
- Wow. - Nice.
- That's a cop.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- There's a funny picture of me holding a pound of weed.
- Yeah, that's a good picture.
- It's a lot more than you would think.
- It's huge.
- It's so much.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I just stepped out of the shower one day
and my brother was like,
"Do you wanna hold a pound of weed?"
I'm like, "Meh, sure."
- I would hold a pound of weed if I could.
- Yeah, you know how heavy it is?
- No, it's a pound.
- Yeah, I gotcha.
Got your ass.
- It's probably less heavy.
- Number five is snacks.
I've sold snacks.
What am I, the vending machine?
Yeah.
Yeah, what is he, the vending machine?
Yeah, what am I, the vending machine?
I sold snacks.
I would sell snacks to the ghost store
that would go by my house.
(laughing)
Yeah, there was a graveyard across the street
from my dad's house.
I was never a seller.
I couldn't--
We set up, I set up a little plastic table
and me and my brother, we would sell water bottles,
Coke products, and snacks from Costco.
And we made a pretty good amount of money.
Nice.
Yeah, I was never patient enough
and no one wanted to buy things from me.
I loved doing, I just loved having a job.
Yeah.
Top comment.
- As a kid I was obsessed with having a job.
- I was obsessed with getting things for free.
- I wanted to, I watched--
- I was obsessed with being friends with the kid
who was selling things and then working for him
and then him being like, yeah, you can get some gum.
- I had a, I wanted to, I saw my big fat Greek wedding
and I was like, I asked my parents,
I was like, we have to open a diner
because I wanna be like a kid who works at a diner so bad.
- You wanna be a diner monkey?
- Yeah, I wanted to be a diner monkey.
- I tried to work at, my mom did work for,
before she worked at the super walk,
she worked at, fuck, I should stop saying the business name.
She worked at a Greek diner.
- Yeah.
- And I worked there for a day, got paid 60 bucks.
- Whoa.
- And then I went and bought a PS2.
- With 60 bucks?
What year was this?
- 2010.
- Oh, okay.
- And then I asked if I could work there again,
and then my mom said, "No, they don't want you there."
(laughing)
- Dude, I worked in food service for four days
and I sucked at it so badly.
I worked at Jersey Mike's for four days
and I got basically fired because my hands were too sweaty
because I would put on the gloves, like plastic gloves,
and I would sweat so much through the gloves
that they would like fall off of me
while I was making a sandwich.
- Probably because you were wearing too big gloves.
- I have no idea.
But the guy, the boss, I was like,
I was like, I'm, yeah, Mike.
I was like, I'm sweating too much,
like my gloves keep falling off
and I can't do anything with these gloves on.
He's like, okay, well we'll just put some yeast
and flour on your hands and it'll just dry 'em out.
And then I did that and I was so sweaty
that it made like a dough in my gloves.
And he was like, you can't work here.
- Damn.
- At LA, at the company me and Alex were interning at.
- Yeah, you said.
- I can say it, yeah, I guess.
Or no, I would say it on a, I'm not gonna say it.
Might as well not.
people probably know if not doesn't matter uh... i was a college humor
yeah
uh...
here i was a little bit about how my result
uh... oh yeah
uh... they can
we're asking like oh what's a good food in the area andy
the guy was just like telling us good food and then alexa as a joke like
okay what's the worst restaurant in the area and i was like oh you know what
definitely jersey mike's i hate that place is fucking shit it's the worst
food ever and then like a week later liquor having click
we had to we were doing like a workshop thing and he was like oh i'll get you
guys lunch uh what do you guys want from jersey mike
just like forgot that he told us that he thought it was like so he's just like i
love jersey mike it's my favorite sub place it's pretty good
by far actually maybe john actually no no
jersey mikes are way better than jim i've never been to jersey mike so i don't
have him around here oh no you know what best sub place i ever went to subway
victor's deli in somerville mass gerard deli
Brownie chocolate shut the fuck down blimpy
Do you guys not a blimpy up here top comment on snacks?
You don't have your weird stuff coming on snags angle shit top comment on snacks is it's an option
But when I tried it as an option a few years ago
I was told only seniors are allowed to sell that only some kids can sell snacks or seniors
Did you guys have a school store? Yeah? No, do you like like where you buy snacks? Yes? I was
I had school. Oh, yeah, that's right
so just camera but yeah we had a you could buy cookies there for like two bucks for
two cookies yeah you could buy everything was so expensive the co-op I went to had
like they would have a bake sale once a month so people would just bring it
doesn't count doesn't matter not it was always over please they would sell like
Otis Spunkmeyer cookies that they heated up in a little ofunk Meyer yeah skipping
ahead to not a name not a skipping ahead to number eight is porn top comment
jerking off every day to this is the best thing I've ever experienced. I like porn
because I jerk off until the end of the video and I faint when the girls say ooh
yes daddy and I die by the happiness of jerking off. If your school has security
cameras you're probably gonna get caught doing this. I jacked off at school. You
jacked off? You fucking freak. In middle school? Yeah dude. If I was bored in class you just go to
the bathroom crank one out, shoot it in the toilet, leave it there for the janitor to eat.
That's disgusting. It's normal. No, it's gross. It's a normal healthy thing.
It's funny that I'm so, I'm not like a horny person now. When I was a kid I
was like the horniest little... I was, it was awesome. That's gross though, I would
never... It was a peak of my powers man. Jack off at school? That's disgusting. I jack
off at school now. The fucking, oh I have... I graduated. Yeah. Six months ago. I just go back in.
I show them I show them my Ralph's loyalty card as if it's an ID and then I just walk to the bathroom I jerk off
Damn feels like home number
I skip ahead to number 12 because the top comment number 12 is or number 12 is your soul
It's kind of like funny. You have to sell your soul at school, right?
That's how common on this is my penis is hard for tamales and I agree with selling my souls to some random kids at school
Just like my penis is hard for tamales
Pretty good my junk food that's snacks. Fuck you homework doing homework doing hair
Hair the comment says I'm bald
Dude hair we did you know this was just at my school there. Did you guys have Pantene's beautiful links locks for love?
yeah, yeah, we had that but it was called Pantene's beautiful links and
Like it was a mandatory thing we had
Crazy, it was like a pep rally
That was also a hair cutting ceremony. Mm-hmm, and we had like they shut down Pantene Beautiful Lengths
But we had the most hair donated by a high school
Dude, my high school is fucking crazy. Isn't most wig hair taken from like like corpses in India?
Yeah, it's like by corpses that half most of the hair that we would donate at our school
They wouldn't use yeah and girls would pressure other girls into doing it
and then some girls would shave their heads completely bald just to be like
"look at how much I'm donating" and it was just like a whole freaking freak fest
of just kids just donating like girls donating their hair and then like the
occasional like guy would grow out his hair. And here's the thing
for these people with cancer, being bald is really actually very cool.
You know and it's normal. Going bald is the most noble thing you can do.
Exactly, it's heroic to lose your hair. It is. Me and Patrick are in agreement here.
- No, no. - It's extremely normal.
- It doesn't matter if it's because of cancer
or like other stuff.
- Just genetics, your grandpa's balls.
- Maybe you have such bad dandruff
that just your hair falls out in giant clumps
with like some weird plateau of skin underneath it.
- And then some of your family members
also have trichotomelia or whatever,
that hair pulling thing. - Yeah, it's normal, yeah.
- And you have a hair pulling thing too,
but you're also going bald,
so you're getting freaked out about it.
- Exactly. - That's normal.
- It's a normal thing. - So donate some of your hair
to me Pantene beautiful links at my high school.
- That's as bad, that's as un-American and bad
as dying in 9/11.
I don't think you guys are heroes.
I think you're the opposite.
I think you're traitors.
- Me and Pat are gonna go get best buddy hair plugs
together in China.
- We're gonna go to Istanbul.
- I feel like that's when we started with the first,
I think the first episode of this marathon
we talked about hair plugs.
- Yeah, we talked about Istanbul hair.
- We started with hair plugs, we're ending with hair plugs.
- It's normal.
- On the end of the marathon.
- I'm gonna, as soon as I have the money,
I'm gonna get some crazy hair plugs.
Yeah, some Wayne Diamond plugs.
I mean, they're gonna look, I'm gonna show up,
I'm gonna go on a six month vacation
and let them grow out a little bit.
And then I'm gonna show up
and you guys are gonna fucking suck my dick.
You're gonna show up with your head in a mummy wrap.
Yeah.
Number 19 is candy and top comment.
This is kind of, let's do a wholesome.
Let's close it out with a wholesome one.
Okay.
'Cause everyone's stressed out.
Let's close out with a--
Well, yeah, we're stressed out.
Definitely by the time this comes out,
stuff is way worse.
Yeah.
One of us is gonna be dead.
Or it's way better, we don't know.
No, it's definitely worse.
It's not going to be better.
We'll end it on a wholesome note.
It's St. Patrick's Day.
It is St. Patrick's Day.
It's my namenstag.
Your what?
Namenstag.
What does that mean?
It is a German thing.
If you're named after a saint in Germany,
you get candy
for your namenstag.
I brought some haichu.
you
to give me candy I tried and you said that it hurts your teeth well I forgot
that it's my nomin dog and I have to eat candy mm-hmm there was in high school I
took German and on my nomin dog on st. Patrick's Day two girls did give me
candy once and I said thank you and I didn't talk and they gave me lint
chocolates lint chocolates made out of lint fuck you got close Patrick put it
in his poop or it went under the couch you think so I think it fell forward no
it went under my couch nice yeah there it was that was the yeah that we were
talking about earlier yeah yes finally was that even that was probably like a
week ago talking about that guy dude everyone's gonna be so confused about
these episodes no you listen to do them in order if you don't understand it
subscribe to the patreon exactly and makes perfect here is a marathon yeah the
We don't have any patrons to read so we'll just make them up.
That's why I said we should have read half of them.
No, we have to end it with the wholesome.
No, that's stupid.
Well, no, we're going to end with the St. Patrick's Day song.
Yeah, well, okay, let me read the wholesome one and then we'll sing the St. Patrick's
Day song together.
All right, I would love to do that.
Yeah.
Read the wholesome one.
St. Patrick's Day is like a week and a day ago, I think, if you're listening to this.
Number 19, Candy.
yes candy because there can be a day when you are feeling a little down and
you need some candy so
that will be a great idea
shane
and
this is the iris rover
i don't know this isn't it
shane you ruined it
is the day of the day and the Irish are here to get all the snakes
out of Ireland and there's friends at the store and they want
to drink beer beers and the best part of the day is when we all go to the shamrock shake
And I went to McDonald's and I got a shamrock shake.
And I got extra cherries in it because it's St. Patrick's Day.
And there was whipped cream, and the shamrock scream weeps.
♪ They were making me sleep ♪
♪ And the Ireland flag ♪
♪ Is orange and white and green ♪
♪ St. Patrick's Day ♪
- Wow, that was amazing.
Thank you. Yeah, you're welcome. Yeah. Yeah. See you next time.