You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the hopeless.
You're a crap monster.
Oh my god.
Okay, so I'm recording from my car.
Yeah.
From the backseat of my car alone.
And my neighbor...
Life has gotten so weird in the past three weeks.
I know.
Can you believe it's still March?
Can you believe...
Dude, the horrors of April have yet to come.
It's a calm yeah, well when this comes out it is April just it's not March. It's true. That's
So yeah, my there's no quiet room in my house. I'm at staying in my mom's house
The walls and ceilings and floors are very thin every you can hear everybody at all times
So I can't record a podcast in there
So I'm sitting in the backseat of my mom's car in front of
Parked in front of our house and our neighbor just came out and looked at me
Pretty fun. They look at you
devilishly maybe they're trying to see you get dressed yeah yeah they're kind
of they're walking around the sidewalk with their dog so they're just kind of
over there yeah it's fucking weird it's a quarantine you have to stay inside but
you make your dog pee in the toilet poop in the toilet get a pad swallow your
dog's waist put a maxi pad on your dog if there was ever a time to teach your
dog how to shit in the sink it'd be right now yeah you know what it what what is
- What is the deal in Boston right now?
You guys, have they said you have to stay inside yet?
- I don't think so.
I don't think they will.
They said they strongly suggested it,
but there's no shelter in place.
- We're Boston strong, we can't get in.
- Yeah, 'cause if you guys have to stay locked inside,
the Sarnaevs win.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah.
- That's what they were trying to do.
They were trying to, their whole bombing the marathon
was just to get us to go back inside.
- It worked for like a day.
You could leave your house for like a day, right?
- That's true.
I was in New Hampshire.
I you could yeah you couldn't leave your house for like a night I think it wasn't
even the whole day yeah it was just like the evening friend didn't your friend
die my friend was a star naive was Jokar star naive actually oh yeah thinking of
no a bunch of my family members are like have close ties to the marathon
Yeah, my uncle Rubikonov, he is closely tied to the Tsarnaevs.
My aunt like has all these crazy connections, like she just knows a bunch of people who were
like hurt or killed in it and like her, well I don't want to, yeah, there's, I don't want
to dox my family, but there's like people's names, I'll tell you guys after the podcast.
I'll post them on the Discord, I'll post his family's names.
Yeah, that'll be a Discord exclusive anecdote.
Yeah, you know, yeah, I'll put you all.
The list of the victims from the Boston bombing.
- Yeah, I haven't been able to,
how have you guys been doing?
I'm going crazy. - I've been good.
- 'Cause I haven't been able to sleep.
- Dude, I've just been,
I went to bed at like six the other day, 6 a.m.
- Oh, okay.
That's normal for you. - That is just
Patrick, but more.
I've got the mission of more.
- I'm in turbo Patrick mode.
I'm like not, I'm staying up 'til six.
Yeah, staying up 'til six every day.
I've been playing Skate 3.
I've been playing Mario Kart.
I'm really mad because my TV doesn't have any RCA ports on it
so I can't play the GameCube.
- You can come to my house.
- Order the Coke Shield cable adapter.
- Yeah, I wanna get the component cables for the Wii though
'cause it does have component cable slots.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be setting up my Wii next week.
- Yeah.
- Whoa, that's a big plan.
- I can teach you how to mod it.
- I don't want that.
I don't want you to teach me anything.
You don't want a hair trigger on your Wii?
Yeah.
Dude, I want a Wii with the real gun.
You can put an extendo on the remote?
Yeah.
Yeah, you can put a bump stock on your Wii.
You can make a Wii.
The Wii Motion Plus is a bump stock.
Yeah.
I've been doing okay.
Right now, I just finished up my quarantine
in the cottage behind my in-laws' house.
Now you're back to coughing
on all the produce in grocery stores.
Exactly, yeah.
I'm back to sampling all the grapes and the strawberries.
Yeah.
Yeah, with my tongue.
But I just like, I've been sitting out here playing Minecraft, smelling like dog shit.
Like absolute horse shit, piss, and fucking cum.
I smell terrible.
Oh, I've been showering a lot.
I have been showering, this is the least I've ever showered in my life.
The other day I realized I wore the same pants for 18 days in a row.
Oh, I did that before the quarantine.
My brown pants.
You can wear pants as long as you want.
That's the thing about pants.
I thought that too until I was sitting on the couch with Jana watching Nathan for You.
You tried to stand up and your pant legs wouldn't bend.
Yeah.
They were so starched with shit.
No, she was just, she was like, "Honestly, like, I think your pants smell like it's maybe
the worst smell I've ever smelt."
And I was like, "I'm breaking up with you.
You can't say that to me, dude."
I used to wear the same pair of black dickies like every day.
That's exactly what they are.
The black dickies are a fucking stink magnet.
It's because you can empty a bottle of ketchup on black dickies and never see a stain.
It absorbs it like an alien.
You know in movies when an alien goo hops out of something and absorbs a bullet?
That's how my dickies are with mustard and mayonnaise stains.
It's like venom.
It's a venom symbiote.
eating hot dogs I'm just outing myself and it's all I'm all so much so much
corn chowder that we keep fucking sending yeah it's so good so good though it's
corn chowder with a pork shoulder bacon that sounds delicious it looks like you
dumped like just like canned corn in half and half yeah yeah I mean that's
- That's essentially corn chowder.
- Yeah, with salt.
- Yeah.
- Today I made a polenta.
- Yes.
- Ooh.
- That sounds good.
- Grade A slop.
- Oh, last night Dom and I--
- That is next level.
- I got a, I got really, I don't know what,
I made like a thing, like a blender full,
like it's like a 72 ounce blender that I have,
and I filled it with like just too much tequila.
I just made like the biggest frozen margarita thing,
and I got fucked up way too quick.
- Yeah.
- And we got, I was so drunk that I moved,
I showed you guys already,
but I moved the corner of the couch out to the alleyway.
- To the alleyway?
- Yeah, so this is-- - Why'd you get rid
of the couch?
- We got rid of the corner piece.
- Why?
- So now there's more room in my apartment.
- Oh, okay.
What are you gonna use that corner for?
- Oh, we just put the corner in the alleyway
and I'm sitting on--
- No, no, where are you putting--
- The free corner, hold on, let me--
- What are you putting in the new corner?
gonna put something like a ping-pong table or something? No, he's gonna put a basket.
A basket? You're right, that was a much better use of the space. No, so the cats can run around.
But look, I put the one chair here and then like the reclining chair and then the big
chair. Man, looks like total shit, dude. Did you guys see that person just run by that
window right there? No. Someone just ran by this window like right by it. Like an inch
away
I mean they're just running with their dogs. Everyone's running with their dogs. I don't know what's going on. Why are people running?
They're running the same direction. No
Okay up and down the street is a dead-end Street. I don't know why people run up and down the street to say hi to you
They want to probably know what it is. It's probably and probably they live here. It's most likely
Yeah, that's fucking stupid dude shut up shut the fuck up I've just been I've been hanging out shooting guns
Yeah, yeah, I'm doing that's pretty cool shooting shotgun. I just found a whole I would actually never touch a gun. Oh, wow
That's that's awesome - I'm gonna touch a gun to you, dude. Yeah, I'm gonna make you touch
Yeah, believe that you're not gonna like I've shot a gun before I've told you guys about this
I'm gonna shoot on to you. Is it a story when you shot a gun? No, I just
Actually my roommates. No, I shot an AR-15 for the like my first gun. Oh, dude, a r-50. That's a cool fucking gun
Yeah, no my shoulder hurt for like two days, but I didn't want to tell them
So I was just like there was like a situation where I had to like lift like I had to lift up the vacuum
in front of them and I just like
Trying so badly to not show how much of a pussy you are. Yeah
Yeah, and they hung up our art. We didn't have any posters on our wall or anything
we did have we had like a big American flag in our living room and then
just the
bullet like the what are they called the targets we had the American flag and
then like one of the targets was supposed to be a terrorist and it was
just a brown person that we shot. Yeah that's that yeah anytime somebody prints
one of those out it's always like it's like a picture of Carlos Mencia.
He's an A-Rab. And then some yeah they put Carlos Mencia in a turban and
sometimes he's got a turban and he's got zombie skin. Yeah. That's how they get
around yeah the races they put that that picture of the that like image macro of
the kid who has Osama bin Laden's beard yeah the baby mr. bean yeah who just
like has has his arm he just has Pamela Anderson in a headlock yeah 15 bullets
directly in the same spot in Pamela Anderson's face. Sorry I can't help myself.
She's so beautiful. Yeah, I got distracted. It's like when you look at like, look at
something while you're driving you start drifting that way. Yeah. Yeah, but you're
so distracted by the Pamela Anderson cutout. Yeah, there's just like, yeah, there's
like ten bullets in Mr. Bean's head and then like just a splat on Pamela
Anderson's face. Yeah. The, uh, I, I, the first time I ever shot a gun it was just like a
a little shotgun. The second time my brother's friend had an mp5. Ooh. Yeah.
And it's called mp3 idiot. Yeah it's called an mp3 file of me of a gunshot and he
listened to it. He made me shoot an mp5 and I was so so terrified. I was
like and I wasn't sure I was like a little kid and I wasn't scared of
shooting the gun I was scared that some like MK ultra trigger would happen in my
brain and I would turn around and start shooting everybody. I was like fuck dude if I like
turn crazy that would suck so bad. I hope I don't turn crazy right now. My parents are
gonna come pick me up and I'm gonna be have no way to explain this you know. I'd have
to frame a crime scene. Yeah. Yeah some guy took the mp5 out of my hands and. Dude it
Mr. Bean. Mr. Bean stole your mp5. Damn. Imagine Mr. Bean dual wielding. With
silencers. Mm-hmm yeah cuz he can't talk. Exactly. Or like if the guns do make a
noise it's just kind of like "ohhh"
The Mr. Bean silencer that makes the the clap of the bullet sound like "hmm"
Or like, like everyone's one he'll say no. James Bond shooting a pistol that goes
"No." That's what Dr. No, yeah that's what Dr. No is about.
You know, fuck. Bam man, it's been um it's been chill today. We're officially not in
In North Carolina, we're not allowed to go to parks and stuff.
You can go to the grocery store at home.
Yeah, they closed all the parks in my town,
but that's just my town.
There's nothing, yeah.
The day before, I did go to a skate park
like in the middle of all this
'cause I had to complete a Patreon request.
You're what we call a spreader, my friend.
Yeah. You spread your legs
and you spread disease. No, I thought
I thought it was gonna be me and then like three guys there,
but it was like me--
- Oh, it was gonna be you and three guys spreading.
Yeah, you and the three guys you brought, your boyfriends?
- Yeah, my boyfriends.
- Chris, Tom, and Todd?
- Tom O'Shea.
But I thought it was gonna just be me
and like three other people,
but it was me, like four people skateboarding,
and then like a bunch of moms with their little kids
running around the pump track.
It was just like, man, you just--
- Oh, dude, score.
You do not give a shit about your kid, huh?
Couple of mommies at the skate park, couple of skate mommies.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
That's worth it, man.
Yay.
Yeah.
Yes!
Oh.
Ooh.
Um.
I've also, I've been playing a lot of Minecraft.
Yeah, I- I've been building wild shit on Minecraft.
I had to kick Minecraft 'cause I have fucking classwork all the time.
That sucks.
I can't believe you're still in school.
I know.
And it's so much like I can't fucking space out in class because all my like attendance
requirements are like, "Watch this hour-long video and send me all your notes on it to
prove that you watched it."
And it's just like, "Oh, great.
I actually have to."
It's fucking sucks, dude.
I'm just going to fail.
Yeah, it is the worst school to have online classes at.
Absolutely.
For sure.
Like...
I cannot wait to be fucking dumb.
Everything is like production-based.
Everything is performance-based.
Like, what are you going to do?
Improv over fucking Skype?
It's funny you say that. I just heard my boss at MIT had her daughter was at the new school
and they choose it.
That school has been around for a while. They should just call it the school.
They should just call it the medium school.
The normal school.
The school that's been around a normal amount of time.
But she was in the middle of an improv class and then they moved it online and so now she has to do online improv.
- Bro, it's so funny.
- That's sick, dude.
- Yeah.
- It's probably a lot like this.
- Yeah, 'cause then one person can be funnier than the other
'cause then they can put, they can make their background.
- They can do a funny background, yeah.
That's how you get an A plus in the, yeah.
- I improvise my background.
- Yeah, do a background, it's that picture of,
that old one of Hulk Hogan doing 9/11 with his fists.
- Well, no, one person says like,
well, it's great we're here at the store,
and the other person switches the background
like underwater and goes no yeah stupid bitch we're underwater her yeah we're
Atlantis you fucking idiot can't you see can't you see can't you see look at the
background look at the zoom background it is April Fool's Day yeah it's April
1st so we have a list from the discord let me see who sent this in the discord
yeah visions of China I that's awesome man he also sent worst things about the
Holocaust and top ten worst things to say to a Holocaust survivor I think those
might be an April Fool's prank on us so if we did do those we would have been
pranked so it's good that we didn't. Top 10 April Fool's pranks it's on the top
tens. It's by Delgia2k. Delgia. That's a cool name.
Delgia2000. That's like a combination of Palkia and Diagla. And Lugo.
Yeah and Luigi. Luigi the Pokemon. And Picochu. Pictochat.
Picto-chute. Have you guys ever been been fallen victim to an April Fool's prank?
Probably. I definitely have. You know the ones where the teacher says we have a pop
quiz today? Uh-huh. I never fell for those man. I was too small.
Teachers suck dude. Yeah. Yeah. Teachers suck, homework even worse than teachers.
And pranks are the third worst thing. Pranks I think are good if you do them on
your teacher. I was the prankster in middle school. I was the prank kid.
Nowadays you put a thumbtack under your teacher's seat, they send you to Abu
Ghraib. You can't do pranks anymore. Society is cracking down on pranksters
right now. You ever heard of PC culture? PC stands for pranks kill and that's why
they don't let you do pranks anymore. Yeah. Especially teachers.
Teachers are a protected class nowadays. Yeah. That's also what PC culture stands for.
Protected class. This is the worst time for pranksters because they're all stuck
up in their homes. What are they gonna do? Prank their mom? Yeah. You know,
this whole #MeToo movement has really been tough on pranksters.
yeah the the genre of sexual prank has completely been destroyed lost to the
gloss to the culture yeah so sad it's your any sexual pranks anymore no no
let's see the first you guys I gotta ask you about your prank so what pranks did
you guys do what price did I do yeah what's your biggest prank well you know
One time, my best friend, I mean I was always super lazy. One time I told, I like woke
Levi, my younger brother up and told him that my dad killed himself. But like I
was not, you know, it wasn't very creative. I would always, I remember one time I
tried, I tried to set up, you remember the classic bucket of water on the
partly open door? Yeah, yeah. So I tried to set that up and then the water fell on
on
of pranks on teachers that I pulled.
- Yeah, like what?
- Just like, some of them just like the mouse thing,
like you put the invisible tape over the mouse laser.
I did that enough times to one teacher
that he, in the middle of class,
he had the IT guy come up and replace the mouse.
- That's nice.
- And there was one other time,
we set up, he had a big timer,
same teacher, it was my science teacher in eighth grade.
He had a timer and we set it up for 30 minutes
in the middle of class.
And then in the middle of his lesson,
the timer went off and we started laughing
and then he like looked at us and went,
"Is this funny to you?"
And then he made us sit in silence
for the rest of the class and he like didn't teach us.
- I just, a good prank that we pulled was,
one time me, my older brother found a two by four
in our yard and he used a saw to cut it down
like the last like half centimeter or whatever of like the wood like in the
middle and then my mom was in the front yard like mowing the lawn or something
and my brother was like okay you run into the yard screaming and I'm gonna
break this over the back of your head and I was like okay and so I did it I
ran out and he hit me with the 2x4 in a way so that like it looked to my mom
like he just snapped it clean in half like Bruce Lee over the back of my
fucking head and I just started like screaming and my mom went like so
earnestly my mom went to go punch him in the face like cocked it back like
fucking punch out and I was just like no no no no no no no no it was fake
because I was like it can you imagine just how different my life would have
been if I'd watch my mom like knock the shit out of my brother. It's good that was her first
instinct. Yeah that's that's a mama bear shit. Yeah she is humongously fat and
hairy. I told you I think I've talked about it before but the it's the
important documents folder I put on the school share drive. Yeah that one that was a
good one. Explain it, I don't think you've talked about that. Yeah I got in a lot of
of trouble for it. I lost my computer privileges at school for a week because I made a folder
on the school's shared drive. It was called the Z drive and it was just like a cloud thing.
It ran over the servers of the computers and it said important documents. There was no
important documents folder before so I made the folder important documents and then I just
put like a thousand copies of beans from even Stevens. Just this one photo of him on the
red carpet and it's just him in like a Buccaneers jersey holding up the peace sign and then someone
else in my video production class found it, started copying and pasting it some more.
So by the end of the day it was 2 gigabytes big but it was slowing down every computer
at school.
That's what they told me and that's why they were allowed to take away my computer privileges
but they said they had to go through every individual file to make sure that there weren't
any important documents in the file.
That rocks.
Yeah, that's...
Number one prank according to this list.
This is the number one prank of all time.
This is the number one prank.
We found the number one.
Fuck those pranks that we just said.
Yeah, yeah.
Fuck the jackass giant hand, which is probably the best one.
Oh, that's for sure.
That's the best prank, right?
I think it's the best jackass prank.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of what another jackass prank they did even is.
Oh, the best one was the Johnny Knoxville's lotion where they put all the horse cum in it. Oh, yeah
Can you imagine being like on on the set of jackass and being like, you know
It's smart to be let everyone know that I put lotion on my face all the time
What a layup for fucking steve-o. Yeah
Number one replace Oreo cream filling with toothpaste sort of a similar prank. Yeah
Basically, I feel like this one's more immediate though.
That's a devastating prank.
90% of pranks are about replacing one thing with another thing.
Well, the thing about this prank is it's really devastating because you go, you eat the Oreo
expecting your teeth to get dirty, but they get clean.
And that's why I eat candy, is because I like to dirty up my teeth and nasty it up for the
dentist.
I want to turn them brown.
I'm trying to get as many cavities as I can so that my dentist, Sandra Miles, will look
That's my dentist name actually.
I'm trying to get my dentist, I'm making my dentist work for his fucking money.
No, she's a lady. How fucked up is that?
She's a dentist and her name is S. Miles.
Woah.
What a fucking bitch, dude.
My dentist was named Robert T. Christ.
What?
His name was Robert T. Christ and if you called him, he called himself Dr. Christ.
And if you called him Dr. Christ, he would correct you because he was a devout Christian.
Fuck it, dude. I would have named my dentistry office "Teeth Christ".
Yeah.
That's what his middle name was.
"Teethist Christ".
But he, in the middle of cleaning my teeth once,
he left for like an hour to talk to some woman and then he came back with her and then he was like,
"I actually have a cassette of my wife's organ music right here if you want it."
And I was like, "That's why you were fucking gone?"
on
organ music. Yeah, I wish I had a cassette of his wife's organ music. Yeah, could you
get me one? I make, I make her- I wish I had a picture of his wife's organ. I play her
organs and she makes music. Yeah. Yeah, you know what I'm saying? And I put a cassette
in her. Yeah, I put a cassette in my wife and I record all of her thoughts to it. And
then I plug it into, I put it into my Commodore 64 and I play my wife's thoughts like a video
game yeah I pressed a click like an eject button and a copy of Kotor came out
let's see any comments on this one somebody says if cheesy nachos says
about toothpaste in the Oreo it tastes good though it probably I mean chocolate
and mint you can't go wrong there it would I mean it would just taste at first
like a mint Oreo yeah there's another good comment from epic Jake says I was
about to read that. My Colgate Total would make a great replacement. So similar vein.
Yeah. I bet his full name is Jake Colgate. He's out here doing gorilla advertising. Yeah.
He's showing a gorilla in the comments. Not so epic Jake. He's putting an ASCII
gorilla in the comments. Or the ASCII gorilla. How about this Jake? I'm gonna go gorilla
on your whole mouth and eyes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
And you're not gonna like it if you don't stop.
I don't think, I think gorillas don't, I think gorillas, uh, they split you in half.
I think chimps are the ones who like the, they like to fuck your hands.
I'm doing the, I'm going all in gorilla style.
And I'm gonna let the listeners decide what that means.
You do look like a gorilla 'cause you're fat as shit.
I'm not fat.
And you have a tiny penis.
You look exactly like a gorilla.
It's completely different.
You have a giant head.
I'm so, I'm so, no.
- Big fat body, you're five foot two,
and you have a tiny wiener.
- Okay, yeah.
- I don't see any lies.
- There's, yeah, where's the lie?
- Yeah.
- The whole thing was the lie.
- No, none of it's a lie.
- Nah.
- I just said the whole thing was the lie.
- No. - You're the liar.
- I'm not a liar.
- Oh, so first I'm a gorilla, now I'm a liar?
Why don't you pick one?
- Gorillas are--
- You're a flip-flopper, dude.
- One of the most dishonest beasts in the zoo.
(laughing)
- They're never trust--
- No, no.
- Never trust the word of a gorilla.
- No.
You should always trust the word Coco one of the most genius creatures of all time.
She's not even smart.
That's the ultimate lie is that she doesn't know how to communicate.
She's making all that shit up.
Yeah.
No, you guys are wrong.
You guys are wrong.
You guys are little bugs.
You want to talk about bugs.
I'm going to show you what it's like to be stepped on.
You can't step on us because you refuse to wear shoes.
I wear a shoe right now.
Because they don't make shoes.
this I'm wearing a fucking shoes. How am I wearing shoes? You're showing me your big hairy gorilla
feet. I know you love it dude. You're showing me that you're peeling a banana with your foot.
You're not even. Dude stop eating bananas. Cameron's sitting on a throne of bananas in his
banana car. Because I'm the king but it's not a I'm not a gorilla I'm just a banana king.
Cam is sitting in the banana car. You can like bananas and not be a gorilla. You're in the banana
car from the Bloodhound Gang music video.
Yeah, yeah.
You're gonna drive it into a tunnel and give the guy a banana.
And you drive it into your house that is a banana, it's a large banana much like a Spongebob's
pineapple house.
I would, I would enjoy living in one of those.
Yeah, because you'd eat it all day, you fucking monkey.
You don't eat your house, what are you talking about?
You have a gold sponsorship like Super Monkey Ball.
Nobody eats their house.
Yeah, yeah, you're, your life is Super Monkey Ball sliding through Boston in a ball collecting
bananas. If you lived in a house made out of food would you eat it? No I would live
in it. Yeah. You can't live in your house and eat it too. What if your house is
made out of uh... Soylent. Gingerbread. I would... Yeah. Gingerbread. Which one? Soylent. If my house... I
wouldn't eat it. I would live in it. What if your house... I would eat your house. What if
your house was made out of gingerbread and your sink only had... and when you turn
your sink on it only had soylent? I would move. That would suck. I would not live there.
okay then what about chocolate milk? I would move. I need water. House of is made out of
calzone like bricks that are calzones from 7-eleven and then if you turn on
the tap water it's Powerade blue. I'd eat that. You wouldn't have a you wouldn't you
wouldn't do a glacier cherry sink? That's Gatorade and I've recently been on
a Powerade kick. It's a little sweeter. Patrick bites every house he sees them
check if it's candy yeah like you bite a gold coin to see if it's candy yeah
Patrick goes up to every single house is this what prospectors would bite gold coins
yeah dude it's not candy I do that to people's cars too yeah you do that to
the rims of people I do that to the rims yeah I do it to the steering wheel
mostly yeah yeah and then if it does work if it is food then you eat the whole
damn side it tastes like a big soft pretzel oh my god
Could you imagine your steering wheel is a soft pretzel? That'd be awesome.
Can you imagine eating Cam's banana car?
Oh yeah.
That his monkey mind goes absolutely bananas for?
No, I can't imagine that.
Yeah, and you use a GPS that, get this, it's like a Garmin,
and you're pressing it and it's talking to you, but then when we see it, it's just a banana.
It's a GPS and it means gorillas per second.
you have a you have a you you move you use a banana like a stick shift both of
the pedals both of the pedals are bananas no no no no no no no no no no no no
extremely fucked up no no I have a race car I have a race car I can drive around
town and that's all I'm gonna say on the subject I dare dare I say it's almost
lynchian you dare not say dare I say no at the risk of scaring us all I will I
I will invoke the name of David Lynch, the master of horror.
It's Kafka-esque.
Yes, it's very Ray Romano-like, what you're doing in this piece.
It's very Sandler-esque.
shows you their music and it's just like it's just oh and you're like it's I dare
I say it it's Sandler esque what you're doing here is incredible every like
anytime somebody like sings about or what's that the Havana Gila just saying
that that's Sandler esque going it going into a into a reading the Talmud and
something about this text is so Sandler-esque yeah yeah just the Hanukkah
song that's the only Jewish thing Adam Sandler ever did mm-hmm yeah not uncut
gems not any no not not his yeah not as a his own self the wedding singer Sandy
Wexler oh my god Sandy Wexler all right number two is plant a grass garden on
someone's keyboard. The comment, the only comment is an anonymous one that just says, "How would
you do that?" Very fair. I would say, I would say the way you do that is, it would, I don't
think you could do it with just like dirt, because they would notice. Yeah. I think there's
a possibility you get this done with a chia seed. Well, I think you'd have to do it with
plants personally. Yeah. You sucker fucker. I think what you'd have to do is pick up all
of the keys and then put little flower pots in the keys slots. That's what I think. What
about if you put dangerous spores? Yeah. Whoa. You make a mushroom garden. Yeah, dark mushrooms
and dangerous creatures that live in the darkness.
- Make a psilocybin mushroom farm.
- Whoa.
- Right?
- Now that's less of a prank and more of a gift,
if you ask me.
- Yeah, yeah, right?
- The best prank is a gift.
- I'm gonna grow a--
- That's true.
- And Noam Chomsky said that.
- Yeah, yeah.
- No, that's the words from Noam Chomsky.
- Noam is one of the greatest prank theorists we have.
- That's what manufacturing consent is about.
- Yeah, it's about getting consent for a prank,
'Cause pranks are never consensual until afterwards.
- My senior prank in high school had to be,
fucking, we had to talk to the principal about it
and we had to get our prank approved.
- That is not a prank, that is an action.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, that's a game, that's a plan.
- You can't plan, you can't have the teachers
in on your senior prank.
What kind of fucking fascist bullshit is that?
- Yeah, exactly, dude.
Yeah. I'm still, I still get heated about it, man.
What was your prank again?
Five years ago.
What'd you say?
We had a rave in a classroom.
Dude, that, I mean, of course you need permission for that, dude. People are doing MDMA and
fucking and women have straight edge X's over their titties at raves. You can't, you gotta,
that's gotta go through a teacher.
That's why they put the X's over that, it's 'cause they're edged.
'Cause they're straight edged, yeah. That's why women have been X-ing out their nipples at
dead mouse concerts.
Yeah, they don't want anybody to offer them a cigarette.
Exactly.
You don't know what could be in that cigarette.
One of the biggest dangers of rave is you could break edge by smoking a cigarette.
Did you guys ever claim to be straight edge?
No.
I didn't really know what straight edge was, but I would have if I did.
I was straight edge, but I didn't know what edge was.
I listened to straight edge music, but then I was like, "Oh, I don't like the straight
edge hardcore bands but then I was like oh I that sounds so corny like I know I'm
only listening. I was just like a crazy person in like middle school and high school
I was just like yeah I can't I can't use any substance that will harm my body in
any way I need to be powerful. I was smoking cigarettes at age 12. I am the weapon of the world.
I got really close to getting a straight edge tattoo when I was 13.
- Hell yeah, dude.
- Nice, hell yeah.
Hell fucking yeah.
- I was almost talked into it by my,
at the time, 20 year old brother.
(laughing)
He was like, "Dude, it would be so sick
"if you got a vegan straight edge tattoo.
"You'd be like the only 13 year old with one."
(laughing)
- Was he gonna give it to you?
- He had a friend who he was like,
"Yeah, he's willing to do it."
- Oh my God.
- It's so awesome, dude.
- Dude, that's so fucking funny.
- I should have done it.
It would have been such a funny,
Like I have way stupider tattoos now.
- Right. - You know?
- You should go get it right now.
Whatever the, do you remember what the design was?
You should go get-- - It was gonna be an XVX.
- You should get that on your back,
but like your lower back.
- Yeah, I should get it on the back of my head in red.
- Yeah, that'd be cool.
- But it's one of my biggest regrets.
Actually, and I think it was,
oh, you know what, I think it was gonna be XV bike punk VX.
Because I was into bikes.
That's sick dude.
Nice.
Yeah.
On what where?
It was going to be on my thigh so my mom couldn't see it.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Yeah.
Well you don't let your mom see your thighs?
No.
Yeah not anymore.
Why not?
No.
Number three, stick a small paper under a computer mouse so it can block its light.
Yeah that's a classic.
I don't think anybody should be blocking anybody's light.
We should be building each other up and not breaking and not blocking the light of humanity.
- They wrote this whole thing wrong.
- You need to be a light worker.
- Yeah, you need to be a Blu-ray Indigo child.
And you know what, if--
- Blu-ray, a Blu-ray Indigo child?
- You heard me, motherfucker.
- I'm an Indica child.
- Yeah.
- That's right, like Wiz Khalifa.
- Like Devin the Dude.
- Like Devin the Dude, yeah.
I would never do this prank because I think,
I think the computer is a human right.
- Absolutely.
- I did this prank and they wrote this wrong.
You gotta use clear tape.
I
supposed to replace the mouse with an identical 3d printed mouse that has no
electronics inside whatsoever and when you turn it over it releases noxious gas
that kills you yeah you're supposed to replace it with a mouse made of pure
gold yeah that's the prank but on the bottom it has a little faucet that
sprays out liquid poop into your face now that's a nice sock dude teachers
would love it my mouse I would hate it if my mouse shot poop at me teachers if
- If you're testing to make sure it's real gold
and you bite into it,
(laughing)
and it shoots doo-doos at you, dude.
- Yeah.
Number four, paint a bar of soap with clear nail polish.
This is a good prank.
Actually, I think we talked about this.
I think this was on the list of the first episode
we ever did, which was a prank episode.
- Yeah.
- It wasn't a prank episode, but it was about--
- You pranked the listeners by getting rid of you.
- We pranked the listeners by deleting all those episodes.
- Yeah.
upload them somewhere but they'll be somewhere but they're not if you if you
want to hear us trying to figure out what the fuck this show is little did we know
the 20-minute episodes of us. The giant puzzle piece we needed was Patrick.
And I was only on the fourth episode. The big round, the circular, the fat puzzle piece. The roundest fucking puzzle piece.
Yeah, we were looking at a puzzle that had a giant circle in the middle.
What goes here? And then I saw you from across the street. And I said him.
And then it took me, I was a guest on episode 4 and then it took me, I don't know what, 4
months.
25?
25 episodes.
You're out here sneaking it on.
To sneak yourself in with your fucking shitty Irish magic.
Yeah.
You fucking piece of shit dude.
And now we're married to you.
Anyway, so the bar of soap with clear nail polish, this is a prank because if you touch
something with nail polish on it you become gay.
You become old.
it's a girl thing to have is nail polish yeah so if you walk into the if you walk
into the barbershop and you smell like nail polish dude you are gonna get
clowned on yeah they're gonna cut your hair instead of the entertainer and
they're gonna give you more hair they're gonna give you extension they're gonna
put you in a machine that turns you into a woman like Jeff Goldblum's the fly you
walk into the barbershop ice cube is gonna fuck you up dude yeah what is
Smelling like a woman, smelling like a female.
He's just slowly becoming a woman over the fly,
but it still has the brundle fly like in between stuff.
(laughing)
The guy.
The guy, it's just called the guy.
(laughing)
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
All right, number five here.
Make a cupcake with mustard on the top
instead of frosting.
- Oh boy. - And there's one comment
from anonymous that says, "That sounds weird."
- I would never fall for this one, dude.
There's no yellow-- - You can smell mustard.
- Yeah, mustard's like the stinkiest
fucking thing in the world.
- Right.
- Well, you guys have never had a yellow treat?
- True. - Oh, you've had
a yellow treat.
- I love yellow treat. - You bring the cupcake
up to your face, you smell it,
and you look at the person giving it to you,
and you say, "Wait, is this sweet mustard?"
(laughing)
And then you take a bite.
You go, "Yeah, it's sweet mustard.
Yeah, go for it.
Yeah.
I'd like to see this, but like somebody accidentally uses like a whole grain mustard for the prank.
Yeah, a brown mustard.
Why do you got all these pebbles on the fucking food?
That's sugar.
It's turbinado sugar.
Yeah.
I made a chunky icing.
Chunky sugar.
Number six, cut a paper into an insect figure and put it in a lamp.
An insect figure?
Yeah, I need to think about what that means real quick.
What the fuck is that?
paper into okay paper I know what that is lamp yeah cut insect figure I don't
know maybe like a paper wasp oh okay cut a paper okay make it look like an insect
yeah okay and then put it into a lamp uh-huh so that the person thinks there's
an insect in their lamp yeah you know I was thinking like a paper wasp and then
you kind of just like show that the stinging thing uh-huh
why would a if you put a lampshade on your head oh and then you get and then
you're standing there with the rubber with a slingshot and a paper walk and as
soon as they tried it they're like my lamp isn't turning on as soon as they
try to pull on your cord you shoot them yeah you yell you yelled pedophile
because you're okay I would love to get my cord pulled on like a lamp yeah why
If you can turn it into anything though, why do-
- A bug?
- Yeah, do like Adolf Hitler.
(laughing)
Put a cutout of Adolf Hitler inside the lamp
and they'll go, "What the fuck?"
- Holy shit, we gotta get this guy the frick outta here.
- You go, "Adolf Hitler has come forward in time
"to kill baby me."
(laughing)
No!
That's when you unload on that fucking lamp
and that's the prank.
Now that person's defying new land.
of a person would you have to be to have Hitler time travel to kill baby you?
Really makes you think. That is that is making me think. Yeah. Yeah. Where even
Hitler is, even Hitler himself is disgusted by you. Yeah. Hitler the
epitome of evil. He would never be disgusted by any person no matter the race.
Yeah, unless they were really evil. That's the bar. It's just be any Jewish guy. Yeah, that's true.
If Hitler had time travel, he would go to the future and just kill any dude.
Just kill Moshe Kasher.
That's what he had.
That's why he had them experiment on twins.
He was trying to figure out how to go.
He thought that was the key.
Yeah, it was the key.
Hitler, what a moron.
What a jerk.
That Norm Macdonald joke.
Oh, yeah.
Number seven here.
Get a toilet paper roll and put it on the sink.
Rip the toilet paper roll into pieces as big as half of your thumb.
Mold the toilet paper roll without water so it will look like poop.
After that put the "poop" on someone's chair.
Just poop on their chair.
Poop is not...
Dude, poop is a way better prank.
That's a way better prank.
Yeah.
That's the thing so many pranks just do the thing.
You lose the arts and crafts feel.
This is a do-it-yourself arts and crafts prank.
This is a Pinterest prank.
This is a fusion.
This is a prank for women who like to make things.
True.
And who also can't poop.
So I mean, you have to be conscious of that.
You can make poop out of your ass.
I'm saying women can't make poop out of their ass.
So they have to make it out of toilet paper roll.
Hand crafting an artisanal doo-doo is an arts and crafts--
I'm making--
I'm a poop luthier.
(laughing)
Yeah, I mean I do feel like doing a,
making a crap is a kind of arts and craft.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, definitely more of a craft than an art.
More of a freaking farts and craps if you ask me.
Farts and craps, yeah.
I did do, I did do.
What are you doing?
I'm doing farts and craps.
I was thinking the other day,
my in-laws I think because I just,
while I'm around them I just run to the bathroom.
They think I have like IBS or something,
'cause I just spend, every time I walk into their house,
I'm just like, "Hey, I have to go to the bathroom
"for an hour and look at my phone."
- Yeah, you go in there.
- They think I have a disease.
- You walk into their house and as soon as they see you,
you go, "Ugh!"
And you run to the bathroom and you're like,
"Oh no, I missed!"
- Yeah, I have to keep up appearances,
so I do a whole, I have like a recording that I play.
- Yeah, it's like, you're playing
like a recording like the the uncle in full hired home alone to where he's in
the shower yeah it's you singing that song but in the middle it's just like
just a bunch of fart sounds in the middle of it mm-hmm number eight find
and download a high-resolution cracked screen image on Google Images what set
the cracked screen image as a screensaver on someone's computer and set
too active after a short period of time.
Now this is devilish.
Yeah, if someone says "ha" I wouldn't do this to someone.
Now that would be horrifying.
Yeah.
If someone says "ha" you could make it look like their computer screen is cracked.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
Oh my, wait, that's even fucking worse.
I didn't even think about that.
You just took this prank to the next level.
Are you kidding?
Holy shit.
I was just thinking how...
I thought you were just giving them a stupid...
Yeah, I thought it would just be annoying to switch their screensaver they probably worked
hard on yeah you have to switch it from like a cry like an angel riding a
motorcycle when someone touches my screensaver i go i go bananas i go to
nut shit i go i go the camera style gorilla i go fucking blunderbuss on
their ass dude i spray on him i'm gonna go get hey if you touch my screensaver
i'm gonna give you a taste of my cutlass oh yeah you know what a cutlass is
that's a pirate sword mm-hmm I'm gonna I'm gonna go piracy I'm gonna commit
fire I can smell the doubloons on your ass no I'm coming and I'm sailing into
your house - you better not and I'm gonna get inside your treasure chest and scare
you like I'm gonna sail the seas of all of your toys yeah I take and take as I
please uh-huh I'm going to pillage and plunder I'm gonna burn your bedroom down
I'm gonna go to your toy chest and I'm gonna pillage and plunder it. Oh, I'm gonna fight
I'm gonna fire a big cannon at you. I'm gonna
I'm gonna go into your snack pantry and I'm gonna eat all the grips if you don't fucking watch it
But I'm gonna take all the wash buckle your mom dude gonna take all the oranges
Take all the oranges lemons and limes any kind of citrus fruit out of your house. I'm gonna get you get scurvy. Yeah
You're not gonna have enough
I still don't really know what scurvy is.
I know it has something to do with vitamin C.
Yeah, it's like a vitamin C deficiency
and like you get fucked up teeth.
It fucks your teeth up?
I might have that.
Oh, I think I do too.
I don't need that first.
I think I brushed my teeth three times this month.
Oh man, I--
Yeah.
Yeah, I woke up this morning
after drinking that big ass frozen Marg
and my teeth hurt like shit.
And you were wearing a sombrero.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I had a little painted on mustache
and a big sombrero and I was sitting,
I woke up and I went--
Oh my god, what did I do last night?
(laughing)
- I was just talking like Speedy Gonzales.
- Patrick, you ran really fast.
(laughing)
Oh no.
- Oh no, you woke up drunk, dude.
You're still talking like Speedy Gonzales.
- I'm not drunk.
- Patrick, when you drink,
you always turn into Speedy Gonzales.
- It doesn't matter what you drink.
- Yeah.
- Water, orange juice.
number nine is my favorite one. Fill the donuts with mayonnaise. One of the ultimate pranks
because we're I mean so you know the donuts. Yeah. You know them. You've heard of them.
You have to fill them with mayonnaise. Yeah. The donuts. You're commanded as Christ commanded
fill the donuts with mayonnaise. Yeah. But do you fill it in the middle? I feel like
the only donut this would work for would be a Boston cream. A Boston cream and then you
have to empty it out first. No, every fucking donut's got a hole in the
middle. You fill the hole with mayonnaise. That's obvious though. Yeah. Not if you
put a cloaking device on the donut. So you have to develop an invisible mayonnaise that not only is
invisible but has to... Oh, is that what the movie is? About? Invisible mayonnaise? Yeah, the invisible mayonnaise.
So you develop an invisible mayonnaise and you have to have it... it needs to
learn how to be suspended in the middle of a doughnut too.
Yeah it has to be AI. You have to develop a sentient- You need to have a nanobot mayonnaise.
Yeah a nanaise if you will. Manon- Manon- You already have a mayonnaise. A manobanaise.
Mano- Manonaise. Manonaise. Yeah. Manonaise. There we go. That's the perfect name for the product.
Okay let's make it. Yeah. Manonanonaise. Manonanonaise. Manonanonaise. And it's-
Okay, so here's my pitch, Sharks. It's this, uh, it's an invisible nanobot mayonnaise that you can put
bear with me here, in the donuts. And it smells exactly like pussy.
How is the onion mayonnaise? It's called may no banana nays.
And it's and my name is and that's my name and I may know banana nays and it's named after me.
Alright, so I have to leave now, huh? Okay.
Yeah, fine.
Uh, number ten, attaching-
You didn't even ask for my offer.
[laughs]
My offer-
You just said yes immediately.
Zero dollars.
[laughs]
Number ten, attaching air horn.
I just wanted to tell you about my cool invention.
[laughs]
Yeah, this is just something I had a dream about, and I just-
I didn't even make it.
Going in a shark tank and being like, "Sharks, last night, I had a dream that a giant snowman chased me and my dad."
[laughs]
Pretty cool, huh?
(laughing)
And if I don't watch a movie today,
I'll probably have it again tonight.
(laughing)
Number 10, attach an air horn under someone's seat.
Where do you get an air horn?
- The store. - The station.
(laughing)
- Attach a gun, attach a stolen service weapon
under somebody's seat.
- Yeah. - Oh my God,
I watched the fucking, I watched the greatest videos.
I watched 15 of these today.
This guy makes these videos where he, he just, it's like in Texas. He's like one of
these cop watcher dudes. I think his name is Jake Freeman or something.
That's like his alias. But he just films cops and then he will go up to
cops that are like not doing anything, like cops at gas stations or whatever,
and he'll talk to them like he's a cop. So he'll be like, "So what are you doing
out here sir you have any drugs on you and the cops are just like I don't what
are you so fucking mad it's so funny and they'll start saying the same things so
the guy the guy with the camera be like have you had something to drink today
sir have you been drinking today and the cop be like have you been drinking today
And then the guy will be like, "I asked you a question, sir."
It's so fucking funny.
He had this one cop to let him search his car.
[laughter]
He goes, he's like, "I'm gonna need to see what's in your vehicle."
And the cop's like, "You need to look in my vehicle?"
And the guy's like, "Yep, I'm gonna need to see what's in your bag and stuff."
like okay it's so fucking fun that's sick yeah I've been rewatching recommend him
Caleb did I ever show you lipstick bail bonds yes dude tackle yeah guys who have
like a they have like a jaywalking oh yeah it's he's like yes he's too like
middle-aged like like for lack of a better word like like Facebook grandma's
yeah like they find people with they do I mean they try to do dog the bounty
hunter but with very low-level crimes and they immediately instead of going like
hey we need to take you in so you can pay your your bond or whatever they just say
like oh they go in with you bitch pepper spray and they go the best one is the
the one at the fucking the Arby's where they go in with the pellet guns and they're just shooting them with pellet guns.
It's so funny. Dude, it's the best.
I've been rewatching those. And they all, and they suck. That's the other thing.
Oh, they never get them. They're like weak old women. They never get the perp.
They can't get it. They just like ruin their day.
Yeah. It's just an annoyance at that point. It's so bad.
It's so fucking funny.
I love them.
What are they called? Lipstick bail bonds?
Yeah, lipstick bail bonds.
That's so good.
Number 11, Rickrolling.
Yeah, you know, that's good.
That's a classic.
Now that's a prank.
Uh-huh.
Maybe I'll, maybe the day this comes out I'll post a Rickroll.
Yeah, maybe we should just, maybe there's going to be a surprise at the end of this
episode.
Yeah, maybe we should end this episode.
You know what?
I'll save that.
We can talk about that later.
There may be a surprise at the end of this episode.
Yeah, you might get a nice Rickroll.
12 put frosting and sprinkles on a sponge so it looks like a cake. Who falls for that?
I would fall for that. I would never fall for that. I am so aware and so
actualized I almost never fall for pranks. I'm very good at avoiding them.
I dodge pranks like Neo. I'm pretty good at avoiding pranks. I'm better at traps than pranks which I
find this much more important and useful in life.
So it doesn't really bother me.
- You're better at being caught in traps
that are a giant cage with a stick propping up one side
and there's a banana in the middle of it.
- 'Cause you're a gorilla.
- 'Cause you're a gorilla, 'cause you have a monkey brain
that desires a banana like I desire money.
- Yes.
- You try to pay with banana peels.
- Yeah, banana peels are money to you.
- No, they're a piece of trash.
- You work in the banana peel economy.
- No.
- Yeah.
- You do.
- No.
- You work on the Dole Standard.
Yeah, I do not.
You're trying to get us back on the banana standard like we used to be in 1600 BC.
I'm going to make you get on my banana standard.
And BC stands for before Cameron.
Before Cameron ever had a banana.
Time doesn't exist. I've always been.
You've always been.
What are you looking at?
You've always.
There's just people walking around.
I want to look at the people who are walking around.
Look at something cool on your computer like, uh, like, I don't know, your friends?
No, you guys aren't cool.
Your two friends. What?
I'm way more interested in looking at this guy with a big umbrella.
Oh, you're interested in looking at a guy?
Yeah, with a big umbrella.
Oh, he's looking at a guy?
Is he a zookeeper? And he's taking care of you?
Yeah. Cameron's in his cage.
Yeah, Cameron's in his cage.
He's grabbing the bars and going "ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh" back and forth.
I haven't done that ever.
You muted your microphone but we saw you.
I don't know how to mute my microphone.
Because you're a gorilla.
Yes, but you admit I can't mute my microphone so I never would have made that noise.
Yeah, but you're still a gorilla.
I'm not a gorilla.
Here's a good prank here.
Number 14, I'm going to skip ahead.
Take out the batteries of the remote, hide all the batteries in the house, but before
that, change the channel to something like Bubble Guppies or My Little Pony.
Oh, and turn it on max volume.
Oh god, they just had to put the last nail on the coffin there.
That is fucked up.
That is devilish.
That's diabolical, dude.
Dude, bubble guppies on max volume?
Yeah, I'm gonna freaking kill myself.
I'm gonna shoot a laser beam into my head if I have to listen to that.
Yeah, if I have to watch Backyardigans over and over and over again.
I'm gonna go Dorner.
Yeah, I'm gonna go Dorner mode.
I'm gonna laugh and clap my hands, but I'm not gonna like it.
Put it that way.
- That's my torture response.
I laugh and clap like a seal.
- Yeah, and I go, this is the best show ever,
but I don't mean it.
- Yeah, I'm actually just really,
I'm hating it, but I'm so sarcastic that I can't help it.
- Yeah, this show is so good, I forgot to watch it.
- I forgot to laugh, I'm actually crying
because of how bad it is.
- Yeah, that's me.
- I do really like number 13 that you skipped, Pat.
Number 13 is-- - It's my fault.
Give someone a Krispy Kreme box and put vegetables inside.
That's the donuts.
That's evil.
You know what the biggest--
That's the donuts.
I would say the biggest prank is,
is when somebody gives you a toothbrush for Halloween.
Damn.
Right?
I think a worse one is putting razor blades in the candy.
I think that's a much bigger Halloween prank.
No, that's not even a prank.
At least they're in candy.
That's true.
You can melt the candy down and then freeze it back together.
Or if you just carefully, like me,
like I always hated Tootsie Pops
because I don't like the Tootsie Roll in the middle.
So I would just lick down to like the last layer
around the Tootsie Roll and then throw it away.
- Where the razor blade is.
- Where the razor, that's exactly,
it'd be the same concept.
- Yeah.
- See, you've been defeated yet again.
- I've never been defeated.
- All right, I guess that's the list.
- I guess that is the list.
We finished it up.
- You got a bunch of patrons to read.
- Oh, fuck, we do, don't we?
- Yeah.
- God, hey, that's good.
- I mean it's good, yeah. - Oh, fuck.
- Fuck. - Oh, I hate this so much.
- The last-- - I hate this so much.
- The last time we read these was on St. Patrick's Day,
right?
What day was St. Patrick's Day?
- 17th.
- The 17th?
- Oh, God, yeah. - Really?
- Uh-huh.
- Damn. - That's like a whole--
- That's pages back. - We might have like 50.
- Damn. - We have a ton.
- Let's go. - All right, wait,
I'm finding the beginning.
Let's see here.
17th, 17th, 17th, so we read, okay, alright, alright, I got it.
You guys, should I just go through these?
Yeah, wait, let me find it too.
It starts on March 18th with the first page we're reading.
Jack Lustig, thank you.
Jack Lustig, thank you, Jack Lustig.
Danny Holtz, thanks Danny.
Thank you, Danny.
Um, Dosh.
This is a dash, Dosh, dot, dash, Dosh.
Some morse code kind of person.
Dash.
- Dosh Dat.
- It's a dot, it's a period and a dash.
- It's Dat Fan.
Thank you Dat Fan for becoming a patron.
- Thank you Dat Fan.
- Young Zoe, thank you Young Zoe.
Colin Connealy.
- Thank you Colin Connealy.
- Seth, thank you Seth.
- Seth.
- Seth my abs, my bitch dude.
- Seth McFarlane.
- Seth you my bitch dude.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh I went too far back.
- Andrew Chan.
- Thank you, Andrew Chan.
- Jeff.
- My name Jeff, you guys like that one?
- Yeah, from Jeff Dunham. - I love that one.
- My name Jeff.
- From Jeff Dunham, the movie.
Peter Job, thank you.
- Thank you, Peter Job.
I will give you a Peter Job.
- Thank you to Sandy Rag for upgrading
that fucking pledge, baby.
- Yeah. - That's what I like.
That's what I like to see, Sandy.
- Thank you, Zero Ice.
- Or Zero Ice, more like Very Nice,
because she's very nice of you.
- Yeah, very nice for subscribing.
- Sarah Hennig, thank you to Sarah for,
I don't wanna play with that name, nevermind.
Matthew Whitman.
- Matthew White Man.
- Matthew the White Man.
Matthew White Man.
Thank you, Matthew White Man.
- Christian Tabiri, Taberi.
- Christian Taberi Good.
- Yeah, Christian, Christian, Christian Da, yeah.
Christian DePimp.
Patrick Miles.
Patrick Miles of Miles's Miles.
I would love to walk a mile in your shoes, my friend.
Thomas DeGroff.
Great cartoons, great drawings by Thomas.
No, nothing on their name.
We can't just great cartoons.
Great cartoons, stupid name.
Kawhi Leonard, thank you for,
thank you.
Dan South.
I love your work.
Dan Sal- Salay? Salay? Salay? Man, we suck at reading names. Oh, man. I hope that we read that right.
Thank you to Leo, uh, Gafinowicz. Yeah, oh, Leo Gafinowicz, the ultimate- Just actually
balling out, dude. The ultimate podcast of the about list baller of the month. Yeah,
I would say easily baller of the month. Baller of the year, you know? Yeah. He's the man. Um,
Ryan Whitesell. Oh, Ryan Whitesell. Shout out Ryan Whitesell. Uh-huh.
Um, Andy Piss. Andy Piss. Thank you so much, Andy Piss. Fresh cut fries. That's the best kind of fries.
Thomas Donovan. It's cool. Thomas Donovan. Nice. Ventriloquist. Uh-huh. There we go.
Joshua Van Beekham. Joshua, you got a funny ass name, my man. I respect you. Respect.
Alex. That was smart to not put your last name on here. Uh-huh.
South. South. Thank you South.
Nicole Trant, $10. Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, Cameraheck. That's my boy. You should listen to his band XRARX.
Bandcamp.com. Really good math core. Will do.
Shout that out.
Michael. Man, we got my middle name subscribing, baby.
We got a lot more people to read.
Yeah, John Smith, I love your work in, uh, in Pocahontas.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-huh.
I love your colonial, uh, style.
Hannah, shout out to Hannah.
Um...
Shout out to Shane...
Jay Bell.
Shout out to Shane Gillis.
Shane Bell.
Uh, Seth Kombrink.
Shout out Seth Kombrink.
Shout out Jace.
I wonder if that's that racist guy that I know from New Orleans.
I'll say no.
Shout out to Jace, Avery Edison.
Shout out to Avery Edison.
Yeah. Richard Murphy.
Shout out to Richard Murphy.
I know Richard.
Richard made a post about being a patron
about how they made $100.
Richard, shout out to you.
Andrew Perry.
Shout out to Andrew Perry.
Shout out to Hans--
Arbitz and Hicks.
Shout out Hans.
I'm gonna say that's our only Hans,
so we could probably just get away with saying Hans.
Yeah, that's true.
shout out to commander bacon 2012 for subscribing to us on youtube
shout out to david that's my dad and then also david tamburello two davids in a row
oh yeah we had a david back to back we went david mode uh-huh nick visotsky thank you shout out
shout out to wide jim shout out wide jim baby wide jim i i'll say you you have the best name
on the so far yeah Alex Freyer shout out Alex Freyer Sean Sean Lander pridgin
lander pridgin and we'll we'll scurbo Oh shout out to a shout out to Larry J oh
yeah thanks Larry oh yeah cast about list official accountant yeah we have an
account is helping me figure out how to not get fucked by the IRS I respect you
Go follow Larry on Twitter.
Yeah, what is his @?
It's Larry J something.
There's underscores in there though.
To search Larry, I'm sure you'll find it.
Underscore Larry J underscore.
That's the official pot accountant.
We love you.
Yeah, so that's--
Oh, and we're gonna change the $10 tier, I think.
Oh, we are?
Yeah. Oh, okay.
We talked about this, Patrick.
Why did you say that like a question?
we just did this after the patrons read I don't know if they're gonna should we
edit this so this goes before the patrons no we'll just talk about it we'll
just post about it also yeah just wanted a heads up yeah but the $10 tears
changing $10 tears changing to what to your fat ass getting eaten by a little
tiny goblin god damn it owned fucking bitch
wait what's that behind you what you have someone there's someone that I
I knock it on your window.
What are you talking about?
What the fuck?
Who is that?
Oh no!
NO!
*Gunshot*
Oh my god!
Oh my god, they shot Cameron in the head!
They just shot Cameron!
Fuck!
We're just kidding.
Oh my god, April fools to you!
We got you, you fucking bitch!
Oh my god, you guys are so stupid.
You're so stupid!
You're all so stupid!
You're such a fucking idiot, dude.
You are all fucking stupid!
Oh my god!
I am in my car though.
And it's really cold in here and I'm gonna get out.
Alright.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]