You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Woo.
- All right, we're here with, we got Bill on the line.
We're zooming, we're zoomed up.
- Mm-hmm.
- First international call we've done.
- Yeah.
- Oh, how's that?
- This is crazy.
We're going worldwide, baby.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, podcast about us.
about this worldwide. The world domination episode. First European, um, yeah. No, Leo.
Oh Leo, yeah, what am I thinking? Well, no, he's British, that does not count. That's
true. That's actually true. Yeah, that is a good point. First good European. Yeah. But
yeah, Bill, thank you for coming, you know. Have you been, what's it like in, what country
Where do you live in?
Sweden.
Sweden, yeah.
What's shit like there?
Are you guys trapped inside?
Well, it's kind of, we're getting, our government is getting critiqued from everyone right now
because we haven't really done anything.
Nice, you seem to be, you know, chilling.
Yeah, I mean everything is kind of open.
They're sort of just expecting everyone to not go outside.
And not get sick.
And I don't think it's working that well.
A lot of people are getting sick disproportionately from other Scandinavian countries, so probably
going to lock everything down.
Nice, dude.
I'm excited.
That's probably the good way to go.
But you guys don't have guns or anything.
Nope.
Unfortunately not.
I really don't have a gun.
Can you like, will they put you in jail for saying that on a podcast?
No, it's not that bad.
I mean, today I was out, I wanted to get some like,
some kind of Tylenol or something,
but I couldn't find anything good.
And I just, I would trade every single part of this,
you know, shitty socialist welfare state
for just access to guns and like Tylenol
with codeine or something.
- Yeah.
So you want to live, so socialism doesn't matter to you, guns and drugs.
Exactly.
I feel like if you have a gun you can make your own socialism.
There we go.
We gotta fly Bill out to Arizona and just like drop you in Albuquerque like a battle
royale game out of a helicopter and just be like, just see how much damage you can cause
before they extradite you to like some Ikea living room.
(laughing)
- Just carve out new Sweden.
- Yeah, yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it sounds awesome.
You're drinking some made up beer.
- Yes.
- I see.
- Exactly.
- What's it called?
- Hengelhofer or something?
- Almost.
- Hopstetter.
- Hockenberry.
- Hopping buddy.
(laughing)
- The hopping buddy.
It sounds delicious.
I'm drinking a Coors Light, you know.
At 3am.
Or 6pm.
I thought, yeah, at 3am.
Fuck!
There's nothing wrong with that.
There's a, I mean.
Yeah, it's a light beer.
It's like, doesn't count.
Exactly, yeah.
It's a, it might as well be a Diet Coke, which I'm also drinking.
So I have both.
You should mix them.
You should put them in a cup and mix them.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm mixing them in my mouth though.
I take one sip and then the other.
You should get like a straw system.
Yeah.
I could get, what I should do is get one of those funny hats that holds two cans.
Genius.
And put one in both.
That's what those are for, for mixing drinks.
That's right.
That's how bartenders mix the drinks.
You guys put rum and coke, they put one can of rum and one of coke, they suck it in and
then spit it into a glass.
Oh, could you imagine a can of rum?
Yeah.
That would taste.
They probably have that.
like a thing yeah a can of rum don't you guys have bag milk no no you're not that
weird oh I lived in Canada for a while and I saw that there and wild it's so
just just doesn't it looks like they took that out of the cow just surgically
remove the milk membrane out of the cow it's like those extraterrestrial maimings
when someone's cut out the like the vagina of a cow or something?
Yeah, exactly.
Did you just cut out the milk bag?
And do you just cut off a corner?
I've never, I've never...
No, it has, it has got a nipple on it.
Yeah, so it's to get the full cow experience.
It's pink.
Yeah, it's a pink, it's a pink bag full of white goo.
Yeah, it's not even milk.
Oh, fuck.
It's bad.
It's bag milk.
It's a different liquid.
Yeah, it's not from a cow.
It's from a bag.
That's where they get it from.
God, dude.
I'm so glad I live in America, the greatest country on earth.
I wouldn't live anywhere else.
Look, we got to get you out here, Bill.
We got to move you out here.
That would be sick.
Let's do it.
I love that.
We're just going to funnel the Patreon money to you and fund your reality TV show about
you and America.
We're gonna make the podcast about List compound.
Yeah, yeah.
It's gonna be.
(laughing)
Yeah, exactly.
Like the, what's his name?
Like Anthony.
David Koresh or?
(laughing)
No, we're gonna make a compound media,
but it's part about List.
Oh, okay.
Oh, did you say Dave Anthony?
No, I said.
(laughing)
The guy from the dollop?
Yeah, the guy from the dollop.
I hate you, dude.
I'm sick of you.
I'm sick of you already.
i'm replacing the bill
yet they're not
so i don't know
yes yes
has uh... we'll need a uh... yet that's too fat for us we can get a lot of
yeah bill is like a bill's perfect he's right in the sweet spot but we're gonna
move patrick to sweden and bill here
patrick
it's
it's just me trying to find it
does it look like a dollar-packed cigarette
using american money
he's confused why it doesn't work
but that could happen
god's is this the end of the
pockets we
he was a little bit
they are speaking at the end of the
like speaking with you for a few minutes
uh... you know you are that
yeah
you know i'm always saying you're always races and yet
uh...
all right uh... we have a list of a from the top tens it's it's uh...
do you have a bill it's top ten coolest names yes
yet nobody none of us have uh...
very interesting names at all
no middle names edward so is mine
uh... shit fuck you do you need to
goddamnit is your name is your middle name also edward bill
it's the
but i mean steve
that's cool all right we got a cool yeah
yeah all right
out of all of our all of us are three names and one of us has one cool and
the
that's the coolest
of fucking skyrim name
i love it though
it sounds good
uh...
yeah my middle name is michael it's just a it's a baby's name
Yeah, that's a name for a little kid.
I know, it's so...
You look like a big baby.
No, I don't.
Yeah, you do.
I will.
I think I'm gonna shave my head today.
Dude, if you shave your head, you're gonna look like fucking Baby New Year.
You should shave your head.
I won't.
You should pull out...
Yeah, you will.
I won't.
You should pull out all your teeth except for one of the front teeth.
One?
It's just one!
Should I become like a prospector?
Like a baby.
Like a cartoon.
No, not like a baby.
You should have one curly hair on top of your head.
You get one big curly cartoon hair.
You should look like that monkey from Super Monkey Ball with the big spiral ears.
No, I'm not going to look like that.
I'm going to look like Jason Statham, the transporter.
And I'm going to do stuff like he does in Crank.
High voltage.
You're going to be a transporter, but you're going to roll around in a monkey ball.
No, I will not roll around in a monkey ball to protect my, the person.
You're going to go collect bananas for a shadow corporation.
I have no interest in collecting bananas.
I just want to shave my head and do cool ninja stuff, which I am going to do.
I'm going to do...
What kind of kung fu does Jason Statham do?
Is he trained?
You say murder fu?
Murder fu?
Yeah.
Is that where you...
If you kill anybody with karate, it's a new thing.
That's like what John Wick does.
It's like murder fu.
He does some sort of kung fu thing, but it involves shooting people.
Is that...
Is that real? Is that a real thing?
It's like bullets with your hands.
Sounds like a real thing.
I will give you that much, Bill.
It does sound real.
Yeah, you go into like a
a kung fu
learning place and being like
no, I want to learn murder food.
It's called a dojo, but
I'll let that slide.
Isn't a dojo Japanese?
No, you're thinking of Mojo Jojojo,
the Japanese monkey from
Yeah, the Powerpuff Girls.
You.
Short little monkey.
Yeah, that's you.
You're an evil green monkey.
No.
Yeah, you are.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Which one are you saying, Pat?
Who are you saying it is?
What?
Mojo Jojo?
Mojo Jojo.
If anyone looks most like Mojo Jojo, it's gotta be you.
It's gotta be Bill.
No.
I have no idea who you guys are talking about.
You've never seen, I guess you didn't grow, did you grow up watching any American cartoons?
Yeah, the Simpsons.
All right, well, stop.
I'm not gonna say anything.
watching any American cartoons? Yeah, The Simpsons. Alright, we'll stick to The Simpsons. That's my frame of reference for American cartoons. I've seen like two episodes of King of the Hill.
Oh, you got to get on that dude. Yeah. We watch King of the Hill, we'll have you on
again and just do King of the Hill stuff. Yeah. We'll only reference King of the Hill. Yeah.
just so you get it. The Swedish version of King of the Hill is called Lord of the
Mountain. Exactly. Yeah that's the dubbed version. Yeah. Lord of the Steak. It's called Steak of the Hill.
Yeah and it's eight guys in a backyard all sipping whatever fucked up beer
your dad's. Just going "da". That's German man, come on. That's Russian. I don't know.
Is that Russian? Da is Russian. Unless it's also German. Da means dad. What? No. Da doesn't
mean dad. Yeah it does, it's Scottish. You're thinking of dada, which is baby language.
Yeah, that's what Patrick calls his dad.
Yeah, that's what I call my dad.
Da-da.
I call my dad Dada.
Alright, so, uh,
Bill, if you, if
the Simpsons is your frame of reference,
just know that, um,
in this podcast, Patrick
is, uh, uh, Ralph
Wiggum. Yep. Uh,
I'm Homer and Cameron is Apu.
Okay.
I was gonna say that Cameron was Marge.
No, he's definitely a poo.
Get to know him.
He's a poo.
He really is.
I think he should do the accent right now.
He does it off mic.
Right now he's doing a voice because he
went to a production school.
I feel insecure about my accent.
About my real accent.
I like to cover it up when I'm recording.
Yeah, he thinks people will get the wrong idea
about him if he does the accent.
Yeah, they'll stereotype him based on his accent.
Yeah.
Alright, um, top ten coolest names.
Number one, um, Neo.
Right off the bat.
Yeah, I mean I guess my question would be like, is there any other Neo besides Neo?
It's not really a name.
I've never met a guy who's like, "Hi, I'm Neo."
i've never had like a little bit all of garden with the new york and about the
singer
new are
uh... i think there's i think he has periods between the you know it's it's
an e_t_ dash why i think i'm pretty sure it's been a short for neil young
yet this is uh... yet i i i guess it is a cool name
not sure it's number one
the on the first few comments on this are insane
uh... there's with the one comment here says
the only meal that i know is a psychopathic dog that lights like seeing
fire and literally tries to catch bullets
i'm surprised he's still alive especially after attempting to eat a
bottle rocket that was about to go out
Someone's dog names is Neo.
Someone named their dog after fucking the Matrix dude?
Come on.
That's boss.
And then it tries to catch bullets.
This dog has no idea what Neo's supposed to do.
He's supposed to dodge bullets.
Not the opposite.
He's not here to live up.
But it was about to launch the ball rocket so in my head he's picking it clean out of
the air.
That's impressive.
Yeah.
he's young you know what they've got to get it
and that the comment right after that says
i think it sounds like a big cat that was born in every month of the year
no
what what that could mean
that that might be a reference to something that we just don't know
uh... would love to be friends with a cool name like this
loves his love my daddy
dark night daddy's names neo dark night two thousand five comments every time i
hear me out by think of a matrix
uh... matrix
also did the dark night come out of two thousand five
but they cannot you doesn't need to get
sorry
wrong
bad username one person here says
one word
matrix
this name makes me think of only one movie
the matrix
somebody says
i feel this name would go with any personality
i don't think that's true
no mostly just a guy who's uh...
mostly just keanu reeves
yeah mostly just keanu reeves
someone said it just sounds cool
i mean that's true
Yeah.
Yeah, we're overthinking it. It just sounds cool.
Somebody says, "LOL my name's Neo."
My favorite is, "I dated a Neo once. He was obsessed with porn."
Hold on baby, I have to go watch porn.
And then he just plugs his computer into the back of his fucking head.
And then he cums his pants. Cums starts bleeding out of his eyes.
someone else on this bucket and someone else just said
piper is a cool name on the hip
that's just a different
bucket made added to the list and fucking bitch that's only says dog name
the one dog
the doggy catches fireworks uh... i assume of his mind
like
the real meal
uh... are number two
bruno
the socks
that's what it is
Yeah, is there a lot of Brunos in your life?
I don't think there's ever been a Bruno in my life.
No, let me introduce you to a little movie
by a man named Sasha Baron Borat.
Oh shit, I watched Borat yesterday.
For the first time?
No, no, no, no, for the 11th time.
Oh Jesus.
It's still great.
Oh, it's the best movie ever.
Every single time I smoke weed,
I have like a panic attack in my brain
and then I look at my girlfriend and I say,
I have to watch Borat.
The only cure.
Yes, it is the only cure.
I wrote a, I had to write an academic paper
and I didn't know what to do it on
for my fucking sex and comedy class
and I just wrote it about Borat.
What was your thesis?
It was called a sex and comedy class
and I needed to fill a credit,
So I took that and I don't remember.
- Don't act like you're trying to fill a credit.
No, you wanted to take it.
You wanted to take that class.
- I did.
- You saw that class.
- Before I went to the first class
and the guy was like,
"If you take out your phone, I'm gonna mark you absent."
- So why didn't you switch?
- 'Cause it was the day after the ad drop date.
- If it was the first class, it couldn't have been.
- It was 'cause we--
- No.
- It was a memorial day.
- Patrick was the teacher of the class.
- No, I wasn't.
- He was.
I did not teach the class.
He taught it.
Yeah, he would bring in various silicone toys and fuck them in front of the class while
he was laughing like the Joker.
And that was the whole class.
And then everybody got an F.
An F for fucking.
I gave all my students F for fucking because it was a sex class.
I want to know more about this class.
It was just academic bullshit.
It was just like, "Oh, well, fucking..."
I don't know why you did that stuff.
It was like that, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, just shit like that.
All MLA formatted, just duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh,
duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh.
But I got a D minus in that class.
Woo.
Nice.
It's because you weren't good enough at sex with the teacher.
No.
Yeah, that's because I hate sex.
The final quiz.
Yeah.
The pop quiz at the end.
Yeah, have funny sex.
(laughing)
But yeah, Bruno, bad name.
Not a good name.
- There's a comment here that says,
"Because there aren't enough gay words already."
(laughing)
- Yeah, throw another, yeah, fuck it,
throw another one on the pile.
Bruno.
Yeah, we already have Stig.
Throw Bruno on there.
I'm sorry, Bill.
- That's all right.
- I'm a monster.
- Oh, Bruno Mars.
uh... bruno mars
that's one of the comments is i'd like bruno because he is like the singer
bruno mars
and even think about bruno mars i forgot about him
uh... but i don't like to do the person who says this was this terrible i could
think of a better name how about a dolph
the
selected prospectors apparently
yeah he he got a little bit
I'm hopping on the top tens.
Yeah top ten easiest post offices to shoot up.
God he would crush it on this website dude.
Someone says sounds like a very 80s disco dancer with an alfro and sideburns.
An alfro?
That's when Alf sits on your head.
Yeah when he sits his asshole over your head like a cap.
Yeah, and he sits there and he's like, "Hey, what am I, chopped liver?"
You know, classic Alf shit.
Is that what he says?
I never watched Alf.
That wasn't, um, that wasn't really my scene.
The dad from Alf, I remember finding this out as a kid, the guy who played the dad on
Alf was addicted to crack.
There's a video of him.
That's boss.
There's a video of him with a sex worker smoking crack.
I mean, wouldn't you also be addicted to crack if you were an actor?
you had your most popular co-star was a fucking monster puppet?
if you were alph's dad.
some aardvark?
if you if you had a baby that was alph
yeah if you had to deal with alph's bullshit all day you might smoke crack too
that's true this guy with his fucking snout trying to eat my cat all day
yeah he was never the same after alph ate his cat on set
Al started hanging up signs on set that it was like Tuesday bring your cat to work.
The last comment on Bruno is a little poem here.
It's a beautiful poem.
Yeah, it says, "Bruno, wow, amazing.
Bruno just sounds so awesome.
Bruno has some amazing flair to it."
It's really beautiful.
That is, that's incredible.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
I want to put that on a card.
Put that on a card and give it to my friend Bruno.
Yeah.
Uh, number three, this is a terrible name.
Uh, Holden.
Yeah.
Someone's read a book.
Like, yeah.
I know a lot of homeschooled Holdens.
Yeah.
That's probably not good.
If your name is Holden, they make you homeschooled.
school. You're not allowed to go to normal school.
Because if you go to public school then you'd get set, your name would turn into Holden
my balls. Yeah, I do think kids with stupid names should,
they just shouldn't be allowed to go to public school. It's just for their own sake. You
know, you shouldn't be around other children if your name is Holden or Suck My or something
like that. Or like Jeffrey Homo or something like that. Yeah, Peter Gawah. Just don't let
the kid, there's no need for that. Homosexual Michael. Kids are going to take that the wrong
way. Black David. It's just not a good, is that a celebrity in your country Bill? Black
David is something like that, right? He's Santa Claus's friend?
Yeah, that's a Dutch thing, right?
Yeah, Schwarza Peter.
Yeah, exactly, Black Peter.
But he wouldn't be allowed in public school.
Mr. Poop, if you name your kid Mr. Poop.
Yeah, Cartman.
You're asking for a world of trouble sending your kid Cartman to school.
Just a bad idea. Yeah.
Um, let's see the comments. Uh, that's my name.
Holden. Holden Maccock. Nice. See, what did I tell you?
That's just a bad idea. Just all around. What are you doing, Holden?
Number four is Miles.
That's a pretty normal name.
Yeah, that one sucks.
Or, I'm sorry, Bill, Meters.
Ah!
Ah, ha ha!
Ah, fuck, dude.
God damn it.
Caleb, lay off the guy.
Yeah, come on, man.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
I come on here as a sign of, you know, as a gesture of good faith.
And I do anti-Swedish racism to you.
To heal the fractures between our nations.
and yeah you're gonna start a war Caleb yeah this is it this you came this is a
diplomatic mission yeah we're trying to yeah we're trying to heal the the divide
between America and Sweden Miles I just think of tails yeah from Sonic miles
Miles Prower?
Yeah.
It says, "This guy is the beast."
I know a guy named Miles, he's good at no-scoping me, from Eli HBK.
That's fucked up.
Someone says, "I always use this in my books."
Miles has good manners, and that's what matters.
That's nice, dude.
It was nice dude.
I don't think I've ever met a Miles, honestly.
It's my nephew's middle name.
I feel like that's like a smart guy name.
This kid Miles that went to summer camp with me in middle school used to pretend to be a dog.
Yeah, what did I say?
It's the name of a very intelligent guy.
I only think of Mikey Miles or Mickey Miles.
Oh, Mikey Miles is definitely... Mickey Miles. I'm just imagining him with big Mickey Mouse
ears. Yeah, that's what we call Mickey Mouse here. It's Mickey Miles.
Number five, Trinity. This is... I mean, I don't know what...
Yeah, Morpheus is going to be later on.
It's funny that like Neo is a name I've never heard. Trinity is a name I've heard probably
50,000 times in North Carolina. Yeah. Yeah. People with Trinity. Yeah. Yeah. So it's like
a, like, um, like a girl with a nose ring who's been pregnant for like 15 years and
has like, uh, um, has like a tattoo on the small of her back that says like Brad and
tribal font. Yeah. Is there like a similar name to like Nevaeh? Would you say someone
Novea is a crazy name.
Novea is awesome. It's heaven backwards.
Fuck.
You never heard that one?
Never.
That was a big thing for a while.
Novea?
Yeah, it's like a white trash name. I think.
Damn, that's good.
Very good.
For me, it's Trinity Crystal.
Yeah.
Crystal is just a crazy name.
Yeah, that's after the hot sauce.
Yeah. No, it's after the sliders.
What is a crystal slider?
slider. What the fuck is that? It's a food chain in the south. Oh. Well don't fucking
don't come up in here talking about southern food chains. Yeah me and Bill are the only
southerners here. Yeah. Bill's a southerner at heart. Yes. Yeah we've talked about this.
He wants uh he wants uh 40 acres and a mule. I want 40 acres a mule and an insane cache
of weapons yeah yeah he wants like a century gun yeah I want to die in like
some sort of shootout with the ATF. The Aqua Teen Hunger Force? I'd love I just
Bill in America just like searching for the ATF weapons just drugs just like
Like, just fucking, he flies into Miami and just like, three hours later he's sitting
on a big throne of cocaine.
Yeah.
A castle built of skulls.
He's like, "Come at me, ATF.
I fucking flew all the way out here."
I got a warthog from Halo.
Yeah.
Yeah. Um, Trinity, is there any good comments on that?
Reminds me of the Matrix and the Holy Trinity. Love it.
You Christian Matrix fan.
Reminds me of Christians. Love that.
[Laughter]
Love that shit.
Trinity is such a cool name. I picture a powerful/pretty girl wearing a purple dark hood.
You should definitely agree with me. Well, it's your choice. I even used this name on Builder Buddies.
The fuck is Builder Buddies?
It's like Bob the Builder. It's the Bob the Builder Battle Royale.
That would be a good game. That would be sick dude. You get to be a...
I would go crane. I would try to be a crane. Yeah? Yeah. I guess or a bulldozer.
I'd be Bob. The thing is all of them they have they have faces so they can easily be...
you know they have brains. It's true.
I like the person who said I named my tin foil person Trinity.
What the fuck is a tinfoil person?
You never made a tinfoil person?
Why is it called... I imagine some sort of figurine you make, but why would you call it a person?
Yeah, a tinfoil being that I made.
This is my tinfoil cousin.
Tinfoil nephew.
Yeah, I don't know what a tinfoil person is. Is that a thing?
I don't know, you just make a... you know, use it like modeling clay.
I can guess what it is.
what it is.
I'm a silver guy.
No you can't.
You're not that imaginative.
Alright.
There's someone commented something in a different language.
I'm trying to translate it.
That looks like Polish.
It's uh, it is Slovak.
And it says, it says he read it and knows the Slovak is cool.
So on, on Trinity somebody just posted that they have the coolest language?
Is that a Slovakian name?
Trinity?
I don't think, I think it's an English word.
That's the name of their president.
Yeah.
Trinity Slovak.
Trinity Suvlaki.
Yeah, Suvlaki.
Number six, Lady.
Nah.
Nah, it's a worse name.
No, it sucks.
Yeah.
That's like naming your kid like, Oven.
Man.
Yeah.
That's like naming your kid like, Oven.
That's like naming your kid "man".
Is that naming your kid "oven"?
Yeah.
How did you go "oven"?
There's a clear...
There's a clear opposite of "lady".
I thought that was too obvious.
So you went "oven".
Patrick likes to go for the niche jokes.
He's kind of a comedian's comedian.
I'm kind of a crazy guy.
"Lady". Someone says "Lady and the Tramp".
I love that movie.
This is a good name for a girl dog, but not for a human being.
Correct. I agree. That's not a human being.
Yeah, ladies are not human beings.
So you heard it here first.
Yep.
Someone just says, "If you say rubbish, you are rubbish."
Whoa.
And then under it, it says, "Rubbish stupid."
Damn.
Which I like to imagine the first one came first.
Yeah.
Yeah, and that person is just spitting in their face.
They're just calling rubbish stupid.
So the name Lady isn't very good, but how about naming your kid The Tramp?
Oh!
Naming your kid any- honestly if you just add "the" to their name, whatever you decided
on, you're like "the Brad."
This is my son, The Brad.
I'm naming my kid The Son.
What about The Oven?
Now that's funny.
That'd be some nutso shit.
Pat, you suck dude.
No I don't.
You suck so bad.
Nah, you trash.
You're rubbish.
You better take it.
You know what happens if you say someone's rubbish Pat?
You know what that means?
Means you're rubbish.
Don't agree.
I agree.
You're gonna have to.
Alright, number seven is Emily.
No.
This is terrible.
Yeah.
There's such a huge drop off from Neo.
I talk shit on Neo.
Neo is a fucking asshole.
Neo is the only cool name.
The reason, the thing is, there's a direct correlation
of like cool and commonality, or and uncommonality.
Like the more common a name is, the less cool it is.
That's why Neo is number one.
Because there's only one Neo.
- Well everyone is naming their damn kid--
- And there's two Brunos.
- Everyone is naming their damn kid Neo
after the Matrix dropped.
- Oh you know that's what happened.
- The Neo boom, the Neo boom of 1999.
- The Neo boomers.
Yeah.
Dude.
There's got to be 50 or 60 of them.
The Neo Boomers.
That's sick.
Just all working at GameStop.
Yeah.
They don't even have to apply.
They just...
There are diminishing returns on this list.
I mean we start with Neo, which obviously, that's the coolest name.
That's boss.
It should be number one.
Then Bruno, which I don't personally agree with, but it's at least different.
Then we go to Holden, Miles, and then we come up with another cool one, Trinity.
The lady, and now we're at Emily.
Was it just gonna keep going?
Yeah, it's a huge drop off to Emily.
Yeah, this one has a lot of comments though.
22 comments.
Probably a lot of people pointing out the obvious.
Probably a lot of people saying--
Somebody says, "I think it is a stop it name."
(laughing)
And you're right.
This is extremely stop it.
This is dumbo stop it.
I will say it.
No.
Someone says--
Someone says, "My sister's name, laugh out loud."
(laughing)
Someone--
It's just Emily.
maybe the same guy just says she's hot.
She's hot. Emily? Oh, Emily? She's hot. She's hot, dude. She's hot as shit. Oh my god.
Oh, there's one comment here saying, listen to these different spellings. There's a spelling of
Emily, E-M-I-L-E-E or E-M-M-A-L-E-I-G-H. What do you guys think of those ones?
That is the old that is even more white trash than like crystal is like absolutely
Trying to trying to do like like searching the way they spell their names as they search it on Google and then look at the phonetic
spelling
It's pig Latin they just add add vowels
Consonant
And this it also twin girls name them Emily and Everly or Emily and Everly or is spelled different
Everly, can you imagine that? Everly, geez.
What about Neverly?
These are my daughters Everly and Neverly, they're twins.
We like one more, obviously.
Number 8, Jason.
But it's spelled... Jason but spelled J-A-C-E-N.
Yeah, no this is from the original Star Wars EU.
This was Han Solo's son's name.
Who later became Darth Cadis.
Darth Cadis, huh?
So it's different from Kylo Ren?
Yeah, Darth Gatissss.
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, like Gayson.
Gayson Holo.
Gayson Homo.
Yeah.
That's what I would call him if I was in Star Wars.
Yeah, I would have said that to Han Solo's face.
I would have said that and he would have force choked me and I wouldn't care.
I would have said, "You're choking another man?
Kind of gay, buddy."
Based on Jason Solo, Patrick, is this a cool name?
Is Jason Solo a cool guy?
No.
Not really.
Cool why?
He, um, god, what was, oh yeah, he just became a Sith Lord.
That's cool.
I think he was responsible for killing Chewbacca or something.
That's extremely cool.
That's sick.
Yeah.
I don't, look, I don't remember much about the story of Jason Solo.
All you know is whoever killed Chewbacca is not cool.
Yeah.
Seriously not cool.
Patrick is in love with Chewbacca.
Chewbacca's cool.
He looks like your mom.
What?
Yeah.
I'm serious dude.
This sucks.
And he sounds like your mom.
You.
He sounds like you.
He sounds like your mom.
Yeah, your mom walks around your house with a crossbow and shoots you if you don't do
your chores like Chewbacca.
That's true.
And then she walks into her bedroom and I eat her pussy and she does the
It's called a bowcaster you idiot. No, she has a crossbow. It's a bowcaster in Star Wars
Yes, like she's Chewbacca in Star Wars and she's your mom in real life
No
God you ate shit right then baby. Yeah, I did. I did. You know what it takes a big man to admit it
Yeah, you got it. So I turned your mom into Chewbacca and then I fucked her
You got to admit it
I'll admit that I was wrong, but I would never admit that you turned my mom into Chewbacca.
I did, dude.
I went to the wig shop and I stapled all the wigs to her.
She asked me to though.
And then I fucked her.
No, she didn't.
Yeah, I fucked her with my Star Wars penis.
It's true.
You can ask her.
No.
She'll do the noise to you.
- Number nine, number nine.
Jen with two N's.
- What's that other N for?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- We don't need that other N.
- Yeah.
- Come on dude.
- Why do you need that?
You don't need Jen, Jen already has an N.
- Yeah.
- I think the top comment on this disqualifies it
immediately, it says two of my teacher's names are Jen.
So, if it's a teacher's name.
- Yeah, if that's a damn teacher's name.
- Yeah.
Yeah, again, it's like naming your kid Adolf.
You know?
It's true.
Naming your kid after a teacher, that's...
He did teach, you know, in a, you know,
sort of a lifestyle.
Adolf, I mean.
Oh.
(laughing)
He was kind of the, that's why nobody liked him.
He was a teacher.
He was the ultimate teacher.
Yeah.
The logical extreme of being a teacher.
yeah he was a he really kind of invented timeout now that i think about it
detention
to ministry
well it's a yeah
now exactly
uh... number ten is is jenna
which i think is a uh...
think that's the name of uh... the made at the name is that classic man
jenna is the name of jason solos twin sister
i really wish i was making that up but no
that's who kills jason solos jenna solo she's like she's the everly to his emily
yes i'm pretty sure jenna jenna's also a mage in a world of warcraft i think yeah i think that's
true which i know from hearthstone somebody just says somebody says i'm horny
just the name jayna just imagining what that bitch is built like is just fucking
It's fucking popping my desk up with my penis right now.
Sometimes that's all you need.
Sometimes all- oh dude, one time I was with this kid, this fucking weird ass dude.
We were at the beach and he was like my dad's friend's son.
And so he was always around but he's a very bizarre guy.
He used to- he like- we would play video games together and he would cry when he lost up until he was like 17 years old.
So one time we were at the beach together-
You should just say it was Cameron.
It was Cameron.
No.
We were at the beach together in high school and there was some girl was like walking on
the boardwalk right next to the beach and he was like, "That girl is so cute."
And I was like, "Cool man, you should go say what's up and get her number."
And he was like, "Her number?
All I need is a name."
*laughter*
And me and my dad were like, "What the fuck is wrong with you, dude?"
"What are you gonna do with her name?"
"Dude, what the fuck does that mean?"
"He's gonna enchant her."
"He's Jason Bourne."
*laughter*
"Yeah, you're gonna kill her?"
"Is that what you're gonna do?"
"He's gonna do a spell, dude. You need their true name."
Yeah and her name is Jaina and he immediately got a bow hair.
Shot out of his trunks.
He got it caught in the mesh of his trunks.
Yeah it went through one of the holes in the mesh.
It squished out like play-doh into a bunch of different...
His mushy blob dick.
"Ah, my dick fell through my quicksilvers."
Can I get your name?
I'm walking up to her with your amorphous goo dick.
It's like, "I need your name."
It's detached from your body and it's sliding down your...
Don't pay attention to that.
I need a name.
Look, I just sneezed, okay?
That's what that is.
I dropped my ice cream.
Just talk to me.
I need a name.
It's crawling toward her across the ground.
It's just some gum I sat in.
It's fine.
That's my little brother, don't look at me, he loves attention.
And don't give me your number because I don't need it.
Don't you dare, bitch.
If you give me your number, that thing's going on your face.
I'm horny.
And then you scoop it up with a dustpan and walk away.
You pick it up with one of those fish picker upper things from an aquarium, the little net
thing.
The net, yeah.
Sorry, they don't have a word for that in English.
Yeah, they deleted net.
Number 11, Clem.
My grandma had a cat named Clem.
So that's, I just think of a cat when I think of Clem.
Sorry!
Clem's pretty good, honestly.
I'd have no qualms with this one.
Someone says, someone says, "That rhino from Lazlo" and then a yum emoji.
I don't know what that means.
I like how two people just said yes.
Yes.
Number 12, Kesha.
No dollar sign though.
No dollar sign for this.
Yeah, it doesn't count.
You guys remember if you tried to put a Kesha song onto your iPod Nano,
it would come up as "Kee-ha" because it couldn't do the dollar sign?
That ever happen to you?
Nope.
Sorry I never had an iPod Nano. I wasn't fucking loaded.
It was my friend's iPod Nano.
Yeah, I just had records, buddy.
I had an iPod Shuffle for so long.
I had records and books.
saying my uncle's had to sing the song I would if I wanted to hear if I wanted to
hear we will rock you I just had to get all my uncles together in a stadium and have them start
laughing
that's how we did it back in the day yeah eating my uncle old English malt liquor
till he starts singing taking requests yeah sitting on the stoop doing doing
doing fucking Leonard Skinner songs together.
That's how it used to be.
It's my uncle singing.
I'm like a bird by Nelly Furtado.
Nephews on the chorus.
The nephews on the verses nephews on the chorus.
Those are the rules of uncle singing.
Yeah, the nephew uncle choir.
The nephew uncle tabernacle choir.
it's like the trans-siberian orchestra yeah
yeah
top down on this is this was the name of the nurse the game the anesthesia when i
got mouth surgery
it's also the name of the really bad pops in your overviews is out of tune
shots fired right there
for a while and said yes comment from dr luke
yet
but
second-time disagrees
was cash is my fav singer
got a rival
Yeah.
It says, "Worst name ever, very ghetto."
That's like a, formatted like a Trump tweet.
Oh man, could you imagine Trump calling something ghetto?
Oh dude, that would rock.
I haven't heard that in like forever.
I haven't heard someone call something ghetto until like the other day when I was at CVS
and they didn't have the pen to like touch like the,
you know like the fucking card thing to like sign.
They had like, the pen fell off, someone stole the pen.
So they just had like a wire with another wire poking out
and the cashier was like, yeah it's ghetto but whatever.
(laughing)
- That's the trick. - Hell yeah.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - Man, we should
bring that back. (laughing)
- Let's bring back ghetto.
yeah we're gonna get a shirt with bills face on it that's that's so good
out of it
this is a good idea
one getaway for it
this weather trial
this is what it would be a good idea
trump tweeting about like a_o_c_ and ending with very ghetto
but it's a compliment to it.
He thinks she likes that.
He's trying to be nice.
Yeah, sorry, I was trying to speak your lingo.
I'm code switching.
Shorty, you're ghetto AF.
There's another poem on this one.
Oh, hell yeah.
Kesha is so cool,
and it's never used.
One hundred percent. If I have a female baby, Kesha is the first thing.
I have a female baby. Having a female. Yeah it's like it's a line break between female
and baby and baby's capitalized so it is like a new sentence. Yeah. It's not even if I have
a female baby. It's if I have a female baby. I'm naming that shit Kesha. Oh we're going
we're continuing on the same thread here with number 13. It's pink. So we're doing. Same
- Name exact thread because there's no--
- Yeah, exactly, that's what I was gonna say.
- I found the pattern, I solved it.
- Someone says, "Ghetto trash name,
"good name for a stripper."
- It's different and it's not ghetto.
We're naming people colors now?
- Yeah, that's normal.
- Yeah, that's me having a normal one.
- Yeah, I'm naming my kid a color
so that she can be a stripper.
Nowadays, people want their kids to be strippers.
Yeah, that's true.
So they'll name their kid,
they'll name their kid Seafoam.
So that they grow up to be a stripper or a prostitute.
This is my kid, Burnt Sienna.
This is my kid, White.
This is my kid, Yellow Green.
Your last name is Green.
No, it's Yellow-Green.
Last name is Blue.
Yellow-Green, whoa.
Yeah, think about it.
I've definitely said this before,
but there's a kid in my hometown
whose full name is Branch Leaf Olive.
(laughing)
I don't know--
Pretty good.
If you can look him up, please look him up.
I don't know how that would work,
trying to Google that name, but let me know.
Yeah.
Look up Caleb's friend, Branch Leaf Olive.
No, he's not my friend.
I don't know the guy.
I heard about him, and apparently he's a rapper.
uh... and it's like a conscious rapper i don't know all in those is rap name is
twenty
uh...
it's a
that's also a
spree six yeah
uh... number fourteen to hear it
now not quite as a sauce
that's just that's a sesame uh... it's a sesame seed sauce
someone says i've never heard it might be good for a book
yeah who's this fucking guy with the books?
It's Chuck Wendig.
It's John Grisham.
Yeah, John Grisham's in the comments.
Yeah, John Grisham, he's writing a book about a sniper named Tahiri.
Yeah.
Who kills Pink and falls in love with Kesha.
Someone else says simple and complex at the same time.
Is that possible?
Who knows, man.
I don't think Tahiri is simple or complex.
Just putting that out there.
It's not a name, I've never met a Tahiri.
I have met a couple Tristans.
Yeah.
That's true.
That's number 15.
I've met probably too many Tristans.
Yeah.
I knew a kid named Tristan in middle school who, and he moved away.
Goddamn, okay.
So this, this, this list has a, it has a peak at the beginning and then a deep valley.
Yeah, I know.
And then it comes back up at 16.
Yes.
And it has a pretty good streak here.
We have Thurston.
That's the name of a segregationist.
Someone says it's my friend's surname.
Thurston.
But they spelled sir's surname wrong.
It's my friend's surname.
Thurston, Kazdia, and Traxxas.
These all rule.
Traxxas is like a cyborg.
Traxxas is like a Star Trek name before they like figured out how to name stuff in sci-fi
like in the 60s.
Yeah.
They were just like, "We'll just name it, I don't know, or like a cleaner."
Take like Travis and switch one of the fucking, move the V over a letter.
Yeah, mirror the V. Yeah.
And it becomes Traxxas.
And someone says my name.
I'm not here.
Yeah, your name isn't Traxxas, dude.
Star and then Trek are back to back. Yes baby. And then fucking after that it's
just Sean. Yet another valley. Yeah. And then Axel. Coming back up we're on the way back up.
Oh another Ernesto. That's probably the coolest one on here in my opinion. Yeah.
I like Ernesto. Ernesto's cool. Yeah. It's like Ernest P. Worrell but like with a O.
yeah yeah it's like an oven yeah Dylan after Ernesto yeah we get into it but
then 26. Number 26 is Pikachu. The coolest name in the world. If any parent is reading this
name your kid Pikachu. Someone says it is so cool man or a girl. I like that it says
it's his parent like somebody already has a kid they're like Brian come here your
Pikachu now I just saw online it makes me want to sneeze two separate comments say
gotta catch that dick yeah Carl show fauna fauna now we're now we're bad in
500 it's just every other one. Oh damn. Carl to Fon and Bobby to Testify.
The first comment is I testify that this game is good.
I'm imagining a guy named Testify going into like a black church service and
then just every couple minutes being like did you say my name? Did you say my name?
the second comment on testify is what name is this?
The third comment is just penis sucks man!
I agree.
Testify baby.
My name is testify penis sucks man.
Number 31.
And I am your lawyer.
Number 31 is raven.
That's a cool witch name.
Yeah.
Sydney and Zeck.
Zeck.
That's just an Australian person saying Zach.
Zeek.
Hey, Zeek.
So number 39 is Sinister, spelled S-Y-N-Y-S-T-E-R.
I think if you're going to do those Y's, you should replace that E with a Y as well, I
think.
It's like a middle man.
Yeah.
Yeah, Sinister sounds like the Pete Best of Slipknot.
That's like...
The guy who got... he was in the original and then he's gone.
It's like a Mudvayne side project.
They all have like...
Like how they had Stone Sour?
Stone Sour's pre-Slipknot so why don't you brush up.
Oh that's pre-Slipknot?
Yup, and it's not Nu Metal so why don't you fuck off dude.
Get out of the call.
What was that...
Hang up.
What was that Stone Sour song?
What was their big one?
I don't know.
I really like Stone Sour.
Through the looking glass, well it seems.
Right, yeah, yeah.
I think it's just called looking at you through the glass or something.
It's terrible.
Yeah, Stone Sour is not good.
I saw that on Fuse TV when I was a kid.
Have you seen that?
I think that one is the music video where Corey Taylor is super fat and has long black hair
and like a...
Yeah, I think so.
And it zooms in on a ring he has.
I don't know if it's a thumb ring or a pinky ring, but it's supposed to be cool, but it's
just Spider-Man.
He is just like the most Reddit person. He sucks so bad. I love him, but he's just like,
he wears shirts that are like, Yoda thinks you should listen to Wu-Tang Clan. And he
like wears a fedora. He's ridiculous. I can't believe it.
It's funny that he is the kind of guy who would wear a Slipknot t-shirt.
Yeah.
He, um, no, it's so funny too, because he'll talk about his childhood and he's like, he's
like yeah when I was a kid I I overdosed and my friends threw me into a dumpster
and left me to die wearing like wearing like a Star Wars shirt and like doing
rocks fucking Star Trek hand Vulcan hand whatever it's called I don't know I'm
not a nerd I love doing Cameron's hand yeah it's called Cameron's hand
Cameron's hand number 48 is Ed Valdo oh that was pretty pretty sick there's a
a
Yeah, you could have not heard of him.
Yeah, you can put it back.
Yeah.
Benefit of the doubt.
I'm gonna name my kid "Mohamed Atta Pitts."
62, Mohamed, yeah.
Eh.
Number 66 is "Gabriel," which isn't that cool, but the comment is just--
There's three comments, and it's just, "Just Gangster Life," "Name of a thief or thug," "This is my name."
[laughter]
number number 119 is Joel and it says name of the perfect man who lost his
daughter
number one number 124 is paradox and the comment is better than naming your kid
Obama damn is there I'm gonna I'm gonna search Obama yeah you guys search
to a lot of people who believe that only he did he only uh...
the only
obama on your besides that one is under a doll someone says best name ever ten out
of ten
obama has approved this message
uh...
inferring that obama a cable is on here number one and all four
now it's not the ideas for the people saying someone so i'll tell you a
comment and said please vote i love this name is mine
That's not me though.
That's you.
That's not me.
It's not, dude.
It's not me.
Number 170 is Snoopy and the only comment is Charlie Brown.
Which is also good.
I'm just gonna load everything and command F all our names.
I wanna see if we made it on here.
See if you can find Stig.
Nico is on here.
Like Nico Lul.
Oh, okay.
see their total on here there's number three thirty five the last one is
Emerson number two thirty eight is just a Hitler
uh...
and neuro a Patrick's number seventy four
yeah baby skip over that I don't know but none of them bill isn't on here
steve isn't on here Cameron isn't on here
it's fucked up. God damn fuck all you guys. Fuck this list. I'm number seventy four I beat
Caleb out. No you didn't. Yeah I did. Yeah I did. I got 74. Yeah there's Papyrus. That's
actually my name in Egyptian. You lost to Adolf. Wow. More damningly. The names get insane
when you scroll down. Oh my god, like around 300. Craige. Like Craig with an E at the end.
Climate. C-H-L-Y-M-A-T-E.
166 is just fizz. Fizz.
Fizz.
The comment is, "Did someone shake his bottle too much?"
Oh. That's pretty good.
Olga. Candice.
Candice Dio Dio would be a cool name. It was a cool name. Yeah, and then he died and then he died. Yeah
Cuz cuz he did he was in pick of destiny
Yeah, too many names Stavo there's so many names
So people can check it out. We will yeah, you can look up all your names. Oh, is this name?
I can't remember if this is from the discord or not. I don't think it is. No, it's not
Alright, so we don't know we don't have to shout anyone out from the discord this time. We do have to do patreon
Oh, yeah, we got a bunch because we have a record. Yeah
All right, well just bear with us. Yeah
Crap man, this guy's Christ I
Can't open the email. You guys are gonna have to read them. Where do we start? Yeah, I'm sure it where
Go yeah, you know dude go grab a beer
Okay, he's gone. He's okay now that bill's gone now that we have we have a huge surprise
Yeah, when he gets back we put a thumbtack on his chair
And when he gets back he's gonna sit on it, and if he moans he's gay
How yeah, what date do we start we starting from here? I have no idea knows who knows
We might just have to head in we can record this separately once we figure it out. Yeah
Yeah.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, we should probably do that.
No, I don't want to.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do you know?
We record, I believe last time we recorded was the 28th, right?
Yeah, because we did.
Alright, let's go.
And then, did we read Wide Jim?
Yeah, I think we read Wide Jim.
Alright.
I think we did Wide Jim.
So yeah, then I think we start on the 30th.
I think that's the day we start.
Alright.
Okay.
Here we go.
Thank you to Alex Freyer.
Thank you Alex Freyer.
Thank you Sean.
You made it on the list, pal.
You were on the cool names list.
Yes, Lander Pridgen.
Where the fuck was that name?
Should have been on the list.
Where was that name?
Will Serbo.
Cool name.
Thank you.
Ethan.
Two Ethan's back to back.
Ethan Seidel and then Ethan Holbrook.
Thank you, Ethan's.
The two Ethan's.
Mike Shadykay.
Shatkey.
Gibson Duval.
If that's...
Sky the Burger.
burger is Gibson Duvall the Gibson from the documentary oh my god I hope so
Gibson if you're listening we miss you yeah yeah Grant Grant s Matt do you see
gone gone oh I think that's Gonzalo from yes shout out guys yeah shout out gons
Jack Terrence thank you Claudia Phillips Ralph Ralph Ralph you are the you are
the pimp you're the boss of the day oh I don't get my dick flattened anymore thank
you I don't get my dick flattened anymore yes guy to bar your patronage thank you
for doubling down Brett Johnson shout out to Brett Johnson if that's the Brett
Johnson I'm thinking of your great guy you're a ball and if not fuck you
You can suck my twat you worm.
Yeah.
Matt Cobbler.
That's a good name.
Mike D.
Thank you Mike D.
That's a cool old hip hop name.
Yeah.
Hank Doody.
Thank you Hank Doody.
Also cool hip hop name.
Yeah.
Ben Holt.
Quincy Judd.
Thank you Quincy Judd.
Poor old Dil.
Oh, poor old Dil.
Maybe this will lift your spirits.
Fub Mar.
Fubmar, Zach Collins, Thomas Lang, what's up Thomas, Ian Sheriff, that's like the coolest
name ever.
And then my man Nile.
Nile, thank you Nile, thank you Tom Young, thank you Craig Rose, thank you Ben Contillo,
thank you, oh no, fuck you Paul Doran, fuck you.
Corny name.
Corny ass bitch, just kidding I love you, that's my brother, shout out to my brother Paul Doran.
Zach Frenchmore I wish you were Zach French fries but you were let your
French you're less you were Zach French less you were less French Jack Jake
Reynolds thank you that's cool Samuel Malloy thank you
boyfriend thank you if that's your real name you're a serious weirdo
Stephen Yazvak. Harry Palmer, brother of Harry Potter. If your name is Harry Palmer, dude, I'm sorry, that sucks.
Sam and Pete have like an old couple Facebook double account. Alexander Tenenbaum.
From the Royal Tenenbaums. Yeah, alright. That's all of them? That's everybody. Yeah.
Yeah.
Congratulations to all of you.
Thank you and thank you Bill.
Yeah, thank you to Bill @ProphetHusband.
Thank you so much for being on the show.
Yeah, follow him.
Thank you for sitting through us reading all of those.
Yeah, he just sat there and enjoyed himself.
Yeah, he's just sitting there drinking his Hoffenhengel or whatever.
Yeah, his Sticky Stunker, whatever it's called.
Sticky got the Blicky Beer.
Yep.
He's drinking the Tekashi 69 beer.
I don't know.
It looks good.
Yep.
Traeway or whatever they're called.
Are you a blood Bill?
Yep.
That's good to know.
His name is Bill, dude.
Bill the blood.
True.
His real name is Sill.
But he says Bill.
Bill, do you have anything you want to plug besides your Twitter?
Nope.
Cool.
Just, just, you know.
All right.
Guns and drugs.
Yes.
Yeah.
Buy as many guns and drugs as you can.
Trump stimulus neat bucks to buy guns
and just have them, point them at people.
Gun safety is for pussies.
Safety off, yeah.
Safety off.
Keep your gun loaded.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Always loaded.
Get like illegal dum-dum bullets.
Yeah, just have it like in the waistband of your sweatpants.
Okay, hollow points.
Yep, hollow points.
and then fill up the hollow points with candy.
- Yeah, with Dum Dums.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
All right, bye y'all.
- Thanks, man. - See you later.