You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- All right, recording two.
Let's try this again.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- One more time.
- Happy 420.
- Because Patrick is so high.
- I'm so stoned.
- He literally, he fucked up his audio
because he thought he saw--
- He tried to smoke his microphone.
Yeah, he thought he saw a chip.
He thought he saw a flaming hot Cheeto.
Yeah.
And it was actually the end recording button.
But it, 'cause it was red.
He saw the red, the record button,
and he thought it was a--
A Taki.
A lengthways view of a Taki.
Yeah, he thought it was a Taki flying towards him.
And he tried to catch it with his--
Yeah, he tried to eat it with his hands.
On the mouse.
Mm-hmm.
That's what happened.
Yeah, and now he's--
I don't smoke anymore.
Patrick's so high.
Dude, I can see it in your eyes.
- I used to. - No, I used to.
- Why are your eyes so red?
- My eyes are red because of allergies.
- What, have you been crying?
Have you been crying about how high you are?
- Have you been crying, dude?
You got so high that you started crying?
- That's not true.
- You did, man.
You got so high that you're crying now.
That's why stoners have red eyes,
because weed makes you so emotional.
- Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
It makes you so emotional, you cry.
- Yeah, they watch Seth Rogen and they laugh so hard
that tears come out of their eyes.
they want their own she's she's and she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's
she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's she's
I'm not smoking weed, I'm never smoking weed again.
- What happened to you?
- I don't remember, but--
- Whoa!
- There was the whole month of January pretty much,
I was high every day.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- And then I think February too,
I did lose the dab pen before New York, which sucked.
That was the worst.
- Yeah, that's probably good for you.
- That was good for me, was not good for Dom.
- Oh yeah, true.
You can still have mine when this is over.
I'm
Yeah, the sequel to 420.
The day that you're listening.
Finally.
What's the most memorable time you guys ever toked?
You ever lit up a fatty?
The first time I smoked K2.
Yeah, I've accidentally smoked K2 quite a few times.
Yeah, that is definitely my worst weed memory is smoking not weed.
Yeah.
in
gamer
and then they didn't have his game reminds sometimes can differentiate
between reality and podium on go
yeah
it's uh... it's a problem and
i'd be walking around my house don't pokey balls
well i'll tell you what i am trying to catch my dog
the
is there a bath bomb in my dog yeah
has a name
the i_d_
it escaped
Fuck, I guess I have to kill my dog.
- Yeah.
- I played Pokemon Go a lot when it first came out
'cause I was in California and I was like 17 or whatever.
- Yeah, no, I'm glad, I think,
I'm glad it came out when it did.
- Yeah.
- I'd be in like high school
or like the very end of high school.
It might've been the summer after high school for me.
- I think it was something like that too.
I just remember I was like,
Me and my cousins were all drunk driving and piled into a car and played Pokemon Go in a
place where the speed limit was like 15 miles an hour.
And we just stayed in the car and didn't talk to each other.
Just swiped our phones for two hours.
Nice.
For me, it was just perfect to be like, "Oh yeah, I'm going to play Pokemon Go with my
friends and just walk around town and drink and smoke."
Yeah man.
Sick.
It's a fucking party.
None of my friends at the time played.
That's the spirit of 420.
Pokemon.
- Smokey Mongo, yeah.
- That's a dispute. - Smokey Mon.
- They should make a--
- Smokey Mon Blow.
- Smokey Mon Blow, yeah.
- Smokey Mon Blow a smoke cloud.
Yeah, I'm catching Rikachu.
He reeks of marijuana sore.
- Doinkachu.
- Yeah, I'm catching Pika choosing to smoke weed.
And also Mew, Mewtwo.
- Mewarwana.
- Mewtwo high.
- Murowana.
- Bondmander.
- Snorlax is me when I smoke too damn much.
- Yeah, I'm Snorlax right now
'cause I'm walking to get Pringles out of the fridge.
- Yeah, and I smoke--
- Cold Pringles.
- You combine Charmander and Ivysaur
in a vase that has Squirtle.
- Oh my God, dude.
- Whoa.
and you make and you can use and you have a long
smoke a bomb
smoke a bomb is one of the best smoke a bomb blow
one of the best smoking on clothes blows
mose via
blow mo
yeah about pokey monroe
and it's and you know the line
and you know the long but also you have no most is lack from simpsons is the
pikachu
disease and yellow
yeah that's correct
he's electric type for sure
Yeah. Yeah. Instead of Pika Pika he's like Mo Mo.
Kind of interesting to think about. Yeah absolutely.
Mo Fire. He doesn't use fire he's electric type. Oh you're right I'm saying
Pika I was thinking of Pika Fire. Well he has the flaming mo. That's from that's that's what
Ness says in Super Smash Bros. Yeah that's PK Fire. Yeah that's PK. I just always thought it was
I thought that they were friends.
Psychokinesis.
I thought, when I was a kid, I thought Ness was Ash.
I thought I was Ness.
Wait, dude, Smokeabong Blow, you play as Ash.
Smokeabong Blow, you're Ash and uh...
Ash Smoke 'Em.
Yeah, Ash Smoke 'Em.
You instead of a bike, you have a scooter.
And uh...
and instead of a hat you have a joint
yeah instead of all your clothes you have a joint for each item of clothing
uh huh
yeah
and uh... surf is still an option in the game
yeah but you also you scooter and you surf
and then uh... instead of
instead of goldeen
it's
it's uh... gold weed
gold weed
Yeah, Chris and Pokemon crystals strains. Oh my god
Pokemon Indica and Sativa
Yeah, damn that's awesome and then there's like a one that comes out a year later called Pokemon hybrid
Damn, yeah, it's that of team rocket. It's team. Don't smoke it
Yes, dude, they're the police. It's team Ronald Reagan
Ronald Reagan is the final four.
Who's that?
That's my mom.
Oh, okay.
What's up, dude?
My mom walked by the car window.
We're talking about Smokey Mon, Mrs. Fetter.
Smokey Bong.
Smokey Bong Blow.
Smokey Bong Blow Indica.
And then there's also Smokey Bong Grow, which is like a farming simulator.
Yeah.
Smokymon, it's like Pokemon Mystery Dungeon,
but it's Smokymon Andrew's Basement.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And that's the mystery dungeon, Andrew's Basement.
- Yeah, and you guys watch old Monty Python Cliffs
and smoke weed.
- Yeah, and you're like, I don't get this.
They, why are they talking that way?
- Yeah, I get real mad. - It's too random for me.
- What is that voice they're doing?
- Dude, do you ever smoke weed
and then the Monty Python's the Holy Grail
totally makes sense to you for the first time ever.
- Monty's, Monty, my bong, the holy bong.
- The smoky.
- Smoky, smoky my bong.
(laughing)
Smoky my bong. - Smoky my bong.
- And the holy strain.
- No, the smoking and the smoking.
- And the smoking bong.
(laughing)
Smoky my bong and the smoking bong.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah the life of Brian the life of Brian. Yeah
Yeah, the high of Brian
The meaning of high
Yeah, Monty's my bongs the meaning of high
Monty
smoky my bongs
high-ying sir, hi
We're high
Smokers
smoking my bongs high in smokess
high in smokess
Fatty Fatty Day
Fatty Day Night High Fatty Day Night High
Really good another one another class is in the bong kids in the bong mr. Smoke
Yeah, mr. CB, but it's the
upright
smoke brigade
the
Ben Stiller smoke
Yeah, the bins yeah, yeah the Dana Carvey smoke
the
In smoking color
In smoking weeder in smoking Potter weed, huh?
Harry bonger Harry bonger and the and the piss in her in the
the pills nerve smoking we
Yeah.
Roly poly smokey dokey.
(laughing)
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
That's really good too.
Honestly, we are just doing what this list does say.
Oh yeah.
I think we're doing a better job.
We are doing a better job.
I forgot what the list was.
Yeah, the list is top 10 TV shows
with one word replaced with weed.
So I feel like this is a good challenge.
From the user, Steven Universe is awesome.
So this is good because I think with all of these,
there's a better version of whatever it is.
- Yeah, so we can just workshop it.
- Yeah, so we can workshop it and make it better.
Like, okay, easy one.
- So do we say what the list was?
Top 10 TV shows?
- Yeah, we just said.
- Yeah, so this is on the top 10s.
The number one is Buffy the Weed Slayer.
I feel like it's so easy to do Puffy the Weed Slayer.
- Puffy the Weed Smoker.
But then you have a problem because you still have the,
and the is still normal.
So maybe weed, maybe Puffy weed smoker.
(laughing)
Puffy THC weed smoker.
Oh my god!
Whoa, there we go.
That's good.
Yeah.
That is really good.
There's only one comment on this and it says,
"This is probably the worst list
"I've ever seen on this site."
Yeah, there's not a lot of comments,
but this one's about the comments.
Because they didn't have us to fix it.
That's true, yeah.
the audience doing that thing again
uh... it is
yeah artists on
number two
sabrina the teenage so he said he was
city that he had seen c_d_c_ we don't we don't we don't
the we don't really need to read the read read the green day
that i don't need
sabrina t_h_ no sissy citizens c green day we'd
easy it's perfect and then with the reboot you have the chill the chill
adventure because it's the chilling adventures of sabrina chill the chill
smoke the chill smoke the chill smoke session session sessions sativa sativa
thc green day weed
number three is perfect
we'd we felt
that was just
great to the case is that that one who would you know that i have a good
we'd fill the area really failed obviously have more to our story
stanza
jupiter smoke stanza bomb stanza
cause smoke
cause be a ramer
costs
the lane uh...
smoking no dinner name would be the strain
of the strain the strains of the other strain penis
uh... yeah
uh... and then you have the weed nazi
uh... we'd for you
right uh...
what it would mean when we go home in
uh... are you calm
and
we need and yes pretty easy
hello we'd men yeah
and then instead of a instead of the diner they'd have uh... like uh...
dispensary yeah and they'd all sit down and roll up a big fatty
yeah and they live in amsterdam not new york
yes yeah yeah amsterdam is kind of a character in the show
yeah instead of the slap bass they'd play um...
dope throne by electric wizard
yeah
in the back a full
they'd play dope smoker by um... sleep
this an hour long stoner metal song in the background of every episode
yet
number four
uh... even we've seen we have so far is a pretty cool for his parents is read
over five
uh... five is perfect
dusty of steven we'd we can do so
yet yes even we smoking weed we did have a leading steve
we didn't see the verse was yes i got yes and i think he's in the evening
mean Steven Universe yeah yeah Keef and... Keef and smoking verse and
smoking turds yeah Keef and and poon poony curse cuz like you know when you
smoke weed and you just get horny as hell
something burn Steve Keefe and Oh Keith Keith you know Keith Uniburn yeah Keith
you can burn yeah that you can burn there we go so Steven universe to Keith you can
burn I feel like that's pretty good number five is Cory and the weed that
That one's perfect.
It sounds, Quarry and the Weed sounds like a,
sounds like a Christian educational VHS tape.
Yeah.
Quarry,
Quarry, you could do like--
Story of the Weed.
How about Quarry, Quarry and the Weed,
because you get so curious when you smoke pot.
Yeah. That's true.
'Cause it's opening up a new chakra point.
So Quarry, Quarry--
from the weed.
Query from the weed.
There's two comments.
Somebody says weed in the house sounds better.
No it doesn't.
I'm going to open this car door to get some fresh air.
Why because you're hot boxing?
It's really hot in here.
Because he's hot boxing his car.
If I was I would not open the door.
Think about that for one second.
Oh that's where Cory would have started.
You open the door just so you can get the smoke to go out.
Smoking in the house.
What if it's Cory in the car?
corey in the car and he's hot boxing
corey in the car was that was so funny car door closing is funny
yeah yeah this every line everything's funny to me
cuz i'm high because i'm high right now and i'm on the record as i i a space
nugget
and that made me high from smoke do they have a weed chicken did we need to
Weed chicken? I think they do.
Do they?
Yeah.
Weed chicken.
That's a new business.
That is a new frontier is, yeah, weed chicken nuggets, weed hamburgers and hot dogs.
Number six is Weed McGuire.
So is this Lizzie McGuire?
I think so.
I think this is.
How about Fizzy McFire?
Fizzy McFire.
It's perfect.
Fizzy McFire and then Gordo's name is Smoko.
Smordo.
Cause he eats s'mores.
He gets so high he eats s'mores.
Number 7, weed titans.
Weed smokings.
No, no, we gotta...
Weed high...
High men.
Weed high mens.
(laughter)
- Um, high ten.
- Weed high ten.
- And then yeah, brackets ten.
(laughter)
- Oh dude, I'm getting a contact high
from this fucking list right now.
- Me too.
- Oh my god, dude.
- Number eight, I don't know what this is.
- The weed house?
- I think it's either the loud house or full house.
- I bet it's the loud house based on what's on this list.
- Dude, that's already done.
Yeah, the loud the loud the loud
House the loud weed house what about the loud loud?
Hmm you use words twice you're allowed to yeah number nine
Gravity weed how about easy gravity gravity ball gravity ball gravity ball. Yeah, you fucking easy
But we I feel like we go harder actually. Yeah gravity
We know what a gravity bong is.
Smoke... cavity.
Grabbing the... bong.
Grabbing the bong.
There we go.
Grabbing the bong is my favorite kids show that I watch as an adult.
It's good.
Number ten.
And, and, and, uh, smoker the garden bong.
Smoker the garden bong?
Yeah, smoker the weed, the weed garden bong.
Yeah.
The... oh.
Number ten, adventure weed.
weed. Weed venture smoking time. Weed venture 420. Mm-hmm. How about just 420?
How about just 420? True, because that's the weed time. Simplify it. 420. Yeah.
Yeah, and instead of Jake the dog, he's... Jake's a guy. Smoke. He's Smake the
smog and he's a cloud of smoke mm-hmm yeah and instead of Finn he's uh sin
because it's sinful to smoke weed yeah 10 10 10 the 20 divided by 2 is 10 and if
there were two tens then now you have that would be 20 20 yeah that's a good
point. The weed adventures of Billy and Mandy. The, how about the, the trim, the
trim adventure, the trim, weed, smoke venture, weed, weed venture, weed ventures of Trilly
and Brandy because sometimes you got to have a little drink with you when you're
smoking a little chiba yeah and yeah number 12 the amazing weed of gumball
what about okay what were me out there the amazing what of the world world oh
that kind of hear me out the smoke mazing weed of gumball gumball is a
problem yeah I'm gonna have to add a gumball
Have you ever been fucking high out your damn socks, sitting at home, thinking, "What do
I want to eat right now?" and arrived at Gumball?
How about...
Okay, alright.
The smoke-mazing weed of hot dog.
This...
The smoke-mazing...
I'll take that.
Okay.
The smoke-mazing weed of hot dog.
I think this next one's perfect.
This next one is untouchable.
Uh-huh.
Regular weed.
Yeah.
Yeah, regular weed.
That's all you need to say.
Regular weed.
It's some of that reggie,
but it doesn't fucking matter for these boys.
Yeah, who gives a heck?
Who gives a fuck, man?
Sometimes the reggie is all you need.
It gets you there.
Number 14--
It's not about the destination,
it's about the journey.
Exactly, and as long as I'm high on that journey,
I'm gonna be okay.
Number 14, Reddy Jet Weed. I don't know what show this is about.
Reggie Smoke Weed.
Reggie Dat Weed.
Yeah. I don't know what this next one is either.
Nella the Princess Weed. Let's find out.
Nella the Princess Knight
is the original. Okay, what about Yellow Wolf?
yellow
the prince of weeds
the
yellow of the prince of weed
yet but you know i like that the title right there
yellow wolf the prince of weed
as perfect
it's on the ads is in its purpose nothing
nothing to do i think it's a change their yeah
we because and
about we d we d
we have a lot of we because i can downloading the fucking you're down
downloading a fresh...
You're downloading a Snoop Lion track for Kazaa.
What about, no I was gonna say, I was gonna say what about Weedy Shazam, 'cause you heard
uh...
'Cause you heard Pasta Dutchie to the left hand side.
Yeah, you heard Red Red Wine and you wanted to confirm that it was not by Bob Marley.
Yeah.
Number 17, OK K.O.
Let's Be Weeds.
What, okay, Smoke K.
Smoke K. 2.
to
smoking how about how about this easy simple
bear smoking weed okay excuse me
I'm into it number 19 another perfect one
yeah nature weed how about creature weed
ok do not smoke creature weed do not that is one of the biggest mistakes you
can make
yeah you want nature weed not creature we do not want anything laced with creature
or intended for a creature.
Creature systems work the exact opposite of ours.
So when you get hot, what makes creatures high,
makes people die.
- Does not make people high.
- Yes, remember that rhyme.
- I'm remembering that rhyme.
- Makes creatures high, makes people die.
- People die.
- Yeah.
- I'll never forget that.
- When you make cream pie, your girlfriend will die.
Just remember that.
Keep that in mind whenever you're smoking weed.
When you go to your dealer and you want to make sure it's not creature weed, you ask them,
"Hey, when I make cream pie, my girlfriend die?"
Yeah.
Every creature is bi.
And girlfriend only tell lie.
If it rhymes, it's with the times.
Yeah.
It's facts.
If my wiener
flies...
If my wiener smokes,
then money everybody gets a choke
lol
yeah
number
twenty the weed guard red eyes red eyes in the morning stoners delight red eyes
at night's all stoners delight
uh... smoking weed
all day that will be okay smoking weed all night that will be alright right
smoke
eating tons of chips with all of my best friends i can't believe i get to eat
these chips with my best friends
there once was a man from nantucket
who smoked a bunch of weed from a bucket
he got really high
and then never could die
and now he lives
in a bucket
yes that's at the old idiom says number twenty one that's so we
how that's a little so so please in
about fats that is so heaven
because when you get a fatty that's like having to make fat so blazing
that's no blazing blazing it's the we did i can smoke
smoke weeding with smoke weed and with me
yeah
Ravens weed is
Perfect don't touch it. Yeah, perfect
Number 23 60 weeds is that 60 minutes? Yeah, probably
Dude, I would love to watch 60 weeds is way better than 420 minutes for 20 minutes. Yeah
That's a long show. Yeah, that's really long. It's okay
You fall asleep to it while you're high, dude. That's the point
Okay, number 24. Star versus the forces of Weedville should be smoke smoking the
forces of smoking Weedville. Whoa. Also they didn't even replace the whole word
with weed. Yeah. They changed evil to Weedville which is where I want to move.
That doesn't even count. Mm-hmm. Tell you that much. So number 25 is Weed Tales. This could
either be dragon tails or duck tails if it's a dragon tails you gotta call it
you gotta call it smoking dragons smoking a dragon's tail smoking a dragon's tail
duck tails you gotta say you gotta call it fuck tails because fucking smoking
tails fucking smoking dragon smoking some fucking weed tails how about that yeah
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Or Chuck Tales.
Or Chuck Testa.
Yeah, you could call it that.
Number 26 is Andy Weed.
I don't know what that is.
Me neither.
We'll just say Candy Weed, because that sounds funny.
Number 27, Over the Weed Wall.
Mine was better.
Yeah.
Smoker THC, Weed Garden Bong.
Bong Cush Garden Smoking Joint. What about that?
Oh, a hundred million dollars smoking weed with my friends. How about that?
How about, uh, um, smoking higher, um, some smoking dragon?
Jacking off high as hell.
How about watching tv?
Watching tv? I love, how about I loving watch tv high?
How about watching tv eating a slice of cake that's left over?
Whoa.
How about the smoking weed makes you realize the cake is a lie?
What about this, what about the smoking fella?
He's a guy who smokes.
Oh my god.
What about instead of the smoking gun, the uh, like the movie, it's the toking one.
And it's about me.
Okay.
And I'm the, I'm like a, I'm like a kung fu monk but I smoke weed.
Number 28 is Infinity Weed.
That sounds awesome.
That does sound pretty cool.
That's my one wish.
Infinity Weed.
If I get a genie, first thing I'm wishing for Infinity Wish is next thing I'm wishing
for Infinity Weed.
I feel like you could do it better though.
You could say Trinity Weed, which would be like Trinity from the Matrix, one of the best
all-time weed movies.
Number 29, Weed over Yander.
Weed Smoker Candle.
Weed Smoker I can't understand her.
Candle.
Weed Smoker I can't understand her and it's when you're high as hell and you're trying
to talk to your mom on the phone.
Weed Smoker.
Number 30, Weed.
Weed the Series/Robunza's Weed Adventure.
That's perfect.
Weed the Series.
Weed the Series is so good.
Yeah, I'm going to order 10 seasons of Weed the Series.
the
And the declaration of indica pendants.
Oh fuck.
It's damn good.
The smokelaration.
The smokelaration of my...
The smokelaration of indica pendants.
That's good.
Of indica dab pendants.
Dab pendants.
Yeah, cause sometimes you get high and all you want to do is lose yourself to the music.
Number thirty... which one are we on?
Thirty-one.
Number thirty-one, weed patrol.
How about, how about, um, claw patrol?
What is it, doom patrol?
No, I think it's paw patrol.
Oh yeah.
Weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed,
weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed,
weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed,
Weed, weed kills trolls.
There we go.
Yeah.
Number 32, the weed.
Cannot, we will never know what they meant there.
THC weed, baby.
THC weed.
It's about as simple as it needs to be.
Yeah.
33, weed and shine.
Weed and rhyme, because sometimes when you smoke a little bit of that er, you just gotta
the
I'm freed. Yeah, I don't man. I don't know if you I mean, I don't know
I mean you may be thinking you do Caleb
Smoking weed that means that I'm I'm freed. I went to the store to get some more weed. I
Brought it back. I smoked a pack of
Pot it's not gonna get me not high. I'm I
cannot rhyme I'm
In bed trying to go to sleep, but all my dreams are made of weed. I
think I
Think about Mario Kart, I think about the Simpsons Bart
Those are the kinds of thoughts I have on weed now. Will you please pass it, please?
- Damn. - Woo!
- Thank you. - Nice.
- That's damn, that shit was dope.
- Yeah, it was dope, like the weed that I smoke,
you know that I have to choke myself with the force.
When I smoke weed, I gain the force.
I love to read about different lores.
I smoke weed and I read, and that's all I need is some weed.
Thank you. Oh my god. That's for you for you busters. Yeah, it was pretty good.
Thank you. You should have said toke though. I love to toke. I love to croak like a
toad. I'm on the road. I'm smoking weed on the road. I drive and smoke and that's my
right. If you don't like it I will still light a big ol' blood in your face. So fuck you
dude I I love every race because I'm so high and I'm just I'm thinking about
but when he's not I always do I always like every race stop stop stomp um weed
guy his number that's perfect weed high weed high yo that's the school I want to
go to. Uh-huh. Tamagotchi you could have you could have... Smoke a lot of cheese.
Smoke a lot of cheese. Smoke a lot of cheebug. That's a lot of cheese.
Smokeable weed. Smokeable. Smoke a lot of cheeb. Smokeable weed. Smokeable weed.
Yeah. I love when my weed is smokeable. Yeah. Number 37 is cosmic quantum weed.
That's perfect.
Yeah, that's good.
I think that's good.
But number 38 is just being weed.
Smoking weed.
No, being weed I think is pretty good.
Yeah.
Because I love smoking weed in the hopes that one day I will just, one day I will transform
like the fly.
Peeing weed.
Because you smoke so much weed it comes out your damn urethra.
Yeah, one time I applied for a job at Micro Center and like the day before I had smoked
weed for the first time in like three years.
And they were like, "Just so you know, we do comply" - this was in Boston - they were
like, "Just so you know, we do comply with all federal regulations on drug testing.
So have you taken any drugs in the past three weeks?"
And I was like, "No, not at all."
And then I did the piss test and they just never - they tried calling me and I just never
answered.
I just gave up on it.
I was just like, "I don't know why I took the piss.
I should have just said yes.
But I was so nervous, 'cause I needed a job so bad.
But what if it failed?
It was like the first week when I moved to Boston.
It would have been a fail.
No, what if it passed?
I mean, what if the test failed?
Then I would still be working at Micro Center.
I'd be building a weed computer right now.
A super computer that could spit out new names for strains.
420 gigahertz processor.
Yeah, and you'd walk up, you'd press a button,
And then it would go, donkey bong.
(laughing)
That's the kind of stuff I would be doing.
Donkey bong.
New strain.
- Yeah.
Nephew's delight.
- Nephew's delight.
- Nephew's weed.
- And I'd be doing that right now,
and I'd still be working on that team at Micro Center,
researching pot.
That was a thing they would have,
If I had passed, or if I had weed my system,
it would have hired me to be the arbiter
for the marijuana community at Micro Center.
- They would have had to listen
to whatever new strain ideas you had.
- Exactly.
- We should make a strain called Dead Dog Slime.
And it makes you--
- We should make one called M&M Weed.
- Like the candy?
- Yeah.
- How about M&Ms, what about M&Ms M&Ms?
- M&Ms smoking them.
smoking smoking weed
and he's getting high from cheap let's make it was a little patrick's the
rapper let's make a strain of weed called heroin and just see what happens
cf let's just do it the alice and i'm an ass smoking is
they're gonna make a straight away lead a strain of weed called heroin and then
whoever buys it there rest
to think it's heroin
they probably will do that
yeah i'm so dumb
there you can do a freestyle pat
my mike is came on
i hate you talking idiot
you know i said i remind you that you don't know the and i'll just rethink it
and you know the after the court there's a couple times it came on for you
kidding me
now find out when it came unplugged i know i know i'm listening back to the
episode i thought i know i know when i know when they got unplugged
patrick got to know how is anything that you got high again i'm gonna put my
I'm gonna put beeps in for when every time it got unplugged. No, you're gonna tell me the time stamps
Loud beeps, but he's gonna put like he's gonna blow smoke into the emergency system
He's gonna make the waveform like a like a weed leaf. Yeah unplugged. That's what I'm gonna do
Yeah, if you blow smoke into the microphone the waveform will turn into a weed leaf. Yeah
Yeah, we should hide we should hide a secret message to all of our stoners in the waveform of this episode
Mm-hmm, so we could hide like a giant pot leaf or like a friendly monkey
That's smoking weed the monkey that's mostly monkey. Yeah, if you don't hold your mic in your hand, it probably won't get unplugged
Yeah, just put it down
Yeah, but like I got a person I don't have like a desk
I have like I'm gonna be hunched over a bunch subscribe to the patreon. Let's try and get Patrick a desk
this
I'm just gonna do this.
Alright.
I mean it's up to you.
And then talk, and then talk into it like this.
It looks like you're sucking your own small penis.
I can get out of the car and still have my butt.
Are you gonna stand outside?
Do a man on the street bit.
Yeah, go interview one of your neighbors.
Go talk to your mom.
Take a picture.
I don't know how to do that.
With your phone.
Oh.
My phone makes my microphone sound crazy.
Patrick will do it.
What are should we move on to the next list? Yeah, yeah, we added we had a double we had a double whammy
Yeah, so we have as many as many episodes as the middle digit in 420 or as many lists as the middle digit 420
Yeah, sorry many lessons. There are letters in THC if you minus the T. Yeah
Which stands for hard to word hard hard core is how hard core getting high?
I am about weed it stands for freaking high
- Hi, Cheba. - Hi, Caleb.
- Hi, Caleb. - Yeah.
- Hi, Cameron.
- Not hi, Patrick.
- No, never again. - It's 'cause Patrick
can go down to the ground like a worm
and he wriggles around and tries to find his way up
people's pant legs.
- Yeah, the early Patrick-- - And I don't condone
that behavior. - That's not true.
- The early Patrick catches his own balls.
- That's not true.
- Patrick has yet to evolve into a biped.
- Yeah, Patrick is-- - I'm a biped.
- Patrick has stuck in the water for 23 years.
- You need to smoke some damn weed
and evolve some legs-- - All right, I'm gonna
smoke it right now. - To climb out of the puddle.
- Oh, there he is.
Dude, he's smoking weed out of the tip of his penis and he's lighting his balls on fire like a bong.
Oh, yeah. I evolved into...
Oh, he went meatwad mode.
Yeah.
Oh, man. I evolved from smoking.
What?
What's that mean?
I evolved from smoking.
That's the thing. If somebody had given one of those fucking weird fish just a little hit of a blunt...
...we would all be meatwads right now.
Dude, this list... I just went to this other list.
the the intro paragraph i'm gonna have to just read this whole thing this is a
great idea this is a case this is from betches dot com that is it's a stout the
stoner series top ten stones topics of conversation
i'm gonna read it
welcome back you fucking potheads
this weekend smoke anomics we discuss the most pivotal cornerstone of marijuana
users far and wide
high thoughts
naturally betches are perceptive is fuck however once we get high our thoughts
become so complex and elaborate that we often confuse ourselves in what the fuck
we were even thinking about. But regardless we honestly don't think it's
a stretch to liken ourselves to Plato. The limit to topics as well as the
enlightenment are truly boundless. What? Like Plato the food? No like...
Well it said stretch. Yeah Plato is a food to Patrick. It tastes like salt.
The limits of topics as well as the enlightenment are truly boundless, and by boundless we mean
until our weed runs out.
We introduce you to our next top ten list in our series of ongoing top ten lists, stoned
topics of conversation.
Oh, so this is a series.
Yeah, I don't want to know any of the answers to any of these.
I just want to discuss them.
Yeah, like number ten, how do people discover drugs and alcohol?
That's a great question.
i think they invented in a lab to make people does try to escape reality
yeah i think that i think that it were all brains in a computer lab
so we can't create this microcosm of the brain of it lab
by creating a cool science lab inside the
simulation science lab
so i think that the stuff that comes out of that science lab would make us escape
to the upper level of the science lab i think that we was made in a also in a
lab by an evil scientist named yakko
And basically he saw an episode of Spongebob Squarepants and he was like,
"How do I make this shit as funny as hell?"
[laughter]
And so he designed an evil drug called weed.
Yeah, I think, I think personally someone rolled a joint and said, "Hey, smoke this."
Well, where'd they find the good stuff? That good good?
It's a chicken or the egg situation.
Yeah, what came first, the puffy bubble cush?
Or the smoky dab?
Or the smoky dab rig?
[laughter]
Yeah, that's a great point.
Yeah, what came first the the the the blunt or the ashes?
What came first smoking or getting high
That's wrong
Smoking that's I think we're getting anyone. I think people were smoking things from the dawn of century
Dude, no until like eight the 1800s you would just get high on the Sun. Yeah, it's true
You just walk out and look at the Sun until you felt real weird
They would and then your skin got red. Yeah. Yeah, that was one of the at-o's people who are allergic to getting high
Those are like the pussies of the time people who got red skin. Yeah
You could get you could get high just from like riding a horse around
It would shine yeah, yeah if you stood behind a horse and it kicked you in the head you get high as fuck
Yeah, yeah, if you went to church you get really high people used to like
They used to put a special powder in
Bullets and people used to go into the middle of the town square and they would get each other high
And you know boy times that's true. Yeah, shoot shoot. It would shoot edible THC bullets into each other
Uh-huh, and then I knew what actually
My god, so Christopher Columbus was trying to find the West Indies, right?
He sailed the ocean blue and arrived in a little town called Jamaica, California
Right. And what do you think the Indies?
Got off the ship. They started waiting
Exactly waving giant weed leaves on him like he was Caesar and they had palm leaves. There are huge weed leaves
Yeah
He worshipped him as a god and they let him puff that Chiba one time for the one time
And then he had maybe one of the all-time weed freak
out. Yeah. He had to freak out like Jack Sparrow did. Yeah he had a serious Jack Sparrow freak
out. And he gave them. Yeah he spread the munchies to them on blankets. Yeah. Yeah the munchies
wiped out the Native American race. Yeah. Sad. Yeah. Sad to think about but it's true.
It also just gets you high just thinking about it.
Also, even mental illness is getting me high.
Sometimes I-- I have a contact high
from Christopher Columbus.
Sometimes I rotate like a old shitty forum PNG
of a weed leaf in my head and that gets me high.
You know what I mean?
A little like 25 by 25.
I got drunk as shit last night.
I drank a bunch of margarita salt.
Whoa.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
How'd it go?
I'm bloated.
You're bloated?
Yeah.
You look good.
You have a good Patrick look today.
Yeah.
I would describe this as "Klattstrick" Patrick.
"Klattstrick"?
Because you're looking like a Jadina Klattstrick.
Yeah, you're straight down.
You're like a Patrical piece of art.
Yeah, I didn't go to bed like you guys told me to.
I'm a Patrick, man.
You can be me if you smoke a lot of weed.
Yeah, I didn't go to bed like you guys told me to.
I'm a Patrick, man.
You can be me if you smoke a lot of weed.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
If it was about me, it would be a Vlasic, man.
I'm a Vlasic, man.
I love to eat those pickles.
Those are the worst pickles.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah, I don't fuck with those pantry pickles.
It's gotta be a refrigerated one.
That Vlasic stork, let me tell you,
I'm gonna beat his ass.
He's a pedophile, man.
Yeah.
So he has a baby in his mouth.
He wants a baby's pickle in his mouth?
Hell, excuse me?
Yeah.
Pardon my French?
Pardon my take.
Yeah, PTI on that one,
because that's some fucked up S.
Uh-huh.
Number nine, reminiscing via backstalk.
I don't know what that means.
I don't know what backstalk means.
You guys don't have a back stock?
I think it's like a...
On your back?
You guys don't have...
It's like a...
It's a pole that you tie to your back.
No, it's...
It's a piece of wood.
You guys haven't been growing any?
Any stalks on your back?
No.
Can you grow weed on it?
I guess you guys aren't adults yet then.
No, I'm an adult.
It's kind of embarrassing.
You haven't gone through 70th puberty like me.
No, I'm an adult.
Cameron's back looks like a lotus pod.
It looks like a damn bamboo field.
There's pandas in there.
Cameron has a butt crack that goes up to his neck.
- Yep, and I reach in there and I fiddle around.
- No, you have to wipe all the way down.
- Yeah, that's why it takes me so long.
- The way Cameron poops is that he has to sit in a urinal,
like one of those stand up urinals.
- It comes from the top of his spine and it goes down.
- It goes all the way down, it goes up and down.
- He fits perfectly in one of those square urinals.
- Yeah.
- That's just how it was made.
- Yeah, it is.
He has all the ice that they put in the urinal.
That's for Cameron to sit on.
Yeah, to make sure his butt's too warm.
Yeah, it burns up.
'Cause it's got such a long crack.
I don't know what this means though.
I guess it just means that if you look
at your old Facebook stuff, you look seriously weird.
Yeah, and your high is crap.
Yeah.
I did that today.
I looked at all my old posts.
the
Everyone's gonna smoke weed at the same time and the smoke is gonna go up and cover the sun all the plants died
No more no more weed. We all die
Do you know all the plants are gonna die and not get in nourished by the?
also
The plants are gonna die cuz I you listen to what I said
I said the smoke is gonna cover up the Sun you fucking idiot plants can't live without the fucking Sun
I'm really I get green rage
weed next to a plant. He's a reefer madness. Yeah. I'm like the Hulk dude. Cameron, the
carbon. I'm the smoke. The smoke. The carbon dioxide from the weed would get into the plants
and they would. No it's not carbon monoxide in weed it's Cush-bin smoke oxide. Bin Laden.
Cush-bin Laden. I would say, yeah the way the world will end is that we're all, if everybody
in the world smokes weed at the same time will ascend simultaneously like
Heaven's Gate. Yeah. Yeah, why not? They just had it wrong. Heaven's Gate is real but you
don't kill yourself, you smoke weed. Yeah. Mm-hmm. When the comet passes.
Blevins Gate, like Ninja Tyler Blevins. Whoa.
So why don't you think about that for a little while? Why don't you get high and chew on that?
blevin's gate
*laughing*
and it's just a bunch of little kids
doing the floss dance
dying their hair blue
doing the floss dance to their mom
yeah
and say mom you have a loser mindset
mmhmm
number 7 conspiracy theories
stoners love a good fucking conspiracy
that's true
that's true shit
what's your favorite conspiracy?
I like I've always been partial to CERN as a portal to hell
CERN is a portal to hell is good. Anunnaki is good. More like Burn is a portal to high
RuneScape Manhattan
What's that?
The RuneScape Manhattan is
It's a conspiracy that all
everything that happens on rune scape
is happening in an underground bunker
in new york manhattan
that sounds like a pretty like lately when you control it you're controlling
like like a sort of a gamer ask like the movie gamer which are butler yes avatar
yes
i don't have a place i can see you know it's like something that nobody nobody
believes
it sounds like some i believe it up
to be funny manhattan doesn't sound like a real conspiracy i think it's real
all right never mind
kill believe that so that's enough for me
number six and musicians slash celebs
i don't think about them ever once they're dead they're gone from my mind
when i'm high i got i'm always thinking about uh... it's a little much to stay
back at some of the do
i'm thinking of a group of skating redhead
i'm just thinking about the guy that of far killed
yeah i just sit around your own and i am
the a_u_ run a mess
they should have called him uh...
i don't know i'm on a miss
the issue of called imposter missus he's fucking dead yeah
bang there we go now i mean
bang uh...
uh... number five was life like that technology
probably uh... we already covered and talked about the topic of time
it would be awesome that's why
number four the universe
i don't know what that is
how does it start? that's another steven universe thing
yeah
yeah THC universe
THC's
it's my favorite form
what is that weird beeping noise?
is there a beeping?
does it not just me? alright
sorry i have a beeping in my head again
Cameron's beeps.
He got too high and he's beeping.
I'm beeping high right now.
I'm so beeping high right now.
Dude, I'm so beeping high.
Do you guys like to beep your weed?
I like to beep my weed.
Smoke vapor beep.
I just like to beep it until it gets so hot that I can inhale.
Number three is just feeling bad about shit.
Damn.
That's right.
That's some true shit though.
That is some true ass bullshit dude.
some facts. That's absolute facts dude. Number one facts. Yeah I smoke weed and I just feel
bad about all the times I wasn't smoking weed. Yeah. Yeah I just think back on those times
like fuck man I could have been high as fuck in school. Damn I could have been smoking and
stoking the flame of fire. I could have been toking at the church. I could have been stoking
in
What if your life is the Truman Show?
Yeah.
Whoa.
What if, but not the whatever your name is show.
What if it's the Truman Show and you're one of the extras?
Whoa.
And you're just not getting paid.
I think it's time to unionize, buddy.
We're saying sag?
Yeah, there's a comment on there that says, by guest, it says, "So I'm not going to say
that I thought of literally every single one of these topics when I was stoned last night,
- What?
Something tells me they're lying
and they can't think about it.
- They're smoking conspiracy weed.
- Yeah, they're smoking, damn.
Can you imagine thinking about all 10
of those things in a row?
- At once?
- I would get too high.
- Yeah.
- If I thought about those.
- Someone says, "Bitches, you nailed it again."
WTF was I saying?
They got so high they forgot in the middle,
without even, they didn't even have three periods.
They just did a comma.
- This is good.
One guest says, "How do you bitches know my life?
Fuck, am I that obvi?
Who gives a fuck?
Pass me the Doritos with melted cheese.
Stealing bag, stoner's delight."
And then there was--
- Doritos with melted cheese?
- Yeah, and then the reply to that is,
"Doritos and cheese?
Get outta here, fatty."
(laughing)
Yeah, Doritos and cheese is insane.
- So funny, so true, so stoned.
LMFAO, maybe this article part of the conspiracy.
(laughing)
This is part of the conspiracy against me.
Yeah, my biggest, my favorite conspiracy is that Betches makes you smoke weed.
Betches gets you high from reading. Oh my god, dude, I have a message on Betches.
Here's a comment. Me too.
What's our message?
It says, "If you tell anybody, we'll fuck you."
Oh my god, dude.
Here's a comment that says, "I loved Tip of the Blunt.
the blunt, clever and witty as always. To the haters, NASA called and said even with the
budget cuts they can still afford to make your mom's dildos.
Oh my god dude. Alien dildo. That's some heat right there.
Your mom likes cheap dildos. She likes dildos that even the NASA budget can cover.
Yeah, giant rocket shaped dildos that have thrusters.
the
are a solid piece of the law on the first one we have to thank his peers
thank you p_r_o_ yes of course
uh... newt and all of a change and named allison brie larson you bitch
thank you
reviewed and all of the other than you did she if you're ten dollar picture in
there right now that uh... directors commentary for uh... the uh... jolly b
documentaries up on peter on for ten dollar tier only
so
just and uh... that out there that's a good and i want to know if we can smoke
a big bond for the joy that's true all of our our content is we'd friendly and for
twenty friendly as well
uh... on that for the parts i mean
except for everything that's in
local that's not a pro-gol edge to tend to know who's the boss
yes we are
great fan art on great member thank you can't conjure arviz
can't conjure arviz thank you so much that's a crazy ass name thank you mark
Mark Smith. Uh-huh. Mark Smith. Uh, Deirdre, uh, do you guys know how to pronounce that name?
Deirdre. Deirdre Brennan. Deirdre Brennan. Thank you. Irish person. Will Black. Will
Black, thank you. Will Black, thank you so much. David. Could be my dad. That's David.
Kamri Caleb's dad. Cappy. Thanks Cappy. Cappy from Mario. Cappy from, yeah, Mario and Cappy's
liquors in Saugus, Massachusetts. Yeah, it's him. Mason Desan, Desan? Yeah. Desan. From Star Wars.
Ten dollars, Devin McLaughlin, thank you. Or McLaughlin. You rock. One of those pronunciations.
Seamus. Seamus Malik Ghazali. Seamus, what's up? My man, go listen to, I'm sure I, like everybody
have probably fucked his last name up, but please go listen to him on True or Not, he was great.
Nigel C, which could all it could be Kate Nigel Caleb
Or Nigel Cameron
Don't think so crunky tiny. Can you shut up for one second? Yeah, you should also my name has an a also
You know, but I see a tiny CAL
Yeah, it's to shape. It's the shape of your penis a
tiny CAL
Wow, yeah
Crunky bars. Thank you. Crunky bars. Thank you Ragnar Narfelt
That's a fucking cool name. Yeah, you sound like a berserker man. That's pretty sick.
That's a troll name. Yeah. Melissa Taylor. Thank you. Thank you, Melissa.
Oh, we got a new sub in the middle of the episode. Whoa. Yeah. Who is it?
I don't remember. I don't have the email. I probably just read it. It is Melissa Taylor. Okay.
Good timing, Melissa. Yeah, Melissa's shout out. Happy 4/20, Melissa. Happy 4/20.
And never, never don't be high.
Never smoke again.
Always smoke again.
Alright, bye y'all.
Goodbye.
Weed out.
Yeah, smoking out.