You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(explosion)
- Shut the fuck up.
- We already started.
- He's playing with Dom's yarn ball.
- Oh no, he's playing with,
the cat is playing with a yarn ball?
- How dare he?
- He can't do that.
- That's what cats do.
- We have Felix Biederman
of
hour for me. Yeah, of course. I'm glad that we are not important enough to jump out of
one of the 500 Counter-Strike games that you play every day. And don't improve at all.
Don't get any better at it. Yeah, just losing over and over and over again. I'm glad that
we didn't reach that threshold. Not learning literally anything. What would make you stop
playing? I don't know. I think if like, I think if like I dated a hot woman who like
kind of hated me and she did one of those things where you break up for a week and
then like you reconcile and then she's like you have to stop playing
Counter-Strike and I'm like okay but then we just like do a mutual activity that
made us both resent each other and then we would just stop talking to each other
like one of those breakups where you just don't talk to each other anymore.
So this woman is what it would take. That's it. Not all the fucking like the hacks that
just happened.
Yeah, not the stuff that gets on your personal info.
I don't give a shit.
Buy something with my fucking stupid debit card.
You think I fucking care?
That's just another phone call I have to make.
Go ahead, buy a fucking $500 knife skid with my debit card.
I literally don't fucking give a shit.
I fucking do it.
Who cares?
No one's having sex, no one's fucking doing anything anymore.
No one's ever going to get pussy again.
We're going to run out of kids.
Fucking buy your stupid knife, you dumb piece of shit.
I guess you're right.
Money does...
Read my DMs, there's nothing good in there.
You know what my DMs are?
It's just a bunch of people being like, "Oh, have you heard of this?
It's Rick Roll."
Like, I don't give a shit.
You're not going to get me in trouble.
You can't cancel me.
It's just going to be me and different group DMs talking about how, like, you know, anyone
who hates me on Twitter, I want...
I think they're hot.
I want to fuck them.
Go ahead.
So you're not going to find the secret fascist, crypto fascist DM?
Yeah.
Yeah, look at me in Ape Chat.
I don't care.
I don't give a shit.
Ape Chat is the crypto-fascist leftist DM.
Yeah.
That's where we come from.
It's the most fascist DM ever.
Oh, DMs are fucked up.
It's because of the apes, yeah.
Y'all, did you know that the Nazis loved nature because they thought it would represent order?
And these MFs have Ape Chat, but y'all sleep though.
The ape represents raw power.
Yes.
Yeah.
And nothing else.
And they loved apes.
Alex is right now at the Chapo headquarters, which is a big building with Will Miniker's
face on the front and it says "CCCC" over and over again.
Yes, yeah.
No, it is.
If there's anything we do, it's...
Well, I like that thread because it was saying that we're not really fascist, but we just
want people to be fascist, which is...
That's cool.
That's the ultimate activist move.
Yeah.
That's like being in the opposite of Oscar Schindler.
Shepherding people into fascism even though you yourself are not one.
Yeah, I mean that's the way, that's how you stay the prominent voice of the left.
You make sure there's no one else on the left.
You get everyone else over the right.
That's the trick.
Yeah, you take down such leftists as Michael Rapaport.
You know what I mean?
On a daily basis.
Yeah, the most important socialist voice we have.
You gotta put him in his place.
I love Michael Rapaport because his main thing is, he's like one of those old comedians, he's
not really convenient like one of those old guys who's like yo yo why y'all
getting offended by anything but he sees any post by a young person like even
referencing like Columbine like today right yeah he's like yo there's some
things you do not joke about that's the best part about it is like he's not he's
not a stand-up like he was an actor who is in like a couple of mob movies and
they're not for teens romance yeah and now he like goes and like edits himself
into episodes of tough crowd and then just talks about how offensive it is that
fucking somebody made a Columbine joke.
Yo on that episode with me and Patrice I fucking...
Patrice O'Neal was a legend dude he was one of my closest friends I try to emulate him in every way including speech patterns.
Yeah and diabetes.
Patrice O'Neal gave me cardboard from his house to spin my head on.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Michael Rapaport, dude pick up a mic dude,
come fucking, come on the pod.
We'll get you and Thomas, we'll squash it, you know.
- Yeah, I had a few with Rapaport before anyone,
by the way. - Really?
- Yeah, I'm really getting into like,
I'm really like, I'm becoming one of those
like old Hollywood guys, it's like,
or like more like Trump, I was actually the first to.
(laughing)
He, so everyone knows Eli Lake,
Eli Lake was the guy everyone made fun of until...
Yeah, the egg boy.
He kinda looks like Harold.
Yeah.
It was before Twitter added new NPCs that you could fight in raids.
And Eli Lake was just... he's like a shitty neocon who everyone hated.
And for whatever idiot reason, Michael Rapaport was like, "Yo, this boy comes with the knowledge!"
And really liked Eli Lake.
So he went on Eli Lake's podcast, which I don't think runs anymore, and talked about how he
was getting made fun of on Twitter a lot by me.
And he said, "Well, one of the trolls is actually very talented and does a piece of political
satire I think is very good, Carl Diggler."
And then Rappaport went, "Yo, fuck Carl Diggler, Duke!"
That was the origin of the feud.
He's I don't hear every week. It seems like he there's a thing. We're like black people like can you stop?
Doing everything you're doing. Yeah, meanwhile. He's saying. I don't know what you're talking about as he's injecting himself with sickle-cell
Well, he like yeah, he attacked I think a friend of the pot about list universe today
Me
Basically immediately at any he was like this is this might be bad because Michael Rappaport as a picture of my penis now forever
I was like it's it's gonna be alright man. You can win this you could live with that
You can say that Michael Rapaport hacked him.
Right?
Yeah, exactly.
He got into my iCloud.
He's in the jail.
I think Thomas is 14 anyway.
Yeah, Thomas is a kid.
Yeah, what's Michael Rapaport doing with that boy?
Thomas is 14 but he looks like that.
He's a very high T child.
I played Warzone with him last night and I hope he doesn't mind me saying this.
He told me that his mom did like a 23andMe thing and found out that his family is in
the 99th percentile for Neanderthal DNA presence.
I thought you were gonna say that.
So good, dude.
It makes perfect sense.
Well, but Neanderthals, Neanderthal, like they were kind of, like it's kind of a good look
if you're like a human.
I have like very low, I got 23 and me, very low Neanderthal and I wish I had more Neanderthal.
Damn, you gave up the DNA, bro?
I got a little bit.
You gave up the genome?
Yeah, man.
Well, my, someone, my friend got it for me and it's like, then you have to do it.
Yeah, you gotta put your spit and sin in the mail.
I got a lot of mileage out of it though because it was like you are 99% Ashkenazi.
Oh dude.
Cool.
Well it ended, we had an Elizabeth Warren type family myth where like my mom thought that
we were like half Spanish, like the sexy kind, the Sephardic.
And it's like no.
No.
We're all the fucking beet farmer kind.
That rocks dude.
I did that.
I got a, I'm like 92% Irish.
I think I already posted about it, but I have like a 14th great-grandfather named Connor O'Connor
Wait, didn't you you texted us and said that you're like 9th grade? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Amaziah Harding. Yeah
My my ninth great-grandfather in like this 1700s or something like that
Killed his wife and tried to weekend at Bernie's her
When the coroner came to like his fucking shack or whatever
They were they were like now hold on
Like he said oh, no he said that she died at natural causes, but like yeah, I don't know
So he when you say he weakened it burnt did he walk her around town?
Hammer stuck in her head. No. No I was reading his will
It was easier to kill your wife back
Oh, it was way easier.
You knew uh...
Yeah, the staircase would have been the shortest documentary ever in 1750.
Pat, you knew...
It would have been like, yeah, he pushed her down the stairs, of course.
That's what you do when you're sick of your wife.
You knew he weakened at Bernie, her, because his will said, um, he's leaving his, his, his uh, really complex marionette set to his son.
(laughter)
His robot exoskeleton.
Yeah, he had a robot exoskeleton in 1792.
He had a piston suit, a hydraulic.
He had a steampunk mech suit.
(laughter)
Well, that's how they created Gundams.
Yeah.
Every Gundam has a dead wife in the middle of it.
(laughter)
A guy during one of the Shogunates killed his wife,
and he was like, "Oh, I'm gonna get in trouble for this."
That's the actual plot of Evangelion.
Yeah, I was just about to say it.
[Laughter]
Literally, yeah.
Eva, yeah, like, uh...
Uh, fuck,
what's his name again?
Uh, Genki...
Fuck, the doctor. The dead wife guy.
Oh, uh, uh, fuckin'
uh, Gendo.
Yeah, Gendo Ikari,
like, he's...
It is cool that he
just made a child wife.
Yeah.
Like, the one thing that was wrong with my wife was that she wasn't 14.
And also she couldn't pilot a giant robot.
Those licked her mind.
Those are the two bad things about my perfect wife.
Alright, so Felix, obviously you're a gamer.
You know, I think that's no secret.
You have a headset on as we speak.
I feel like this was the... Halo is a big part of this show, just 'cause, you know, I love
Halo. Although if...
I fucking adore Halo.
You gotta love Halo, baby. If the Secret Service is listening, I've never played a first person
shooter in my life. I just appreciate Halo from a very far distance.
He reads the novels.
Yeah, exactly. I swear to God, the first like real book that I read was The Fall of Reach.
I don't think that's a real book. I don't think that counts. It's the first real book. I think
it was whatever you read after that.
Real book. No. That was my first real book.
Your mom made that book for you so you would start reading it.
It was a custom book.
No. No.
It was just pictures.
Yeah, it was not like it sold so well.
Your mom went on like Vistaprint and then made that.
No, I got it at Walmart and it was $7.
Oh, okay.
Come on, dude.
That confirms it.
We did, I picked out some lists from the top tens,
which is a website we use a lot
that are Halo themed vaguely.
They're about, so the first three,
these are all people arguing that other games
are either better than Halo
or Halo is better than other games.
So this first one is top 10 reasons
Minecraft is better than Halo.
And I don't know how familiar you are
with this website, Felix,
but basically the entire website is children fighting about video games.
Top 10? I think I've like...
I like list websites like this because it's like...
It's the last thing you do.
You just read those to have white noise in your head.
That's the thing you do before you like try to kill yourself or call the suicide hotline.
Yes, this like creates schizophrenia.
Like this is the... this is how it happens.
And this website does is...
It's different from Ranker or other ones that have an editorial staff.
This is just a crowd-sourced voting website.
Yeah, it's their user submissions.
And yeah, they're all 13-year-olds who are just struggling on the internet.
13-year-olds and us.
Yeah, and we're a year and a half into talking about it every day.
[LAUGHTER]
I think it would be awesome if that was the only media job left,
was being the editor for Top10.com.
all these all these people who like wrote articles that are like well Bernie didn't
literally rape but he is kind of like a rapist doesn't everyone agree like they
have that's the only they become they become journalistic serfs we have to
work for the yeah they're just like they're just getting bullied by like the
Glen Greenwald of top ten the best top ten list just keep this is still have
Top 10 reasons Justin Bieber is gay and just get him flamed on the internet.
That's his most viewed article.
That's like the Snowden article.
Dude, that's the thing, this place is the final frontier of posting.
Oh yeah, it's got a ranking system, you level up on here.
Yeah, you can finally put a level, they finally gamified posting.
Yeah, the person who wrote this article is the vicar of St. Louis up the cream bun and
Jam. That's a level four.
Wow.
That's only level four.
Level five is mayor of Michelle Delving.
Awesome, dude.
What, who is Michelle Delving?
Where do you think this website comes from? Like what, what
country did this?
I'd say probably like one of the countries that like, used to be
in the USSR. But then when you read their Wikipedia, it's like
the age expectancy, or life expectancy after 1993 is
26 years old.
The chief exports are second-hand coffins.
It's whatever country Tom Hanks was from in the movie Terminal.
Yeah, yeah.
Just one of those landlocked piece of shit countries.
Yeah, that all of your relatives are from.
Yeah, well mine, yeah.
Mine, yeah, definitely.
number one reason according to uh... the top tens white minecraft is better than
halo it doesn't have any inappropriate violence
that's all
that is true is only a program i'm crafton
you have a very appropriate violence in uh... uh... slaughtering house jenny
goes
yes i mean i'm all hitting a pig with a pickaxe or something
you know what he did come out against the animal yet
The creepers are subhuman.
[Laughter]
When you really think about it.
To look at a-
To look at an innocent person's house and to blow your cell phone.
[Laughter]
It's absolutely abhorrent.
Minecraft is responsible for a lot of-
This is- This is violence in the way that
people in academia say it, but
you know who Tfue is?
Yeah, vaguely.
Yeah, so he's like one of the biggest streamers on Twitch
and he's like, he's the guy who said that ninja sucks. Yeah, he called ninja a pussy recently.
That's what it is. Well, he was playing Minecraft with a 15 year old streamer and just said the n-word like the soft a
Damn
It was like, it was cool. Like he like it was like everyone was cool with it
Like he didn't get in trouble, but it's like how do you say that during Minecraft?
*laughter*
Yeah, yeah, what what what part of Minecraft will drive you to the n-word?
He wasn't even mad though, he was just like doing this weird move.
He's yelling at the villagers.
He was!
Oh no!
Oh my god.
That's the highest level is calling the villager the soft day at work.
Please, be Minecraft.
Yeah, the term of endearment version.
Yeah.
To the villager.
Yeah, the Michael Rapaport version of it.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I was trying to say they weren't my friends.
Just...
Yeah.
I watched today, just because Michael Rapaport was driving me insane, I watched a like 20
minute interview that he did with Taleb Kweli and he keeps saying, he keeps saying, he keeps
calling him Kwa, first of all.
He's being like, "Kwa, you know me, dog.
You know me."
And apparently there was some controversy where he like made fun of a woman for having ashy
ankles.
Oh my God.
(laughing)
- And Talib Kweli is like,
"Why are you calling black women's ankles ashy online?"
And he's like, "Yo, I just call it like I sees it, bro."
(laughing)
I fucking love him, dude.
- My friend trolled Talib Kweli
for about seven years, I would say.
- He's one of the all-time,
just like he'll respond to anybody.
- I've been thinking, when I got my check,
I thought he will definitely respond to me now,
but it's like, I couldn't think of anything.
But that is a great guy for Michael Rapaport to talk to.
- Oh, yeah, absolutely. - That is top level.
- Yeah.
- He should wear the hat, honestly.
The black thought, telepoly, most F hat.
He would look good, man.
- Do you remember the New Danger?
- Yes.
- I got a $20 iTunes gift card in Christmas of 2004,
and it was, I had my first PC ever,
like Half-Life of Two was out, I was playing that,
and I was like, oh, what am I gonna listen to
while I play Half-Life?
Oh, I know, Most F, because I liked the song Mathematics
and I bought the new Danger on iTunes,
and I was like, this is dog shit.
- Oh, it sucks, dude.
- That's, I think that's what got me back
into pirating music.
He says like, I think I like felt bad about pirating,
and I was like, I'm not gonna do it,
I don't wanna like get my parents sued,
I'm gonna stop doing it. I'm gonna use iTunes and then I bought the new danger and I was like now fuck this
Do you like the video do you remember the video of most deaf?
He goes through the tube feeding process that they did to the prisoners at Guantanamo Bay. Yes
It feels like a dream yeah, there's a video that
Like he did it with like like vice or something and it's him in a white room in a in an orange jumpsuit
and they stick tubes in his nose and he is hamming it up so hard and and then like
as soon as it's in and then out he's like yes that's basically what they're
doing thanks to George Bush this was it was in like 2013 this is it this is from
an alternate universe that only you and Felix know about. In our world this was the biggest
video. This was the first viral video in Calebverse. It's you, it's you, Felix, and Michael Rapoport
and you guys. I would love to live in the Michael Rapoport alternate universe. In his
I want to do I'm gonna do being Michael Rappaport
So fucking badly it's just it's just different rooms of him hanging out with a tribe called quest
You go through the little door and then it's just like you have to like go to some bodega in Brooklyn and like
Everybody in every scenario calls him black Michael Rappaport
Michael Rappaport, I was, I forget where I was talking about this, but you know how like
the my favorite like New York slang was when guys would call each other God because it was like the
5% nation thing where every black man is a God
And I think Michael Rappaport's probably the only white guy who ever tried that. Oh, he said God
He says he still uses B all the time. Oh, that's awesome. Yeah, so like in the telequality interview
So he's like, "B, you gotta listen to me on this one.
I'm spitting facts right now."
What was the interview only about?
Because I remember when he got catfished for that.
I saw one section of it, which was 20 minutes, but the full interview is like two hours,
and I will never watch two hours of him telling Quillian.
Why was he interviewing him?
Go for it.
30,000 views on YouTube.
And it's Talib Kweli doing some,
doing like some podcast that he did for like six months.
And he's talking to Michael Rapaport.
Oh, is that the Barstool one he got fired from?
No, that's Michael Rapaport had a podcast.
Oh, oh, oh, right.
And he got fired from for beating his wife or something.
Yeah.
(laughing)
I think it was, I don't know,
I may be making that up.
I think you might be.
No, no, I'm actually not.
He beat the shit out of his wife.
No, he absolutely did.
Wait, did he?
Dude, he killed his wife, dude.
Oh, wow.
Wow, that's what I know.
That's what I know, dude.
Yeah, dude. He killed his wife and he held the gun sideways and shot her.
[Laughter]
I'm serious.
He said, "That was awesome," and then he threw her into the Hudson River.
And then they fired him from Barstool Sports for that. Can you believe it?
Yeah, and Portnoy does not abide with killing your wife. He's a responsible man.
I respect Dave.
He's a real Boston Catholic. He doesn't abide by the law.
And nobody from Boston ever hit their wife.
No. No. It just doesn't happen.
It doesn't happen.
People in Boston, like, people have this like, bullshit attitude about Boston
because they themselves are too cowardly to drunk drive in Boston.
Right. That's right.
Finally something happened.
That's right. That's right.
That's fucking right.
Well, I if I was so I've been fantasizing about the breakup of America and obviously I would go back to the Midwest to try to
Become like, you know the Charlemagne of the Great Lakes, but one of my first actually made the God
The God was on radio and was like, yeah, so I drugged and raped
Yeah, and then like just nothing
No one gave a shit, but I thought it was awesome. Yeah, he was like yo, that's how we do it
But no I more like the French Charlemagne, okay
One of my first dad.
Prince Charlemagne the god.
Oh that's even, he's even worse.
He's a way bigger rapist.
He does that all the time then.
I would, I would like create a drug driving license.
Yeah, oh smart.
That's one of the things I would do.
Yeah, an endorsement for your license.
Well yeah, you should be able to.
It's like, yeah.
It's a, it's a little beer emoji.
At the bottom of the license where it's got the heart for organ donors is Nick Nolte's
mug shot.
I've been trying to like pretend to be a drunk driving advocate on Twitter and no one's yelled
at me for it.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, no one's taken the bait.
Because I know you're right.
I think people are going to defend it.
What are you going to do?
I want Rappaport, I wanted Rappaport to like notice the emojis in my name, like the clicking
beers in the car.
Oh yeah, and be like, "You scumbag drunk driver."
Yo, drug driving killed some of the best hip hop artists of all time.
Bushwick Bill?
Fucking Bushwick Bill?
Fucking I don't know who else.
Bushwick Bill is like in Michael Rapaport's brain, it's his mini me.
He walks out of his Brooklyn apartment and it's Bushwick Bill.
Alright, back to this list.
Number two, you get to be creative in Minecraft, I guess, unlike Halo.
You can be creative in Halo.
Forge, baby.
The top comment here, "What about Forge?"
"Oh, burn."
"What about mods?"
"Castles?"
"Pixel art?"
"House statues?"
"Oh, burn."
Definitely seven-year-olds.
Fucking do notice, baby.
Fucking destroy.
Well the reply to that comment doesn't realize that they're talking about Halo and thinks
they're talking about Minecraft and says "Do you realize that those can be built in Halo
as well?"
Damn, I love the confusion.
Yeah, no one's getting like, I don't know what.
You can build whatever you want.
Also, you can like think about the greatest cop player of all time.
about Walshii and like Bestman, even my own friend, girlfriend Haver, they're incredibly
creative players.
That's what makes competitive Halo awesome.
And that's why it's like one of the first eSports in America.
So take that you fucking idiot seven year old fucking moron.
You fucking pussy.
It is funny that this whole show is yelling at children.
But they're wrong!
They're fucking wrong all the time!
That's what keeps us going, is that we know that we are right and they are wrong.
Like number three, you can install mods.
You can install mods on Halo, man.
You can do the Master Chief Nude mod.
I know.
Yeah.
Oh, trust me.
Why doesn't this fucking kid get a job, buy a PC, it's only $3,500 for everything.
Yeah, get an RTX card.
get all of it, get a good motherboard, then you can play Halo on PC and then you can mod
it instead of just playing on an Xbox like a fucking imbecile like you are.
You don't even need to get all that shit, you can just download the Halo CE demo and
download a Mario map into it.
I've done it.
You can download the fucking Mushroom Kingdom into the demo of Halo CE.
How many Cortana nipple mods exist?
Oh a billion.
Yeah, with all different lengths.
[Laughter]
I like that in the later bad Halo games, that they realize that every player's fantasy is to fuck Cortana.
So like, "Yeah, she's like kind of a woman now."
I don't know.
Yeah, they also make her butt crack longer and longer in every single version of her.
It's awesome.
They made her the Siri for the Lumos.
Yeah, I talk to her on a daily basis.
That shit is so funny.
Yeah.
Awesome dude, and guess what the icon for Cortana is?
A hole.
And you want to tell me you're not sexualizing her?
Microsoft?
No.
There have probably been a lot of guys who, like, after a schizophrenic break, probably
during quarantine, have killed themselves while operating Windows 10 because they think
like Cortana's in love with them and they want to live in their computer.
Yes, dude, that's the danger of the AI version of Clippy or whatever, is that it talks to you.
What?
It's like every sci-fi movie has always had an evil robot with the exact voice that's on my computer right now.
Well, Clippy, everyone knows Clippy was for gay men.
Yeah, Clippy was fan service for gay men in Microsoft Windows.
So like once straight men started buying computers, they introduced Cortana.
Straight men didn't buy women.
So everyone has something and that's like why I'm a Windows guy.
Because they like, they accommodate people.
Apple just like, Siri is just like a fucking sexless whatever.
Absolutely no pussy on Siri.
There's no clippy, there's nothing for anyone.
You can make Siri Australian, I know that.
Okay, alright.
That's something.
Yeah.
I have an Australian male Siri.
You would, dude.
Yeah, you would, dude.
No, I do.
Yeah, you would.
Yeah, you would be- you do because you would.
Yeah, you do, dude.
What?
That doesn't even make sense, you gay bitch.
Number four, um...
Number four, if you die, you can get your stuff back.
Wow, that's fast.
Have you ever played Respawn or campaigned with checkpoints, you fucking moron?
God, it's like these kids, I think they misunderstand Halo because they are not old enough to buy
it from GameStop without a parent's ID.
Facts.
Yeah.
From Fed, download it.
Learn what Steam is.
I remember I had, when I was growing up, I got the Modern Warfare 2 at Costco and I bought
it with like my birthday money or whatever and we we my dad was with my dad
because I didn't have a Costco membership I was like 14. Did they have any like
Costco exclusive items like they do? No no but when I bought it they were like
the guy at the cashier said to my dad... Like some Kirkland signature like...
The guy said to my dad... You get a Kirkland signature item in game.
You get a Kirkland signature... You get yeah you get a chicken bake icon in Modern Warfare 2.
You can only get that. I would love that.
Dude, yeah, they did that with Skate 3 and Miracle Whip.
[Laughter]
But the cashier, he looked at my dad, he was like holding the game, and he was like,
"Sir, I'm legally obliged to tell you that this game has a mass shooting scene in it.
Are you sure you want to purchase this for your son?"
[Laughter]
He said that he was legally obliged.
Like there was some fucking, some law that uh, kids couldn't play the most awesome part of the game.
Sorry.
There, when I was like uh, when I was like 12, my dad like, I guess he was like kinda interested in it.
And I couldn't think of what mission to like, make him play.
Like I didn't think like, oh maybe do like the combat training mission.
So I made my dad.
You made your dad play No Rush.
Yeah I made my dad play No Rush and he was like, wait I'm just mowing people down?
What the fuck is this?
Hey this is kinda fun Patrick.
It would have been worse if he really liked it.
He was like, "How many more levels are there?"
Are they off?
That would be so fucked if you made your dad a mass shooter.
With video games.
I show my dad NoRussian, then like next week he's got like Postal 2 running on the computer.
What was that fucking game, Hatred?
Yeah, yeah, I was just reading about that.
Yeah, he becomes the Hatred guy.
Yeah, they're putting that game on Switch, which is so funny to me.
That's hilarious
That's the only people I know switches are like
women
My late my like young very young cousins
Yeah, there's no there's no real games on the switch except Zelda and
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That was so fucked up, dude
Come on guys. I'm sorry vote to really
I use it for Halo. I throw it at my wife while I'm on warzone and say like play
play gone home or something. Here you can play too, here's your controller.
Your controller to other people. Yeah I tape a screenshot of Lizzie McGuire to the front of it
Just let her press all the buttons for a while.
[Laughter]
Number five, uh, it's controlled by keyboard and mouse.
Again, it's- these kids are so oblivious.
[Gibberish]
I'm getting so pissed off right now.
I have to take a- I'm fucking pissed off.
I have to take a leak. You guys handle this one.
I can't even fucking speak.
These kids have never used, like, a Razer Deathadder Elite.
Gotcha, yeah, so, okay, so let me get this straight.
You ever heard of the Master Chief Collection?
Yeah.
Ever heard of that, like I said earlier, the Halo CE demo?
Oh, Felix actually, we can say whatever we want about him right now.
Um, he, uh, Felix, fuck, he, um, shit.
His favorite candy is Tootsie Rolls.
Oh shit!
Dude, we have to edit that out.
He's gonna be so pissed.
He's gonna be so pissed off, dude.
His favorite candies are Tootsie Rolls and toothpaste.
He told us before we started this that he likes brushing his teeth.
He eats floss.
Yeah, fuckin' sicko.
Number six, there's no war going on.
That's not true.
Yeah, ever heard of it?
There is a war going on in the Ender, or whatever.
The Ender Dragon.
There's a war between the creative geniuses and the griefers.
Yeah, a never-ending war.
And the griefers are winning.
We need more creatives in Minecraft.
Everybody get on Minecraft.
Kill your local griefer.
Just DIY kids walking around with that on their shirt.
It's got like a creeper.
It's like one of those big back patches.
Add it to the teespring.
Yeah, kill your local griefer.
That's gonna be the second Minecraft themed shirt on our merch store.
There's already a Minecraft shirt.
We already have a shirt that says "I went to your mine and nobody knew you."
And now we're gonna have "Kill your local griefer."
How do you grief someone in Minecraft?
I like literally never played Minecraft.
You just, okay, so there's a-
You take down their house.
There's a Potabat List Minecraft server that somebody started.
And I spent like two days at the beginning of quarantine building a very cool modern
house designed by an idiot boy on a chair.
It was not a modern house.
It was a tower of wooden blocks that had no windows, no doors.
It was just a tower.
No, no, no.
At the top I built the house.
Maybe you never saw it because you were invited.
It was a platform.
It wasn't a house.
But in the middle of the night, two griefers joined the server and burned down my house.
And it was like, it was a heat in my body I've never felt in my life.
It hurt so bad.
And I asked the guy who mods the server, I was like, "Is there any way you can fix this?"
And he went into the code and reversed what they did.
But for those few moments where I saw my creation on fire, I wanted to kill myself.
That's what John Wick felt.
Yeah, exactly.
The exact same feeling.
Yeah, that's what happened.
That house was a gift from my dead wife.
Like, he met his-
Well, John Wick had a-
John Wick had a 15 year old, like, dyed hair Minecraft wife,
and that's why- he's like a morally complex character,
'cause you shouldn't do that as a 45 year old man.
True, yeah.
But also, like, that was his Minecraft house,
so it's like, that's why I like that movie,
because there's like- you don't really know who the bad guy is,
or who the good guy is, but you can appreciate
how good John Wick is at action.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's reasonable.
And how cool his house was before it went down.
He did have a very cool house.
Yeah.
I never found it-
I've started that.
What is he-
What was his job?
Why was he so rich?
Why did he have such a cool house?
He probably saved a lot of money from being an assassin.
Oh, true.
He probably like-
Because he was retired and it's like-
I presume-
Well, I'm something of a financial expert.
Yeah.
So, with John Wick-
John Wick probably got paid like a million dollars per hit.
And what he probably did was-
He bought these things called municipal bonds.
And when you buy-
it's those are corporate bonds the interest in corporate bonds is taxed at
uh... the rate which we tax capital gains
but the interest on uh... municipal bonds is not
so if john wick bought you don't say five million dollars worth of huntsville
alabama municipal bonds paying out at three point five percent
that's like
he made so much money none of those taxed
he got the original five million back and he retired he was done
and then he also had pirates coins
in a briefcase
it's true
they also found a pirate's chest
which is a used coin
that was like one of my fantasies
as a kid
finding ancient money
dude pirate coins are so cool
for some reason old money, old gold
feels like it should be worth more
that was my thinking
if you find the equivalent of a million dollars
from ten thousand years ago
it's like a billion dollars now
give it to me a child yeah you go to the you go to the exchange the money
exchange in the airport and get good give them your doubloons and you can
there's a great exchange rate on the millions of one million dollars in a
briefcase just in case yeah I said earlier before we started recording that
oh yeah yes yes for you his ancestry told him he has pirate blood I would like you
explain what that means I am related to someone who has captain in their name
according to ancestry.com that's and you just that's all I needed to know it's
all I needed to hear where else would he be the Irish Navy like I don't think so
yeah exactly 70% from Ireland 30% from the sea 99% bitch I could just be named
captain I mean yeah I have mafia blood yeah oh yeah yeah my my like a Jewish
mafia no no he worked for Capone. No, 3/6 Mafia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, me rap before baby.
Yo, this goes back centuries, blood!
Um, no, it was, uh, he worked for Al Capone and stole money from him and then got
nervous and killed himself.
(laughter)
So yes, Jewish Mafia.
He fucked up. That is the Jewish Mafia.
"Oh God, they're gonna be so mad at me!"
(laughter)
"Oh God!"
"I should just die!"
(laughter)
I have,
and then like another ancestor,
like the biggest thing they achieved
was he was a piano player in the Russian
Imperial Army. Oh nice.
Yeah, well he played the Halo theme like so that was he played it on cellos like yo-yo mob, but yeah
I'm just imagining a version of casino where every character is Robert De Niro in that movie
That's like your whole family yeah, no, it's they were not an accomplished gang
They didn't they didn't get a whole lot done before like the 1900s. They were
They just lived in like you know
The worst part of the Russian Empire and like oh my dad's side
Pretended to be German, which is a very ignominious faith
That is cool though. Yeah. Yeah. Well, they pretended to be German Jews
They were like we're still Jewish, but we're like the the fancy kind
Did that get you points back then it did well it should have because like
Do you know who invented the word kayak?
It was German Jews describing Russian Jews
But they were probably right because they'd like they swear they could speak German and they like can't
That's kind of like that's kind of like me I took two years
- I feel like your goal in life should be,
when you're 300 years in the future,
when your ancestors, your descendants do 23andMe,
they'll be like, "Oh, he had a podcast."
- Yeah, yeah, they'll be able to tell.
- Podcast or what?
- It's just like the pirate thing.
It's just like the pirate thing for me.
It's just, I talked about, I made fun of little kids.
- Yeah, he made fun of little kids online all the time.
He loved eating cheeseburgers.
It says right here.
It says right here that your grandfather was addicted to cheeseburgers.
It says right here he tried to put a bunch of chips in a 7-Eleven hot dog and choked at
24.
That's like your version of Final Destination, is you see that vision as you're sprinkling
the chips on the hot dog.
You can't help yourself, you just go, "Oh well."
It's like, "Ah, I'm dead.
I gotta do it."
There's no choice.
It's lunch time, I gotta do it.
Let's see, what else is good on this list?
You've got a little own here.
You can play with six or more players and then two comets back to back.
It says you can play with 64 on Halo.
I don't think I ever did a 64 person Halo match.
You could, you could, you absolutely could.
I played Halo Reach for a while, but then I went to Battlefield.
Bad Company 2 is so good.
Best FPS of all time.
We talked about this.
It was cool to blow up a building.
Oh, didn't you?
Caleb, weren't you ranked or something?
So like at the beginning, when Bad Company 2 first started being like a competitive MLG
game, me and a friend started like a clan that there was nobody in it except us, you're supposed
to have like 8 people at minimum, and we registered on the MLG website.
And then our first week we got paired with FaZe, and we started the match and there was
only two of us so we had to forfeit but they reported that it was a forfeit and
we reported that it was a win and for some reason the energy system it got
they've just believed us and so for like two weeks we were the number one bad
company clan in the world and we never played a game. That is, no, that's well
that's gonna be on the 23andMe. Yeah. When they got the stories on the side of
ancestry and it's like oh my uncle fell down a fucking elevator shaft or whatever
it's just Caleb lied about gaming when he was 15. He was ranked number one for two weeks.
Your uncle rocked. Those were, Battlefield those are the best games because they
were like openly ridiculous but then when that, Battlefield 1 happened because
like enough people at DICE were like war is serious. Yeah, we need to do the
least fun war. I also think Battlefield is the ultimate pipeline to the actual military
for kids. As far as games go. Because the thing is, because of the bullet drop with the snipers,
a kid gets good at that and they're like "I could do that in real life." It did almost
happen to me. I would play Battlefield, I would play Bad Company and be like, I would
ARCA shot and be like, I could definitely do this.
- Yeah, it'd be easy.
This is so accurate.
- I probably have talked about this on the show before,
but did you ever play America's Army?
- No.
- America's Army, it was just Operation Flashpoint,
but re-skinned by the army.
And me and my friends, I was,
'cause I'd given up the idea of getting posy in high school.
I played Operation Flashpoint all the time.
- Nice.
- And me and my friends were amazing at it.
So we, like American's Army was a recruiting tool,
but we would absolutely like wash
just like dumb people from Mississippi
who were like, they thought it was gonna be like COD
or something.
We just fucking decimate them
because we were fucking nerds.
And I think we probably kept a lot of people
out of the military.
(laughing)
- Damn dude.
That's praxis.
That was the start of my journey as anti-imperialist.
Yeah, it was a good buck.
Owning my cousins on America's Army.
Yeah, yeah.
That rocks, dude.
Thank you for that.
No, you're welcome.
Thank you for your service.
I kept them out of Iraq.
You did.
Yeah.
That's true.
All my cousins who joined the military
just like went to San Diego
and then convinced themselves that they were heroes
and then came back with the worst tattoos
that anybody's ever had.
And now they work as electricians.
They ate a bunch of California burritos
with the French fries in them,
and they're like, "Yeah, that's the same
"as doming some little kid.
"I don't care what you say."
- Exactly.
- The coolest thing that I ever heard a veteran say
was when I bounced at a bar when I was in school
in Minnesota, there was a guy who was
in the Air Force Reserves who we were throwing out,
and one of the bouncers, he was 19, 20,
he was just like, I don't know why
they made him a bouncer, honestly.
He was very diminutive.
but he had a camo like flat brim on
like a camo twins hat flat brim
and the air force guy was like I'm a veteran I fought for your right to wear
that hat
*laughter*
I fought for your right to wear a fifty nine fifty
I didn't want to throw him out
to get a little bit yeah yeah he did he did he killed rob dear dick and still
have a
yeah
iraq's that veterans are all veterans are smart and should be respected
you know that you're on the rock that's what we say that we say at the
beginning of the episode every week before you know yeah we have a clear
clip like we like mark marons lock the gates but it's a status that the
veterans
that that bill
There was, I worked at a, uh, I, there was this gym in Brooklyn that I left because of a veteran.
It was like, Oh my God, this guy, he was like, I don't know if he was an actual operator,
just pretend and be a veteran, but he's like one of those vets who like has a dog because
the war scared him. Oh, yeah. Like, Oh, yeah. Oh, I need to, I need this dog or else I'm going to
scare my wife. Uh, but he would like bring the dog to the first floor where all the Olympic shit was
and would throw the tennis ball everywhere for his fucking shithead dog
and the dog would nearly get killed by weights every day
Jesus Christ
and I was like I don't want to deal with it like I'm done
I'm dead
Yeah that's the last time you go to Chris Dorner's pump house
Yeah
Because it was just like I like I like catastrophize sometimes but it was like
what if I got into an argument with this guy and it became this whole thing
and it would be like, "Socialist Podcaster Yells at Veteran."
(laughing)
For having dogs.
- Yeah, that'd be such a good Joey Salads video.
- It would ruin my life.
It would ruin my life.
Because I would be on video like,
"Well, you didn't even have to go to the fucking war.
"You don't even need that fucking dog."
(laughing)
- You're still lifting as you yell it out.
You're squatting.
- It'd just send me down a really dark path.
I'm glad I didn't engage.
Yeah, I used to work at a gym
and people would bring dogs in all the time
and they would ask if I could keep them behind the desk.
Which is such a weird thing.
I'd watch my fucking dog.
Yeah, it's completely crazy.
I worked at a very high-end gym too
and I was making minimum wage
and it just felt so goofy to be also somebody's dog sitter
for 12 bucks an hour.
That's the job they did hire me.
Yeah, Patrick applied at that job and something about him threw them off.
Yeah, I don't know what it was.
At a gym.
Maybe you were eating a burrito in the interview.
I did get a 7-Eleven. I can't go to 7-Eleven.
I know you did.
You got one of the chimichangas in the bag.
No, I got the hot dog. I got a hot dog. I'm standing by mine.
I want a 7-Eleven microwave with the numbers on it.
Yeah, that would be sick.
So much better, I never have to look at the wattage,
I just know that this is a four.
I'm looking up right now if you could buy a 7-Eleven
microwave on eBay.
Probably $10,000.
Yeah, okay, 7-Eleven microwave.
They have to have it, you have to be able to buy it.
Oh, no, you can get pre-owned microwave filters.
(laughing)
That is, what is happening if you're buying that?
What is happening if you're selling them
because they're $3, like how bad do you need $3?
- Yeah, and also, I mean, a microwave,
microwaves are free.
They're like couches and white fridges.
You just get them on Craigslist on the side of the road.
- Yeah.
- The microwave I got came with the apartment.
Have you seen that?
- Same with me. - That's a come up, bro.
- Same with me.
- No, the one that looks like the TV
from fucking Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
- You have like a microwave that looks like
what Walt Disney thought a microwave was gonna look like
in 50 years.
It's like it's fucking huge and then like you open the door and then the opening is like the size of like a box
It's not even looks like you looks like you put a little bit
It looks like you put a cube in it and a steak dinner on a plate comes out
Spy kids microwave I
Know I don't know how my mom always had it
It's like one of those things where like yeah your mom has the best version of it
You don't even know where she found it my mom has some like fucking chrome bullshit microwave. That's really good
I'm like Rome yeah Michael Rapaport would love
Yeah, oh man, man, I'm running spitter in my popcorn.
[Laughter]
Damn, you got a chromed out microwave.
Felix's mom, you'd pop his hell for that one, bro.
He's got hydraulics on the microwave.
[Laughter]
That's how it pops the popcorn and chips it up.
He's just got a hot pocket bouncing in there.
[Laughter]
God damn dude, he's just got the Saints Road 2 microwave, it's got like the Saints fluor
on it and shit.
Oh my god.
It's chrome and purple, all the buttons are purple.
Dude, you know what I saw the other day?
I saw the Call of Duty Black Ops 2 F-150.
Woah.
On the street, dude.
Wow.
You get a pic?
Oh my, no, no, it drove by, it was so fast.
(laughing)
- He was going so fast.
But dude, I forgot about those.
That is the ultimate fucking boss car, dude.
So cool.
- That, oh man.
- People, I mean, that's what I would do if I had money.
- If it didn't cost like $500,000 a year
to have a car in New York, I would buy that.
I would start going to media parties again
and just pull up in that.
- In a fucking sweepstakes car?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's so sick.
Halo 2, Hummer 2.
Imagine your dad picking you up from school on a Call of Duty truck.
Oh my god, dude. You would get so much pussy.
In a Baja Blast Morita Fiesta.
Yeah, there's a Baja Blast in the cup holder.
It's got a dispenser.
And that's right, no ice, because ice is a waste of soda room.
Yeah.
It comes out cold. It uses the AC.
That's correct.
Dude, I would just do the pimp my ride.
I would just put a PS2 in that thing.
Yeah.
And fucking, oh, I would never leave.
I thought that was the coolest, if you had a PS2 in your car when I was a kid.
The most impractical thing.
First off, you have to have at least, you have to have somebody driving.
For it to make any sense.
You have to have a chauffeur or a parent.
And parents are very adverse to putting PlayStation 2s in their cars for whatever reason.
would put a homework machine in the car.
That's right.
Yeah.
Parents would put dishes in the car.
Yeah, they're gonna put freakin' broccoli in there, dude.
You're gonna have to eat broccoli.
Yeah, Felix, we should have told you, we're very anti-parent, pro-kidding, anti-grounding.
I'm really not trying to get in trouble here.
I mean, like, I understand that vulnerable communities have attitudes towards homework
and dishes, right? They think that they cause harm and in the liminal spaces of homework
cause these issues.
You're almost sounding pro-chores right now, Felix.
Okay, well I'm very sensitive to the issues of the child community, but also many of my
listeners do assign homework and do assign dishes in those liminal spaces of chores.
Maybe that lady was right.
Yeah.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Yeah, name three toys, Felix.
Yeah.
Okay, alright.
I shouldn't even dignify this.
But if you really want to call my activist credentials into question, the Tonka Truck
is a classic one.
The Tonka Truck?
Okay, someone's out of touch.
Yeah, somebody just Googled "toy."
googled toys you click the first three answers like that info box popped up and
said the Tonka truck the Tonka truck the Hess truck and the jump rope I was gonna
say Jenga next? Jenga is a game, you absolute lepton. Jenga is a game. What is wrong with
you dude? Alright, I guess I shouldn't give my third, well it's um, I was gonna say a
Playmobil set. Playmobil is a tool. It's a material. Yeah, that's actually an imagination
aid completely different category I just like people the only thing we could do
to unsubscribe would be to come out against homework insurers are you guys
you guys would lose a lot yeah that's true yeah you guys are
like oh go below us today we had somebody on our on our patreon edit
their $40 pledge to $5 and it just was it was just a shot to the heart why was it
- Okay, was it $40 'cause he was like,
I really believe in the mission and then like $5?
'Cause he's like, I still like this show, but it's like--
- It had to have been an accident.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- 'Cause they--
- I like to think it wasn't,
because it's like he was just like,
I support the mission,
but you're not making any progress
against these seven year olds
who are still making these posts.
You're not putting a dent in that.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yeah, we're not making any of them log off.
The thing is, oh, speaking of,
this this list has a the reasons Halo 3 is better than fortnight the second list
has trigger trash kid on it
whoa sort of one of our there's a rotating cast of characters and ne'er
do wells from the top tens that we interact with or don't interact with the
we view yeah we do not interact
yeah and trigger trash kid. Caleb interacts. No I don't. Patrick interacts.
No. We interact with each other.
Caleb interacts with the... Trigger Trash Kid is one of the all-timers though.
He says, "Life is a meme, sarcasm is an art.
Cows go quack." Was Trigger Trash Kid the one...
Was he the dangerous ISIS weapons?
I think so, yeah. Oh, so he's kind of like a more worldly
seven-year-old. Yeah, he was the one who said that
if isis ever got uh... a hold of the dubstep
uh...
you know that all the time
isis is constructing the dubstep gun
what is the dubstep gun?
i think it's from worms
no no it's in saints row 3
it must be in worms from saints row then
or the other way around
it is in worms uh... worms whatever one that is
worms reloaded or worms unloaded worms gun loaded worms dirt loaded
They were trying to do a pun and they fucked up.
[Laughter]
Yeah, if Ice just got the dubstep gun, that would be truly catastrophic.
So I was on a Saints Row play. I played Saints Row in...
Just when I was waiting, I think in between GTA San Andreas and GTA 4.
Because I was like, "Alright, we need some..."
Which Saints Row? The first one?
I think two. And it literally depressed me too much.
Like, it made me depressed.
It was the only one I ever played.
Because it was just like...
I got this feeling where it was like, "This just isn't..."
Oh shit, hold up. It is in GKE. This isn't legal, it's too crazy.
Michael Rappaport was the voice of the one white guy in Saints Row 1, the one
white guy in the game. You know he was pissed when he started it up and he was
white in the game too. He's like, "What the fuck?" He's the informant. He's the fucking, he's the
undercover and they made me a fed he's like he's a he plays like a fat Italian
guy with a middle part I gotta find a picture of this Michael Rapaport
St. Joe - I'm looking this is a throw one is uh it's like Troy I think oh damn
dude Troy yeah he's the chief of police in Saints Row - oh my god
well my girl Berg probably like wishes he looked like like he obviously primarily
wishes he was white but like well yeah because this guy has this character is
like a pencil thin mustache that he maybe could play off for Puerto Rican
but yeah I mean Michael Rappaport cannot grow facial hair no he can't he has a
smooth but bumpy face. He's a smooth but mold face. Yeah, no he is he's half mold
he's half fungal. Yeah, did you guys remember when he got in some fight with
Dan Levitard and Levitard kept posting that. Dan Levitard from ESPN. That's his name?
Yeah, Levitard, that's right. He kept posting that picture of Michael
Rappaport with that that fucked up red spot on his chin. Oh yeah the herpes.
And yeah and then Michael Rappaport was like he went on his on his like radio
show at the time that has like he had like a hype man and I just remember
listening to it because I kept up with the beef and Michael Rappaport was like
and you had the nerve to bring up that photo of me with a lesion on my face
it's not herpes it's a lesion and then his hype man was like yeah that's right it's a lesion.
Well, he had a weird like pro wrestling-esque bit on his show that his son, he had a young
assistant who was rebelling against him, but I think it was just him.
It was very strange.
It was a very strange act of theater.
Theater of the mind.
Dude, he's a comedian, capital C. He can't stop.
He's an entertainer.
Dude, he's like Kaufman Reborn.
That's right.
I think he wanted to call himself Michael the Entertainer.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, no, he wanted to go with like--
he wanted to do like a hamburger-esque food name,
but like soup or something.
[LAUGHTER]
Soup.
Yeah.
Bread.
That's how he ends all his jokes.
Soup.
[LAUGHTER]
He fucking rocks.
All right, we're--
We're at an hour.
You did your time, Felix.
Okay.
We can let you go.
I'm sorry.
You talked about toys and Michael Rapoport.
I probably was about to do it.
Well, I embarrassed myself talking about toys.
You did.
I lost a lot of activist cred.
You're always welcome to come back on and correct the record.
I would love to.
But for now, you are known as sort of a crypto parent.
A pariah.
Crypto principal.
Well, I am teacher adjacent, unfortunately.
Yeah, you are.
You engage in teacher spaces a lot.
It's kind of sus.
Thanks man.
I'm not going to ask if you have anything to plug.
This is sus episode four with Will Maneker.
I just posted.
Okay, all right.
All right, go for it.
Go listen to that.
Thanks Felix.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, what's up?
We forgot to do the Patreon subscribers, so I'm going to thank all you guys real quick.
Thank you Trip Liquid.
That's a sick fucking name.
I hope that's your real name.
I do.
Thank you, Marcin, or Mar-kin.
Thank you very much.
Tucker, upgraded the pledge to $10.
Thank you, Tucker Menzies.
That's a Master Chief subscription right there, so thank you very much.
Lelo, thank you.
Sam McGorin, or McGowran, I don't know how to pronounce these names.
Nate, thank you to Nate.
Hansen, thank you. Spencer Greenfield, thank you. Steven Diaz, $10, Master Chief. They
should call you Spartan 117, Steven Diaz, if you ask me. Anthony Alves, thank you. Griffin
McGee, thank you. Matthew Magiarosi, thank you very much. Vince, I assume that's Vince
McMahon, so thank you a lot. Let's see. Brock Billings, thank you so much. Mr. Business,
Mr. Business back again, double dipping, thank you Mr. Business, we love you.
George Kenny, thank you.
AFG, $10 patron, that's the Master Chief, so thank you so much.
Yes, thank you to Yes.
David Kordelewski, thank you for subscribing.
And yeah, that's it. Thanks guys.
Check out my SoundCloud.