You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I'm never joining the military.
- Yeah, me neither.
- Never again.
- Never, yeah.
- Yeah, fool me once, military.
- Shame on you.
- Shame on you, fool me twice.
- Fool me twice, I'm never joining the military again.
- Fool me twice, I'm in the military again.
- Fool me again?
I'm a major.
Yeah, whoops.
Sorry, I'm a war hero.
Yeah, bummer.
Fuck, I got a Purple Heart and they let me get a discount at Applebee's now.
The enemy fooled me today.
The enemy fooled me and I became a prisoner of war.
That's what the pin says.
That's what the Purple Heart says.
It's like a sticker.
t-shirt that says I went to Vietnam and this shirt and minus two legs have
different shirts depending on how what limbs you lost yeah or what happened to
you in Vietnam yeah I went to Vietnam and all I got was this destroyed lung
from mustard gas they have one that just says they went John McCain on this white
ass that's all it says doesn't elaborate and there's a purple heart on it I guess
there's a purple heart on the shirt there's a purple heart that says I
inhaled the most Asian orange yeah yeah yeah yeah
bioweapon eating contest champion that's how they decided who won the Vietnam War
more. They got a Vietnamese guy and a big fat American dude. Joey Chestnut's great uncle
and sat him next to Kobayashi. He wasn't even Vietnamese. They were just like, "He's the
closest competitive eater." And they just made it see who could eat more Asian orange.
They had a dunk tank too.
It was a separate thing.
And a contest.
Yeah, they like the Agent Orange was just the carrot hot dog that Kobe Ashae endorsed at
By Chloe over the summer.
Vietnam was really just one long NBA All-Star weekend with different events that everybody
was participating in.
It was sort of East Coast All-Stars versus West Coast All-Stars, but it's Vietnam and
America.
They just had little contests like who could smoke the most out of a shotgun.
Yeah.
Man, the cats are--
You could have the most Vietnamese wives.
Yeah.
Who could run--
At the same time.
It was like a race.
It was a race to see who could run from the altar the fastest.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
How we doing, boys?
What are we--
The cats are--
I don't care.
They're sitting in their basket just fucking-- they're like fighting.
I don't know what--
Whoa.
Every classic episode starts with a little bit of cat talk, so I'll allow it.
going on with the cats? They're Yoda they're like half asleep but fighting.
Cool. Half asleep but fighting. Yoda's like asleep on top of fucker just like swatting at
his head. He's having a dream. Yeah. Yeah. He's having a dream that he's beating you up.
That you're cat size and he's beating the shit out of you. He's finally killing me. Yeah. Yeah.
Damn, they look weird. Cool man. Finally he admits that they look weird. Yeah. They don't look weird,
they look bad. They don't look bad. They look bad. God damn, I want a Coke Zero so bad
since you cracked that seal. Oh my god. This isn't a Coke Zero, this is a Polar
Grapefruit. I know, that's Water Zero. I've just been, I've been craving.
- Water zero.
- I'm ramping up my caffeine intake again.
I think I'm about to hop back on the Monster 000 pretty soon.
- Have you had the new, have you had the Fiesta?
- No dude, I've been out the game for like five months.
- Yeah, they got a mango one now.
- Is it like a pinata?
Why is it a Fiesta?
- They got a pinata on the,
it's an embossed pinata on the can.
- They should make, serve it in a pinata.
- They should, wow.
- And you have to hit it to make the drink come out.
They got another one it's the Rosa one it's not that good.
It's a grapefruit or something.
Do you think with pinatas candy was the first choice or did the inventor.
No there's definitely like the first version the inventor of pinatas.
Had like empanadas.
It was like milk in there.
Well the first.
Yeah it was always dulce de leche.
He just busted open a donkey's head and milk started flying.
The first pinata was just a guy saw a hornet's nest and he was like, "I bet I can make that
beautiful.
I bet I can make that look like an animal."
Kids, you know how much fun you have hitting a hornet's nest.
You guys know how much fun you have when you hit a horse with a stick?
Yeah, the guy got the idea after he lynched a donkey.
He was like, "What if there was candy in this?"
Yeah, what if the kids could come too?
This was already so fun.
Yeah, what about a kid's version of this?
- Yeah. - I got it.
- They all got together and lynched a donkey
and they're like, "Oh, but we spent so much money
"on babysitting to come out to do this."
(laughing)
We need the kids to be able to get in on this.
- Yeah, it's just a pinata full of ground beef.
They call it the pinata prototypes.
- I would like that.
- Yeah, I wouldn't mind that, honestly.
- I made a killer hamburger the other day.
Killer, I'm talking killer.
- Killer. - Yeah.
It made a smash burger the other day.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
- I just got this new plant-based meat
that they made it look like real ground beef,
like it went through a grinder and everything.
- Is it the Beyond?
- No, it's not Beyond.
- Or the Impossible?
- It's called the Meatless Co. Company
or something like that.
- Meatless Co. Company.
Let me look it up, hold on.
- Is it good or is it bad?
- I haven't tried it yet.
Now everything, the people who make fake meat think that meat just tastes like soy sauce.
Because that's what all of that tastes like.
Like everything tastes like soy sauce.
Like the Beyond Burger is a soy sauce sponge.
Yeah, well I mean they can't, the people who make it don't eat meat.
So they wouldn't know.
True, they're just guessing.
They're guessing, yeah.
That's a really good point.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean it's like a lot of, oh man.
I fucking.
yourself in the face right now. Whoa that was like a, that was like you knocked yourself.
He just hit himself in the face with a plank of wood. With a nail at the end. Yeah. Yeah
it's the meatless farm company. A meatless farm? Those are pretty common. Those are actually
really common. Yeah. It's not that crazy. Yeah. I don't even know, what is in there?
Yeah, it's always like a shit ton of oils and then starches.
What it is, is it's phytoestrogens and soy oils.
Yeah.
And...
It's HRT.
And breast meat.
They make you eat meatless food to turn you into a girl.
That's right.
And that's what Obama initiated.
Yeah.
That's what he initiated with the H1N1 pandemic.
Or as I call it a fan-demic, which is a fake pandemic.
And then, yeah, and then he turned my mom into a girl.
And now he's trying it again with this shit.
Yeah, it's his fault.
Yeah, he's, he's, Kovic.
If you, if you translate Kovic from Slovenian,
it says Obama.
No.
No, it's not.
It says girl.
It says girl good, which is even worse.
Yeah.
Oh no.
It's kind of a broken translation, but it literally means girl good. They're brainwashing you. That's
why they can't stop saying COVID. It's because girl good and then they say 19 because they're
trying to raise the age of consent to 19. So they're saying girl good at 19. It's basically
what they're saying and they're brainwashing people. But think about it. But y'all ain't
ready for that conversation. It affects men more than women, right? Because women are already women.
You can't translate the word "COVID" into any other...
Well, you're wrong, because it translates to "girl."
No, you're wrong.
On Google Translate, they have a shield.
Obviously, Google's not going to tell you the answer to the conspiracy. They're part of it, dude.
No, I'm just saying...
They're part of the ones who created the translation in the first place.
If you type in "COVID" into Google Translate, it gives you a warning,
and it says, "Get information about COVID here."
Check out a little website, I think if you hit Google,
check out, basically it's sort of like the,
no, it's even better, it's sort of like the
uncensored version of Google, it's called elgoog.com.
Check it out.
- Oh yeah, look up nip steam on elgoog.
- Look up, yeah.
- And hit I'm feeling lucky.
- That's right, hit I'm feeling lucky.
Or hit eekoolme,
- Iku, I give up.
Go to El Gug and type in B-Lack
and hit I'm feeling lucky and you're gonna see my face.
- B-Lack. - Guaranteed.
- Look up, look up, go into El Gug
and then look up Puck Out.
(laughing)
- Puck Out.
- Puck Out, wait no.
Puck, Puck Eno.
- Puck Eno?
Puckino out, surlg.
- Girls, girls, two girls, one cup.
(laughing)
That was one of the,
that was like the most stressful brain moment
of the past two months for me.
I can't believe you did that, dude.
That was amazing.
- I think I said, I think I said--
- You're a genius.
That should be like a drunk,
that should be like a field sobriety test.
I think I said one cup.
Many girls.
Or just girls too.
Girls too?
I think I said that.
I wish that Lena and Adam would make a girls too.
Yeah, girls too.
Girls too, now it's guys.
Whoa, guys.
Guys.
Yeah.
They would never make a show called guys.
Yeah, because it'd be too awesome.
There's always, it's like you have, your window is another TV to you.
to you know it's not even it's a never anything interesting it's always they
were fighting in the other one they were fighting the basket every time fell onto
the couch oh that's actually dramatic whoa the cat moved from a spot to
another spot and when they were fighting he pushed him holy crap you guys the cat
is blinking and opening and closing its eyes no that's pretty cool that's like a
It's like the Cain and Abel story.
That's like Luke Skywalker and Anakin Skywalker fighting in the lava.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
Have you watched the new Clone Wars at all?
No.
Me neither.
I was just wondering.
That's exciting.
I watched some of like the old Clone Wars series, the animated one, but I always found
interesting how many grown men just love that show yeah including my uncle but my
uncle also likes Ben 10 which is like my uncle is like a huge Ben 10 fan weird
he's like really weird stuff is yeah but your uncle sits there with an Omnitrix
I yeah which uncle is except he's well yeah he's the one he honestly looks like
one of the monsters yeah Ben 10 presses two and then just switches to be a big
fat guy with alopecia what are his powers what why would Ben 10 turn into
eating cheeseburgers and holding a ghost hunting magnet thing okay I don't know
or something like that, going to technical college
for computer science.
Is that a superpower?
That is a superpower, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
That is a superpower.
That's one of the modern superpowers.
If you're listening.
Yeah.
You're like a real life superhero to us.
You're like a real life superhero.
Get that degree, baby.
That's right, going to technical college,
learning how to write HTML in the same room
that a woman learns how to put shitty fake nails on somebody.
That's what it's all about.
I went to technical college.
Yeah, but then you, it's like you just got progressively,
like went to progressively more evil places for college
and then you finally dropped out.
Yeah, that's pretty true, yeah.
Which is kind of, that's how it should be,
that's what I did too.
But I only made two stops.
But you graduated, dummy.
I did, which is one of the worst mistakes ever.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm in debt, but I'm only in like two years of debt.
I'm still in less debt than you.
No.
Yeah.
'Cause I went for the same amount of time as you,
but I also am, I was super smart with money.
No, you have the same amount of debt pretty much.
No, okay, let's say it at the same time.
I don't know, I don't know how much.
(laughing)
I know it only cost me like, I don't know what it was.
It only cost Patrick $5 because his uncle--
It was like 8,000 or something at the second school,
and only went to the first school for like one semester.
My old college before I transferred was $900 a semester.
University of North Carolina in Wilmington.
It was $900 a semester.
- That's 'cause it was in state, right?
- Yeah, and that was with me, I was living on campus.
And then I had to drop out because it was too expensive.
I couldn't afford it anymore.
- I was on loans.
- Yeah, I wasn't on loans until I started,
until I moved, until I met you guys.
Coincidence?
Hmm.
- Well, I think--
- I don't know.
- You borrowed money from me.
- I think I--
- I got a loan from Cameron.
- Yeah.
- I think I paid in-state for Emerson somehow.
- They don't have in-state tuition at Emerson.
- They don't?
- Private school, yeah, there's no in-state.
- Then I was paying.
- Then you were paying a whole lot of money, baby.
- Yeah.
- Fuck.
- Yeah, man, we're fucked forever, it's okay.
- Yeah.
- Man, it's so shitty that, man.
It sucks 'cause like, it literally,
like you learn nothing there.
- Oh no, dude.
- Yeah.
- No, absolutely not.
- Like you go to like--
- Just so you can like know everybody in there.
It's just like so people,
like 30 year old Elizabeth Warren stands,
we're like, oh my God.
We'll see Emerson next to him and go,
oh my God, this is my new assistant.
And you get to work for minimum wage for like six years
before you finally, before--
- Before you pitch the worst script in the world to them.
- That person who hired you dies,
and you lose your job.
Yeah, you have to work in a restaurant
for the rest of your life.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- And you're living in LA.
- Yeah, you really are just like,
you're paying for like a little asterisk next to your name
that can only be seen by the worst people in the world,
and it will give you a job.
- It'll give you a job only in LA.
All the scripts that I read in school,
it was always like,
she's a 19 year old in New York City
and both of her parents are too busy
working for the CIA to hang out with her ever.
So she's gotta make it on her own.
She's gotta make it on her own doing stand-up comedy.
But she has depression!
Yeah, and huge tits.
Huge, big, beautiful tits.
It's either that--
That might have been a note I gave.
(laughing)
That's been in every single class.
They're like, yeah, so this one's about my mom
who was actually an alcoholic and then killed herself.
So it's about, she should have huge tits in the script.
Can you just write that in?
- The male analog of that show, that script,
is like lethal weapon, the show.
- Lethal weapon, yeah, well just people just kept
writing Brooklyn Nine-Nine. Yeah exactly it's just guys writing Brooklyn Nine-Nine
scripts. Well it's half Brooklyn Nine-Nine and then it's half like um like this
this quiet boy his mental illness comes to life and dates him. It's just like
stuff where it's like... His mental illness becomes a big supermodel. Yeah his mental illness becomes a humongous penis that he gets to use.
Yeah, he has to navigate his way. He has to navigate his way through this
through this awful college dorm that every single person is a supermodel and
and yeah yeah and they all they're crazy they like him too much they don't
realize what he has underneath in his brain but then also desire to make
movies one of the darkest most twisted things you could possibly have. I would also read
scripts where it was like I like so many of the scripts took place in high school
Yeah, no, what the fuck was that?
And it would always be the thing of like her, like, her hot high school body.
Yeah.
And I was always like, yeah, and his girlfriend who was in ninth grade, she was so hot.
It's just fucking, it's just weird.
Let's take back the school from my ex-girlfriends.
The pilot.
Yeah.
Yeah, whoops, I dated every single girl in the school.
And so now every episode is me going through and apologizing to them.
Yeah.
Because I would, because they would talk during movies.
Well, it's not even that.
Most of the time it's like, and I go through the school and I use my verbal wit to make
them apologize to me without realizing it.
Something that I think that is so funny.
I still do.
Something I think is so funny, like this is very much like the Aaron Sorkin model for
like writing is to be a guy who is like in conversation extremely dim and slow
and then spend like five hours writing like one very like one like smart quip
or whatever that's supposed to take place in conversation and then being like
I'm like the smartest guy ever yeah yeah cuz I just I just spent five hours
writing a conversation that appears to be like smart and witty because I spent
five hours on it. Yeah. Yeah. And then like the the right like have you seen that
fucking clip of it's studio 60 on the Sunset Strip and it's the fucking oh my
god he's like he's explaining to his dad he says something like this is like the
the French whatever of sketch comedy writers like that what's that fucking I
don't know. Salon. No oh the salon yeah it's something the salon of a sketch
comedy writers and he's like well your brother is over in Iraq serving this
country it's so fucking crazy I cannot believe that show exists yeah yeah
exists so great I want to get on this like Alex was telling us about like a
scene where somebody like steals a joke on the show or something like that and
and they go into the room and beat the shit out of them.
Can you imagine how much cooler SNL would be if people were beating the shit out of each other for jokes?
Just people waiting in the wings at all times.
That'd be sick dude.
Julio Torres shoots somebody for a joke.
That'd be sick.
All right we have um we're revisiting just an absolute
So, a lot of people said that their favorite episode of this podcast was Diaper Talk, which
I just looked up.
It's episode 73, if anybody cares.
But I figured we should revisit.
We looked at this adult, this diaper lover forum for adult diaper lovers in that episode.
We read through some great-
A-Disc, a-disc community.
A-disc.org.
Yeah.
And so I thought we should go back to that forum because there's just so much going on
there.
ever we will ever plumb the depths it's a this was this was also Cameron's idea
because he is so attracted to the smell yeah no I just use the forum constantly
so I figure I want to spotlight some of my favorite yeah any members really he's
trying to he's trying to plug his own account he's kind of clout chasing right
now yeah a disc stands for a diaper di di that's the di diaper shit crap no a
Now a disc stands for a diaper in Sir Cameron's.
Because he is eating it.
But I scrolled through a bunch of threads last night to find stuff and I think I found some
really like heinous, awful stuff for us to read.
Are we looking at this first one or did you cross out that it's too heinous?
The first one, no, it's just not good.
It's boring.
I figured we should just start with the bangers right away.
So this first one I want to-
These are bangers.
I mean, wait until you hear this, okay?
This is um...
Yo we found some diaper forums last night that was bangers bro.
I'm gonna read this first post, okay?
Sorry I'm wearing my young money shirt.
This is by ID Diaper Boy.
IDF Diaper Boy.
ID Diaper Boy.
Question about being caught.
I have a question that I'm hoping for some help.
In junior high my mom caught me twice.
Around the same time I also hid the diapers under my mattress.
Then when I was about 23, my parents visited my house while I was in the military.
I forgot to throw away a used Depends.
While we were all watching a movie, my dad reaches between the cushions and grabs the
rolled up green Depends.
*laughter*
Why is it green?
He said, "Is that the color?"
Is it green from shit?
Yeah, is that the color that Depends are?
Or did it turn green because of how long it was in the cushions?
Because it was in the cushions.
Yeah, or how long it was in the cushions.
It's the same one from junior high.
If you want to shit in a diaper, that's fine.
But like at least have a common decency to put it in the trash can.
Fucking throw it out!
Throw out your diaper!
I love- he was in the military.
Was he like-
Oh, they're green cause he's-
It's a camo diaper!
Wait, wait, wait.
It's like an army khaki diaper.
He says, he says, he said, "A diaper?
I jumped up, grabbed it, and threw it in the trash.
I told them a friend was over earlier with their baby and must have forgotten.
Nothing was said when we went back to the movie."
Imagine pulling out clearly an adult-sized used diaper.
Yeah, it's a paper.
A huge diaper, it says, depends on it.
It's green.
It's in your son's couch.
Your military son.
I can't get over the military part.
First off, you have to think, "Well, that's one big baby."
But then you have to think, "Not only does my son have a friend with a kid,
eat this friend changed this kid on my son's couch and then hid the diaper in
oh they must have forgot it what are they gonna carry it with right then
there's a there's a wrap on the door he's like hey I forgot my son's diaper I
think I left it in the couch I think I may have left it think I might have
fallen out of my ugly looks at his dad yeah I told you I told you yeah in tow is
the is a six-foot baby it's just a baby but it just looks like Charles Barkley
and then the response to this post is I'm guessing she knows and it's just
being discreet for your sake if nobody has said anything great I would not
stress over it and then ID diaper boy response to that and says oh I'm not
stressed over it that was almost 20 years ago almost 20 years ago yeah that's
why would you post it then? This is from April 20th 2020. This is from 4/20.
That's why it was a green diaper dude. Didn't post it then because this
community had been confined to the shadows at the time. Yeah. This was before
you know the... For Obama. This was before the Cultural Revolution. The person responds
again and says she knows then. My mom would have gone all Sherlock Holmes and
My father would have come unglued.
Consider yourself lucky.
- What is it?
Is that like, is unglued like a diaper?
'Cause there is that video that we watched at one time
that's the guy who glued himself to the chair
with the diaper.
- I don't think we watched that.
- No, I was thinking his father was flat Stanley.
And he was two pieces of paper glued together
and he would get so mad, you know.
But yeah, see, I mean like 2000,
that would have been 2000 that that happened right 20 years ago that was
that was before Glee came out you know yeah these people still had to had to
hide and then somebody says wait so you change yourself on the couch some point
and just left the used diaper end up between the cushions gross and then ID
diaper boy responds and says no I set the diaper on the arm of the couch the
couch was next to the front door and the garbage cans were right outside I must
have knocked it down and sat on it while I was waiting for my parents. You would
know if you sat on a diaper dude. You would know. Changing yourself. Yeah. That's
gonna be hard. Yeah. That well if you teach a baby to do it. Or you could
sit on your hands so it feels like somebody else is doing it.
diapers man shit shit diapers man how big is this form how many users does it have
a lot it's really active it's uh there's a lot of there's I didn't put any of
these in the ones we're gonna look at but there's a bunch of discussion there's
like um there's discourse over coronavirus because a bunch of diaper
lovers are on there like like being like what the hell why are there shortages on
diapers right now this is so fucked up and there's a thread that was like
please respect that right now like there are shortages on certain products and I
don't want to get it to give the diaper lover community a bad name with us
complaining about this there's a lot of arguments about that.
Damn.
Imagine someone just walking out of Costco with a pallet full of adult diapers.
Or like 10 years from now when people are reminiscing about how horrible this time was, somebody's
like, "Yeah, I had to, my dad actually died."
And the guy's like, "Whoa, I had to start using the toilet like a big boy."
It got dark there for a minute.
Yeah, they ran out of the Sesame Street diapers for a really long time.
Yeah, exactly.
I'd use the Lego Batman diapers for like two months.
This next one we can't read because it's so long.
It's like novel length, but I just wanted to put it here because of the name, the name
of the thread.
"Confessions of a British Diaper Lover."
Yeah, it's really "Confessions of a British Diaper Lover."
And it starts with, "Well, where do I begin?"
It's literally the longest thing.
It's so long.
Oh my God, dude.
Where the fuck do you begin?
This is like 3000 words.
It's insanely long.
This is a tale of two cities.
I am a diaper lover. I'm in my 30s, heterosexual, and I live in the UK.
I have a partner or a responsible job.
Read it in his voice.
I can't do it.
And a fair number of friends.
Where do I begin?
My interests are all fairly normal, and nothing about me screams odd or weird.
not true. Read it in a goth voice. Yeah, you're British. Do Bill Cosby. Do a Bill Cosby's voice.
Confessions of a Cosby diaper lover. I can't do Bill Cosby's voice. What is the truncated
version of this? I don't know, I haven't read it. Oh, you didn't read it? No, it's so long.
Dude, there's a diaper bread he lists here called a P. Deuce.
It's P-E-A-U-D-O-U-C-E.
P. Deuce.
Because they only say like nonce over there, so they didn't even know.
There's so much detail.
This is like...
Oh my god, wait, okay, I found a good passage here.
This is like the... this is like Nouseguard for a diaper lover.
Just every single detail of this guy's life.
We were at home one day and I have a very clear and vivid memory of looking at some kind of leaflet.
In it was a picture, probably a sock image, of a smiling girl who I thought looked about my age.
She was white with dark hair in bunches.
She held a teddy bear by its arm in one hand.
She was wearing only what looked like a large pair of white knickers.
I studied the picture closely and could see that what I thought were knickers
in fact had tabs and she was actually wearing a nappy.
For some inexplicable reason, I suddenly felt a surge of the most intense jealousy that one could imagine.
I suddenly wanted to wear a nappy too, like the girl.
That's an origin story right there.
Here's a good one right here.
I had no childhood traumas, toilet related or otherwise, and was neither neglected nor
privileged.
There was no new baby or sibling rivalry issues that it caused either.
My sister and I get on very well.
My diaper issue is not, there's a, my diaper thing stems from a non-sexual incident.
Is that what, is it, is it theorized that people with diaper fetishes, it's a, it's
a, it's a kid sex thing?
Why would you need to put that in your diaper forum thing?
I don't know, I feel like, I mean, I feel like he's probably the outlier as far as having
some sort of kids sex thing that he did
that makes in this way
the uh... which is the next one
is where started stuff starts to get kinda crazy i think
uh... this one this post is a
what is in your most memorable diaper moment
and some of these most memorable diaper moments of the decade
uh... structure i just want to go into the third post here which is by user
username PC baby who shows up a few times in this um in these posts. Their profile picture
is literally just a baby, an angry baby on the computer. And the art style is like a
boomer like funny comic in the newspaper. It's like the I need to go look for my Pokemon
on go creatures style yeah, but yeah this would this PC babies most memorable
diaper moment. The first time my auntie put nappy on me was when I was twelve and
a half shortly after my parents were killed by a drunk driver. If you want
details, look for my early life in the story section. I want details. I want so
many details. There are a few more details of this person late in some of
later post i think uh...
all five of you guys want to know if you listen
uh... he's a baby has a
long-term spirit that's health
quickly
the free
it's like that man
nobody here i was to put on the day for her
uh... man
of
uh... with there's one second there's another oh yeah this
this next one
what is the worst thing that ever happened to you
uh... here's is pc baby posted in this one as well as the worst thing that
ever happened a pc baby is sitting next to my late wife in i_c_u_ well they
withdrew life support and watching her take her last
all
and then and then another and then the next post
pc baby on will somebody says the death of their mother and if you see me says i
can sympathize but when my parents were killed by a drunk driver it was the best
thing that ever happened to the white dot
yet because you get this there were in diapers yeah
on my hand to god do it
that's so we're going to have a look at the pc babies
pc babies uh... page
And their most recent post is, "I am ex-UK Royal Marine Commando."
[Laughter]
Jesus fucking Christ, how many of these people?
How many of these people are in the military?
Yeah, all of them. I'm learning that veterans are big babies.
Wow.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I broke my arm at summer camp a long time ago. I was trying to jump over a rope of chains
Yeah, well one right above that is age 20 witnessing my best friend die in a car accident
Best and worst diaper experience from PC baby best was the first time my aunt changed me after my parents were killed
It was done so gently and lovingly worst experience second day in the children's home not wearing a nappy and wetting and soiling
Myself as I walked down the corridor to the kitchen
There's another in the worst thing that ever happened. There's another military person
This is the worst thing in adulthood being overseas in a country where they don't want us
And I don't want to be there either and getting injured and needing back surgeries
Crazy god damn, dude
I
Broke up with the girl I dated for a year and thought I would end up marrying
Ending up being one of the best things that ever happened to me, but I didn't feel that way for a long time
from wandering toddler
Gay Gus 91 in the off-topic section says for non pooers has any
Has any not poo lover ever put a fresh nappy on then need a poo?
What do you do change a waste a nappy try and hold the poo for a couple hours?
Back to the to the what is being enjoyed a big poo in a
Back to the what has been your most memorable diaper moment on the second page. There's a post by loves and Pampers
Their most memorable diaper moment was waking up in the hospital after a car accident wearing a tens back in the 80s
I had always enjoyed diapers before then but never dreamed
I would end up in them at the hospital
The accident left me paralyzed from the waist down a short time later the nurse came in the room to change me felt like I was
Two years old again
Yes, dude. God some of these are just so fucking sad. I'm gonna get into this man. These people are actually these people are truly happy
Yeah, I guess I mean they have escaped. This is the ultimate
just like
Matrix red pill yeah
Did you take the diaper pill?
The brown pill and you just diaper yourself you treat yourself like a baby you piss and shit
You only fuck with with with women who are true rider dies and are willing to change that shit
I heard that's true busy pooper rider diapers. And yes, sometimes you enjoy a big poo in a diaper sometimes
Listen to this one. That's how God intended it. Also PC baby is a 12 and a half years Catholic. He says Wow
Yeah, you made I
Think the first time my wife then my girlfriend I was 17. She was 16
We went parking out in a field full moon that night took my brother's old four-door Mercury
She diapered me in the back seat of the car, and I ran around playing in the dirt in just my diaper and plastic pants
I was you imagine I was so much by then thought life couldn't get any better. I was right
It was a high-life moment never got to play outside again except a few times by myself
Could you imagine just?
Walk it like you're going like oh me and my friend like you're in high school
and you like stumble upon that like oh we're gonna go smoke weed in the field
tonight yeah you smoke weed for the first time and just in the middle of the
field you see a guy like two years older than you just fucking what is plastic
pants mean this like they're like British yeah no they're just like they're
I mean just plastic pants, just like waterproof sweatpants basically.
Azmat suit pants.
Or is it like that Tim and Eric spaghet where they put the cigarette juice into the pants?
I don't know, I don't think I've seen that.
You guys are not true fans.
No, you're thinking of D-Pants.
You're thinking of Tim's Kitchen Tips.
Oh yeah, that's what I was thinking of.
You're thinking of D-Pants from Diarrhea Jones.
You're thinking of Tim Allen's Tool Time.
Tim Allen's.
most memorable diaper moment the first time I woke up wet I don't get a chance
to wear to bed often so with the right drink and the right hypnosis it's still
as great as the first time. Hypnosis. This is making me have to pee and shit. Me too.
I got it's really it's giving me it's giving me just a like a deep desire to
just shit my pants. Don't do it. You should try it. Do you think you
You could just shit your pants.
Yeah, I don't think I could.
I don't think I could piss my pants.
I don't think I could shit my pants.
It's one of those things like when you can bite into your finger like a carrot but your
mind doesn't let you.
Yeah.
You can't shit your pants unless you have a doctor.
That is what is, that's why these people are happy.
They have a meditative mental, they've conquered it.
Yeah, they've removed the mental block.
Exactly.
It's like a tantric thing.
have so focused their desires on one thing that they can bypass their bodily
needs. So they, their all instinct tells them not to shit themselves and yet they do.
Ruby Rainey's most memorable diaper moment. I was just about to read that one. The first time I
toked while wearing a disposable one. I don't think I've ever been more
blissfully relaxed. It was amazing and incredible. I recommend it if you're 420
friendly. I'm cross-faded as hell off this blunt and this diaper I'm wearing. I'm 420 and
diaper friendly. God what a combo. Yeah. Man if your whole thing is like pretending to be
a baby. Yeah you can't be smoking weed. Babies can't smoke weed and drink. No. What like
you're not putting vodka in the bottle. Maybe. Maybe they are. I wouldn't put it past these
sick fucks. These freakazoids. Y'all need Jesus. The next thread is what have you done
in a full diaper today
you know capitals
uh... patrick answer yeah what if you have a right to have a good today yeah
uh... labor
i see it poking out i see that
bang in their view i see those chunks and and and and i think you're going to
always have already mama you better get back over here and i press
uh...
who let me get off a piece it at will be diaper you have already a b_j_ on there
acting for was there
uh... god to someone to repeat the latest is just hollering hollering at a diaper
wear
case we are
i can see it you know that's a good construction workers
construction workers cat why why do you like a poke above the jeans if you
didn't want us to see it that's all i'm saying that it
- I'll bet you come back later, I'll change you.
- Amber Starfield, mine wasn't full at the time,
but I peed in my diaper while grocery shopping.
Picked up a Pokemon themed birthday cake for my fiance,
then got some lunch.
I am still working on filling my diaper,
but I'm now back at home,
relaxed playing Second Life on PC.
- Oh.
- D-boy life right above that.
- So this is from Saturday though.
So this person peed in their diaper while grocery shopping
like right now in this current coronavirus crisis.
- Oh, you can't be, I, yeah.
While there's a pandemic, you gotta like at least stop.
- I'm gonna go to the grocery store
to pick up a Pokemon birthday cake
and piss myself and just leave a trail.
- You gotta stop pissing and shit.
- Just leave a trail of biohazard fluid.
(laughing)
- Right.
- Close down the whole grocery store permanently.
- What's worse, people having parties
people shitting and pitting pissing themselves at the store right now people
shitting and pitting pity patty pissing themselves padding yeah well I think
when I pee in my diaper today I will watch Avengers endgame as the end of my
vacation is at hand a long time ago then I will sleep in them there's some like
free Chris says I wrote a bike trail an hour each way at least this person's
active yeah free free Chris stereotype a full diaper bike ride for two hours
goddamn God oh my god so it wasn't just it wasn't full just wet through the day
grocery shopping the in-laws liquor store and the car wash figured I was good
so I got out of my diaper went about my day and had a mishap it was a fun night
for the wife and imagine imagine the raw fucking masculine power of sitting in
front of your father-in-law and with your wife and taking my fucking your
daughter
Earlier today at lunchtime I sat at my kitchen table in a wet and poopy diaper.
All during the time I was eating I sat in my own pee and poop.
Not unusual for me since I am medically incontinent.
Alright, that's fair.
You're medically incontinent.
Yeah, you get a pass.
But just change.
Change.
That's true.
Eat a whole meal.
There's a post here.
Yeah, wait.
There's a post here from Baby David Messiah whose bio says make diapering great again.
They said, "I drunk coffee, smoked three cigarettes, and just sat quietly alone."
Chamberpot says, "Did a little yard work, peed a few times, started a nice campfire in my
fire pit, and sat there poking the fire and adding wood to it and adding pee to my diaper."
I'm just adding some pee to my diaper.
Yeah, I'm adding.
I'm building on it.
Let's see, what's the next one?
Oh yeah, this one, um, Mayday, family may have found diapers.
Um, this is by, a post by a Canadian diaper lover.
So I wore a goodnight last night while my folks were out and left another one in the washroom,
hiding behind the toilet paper rolls.
Now today, I went in there and noticed that the toilet paper was disturbed,
and my other last goodnight was gone.
My dad does not know about this, and he may have taken a toilet paper roll out
paper roll out and put it on top of the toilet as a signal that he did not flush the toilet
in the early morning while everybody else was asleep. It could also have been my twin brother,
who also did have a diaper fetish at 12 or 13. The lead is so buried there.
This is like fucking, have you seen three identical strangers where it's like...
It's just like that but with diapers where it's like
like they're doing like a study to see like if it's inherent.
Um, I just found a really great subsection of this forum.
Yeah.
It's called "Mature Topics."
How mature are we getting here?
The first post, uh, Virginia pro-second amendment rally.
Removing firearms from the law abiding will never stop a bad person from using a firearm against the law abiding.
This is by...
Diapered Stag.
*laughter*
Oh my god.
Oh fuck dude.
*laughter*
If you are looking for a terrorist group, look at Antifa.
dressed in combat gear and carrying guns does not automatically make them evil. In
fact the Virginia protest was one of the most civil protests I think I've ever
seen. They even cleaned up after themselves which is an amazing feat to
these people. Yeah, cleaning up after yourself is just so hard for them.
Oh this rocks. Yeah, I'm looking at mature topics now. Why everyone thinks circumcision is
mutilation social justice themed songs
is this all just a there's a religion social justice marriage etc there's a
thread from diaper freak who says pegging I have dropped hints to my wife
that I want to try to try pegging and someone else says I have brought up the
topic it is not going to happen. Goddamn dude. Yeah. What a fucking site. Buddhist thread
ask any question about Buddhism. I'm just searching Israel. This might be dangerous.
yeah any other pagans just wondering if I'm the only pagan honestly they're all
pagan of gods and goddesses do you follow they're all fucking pagan freaks
absolutely my therapist says that diapers and regressions are healthy yeah man
Oh my god, it goes all the way back to 2008.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
"Using diaper gel for science" from Sleepy Brandon.
You can use the gel for plants.
It actually works.
My science experiment actually did work.
It doesn't matter if it's used on or just used.
You can use still on some plants.
Believe it or not, it actually helps plants grow and last a very long time.
- What is diaper gel?
(laughing)
- It's a gel that's, it's a gel you put, I don't know.
- Oh God, Caleb are we looking at the same one?
- No I just,
(laughing)
I just scrolled back to the very beginning of mature topics
and the first post, from April 13th, 2008,
All lowercase "hey" really embarrassing question.
Here's the body.
"Okay, well, I got a white head on my balls, like a big one, and I just popped it like a normal white head and it sort of hurted when I did it.
Is it normal to have these on my balls?"
*laughter*
And someone says, "Yeah, it's normal."
"You kind of explained it in a gross way though."
the guy responded, "Well sorry just so nervous though never has happened to me
before I'm just really scared right now."
I found someone from my hometown on here or the town over.
Oh yeah it's your dad. Well I found someone on here and the post was "Sigh
yesterday afternoon my younger brother in quotes passed away yeah this um this
website I feel like the deeper you go it's just like it's so it's it's dark
it's like Lovecraftian knowledge yeah just the knowledge that this
specifically that like someone in the town over from you is not only a diaper
lover but posts on the diaper lover forum. Not only a diaper lover, a 62 year old diaper
lover. And engaged enough in the in the in the practice to join a website a
community. Yeah. Dude it's like it's like they live. It's like Dracula.
you put on the sunglasses you can see the diaper under their pants.
You see the diaper.
Let's talk sports.
High school shootings.
This thread is locked by Roland.
And there is that.
We know what Roland that is.
Yeah.
That's a photo. No, that's not Donald Fagan.
Hunting in a diaper. First time hunting in a diaper.
Peed two times and no leaks.
Kind of like just sitting in my stand and letting go.
Ultra-nationalism. Is it coming back from Roland in 2008?
God, what the fuck is going on? I don't know if it's happening as bad here, but I'll give you a portrait of the scenery here.
There is a fight between if a southern part of Bulgaria can be called Macedonia.
(laughing)
Bro, they're getting into fucking issues here.
- Yeah man, it's, wait, there was another,
one second, there's another one I wanted to read.
Let me find it really quick.
First public diaper accident.
This is Rearslover97.
This is my first public diaper experience.
I was doing some late night shopping.
I had the sudden urge to number two.
I had to hurry up to buy wipes and pay for everything.
there was a long line because there is only one register open
i was crossing my legs and doing everything in my power to hold till i
get to the family restroom
so just
first pay to spin a picture of this guy is is at the front of a long line at one
register
he's crossing his legs
the stubbornly that it is like that's very visible hold the crops your legs
uh...
it was my turn to pay and as soon as i was paying i couldn't hold and it just
loose
luckily it was not allowed but it was not a solid one
no one noticed, but i looked really embarrassed. After i was done, i just went to the family
restroom to get changed. It took me some time to clean up, as that is all i'm going to say
about cleanup. From my public diaper experience, i think i handled it well. I just need to
stop panicking because it shows on my face, and then slo-mo responds and says yeah that
sudden change from a panicked face to an embarrassed one is a bigger tell than just pooping yourself.
I think pooping yourself is a pretty big tell.
Yeah I wonder how numb these people are to the smell of their own shit.
Russell100.
They don't realize everybody can smell that they have shit themselves.
Oh one I read last night that I didn't put in here because it wasn't very funny was somebody
was like saying like yeah I poop in public all the time in my diaper and I just walk around
all day like that and someone else was like don't do that like that's not fair to other
people to make them smell your poop and then they're like and since you're pooping all the
time you probably got used to the smell of your own and you think it smells good
but nobody else thinks that. Which diaper has the loudest crinkle? I found a post here it's
it's from 2008 it's from Craydon and the the topic in mature topics is
homosexuals and in quotes faggots and it I'm not gonna read the whole thing but
the first sentence is as a wise man once said there are black people and this is
it man this is the every episode from now on is about this website we're making a
whole i have about it is we're starting a podcast network and this is the first
spin-off podcast yeah yeah
and russell one hundred says it is a long time ago now
but i remember for digging a clothes shop and then doing a massive who in my
nappy as a complete accident
and they said i think i was about seven years old at the time
it doesn't count
mhm
if you're seven years old seven years old you shouldn't be having accidents you
You should be making awesome LEGO guns and getting shot for them.
You need to be two years old or forty years old.
Exactly.
In between that window there's no...
There's no...
Have you ever felt the need to poop and rush to put on a diaper just so you could take a
poo in it?
No.
No, I've never done that.
Yeah, I can't say I have.
Here's a post from Anon E-Mouse, I think we talked about them in the last diaper talk.
Their post topic is "What do you think about one player sex?"
Oh fuck, that's so good.
Oh my god, wait, okay, wait, wait, wait.
I'm going single player.
Okay, listen to this.
This is a diaper lover and celebrity.
What would it be like to be a diaper lover if you were a celebrity?
would you do if you're a celebrity and I scrolled down and there's somebody said I
thought I remember hearing a while ago that this guy was a supposed diaper
lover not positive maybe I'm remembering wrong and it's a screenshot of Samwise
Gamgee like in the Hobbit outfit not that would be funny though it's like like you
just like finally get a job as like a PA on like you know the new movie about like
Tom Hanks as a magician or whatever and he shows up on set for the first day and
you like go to bring him something in wardrobe and he's wearing a diaper and
there's a closet stocked with diapers and then he shoots you with a silenced
pistol. Someone responded to the celebrity thread and just said Tiger
That's a good guess.
If you had to guess, I would say like, I mean, probably like John Travolta.
Because I feel like if you have a couple things going on, you kind of have everything going
on.
Oh no, this is a post from GameBaby in 2008.
GameBaby says, "Is masturbating at 14 ok?
I really got something on my mind. I masturbate three times a week. Is this okay or should
I stop? It feels good, but I wish to know.
What's your professional opinion as an expert on teenage boys masturbation, Patrick?
I don't know, but a lot of people on here are saying like, "That's fine. I do it three
or four times a day."
Why aren't there diapers with adult themes on them? I mean, there are diapers with Disney
characters like Lion King, Cars, and DreamWorks characters, the ones from Madagascar, etc.
However, I have never really seen diapers that have adult-themed licensed characters on them.
Why not? How fun would it be to have a diaper with the Enterprise, an X-Wing, a Xenomorph,
a Necromorph, or the Back to the Future DeLorean, or Master Chief, or Johnny Five, or so on and so forth?
We need a Watchmen diaper set.
Right?
And it's like, "Oh, and it could look like Rorschach's Meer-Rorschach's Max."
So when you pee it makes a different ink blot.
What does this look like?
Shit.
It looks like a poopy diaper.
It looks like shit.
Here's a poster, I'm looking like it really early in 2008.
There's a post here from Valentine that says Obama Biden '08 and it says, "Well, Obama named
his running mate and it's Biden.
Any thoughts on this?"
And someone with a political compass thing that shows how libertarian they are says,
"Any reason you're happy he picked a white person?"
Whoa.
Wow.
Damn.
That's fucking crazy.
Biden has all the experience of McCain.
He brings foreign policy.
Oh, this is just...
Yeah.
Yeah, that's just Patrick.
This is just a very serious...
Oh, that's just my thoughts.
That's just my thoughts.
Oh, that's just my thoughts on Joe Biden.
I'm just thinking out loud.
Um.
Do you guys see any more good ones?
I see one.
There's one about weed legalization.
But they just love pot, dude.
There's so many military people on this site.
I don't get it.
I get it.
That makes perfect sense to me, dude.
You spend all day being yelled at by a guy who's bigger than you.
And that's his job.
You want to go home and you want to shit in your pants.
Oh my god, wait.
somebody was i found this but i think that's what it's tactical
somebody listed new to the site a little shy lake and just posted like a like a
hello message and pc baby responded to it and said
hi jocelyn firstly welcome to the group i hope you find the support you need
it's also nice to meet a girl gamer as most of the girl gamers online are
usually boys are men playing at all to character
as far as being a furry though goes though someone passed me my shotgun
If you can't find the info on making a nappy that you need, let me know as I may have some
external links that could be useful.
Now I'm just thinking about like an MKUltra type program that the military like tried sometime
in the early 2000s where they just made everybody wear diapers.
Imagine though being a diaper lover and you'd say, "Furries, pass me my shotgun."
Yeah.
Pass me my military issued hand- service weapon because...
Yeah, you can't...
Yeah, at least furries don't fucking shit in their fursuits.
Well maybe they do though.
Maybe some of them do.
Yeah, maybe this one does.
We don't know.
That's sort of a deadly combo.
I found- I don't think the post is funny but I think the title of it is very funny.
So a post from Kite that says "Free speech is dead."
(laughing)
- They were right, dude.
- God.
- They're fucking right.
All right.
- Yeah, I think we're at an hour.
- You guys wanna do patrons?
- Yeah, sure.
- Wait, let me go pee first.
- All right, well we're just gonna start.
- We're just gonna do the patrons.
- Okay.
- Bye, Pat.
Big shout out to Poco.
- Oh, yeah, Poco.
- Poco for everything.
Poco, we love you.
- All right, actually, we gotta really pee.
- All right, then go, dude.
- Poco's a boss.
one second the last one was
i think that i poker was the first i think she
no you're wrong
now now the last time you recorded the recorded was the twenty eight
uh... and so the last one
was the the the the brian gonzales thank you brian gonzales
mean a patron douglas
thank you
so it's sweet and simple
is that keyword
thank you
on my age
my age age
uh... hope the age stands for hello because i i hope it stands for happy
birthday because i think they recently happened
uh... ryan smith
thank you uh... tiny tiny and him
yeah i guess he we like it when you guys make your names funny yeah because i
think there's something to work with a tiny tin tin was also the name of the
british diaper lover
uh... daniel mckinnon
See, now that's some funny shit.
Two capital letters in the last name.
Josh Camp. Josh Camp?
Yeah, I'm going to Josh Camp.
Yeah, me too.
And I'm gonna learn how to fish,
and I'm gonna finger somebody.
That's what you do at Josh Camp.
Thanks, Tyler.
Thank you, Tyler.
Michael Naboo.
Thank you, Michael Naboo.
Michael Naboo, fuck yeah.
Poco.
Poco again.
Thank you for upgrading to Patrick Pricing.
- Our first Patrick Pricing princess.
- Yeah. - Look at that.
Will McGovern.
- Will McGovern, thank you.
Justin Kweepoff.
Kweepoff.
- Thank you, Justin.
- Ben J. Fry, what's the J stand for?
- Just smoking it up.
- Ben just smoking it up with weed.
- Just fucking smoking that.
- Fry.
- Brad Stockmo.
Thank you.
More like Brad Stockmo.
Raychill Dolezal.
Whoa, Raychill Dolezal.
I think that's like the fourth time
Raychill Dolezal has--
Yeah.
(laughing)
Honestly, yeah.
Taylor Wood.
Shout out Taylor Wood.
Art Jacob Marinus Cortis.
Nice one dollar patron.
That's a cool name.
Oh yeah, it's a one dollar patron.
You don't get anything.
Yeah, what do you get?
You're just in it for the love of the game.
Thank you, Art.
William Morrison, thank you.
Cool.
Caleb E. Karma.
Very powerful name, very strong name.
Yeah, the last name is very strong.
The first name is incredibly weak.
No, no, no!
Dude, take that back.
Some Girl.
That's my name.
Thank you, Some Girl.
Thank you, Brad Diaper.
Brad Daper, Diaper.
Brad Diaper.
Yeah, it's kind of topical for considering the episode. I hope it's probably Debor Mike Brolin
master chief level
Subscription, thank you
Kai's master chief level great guy upgraded to Patrick pricing. That's what I'm talking about. Thank you Kai
Oh, yeah, Kai. You're the man. We love yeah
Chris Maddab ag
Thanks. Thank you
Big bug. Thanks big bug. You big bug a little scary, but
Kevin F. Kern
Thanks, and uh Corey Dillinger are you the one with the freaking escape plan is there?
Oh big bug edited their pledge to $10 in the middle of the episode so
Yeah, biggest bug yeah, uh-huh even bigger bug
All right, all right diapers forever
diapers never stop
- Divers never stop shitting and pissing.
- Yeah.
- All right, bye. - Dookie.
- Bye.