You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Matt are you ready man?
We've been talking big shit.
We've been here.
- I am ready guys.
I drank my protein this morning.
I'm ready, I'm pumped.
- Oh my God, what kind of protein did you drink?
- Yeah, I drank this high testosterone,
like testosterone boosting protein.
Cause I think honestly that's probably the best defense
against COVID right now.
- It's just being so manly that it's scared of you.
- Well, it's proven that the higher your testosterone levels
are the more protected you are against COVID-19
which is why so many women are getting it.
- Wow, that's insane.
That's why. - Sorry ladies.
- Why have I been worried about anything?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I don't think you guys have anything to be worried about.
- No, I mean. - I got too much tea.
Yeah, I have so much tea that it pushed all the hair out of my head.
Yeah.
That's true.
I don't know if that's true though.
I think that's maybe like a cope that people have.
I think that's kind of a lie.
But people say like, yeah, sometimes you have so much testosterone that it turns you into
a bald gay baby.
And every guy who is bald looks so shitty.
I actually lost all of my hair because I have too much testosterone.
You know, like there's just so much of this manliness
flowing through me that I lost all of my hair,
but you know, it's just a side effect of being so masculine.
- Exactly, yeah, it's a give and take, you know.
- It just fries your hair from the inside.
- I actually look like The Rock.
- All the male thoughts just fizz inside your head
and they fuck up your follicles
and all your hair shoots out.
It shoots out like a darts.
- But it's a good trade because like,
yes, on one hand, I have so much testosterone
that the hair, I don't have any hair,
but I also can't cum or get a bone or two
as a side effect of having so much testosterone in my body.
You know?
- Yeah.
- So that's good.
- My hair's gonna be gone in two years.
That's what I'm giving it. - You have two years?
- Me too. - Probably, yeah.
It's starting to thin, I can tell.
Like I look in the mirror, I see it's going up.
I'm like, uh-oh.
I'm 24 right now, so I'm guessing by 26 it's gonna be gone.
- Dude, my shit started going when I was like 17.
- Yeah, you were like going bald when I first met you.
- Yeah, dude, God hates me. - Your hair used to look crazy.
Your hair was awesome.
Back when you were like trying to deny
that you were going bald.
- Yeah, I held onto it for a long time, Matt, don't be me.
You have beautiful hair.
You have beautiful little boy hair.
- No, no, no, no, it might look like that on camera,
but it's actually very thin and greasy.
- You have little baby hair.
- Yeah, you look so, you have such like tussle-able hair.
I just want to patch you on the head. I'm all sweaty. I went skating so I look like oh
nice
Patrick just revealed his hair and
No, no that was it that was a that was that was in ooh because he was a he's a skater boy and that impressed me
Yeah, are you a skater Matt? I?
I dabble when I was in like fourth grade. I I tried skateboarding nice. Yeah, that's the best age to start
What did you start hurt myself?
You hurt yourself in fourth grade?
Yeah, I hurt myself doing what? You go down a hill?
Yeah, I went on a ramp and I fell.
And I smacked my head and I passed out.
I don't want to skate anymore.
And then when I was in about seventh grade,
I decided I wanted to pick it back up
and my next door neighbors,
they were like a couple years older than me,
they were maybe like 16, 17,
I thought they were really cool.
And I saw they were skateboarding,
I was like, "Ah, fuck, I'm gonna go join them."
So I got my skateboard out
and I started skating towards them
and I hit a rock, like a little rock,
and it just made the skateboard stop
and I flew off and I smacked my elbow
and I was trying so hard not to cry.
I was holding back tears and they were all looking at me.
I just got up and went back inside.
Since then, I haven't skated that much.
- You haven't hit double boards since?
- I skate a little bit, yeah.
- You should try it when there's no rocks,
there's no pebbles.
Yeah, you should skate on the beach.
Yeah.
Exactly, that's the best spot.
You should try your kitchen floor or something.
They filled up Venice Park with a bunch of sand.
You can just go there now and just fucking--
It's the perfect time, yeah.
Yeah.
It's a surfer's paradise.
Exactly.
A ski park with sand?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Dude, it's awesome.
Go in there with some Johnny Cappahalla 2 board.
Just fuck that place up.
I don't know what shit you're talking about.
Exactly.
- Disney movie, Johnny Tsunami 2?
- Oh, okay.
- Yo, I've never heard of Johnny Tsunami until this week,
and then it's weird that now you bring it up,
because earlier this week, I was in Ventura
and I had a cocktail called Johnny Tsunami,
and I was like, oh, that's a funny name.
And then now, I'm hearing that name again in the same week,
I'm thinking there might be some kind of weird
simulation glitch going on.
- God damn, dude. - Oh my God.
- Johnny Tsunami broke the damn sim.
- I had a-- - Yeah, that's what did it.
- I had a giant simulation glitch today.
I posted about this, but I went to Dunkin Donuts,
as you can see, and I had a high, I pulled up,
it's a, so far, to the point where I order my drink,
it's a completely normal experience.
I get a cold brew, it's 3.19,
but then I get up to pay for it,
and I see that my cashier's name tag says her name,
her name is Meech Creech.
(laughing)
That's what they said and I was like, I had to give my fiance...
- You had to give your ID.
(laughing)
To buy Dunkin' Donuts.
- Is your name also MeechCreech?
- You get 10% off if your name is also MeechCreech.
- I was uncontrollably laughing
as soon as I looked at her name tag.
Just like in this woman's face.
And so I had to have my fiance pay for the drink
I couldn't even look at it. I had to hand her my card and be like, "You have to hand this to MeechCreech."
My thing is... Oh, go ahead.
So that's nobody's name... Nobody's name is MeechCreech, first of all.
But also, her first name had to be MeechCreech, because you don't put your last name on a name sheet.
Yeah, that's what I was about to say.
I was about to say your last name doesn't go on it so her first name is just Meech Creech.
Meech Creech Wilson.
Or maybe it's like an Ichiro situation.
It's a what?
It's an Ichiro situation where they put Ichiro on his jersey.
Oh maybe.
It could be an Ichiro situation.
I'm gonna go back to Dunkin Donuts tomorrow and be like excuse me ma'am.
Is this an Ichiro situation?
Yeah is this an Ichiro situation or is your first name two words, one of them being Meech
the other being Creech. You're gonna go back there tomorrow and be like, "Oh, can I, I
had a question for Meech Creech," and they're gonna send you to a mental hospital. I just
want to call and be like, "Has there ever been anybody, not even who works here, has
there ever been somebody named Meech Creech?" I'm gonna look this up real quick. I just
I wanna look this name up.
- MeechCreech? - Is it M-E-E-C-H?
- M-E-E-C-H-C-R-E-E-C-H.
- It's a catchy name, I will say.
- Yeah, Ryan.
- Oh, I found someone on TikTok named MeechCreech.
- So I also found that earlier because I was like, okay,
to confirm that I'm not just completely going crazy,
I need to see if this woman exists.
But she doesn't have like a Facebook or like an Instagram,
at least not under the name MeechCreech.
but she does have a TikTok @meachcreach.
- Yeah, I thought, is that her?
It's like a girl that looks like
she might work at Dunkin' Donuts.
- Yes, yeah, it is her.
I confirmed, it is her.
- Yeah, her name's Meachcreach, yeah.
- Her name is Meachcreach.
Also, she was the only person in the Dunkin' Donuts
whose name tag was handwritten.
Everybody else had a typed one.
(laughing)
- They refused to print that shit.
They were like, no, you want that on there,
make it yourself. It's not even that the computer just won't print that.
It's not a valid name.
Error. MeechCreech is not a name. Yeah. Got a 404 on that one.
Oh yeah man that was um that was fucked up. It's awesome. That's fucking ridiculous. Yeah.
You know Covid, you know these quarantine times got everyone going a little crazy.
Yeah how have you been? You just uh you're in LA right? We didn't even introduce him.
Yeah, we're here Matt Matt Watson from Super Mega everyone. How's it going Matt? Hey, it's gone great
You know, I'm just chilling in quarantine actually quarantine was supposed to end on Thursday and then today they extended it for three more months
so
Yeah, we're dealing with that. But that sucks. Other than that. It's it's pretty it's pretty fucking good. Yeah
Yeah, I've never properly, you know said hello to any of you guys. Hello. You can go ahead now. Yes. Yeah
Hey, how's it going? It's good man Patrick. Hello to meet you. Hi
Nice meeting you too. Hello
Wait, I'm trying to skip through and Cameron. It's nice to meet you. Cam. Nice to meet you, man. Thank you
Oh my god, you're a couple of handsome boys. Thank you
You know, yeah
What's the hair yeah, these I know it is there I know your team hair because of your head
But you know what Matt, you're pretty good looking yourself, buddy
Shucks. Yeah. Thank you so yeah
I'm gonna kill you're really handsome first time I ever saw you on a Twitter video
I said who's that handsome man, and how can you sit that out? Well my way into his world?
Yeah, yeah, and then you did you did a good job. Yeah. Yeah, somehow did yeah somebody
Yeah, somebody who I know who's a big fan of yours. I guess notice that you were a 14 year old boy
It's a it's 14. It's a yeah. It's one of my 14 year old boyfriends that I play
I'm
old boyfriend so for boys they could be 19 they could be 14 year old boyfriends
no I feel like I'm caught up in a web of lies but it's but I don't have
boyfriends or teenage fuck you guys I was thinking we do have I feel like our
- I think both our, both the fan base,
or your fan base is the exact kind of people
that we make fun of on this show.
- Yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause we go on a website called the Top Tens
and it's all just kids who probably have
like a super mega quote in their bio.
And we're just like--
- I love, I think about putting a super mega quote
in my bio as well, you guys should too.
- Yeah, I might throw one in.
Give us a, anything out of your mouth is a super mega quote.
- That's true, yeah.
- So go ahead and give us one for our bios.
- Yeah, you can just grab any one out of this entire podcast.
It's free to use.
- And just snip it, okay.
- Yeah, just snip it, snip it please.
- All right, good to know.
- Or put the date I noticed you on Twitter in your bio.
- Yeah, Matt followed.
Matt followed for whatever, whatever.
- 'Cause like we have a lot, like most of our fans are like,
I'd say like above 18, but then there's a big,
a big loud minority that's like 14 to 16.
- And kids are a minority.
We've been arguing for quite a long time.
Kids are--
- We're pro kids, we're anti-principal on this podcast.
- Anti-principal, anti-parent.
- Anti-homework.
- Pro lunch and recess.
Anti-class, anti-gym, honestly.
- Lunchables for all, that's one of our platforms.
- I had a dream last night, I was buying Lunchables.
- Damn, I got one the other day,
I got a ham and Swiss Lunchable.
- Man.
- Those are actually my least favorite.
- Really?
- No, the ham and Swiss, yeah.
- Turkey and cheddar.
- Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what particular,
like it was just a particular day
where the ham and Swiss hit.
I don't know.
- Swiss is just such a bland tasting cheese.
- Doesn't taste like shit, dude.
- No, the Swiss, it didn't taste like Swiss at all.
- Yeah, man, you wish it tasted like shit.
- No, I don't.
- Yeah.
- No.
Swiss tastes like you are remembering what cheese tastes like
and you get like a little,
you're like, oh yeah, kind of.
- All right, yeah, there's something there.
- A memory of cheese.
- Like a faint neuron passing in your brain.
- Yeah, exactly, just like a synapse,
the cheese synapse is going like, is firing.
- It tastes like a picture of cheese.
- Yeah, exactly.
It tastes like how a picture of cheese tastes.
I was thinking about kids cuisine the other day.
How fucked is it that they give you a frozen brownie?
- Oh, dude.
- That was my favorite part,
and actually this sounds weird,
but I think that sometimes,
you know how like the corn would kind of
end up in the brownie?
- Yeah, under the fucking brownie.
I liked that shit.
No, I liked that shit.
It was pretty good.
That's why they put it in the Hungryman.
I expect this kind of behavior from Patrick, but you...
I mean, come on, dude.
I'm glad Matt and I agreed on that, like almost instantly.
It's not bad.
It's really not bad.
And I love how Hungryman's just the grown-up version of Kid Cuisine, but they still were
like, "We'll put the brownie in there."
We need that fucking brownie in there.
It's a transitioning food from kids to adulthood.
- Hungry Man was like, they were,
they originally called it abusive husband cuisine.
(laughing)
But then they were like, I guess we'll go Hungry Man.
- See, you know what I mean?
- Fucking like 45 year old dude in a tank top
sitting in front of his TV, eating one of those.
And the chicken, the chicken was my favorite,
but God damn, it was so soggy every time.
- Dude.
- Flip it over, the underside's just smooth and soggy.
- They, I think one time I ate a feather out of one of them.
Like I swear to God, I ate, I swear to God,
I pulled a fucking feather out,
unless it was some kind of muscle tendon
that looked like a feather.
- And then you ate it, you pulled it out and ate it?
- I pulled it out of my mouth and I put it in the tray.
- Oh, and then you put it back in your mouth.
- I ate the rest of it, I fucking paid for it.
- Yeah, the rest of the feather.
- You got a feather and a hungry man?
- I think I did.
- Jesus Christ.
- It was when I was in community college.
- Oh.
- You got a little more than you paid for, that's a burden.
- Ooh, I got the whole damn bird.
I think the most piss poor excuse of a Lunchables is the nachos one, because it's like, that's
not a meal, that's just a bunch of little tiny little circular chips and some horrible cheese
sauce from a 7-Eleven like pump.
Yeah, that's baby food.
Have one of those fucking hot dogs.
But they are pretty good I will say.
You gave me little chips and slop, and you expect me to do things with this?
Uh-uh.
That's not a Lunchable, that's a snackable.
Yeah, that's right.
God damn.
That's fucking right.
That's a snackable bitch.
Go off, go off camera.
- Go off, Cameron. - King.
- Yeah. - Why fucking have one?
- They have Lunchable, like, extremes now.
- What does that mean? - Those are for the bullies.
- Yeah, the bullies.
- Those are the bullies' food.
- It's just like a burrito, though.
- Yeah.
- It's just like, slightly one step up from the shitty nachos.
It's like, we have several tiers of Lunchables food.
You can have some circular corn chips,
or you can have a really shitty burrito,
is gonna be classified as extreme because this is one step higher on the food chain.
Exactly. Also, with the burrito, you can eat that and skateboard.
That's true. Remember, there was a Lunchables kid, right? There was like a mascot.
Yeah, it was you.
No.
It was you. You ate all of them. That's why you're like this now.
That's what, yeah. No, but he like looked, it was like some claymation kid. He kind of
looked like the Fruit Punch guy, but the Fruit Punch guy's wearing a hat. So I don't know,
like I like this hair looked like the fruit punch guys at I'm gonna Google
Lunchables mascot yeah it was Rob Dyrdek for a little bit in 20 like 13 was the
Lunchables guy yeah that's what directly landed him as his job in the fantasy
factory was after that they said this guy's so fucking good in the Lunchables
commercials we're gonna give him his own factory we're gonna we're gonna make him
the foreman of the fantasy factory there was so there there was a there was a
line of Lunchables called Lunchables Uploaded.
Oh I remember that yeah.
Yeah and Rob Dyrdek was the spokesman for Lunchables Uploaded because of
ridiculousness and stuff.
I connected that as a YouTuber. I like it a lot.
It's the only ones I eat.
All that's coming up with for the Lunchables mascot is a
platypus and a jackalope for Lunchables Mixed Up.
Mixed Up Challenges it says.
mixed up my tongue. Here's Rob Dyrdek and the Jabberwockys for Lunchables uploaded.
How many fucking iterations of Lunchables were there? I have no idea. They went
through a lot. And the platypus is just, the platypus is just a real platypus.
Yeah. It's not like the apple jacks mascot. It's like taxidermied. Yeah. My least
favorite fucking mascot in this this type of realm is the SpaghettiOs one. Oh the SpaghettiO?
That big fucking ring. Yeah. Yeah. Cause like I don't know like. What does he do? Cause he's
he well it's like an open ring but they make it look like it's his mouth. Oh yeah. It makes
literally no sense. He's got a tongue coming up like under his chin. Yeah it makes no sense
and then I remember they got in a lot of trouble cause they did that uh was it the Pearl Harbor
Yeah, with Pearl Harbor.
Did a Pearl Harbor SpaghettiOs tweet?
Yeah, with him holding an American flag.
And it says, "Take a moment to remember #PearlHarbor with us."
And that's a picture of SpaghettiOs mascot holding an American flag.
Oh my god.
That was one of the best times to be online.
That day.
I remember when that happened.
That was one of the most beautiful moments of the internet.
moments of the internet that when American Airlines tweeted out the the
picture of the woman with a model airplane in her vagina. That had to be intentional.
Yeah that was back when like the like the pictures didn't like like have a preview
so you had to click on it to open it. It was a twit pic or whatever. Yeah and then
you had to click the link and it would open in the app. Yeah man Wendy's ruined all
that shit man. Yeah Wendy's did fuck everything up. Wendy's hired some fucking Vassar grad and
they were like yeah you get to like some Vassar Brad with a fave star in his bio
yeah exactly let's make it on his eyebrow
art that's yeah fucking sucks man and now all the brands go yeah we got steakums
yeah you have steakums followed me and kept DMing me it was it was just the
most obnoxious like brand trying to be funny shit damn they were just trying to
riff with you or they were they didn't want anything no they weren't they
weren't doing like so like it wasn't like a sponsorship like we're trying to
hire you no they were just riffing with me and I was like all right well I love
riffing with the Stakehams brand it is DM you like sometimes Stakehams be
hitting different sorry mom let me call you back I just got a DM from Stakehams
again yeah now like you know now he's did start that subway is trying to pretend
they didn't have the pedophile guy is their main dude for 20 years they're
just like dope fucking women deserve 70 or 80 percent of the since it's like you
a fucking yeah you let him go around the country to schools he's in size me going
to a fucking school telling kids how hard it is to lose weight there's so many
pictures of him at movie premieres I found yeah what the fuck yeah go yeah
you can use it a bunch of Avengers movies I think and he was that maybe the
Scooby-Doo movie there's like a bunch of a bunch of stuff he's a real hero in
movies? He wasn't in them, he was just not invited to the premieres. He was in Super Size Me, yeah, with Morgan
Spurlock. I'm surprised Morgan Spurlock didn't convince him to stop being a pedophile with his
brilliant wit. Yeah, so what if Morgan Spurlock makes a documentary called Super Pedophile Me?
Yeah, and he's a pedophile every day for 30 days, and he sees how much weight he loses.
He sees how much weight he loses and he also he has to convince Jared Fogle to stop being
a pedophile.
Yeah, that's pretty smart.
And we made this in 2008.
It would have killed honestly before Obama got elected.
That would have been like, that would have been like.
Thanks a lot Obama came around and ruined everything.
We can't make, we cannot pedophiles anymore.
I know, yeah.
God damn it.
Damn it.
before Obama you could make what was that movie with with like Morgan Freeman and
it was right after March of the Penguins came out and it was called like fuck of
the shit penguins and it's whatever it's the same footage from March of the
Penguins but it's just Morgan's part or Morgan Freeman being like suck my pussy
you stupid penguin yeah yeah Bob Saget's in that dude it's good man yeah came out
- I hated that fucking movie.
- Which one, March of the Penguins or Farce?
- March of the Penguins.
I didn't see Farce, I should have seen that.
I've never even heard of that.
But March of the Penguins was one of the,
I saw it in theaters, one of the most boring movies
I think I've ever seen.
- Yeah man, I was young.
I was homeschooled at the time,
and my mom was like, 'cause when you're homeschooled,
you're not schooled at all.
And so my mom was like,
"Today we're gonna watch a movie for school."
And so we just went to the movie,
and I was like, "Fuck, I rather would have been doing math."
fucking boring ass stupid penguin movie.
What a shit, they should have done a movie about tigers.
- Yeah.
- That's what they figured out with Planet Earth,
was they were like, oh you have to show things getting eaten.
- Yeah, right.
- You can't just have a penguin sitting on an egg.
- I mean honestly--
- And walk at like two miles per hour
and just waddling and that's it.
- Yeah, slowest walk ever.
- In a bleak white background.
- Yeah, penguins are the most boring thing to choose for that.
they're just like slow birds that can't even fly
and there's walk around and it's just snow
is nothing
exactly they could have just made like that they could have made that movie in
a gmod map
(laughter)
they could have just done that, would have been more interesting, you could have had a heavy weapons guy in there
a more interesting movie would have just been like march of the guy and they
just follow a guy around for a year
because guys do stuff
yeah exactly. March of Daniel. Yeah and then he went to the he went to the to the
arcade. Today Daniel went to Dave and Buster's. He went yeah he went to Dave and Buster's and he
put his name on the game as A.S.S. Yeah. I was like that's actually kind of funny.
When I got my first cell phone I did that and I took a I remember I took a picture and I sent it to
like every one of my contacts. Nice. And I bet it killed. It landed it stuck
It's done. You should send that to Stakehams. Yeah
Y'all check this out, and I'm sure Stakehams would would whatever college intern is running the Twitter account would get quite the chuckle out of that
Yeah, oh, it's the the address that son. Yeah, it's the executive son. Is it true? Oh, yeah
Oh fuck I just shit talked him. I didn't know it's the executive son. Mm-hmm. Yeah, dude
Every state is a game at Stakehams. Yeah, dude. You just fumbled that bag so hard
I just blew the fucking Stakehams deal god damn it
Alright, this first list, I sent a link in the Zoom chat, Matt.
This first list is called "Top 10 Stupidest Ways to Defend Yourself from a Murderer."
Okay.
And you strike me as sort of like, well you mentioned you use the same microphone as Joe
Rogan.
Wait, like the actual same microphone?
Like the one that he uses?
Yeah, no, he let me borrow it.
Yeah.
At the same time.
You have to be sort of like a self-defense, karate,
fighting other guys kind of fella, kind of style guy.
So I figured we would do like a self-defense
themed list for you.
Thank you, thank you.
When you see me, do I strike you as the type of guy
that you might get in a fight with,
you might like, you might ball on the street with?
I'll put it this way,
you are not the kind of guy I would try to murder.
You strike me as a--
You know I'm 130 pounds, right?
- 130 pounds of pure lean muscle.
You already fucking said you're taking
testosterone-laced protein at the beginning of this thing.
You think I'm gonna fuck with you?
You kidding, dude?
You'll crush me between your bicep
and your forearm like a melon.
- My big fucking muscles.
- Yeah, I don't know what you're hiding, you know?
- Dude, when I'm really on the testosterone,
when I'm really on the T,
these things fucking explode out of my arms.
should see it yeah they just it rips the the skin oh my god oh yeah whoa
plus you have a tattoo I mean a Simpsons tattoo oh my god dude
fuck yes I wouldn't fuck with you if I see it I see the you know he looks
exactly like Joe Rogan yeah we go to the gym together we trying to beef up like
him I'm trying to lose my hair and get as red as him - that's where you grabbed
I'm looking I mean I think it's just something that happens when you're bald look at how red I am yeah
Yeah, I think you were always red
No, you've been pretty red. You've always been pretty red. I've met I was almost never read until I shaved my head
No, no you guys are you unlocked your redness chakra?
That didn't
So top 10 stupidest ways to defend yourself from a murderer
Do you have it up? Do you have it? Are you able to have it up Matt?
Yes, I I have to google it cuz I don't have zoom on my computer. Hold on
Oh, it's not a mom in Twitter or something the defender show should top ten ways to defend yourself in Minecraft
No, I'll just send it to you on Twitter. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got it
Oh my god, he's a genius with this with the computer, you know, I uh, no, I don't have it actually
Oh, yep. There it is. I found it. Sorry. All right, we're good. We're good. All right. Nice
Number one, grab their knife by the blade.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know how that, I mean, come on, that's a rookie mistake.
You know.
That's not one you want to do, I'll tell you that right now.
No.
Be it attacked by a murderer, you grab their knife by the blade.
That's the first week, the first month of self-defense classes, they just tell you over
and over, do not grab the knife by the blade.
That's going to be your first instinct.
Also, this is a, it's a double as good advice if you are a murderer.
Yeah.
Just don't grab your own knife by the blade.
They're giving away all the secrets right now, honestly.
Yeah.
Even a chef's apprentice don't do that.
Yeah, anybody who messes with knives, you know, a little kid.
Anybody in general, honestly.
It doesn't even matter if you're messing with the knife.
So far it's more just life advice than anything else.
Matt, have you ever been murdered?
Once, once back in like eighth grade.
Back in eighth grade?
Yeah.
And did you survive?
No, I didn't.
I hate to hear that.
Yeah, no, it sucked.
It did.
It sucked.
It was kind of a really shitty day, but you know, I got past it.
Just as you're starting to love somebody, they get murdered in eighth grade.
I'm in that situation right now, so.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somebody said, "Don't trigger Trash Kid."
There's kind of a rotating cast of 13 year olds on this website who we see in every single
list and this is one of them.
And he says, "I got bandages."
Shit, he's got answers to everything, dude.
This guy's a problem solver.
In the middle of being stabbed, he's going to rip out some bandages and tape his hand
up real quick.
That would be the ultimate "fuck you" move to the murderer.
Sorry buddy, I have a health pack on my wall, like Halo Combat Evolved.
I'll just grab that and we're good.
I got a pocket full of gauze he just pulls out and unravels and wraps around his hand
right after grabbing the blade.
Yeah, sorry buddy, I have a self-revive.
That's right.
I'm overhealed.
You only hit my shield.
You only hit my shield, you didn't even do that much damage.
Yeah, you broke one bar of shield.
You didn't do fairly any damage to me, buddy.
I still got 56%.
I actually get to make a counterattack, actually, now.
I actually parry you.
It's my turn now.
You attacked, it's my turn.
Somebody else says, "If you were to grab this incorrectly, it would result in your hand bleeding.
But if you were able to grab the knife at the correct angle, it may be a possibility to get it from the burglar without cutting yourself."
I'm the only...
You just pinch it.
Yeah.
Yeah, like a...
You have to have really strong fingers to do that.
What other part of the knife is exposed?
You'd have his hand all the way around the grip.
Yeah, you just use two fingers and pinch the 5mm of grip that's exposed outside.
Maybe you do... maybe you clap it.
You clap the knife like this.
A clap might work.
And then pull it away.
Honestly? Pull it towards you.
Yeah, you clap it and then you pull it towards you.
You pull the knife towards yourself.
Yeah, you pull it right here.
Yeah.
And that's gonna cut your third eye right open and then you can do some psionic attacks at
it.
Yeah, you can unleash the DMT that's actually in your body.
Yeah.
By dying.
Your naturally occurring DMT.
Yeah, the naturally occurring DMT.
There's another -
There's another comment, there's a pair of comments here that says, Sir Sheep comments,
why would this be a problem?
And then someone responds, "@sirsheep, you might hurt yourself with a blade like that.
The dark one.
221B."
That's a terrifying username.
Oh, dude, he has a clapback, though.
Sir Sheep has the fucking clapback.
You see that?
Oh, the internet.
The place where you must explain every sarcastic comment.
Sometimes I forget that I'm not saying these things to people in person.
Oh, shit.
God damn.
Oh my god, dude.
Some ice for that burn.
Yeah, sometimes people take the gloves off in these comments, man.
Yeah.
Number two, you headbutt their weapon out of their hands.
That seems fine.
That seems like, I mean, if you headbutt the weapon out of their hands, if it works, that's
good, right?
Firemist in the comments brings up a great point.
You'll shoot your head.
That's actually, I didn't think about that.
Because I forget that so many guns have another trigger on the barrel just in case somebody
headbutts it and it automatically shoots them. That's that little thing on top of the revolver
that little the little fin on top of like the little thing that little sticky thing that
sticks up. Yeah. The sticky thing that a cowboy oh no no the thing at the oh okay the thing
at the front. That's the second trigger. Yeah. Yeah. You hit that smack that bad boy with
your head you're gonna get you're gonna get popped. Yeah. Yeah. But if you can get the
murderer to headbutt the weapon if you can trick them into headbutting it. If you can
and send murderers are so susceptible to dares.
- Yeah.
- That if you just say,
- Dare you to headbutt the weapon out of your hands.
- You can say, what are the odds?
What are the odds you headbutt your own gun
and shoot yourself in the brain?
- They're betting people.
- One in five.
- Yeah.
- And you count it down
and that's actually a pretty high chance he's gonna get it.
- That's a pretty good chance
that you're gonna get off scot-free too.
'Cause you also can't get in trouble for murder
if it was on a bet.
- If it was a fair, what are the odds?
Then I could see that holding up in court.
Exactly, yeah.
The judge will be like, "Well, it was the odds."
And if it doesn't, you can just ask the judge, "What are the odds that everything is dropped?"
I'll give you one in eight.
Three, two, one, seven.
Everybody goes seven, you fucker.
I'm free.
And guess what?
I'm going to do it again.
Yeah.
I'm going to do this over and over.
And it doesn't matter that I'm saying this in court.
I can do it as many times.
- That's how Casey Anthony got off actually.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- What are the odds I didn't kill my kid?
- That's also why she did it in the first place though, Seth.
(laughing)
The kid could only count to one.
What are the odds?
One.
(laughing)
- Ah, shit.
- Fuck.
- She didn't wanna do it.
- She didn't wanna do it, but she's--
- What are the odds though?
Yeah, she's somebody, she respects,
if you're with Casey Anthony
and you are walking out with your parents
from the grocery store and you call shotgun,
she's not gonna say blitz,
she's not gonna try to steal that from you.
You get to ride shotgun.
Yeah.
She's gonna honor that, no matter what.
She honors it.
And that's why I respect her a lot.
She's an honorable person.
Yeah, yeah.
Number three, tickle them as a distraction.
I feel like this one would actually work.
It could work.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
So what if you're being murdered by a kid?
Mmm.
One of Caleb's 14 year old boys.
No.
No Matt.
No. Not.
You're gonna say not at the end of that.
Yeah, then you're in trouble because there's 14 of them.
Exactly.
You can't tickle them all at once.
Yeah I can.
You can tickle 14 boys at once.
No, no I can't.
I can tickle no boys.
Fuck dude, um, you just set yourself up you set yourself up for that dude. Yeah, you set yourself up on 14 dates
It'll work if I'm being killed by a tickle me Elmo. Oh
But not much else. Yeah. Yeah, or a tickle me Caleb
Or a tickle me. It's just normal me. That's pretty ticklish
guy that'd be the most looking thing I think the tickle me Caleb yeah it was
like a bald kids boy that's covered in tattoos I look like a cat has the face
apt monkey face yeah every time I think about tickle me Elmo I think about that
poor woman that got her face ripped off as a result of yeah Travis yeah friend
the show. Oh yeah, Charlotte Nash did. Yeah, all because she was holding the Tickle Me Elmo.
Yeah, it was a Tickle Me Elmo and she also had got a haircut so Travis didn't recognize her
and also she gave Travis Xanax. Oh yeah, Matt, you just stumbled into like one of our biggest
knowledge bases I would say, that us three share. White women that have been attacked by chimpanzees.
Yeah, we have one. It's fun. They do an interview with her like every two or three years on NBC.
Oh, I thought you meant Cameron and Patrick. You were like, yeah, they do an interview with her
every year. We do. That's pretty sweet. Every couple years, she gets like a new surgery and
they do a new interview with her. And every year it's like a little longer because she's a little
more like easy to look at a little longer. But recently, like they they gave her eyes,
- Damn. - Which is huge.
- Whoa. - 'Cause she, for a while,
she just looked like, she looked like Keanu Reeves
in the Matrix when they take his mouth away,
but for his eyes also.
- She looks like, yeah, she kinda looked like
the putty guys from Power Rangers.
- She looks claymation.
(laughing)
They're getting close to making her really giant.
One of these days.
She's going to be so fuckable.
Oh my god.
One of the surgeries is going to be a big old tit job.
Yeah.
Before.
That was the first one they did.
She didn't do anything.
Travis didn't touch any part of her body except her hands.
Travis did you a favor.
Yeah.
grass we put some huge fucking from B's to D's yeah we got you
Charlotte Nash has absolutely bolted on tits now. Oh Charlotte if you would have come on and set the
record straight by showing us that you don't have. I'm sure she's an avid
listener and I'm sure that I'm sure that that is that also this conversation she
would approve of. Well yeah she's a total whore for attention I mean I told you
she keeps going on TV bragging that she doesn't have any hands. I mean just...
I just knocked my phone off my desk. She's a huge super mega fan I don't know.
she's always commenting on the videos
I'm sorry sure what it is it makes me want to be so mean to you it's cuz you're
it's cuz probably the face yeah I look like I look like Travis and I as my
reflection and I feel the need to defend him. He actually did it because he was on
Xanax and apparently in chimpanzees that causes paranoia and hallucinations. Yeah
I don't know why you would give a monkey a human drug. Well first of all
it would be very funny. Like that video of that monkey smoking weed? Yeah. Well
yeah you know that monkey fucking just disemboweled one of those guys
immediately after. Nothing's funnier to me than monkeys smoking cigarettes
that's one of the funniest things in the entire world to me.
It's funny that they know what to do with them. Like they get a life cigarette.
Yeah, it's like they immediately know what to do with a cigarette. It's crazy.
It's in our ancestral memories. You can like...
That's right.
Yeah, you can meditate and the caveman knowledge will come back to you how to
correctly smoke a cigarette if you don't know how.
It's true.
Yeah.
Do you imagine a caveman cigarette all covered in like...
Yeah, man, it was a mammoth tusk.
Yeah.
It was a giant...
Hollowed out man. It's a giant spike. No, not even hollowed out. It was a leather wrapped cigarette.
It was a saber-toothed tiger tooth dude. Just smoking leather. Smoking that wheel. Yeah.
Smoking that caveman wheel. Yeah. Yeah. Let me hit that wheel.
Number four, hit them with a pillow. Could work. Somebody says uh,
How about a pillow of rocks?
Whoa!
Yeah.
That's a really good point.
When I was a kid, I thought, I heard that like people in, like people have socks full
of quarters as like a defense thing, and so I would walk around my house with one.
I just thought it was cool.
You're defending it's your mom giving you chores.
I would just have dad comes out and yells at you and you can swing it around.
Yeah, how about you try doing the dishes, Nathan?
Like a greaser standing on a corner with a chain just kind of spinning it around.
Yeah.
There's a comment by Trigger Trash Kid that says, "No, I have candy stuffed in it."
What?
Wow.
In the pillow, not the pillowcase.
That's what I did.
I used to trick or treat with a pillowcase.
Oh, me too.
Yeah, me too.
That was the best way to do it.
Yeah.
You can get the most volume.
Exactly, yeah.
I think I've talked, I probably posted about it before, but there's like a, here's another
Patrick story.
I did a, I, we, we went from like my mom, my aunts were my neighbors or were my neighbors
and we like had like a bowl out that said like, take one.
So like, as soon as I like got to my house in the neighborhood, I filled up the bowl.
I filled up my bag with the bowl and then I went in the house and then just filled it
up with microwave burritos and put it out on the porch.
This is when I was like 11 and I only got caught because my cousin took one and tried to make
one as soon as he got back to my aunt's house.
Did you guys ever do like a, do you have any super problematic Halloween costumes in your
past?
Ooh, I don't know.
I don't think so.
One of my uncles, there's an old picture of him dressed up as Sambo.
What?
Which I won't elaborate on.
Not a specific guy, just like, he did like old school blackface.
Yeah.
Ah, damn dude.
Wow, that's crazy.
Yeah dude, Boston's awesome man.
One year I went as Jamaican Jackie Chan.
How did that work?
What did that look like?
Can you do it again?
Can you do the impression?
Yeah, I can do the voice.
do the impression? Yeah I did, I was dressed up in my Taekwondo gi and then I had one of
those Rastafarian hats with the dreadlocks and I was also a year that I
brought a, instead of a pillowcase I brought a trash bag because I was
like, but that was pretty ambitious. Right you got to get the, you got to bring the
pillowcase you can't bring a trash bag because then like they're throwing away
to get you're expecting you to get more candy rush hour would have been so much
funnier if Jackie Chan was doing a Jamaican voice that entire time. Jackie Chan in hard
blackface the entire movie yeah yeah and Chris Tucker just the whole time
like hey man what are you doing come on fighting crime this is not helping no
Just creating tension between the two of us.
Number five.
They're just so mad at each other in the car.
They won't talk.
Like all the witty banter from Rush Hour or whatever.
Just gone.
It's just the two of them just sitting in the car and Jackie Chan looking at them like.
Yeah, and Jackie Chan, he doesn't understand why he's mad.
Just can't wrap his mind around it.
Yeah.
Number five.
Offer to play a video game with them as a distraction.
Whoa.
Hey, I know you wanted to shoot me dead, but how about we play a little Minecraft instead?
Yeah.
How about, do you have Jackbox Party Pack?
Because, man, that thing is funny as hell.
Yeah.
I don't know, it might work.
Here's what I would do.
I would tell them to delete system 32.
And then they'd be so distracted.
I'd be like hey before you kill me take out that to get that Lenovo
You got a strap to your back and delete system 32. It'll really speed up your computer. Yeah
Yeah, oh man. Well. I'm always looking for a way to speed up my computer. Yeah, I heard you'll be able to try force
After you delete it. Yeah, if you run a magnet over your computer over your hard drive
Just run a magnet over your dad's hard drive, and then you can come kill me
Just do that first hold on getting a call from your dad. Yeah, he says
you need to put a magnet on his hard drive before you can come kill me.
Yeah.
Number six.
I'm tired of dealing with the geek squad.
Number six is put a plastic bag over their weapon.
That one might work.
Yeah, you can't see it.
The top comment here says, like, surrounded in asterisks, like an action, house catches
on fire.
What does that mean?
What kind of weapon would putting a plastic bag over it make your house catch on fire?
They're coming at you with a torch.
- Yeah, they're a...
- It's like an Indiana Jones torch.
- Yeah, I like Trigger Trash Kid says,
"I would wrap it with toilet paper."
But then it's, to me that's even scarier
'cause then that's like a mummy gun.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- It's terrifying.
- That shit could be haunted.
- Yeah, you know, I mean, and you just know
with this whole COVID thing that mummies
are having a rough go of it with the toilet paper prices.
- Yeah.
- Am I right, folks?
mummies are they haven't had a change in quite a while yeah you can say that
again they see that he has to use toilet paper yeah a mummy with paper towels it
just feels different yeah it's sopping wet brown a copy of printer paper mummy
have you seen the the reusable toilet paper well I've seen it in your bathroom
No. Yeah, where you use it. No. Yeah. No! I've heard of this.
And he's never cleaned it either. I saw it on Etsy. Yeah, it's called "Your Hand."
Oh, shit! Goddamn. I don't use Matt's hands to do that.
No, I'm talking to you, Patrick. No, I don't use Matt's hand to wipe my ass.
Patrick, I... That would be crass. You can wash... There's soap, dude.
Hands are made to be washed. You know what I'm saying?
That's why God gave us hands.
That's why God took them away from one Charlotte Nash.
He's like, "I've been watching what you've been doing.
I'm not a fan of this.
We're going to have to change some things around here."
I like to imagine she has OCD and now she goes to wash her hands and just holds them
in front of the water 30 times a day.
I've hit my limit on Charla Nash.
I can't.
That's the most in an episode.
You're going to be walking down the streets of Boston and a chimp's going to escape from
the zoo in like in the true karma fashion.
It's going to directly target you and rip your face off.
No man, he's going to shake his hand.
He's going to say thank you.
He's going to think it's his brother.
Thank you for your activism.
just gonna think that Caleb is Sharla Nash. I see the two of you together I
wouldn't be able to tell the difference. Yes you would dude I have beautiful
hands and I don't have big fat pretty tits. Number seven set fire to your house
that's a that is dumb this is definitely this should be number one this is one of
the stupidest ways I can imagine.
- Yeah, unless you're not inside your house
and the murderer is, and you--
- Unless the murderer is your parents or roommate.
- Yeah.
- And also you have a fireproof room.
- Yeah, or you have another house that you could go to.
- Yeah, joke's on you.
I have two houses.
- Yeah.
- I like the first response from firing this.
That's pretty funny.
- Go ahead, you can do what you're allowed to say.
- Oh, I can read it?
- Yeah, you can do it.
- This is Bob.
Bob says hi.
This is Bob when his house burns down.
Bob is homeless now and probably dead.
- Whoa, that's one of the saddest stories I've ever heard.
- This is how they-- - It's pretty epic.
- This is how they try to kill Michael Myers
in the 2018 Halloween.
I just realized.
They do it in a movie.
So it's gotta be work then, right?
- No, true. - If it's in a movie, it works.
I mean, they wouldn't-- - Did they kill him?
- Well, it's a cliffhanger ending.
- You don't know.
They filmed that in my hometown in South Carolina.
- Really?
- Oh, forget your,
somebody told me you were from South Carolina.
You know where I am right now?
- Where?
- North Carolina.
Just one, just one spot up, baby.
- You guys are state brothers.
- Yeah.
- One step over.
But I go to South Carolina sometimes.
I go to Boardwalk on the Beach at Myrtle Beach.
- Myrtle Beach is so great.
- I love it, dude.
Oh my god, the Hard Rock Cafe in Myrtle Beach.
Ooh, I'm gonna go.
That's where it pops off, dude.
Man, I used to have a Hard Rock Cafe Tel Aviv t-shirt.
I don't know where that went.
(laughing)
I gotta find that.
I fucking, I need to go hit up the Hard Rock Cafe
in Myrtle Beach, do the karaoke night,
perform Rap God in its entirety.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, but change it to Rock God
and watch the crowd go absolutely wild.
When are they gonna make a Hard Rap Cafe?
That's what I want to know.
- Yeah.
Yeah, the hard rap cafe.
- Yeah, music is changing.
- Graffiti everywhere.
Oh my God, it'd be so cool.
- Yeah.
- Surrounded by police officers with guns drawn.
- Oh, your waiter is a police officer.
- Hip hop fries.
The signature burger is just called the N word.
With a soft A.
that Jackie Chan in the kitchen with a black face on,
cooking some shit up.
He does stand up there in black face.
- Yeah, he does Def Jam stand up.
The hard rap cafe.
Number eight, fight them off using a water pistol.
Well, I got two words for you, buddy.
Good luck.
- Oh, you could do this though,
if their knife is made out of paper mache.
- Or if it's hot water.
- Yeah, if they have World's Sharpest Paper Mache Knife
from those videos that guy makes
where he sharpens like a B until it turns into a big knife.
I love those videos.
- Those are awesome, dude. - Oh man, those are the best.
- World's Sharpest Dog Shit Knife.
- Yeah.
- It's just two hours of a guy.
- He's melting it down on his stove.
- Melting dog shit, putting it in a mold.
- He's just stirring it with his finger the whole time.
- Trigger Trash Kid's got a bit of a clap back.
He says, "I'd rather use a .45 Defender."
Whoa, true to his name.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Fuck, I don't want to get in a fight with him.
Right?
He has guns, dude.
Fuck it up.
Siri, O-P, Siri says, "Someone tried to rob a bank like this."
Wait, Siri wrote this list?
Yeah, C-Y-R-I.
Siri from Apple?
Cy-R-I.
Sorry.
Cyri said that someone tried to rob a bank by defending
Themself with a water pistol
Rob a bank by defending themselves, uh-huh
Yeah, luckily the bank. Yeah, all the tellers were witches
rubbing
Robbing the bank and saying this is in self-defense. Yeah. Yeah, your honor. It was a self-defense bank robbery
They were trying to make me do it.
Yeah, they were trying to not give me money and I had to defend myself.
They're trying to not give me money to death and I had to defend myself with my gun.
I had no choice.
Number 10 slapped their butt.
Yeah, one of my basketball coach, one of my Caleb's basketball coach at Halo Hoops at
Myrtle Grove Christian School in 2006.
No.
No
That's the answer no
Someone says him and I we're gonna date after we're engaged Wow the D smile that's from oh, woo woo. Oh
Mom sweet. Oh, it's gonna have the ending. Yeah
And then you get into the contenders. This is when this is when you get the real gold on these lists, man
You get stuff like number 12 flick their nipple. Oh
Oh fuck yes.
Yeah.
They gotta have, I mean, to do that from a safe distance, they gotta have one extendo
nipple on them.
Yeah.
You know, just a long hard nipple.
One big noodle coming out.
Yeah, one big pink noodle.
Have you guys seen that picture of that dude that is like 40 years old and he's used like
a nipple pump.
He's got such erect nipples and he's like too much long.
Oh my god.
Yes.
I think I've seen it.
The guy with the cigar.
- He's got a very, like a real faint grin,
but like it's a grin of satisfaction.
Like he's very proud of himself.
- Well he does that, you know, he does it for him.
I would love to have--
- Jamie, get the nipple pump.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Joe Rogan is one inch tall,
but he puts himself in a nipple pump every morning,
and that's why he's so red and big now.
- He's nipple pumped himself up,
and he takes all those, like, he smokes DMT
so he can see people normal but yeah I smoke CMT the channel yeah yeah
no not Caleb's Me Tiny that doesn't make any sense dude I'm smoking BMT dude no
Caleb's Caleb's Mary time you didn't think about that did you think I'd have
something perfect Mary time yeah that's when you dress up like Mary from fucking
you do with your boyfriend's dudes. You all dress up as your favorite hobbits and you guys run around.
Our favorite hobbits? There's like four. There's enough hobbits. You guys could do the seven
dwarves but do 14 dwarves instead so you can have double the dwarves. And Caleb plays Snow White.
I would probably play the guy in the movie. No. You play the wit dude. You'd be dopey because
'cause you got his dumb ass ears.
- No, I don't, my ears are normal and not huge
and they don't stick out of the side of my head.
No, I would play probably the guy
or the hot version of the witch.
- You'd play the poison apple
'cause your head is perfectly round and red.
(laughing)
- No, no.
If I did play the dwarves,
I would be in this situation of them all stacked up
in a trench coat because I'm so tall.
I could never play a single dwarf.
You can play all the dwarfs.
With like the most handsome dwarf at the top.
Uh...
Which one is the most handsome?
Me.
So you are a dwarf.
No. Which... sexy.
Yeah, so you've admitted.
We got him again.
No.
You don't have me.
I do.
No, back to the contenders.
Politely ask for them to put down the weapon.
Yeah.
That might work actually.
Tricky trash kid just says, "Thanks for the advice."
[laughter]
Nice.
Number 15's not like a bad option, actually.
Yeah. Scream.
Yeah, just yell.
But then somebody says, "It's rude to scream at people."
[laughter]
That's a good point.
I was about to be murdered.
I was about to be murdered but thank god I didn't scream otherwise I'd be so fucking rude.
Yeah.
I'm gonna skip ahead number 20 here.
Threaten to tell on them if they shoot.
Okay, you know, um, I just can't in good conscience endorse this one.
I mean, telling, tattletailing is one of the, I mean, I would rather die before I tell on somebody.
Yeah.
I feel that, I really do.
What if he gets grounded?
What if he goes to detention? Yeah, what if he gets detention?
You know, or they take his toys away. His toy pistol. I feel like I can't,
I would have to, yeah, agree with Caleb on
this because I have a past of snitching and I'm
trying to move past that. When I was in fifth grade, I was
sitting at a table with this girl and this is right around
the time when Justin Timberlake's sexy back came out and
And she was singing it to herself and I heard her under her breath say the line, "Those
motherfuckers don't know how to act."
And I remember I looked at her and I was like, "Are you serious?"
And I told the teacher.
And she got detention, lunch detention that day where you had to walk the perimeter of
this big oak tree.
I was like, "Detention?"
Everyone got in a line that had detention and had to walk the perimeter of the oak tree
for the entire duration of recess.
And I remember she came back, she came and she sat back at the table and I remember she
looked at me and it was just this genuine question of like, "Why did you do that?
Like why'd you tell on me?"
And I felt bad after that.
I've never snitched on anyone since.
You are never invited on this podcast ever again.
Y'all, y'all, I know, I know, that makes me sound like a little piece of shit but I
was fifth grade, I changed after that and I remember being out on the playground and
seeing her walk the perimeter of the tree and I remember I was like, "Fuck, shit."
- That sounds like a medieval torture method.
That's like, just making some--
- Since then, Matt has been witness to over 30 murders,
but he won't speak up.
(laughing)
- Can't go to the police.
- No, listen, I have principles.
I used to be a tattletale too.
One time I tattletaled on myself, because--
- I did that shit all the time.
I saw porn by accident and I told my mom.
(laughing)
- By accident.
One of my most impressive tattletales was I was watching My Bloody Valentine 3D.
Oh yeah.
And then it was right when I can't, it was like this shitty remake of like some slasher
movie.
2009.
Yeah, 2009.
And I was at my friend's house and we were watching it.
We rented it while his mom was out of, was like at work or whatever.
On a bender.
She was on a bender, probably.
there's a there's a section with nudity and I got up and I stood in front of the
TV like did like a superhero pose and I was like guys I'm not sure we should be
watching this movie and they were like okay like if you're gonna be weird about
it like we don't have to watch it and I was like yeah what's your mom's phone
number and I was like yeah miss we were watching a movie with breasts in it but
yeah we turned it off and she was like okay I'm at work at Waffle House like I
I don't care.
Dude.
I did that the first time I ever smoked weed.
Oh my god, you self told?
Yeah, okay, here's the worst part about this story.
I was a senior in high school.
Whoa.
And I used to have, okay, so no, but there's context.
I had a form of OCD where I like would feel hyper guilty if I like did anything like bad
And I was a huge Christian when I was in high school.
And I was like, "Shit, smoking weed is like,
"it's a high sin, punishable by like going to hell."
And my friend came over with a fat bowl
and went on my back porch, my parents were in a home.
And I was like, "Are you gonna smoke that?"
And he's like, "Yeah, dude."
And he lit up this bowl and he took a fat rip
and he passed it to me.
He was with a girl I kinda had a crush on too.
And I was like, "Okay."
And I took a rip of the bowl and then they left
and I called my mom and I was like,
"Mom, I just smoked marijuana."
*laughter*
My mom was like, "Okay."
And she's like, "Hell yeah!"
"Hell yeah, playa!"
"My son's finally cool. I thought you were a poser."
"Finally I can have sex with you, son. You're finally kind enough for me to fuck."
That was going on plenty before that, 'cause the marijuana had nothing to do with the first appreciation.
Yeah, you said you were super Christian.
Yeah, I've been there.
close family.
The first time I ever smoked weed, I just ate a whole jar of peanut butter.
I was like 14 and there was a brand new jar of peanut butter and I was so freaked out
that I was like, I think eating, I think I read somewhere that eating helps you not be
high anymore.
So I ate a jar of peanut butter and then my brother was like, he was like, "Did you just
eat my whole jar of peanut butter?"
He was so mad and I had to explain to him, I mean he was like, he smoked weed every second
in the day and I'd be like, no, you don't understand I'm high.
And he's like, who cares?
And then I watched the Avengers.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, dude.
I was still out in theaters.
And I remember I was at the,
while I was at the movie theater,
I spilled my giant Pepsi all over the place.
And I just, I just left it.
I just didn't even try to get another one
and tell anybody just like while walking into the theater,
I just like spilled it in the lobby
and then just went into the movie.
I was like,
Oh, it was like in the lobby on the floor.
the lot I had I had literally just filled up a 64 ounce and then I walked and I
just like it just dropped out of my hands like I just forgot to hold it and
meanwhile meanwhile and pick up a Nash is going to going to see her first movie
since the incident because she can't see she slips in this giant yeah her also
dropping a Pepsi because she's like oh I forgot I don't know oh man this is just
It's a Sharla Nash themed episode now.
Really, we should have found a Sharla Nash list.
I think that was enough.
Funniest Sharla Nash.
Sharla Nash themed.
I gotta pee real bad.
I'll be back.
We're almost done, Patrick.
What are you doing?
Just sit down.
Dude, I gotta pee so bad.
You can hold it.
I cannot hold it, dude.
Let's just make fun of Patrick when he's gone.
Alright, fine.
You can make fun of me all you want.
I got some things to say.
Alright, say them.
Go ahead.
Talk your shit, man.
Does he have a hairless cat?
He has two of them.
Yeah, dude, fucking believe me.
Now I know what type of person Patrick is now.
Yeah, a rich person.
Those things cost like, what, $50,000 each?
Yeah, fucking expensive, dude.
I know.
And they're named Fucker and Yoda.
Really?
Yeah.
Those are the names.
Goddamn it, sorry.
I just got a Twitter notification from Pete Buttigieg.
Oh no.
I have an alt Twitter account that my friend and I use to follow fart fetish Twitter accounts.
Nice.
Because we kind of went down a rabbit hole one day and found all these fantastic ones
so we created a Pete Buttigieg fart roleplay account.
I followed him on the account while he was still in the race and I'm not even signed
into this account anymore but for some reason every time Pete tweets I get a notification
on my phone and it's so god damn annoying and I don't know how to make it stop because I'm
not even signed into the account.
Damn, that's uh he's getting revenge on you.
Yeah, it's nice though because at least once a day I can have a little moment of inspiration
when I can see a tweet from Pete Boothrow.
Yeah, Matt, we should mention Matt is wearing a t-shirt that says "Boot Edge Edge" long
after he dropped out.
He's still repping the man.
And I got a "Gays for Pete" sticker on my car.
Yeah, and a straights for P1.
Just keep in all the, all bases covered.
Um, alright, we read patrons?
Oh yeah, we have some patrons to read, Matt.
You can either stick around or you can fuck off, it's up to you.
Yeah, I'll stick around, man.
I love patrons.
Why don't we just do it after?
Because he's already here.
We already said yes, we already tricked him.
You want me to leave Patrick?
No, I'm just saying, I don't want to...
Patrick, you just left to take a pee, you don't have any opinion.
Whenever you leave the microphone you lose all the say you have in any decision.
It's just disgusting ball sack looking cats.
Yeah that's right.
No.
Yeah they're all balls.
Here's my, here's my, let's make fun of Patrick more.
Here's a Patrick story.
Okay.
This is Patrick telling a story.
You know the other day I was looking at my cats rolling around on their beds and it reminded
me of in high school I printed out a picture of a skateboard.
Fucking beasted on them dude.
Fucking gone. That is not what I sound my man. I'm a sicko mode on Patrick. Yeah, dude. You just went you just that's the cipher right?
There yeah, just you just hopped in the cipher and spit bars. I mean sometimes you have to take him down a machine gun
Kelly them dude
Yeah, I was thinking the other day about how funny it is that a guy was just like man fuck
What's my rap name be?
How about machine gun?
(laughter)
- Machine gun Kelly.
- There was probably like a few iterations before that.
- Yeah.
- Kelly.
- Kelly the Rapper.
- First he tried Kelly and people were like,
that's not tough enough.
- Normal gun Kelly.
- I need a tougher name than Kelly.
What if I just add machine gun to the front?
- Knife Kelly.
- My first name is Kelly.
- Yeah, yeah.
Bomb Kelly.
(laughing)
- Napalm Kelly.
- That one's, Napalm Kelly's way better.
That's like, that sounds way cooler than Machine Gun Kelly.
- Like he wanted to go with it,
but his grandfather fought in the Vietnam War
and suffers from extreme PTSD.
- Yeah, Agent Orange Kelly.
- MK Ultra Kelly, see that sounds cool.
- MK Ultra Kelly's way cooler.
- Vietnam Kelly.
- Vietnamese Kelly.
- Viet Cong Kelly.
Mr. Vietcong.
Yeah, I might as well go for it.
Just VC Kelly.
Vietnamese, that's it.
No name, just...
Vietnamese is the rapper.
Hold up, it's Lil' Vietnam.
It's Lil' Vietnam.
Go ahead and spit, Matt.
Lil' Vietnam, go for it.
Let's hear that shit.
It's Lil' Vietcong up in the house.
Oh shit.
Yo, I feel like I should stick around for Patreon though because I haven't posted on Patreon
in like a month and I feel really bad about that.
So, this might in some universe make it to the top.
I don't know.
I feel like I should stick around for Patreon though because I haven't posted on Patreon
in like a month and I feel really bad about that.
So, this might in some universe make it to the top.
Yo, I feel like I should stick around for Patreon though because I haven't posted on Patreon
in like a month and I feel really bad about that.
So maybe this might in some universe make up for that.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, alright.
Thank you, Jem Apru.
Thank you, Mitchell Jump.
That's a cool name.
Mitchell Jump?
Like Mario's Jump?
Like Mario's Jump.
Just like Mario's Jump.
Nile, thank you.
It's from One Direction.
I don't think it's him.
I think it's from One Direction.
direction. Thank you Kaibu Zetta. Thank you Cameron. This is not me. That's yeah
Cameron bought it his own patron. That's not me. He did dude. Anything to bump up
those numbers. That's right yeah. Thank you Chast and Grinchpilled or Chast.
Chast and Grinchpilled. Ben Snape. Let me tell you what we don't take too kindly to Snape's
around here buddy. Yeah that's a teacher right there. But we take kindly to you. Yeah. Kevin McHugh.
Thank you. Thank you, Kevin. Brandon Cooley. What a cool name.
Coolest name in the world. Brandon Cooley. Jack Richards, thank you. Dylan Chichowski.
Dylan Wachowski. Dylan Wachowski, one of the sisters. Jim Ziegler.
Thank you, Jim Ziegler. Daniel Pollen. Daniel Pollen. Pollen out, baby.
Wow, Ben.
Hell yeah.
Ben Contillo went up to $45 to see Patrick in a dress.
And Pat still hasn't done it, but we're getting there.
I'm looking for a dress that fits me.
Matt, we're making Patrick wear a dress for the Patreon
once we hit a thousand.
I saw, I saw.
Oh, you saw?
Well, you're gonna see, you should see.
I'll send you, you don't have to subscribe,
I'll send you the picture when it takes it.
No, I'm doing it right now, I'm subscribing right now.
Oh my God, we have to call him out too.
Also, I'm about, wait, I'm gonna subscribe
before you guys finish so I can uh okay let's go fast. Jesse Huisken. Thank you Jesse Huisken.
Alex. Thanks. Bill Amen. Thank you. Bill Amen. Finn Boner. Finn Boner. Nice. Damn that's
a good name. That's absolutely well owned. Jack Boyer. That's $10. Thank you. Master
Chief level. Maxwell Bomback. That's Noah Bomback's brother and cousin. His brother and
cousin but del Lally Barrett bald Ellie thank you Barrett bald Ellie work
Linton
that's
Connor Privet thank you movie from the movie Egypt from the Ryan Skelly from my
nightmare he's a skeleton Luke from the Bible Luke from Skywalker slime farm
farmer thank you okay Zach thanks nice pulled over in the Gundam it's pretty
cool Matthew and Ryan hard thank you Matthew
Dominique thank you Dominique yeah and Patricia
- Yeah, Trayvon Fartin, that's disrespectful.
We don't like that name.
- Yeah, we don't condone that one.
- Thank you for the money.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Jeffrey Pignona.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for saying that that way.
- Silas Jordan.
- Jeff, you Pignona?
- Connor Boyd.
- Yeah, Bailey F.
- Bailey F., thank you.
- Thank you, uh, thank you, Lucas.
- Lucas, but thank you, Lucas, just barely.
- Yeah, it's a $1 paycheck.
- Just, you know.
- You get a thank, but no you.
- Earlier this week, I realized that if you subscribe
for $1, you could still get everything.
(laughs)
But I fixed it.
- Did we fix that?
- Yeah, so people who are gaming the system,
I'm on to you now.
- I got the Patrick pricing.
- Oh my God.
- Whoa.
- Wait, thank God, because Ben Contio,
the guy who had the $45, just edited it back to $5,
- First, 'cause we already hit 1,000.
So, huge thank you to Super Vega.
- Wow, Super Vega. - Absolutely.
- But we still got more.
We missed something. - Oh, Corgimatic.
- No, Black Coolman. - Black Coolmatic,
thank you. - Black Coolman
went up to $25.01.
- Whoa. - Whoa.
- And I think Black Coolman was maybe our first patron ever.
- Black Coolman was our first patron.
- That's true.
- Shout out, special shout out to Black Coolman.
Change your name, but--
(laughing)
What's up, it's Black Coolman.
Oh, we have him here, Black.
So thank you so much, Black.
It's so nice to personally give you our appreciation.
Can you say one more thing?
(laughing)
Can you say it with your voice?
I'm actually, I'm regretting that one a little bit now.
So I think I'm gonna pass on the Black voice.
No, that was the cool man voice.
I thought you were really leaning harder
into the cool man part.
Yeah, that was the cool voice.
Nah, it was a cool voice.
It wasn't even initially charged.
- All right, and that's it.
Matt, thank you for coming on, man.
- Thank you so much. - Shout out to Super Mega.
Watch Super Mega.
Let's get that average age on Super Mega up to 14 1/2.
- Yeah! (laughing)
- Let's boost those numbers.
- Let's raise it up, guys.
Let's get it up there.
- All right. - All right.
- Thank you guys for having me.
- Of course. - Yeah, of course.
- Thank you for coming on. - Anytime.