come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
you can't
i already ruined it all
uh...
we have to start the whole show over episode one i really entire episode
arteries are two hundred episode already fucking ruined this is the worst
episode we've ever done all my god don't say that
Okay, this is the worst episode right now.
This may be our fifth time trying to record this.
Yep, and it's complete shit already.
It's already shit.
It's absolute dog shit.
Guys, we-
Wait, that's-
Absolute dog shit.
That's something.
Keep going.
That's something right there, yeah.
I, this is how I talk.
I say absolute dog shit.
That's really good.
That could be something.
I got diagnosed with cancer.
I got fucking cancer.
I have cancer. Yeah, that's like a good bit.
Cancer? You really have cancer?
Yeah, oh yes. Bowel cancer.
Bowel cancer?
It's funny because they sound like the same bowl.
Bowl, yeah.
What is that? Australian? Those guys are upside-
They got everything upside down.
I don't think that was an Australian accent.
That was closer to a Russian, Turkish kind of...
Alright.
This is the 200th episode. We're really excited to be a part of this.
this it's great I'm here with you I know absolutely it's nice there were some
there were some hiccups you know as people may remember last week our
corporate sponsors stepped in and kind of did some stuff to our morning
that we were all fuckers listen and I'm completely into the Bible so I saw that
it was Adam and Eve they made us do a bunch of disgusting porn content I had
single thing what kind of this what kind of God made any money from a theist
they leftist Democrat would make an a sex store yeah and call it Adam and Eve
after the two most biblical fucking people of all that is so sexually wrong
it's actually completely just off the rails yeah you know yeah I mean nowadays
a store like Adam and Eve they'd they'd probably want to call it Adam and Steve
Steve or even Madame and Steve, a completely different couple who are
Satanists. Exactly, yeah, a kind of a Wario style reverse world of Adam and
Eve, Madame and Steve. It should be really scary, because Madame is the most
common name for a woman in France. Yeah, it's about as common as Adam is for
men, is Madame. Well, Adam in Turkish means guy.
I think Adam just means guy in every language. Yeah, it does. Yeah. No, like
the direct translation, it's probably like a nom or something, but
word Adam is just isn't that the same in like Hebrew - I think he was a man what
the word is man well they got French guys named gee you know there's guys have
you ever met a guy named guy yeah it's like what's going on no gee you know
there's some guys who are guys yeah I know but gee gee Liz you just want to
bring something up right now yeah most extreme Chinese what is that remember
that show no oh you never saw that most extra oh that was what that stood for
for no it's not we've had this conversation wait a minute yeah roll the
clip
because we've had this actual conversation we've had that same conversation mean
most extreme that's what you thought that's what it was
nope all right find what it look fine what it says we don't I don't think we
I don't think we have that close.
I can't believe that.
I can't believe we've had the same fucking conversation.
I mean, I corrected myself once and then never corrected it again.
Wow.
It probably stands for competition that last one.
Yeah, yeah. It's probably like...
Most extreme one.
The premise of the show is on Spike TV and the premise of the show is that it was like a Japanese game show or something that they overdubbed.
Yeah, no, I know the show.
Yeah.
You knew it!
I had stopped calling that.
Well, you said, you said, "From Most Extreme Chinese," and I know the show you're talking
about, but why the fuck would I... that's not the name.
Why the fuck would I...
What was it called?
Most Extreme...
I think it was like M3C or something.
Why have we... we've had this exact conversation.
Most Extreme Chinese.
Look it up.
Don't look up Most Extreme Chinese, though.
No, I'm going to look up most extreme Chinese. I'm curious. Nobody's gonna know
what most extreme elimination.
My yeah, because I remember my brother's friend told me it was most extreme.
I was your brother's friend. Yeah, it wasn't just you being a racist child
racist child at 24. He's a racist child.
Oh my God. Holy if you go.
I googled most extreme Chinese. The show comes really. Yeah.
the top result in a common room most extreme elimination challenge. Oh wow
yeah but listen we're 200 episodes in uh-huh we don't have the same
conversation. We don't like to rehash stuff. Yeah we don't like looking back
right we want to look forward. Yeah, how are you guys gonna... I guess today we
don't. I guess we're kind of looking back a little bit today though. Yeah yeah I
guess we are kind of gonna. I guess we're doing exactly that. Do a journey through the
history of the podcast. Maybe a little bit of a... You have your favorite moments, we
have our favorite moments. They're completely different. You guys have
horrible taste. You have terrible taste. Oh yeah, all these clips you guys are making,
not even the choice cuts. First of all, where are the animatics?
So let me show you, let's show you how it's actually done. Where are the animatics? Where are the animaniacs?
Where are the cool clips where like I'm saying something awesome? Exactly, yeah.
Where is like, "Patrick says coolest skateboard trick name." Where are the clips where
one of us is actually right about something? Yeah. And it just,
We're just a correct fact.
Or like three guys act like friends.
And what about our singing compilation?
Where is that?
Where's the singing compilation?
We sing so much.
I know, we sing all the time, you know?
Just amazing clips.
I mean, let's do some--
Where's the video of every time we say the word swag?
Yep.
I would like to see that.
That'd be awesome.
But let's go ahead and let's--
we're basically doing a clip show today.
We are going to do a clip show.
These are the actual good clips.
Yeah.
A little reminiscing.
The ones that we remember.
But guys, do you remember when Patrick showed up in a dress?
This is just something I'm wearing now.
Why are you wearing that?
What are you doing?
It's like a young thug thing.
Why is it?
It's not a young thug dress.
It's pink.
It also doesn't even cover your penis and your balls.
It was a blue dress.
It was a blue dress and it was a boy's shoe.
That was a masculine dress.
Let's be real.
Yeah, because it was blue.
That was a dress.
You know what a real, you want to talk about a masculine dress, Lady Gaga meat dress.
Oh my God.
Now that's a good story.
First of all, why did you come in in that?
I don't know. I don't have the money to buy all that meat.
Where'd you get this?
Why would I fucking...
Okay. I saw this at the store.
Which store?
Uh, the L Train Vintage.
You bought that at L Train... you bought that at a vintage store?
Yes.
What are the brown stains...
It was only...
Pat, what are the brown stains on the back of it?
It was only six dollars.
Pat, I'm 90% sure that's a pillowcase.
And it was only six dollars and I turned it into a dress. Why is this...
It's a pillowcase with poop stains on the back of it.
As if someone was already wearing it like a dress, and then they pooped into it.
And you bought that.
It's like somebody was- And came to work in it.
But it's only six dollars.
It's fucking- Oh my god, it smells like complete fucking shit.
You just shifted your leg and the smell of shit just wafted over here.
Wait, that's not from the dress, it came from your legs.
Did you shit your own dress?
It's running down your leg onto the floor.
It's running- I think- No, no, this is part of the dress.
- That's not part - It's covering your entire body.
- Yeah.
- That's kind of impressive actually.
Who designed that?
- Jeffrey Tambor.
- See like moments like that, like that was,
I mean that was as fun as a moment can possibly be.
- Yeah, that was in the dark 31 or whatever.
- Yeah.
- I mean and that's one that you guys have never heard.
- The thing about that one too is you know,
I know a lot of people, they say we're too harsh on Pat,
we're too mean to him, and that one,
you know you can kind of hear it in that.
We're being a little mean.
There have been times when we when you know Pat was was um was kind of the shining star and really stood out
Do you guys remember when when Patrick won an award?
Fuck you, man. Fuckin idiot. Fuck you. And anybody but you deserve that shit. You are such a fucking idiot, man.
Dude, that award smells like fucking shit. It's like you fucking shit your pants. There's a brown stain on your award.
There's brown shit dripping down your award.
I have COVID
Yeah, that was the day. I don't know if you guys remember I was patient zero in the States for Kovu
I think that was in like 2018. Yeah. Yeah, and we're trying to do what Cove it was. Yeah, and we yeah
Well, that was that was the only that's the thing about it was I got I
Did like a trial?
Mm-hmm for from like a scientist college a science college a science college in Boston. Okay members
Yeah, who can remember MIT think yeah, and I
You know that was my that was my award I got to kovat 19, that's a pretty cool and then you went to Santa Con
Yes, yeah, yeah, it was tough. Well. I went to Santa Con 2018, but I also did get kovat from Santa Con 2020
I mean you can actually 21 it's pretty easy
I got kovat pretty much every time that there was a Santa Con
I mean Santa comes fucking crazy you guys bringing up Santa Conor but just
reminded me of something that we did on the show before the episode where we met
Santa oh my god
Santa Santa do the head spin do a head spin
Yeah! He's doing the head spin!
Woah, woah, woah
Santa you sound exactly like talking Ben
Yes
I wish Caleb would get out of the bathroom to see this
Oh my god, well Caleb was not, was Caleb naughty or nice this year?
Guys I'm coming back from the bathroom
You better hurry up Caleb, Santa's right here
No
Oh my god Santa just where the fuck is Santa you went up the chimney. Yeah, okay
This is officially the day I stopped believing in Santa Claus
Yeah, that's the day say Caleb stopped believing in Santa. I don't really like relitigating stuff like that
Yeah, I like that was honestly one of the worst days my fucking life
Yeah, you did we were crying a lot yep, and there was white hairs all over the floor
You try to get the hairs DNA tested to prove to us that that wasn't a real Santa
But I tried to get 100% completely Santa yeah every time that you would send the hairs to 23andme
They would send you back just a candy cane. I tried fucking that's like
Didn't work
Yeah, yeah, it's a promotion 23andme has though if you get one of Santa's beard hairs
You can send to them for it is it's so embarrassing when people wear a black shirt on on Christmas morning
You can see the Santa hair all over it. Absolutely a little bit. Yeah. Yeah, he got on your lap while you were asleep
asleep. He doesn't have some foresight where white can you imagine being
allergic to Santa hair how fucking brutal that must be or the I mean I
don't dander as much where I hear the hairless Santa's actually really yeah,
they have a lot of dander speaking of dander yeah remember that episode with
her guest.
Jeff dander
oh yeah, Jeff dander yeah, let's roll that clip. Yeah, let's play that
hey Jeff.
Hey, thank you for coming on Jeff. How are you doing pretty good? Oh, you are
And so why are you here and what do you do and who are you?
I'm Jeff Danner. I'm from that store.
You're from where? The store or next door? The next store.
I'm from your neighbor next door. Okay, and we had you on why?
So it was you guys, you were
recording and I walked in and told you to keep it down. And then we just
kind of waved you in? I remember that now. I had completely
forgotten guys put a microphone in my hand uh-huh and here you are Jeff I mean
you're so far one of the worst guests we've ever had I mean you're completely
useless here to complain about you guys and then I don't know what happened you
guys made me fucking sit down here and start recording what even is this show
called Jeff this interview seems like it's going almost nowhere yeah I mean
who are your guys who are my guys yeah who are your guys like your guys like
your guy yeah he's yep that's a big one for me I'm starting to like you Jeff
hmm Kyle Dander I'm kind of culture which you don't know Kyle Dander as my
nephew oh you know Kyle Dander you who else you got two more guys right out the
list Ethan Dender Ethan Dender Ethan Dender okay is that like a different
family or is it a little silent kind of okay gotcha okay just similar name is the
the same same last name is your stepson because I adopted him after his father
died
and he you changed his last name and his and and I guess my fifth guy is his
father. That's very sweet Rico dander. His father had the same last name as you
to Jeff. Yeah, it was my brother, his father.
All right, Jeff, this this actually just became one of the best interviews.
That also he's also your nephews, your stepson and nephew, so
'Cause you said that Kyle Dander's your nephew and Ethan Dander's your stepson, but he's also your brother's son.
Different brother.
*knock knock knock*
Police, open up!
Oh shit.
That's my other brother.
Don't open the door.
That's my other brother, I go up to the door.
Yo, we don't play that with cops!
Keith Dander, that's my other brother, he's a cop.
Wait, you don't fuck with cops like that?
We don't fuck with cops like that.
Well then, I guess I'll leave.
A-C-A-B.
Alright, I'm leaving.
All cops are bad, motherfucker!
That's fine, I'll just go.
Yeah, that had a crazy ending.
that was one of the craziest days of that was I didn't realize that you could
just tell cops. I don't I don't know if you like that you yeah and they're like
oh shit. I don't I didn't even know that that must be one of the episodes you
guys did before I was a guest or yeah might have been when I was still a guest
on the show and not a host. Yeah, yeah, I don't remember under what was his name
fucking Jeff Dander Jeff Dander. Yeah, yeah, really great name. Obviously his
parents. I was coming up with that name. Yeah, yeah, it's impossible to come up
up with that on a spot yeah. Do you guys remember that episode we recorded
underwater
actually talk pretty normal underwater
pretty good thing to have is a good skill set. I can talk underwater. I
think I might have been part atlantean another life.
Are you okay Cameron? Are you okay?
*gurgling*
Is he okay? Can you check on him?
Oh god!
Oh he's drown- OH SHIT!
HE'S FUCKING DROWNING!
I don't know why we thought it would be a good idea
to record an episode underwater
I have gills
I completely have gills
and I can talk and
I had a near death experience and I saw
a guy
Yeah well he was a scuba diver
rescued your life. Yeah. Saved your... rescued you. That guy was weird though, the
scuba diver. Yeah. We did that interview with him afterwards. It didn't make any
fucking sense. Yeah.
Hey, how's it going? I'm a scuba diver.
Can you back up off the mic a little dude? That's my bad man. It's just how you know,
just breathing a little heavy. All right, scuba diver.
all right how's it going hey what's up wait wait talk again what's up wait take
that take that scuba mask off yeah how you doing oh my oh my fucking god
dander bro what the fuck are you doing here uh I scuba you scoop well I guess
you didn't really learn anything about you last time so this is good we get a
chance actually talk yeah what would you rescue Cameron I saw a person in trouble
and you just always take care of it you're a good guy like that I'm a good guy
oh I already have your suit on or I've not done anything wrong ever open up it's
the police you have somebody who's done something wrong in there yo get the
fuck out of here motherfucking pig oh my god that was so rude that I'm gonna
leave who is this guy the scuba gear that's Jeff Dander I'm just and yeah
come on you know Jeff oh you weren't here when we first met Jeff okay here
okay listen you two just have a conversation together a little bit get to
know each other hey so who are your guys Jeff now they already asked me that yeah
we already asked that yes okay what's your favorite ice cream I'm allergic to
ice cream I'm allergic all milk we covered that - it wasn't in it was a very
first question I asked me I was allergic to milk all right um do you what do you
play like Patrick what you have shit dripping down your fucking leg the fuck
is going on with you yeah what do you mean again yes I'm not wearing the dress
this time so that must be actual shit yeah that was that was a serious
scooby-doo moment unmasking that scuba scuba do my God ever yeah let's do a
a dweiber a dweiber yeah yeah
taxi dweiber. What ever happened to the Jeff Dander guy?
I think he was a, I think if I remember correctly he was a pedophile
Jeff Dander was a convicted pedophile. I think, well I think they were trying to convict him
that's why the cops kept shooting him. Yeah and we unwittingly were kind of harboring him
and that's why we had to do that episode from jail.
Alright guys so you all gotta walk up to the biggest
guy in the entire jail and you gotta punch him directly in the face.
on the face camera come here I heard you're supposed to go to the come here
camera clear what dude I'm following the rules for orange or black out fuck
well I'm just trying to follow the rules I got you both myself I thought I was
the biggest guy you know you're not the biggest guy okay I'm the biggest guy oh
fuck guys why are we hitting each other the biggest guy is clearly the Hulk all
right we got to find the Hulk the green Hulk he's literally right across the
hall okay we're Patrick go punch the Hulk right now that's what you're supposed
to do in prison you're supposed to find the greenest Hulk and punch them and
he's dead remember the craziest part about that clip is that you killed the
Hulk with a single punch yeah that was crazy I've never seen hit him right on
the button you ever seen that documentary that I was in jail for a
reason I heard the the Hulk was in jail for a bad reason - yeah yeah I'm guessing
I was in jail because I have a very hard punch.
I think the Hulk was in jail for that.
I can punch pretty much anybody and they'll die immediately.
Did you ever see that video where the Hulk he fucks Black Widow?
Roll the clip.
(upbeat music)
(grunting)
(screaming)
- Gamma wave!
(grunting)
Gamma crush!
Smash you!
- Yeah, and then she died from that, actually.
- She dies from his big hole penis?
- It's gamma radiation.
- Okay, does the Hulk have a normal dick?
- Why, what is, why does he need--
- Does his dick grow with him,
or does his dick stay the same?
ears get bigger also why is he's here's what if his penis does grow what's the
reason here's what here's what I'll say I think that his penis stays small
because otherwise they would not put that much effort into finding completely
indestructible shorts that's true if he had a big giant penis he would be
flaunting let it fly but also yeah probably not these rescuing kids and
stuff that's a good point that's why the Hulk was in jail the Hulk's a bad guy
right am I stupid the Hulk is a green guy he's a green Lee big bad league guy
yeah bad to be green you guys remember that episode we did when we all turned
green I feel very bad oh my god we're all seriously green I'm trying to speak
like an alien green I just it just doesn't feel you don't look very good
green well that's not an alien - yep we earned yep we ate green berries yes we
Green
Green berries
Audience
They don't need to know it's an audio. I'm completely green from all the green berries. I feel too green
I'm not liking the amount of green. Okay. Let's all eat white berries
Yeah, and then we discovered that white berries turn you white yeah, yeah, yeah, I just ate a blackberry
Okay, that's a normal berry. It doesn't do anything to you.
Yeah, it didn't do anything to me.
I was just hungry.
What's your favorite berry?
Strawberry for me.
Really? Strawberry number one.
I've never even seen a boysenberry.
I've only seen the boysenberry syrup at IHOP.
Yeah, that's good.
It's the only time I've ever had a boysenberry.
I think the boysenberries and blackberries
may be the same.
That's not true.
Boysenberry is like a crossbreed, I think.
think of really different berries. I think I could be thinking of a
different berry. Actually, I'm looking up boys and berry boys and it's a cross
between a blackberry and a dewberry and a loganberry. Oh, is it actually
red? Yeah, red boys and berry. Yeah, it's like a boys and colors just like
our it just looks like a blackberry. Yeah, it's like a mixture. Oh, but it
was named after rudolph boysen. What's a mixture a mixture of berry
it raspberry and blackberry you just said oh wow okay so the blackberry dewberry
and what's a dewberry so the okay part of a boysenberry dewberry so the route
Rudolph boysen obtained the dewberry loganberry parent from the farm of farm
of John Loving parent and then George Darrow of the USDA began tracking down
reports of a large reddish purple berry reports on poison spawn it to track down
reports of a berry yeah like Bigfoot and then Darrow enlisted the help of
just an example any guy coming back speaking of Walter not very Walter not
Walter not owner of knots berry farm swallowing of which remember that
episode when we went to knots berry farm
okay the line is not that fun guys but it's not as bad as I was making it out
to be either. Yeah, I don't know any of these rides names. Me neither. I've never
been. This is my first time here. What it's a there's I see roller coasters.
Yes, you do see roller coasters. I see do I see characters? Yes, you see walk around
peanuts characters. Charlie Brown. Okay. I wonder why it's called Knot's Berry Farm.
I wonder what who this Knot guy is. One day I hope to find out. Me too. But yeah
That was such a fun trip. We did that, we did Disney, we did Universal, all in like
kind of one fell swoop, you know. Yeah. We need to go on more trips. Oh my God.
Do you remember that trip we went on to... No. Yeah, me neither. To which, to where?
Come on. The moon. I don't remember that. I don't think we went to the moon. Yeah, I
don't think we did either. But we did go to medieval ages Europe. That was a medieval
times in a time machine. No, no, you're thinking of a different time.
You were confused then too. I do remember that. Remember when Patrick was
confused? Yeah. Is this medieval times the restaurant? It is. No,
it's medieval times the times. Listen, we need to go find, I think,
a witch. Is that what we try to find? All I know, all I remember
is that we got in this time machine, we got out, and a guy
with a funny haircut ran away with it. I'm kind of liking being
peasant though. Yeah the smell here is really nice. Right? Patrick... I could punch
anybody here and I won't get in trouble. I don't think that's true. I think that's even less
true than where we... Well you're onto something. And I won't get in trouble.
Let's think about what we remember about medieval times. I think you're supposed
to go up to the biggest guy in medieval times and punch him right in the face.
Yeah I heard that that's something that you can do. Patrick go punch that horse.
okay I don't think I don't think that helped anything yeah I don't think that
my news that's okay yeah that's fine kick my tooth there's no dentist in this
time we'll go to a with a fat lip to listen to me it sounds weird I can
completely hear the fat lip oh yeah Jesus Christ I I just had an idea
time travel, fat lip, let's write a hit song.
Somebody give me a lute.
Wait, I think I just had an incredible idea for a song guys.
Let's travel forward, oh I don't know, maybe
600 years, write a song, give it to
some weird looking guys, and then maybe we'll become
famous. Yeah, but that didn't work at all it turns out.
know it turns out they are no why we would thought it would work to give it
to other the other guys got famous and they already wrote this song before us
yeah because like that's who we got it from yeah you know like it was just
pretty stupid it will and it didn't make any time travels very confusing the
fact that we got the way that we got back from time travel it's just too
boring to even get into yeah right it's just a lot of yeah science remember how
boring it was
oh my god
shut up i'm just trying okay the red wire connects to the red wire
Yeah, my lips just got even bigger from the swelling.
The green wire connects to the green wire.
Hmm, what do I know about science?
The blue wire connects to the light blue wire.
Does anybody know anything about ice packs for my lip?
They haven't invented ice yet, you fucking idiot.
The yellow wire connects to the yellow wire.
Okay, now I have to type in the code.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one,
one,
two,
but yeah that was the wrong code. It turns out yeah, yeah, work it on to
three. Yeah, the easiest code ever yeah anyway. That was boring. It was really
boring, probably one of the most boring things that we ever did on on the show.
Yeah, are people going to be mad that we're doing a clip show people do tend
a bitch about clip shows, but I think it's I mean I think I feel like you know people
they post their own clips like we said they suck ass they're horrible yeah. We need to
set things straight you know yeah people these clips people are posting are not funny, but
we've had some serious funny moments that people don't even don't even care about and
it's like it's like to these people these moments never even happened. I know it's as
if they don't exist in the and on the podcast fucking unreal dude. I just feel like like
what was you guys's favorite funny bits that we did the funny bits like the really funny
stuff it's yeah like any bit where any bits you guys want to throw a clip of
yeah probably a Stevie the squirrel so wait with it the squirrels name Stevie
literally name Stevie. His name is Stevie.
How many dogs like this?
No!
That's awesome!
He's kind of got a third gangsta thing to him.
That's so awesome.
He's holding an acorn sideways.
Where my motherfucking nuts at?
A hat backwards?
Maybe not a hat because he's a squirrel.
They don't make a squirrel hat that small.
Oh my god his tree is in the...
His tree is backwards.
His tree has a...
Yo Stevie, Stevie!
His tree's a low-riding tree.
No!
That's funny as fuck, man.
That's like a bush.
He lives in a bush!
Yeah!
Oh my god, that's so fucking good.
Dude!
Oh my god, and he has tattoos all over his body.
Yeah, Stevie the Squirrel, that's gotta be one of our best.
Like, it's just like character shit.
I just like doing character shit like that.
No, I mean, I-
I'm like, completely like Paul F. Tompkins, Lorne Lapkus style.
One of my favorite clips that I feel like I haven't seen anybody post, one of the bits
that we did is was a McDonald's in the morning. I'm just going to roll that
really quick. Just roll it. You know when you like go to McDonald's, it's like
it's too early for this shit. Yeah. Oh my God. What I have to get up. What is it a
McGriddle? Yeah, I want to I want to make burger man, bro. They stop serving
breakfast at like not until like noon or some shit. Yeah, it's like oh my God. I
don't want this breakfast. I fucking hate eggs. First of all, that's nasty.
That's that's chicken poop, bro. I don't want that bullshit. It's like oh my God.
I wish I was at home asleep instead of a McDonald's at the morning. That's right.
Just let me sleep in. It's too damn early for this shit, bro. Are you really a
McDonald's? Are you really doing this this early? Why do I have to be in here?
Okay? Yep. My life is seriously fucking shit. I love McDonald's. I don't know
why everybody's making fun of it. Not at breakfast, though, because breakfast is
like, bro, where are the fries? It's like, yeah, I don't want a pancake. It's
true. Yeah, every time that I get breakfast, I do want some damn fries.
Yeah, I'm like it's too early for this shit. Ronald bro. I call you every day. It's too fucking early. Okay. Yeah
McDonald's early I'm like the early the early bird gets the crap meal. That's right. The early bird gets the fucking stupid McGriddles. Yeah
early for that
So that like coffee bro, I'm not trying to be awake
Early to be awake. I want to be eating a burger in my sleep.
Exactly. I can't eat a burger in my sleep, bro. I want to be awake on the later part of the day,
and it's too early. If I'm awake early, I'll have to go to sleep late.
Makes no fucking sense, McDonald's. I can't believe I decided to go
McDonald's in the morning. And also, a lot of your fucking employees are actually fucking stupid,
especially the early shift. Yeah, it's like early bird gets the worm. No,
More like the early bird gets shit. Yeah, it's like I said that
Completely said that sorry I was in line at McDonald's right McDonald's right now is in line. Yeah, and it's basically fucking
You get here and in the morning in the early and all of the the entire staff is completely asleep
It's like what did I walk into a hotel the other because I'm you guys that's the only place that someone should be sleeping
Oh wait, so they're basically fucking they it's called the graveyard shift that goes into the early morning
I wish that the people who worked it were in a graveyard. I wish they were fucking dead.
Absolutely.
Anyway, McDonald's, you funky AF.
But do you guys remember that Halloween episode when we all showed up in the same costume by accident?
Oh, I remember.
Fuck me.
Why certainly.
Why I oughta.
I told you guys I was gonna do this. I told you guys I was gonna wear this.
Three stooges, but I thought that it was pretty obvious who was who
How is it obvious? I'm listen if anybody's curly it's gonna be me
Oh my god, I'm sorry
Took so long to put on this fucking bald cap. Yeah, me too. Telling me I shaved my entire head. Yeah me too
That was like the worst Halloween we ever fucking had yeah
No, it's gonna get the same the next year. We did the same thing again the next year
Yeah, I think we have a clip of that as well
All right, three shamps. I don't even know what he sounds like
Bet that neither of you guys would do champ. What the fuck does he sound I was just why don't we just why don't we just
Coordinate why do we all just we?
Be a Halloween's always been a contentious time for us. I feel we do I mean we did again the next year
I remember the same thing
Okay, so three spongebobs
I'm ready
Okay, fine fine, then I'll be spongebob when he pretends to be Squidward that one day hi guys
It's me. It's doesn't feel right. You can't have two spongebobs and one Squidward
We just heard fucking we just don't do Halloween well, yeah Halloween is never really great not good for us no yeah
You know it was a Thanksgiving though. Thanks giving that we're no Thanksgiving episode remember when we all had dinner together
Mm-hmm, and we were eating guys, but there was that one Thanksgiving. Let's just roll the clip
- Bless us, oh Lord, for these thy gifts.
- Guys, are you fucking serious?
- I'm doing grace!
I am doing grace!
- I said I was gonna dress up like a turkey.
All three of us dressed up like a turkey?
Yeah, I know what a turkey sounds like.
- I was breaking the turkey character for a second.
I was doing grace.
How are we gonna eat?
- I thought I was being so stupid
by dressing up like a turkey on Thanksgiving,
and both of you also dressed up like turkeys.
- Couple, couple, couple.
And he won't even stop doing the gobbling, he hasn't said fucking anything.
That might be an actual turkey, actually.
My whole family's in the other room right now.
They made us go into the other room because we were all yelling too much.
Because we were all fighting about this turkey bullshit.
Cameron won't even break the character.
Gobble, gobble, gobble, gobble.
That's not Cameron.
Wait.
That's a real turkey.
Real-
Well, no, Cameron's always been like two feet tall.
No.
I don't know who Cameron is.
Oh my god, wait, check the oven!
yeah i'm sorry that i can't that's fine i mean yeah that that kind of stuff
happens uh... i luckily a lot of a lot of people at the beach think that the grill
marks on my backer cool
yeah you know it's like a tattoo it doesn't look it looks like a tattoo of a
ladder also i'm sorry they put a thermometer in you
that's okay that was honestly kind of feel good you look like you had a tan
for like a couple weeks to me i was good 'cause i call it the beast you guys
remember when i let you know we might see it
when my skin was like it was all roasted crackly all you guys eat my skin you
and you said it's even better than chicken or turkey skin. It was really
really good yeah. We should do that again, so and then it grew back. It did
all the skin grew back. That's when we learned that you had a lizard ability.
Yeah, if something gets cut off of you that puppies growing right back.
Remember when we found out we all had super powers of different kinds
oh man, I just did. I'm not feeling so good bro. I got bit by by some kind of
like glowing green dog yesterday and now I'm not feeling so good. I have
superpowers mind control sex and now it's even better actually today, because
I want to have sex with Cameron Cameron come over here.
Oh, no, that dog's coming out of me. Oh, no, your penis wait, it's growing
back. Yeah, it sure is my superpower
being an uncle.
Shut up dude, that's not a superpower.
Okay, then I...
Mind control, kill yourself!
Just joking.
Mind control, just kidding.
Mind control, just kidding!
And I was left in a completely catatonic state.
He was in a coma.
Some people think you still are completely catatonic in a way.
In what way?
They think that these words that come out of your mouth are kind of the death rattle.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I think I've been dying for...
Like maybe you've just been already kind of just...
You're pretty...
Like 99% close to death.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I guess that makes sense because I got all these IV tubes hooked up to me all the time. Yeah
Yeah, remember when we got poison ivy
I
Can't even see my eyes are so puffy ever doing urban exploration again guys. Why is it just on my wiener?
Ow fuck cuz you didn't come on the on the trip remember
Why is my wiener red and itchy? I think I got your poison ivy. You and Patrick hung out after we got back
How am I so bloated?
I'm so bloated from all the poison ivy
Spreading all the pus is spreading to my eyes.
I can't see a fucking thing
I can't see anything
There's too much. I don't even know I'm so allergic to poison ivy
It sucks.
It sucks so much.
I hate Poison Ivy.
I hate it so much.
Yeah, that was awful.
That was terrible.
I didn't have Poison Ivy, I actually just had a stomach cramp.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yeah, that clip is good, but...
I don't know.
I feel like everybody forgets the episode that we got a soundboard.
The soundboard episode was fire.
Let's play a clip from that right now.
And then I said to that bitch, "Bitch, get a new house."
Yeah, that's right. I like the soundboard.
Soundboard's working.
You guys like the soundboard?
Yeah, I really like it. It's cool.
Do you have any other sounds on there?
One second, let me see.
Okay, so there's that.
It's the same one.
It's the same one as before.
I feel like I gotta say another bro moment.
Yeah, I know, because now it's just...
Alright, stop clicking.
And that's when I told him, "Get the fuck out of Chi-Rac. That's my neighborhood."
Yeah, sorry, I'm like so distracted, he keeps playing the same sound effect.
What's going on Cam?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to figure out if there's another sound here.
Wait.
Did you only put bro sound 2 on there?
I don't know what's happening, I'm trying to play, hold on, wait.
Guys something's going on with the sound.
Yeah, clearly something's going on.
Now we have to come up with like a million more bro moments.
Can you guys just, yeah, just hold on, I'm just trying to figure it out, just keep talking.
And then I said, I said fuck you.
And then I said pay for popcorn not at my movie theater
Okay, it doesn't make any sense. No. It's not like even live up to and then I ordered a sandwich
And I said and no mustard or mayo dude. Can you turn that shit off?
We just do a normal I'm trying to turn it around where it's like it's guiding us into bad conversation
It's fucking shit. Do I say some breast?
Pulled out for this goes fucking her so bad and then she and there's poop on my dick
Hate this I hate this so wait. We got come on do a bro moment. Don't cry. It's okay
No, and then I put and then I pulled my dick out of his ass and there's poop on it
No, and then and then I said chef Gordon Ramsay is the best food. I've ever had chef Gordon Ramsay
And then and I said it's not called Frankenstein. It's called Frankenstein's a monster
Okay, bro
Now I'm doing it, bruh.
Fuck, now I'm saying just "bruh", dude.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's too much bruh stuff!
It won't stop!
And then I said, "I can't even swim!"
Oh wait, that's one...
That's a new sound!
I don't know what's going on, guys.
It's a new sound!
Alright, I can't do this shit anymore.
I'm leaving.
I'm fucking leaving.
I'm done.
[Bruh moment]
just become a bro moment. Yeah, talk about a bro moment. I know, I felt so bad. That
soundboard cost so much money and it broke the first time I tried to use it.
That's, I mean, that's what you get for buying a used soundboard. I guess so, yeah. It was already
pre-programmed to do that. Yeah, it was probably, I think it got hacked.
Yeah, it must have. It's probably that link I clicked on on Instagram. Yeah, those hackers are
really, really good at getting into our shit. Remember that episode when they
They tried to make an episode as us, but it wasn't us.
It was actually them.
Oh, the hacked episode.
Yeah.
It was actually the hackers who hacked the show to be them, but it was a different thing.
I remember they were hacking us to impersonate us.
I do remember that episode.
There was a crazy- there was a crazy-ass clip from that one.
There was.
Let's play it.
Let's play it right now.
I'm Patrick.
I'm Cameron.
And I'm Caleb.
I'm Patrick.
And I'm Cameron.
I'm Cameron.
No, I'm Caleb.
No, wait.
You guys are-
Welcome to the show. Podcast that's about list. It's about lists and
We're bald and today we're doing a list of every listeners
Passwords and email addresses. Okay, let's see here. Send us a list so we can do the episode
We'll wait. Smiling one two three. Oh, that's mine. Don't okay. Hold on smiling four or five six. Oh, that's mine
Wait, okay. Don't let's don't read that one. One two three smiling four five. Oh, don't say those ones those ones are though
That was mine
I'll just, maybe we'll do no password.
Oh, okay.
- Maybe, oh.
- I'm Patrick.
- Wait, is somebody in the office?
What the fuck?
- Oh, no.
- Oh, God, we have to get out of here.
- Guys, let's open up the door.
- It's my favorite funny comedians that I hacked
because I love them so much.
- Are you mad at us?
- Yeah, I don't know what you're doing.
- What is your name?
- My name?
- I'm Patrick.
- I'm Pablo.
- You're Patrick?
I'm Pablo. I'm Consuela from Family Guy and I'm cleaning the office. I'm Pablo and I've
hacked the whole show.
Great, a fucking hacker hacked us, awesome.
Yep, do you like that?
No.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
So now remembering, now that we listen to that, I'm remembering that's probably one of the
worst clips of all time. Yeah, that was the worst. It seems like every clip that we've shown.
I don't know why we released that.
That was like a, there was like a police investigation and stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
That was like, we should not have put that out.
It seems like every clip that we've shown so far has just been...
Funny as fuck, yeah.
Funny as hell.
But why are we doing these like kind of, like let's not sway into these kind of banal moments
like three hackers hacking us that didn't really make any sense.
What about like, do you guys remember the time when I was like in this whole battle
with Batman and I was like walking down the street like shooting at the ground
and saying hit me I do remember that let's play that clip yeah
(gunshots)
Holy shit dude I used to be a fucking badass.
That was a sick ass clip.
I'm gonna stop taking my medication again.
That shit is holding me back.
We need to get back to the golden age.
Back when it was like that.
That was what like episode like 60 right?
Yeah episode 60 the one where I came in
and I gave you guys incentives to sell more.
Oh yeah.
I do remember that.
Let's play it.
Did they get the picture?
You laughing now?
You got leads. Mitch and Murray paid good money. Get their names to sell them.
You can't close the leads you're given. You can't close shit. You are shit!
Hit the bricks, pal, and beat it, 'cause you are going out!
- The leads are weak. - The leads are weak.
Fucking leads are weak. You are weak.
- I've been in this business 15 years. - What's your name?
Fuck you! That's my name! You know why, mister?
you drove a Hyundai to get here tonight, I drove an $80,000 BMW. That's my name. And
your name is your wanting. And you can't play in the man's game, you can't close them, and
go home and tell your wife your troubles. Because only one thing counts in this life.
them to sign on the line which is dotted. You hear me you fucking faggots?
A B C. A always B B C closing. Always be closing. Always be closing. A I D A.
A.I.D.A. Attention, Interest, Decision, Action.
Attention. Do I have your attention?
Interest. Are you interested? I know you are, 'cause it's fuck or walk.
You close or you hit the bricks.
Decision. Have you made your decision for Christ?
And action.
A.I.D.A. Get out there. You got the prospects coming in.
You think they came in to get out of the rain?
A guy don't walk on the lot lest he wants to buy.
out there waiting to give you their money. Are you gonna take it? Are you man enough
to take it?
I'll tell you what man, you sure have a fucking way with words.
Okay.
Yeah, that was, that I, I did, before that I didn't really want to do the podcast anymore.
I was feeling, I was feeling bad, I was feeling down and then I just like, something clicked
inside me. That's right. And I think I, did I kill somebody or? I think you killed somebody.
Did anybody get killing somebody in that? No, I think you did kill somebody. Or I think
I maybe killed myself. It's been a long time since I've listened to that, I listened to
that episode one time in a class in college and I don't remember what happened in that
episode. That makes sense. Do you guys remember when Cameron, when we got, he was on Conan,
that was fucking huge. Oh yeah. He was on Conan but then he pranked Conan by playing the Mac
Yeah, show the clip. Oh my god.
That was just funny as fuck.
But this is between Kencroft and Gladys,
and this is from our podcast.
Or our audible podcast.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Harry!
Why?
You can't do this on a pod-
There he goes.
Wheelchair.
You can't do that on a podcast.
That's why I didn't see it coming.
- Right.
- You can't do that on a podcast.
It's a visual joke.
- I know.
- I swear to God, how could I?
Well, that was.
(laughing)
- No, it's never.
- It's an audio medium.
- I know, would it work that way?
(laughing)
- I don't know.
- Was there any truth to anything you said in the setup?
- No.
- What great times we've had on this show.
- Just good memories, bro.
Just straight up good memories, you know?
We've been through it all.
- Do you guys remember when I was Buzz Lightyear
talking to my friend Woody. I completely remember. Play the clip.
You are a toy! You weren't the real Buzz Lightyear, you're an action figure! You are a child's
play thing! You are a sad, strange little man.
Do you guys remember when we did that, when we opened up that restaurant? Then Gordon
Ramsey came in. Oh yeah, Gordon Ramsey came in. Yeah, I do
I think we got a clip from that.
You do the cheese in the middle, you seal the beef, and then you do the cheese on the top.
That's what the ultimate cheeseburger is.
Do you guys remember when that fucking speech impediment hunter was trying to find me in
the woods?
Oh my god, I do remember that.
Shit was annoying.
Play the clip!
Kill the wabbit, kill the wabbit, kill the wabbit!
Oh that reminded me of another- do you guys remember that awesome ass fight scene from
John Wick?
(gunshots)
- That one's awesome.
- Yeah, that's one of the best ones.
- That shit was badass, bro.
- Yeah, it was fucking fire.
I was like jacking off in the theater.
- Do you guys remember that song that was like,
♪ I'm blue, da ba dee da ba da ♪
- Roll the clip, play that.
- Roll to play it.
♪ I have a girlfriend and she is so blue ♪
- See, that's gotta be one of my favorite moments
from the podcast.
- Yep.
- Yeah, I seriously loved that shit.
- One of my favorite moments from the show.
yeah what is it huh must have been i first joined the show and uh... i told
you guys they'll never take our freedom
well the clip
do you guys remember also i mean that i mean okay well first of all pat
you did great
those of those that was that was the thing that convince there's another
clinton's another clip of me
uh... as that there's a couple of these things are part of a very bad things to
a cop. We're not gonna roll that one. Pat, we're not rolling it. Pat, we talked about
it before we even started recording. And you remember that clip of me when I'm in Lethal
Weapon? Do you guys remember when Chloe Sevigny sucked my dick in that movie I directed? Guys,
you're saying clips that we can't roll. We can't roll these clips, okay? We don't have
them. That was back when we were recording on tape and all the tape got burned. Do you
Remember that clip when I was in Lethal Weapon 2?
Pat, that clip is lost.
Do you remember when I was in Always Sunny doing an impression of Lethal Weapon 2?
You wanna see crazy?
I don't think we can roll that one.
Yeah, guys, you have to name newer episodes.
Oh, okay, what about that one where I go to the Thunderdome?
That one?
[Music]
What about that one where I came out as gay?
Hey Cam and Pat, I just gotta tell you something.
What's up?
I'm actually...I'm gay.
Okay.
Whatever.
Remember when I was Darth Vader?
Remember when you were Darth Vader underwater?
Remember when we saw two birds?
*sped up audio*
You guys remember that clip where I got completely hit to train?
You guys remember that clip where I lost my son?
*sped up audio*
I guess that's probably- we rolled a lot of clips today.
Oh, but the one final clip.
Okay, yeah, before we hit the final clip though, I mean, yeah, just don't- don't- don't rush it here.
here. Just chill, slow your roll a little bit.
Yeah. All right.
Shut the fuck up!
Yeah.
Seriously, shut up.
I just like, you know, it's been such an honor to do 200 episodes, you know, and
we work really hard on this.
We try, you know, we try to fill every moment of this show that we can with
just like funny-ass shit and really just kind of just make people laugh
and we don't, you know, our ethos, we don't slack off, you know.
We're not funny ass bullshit. That's the money. I'll bullshit all you like that like that was funny. It was like a dream
Yes, fuck. Yeah
Talking about yeah, I mean we we work hard and we're gonna continue to work hard
Yeah for you guys for you guys, and we yeah, we don't we don't play like that
We don't we don't play that play like that. We don't play like that. Do you want to introduce the final clip?
Yeah, but before I do I just want to say
We have merch for sale, and we also are going on tour look at you going corporate on us
we're gonna be in Seattle uh-huh on the
19th
Shows in Seattle, but before that on the 18th we're gonna be in Portland, Oregon
People came in for clips not this yeah shit. Okay. I'll heed you up for the last clip so well all right well
Well I I forgot whether this was a premium or a normal and I genius please
Intro the clip? Oh my god.
Alright, well do you guys remember when we did the 200th episode?
*Dramatic music*
*BOOM*
*fast forward*
[fast forwarded speech]
[unintelligible]
[Rambling]
*fast forwarded speech*
*Random gibberish*
*fast forward*
[fast forwarded audio]
[fast forward]
[fast forwarded speech]
*fast forward*
[fast forward]
*loud breathing*
*fast forward*
*Rambling*
Um, what's your favorite ice cream?
*Random gibberish*
*Bang*
[fast forwarded speech]
*Sped up talking*
*fast forward*
1 and 1 and 1 1 1 2 1 1 1
*Random gibberish*
*fast forward*
[unintelligible]
[fast forwarded speech]
(laser sounds)
(roaring)
[Rapidly fast forwarding]
[fast forwarded audio]
*fast forward*
[fast forward]
AIDA, attention, interest, decision, action, attention, do I have your attention?
Interest, are you interested? I know you are, 'cause it's fucked for a while.
Do you close or do you hate the bricks? Decision, have you made your decision for Christ?
Action.
AIDA, get out there, you're a prospect, a scoundrel, you're a kid, you're out of the ring?
You've got no one but the best you want to buy.
You see, I've been waiting to give you the money for the ticket.
You're a man of faith.
What's wrong, pal? You lost?
You're such a hero, you're so rich.
How can you come down here and just come to a box?
This is your watch?
Yeah, that watch costs more than your car.
[Rapidly increasing in volume]
[fast forward]
[unintelligible]
Leave.
Do you want to see you?
Do you?
[unintelligible]
[Sped up audio]
[fast forward]
*fast forward*
*Random gibberish*
[fast forwarded audio]
(fast forward)
Well that was a great clip.
Yeah, that was probably the best clip ever.
A little long for my tisba.
Yeah, but it was probably one of the funniest.
Definitely, no question.
Do you guys remember when the episode ended?
Nope, roll it again.