You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
[Ooooh]
Fuck!
We're back.
We're back, man.
Fuck!
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
God damn it.
I'm back.
I'm back from the...
Guess who's back?
Back again.
Patrick's back.
Back on the team.
He's not slim.
Live from the womb.
What about guess who's fat?
And it's... you have to guess.
I'm gonna guess Patrick.
Yes!
But, just a guess.
Will, I don't know you that well.
He knows you that well.
I'm sorry, man. I feel bad.
The first time, the first time,
the first and only time Patrick's ever, or Will ever
met Patrick though, we were making a documentary
about Patrick eating food.
Yeah, I guess I guess yeah to be fair though you you were projecting just insane alpha status the way you were eating that like
Cheddar cheese spaghetti shit. Yeah, I thought you might yeah, I thought you were like 26 28
There's nothing more
We gotta make a documentary about this old guy.
But yeah, that's me man.
I don't know what to tell you.
We have Will Duncan here.
What's up everyone?
Will Duncan.
We had to teach Will how to download Audacity before this episode.
Yeah, it took 21 minutes.
Cam came through because he's the best with computers.
He kept downloading Opera.
I don't know how.
I have three copies of Opera on my computer if anybody wants one.
They each cost $8.99 so it's like...
Yeah, we can sell that shit, dude.
You can sell Opera Browser.
Yeah.
I'm an app flipper.
I download apps and I sell them back to people.
Yo, you should write a little sci-fi-esque, kind of...
Black Mirror episode.
George RR Martin-esque.
Yeah.
Kind of Shire-esque.
Yeah, kind of J.R.R. Rowling.
But it's a team of apps.
Yeah, there's a good lot of apps.
The team of apps and they all have to have sex with each other?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and there's a bomb.
You have to figure out how to do that.
And there's a bomb and it's in one of the apps.
They get downloaded at the end.
And there's a car and there's a heist.
It's like a version of that Seth Rogen movie about food that once they get eaten, it's
so-
Yeah, apps part of it.
50/50?
Apps want to get downloaded.
What about, what was the fucking Emoji movie?
It was like emojis want to get sent or some shit?
they were like yeah yeah I need to be the first in line in the text chamber
please send me yeah there's a fuck I forgot they go into the just dance app
and they do emoji dance which is so funny like the just a hit my app Dom's
brother came home from that movie and was like explaining like he saw it with
his friends as a joke and then he came home so mad he was like explaining it to
us and he was almost like crying. I saw that movie in the theaters. It's so sick that just movies that are just
commercials the entire way through. Yeah. Dude. Like not like a Beats Pill and a
Transformer movie just the entire movie is a commercial. Yeah. Like the Angry Birds movie. That was a whole fucking like moment I feel like in like Wreck-It Ralph
that movie like Pixels or whatever. Pixels. The Emoji movie. Pixels is an advertisement for video games. The Geico movie.
They were like, "Oh!"
They were like, "Wait, can we just do this shit?"
Oh yeah, we can.
Oh yeah, nobody's gonna notice as long as we get like Hans Zimmer to make a slow-mo underneath the fucking movie.
You know where we are now in this timeline?
You know where we are now?
We're in the like, movies about candy shit now.
Yeah.
The new wave of like, troll movies where every character just looks the same, it's the same troll and you're like...
And you can eat the movie.
Sherlock Gnomes.
Sherlock Gnomes. We should make a, they should make a just truly a candy movie
just go all out. Candy movie. Skittles versus Hershey's. That would actually be sick.
Versus me and I get to eat all the candy. This is a big naked man at the end
eats all of it. Yeah, big naked ball baby. Yeah and like Twizzlers plays like a racist sheriff or
something yeah that'd be good Twizzlers played by Walton Goggins I was thinking
I was thinking like Clint Eastwood yeah his final before he croaks before he
ascends mm-hmm that's right to the RNC chair can I just make a disclaimer about
my fart take yeah in quarantine I've developed a pretty bad tick of just
Making a really piercing kind of disabilitating fart sound whenever there's an awkward sounds or just remember
I'm not interested in what someone's saying so if that pops up a lot
That's why that's why that's happening is that you do you want to don't want to be here. Yeah, okay?
All right, I just wanted to make sure just so people know that yeah, I had to move a bunch of stuff around
I don't really know you guys. You know it's kind of weird. You know mm-hmm. Yeah, no we hate this, too
Yeah, it's kind of like a Twitter thing. We're doing it for Twitter really yeah
We're doing this to promote your videos where you talk to our friend. Yeah, exactly. Yeah
That's the connection here pretty much and all of the money is actually going towards kovat 19 relief. So yeah
Yeah, so donate
Yeah, just hit my memo it's all going to
19 relief. Yeah, the trick is to make your Venmo kovat 19 relief and people just donate all the time. Yeah
That's not a bad. That's what I do
I go I open up Venmo and I just type in whatever I want to donate to I just open up and when
I type in starving children in Africa and send ten thousand dollars.
That's how it works.
And you hope it gets there.
That's like when people would like buy up websites.
Yeah.
When websites first came out you just buy up any fucking URL.
It's like land.
Yeah exactly.
Yeah.
First it was land then it was websites.
Now it's Venmo and cash app accounts where you just call it like at God.
Yeah.
And then you just get fucking so much money.
Six million dollars.
Yeah.
What do you do for work?
My pinball is at God.
I just kind of sit around, rake it in.
Yeah.
Doing cool shit.
Ooh, smokers lounge for old Will.
Smokers lounge for old Will.
That's right.
Makes me feel like I'm in the airport, you know, 1950s, the good old days.
When weed was legal and you could smoke it at the airport.
And when men used canes, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, Patrick, um, yeah, Patrick, go ahead. Before we go any further. Go ahead and do it, man.
Just put me in my grave. Put me in the dust. I actually, I don't, I don't have a rap, actually. I've written a poem
in response to you.
So wait, yeah, so last, last premium episode. He's gonna bomb. He's gonna eat shit. Last premium episode,
Caleb did a battle rap against Patrick and it's really pretty vicious.
I just want to get that back in case people didn't remember. It actually, it actually did hurt.
It did hurt my feelings and I want to express to you exactly how much it hurt my feelings.
I'm probably not even going to listen.
Well you should, you should definitely listen.
He wrote you a poem dude.
Let me read my poem.
So what are you in love with me?
What are you my girlfriend?
Let me read my poem.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Caleb, when I heard your diss rap it hurt me so deeply.
I've always looked up to you like you were Ned Schneebly.
I've been a loyal friend to you this much I know.
That's why it hurts me so much you would diss me on our show.
I would never insult you the way you did to me.
For instance, six months ago when you were fat, I would have never said that you look
so fat and racist if you were in prison you would be the leader of a gang called the White
Castle.
I would have never told you that you are so fat and racist looking that when you go to
your Ku Klux Klan meeting people think they're at the movie theater because of how big your
white sheet is.
Or that you are so fat they declared an Amber Alert on your penis because you're fat and
you cannot find your penis and it is child sized.
I would never have said any of this because I am loyal.
And even now that you're bald and thinner I would never say that you love to replace
the brownie with a piece of poop in your kids cuisine dinner.
Or that with your bald head and orangutan features you look like Dunstan checked into the hair
club for men.
Or that you are such a weird little pervert you would ride on the bang short bus and you
look like the only baby Jared Fogle would not touch.
I would never say "Caleb you went viral recently for an Obama video, it's too bad that Obama
video was not taken from a Raytheon coyote."
I would have never said this to you because I am loyal.
That's it?
That's my poem.
That was really beautiful.
I don't think you can...
I think it sucked.
It did not suck.
I think it was...
It expressed my feelings.
No, it was not good.
It was nothing.
It was less than nothing.
I took a course.
I took a WLP course in sucking at poems.
He paid $3,000.
It kind of seemed like just a way for you to rose Caleb.
Like a Trojan horse full of...
No.
at poems. He paid $3,000. It kind of seemed like just a way for you to roast Caleb. Like a Trojan horse full of kind of roasts that you hadn't used.
No, it sucked man. It wasn't even that. These were things I would never say to my friend. You can't, also there's no, you can't diss me for...
I wasn't dissing you. I was saying I would never say it. You can't make fun of me for having been fat. That's like me making fun of you for like, you shit your pants when you were a baby.
when you were a baby.
I can't, I'm not gonna come at you for that.
- Were you fat too?
- I wasn't, I wasn't making--
- Yeah, he was fat. - I was kinda fat.
- No, he was pretty fat.
- I also was kinda fat in like eighth grade.
I was like the fat farty.
- This was, this was like a year ago maybe.
- Less than a year ago.
- You can make fun of someone for that.
You can make fun of someone for that.
- Not, no, 'cause it's an achievement.
- It was less than a year ago.
- Yeah, two weeks ago.
It's humongously fat.
- Yeah, I'm fat right now, actually.
- Yeah, it's called Caleb.
I'm being fat right now.
Fuck.
Yeah, I actually just got fat.
You know how like Watsky frees--
wait, are you about to come back at him?
No, I already came at him.
This was his comeback.
That's how weak it was.
You know how Watsky like freestyled for like 33 hours
or something?
No.
I don't know anything about Watsky.
Yeah, so really important Emerson grad Watsky,
the fastest rapper alive.
Freestyled for 33 hours or some shit for like COVID relief.
That'll stop it.
I really wanted to just immediately challenge and just do acid and energy drinks and stay
up for like three days just spouting gibberish just to be like you lost Watsky.
You were for 33 hours and I went for like 42 and I just lost my mind on camera.
Yeah.
I think I could do it.
You probably could.
Dude, fucking, that'd be so much better than.
And donate all the money to COVID, not to relief, but to the disease.
To COVID.
Make it worse.
That's right.
Yeah.
He was fucking reading from a dictionary by the end of it. I was like, you can't...
What the fuck? You just...
You can't disrespect freestyle like that, bro.
What the fuck?
Damn, you got Daniel Webster's dictionary on your side, man?
Shit's wag, bro.
Yeah, that's a cheat show. That's a game shark for rappers.
Yeah, you're used to the game shark.
That's fucked up, man.
You're not even rapping at that point.
Yeah, I don't want to get into it.
He's reading.
Yeah, I read all the all of the lyrics from the Lord of the Rings movies just over and over again for 50 hours
I'm with the greatest rappers ever
Heard the dictionary front to back and then I just bent all the words to make them rhyme from memory
That would be a better that would be a recite the dictionary from memory then why are you a rapper?
Cabinet can't allow crab
He's doing it now boots berries. It's like I'm pretty sure there's a lot of words between
No, and also all of a the dictionary's just
He was using the B dictionary
Volume B you keep saying boots best of the dictionary
75 hour long dictionary against humanity. That's the dictionary
You should we should have will on to respond
Absolutely, you can't get through it it's right near it's a brick wall
Patrick I'll have something again for you next week. No, no
No, you know come back. No, I'm actually you know, what is supposed to qua is supposed to quack the beef. Listen guys next week
Next week next week on the premium. I'm gonna write us. All right, I'm gonna write a speech to make you guys friends again
Yeah
We're gonna get Jon Favreau and all the all the pots of America guys together and have them write a healing speech for no
I'm writing a fucking speech. No you
I already wrote it.
You don't even know how to write it.
I have it right here.
Then just say it now.
I'm gonna say it now.
Fine.
This is here.
Why would you save it?
Because it's...
Because otherwise I'm gonna have to come back next week.
Alright here, this will squash the beef between you guys, okay?
This is a speech.
It's called "Why Can't We All Just Be Friends Again?"
Okay.
I hate when my co-hosts fight.
It's like watching two preschoolers do hate crimes on each other.
Why can't you just go back to showing each other your peepees under the play structure?
Caleb, just because Patrick's cats remind you of the Asian cats from the Aristocats,
doesn't give you the right to break into Pat's house and go "Wahlberg mode."
And Patrick, just because Caleb looks like Commander Snoke on hormones, doesn't give
you the right to try and blow him up in your XL-wing Starfighter.
Caleb, you are like if Jim Carrey's The Mask joined the Aryan Brotherhood, and Patrick,
You are also like a Jim Carrey movie, but I can't remember which one it was.
Man the Size of the Moon?
The Number 7-11?
Obese Ventura Pud Defective?
Anyway, the point is you guys should try to get along more.
Patrick, just try pretending Caleb's lumpy bald head is a potato.
I think you'll discover a newfound ancestral love for him.
You might even start to find it hard to live without him.
And Caleb, just pretend Patrick can write prescriptions for Suboxone.
I'm pretty sure you'll find yourself practically ripping off his ginkos to suck his dick.
Can't you guys see you're meant to be?
You just belong with each other, like PB and J.
Which is crazy because PB and J also stands for your dream jobs.
Caleb wants to commit PB, police brutality, and Patrick just wants to J, just eat a shit
ton of food.
You guys have so much in common.
Caleb attracts dozens of gay men online who want to fuck his ass, and Patrick attracts
everything in a hundred mile radius due to his gravitational pull. Caleb has the
face of a chimpanzee and Patrick is the body of an orangutan. And guys, even
though one of you is Italian and one of you is Irish, you're both part of the
same race. The subhuman race. You guys are like two pedos in a podcast. Caleb,
remember when you accidentally locked yourself in a hot car while trying to
record an ironic rant about AOC's feet and Patrick rescued you by unlocking the
door with his bizarre car key shaped penis.
And Patrick, remember when you had toxic blue diarrhea
from drinking an experimental new monster energy flavor
you invented by mixing cleaning solvents with cat litter
and Caleb acted as your personal toilet for the day
so you didn't have to get up to go to the bathroom
and pause your game of skate two?
- I remember.
- And come on guys, don't you remember when you starred
in that movie together, the crossover between
Super Size Me and Song of the South
called Girth of a Nation?
I miss those days, the good old days.
So let's squash the beef right here right now.
What do you say, fellas?
Why can't we all just be friends again?
- Now that was a-- - Well?
- All right.
- Is it squashed?
No more rap battles?
- You know, I'm, yeah, I'm over my beef with Patrick.
I actually am.
But I'm starting a new beef with you, Cameron.
- No. - 'Cause that was hog shit
in a hole, buddy. - No.
- I'm gonna come at you next week even fucking harder.
I'm gonna decimate, destroy, and decompress you.
That was friendly, that was nice.
That was not friendly, he was being an arbiter.
I was being, I was, I was, yeah.
Will, that was friendly, right?
His, his, Patrick's the carbiter.
Sorry.
You read it in a friendly voice, but it definitely was not nice.
It was, I read it in a friendly voice, so it was friendly.
At least I had the fucking guts to call it a rap battle freestyle battle.
What?
Rap battle freestyle battle.
That's right, a king of the dot freestyle that I threw at Patrick.
that I threw at Patrick you know? It wasn't a freestyle. Fuck you. It was a freestyle.
No you wrote it. I was using the poetry I learned. Yeah Patrick took a $3,000 online
poetry course to write that. Yeah poetry is kind of like rap and Shakespeare is
kind of like the first MC. Alright Chance the Rapper. Yeah he is Chance the Rapper.
yeah I'm gonna say Patrick's Chance the Rapper who's probably like a Jay-Z type
Caleb is gonna go probably like an Earl sweatshirt logic yeah that case
definitely logic oh no Caleb is Hobson dude yeah yeah I have an orange beanie
yeah eat a dick white you wear the contacts and you're like fucked out of
the Creator he stole my my swag. Goblin sucks so hard I got blowjobs from it
One of the all time lyrics.
One of his best lyrics on rapgenius.org.
Oh I thought you were saying one of them and then you did the fart noise.
I was like oh it's probably his lyric.
That's my lyric bro.
Hobson's song I fucked a fart.
I fucked a fart.
I actually have not listened to enough Hobson to even make fun of him I'm gonna be honest.
He does a, he did a series, it's called like the mind of,
the Illmindahopson.
The Illmindahopson, that's Illmindahopson2.
Where it's just like him, it's just him taking on
the entire rap game.
The Illmindahopson2's video is him with the white contacts
in his bedroom and there's just a huge
Stewie Griffin poster in the back.
(laughing)
No.
Fucking rock, dude.
Yeah, I'm like, him and like Tech N9ne,
like all those like Hot Topic rappers,
like they just don't exist anymore.
Dude, Machine Gun Kelly.
- Machine Gun Kelly acts now though.
- Yeah, that's weird.
- And he still bills himself as Machine Gun Kelly.
- What does he act?
What does he act as?
- Do you have a machine gun?
Have you ever used a machine gun?
He's like, "No, I am a machine gun.
"I'm Machine Gun Kelly."
- I'm a human gun.
- Human gun, Kelly.
- I shoot human loads.
Dude, he's gonna be on SNL.
He's just gonna replace Pete Davidson on SNL.
- Yeah, nobody would notice.
- Aren't they best friends?
- Yeah, they are best friends.
- Yeah, they made a movie about it.
- They got matching tattoos and faces.
- Oh yeah.
it.
Yeah, that's right.
When Will does the self fart noise to his own line, that's next level.
Like you can tell it's not for you guys, it's just for this room.
There's a guy watching you and you're just signaling to him like, "Yeah, that wasn't very
funny."
He's like, "You are roasting them, bro.
You are burning them, bro."
He gets off to it, he's like, "Waka, waka, waka."
You know what I mean?
Yeah, he does waka, waka, waka.
He's like Fuzzy.
He's like Fuzzy Bear.
He's like, "Ooooh."
Yesterday I edited an audio sketch for you guys actually.
Me and Pierce started working on some of that shit.
I don't know if that's still easy.
Oh yeah, we're not allowed to talk about that yet though.
Alright, that's my bad.
It's alright.
Well, yesterday I edited an audio sketch privately for just whatever I wanted.
Me and my friend were making an audio sketch just for fun.
Yeah, we just decided to randomly make an audio sketch.
I had to edit a sound of me as a doctor masturbating Pierce, like scientifically.
And it's just like a very well edited scene of me like, "Yeah, yeah, into the pan, into
the pan, into the pan."
And Pierce is like, "Uh huh."
What did you do for the jack off noise?
Did you go like...
I did...
No, no, that's a good jack off noise.
I did two layers, so I looked up beat...
I looked up meat beating on YouTube, and it's like a...
It's a wet sound.
It's got the slap of beef on the chopping board.
Wait, I like the idea that you couldn't just find audio of somebody jacking off on the internet
for some reason.
I couldn't look that up, yeah.
Like, that never crossed my mind.
But beat meeting, and I sped it up a little bit because it was pretty slow, and then I
looked up just fapping sound effect on YouTube.
So it's two layers, doesn't really make any sense.
Also in the video I'm supposed to be sucking his dick, so it's just kind of, yeah.
Wait, so it's a sucky dicky sound with a with a sort of fappy jacking off.
A cartoon fappy jacky.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Oh, you got an old jacking off noise from a cartoon.
Fappy jacky.
He got, he pulled it from the Sid Caesar show.
That's how old it is.
When Ren jerks off Stimpy's enormous penis.
Yeah.
Um.
Doesn't he fucking like eat his butt in one of those?
Or his nose or something?
Does he eat it?
Yeah.
Wait, doesn't he snuck off his nose and put his pussy on him?
I think there's an episode...
He snuck a fart out of his ass and put his dick on his fucking dick, nose, fucking eye, pussy.
Yeah, I think he comes in his own eye.
That's every episode of Ren & Snimby.
Yeah, and now you have Steven Universe and all these cartoons about depression and being gay.
You know the, like, Louis C.K. factor where you, like, you see what Louis C.K. was, you know, me-too'd for and what he did wrong,
And then you look at his comedy and you're like oh, yeah like he talked about it every day
It's so obvious that he wanted to actually do that to people now when you look at Ren and Stimpy. Yeah
You're like what the fuck are you talking about? Did you want to jizz in that guy's nose?
You are that's a creator of Ren and Stimpy like a pedophile. Yeah
Years later Ren and Stimpy actually did get in trouble
It was right in front of our eyes the whole time. Yeah, it turned out they weren't acting out any of those scenes
They were actually doing them. Yeah
They actually bought a log from a TV commercial
So yeah, Ren and Stimpy
Done, bro. You can't like it bro. Yeah, no no more no more Ren and Stimpy
City Hall, but he
Like will just protesting Ren and Stimpy right now
Stimpy no more the devil's program the red cat no more
The red cat
It's like I'm gonna tweet that later, that's good
They are brothers and they are having sex
That is not good. The red cat with its cursed body. Oh, no the Bible says the red cat
sucks the dick of the dog
I hate Rocco's modern life
Yeah, didn't they
Didn't Ren and Stimpy come or fucking Rocco's modern life come back?
They come in the nose
Didn't they didn't run in Stimpy come in Rocco and get him pregnant and make a baby from a boy or was that my
Yes, yes, it's our no, it's not
90% of the time when I make a joke it's just I'm actually dyslexic and I mix up words and people are like wow
We'll do it on purpose. He's so cool
Yeah, and then you and then you go Ren and Stimpy on them
Mango Ren and Stimpy mode like creator or Ren and Stimpy
He get happy happy joy joy
red cat oh man come on like tall hat oh
fuck fuck
will's starting his freestyle right now to beat george watsky
okay it's gonna kick off you guys have to supply the beats
that's fine
oh man go there he goes
Mango way like a boat like a boat
Man do dirty in a basement Oh
Face way. Oh man stay home like Halloween Oh
Smoke green Oh
Man, so high like a roaster. I'm so high like it's pasta. Oh my god fucking Dickie Ravioli
Duncan bro, so trolly oh so trolly like gummy worm. Oh my god
Young Willie make penis squirm. Okay, we night Jack and no young William don't can be like mr. Peanut
Oh my god
Yeah, so that's just a little
That's that's we got to wait cuz that's for kovat relief. Yeah. Yeah, you just made you just made 50 bucks
No, I just wasted $150 just then by squirting one of them.
Yeah, because you didn't finish it.
You don't get the money until you finish it.
So you finish the 33 hours.
Well, technically, if you start it today,
you can pick it up later.
So, that's true.
Yeah, it doesn't have to be in a row.
And you're allowed to--
That's true.
It does have to be in a row.
No, it doesn't have to be in a row.
I don't think he said that.
Why would it not have to be in a row?
Why would it have to be in a row?
It just doesn't have to be in a row.
You can go one word at a time.
Yeah, what, so you're gonna say all the words
at the same time?
He was doing one word a minute for a little bit there.
I was watching the whole time.
Like I fucking cheated, bro.
He could just go super slow
and kind of like do like a deep voice too.
Yeah, yeah.
You know?
Me?
No, you could.
Yeah, you could really stretch it out.
You could just do "Till I Collapse" by Eminem,
but just stretch it out over 34 hours.
Dude, Watsky came into the cafe I worked at, bro.
Looked bad, dude.
Looked like a Slytherin, bro.
Long hair.
(laughing)
Long hair?
What does he look like now?
I remember him looking like a little boy.
- You guys know he went to Emerson, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, I mean, it makes sense.
- I knew that, yeah.
He did a performance or something, I think.
- For COVID in like 2015.
He's like, "There will be a play.
There will be a play, Ren and Stimpy.
This college has watched too much Ren and Stimpy."
- Ren and Stimpy.
- Have you guys heard of the other Tom Hanks?
Tom Hanks, other--
- What? - Or sorry.
No, yeah, Chet Hanks.
Yeah, dude.
Not Colin Hanks.
No.
He's like an insanely racist DJ,
just lost cause random.
Yeah, he does the Patrick.
I love Chet Hanks.
Patrick, I would say,
is like a foremost expert on Chet Hanks.
I love, yeah, Chet Hanks.
Have you seen, the other day,
he posted a picture of him in his car
and it says just like,
you, dude, trust me,
right now you need to go listen to Kokomo
by the Beach Boys.
(laughing)
Dude, there's one video,
I forget what he says,
He's on the red carpet talking to someone and he's just like, "Yeah mon, welcome!
We f*cking out round!"
"Chetana!"
Yeah.
I love the one where he's drinking the smoothie.
"Hey, it's your boy Chetana!"
Oh yeah.
And he goes like, "Buyaka, buyaka!"
"Internet went crazy!
Buyaka, buyaka, buyaka!"
"I wish so bad that accent was not, like, just offensive.
Like I love doing that with my man."
I wish that he, yeah, I wish it was real for Chet.
I wish he was not.
Oh yeah, I wish his hair was mixed in.
Call him out. He's like this just how I don't I had him on the set of castaway. So actually
He just talked to the coconut and then got that. Yeah got that accent. It's natural. It's it's not offensive
He just doesn't know who he is. We had him born on the island so he could do that voice
I got born on island like cast away. Okay
Drive in the Mazda. Oh
Dude the O is really a lifesaver in those moments. Oh, just at the end of every line. Run out of it. Oh
Everyone's like
He's surprised at his own skill
He's so good at being a mean Jamaican guy
I'm drinking espresso out the Fanta cup man.
I got the bean
That's what Jamaica is like you drink everything out of a Fanta cup. When I went to Jamaica I was like fucking seven years old
I just had beautiful long Aryan hair. I don't support the Aryan nation. Just want to make that clear
But that is like I feel like it's an acceptable use of the word Aryan, you know when describing blonde hair of like a child
You'd when you describe a child
Innocent beautiful cuz like Hitler could never be like young, you know what I mean?
There's no young people that support Hitler like there's too much. Yeah, there's no young people
Youth or anything
That's not a concept that happened in Germany. So yeah, I was in Jamaica just beautiful hair and
Everyone's just screaming at me to braid it like chasing me down grabbing my hair like
$15 to braid your hair. My dad was just like please get away from my my darling touch my boy
Yeah, I got caught in it when I went to the Bahamas you had you like it. I came back with a couple braids
Picture of that I was like 11 or 12 and
Yeah, and I got I got pretty clowned on a youth group. I won't lie. Really everyone's like nice dude nice fucking hair you idiot
Yeah, yeah, I was getting owned
Hey Caleb your hair fucking sucks ass you're an idiot. Yeah, I went to an all-jamaican youth group
They really got me for it man, oh, I just remembered the fucking you're talking about
The like how there's like Aryan kids. There's a fucking the Ku Klux Klan does have a little kids YouTube channel
Yeah, they have like a video where it's two little kids and it's like shot in like a public access thing
I don't I can't find it. I don't remember what it was called, but it doesn't exist
It's straight up after two little kids. It's two little kids and one of them's like, did you know that miscegenation is like
She is fucked. I gotta find that you there was I remember I say I
One time in high school me and my friend found this channel that was called like hey kids TV
that was one of those like auto-generated like kids channels, but like the like
narrator like the main character who like like
Just like talked in all the videos was this guy who was like it was like this like 3d face
But it had all these like scars and like Darth Maul shit on it
and it would and it just said really fucked up shit it was crazy it was a
crazy they took down the channel I can't it doesn't exist anymore but it would be
like it would be like this like and had this weird accent and it would be like
like does you do your parents hit you comment below and but and then it was
also like a bunch of like finger family videos it was crazy dude I wish I saved
like the downloaded the videos we still find some pretty good like AI generated
YouTube videos yeah they're just like pictures of pyramids yeah and it was like
15 best pictures of pyramids. Yeah, 20 minute video.
Have you guys, uh, you guys have talked about like,
oh, Dr. Blue Spider-Man and shit on the show probably?
Dr. Blue Spider-Man?
We're talking about the blue Grinch.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Okay, this is kind of Pierce's bit, so I don't want to bite into it too hard,
but Dr. Blue Spider-Man.
Like, three and a half years ago, Pierce, like, got obsessed with these videos
that was like grown-ass actors who looked like kind of vaguely,
It looks like it was shot in LA and it's like people who are really desperate for money are doing this
Mm-hmm
and they dress up as like Elsa and spider-man and the Hulk with like Target just like
Brand shit like really bad costumes and shit and they act out little
sketches
For kids that are like 13 minutes long. It's like the classic weird creepy YouTube shit
Yeah in every episode or not every episode. There's a recurring theme of a doctor blue spider-man
He has a blue spider-man suit doctor's outfit and a huge hyperdermic needle doctor blue spider-man
And he always injects Elsa's ass
in like
It's always like a doctor
Yeah, I don't know I forgot about that
Here's was on to that shit like so long ago. Just naturally and then this whole exposition came out about like
You know companies using algorithms to make shit for kids and the algorithm fucks everything up and makes it horrifying and fucks up their brain
But that shit is different because it's like humans.
Yeah, yeah.
It seems like they're being forced at gunpoint to do it, literally.
Yeah, there's so many crazy videos like that.
It's disturbing.
It's just like...
There was a...
I can't find it, but I've just been... I'm realizing my Google searches are just so...
It's like literally I'm looking up "White Power Children's Show", "Nazi Children's Show".
God damn, dude.
Just a knock at the door.
Yeah.
Why? What are you doing?
Hey sir, have you been keeping up with the Nazi children's show?
Because the regular Nazi shows are too complicated for you.
We would love you to work at Google.
Badgers like, know, they're like, okay.
Just don't walk away, don't make another case.
Yeah, never try again.
They just found his address just to ask one question.
They just knock on every door, every day.
It doesn't matter if you've actually been searching it or not.
or not.
Unless you put lamb's blood on your front door.
They're genuinely just asking, they don't know whether you have or not.
They're just like, "Hey, have you been looking this up?"
Because if so...
Weird timing, but we're the FBI and we were just wondering if you wanted to hang out.
We've just been knocking on every door in your neighborhood.
We're bored.
Yeah, we're bored so much.
We like basically solved every problem in the world and we're just kind of knocking on
everybody's door to see what kind of TV they like.
Do you want to go play soccer?
Yeah, we're the FBI.
the FBI. You wanna do like a crossword puzzle or something? I don't know. Wait, what were
we talking about right before FBI? Oh, Hitler, like Aryan people? Aryan white supremacists
who are just super pushovers. They're like, you should be a white supremacist. Nah, I don't
really think so. Like, fair. That's true, it's kinda hard. And I get that, honestly.
Pat, what are you doing? You're spacing out. Pat is getting hypnotized by the KKK hypnosis
I'm getting radicalized.
He's getting hypnotized by a monkey in his room.
You haven't blinked in like a minute.
I've been watching the-
I was trying to find this thing.
Because it was fucking insane.
It's shot like it's all 4x3.
And it's all like
straight up shot like the same shit that I was making
in like high school.
You were making that kind of stuff dude?
It's actually the exact same thing that he was making in high school.
I think it's because I made it.
No, that was one of the
I just found it one morning and I like a fit was it on the official does the clue?
No, I don't know to change it was I mean it's been taken down now because people probably like they cook
Let's go and have a terrible website by the way really. Oh, that's probably where I found it
Yeah, it's very light. It's like web to camera or Caleb. Are you filming like from the little clitoris on your laptop keyboard?
Yeah, we have tight when you type your fingers are just so right. I'm filming from the little red button
The little red button.
Little red button.
Let's see, I'm gonna look at their website.
I just remember, speaking of racist
kid shit, I fuckin'
I was talking to Cameron.
The movie Little Miss
Sunshine?
Racist kid show.
I just remembered earlier, my
fuckin' middle school, I was
talking to Cameron about this, we had a thing
called Immigration Day.
Dude. Where we
We got assigned an ethnicity.
Oh my god.
And they had the whole school set up like Ellis Island.
And you go in.
Oh my god.
You go in and then there's like...
Patrick's one of the officers just saying no to everybody.
Fuck out their names.
He's like spell your names, just fuck your name.
You had to like, you get assigned a name, you're supposed to make up a backstory for them.
them you're supposed to go through the whole Ellis Island thing.
We are the Hanksees!
We hail from Jamaica!
Castaway Island!
Dude I don't know why but that concept, sorry real quick, of like oh a bunch of people's
names got fucked up at Ellis Island is so funny.
My name got fucked up at Ellis Island dude.
I think about that once a day.
Anyway back to you.
Yeah but they fucking, so they had to, we had to work for like weeks.
Like it was a whole unit, like it was until the end of the year and then like towards
the end of the year we go through the Ellis Island thing and you're supposed to dress
up in little 1910s clothes and bring like food with you and it's like to teach us about
like how like some people didn't get in they fucking they assigned you diseases if you
didn't do well enough on a paper or something like that and you're supposed to like you
were supposed to you know that like-
They tested intelligence of all the races.
Yeah.
And they let you in if you did poorly.
Oh my god.
They like rolled the dice and then whatever number you got, you got that ethnicity.
So like they had like the Asian kids who were like, they were Italian.
Like it was just so weird.
Wait, the Asian kids were Italian?
They put all the Asian kids?
No, just like not like...
They kept like racial lines when they just switched them around.
Yeah, they were just like, no, the Asian kids are not allowed to be the Irish people.
That does not work out.
Everyone's like, why are they Italian?
What the fuck is that about?
No, they like funny because of Mario
Dude, oh you get you get assigned an ethnicity and then you have to go through and then you have to learn the history of like
The immigrants like at the time and it's like oh a lot of like Italian immigrants had whooping cough
So then some people would just get like whooping cough or if you didn't do well on a paper
You didn't do your homework. You had to go into a bag and pick out
the bag
You had to stay in the bag for the day.
Dude, when I was in fucking middle school, like fifth grade or whatever, I lived in a
very historic small town, so we had a project that was like, "Everyone is assigned a character
from this time period that actually lived in Annapolis, and we're gonna dress up as
them and walk around downtown and tell little stories about where you lived and shit."
So we were like, "Okay, my best friend Sammy Stag got cast as Kunta Kinte, who's just the
slave in Annapolis."
He's like, he's roots Alex Haley's roots.
Yeah, that happened in Annapolis, Maryland.
So Sammy stag my best friend is just cast as a slave does not
like we have to make a costume and shit.
Like my mom is really good at sewing.
So we worked up a fucking amazing costume for John Shaw
who like made the first flag or whatever.
I fucking killed that shit Sammy's like parents like just
gotten divorced.
His dad is like a 65 year old New Zealand sailor who looks
like the little baggins just had no concept of how to handle that project
like help your kid make a slave uniform Sammy came to school in a pillowcase
with the sleeves cut out straight painted black and my teacher was just like no
you're not allowed to wear that like here's a fucking shirt you're not gonna
to do this project. And we're just like, what the fuck is wrong with you? Why are you even
assigned? Like, what the fuck? No, I know. Both sides fucked up. I mean, I also in like
high school, I probably shouldn't tell this story, but there was a day, there was this
day called like diversity day, which was organized by like the diversity club. And it just was
kind of a like really poorly organized day. Like it, the programming was thought up of
by students like twice a week in 45 minute blocks for like two months.
So the shit that we were doing was just like really dumb.
But also like the kids doing it didn't also really understand like, like they would just
be like, raise your hand if you're poor.
And it's just the whole school, the whole school is there.
Yeah, just like stand up if you're poor, stand up if you're black.
And it's just kind of like, you know, I went to like a mostly white school too.
So it felt very just like performative and just like, okay.
So we did that every year and every year was just kind of a
nightmare.
Like student led discussions of 15 people where the person
next to you says the most racist shit you've ever heard.
But no one in the room is a like teacher qualified to like
shut that shit down.
So that kid just like has a platform and you're like, whoa.
So we like, we skipped one year and we went to this diner
and just fucked around.
And then we all came to school at the same time,
a bunch of dumbasses, like 10 of us, and the secretary or whatever was just like, "How
was breakfast boys?
You boys are racist."
Oh my God.
So it's huge disciplinary shit.
My whole friend group got brought in there.
Just like, "How disrespectful is it that you guys fucking did that shit?"
You guys are on the hook.
The first week of college when I went to, before I transferred to Emerson, when I was at UNCW,
We did like a, you know, like our uni class,
which is like a freshman orientation class basically.
They did a privilege walk, which is like a similar thing,
where they line up everybody in the class
and they say like, if your parents like own a home,
like take a step forward or whatever.
And it's like a pretty like poor college.
And so everybody was like, I was so far back
that I was like, they didn't plan for anybody
to step that far back.
And I was like, you know, Bush.
(laughing)
There was this one kid who like looked like a, um, looked like a, like a fop from like
the 1600s.
Like, he had like curly blonde hair and like dressed like a sailor and like, yeah, no,
except he was like 300 pounds.
Like he was like, he was like medieval rich where like the fattest guy is the king.
And like in my brain, he like, in my brain, he always had like a giant lollipop.
He was similarly in the opposite bush of me
because he was so far ahead of everybody.
But I mean, the thing is, in a situation like that,
I'm winning so much more than him.
Like those are all just like, how far back are you?
Whoever's the farthest back is the king of the game.
- And the king of the game is whoever goes the least?
Whoever is the farthest back by the end of it?
- So it was like, you step back if you are this,
step forward if you are privileged.
- And if you win, if you get the privilege?
Yes, you know the winner gets a hundred bucks
Dollars if the winner gets a hundred privilege
like you
You all started the same spot
And if you like if you have a house step forward if you whatever step forward and you just started way back
And then by the end of it you were like yeah, I'm the least privilege of all of you guys
So maybe think they would be like if your parents are divorced take a step back if you're white take a step forward
if your dad is...
And you didn't step forward.
Yeah, and I didn't step forward.
Yeah, I kinda cheated, to be honest.
My shit was like, if you're white, punch yourself in the dick.
If you're gray, like, tie your shoes.
And we were just like, this...
This is...
I rock.
I just remember, I went to like a mostly all-white
school too, in New Hampshire, and I just
remembered some fuckin'
So we were supposed to bring food, to like...
Whoa, he's shining the light at me.
Are you guys recording a video?
No.
No, okay.
(laughing)
Dude, put your pants back on, stop.
We were supposed to, oh, so we're supposed to bring
like a food for like, because like they had food
or whatever, and this kid like brought a box of dry spaghetti
for a market basket 'cause he got Italian.
So sick.
I brought like a thing of bread, like a soda bread,
'cause I got Irish, I'm fucking Irish already.
I didn't need to be Ira.
I didn't know who to go.
So I fucking, I watched the kid.
He got so hungry 'cause like we didn't have like lunch
that day, like you were supposed to bring food
and he thought you were only supposed to bring--
- There's no lunch in Ellis Island, dude.
- Yeah, so he thought you were only supposed to bring
the food like you were, like that was gonna be,
he didn't think that like we weren't gonna have lunch.
So he just ended up eating dry spaghetti.
(laughing)
No!
My brother did that shit all the time. I used to eat dry spaghetti and pretend I was a farmer
And it was like a piece of wheat. Oh, yeah, no no not dry spaghetti. I'm really into eating the wheat.
Dry, dry ramen. That's like a thing people do. I think I've told that story. I got sold a dry ramen packet.
When I smoked K2 by accident. Someone sold you the like seasoning bouillon shit?
It was just like, yeah.
He sold me, I, so he lived, like I smoked K2 with these kids by accident.
Yeah.
And then we went, I like, we went back to his house and then like on the walk there
I was like, man I'm so hungry, we should go to Nutfield, which is like this convenience
store that was like literally-
Can't say, can't say Nutfield.
Yeah, I bet you want to go to Nutfield.
No, no, no!
You want to go to Feel Nuts, dude.
You want to fucking feel some nuts?
You're back as a football field where a bunch of guys, sperms and penises, you know, you
know, you're like, "I'm going to go to Nutfield."
I'm like, "I'm going to go to Nutfield."
a
And this kid was like no I got you come to come to my house. I'll get you some food
So I gave him I saved my lunch money that day I gave him two bucks, and he sold me
I'm standing outside of his house. It's Valentine's Day
It's not alright, it's the end of winter, but it's still cold, so I'm standing outside
I'm outside in the fucking cold for 30 minutes
waiting for this kid to come back and he hands me,
I gave him two bucks, he comes back with a ramen packet
and he's like, yo, put this seasoning in it
and shake it up and eat that shit, dude,
you gonna be on heaven.
You gonna be on heaven, bro.
Once you eat this dry ramen player,
you gonna be on heaven.
- When I was in high school, I had this friend named Pencils,
that was his nickname, Pencils.
- Yeah, I bet you did.
- Everybody called him Pencils,
teachers called him Pencils,
parents were like Mr. Pencils and shit and whenever there's like an open email
account or whatever people would write like "70 virgins must be sacrificed to
pencils pencils is the best" like he was just like a weird urban legend at our
school really fucking weird dude but he was big on like black market Silk Road
bullshit and looked up or found out how to like do robo-tripping where you like
yeah you pour a bunch of yeah you pour a bunch of that in like a big soda bottle
and then you fill it to the top with water and let it sit overnight and then the DXM
Sinks down to the bottom and collects at the bottom and then you like chop the top of the thing off
Pour the water off and you just have like that fucking much DXM and then you just gum it
So that's the first thing I ever did
Was do that in a parking garage with pencils and Kyle Feldman just fucking
Yeah from a sun-kissed thing or whatever nothing happened, and then the next day pencils, and I just woke up in my house like
Absolutely tripping balls, but it's the first time that it ever happened to me
And it happened when I woke up which was so weird and I got lost man. Yeah
Whoa you got lost I?
Got lost no far for that one. Yeah, that was just that was real. That's do shit shit
You can't fart for real shit. That was some real pencils ass shit. Yeah, I get it.
There you go. I tweeted about this, but I smoked with these kids once that I didn't really hang out with and
We went to this, yeah
We went to this like tree house that this kid knew about on a house that was foreclosed
Like their family got kicked out, but they built this like super sick tree house
So we walked in the middle of the like it was pouring rain
We walked to this tree house, and I'm like it's like one of my first couple of times smoking weed
So I'm just smoking way too much too high and this kid is like yo
Did you know?
What they were doing in that circle in that 70s show?
Like you know like what they were doing like now like it's like Shaggy and Scooby were stoners, too
And like people know like and then Shaggy and Scooby just liked food
He pulled out his phone and started doing the 70 show thing.
Wait, when I read that tweet, I thought you meant something else.
Like, did he start filming you guys?
So he recorded himself like this and then turned it to this kid Trevor.
That's crazy.
And then once it got to me, I looked at him and went, "What the fuck are you doing?"
I want to find that video.
I think I kind of bullied him into stopping it.
Patrick was definitely the Fez of the group.
Yeah, so I was Eric Foreman because I knew about Star Wars.
Yeah, you were Eric Foreman's actor.
It was me, a classic Eric Foreman type with two Fezes.
That was the problem.
I'm f*cking Ariana Grande or whatever her name is.
[Laughter]
That's right.
Mia Wallace or whatever the f*ck her name is.
Yeah, Mia Farrow.
Yeah, what is it?
She's so good at it.
is Greta Thunberg she's on that 70 show yeah my favorite character in the 70 show is Greta Thunberg and
Mother Gaia and the guy at Korn. I'm actually into Anubis. Favorite gods bro let's go
Caleb you get top three cuz it's your birthday but everyone else just gets one
I'm on this episode.
I thought yeah, I was like Caleb been like, because we have the same birthday.
Yes, we're both tourists is ready to do.
You're both sex tourists were sex.
- You're both Aryans.
- We're not?
No, he is, he already admitted this.
I don't have hair, so you can't ever know.
- I said my hair was, could be described by a Nazi.
- It still is, it still is, dude.
- My hair could be described as a Nazi as Aryans.
- You have surfer hair, Gene.
- Oh, bro, yeah, man.
(laughing)
- You mentioned a kid who did like Silk Road shit.
I knew a kid in high school who similarly was just like,
he just like sold acid and shit.
And he bought like a bunch of sheets,
he bought like a thousand dollars worth of like LSD sheets
on the Silk Road.
And then they arrived and his dad opened the box,
looked at them and flushed them down the toilet.
- Ooh, you knew what they were?
- Yeah, and then, but I guess he didn't know
how much money his son could make from it
because when he told his dad how much money
that he had just lost, his dad started crying.
(laughing)
- But that shit is so cheap.
Like you buy a hundred tabs for $10.
That's what I mean.
Like it was so much acid and he would have been rich forever.
Dude, that same guy Pencils started doing that in our hometown.
He started dealing acid to like freshman girls, like 14 year olds and just a 14 year old.
I'm like, "Pencils, you've been my best friend for a really long time, but what you're doing
is morally very wrong."
I could like sense Pencils' effect on my entire town.
I could see it.
Will thinks that girls can't handle acid.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
He thinks that it turns them into boys.
It's a highly masculine experience.
It turns your brain into a boy's brain once you trip.
That's what it's like being a boy.
That's what Terrence McKenna would say.
That's what being a boy is.
When a girl looks in a mirror on acid, she turns into a boy.
That's true.
I think we all know the divine power that comes from just being a nine-year-old boy.
You just can't get hurt.
Yeah, that's true.
You squirt and cum out of every orifice nonstop.
You're literally just pure life energy, just boogers and cum and scabs and pus and...
That's beautiful.
You should write a poem.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
You should write a poem.
About being... about nine-year-old boys.
Yeah.
About your favorite nine-year-old...
Yeah, about nine-year-old boys squirting cum.
About how precious their bodies are.
Yeah.
About how precious and life-giving nine-year-old boy bodies are.
And how they're full of cum.
And it's how it's impossible to hurt them.
Okay.
You guys are misquoting me and you're having a little bit of fun with that.
No, we're not.
You said little boys are full of cum and they have beautiful bodies.
I didn't say that.
Say that you did delete this I don't know if you really know we're gonna post twice
Two times in a row. I want you gone. No, you're gonna be gone once we put you in jail for this podcast
Yeah, this whole thing was a sting
Whole thing was a sting. Oh, okay. Why don't you direct labor in my butthole you I did
Yeah, it was called it was called lady boy
(laughing)
(vocalizing)
- You went race car to Jamaica real fast.
- Race car?
(vocalizing)
- Like that.
- It peaked.
- Sped up.
- Couldn't hear you hit the tip.
- Fuck.
- Yeah, I couldn't hear you do the beat earlier either.
- You couldn't hear me do the beat?
- No.
- 'Cause when you get too loud it cuts your audio.
- Yeah.
(beatboxing)
- Yeah, let's close it out with another.
Let's do a five minute freestyle to close it out from Will.
Okay, let's do the cypher.
(laughing)
Back to the cypher.
It's like a OK Go music video.
I actually have to piss my pants so badly
so we didn't this early
'cause I've been holding a pee in for 30 minutes.
You guys can let me--
No, you just leave.
You can just leave, we'll keep talking, you fucking idiot.
I'm in the middle of the Matt Watson--
Go do it.
(groaning)
Just go pee, I gotta get a paper anyway.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
Will's leaving too?
- Will's leaving, it's just me and Cameron, baby.
- Nice.
- Damn, it's like when you go to KFC
and they got the original recipe
and then they got the spicy recipe.
- Don't know what you're talking about.
- That's us right now.
We're the spicy recipe.
- No, you're a spicy recipe, dude.
- When it's you and Caleb, that's original recipe.
When it's me and you, that's the spicy recipe.
- No, when it's me and you, it's the cool guy in bed
and ugly guy recipe.
- All right, now Will's back,
so now it's not the spicy recipe.
- You talking about chili?
(laughing)
- I'm talking about KFC.
Patrick was trying to tell me how KFC works.
- They said that--
- They said that.
- Yeah.
- I gotta go to Stop and Shop after this.
- No you don't dude, shut the fuck up.
- What?
- Man gotta go to Stop and Shop,
sounds to me like man gotta go to Stop, Drop and Roll,
'cause you're on fire.
I'm on fire.
- Bad fire.
- Man go to stop and shop, man go to stop and shop,
like shoppers.
- I gotta find the fucking, they don't have the,
I think people are panic buying them.
I don't know what the fuck's going on,
but the Gardein fishless fillets, the vegan fish.
- I thought you were gonna say Nintendo Switches, but yeah.
- No, people are fucking panic buying these things, I guess.
I can't fucking find them anywhere,
so I gotta go to a grocery store that's like--
- It doesn't exist, dude, you imagined it.
- 30 minutes away.
- Like Drew, you invented a type of food in your mind.
I invented this in my head like the Neo-Nazi Kid Show I was trying to find.
You invented this in your head like Fight Club.
Yeah.
Tyler Durden!
Tyler Durden on a track like, "Where is my mind?
Whoa!
Where is my mind?
Whoa!"
Dude, when you watch that movie, it's crazy.
never seen a movie where buildings fell down and they played a pixie song at the same time.
That is mind blowing.
You get goosebumps all the time.
I've never seen a sex scene in full 3D rotational camera vision.
Between
Oh dude I forgot about that matrix sex scene.
And there's like the weird echoing like "Huuuuuhhhhhh"
I'm gonna be real bro, fucking Bellatrix Lestrange or whatever her name is, Rihanna, Tim Burton
and
in
Caleb cuz he's in that little zone. Yeah, he's trying to whizzle
We'll start a way into Bella Bella tricks list ring
Jack Skellington's he's got a hell in a bottom Bella tricks
Elaine Louise Dreyfus. Yeah, we'll try to turn her into hell and bottom farter
Whoa?
It's spreading
That's the real virus
I'm getting disgusting dog shit out of my teeth right now. Not cuz I ate it not cuz I
Say you went to go pee and you came back with dog shit in your teeth
Get there the dog shit. It was in the toilet and had to clean it out before I could pee on it
I just drained the toilet water through your mouth
Honestly checks out
I'm crazy
You have to drink all the toilet water through a straw and then and then spray it out through the gaps in your teeth and it
Leaves on the dog shit. I didn't have to do also let your dog shit in your toilet. I was thinking about
Last time I was in the ocean I really had to shit and I got I got probably
92% of the way to just shitting in the ocean
Have you ever seen you sucked it back my my I have not pooped in the ocean my cousin one time
I was one time I was in the ocean with my younger brother and I was like damn after shit
and he's like yeah me too and
I was like yeah
And I then he like started making like a shitting face and I was like that's funny
He's pretending to shit in the ocean and then a piece of shit floated up right to my belly button
and then I ran out of the ocean to the beach.
- It's the first time I ran out of the ocean.
I wanna shit in water, that sounds kinda nice.
- It's kinda like a home birth.
- He'll shit in a dry toilet.
He never shits in the water.
- And I scrape it out and like half it.
When I was, I worked at a summer camp
and one morning I had the day off
after like three weeks of working straight
and took my time, woke up late, took a nice shower,
walked all the way up to the like dining hall or whatever, was
getting some food, some breakfast style food and I turned
around and this other co-counselor was talking to me and
I farted really loudly like as a joke like, you know, I had to
fart working at summer camp, that shit happens, you just do
it right in the middle of someone's conversation, you know
what I mean?
It's like that type of shit.
So I did it as a joke, but it wasn't loud enough for her to
hear and I just completely shit my pants like the most I've ever
shit my pants and I was like probably 21 my pants filled with
shit I immediately just walk away from her do not leave the
conversation she's still talking to me I'm just shuffling away I
go to the little boys cabin and I take my underwear off they're
not there of course and my the underwear I'm wearing is like
blue digital camo underwear from Target like it looks like a
little boy's underwear.
it looks like a little boy so i just
filled it's a diaper filled with shit and i just leave it in their trash can
i'm the director of the summer camp and i do that
i just sabotage a kid i just leave shit in their thing go back downstairs
shower again new clothes walk all the way back up the hill
so like two and a half hours total
crazy hand. One time i shit myself this is when me and cameron were working
together cam you definitely don't remember this but you were there
I shit myself on the way to work while riding a blue bike through Massachusetts, and I didn't
realize the shit my pants got to work.
I was like, "Ugh, I feel something in my pants."
And then our boss was like, "It smells like complete shit in this office."
And Cameron was like, "Yeah, it does smell kind of weird."
And then I just so conspicuously ran to the bathroom, threw my pants away.
And my pants threw my pants away.
I threw my underwear away and then nobody was ever the wiser.
Including Cameron, unless Cameron admits right now that he knew.
I didn't know.
I don't think I noticed.
I think everyone was the wiser.
Everyone saw your underwear with your name written on it and sh*t.
Yeah, he just left it hanging over the top of the bathroom stall.
No, I left it on Cameron's face actually.
And he only took it clean for me.
Oh my god.
Get owned.
Get owned Cameron.
I almost sh*t my pants when we did acid that one time.
Do you remember that?
I think I do remember that.
We were taking that picture and I was like, "I gotta fart."
And then I just did, and then I was like, "Oh no."
He shit himself.
I was like, "Everyone needs to leave the bathroom right now."
You know what was funny?
It was fucking, there's a picture of me just in the shower and like, Neil's ex-girlfriend's
there and like, I almost shit myself in front of like, God.
You should have man.
That must be like her image of me.
Must be the worst day of her fucking life.
Yeah, I know.
God, yeah.
I think about that girl.
worst day of our life. We fucking the whole time to the island. Oh yeah. We were just doing
we were it's the middle like it's winter in New Jersey. What fucking island are you talking about?
We were staying we're staying. Patrick invented an island in his mind to deal with the trauma
of almost shitting his pants. That's where the trauma lives. Yeah. You guys remember the island we went to
and they had those monsters made of shit covered in pants. The shame monsters.
Yeah, they're like big piles of shit with pants sticking out of them. You guys don't remember we battled them and I almost died
We fought all of them
Swim back in the eye and the back across the toilet lake back to the cabin. That's Scooby-Doo Monster Island
I know you're thinking of toilet island Patrick Doran adventures. Don't shine a fucking laser pointer in my eyes. You're thinking a toilet adventure
I'm thinking of Will Duncan's
Will Duncan's dookie pants explosion 2.
The island of misfit fucking Patrick.
The island of misfit toilets.
It was, the island was like this, uh, it was like this thing where you could see like the
whole lake so we were like, oh let's go see like the entirety of the lake.
I was wearing like Converse and we had to walk through like a sheet of snow.
You were wearing a skirt dude, you were wearing a skirt and a baby's bonnet.
I'm trying to find one for the patrons.
Yeah Patrick will never wear a dress.
Do you have a dress you could send Patrick, Duncan?
Yeah.
Um, nah.
I have a night dog.
I have no idea why.
Do you have a dress for a 220 pound man?
Yeah, I do.
People call me Duncan all the time.
That makes sense.
Really?
You have one of those last names that you can say.
To me, Duncan is not a first name.
Probably because it's my last name.
That's because it's your last name.
It just feels weird, but yeah, I'll introduce myself in an email.
Hey, it's William Duncan.
Nice to meet you.
Best, Will.
My name is Will, by the way, not Duncan.
And people respond like, "Hey, Duncan.
Didn't see you there."
Here's a response.
Didn't see you there.
Yeah, I didn't see your email there. All right, you got a shit
Will you have anything you want to um plug besides just your Twitter account? Yeah, follow wheelie Duncan follow my Twitter account
It's the first Twitter account to get 1,300 followers and we're gonna get him did yeah hundred and probably thirteen hundred and ten
Yeah, we're trying to get we're trying to get will up to 1 million followers for some reason. We're just trying to juice this man
So that's it's cool
So I definitely, probably is the wrong time to ask, but me and Pierce want to make a zine
with you bros.
Just a big old fuckin'-
What's he doing?
Yeah.
I'm down.
Literally get 30 people.
I'll do that shit.
So that shit would happen soon.
So we're plugging that now in our future project.
Yeah.
Yeah, so that's gonna be sick.
That's gonna be sick.
Yeah, and then, you know, check my Instagram for some videos.
Wheels Duncan.
Oh yeah, what's your Wheels Duncan on Instagram?
I think it's Wheels on the Bus Duncan.
Yeah, I think that might be it.
All caps, all spaces.
All spaces.
All right, let's go.
All right, thanks.
Peace mode.
Thank you, Will.
Thank you for having me.
Of course.
Thank you, Will.
It's been a pleasure.
Stay safe out there.
See ya.
I'm leaving.