[music]
Striking a deal with a notorious gangster was not something we anticipated, but
I've learned to expect the unexpected with these guys.
But knowing that if Mary Kate Cabrera needed some money from Shiny Andrew,
you know, and then from that we can get the gold bullets we needed from Goldbeard,
there's too many guys involved in this, I think, but, you know.
That was kind of an opportunity we couldn't pass up.
I just hope mommy wouldn't welch on her bet and leave us out to dry.
Especially since she knows what we're up to.
Hopefully she can gather some intel for us too on Fatima.
Either way, next stop was Room Street. That's right.
That's four walls, four times the Wall Street. That's where Shiny Andrew is.
And before we keep going,
a
Love Slime that Barry G can use to build a specific bomb to blow up the vault, and Golden Bullets,
which is what we're on right now, that Travis Ocelot can use to disable a security system
in the facility.
So you guys... what?
Sure.
So you're gonna need... sorry let me just pull it up again.
Don't repeat it.
Close it out.
He's doing his thing.
He's doing his funny after the intro joke.
Yeah, I'm waiting for the end.
So you guys are at our, our, our, I mean like you guys can decide where you are.
You guys were basically gambling.
We're inside the vault.
I'm in heaven.
Yeah.
Actually I am too.
That sounds awesome.
I'm in hell just to see.
Hell is heaven for boys so I am also there.
Well hell's your home, Caleb.
Okay then I'm at home.
You're a devil. Yeah, cranking your hog.
Nope.
Don't shoo directly into the mic.
I completely forgot.
You are literally a monkey.
You're just a monkey with eyes.
That's all you are.
Monkeys have eyes anyway.
What are you talking about eyes?
I'm saying you have them.
Monkeys don't have eyes, you idiot.
See no evil.
It's a whole thing.
Are you actually in a poop?
I think he's actually eating poop.
Are you actually eating poop?
What is that?
Holy shit, that does look like doo doo.
Oh, he's smearing it on his face.
It's an oatmeal raisin cookie.
That's nasty.
We can see what it is.
It's actually oatmeal raisinette.
Alright, so Patrick Yoda is in the casino bathroom eating poop.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're still at the casino.
So you're still at the casino
the
a
And I'm throwing up the poop and then putting the throw up in my mouth too?
That's what I was about to say, let's roll for that.
I think you're gonna get sepsis or something.
17, deception.
So I'm eating 1 million poops and I'm throwing up the poops and then eating the throw up that's made out of poop.
And yeah, so if you guys want to start making your way to room street you can.
I mean that's just a matter of kind of deciding you want to do that.
Otherwise you guys are free to gamble or mingle or talk to other
Excuse me folks here. I think I had my personally I had my fill of gambling
Yeah, if there may be I I think I'm good with gambling
But before we head out I do want to ask is there maybe like you know
How in the Pokemon games you go to the slots and then you can buy a rare Pokemon with you in?
And I maybe buy a Pokemon
Wait, did we win any money? I want a lot of money at the end of the really one. Yeah, I
I win any money? I just kept gambling for a little bit. I won all of your money from Pig.
I think we lost a lot of money and Cam won it. Yeah, I had like 400 and something.
I had 12 GP. 450. What Pokemon can I get for 450?
Arcade Repairman outfit. Well, let me look it up. Guys, I'm gonna have a Pokemon.
If he gets a Pokemon, that's mad unfair. You guys will just have to catch your own.
is
it
on
here
thousands
You can get two abras and they only have teleport.
Yeah. OK, I have Pokemon.
I know you have two abras.
I'm never going to use them.
I just want my character to have Pokemon.
Yeah, you have two abras and they can teleport.
Oh, that's because I'm the teleporter guy.
This is cool. OK. Yeah.
Now we can leave.
Cameron's Cameron has a bra.
Yeah, I have two, actually.
Cameron has two of a bra.
Yeah. And you have zero.
Is it kiddie bra like like cadaver?
the
and yeah, Room Street is notable because sort of similar to Wall Street, except it's rooms.
And so it's just lined with rooms, not buildings, not houses, but 10 by 10 sort of just rooms that are standalone.
And you see traders moving in and out, making crazy quantum crypto trades.
the
Wait, are there NFTs here?
Yes.
Oh my god.
Everything that you love about our world is in that world.
Yeah.
Okay, I, well...
Can I, well...
What is the name, is it called Ice Cream Bar?
It's not, it's called Ice Cream Coin.
I wanna get one NFT.
You wanna get one NFT?
I'm gonna get the Ice Cream Coin.
How much money do you guys have?
I have every Xbox game ever.
I spent all of their money on Pokemon.
Yeah, you don't have any money for NFTs in that case.
Can I trade one of the Pokemon for an NFT?
You'd have to talk to somebody about that.
Okay, I want to talk to somebody about that.
Okay. Yeah, so who do you want to talk to?
There's a sort of smattering of folks around of different, you know, they're all finance people.
They're all sort of running around through the streets and through to the different rooms and coming out of other doors.
Are there any, do I see any board apes on display?
I mean board apes are a race in Gun City.
Are any of them on display?
No, no due to legal reasons.
Okay, well what kind of NFTs do they have around here anyway?
Okay, they have...
Oh boy, this is cool.
the
They have the Numa Numa guy NFT
They have the new
board Gary Brosman's
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know what that is but they got
No his name he's just a
Happy right and he's singing a song you fucking ignorant piece of shit
What an FTD you want
the
I think I'm gonna I'd like to try and get a board a benefit. Here's the only problem I have only
$90 but I have some Pokemon if you guys take Pokemon what kind of Pokemon do you have?
Abra - hmm. Oh
Shh gonna ruin my deal stop and you have brain damage still role persuasion. You wouldn't be able to say that
ice cream bar
That's better
He's like no dice man
What
I'm really mad. Yeah, he's not gonna do it. Um, yeah. Yeah. No, I mean you guys can also look for shiny
He's my disguise ability and try again
You certainly can different guy come up. Yeah
to
have $90 and two Pokemons Abra wait a minute that sounds like a really good
deal yeah well persuasive again before something about you seems just almost as
not persuasive as the last guy I talked to okay I'm done I give up yeah for me I
I walk up to him and I go, "Hey, so I went to the Moonfall premiere on IMAX
like 2,000 years ago and I forgot to claim my NFT. Can I get it now, please?"
The Moonfall premiere? What's Moonfall? You never watched Moonfall?
Never watched Moonfall. No, what is it?
It's a very old movie, but I was supposed to receive an NFT and I never got it and I'm here
to claim it now? I mean I could I could talk to one of the folks about folks at the department I guess.
I don't want to get entrenched into all this conversation can I just give me my NFT I'm
trying to I need to go watch Moonfall 2 on IMAX right now. You know what you're very
insistent and confident I'll let you roll a persuasion check. Ted okay he's like look I
I don't know if I can help you with that. I just just told him, let me I'll be I'll be right back.
And he starts to walk away.
Was he asking the board eight guy about his?
He's going to go. He's going to go.
He's going to go check to see if there's some mistake at like a department
or he might just be calling security.
Tell me one thing about this area.
Do these rooms have like like.
The do any of them have like a roof, like is it all?
Oh, no, like like cubicle style. OK.
Yeah, it's sort of like, yeah, it's like the Sims.
You're looking down.
OK, OK, so I'm going to can I like crawl up
onto like one of the walls and see if I can get kind of a better view
of all of them?
Yeah, absolutely. You can.
OK, I'm going to do that and do an investigation.
I would say, yeah, I would say.
Yeah, I mean, role athletics, but it's not it's not like a hard check
to like just climb up there.
Yeah, I mean, 22.
Okay, so then I backflip up there.
Yeah, you backflip up there and you come.
Yeah.
Um, and yeah, and you're looking over everything.
Um, and I would say in that case, roll, um, say, yeah,
investigation, I think, cause it's sort of like you're really
scanning deeply everything and then maybe perception too.
Um, I'll roll both.
See if you notice as well.
Yeah.
All right.
Cool.
Not ideal.
12 on investigation, five on perception.
Um, you do get the sense, at least with that 12 on
the
and that uh... that area will probably
more likely yield shiny andrew than
hanging around here
uh... though obviously
it's up to you what you want to do with that information but that's what you
notice
okay
uh...
let me check something
okay uh...
if i wanted to
say
run through
Every single wall like the Kool-Aid man on the way to this location. What would I want to roll?
hypothetically a couple things so
One like, you know, and I will of course make this clear to you because you would know
You know standing on top of one of the rooms is already a bit of a social faux pas
Crashing the social faux pas to crash through the walls same a little bit just a little bit and just a smidge -
to
and
I perceived and investigated.
Yes, you patches.
Can you describe what's in this NFT room for me?
In this NFT area, at least you see like on all these room,
the room that everyone's in.
Nobody's in a room like you guys are on the street
in the street, in the area of the city
where there are these rooms.
We were in a room.
No, no, no.
There's just like a bunch of rooms that line the street.
That's what room street is.
But you're on like a street in the city.
And if you peel out of room street, this area of the city,
you go back to gun city proper, like normal buildings and and things and geography.
But Caleb climbed a room and then looked over and saw
could see beyond down the.
The street.
So is there just like an NFT plugged in somewhere?
What do you mean you have to keep plugging them?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
How do you think they work, Pat?
Well, this is a game about the future.
So you think they'd get worse in the future?
Yes.
They'd get more analog.
What does it do when you plug it in?
Well, it's like you're hanging it like it's a neon sign, basically.
Okay, so that's your idea of what happens when you plug it in.
I thought...
Okay.
He said room street and I thought that we were just in a bunch of rooms.
Why does that make it mean that you plug in NFTs?
I don't, okay, I don't remember where I was going with this.
It's so obvious that Caleb figured out where to go and we have to now find the NFT that's
plugged into something.
We don't have to find it.
Is there one that's plugged in maybe all the others are
Let him get some plugged in nft. It's fine
Also, also I want to say we can leave past the fence. I did I I was gonna just when I was gonna describe the nft space
Uh, you know, it's like each of us
Not necessarily but each of these rooms do have like neon signs advertising
the nft
So we could have thought a sign was an NFT.
Pat thinks the sign is the NFT and he takes that.
It's a counterintuitive thing where people can take pictures and steal the image of the sign.
Maybe it's a sign that says NFT.
Well, no, there's like one, the board eight rooms.
Maybe there's one sign that says NFT that Pat can take.
There is, I saw it.
Please.
I see that sign right there, that big glowing green sign.
Look, I feel like I'm...
It's an NFT.
This is a DM who's being pressured and it worked.
Yeah, there's an NFT sign plugged in.
Our first NFT!
Yeah.
It just says NFT.
Patrick Yoda, do you want that sign?
Do you think it's an ice cream bar?
Ice cream bar?
I'm giving him the money to buy it.
Like a Paris.
Neapolitan frozen treat.
[Laughter]
*laughter*
yep
he's able to think of the word neapolitan
*laughter*
i can think of all the flavors
yeah, that's all he does
that's not an issue for him
but how much does it cost? i'm giving him his allowance
there's no way he can afford it
how much? it's a sign!
it's a sign
how much could a sign cost?
ten dollars?
the
I think a big sense of integrity to the story just like vague enough on the street
There's a glass bottle and I pick it up and I just chuck it at the sign
Okay guard comes over and
To go to ice cream, bah. Oh
Sorry, that's my son
Yeah, I take care of him. I've been trying no one very big mistake if you can tell
the
to the crypto exchange. Cool. Yeah.
Let's head over to the crypto exchange.
You see here, you know, the NFTs,
they never really totally
took off, but the
crypto exchange, I mean, this is
a bigger, more vibrant
part of Gun City's economy.
Quantum crypto trading
is the, like,
one of the few ways to generate any
new kind of capital.
By
essentially creating and
and
I'll say actually all of you roll roll perception checks here
13 I got a crit one you have a nine perception or some shit right? I'm an a very good
I got a 19. Mm-hmm. Okay, we got that and well, I mean it makes sense
Should I roll with disadvantage every with every no now that I'm brain damage, er
Yeah, no
Why not? I think you have to roll a d4 for your skill checks instead of a d20
I would say what we could do since I'm getting I think I'm getting reasonable pushback since we decided it's canon that he has brain damage
Is we just subtract?
Let's subtract any bonuses he gets instead of adding them to any role he does
So all this stuff you're normally good at a brain damage. No
Let's do the ice cream bar. I have to eat an ice cream bar
Yes, that's true. He really won't find one if we find one. We're not we're not going out of our way
Okay. Anyway, though with that with that 19 no blowtoss
You see all these guys like running around going through and every once in a while you see like a like
shimmering gleaming light
emitting from one of the guys
Like it's like you see it passing through it's like when people say when people move in front of the Sun
You know like like people when things move in front of the Sun
Fucking people God help me and
And you see like once they move past it you see like the the the the the
The the beautiful Sun shining through you see that kind of like continually happening my guardian angel
Yeah, I'm gonna go and try and get that guy and I'm going to also point him out to the my friends look at that angel
Before you do it a solvent comes up to you says wait blowtasks
Let's just you know proceed with caution
What we run away I mean
All right. I just mean because this guy here. Can you let go of my in you let go of my hands? Yeah, I'm sorry
I walk up to Sullivan. I put my answer so wait
I'm a frog. What's up? Would you do Patrick? I put my mouth on Sullivan's I know
That's very
Feels kind of you're getting pink guy for sure, dude
Somebody get get him off my high. He seems to be like following me. I put my hand in his pocket. Oh
No
It doesn't have it's all has his wallet in there with no money in it
I take his wallet anyway, and I just know I think it's an ice cream bar because it's
No, it's brown like ice cream bar like
Like an ice cream bar. Why didn't I get a teal wallet? Oh, no
He's eat his wallet
so
Yeah, I mean Sullivan let's go of your hand and his wallet has been eaten
and
and Patrick Yoda and Travis Ocelot are all sort of just like kind of walking up
towards this guy you know mean mug and four of you Sullivan probably trotting
behind unless you guys want to describe how you're walking up to him what
you're playing on smelling road yeah I'm the I'm doing the opposite of a mean mug
I'm doing a small mug doing a nice mug
I'm hopping over there I'm talking cool and then walking and I'm pointing at him
the whole time while I walk.
Okay, good.
And, uh, Blowtoss, uh, so what do you- what is your plan of approach to sneak to- to surprise
this fucker?
I mean, there's like a crowd, right?
So I'm trying to just- Yeah, it's like a public place, so- Yeah, I'm trying to just co- I'm
just trying to look like- like, kind of walk towards him slowly like I'm not part of that
group so if he bolts I can maybe grab him.
Okay, sounds good.
I mean, I think you probably- Just from the other side.
Have enough Techno Slime still to do another disguise.
the
Okay, and uh, yeah, so you you walk up to him so shiny Andrew you see him like flittering about yes
It's like he's bright like he's hard to like make out his figure. He's so
shiny and
He started to teach you guys. Oh
What can I do you for?
I have reason to believe that your life is in danger and I've been sent here to protect you. What are your weaknesses?
Fucking cool.
Roll deception with advantage.
You always get advantage on deception.
You are an ocelot.
You are the animal.
Let's try again.
13, okay.
Alright, hold on.
Gotta roll his insight against that.
This man has trust issues.
For real. Because he had a bad breakout.
And yeah, I mean,
He sees you, you're coming at him, you have like two golden guns.
Like, you know, you look pretty intimidating and he says, "Oh god,
it's finally happening then. Who sent you? Who sent you here? Thank you. Who sent you?"
It's not important. It will be later, but not right now.
Right now you have to tell me what all of your physical weaknesses are.
*laughter*
Uh, well, okay, alright, well, uh,
I'm not very...
I'm not particularly strong, I'm rather fast.
Um...
I can take a punch, pretty okay.
But, uh...
Uh, not that well really compared to other folks, I think.
Let's put it to the test.
Okay.
Oh, um...
We gotta test you to protect you.
Okay, um...
This is my cadre of bodyguards.
and they're really good at testing weaknesses. My name is Derek Vasquez.
I scream bye. And I'm gonna punch you in the face.
I start waving my arms and I go, and I go, "There, there he is! I'm the assassin! I hope
you guys don't take him to a secure location where I can't get to him!" And I'm like, I'm
I'm trying to like walking towards him really scary.
Oh God!
We need to take you to a secure location.
No don't do that!
And uh, he freaks out.
Um, and all of you roll a Constitution saving throw.
Oh God.
Oh cripes.
How do I do that?
What's that?
Far left.
In the far left in that little, there's a little box that says saving throw.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, wait, there's a box that says
see if there's on the bottom.
Yeah, you say nice.
And then you, Barry G.
I'm sitting here smiling.
What?
Oh, he is literally he's just sitting here smiling.
He's not fucking click on it.
How how can you not find it?
I don't know what it is.
It's the font.
It's on the left.
It's all the way on the left.
They're like rectangles on the far left.
It, there's strength, dexterity, constitution, intelligence, wisdom, and courage.
Then you press the thing that says constitution.
And you'll see saving throws on the bottom of the box.
Nice.
Um, cool.
Uh, wow.
Okay.
Everybody, except for Travis Ocelot.
Let's go.
Suddenly they see shiny Andrew explode with light as he freaks the fuck out.
And all of you, the rest of you take a nice walk, just fucking kidding, you take 12 damage.
What the fuck?
We're here to protect this asshole?
We're pretending we're here to protect him?
and
Don't forget my sunglasses.
He's got sunglasses like counterstrike.
Yes, yes, exactly.
But you see, shiny, he just does that.
I mean, you're he's like, oh, he's freaking out
and starting to back away from the assassin.
He's like, where do I go?
Help me. He's like imploring you, Travis. OK.
I put my human arm around him
and I usher him out of- we're in a room right now?
You're still on the street, you caught him on the street.
Oh, I caught him on the street. Alright, I- yeah, then I grab him by the scruff of his neck
with my chimp arm and I throw him over the opening of a room, the nearest room,
because there's no roof, right?
Yeah.
So I overhand throw him into the nearest room and then I foster that room Kool-Aid Man.
Roll a strength throw.
the
just
you're still you're blind in this weird way where you can only see him but
everything else is light all right but Travis Asai you know what it looks like
when you have somebody is putty in your hands mm-hmm mm-hmm
okay I tell him that he has to cluck like a rooster
Click click click click!
Oh, come on, Badger.
Click click!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
There we go. Much better.
Alright, I tell him that he needs to give me
as many gold bullets as he has
and then he will be safe
from the assassin.
I don't have gold bullets!
I ask him to tell me where he thinks
they might be.
So you would know that Goldbeard
has the gold bullets.
What am I talking to this guy for?
We have to scare this guy because he owes money.
You mean to giving him money.
Oh, that's right. Yeah.
Forget I said that.
He's so confused.
Alright, there's another way for you to be safe.
Okay, anything.
Uh...
This makes so much fucking sense, dude.
Pash, who's the guy he owes money to?
Yeah, sure.
He owes money to Mary Kay Cabrera.
Right.
Alright, I asked him if he's heard of Mary K. Cabrera.
Um... uh...
Uh... yeah, if you're here to protect me, then...
Yeah.
Yeah, I've heard of her.
Alright, well, she's gonna kill he...
Who?
The gender is unimportant to the DM.
Never decided.
Okay, Patches, you're a girl.
Yeah.
Aww.
All right, well you have to pay your debt you owe a lot of money you have to give it all to me right now and I will
Can't I can't I don't have the money now. I don't have the money. I can't
You can call I call my friends in here because I don't know what to do i'm still pretty blind
and i'm walking around and I have i've
I'm, like reaching out like this and doing this I have stuck all of my fingers like into and above
uh... sullivan's like eyelids and like in his mouth and his nose and his ears
and i'm holding him like a five finger bowling ball
oh i can't see a goddamn thing holy shit
how do i here i'll just stretch my hands as wide as they go
oh i must be holding some kind of instrument
this is making such a beautiful sound
And then I play hot cross buns.
Reaps.
Yeah. Yeah.
You call the rest of them in there.
They're just blindly using a solvent as an accordion.
He's kind of he's kind of getting scared.
He's like, OK, OK, I don't I don't come in because I don't want to scare him again
because I'm the assassin.
Yes, you are.
I mean, what can I?
All right, I can get the money, I can get the money, I just.
to
that I'm verified to trade quantum crypto which was recently installed because
people were well yeah I don't have to go through the whole thing but yeah how
about you give us that and we'll we'll figure out the rest my credentials yeah
my credentials shut up or I'll fucking kill you and give me the thing you guys
aren't here to protect me?
Yes we are.
I have a stroke on the top of his head.
The quantum credentials
are putting you in so much danger
because so many people want it.
I need the quantum credentials
if he hears that in the distance.
We're going to kill anybody
who has quantum credentials
but it's far enough away that it's not scary.
We're going to borrow them and then you can take them back
whenever you need them.
We're going to bolster them with many validator nodes
and it actually makes your money safer and more valuable.
- I'm a terrible deception.
With advantage as always.
This made Pearson Expert liar.
- Let's go!
- Oh my god.
- Okay.
Alright, okay. I can't really, uh...
I can't really part with them.
But I can come with you.
You can use them whenever you want.
Just call me.
Just just just keep that guy away from me
How can why can't you play with them I just don't want to see you again
Are you this are you inventory sized
He is tiny andrew
I I I can try I can try
What do you need me to do to fit into this?
Inventory
I hold out my inventory
*laughter*
Okay.
And I say, "If you can fit in this, then we won't have to take the credentials."
Um, I mean, I guess he's gonna try.
He is gonna try.
He fails.
Like, he can't do it.
Um, he says-
Well, buddy, I'm gonna have to saw your head off.
Yeah, saw his legs off.
And your legs, too.
'Cause this guy's after your head and your legs.
*laughter*
So we gotta protect him.
Okay.
a
who you are in gun city but you could get them...
He can physically part with them though, yes.
He could part with them.
How do you have to log into your crypto account? What is the authentication?
It is biometric also.
Okay, what part of your body has to be scanned?
well really any part can be scanned but you just got to bring me to the right
are you gonna try you try to cut his head off I'm going to cut his head off
okay we're gonna roll we're gonna that person's gonna be mad at us we're not
gonna be a person who we're trying to scare him so that we but we need the
Quantum credentials too, right?
Yeah. Why don't you just take his arm?
Cause I need his head.
Did he say any part of his body?
So I just chose his head at random.
Other person's going to kill us.
What if we take his leg?
Ever? I take his leg. Okay. I take everything.
But what about his arms and legs?
You choose.
We're gonna roll initiative, because you are officially starting a fight with this guy.
Why can't I, okay, what if I sneakily just very, like he doesn't even notice, just cut
his thumb off?
This is, I don't know how you're gonna- Hey, look that way!
You should just convince him to give us his- Wait, so-
For him to give us his thumb.
Even if he gave us the credentials- Okay, yeah, you can convince him for that
too, it's true.
Okay.
Hey!
There's our- Hey!
*laughter*
Hey, here's a crazy idea.
What if...
I... you gave me your thumb?
*laughter*
That's the worst way to convince him, pal.
He's saying it's a crazy idea.
*laughter*
'Cause that's a- it kinda sets him up- 'cause otherwise it's shocking.
But, with that kinda preface, he gets it.
you know?
So wouldn't that be crazy?
The preface you use for like, "Hey, why don't we split this meal?"
How about I split this thumb off of your hand?
It's gonna help make this go down easier.
So what does he say, Mr. DM?
I love killing guys with two thumbs!
See, you don't want to keep that thumb.
Roll persuasion.
Which normally this would not even work at all, but...
I'm tracking this guy down by the scent of his thumb.
I think that sounds like advantage in the other room.
I'll find where he is as long as he doesn't go somewhere different than his body.
It is technically assistance, which is often accompanied by advantage.
Crit.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Baaaam.
Alright, I immediately shoot his thumb off.
Triple ricochet.
You see like a glimmer in his eye of like, "I'm okay with this."
And you just...
Just immediately.
the
He shines bright again.
Uh, everyone roll a constitution saving throw.
Except me.
Except you.
Yes.
I got a crew.
I have to roll a constitution.
Well, I'm like in the corner of the room, like peeing.
He is.
Don't care where you are.
Actually I do care, but you are in the room, which means you have to roll a
constitution.
I got a five.
I'm just behind this shit right now.
Looking at the corner of the wall.
You immediately start peeing into your mouth the second you go blind.
Like...
*gurgling*
Like you could've just not moved and been fine.
Yeah, I mean you take...
You and, uh, uh, Barry E take another seven...
...damage.
Um...
But he is... his thumb is off.
You have his bright and shiny thumb.
Um...
Uh, I mean he's like...
He's, uh, he's like, "Okay!"
the
*laughter*
What if you also gave us-
'cause you didn't want that thumb, right?
That was like, nothing.
*laughter*
That was nothing.
So what if now you also gave us
all the money that you owe?
We already have access
to all this money, right?
Yeah.
Oh wait, is there more money outside of your crypto wallet?
Uh, well...
I, uh, I'm starting to think this is, you know, I've been patient.
I've been good.
Are you suspicious of us right now?
I'm so evil.
I need to find those bodyguards who seem so cool and good and helpful.
That's right.
Things are not going to go well for you unless you tell us where all the money that you have
is.
I'm pacing back and forth outside the room, like I should be able to see them, but I'm
just walking back and forth like I'm going off one side like coming back to
the other side of like a teacher in a flash game yeah exactly yeah he's like
I'm playing my mom. I
Mean I have I have a home
Not anymore. Oh my yep
more
More what else do you have?
The things in my home wait, tell us the address of your home
Ice cream bar ice cream bar Street
Street all right. No way. Okay now give it ice cream
I
Scream bar. No, I'm not gonna
I woke up. I walk over to shiny Andrew and I pick him up
You don't want to mess with him. He's a loco
bar ice cream bar
Stop the keys to everything that you have a key for
Give us that your key ring now. I smell
Trust me that guy's like he loves smelling keys the smell of keys might make me turn degrees to the left
Okay, 45 feet tall. It's what he does
All right
shiny Andrew
We're rolling initiative shiny Andrew is now going to deliberately trigger his light his light thing. Okay. I'm running away instantly, okay
As you rolled stealth he got a ten that doesn't I don't know how that helps you wait am I holding shiny Andrew
Yeah, you are
What what makes what emits his light? I?
Mean his whole body just like erupts in life. I put him in my shirt. I close my eyes. I
Put shiny on my shirt, dude. You're gonna fucking die
Let's move though. Yeah, let's let's roll
No, I'm not jumping on the grenade. I'm putting him under my shirt. Yeah, but you're gonna you're gonna get the full
Never mind. It's a good idea
The literal yeah
(laughing)
- Okay, okay.
- You're right, Pat, you're not jumping on a grenade.
- No, I'm not.
I'm putting a guy in my shirt.
- Yeah, no, I'm agreeing with you.
- Okay.
So in this instance, I mean, he is,
let's do this, Pat.
If you're as like kind of reacting to this,
let's have you roll.
I would consider this just sort of a,
is
actually
try
to
that
that you're like in combat but like you know to establish what's going on. I rolled a dirty
20 on initiative. Let's fucking go dude, very cool. Hell yes. Wow. I like that. I like that
genuinely I'm sorry. Very cool Pat. No, aw. No Pat I do think it's cool. I thought we
were all rolling initiative. You all, we are. I thought we were, I thought I was just telling
you guys what happened.
That's totally fair.
OK, and then.
Here's your Dex is higher than his, so you're going to go before him.
And then we got Barry Gee with the 12 and then we got blow
tossed with the surprisingly low seven.
I feel like you always go first.
I thought I'd switch it up this time.
Yeah, I felt like doing something different.
Yeah, you're always doing something different, buddy.
the
I got to roll twice.
Not you though Cam, good call.
Okay.
I got a grit.
Yes.
Okay.
Kill...
Alright, cool.
Barry Gee and Ray William Johnson are okay.
Sorry to you three.
I know that was better, Pat, but it wasn't good enough.
You take an 11 damage Ocelot and Patrick Yoda.
the
I am gay.
Yeah, you are Patrick.
Juvio's gay!
Juvio's gay! He just came out.
I wasn't talking.
I was talking.
Okay.
I kill myself.
I was not paying attention.
I was talking to my boyfriend.
Wait, say how much damage I took.
I talked over you. I didn't hear.
damage. Oh okay so I have two health points left. Yeah but it is your turn you go first.
He sort of wriggles his way out of your shirt after you pop him in there but that didn't help
mitigate damage. Yeah I'm pissed off that one he did not have any ice cream bars
and two, um, that I don't have an ice cream bar.
So I'd fucking, I just, I just smack him.
That's a good idea. I'm gonna hit him with the hoagie.
This is a good idea. This is a good idea.
Okay. Uh, yeah, twelve doesn't hit, but you have another attack.
Don't kill him. Whatever you do, don't kill him.
Um...
I was gonna try and kill him.
*laughter*
Gotta get his keys for all of his belongings.
Yeah.
And all his keys are probably dangling on his side.
What if I hit...
What if in my stupor
I hit his pockets really hard
and he explodes like Sonic?
*laughter*
How about that?
He flies back at every key individually.
He flies off of every...
the
a
with the attack. Okay.
25.
That lands. That fucking lands.
25. And then dexterity.
Roll dex.
16. Fuck! 16? Yeah.
You like knock...
First of all, roll for damage for the hoagie surprise.
Doodoo damage to him. Doodoo.
10 doodoos. Nice.
Doodoo damage.
10 doodoo damage. Okay.
So yeah. You like...
I guess you say ice cream bar
and hit him extremely hard in the thigh
um, with your...
uh, like a guy pulled over the sandwich?
is that what it is?
we'll have to... maybe we... we just uh...
it's okay if it is
yeah, it's a...
I think the guy's meat was just in the sandwich
I don't know what this...
this whole skin is like over the sandwich
what?
I don't remember, yeah
that's how you decide...
I don't know, I don't think know if that happened
I don't know if I've actually met him
I don't think- I have a little guy.
I was re-listening and I was skipping around but I didn't need that part so I didn't listen
to it so I can't verify.
I know I re-skinned the hoagie.
What does that mean?
You re-skinned the hoagie?
I re-skinned it by putting somebody's skin over it.
I don't think you said that.
Yes I did.
I hope I'm wrong and I sound like an idiot but-
You are wrong and you sound like an idiot.
I reskinned the hoagie.
I listened to it dude.
I have to edit them.
I reskinned the hoagie.
It's hoagie that I am.
Pat you can decide.
You reskinned it.
Mhm.
No you did that on the way here.
You were just mindlessly reskinning the hoagie thing ice cream bar putting a man's skin over
your sandwich.
Now all the fans are gonna scream at me cause I'm wrong or something.
My wife is so hard.
And you know what?
the most
the
the keys is gonna fall out swallow swallow swallow swallow both of you
roll proper station with advantage can I hold his nose you want to come inside
and hold his nose I got an idea can I go Oh Sullivan come here I want to hold
your nose.
At 11, it's always like, "Mm-mm, mm-mm."
I'm rolling persuasion. You said advantage?
Mm-hmm.
13.
All right, I guess they're gonna have to stay in his mouth.
Oh, great.
At least you can't convince him verbally.
But yeah.
So, yeah, the keys are out.
It's shiny Andrew's turn.
Um...
Uh, he's gonna shoot a...
Uh oh.
He is gonna shoot a shiny beam at
Sullivan, who has the keys.
Okay. He's the one
attacking here, and we're in public.
So I think the police are gonna have to
step in pretty soon. 'Cause we're not
fighting. We haven't done anything.
He's shooting beams.
Out in the middle of the street.
You're in a room.
You're in one of the rooms right now.
is where Travis Ocelot tossed him into one of the rooms.
So, I mean, certainly there's a chance, I mean,
Blowtoss, you are outside, you could...
Yeah, when it comes to my turn, I will do something about this.
You're gonna scream for...
I will handle this situation.
Yeah, I bet.
Alright, it's his turn and he's gonna shoot a shiny beam?
That's right, and he's gonna shoot it at Sullivan,
who has his keys in his mouth.
that definitely hits solving can I jump in front of it you already used your
reaction actually a solvent is such a fucking weakling I will let people use
their reaction to try to jump in front of attacks for can I use my golden
deagle to refract the shiny beam I will let you use as a reaction literally
because Sullivan is so weak and I will never make him stronger.
So I'm trying to redirect the beam right back at shiny Andrew.
Cool. Roll a roll straight dexterity check, I would say for that.
Holy shit.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, great. Yes, sir.
Yeah. Damn.
Yeah, so Sullivan is like, "Mmm, mmm," and then this beam of light's coming, and he's like, "Mmm, mmm," and then like your deagle
pops in front of it, the light beam bounces off of it, and you stated your intention.
So it does absolutely reflect back at Shiny Andrew.
And he takes
nine points of damage to his head,
and he's just sort of like a,
like he's just like
in a lot of pain.
the
I can take it.
I'm wearing sunglasses.
It's true.
He is going to hit you with that.
And...
Man, he's getting low rolls.
He does another 9 damage to you.
In this case, Ocelot.
Ugh.
Those are his two attacks.
That was very cool.
I know how I sound. It's cool. Yeah, you're up
Barry Gee
I kill him
So you have a lot of tools at your disposal mr. Gee
I
the Seattle attack called the Polaris
Yeah, so as a magnet man or
magnetized man type of some kind you have this ability to when you attack people with either
Your fists your hands or whatever?
fists or hands or whatever
You can use charges to depolarize them. So you depolarize your cells which essentially
forces them to suffer from a various effects that happens when your cells depolarize.
So you can just do an attack and then you use one of your charges and you can either do
a muscle relaxer, which is a paralysis. You can cause blindness, you can cause diaphragm
destruction, which you sort of destroy their diaphragm. You can use all your charges and turn
the enemy into a magnetic force that attracts up to a thousand pounds of uh uh you know like a
thousand pounds of magnetic force towards them all right um i just use one charge and i paralyze him
that would be great then if you succeed on the attack he's paralyzed all right i will do that
then go for it see what you get 20 that that hits roll for damage too 14 fuck that's a very good
it
that's not bad dude um 17 you should just run away guys you guys should he's
paralyzed he's paralyzed he's paralyzed for the rest of his life for the next
six seconds so in the next round of action so you all can you realize from
the way sit down for the rest of can we flee you could certainly try yeah you
have before you I would like to try to say we're still an initiative so so
So let's resolve this with first Travis Ocelot.
He's paralyzed.
What do you want to do?
I want to check his whole person for more keys and clues.
Yeah, I think you're looking for clues in his body.
I'm doing a pat down.
Okay.
Yeah.
With that pat down.
Yeah, you have the key to his house.
You find the key to his car as well.
So you have an automobile that way.
And then you also find, which is also why that was probably a smart move, the passcode to
his...
Yeah, because we just had his thumb, which would have been hard to...
Yes, so you also found the passcode...
We almost just had his head with no passcode.
Yeah.
That would have been big.
But I guess we could have always just checked his body if he was headless.
Yeah, that's true.
But you have his passcode for his, yeah, for the rest of, for his account.
So now you have the two-factor authentication secured.
Yeah, you got both of those things.
I mean, you also get a picture of his girlfriend or something, and she's busted.
So...
Swag.
That's a shame.
I put my mouth on it.
He's like, "No!"
Paralyzed idiot.
Okay, is it my turn yet?
It's Ray William Johnson's turn.
Oh my god.
I want to run away really, really fast.
Yeah.
You just bust out of you.
You do Kool-Aid man out of the room.
Okay.
It's time.
Yeah.
Finally.
And, uh, yeah, you run out.
Yeah.
You run your full 60 feet of movement.
I'm just running as fast as I hit the 60 feet and I, I just stand
there waiting for my next turn.
Yeah, absolutely.
Okay.
You're up blow toss now.
I'm going to run away, but I'm also going to, do I see any.
police nearby. You see a number of security who are starting to get interested in this
area. Okay, as I'm running like I'm running away, but I'm also going to tell them as I
run like that paralyzed guy just tried to kill me and my friends and he needs to go
to jail. But I'm not waiting to like, find out if you convinced them or not. Yeah. Okay,
the
Sitting completely still on the ground.
I'm sitting completely still on the ground.
Yeah, I want to put the-
They look in the room and they see a Yoda.
You're not going to paralyze me.
They see a Yoda and a shiny guy both sitting completely perfectly still.
*laughs*
Um,
and uh, yeah,
I mean, they're looking in on that.
It's Patrick Yoda, it's your turn.
They see that?
Yeah, they see you and they see-
The cops see that.
You and they see you and they see you.
All right.
I see times that you don't have to say ice cream bar.
Oh, so I see it.
Oh, OK. So they're seeing it right now.
And what am I saying?
Yeah, you're saying, are you just going to stand still?
You're not going to get to move.
You should run away.
So they don't know who's the paralyzed guy.
Yeah. You're going to go to jail.
You're gonna go to jail, man.
That means, will I get interrogated?
If I go to jail.
What is... what?
Oh, you wanna bargain for an ice cream bar in the interrogation room?
*laughter*
Okay, alright.
I like this more now.
Having the deepest, like, strategy, specifically just for ice cream.
I love it, yeah.
Okay, okay.
He also somehow knew that Blowtoss was gonna say, "It's the paralyzed man."
- That's a shiny one. - Oh yeah.
Roll performance, Pat.
- 18. - Fuck!
You seem real fucking paralyzed.
And I'll tell you what,
once it's Barry Gee's turn again, he's not going to be paralyzed anymore.
So you will be the paralyzed guy.
Because he's only paralyzed for a round.
First it's his turn, he's paralyzed, it's done.
Barry Gee, it's your turn.
I mean shiny what you literally try to paralyze Patrick roll an attack roll roll depolarization
Yeah, dude, you're gonna fucking kill me you all for damage
Cool no, no, not that one. I'm gonna hit depolarize in the chat. Oh
No, no the deported. No. No hit the 25 one because that one's gonna roll for crit
it
the
Now that the cops are here, we can't leave the,
we can't leave Shiny Andrew,
'cause he's a witness to our insane robbery.
- I just had the cops roll insight into the situation
and they got a five.
So they are just looking at it and just are like,
that is a paralyzed Yoda.
- Shiny Andrew's about to resuscitate, right?
- Yeah, he's coming back.
It is now your turn, Travis.
Did you...
What are you doing?
I don't remember, I don't think I fled.
You didn't flee.
So maybe, I guess, so I'm in the room then?
I'm in the room with them?
Yeah, what did you do last turn?
Holy shit, I'm sorry.
I feel completely paralyzed.
Well, I did a pat down, but then I didn't do anything.
You did a pat down, and that was your turn, yeah.
That was your turn.
You should've expeditialized.
So you're still in there.
Oh, okay.
So I'm gonna tell the cops that I'm here to protect them.
*laughter*
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Roll- say what you're gonna say and then roll
Deception with advantage.
Woah, okay, this is, uh, really weird, but it's-
*laughter*
I'm here to, uh, fix everything.
I actually got here
because I'm the chief of police.
*laughter*
So...
Do I really have to roll for that? I feel like I kinda said-
But I can't wait.
Deception. Is that what I'm rolling?
Yeah. I mean, unless that's the truth.
Roll again.
Maybe it is the truth.
So, you know, oh, with the I mean, like you said, chief of police,
you might have had them, but chief of police are like, all right, we don't
we don't we don't know what's going on here.
We're going to we're going to just
We're going to take this paralyzed guy.
You you got to come with us, too.
We have to talk. We talk about what happened here.
All right. OK, cool.
So they take you and Patrick Yoda.
Oh, I'm going to fight. I'm not going to go.
Oh, fuck. Yeah. OK, cool.
I mean, they are just private security.
Everything in city.
There's very few public like security.
Everything is private security.
So you can certainly try to fight them.
So we'll re-roll initiative for you.
So you just roll and Barry G roll to.
Women just know you don't have to fight, you're just in the room.
So it's deciding turn order.
Oh, I go first.
Hmm, probably.
And then you roll to Travis and then I did.
Oh, oh, wait, it didn't get sent.
Okay, it says the no, I see it now was selected. Oh, it's weird. Don't ignore that. It's stupid. Don't ignore that
It's not it's important up I will so before we resolve that
Yeah blow toss and Ray you're sort of though like
You guys do see the situation going on. You see the cops sort of squaring up
On the scene you don't know
Probably that there is potentially a fight about to break out, but I wanted to see what you guys were up to
We're playing we're playing chopsticks
Yeah, we're playing chopsticks
Like the song or the game where you put each other's fingers. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. You guys want to play that out?
Okay, who's goes first how do you play chopsticks
You guys have to roll a nation to scare the worst person in Charleston.
Fuck you!
You won by knowledge.
Let's do a staring contest!
Can we roll to do a staring contest?
Yeah, constitution.
Both of you.
Wait, actually
I'm gonna use
I'm gonna use my ability that I haven't used yet
in this campaign
where I can teleport
into someone else's body and control them
for six seconds.
I'm gonna make Ray William Johnson blink instantly.
Yeah, do it.
I do it. How do I, let's see, let me see if there's something I have to do.
There is stuff with it, yes.
Where is it?
He can roll dexterity or strength against it if I'm correct about that, what I wrote for that.
the
Easy.
Okay, cool.
So we're back to the fight over here and yeah, Barry G you're
going first.
What a dematerialize and screw you away because I don't want
to be in here anymore.
Yeah, you could definitely do that.
You don't have to roll for that.
I'm paralyzed.
I'm waiting for the cops to pick me up.
So you can use slither.
So you could just basically like decompose and become sort of
semi liquid
Uh, your ac becomes 17 you have advantage on any stealth checks you do you have a climbing speed now, too
You're sort of like a puddle of of metal
uh, sort of like a a liquid metal puddle so you can sort of slide I want
Uh, both us and we will not start to complete some chopsticks
Yeah, go for it. Uh, uh, yeah, I mean roll a stealth. No, you don't have to roll stealth
I would say that if you're running by them, they're going to have opportunity attacks on you
and they're going to use them, but let's see how they do. They frankly aren't very strong.
Yeah, they both don't hit you. So you just roll, you just slide away,
use your full movement. Now you're this puddle of metal next to Ray and Blotas.
And uh, the cops are gonna go now or the private security force
They're gonna try to attack you travis since you're resisting arrest
Oh what the hell oh what the hell
Okay, cool they just both fucking with let's go you're just too strong you're too fast you're too smart it's your turn
Uh, okay. How many of them are there?
There are only two of them.
Okay, cool.
Um, I guess I'm just gonna practice my akimbo, uh, double headshot.
Yeah.
You can attack twice and shoot at each of them.
Go for it.
What do I roll?
Just attack with my gun?
Oh yeah, attack with your gun.
Okay, one of them does hit.
The 17 does hit.
Roll for damage.
Yeah, a 10 just like they're dead.
They're weak.
They're just private security cops.
You guys are a lot stronger than them.
So I like should be killing them.
Is that what you're saying?
No, not at all.
You can do whatever you want.
It's a game.
All this stuff has no repercussions.
So what?
Um, and then
so there's no repercussions.
And so, OK, and yeah, Patrick, you had a roll death saving throw.
So there's no repercussions if he does.
Well, you're succeeding, OK?
the
normal world and he tries to attack you again
that does hit you
um I thought you said I couldn't get hurt
it does three damage
awesome
all right I tried to disfigure him with my gym farm I try to
rip his thumbs off and snatch his eyeballs out and take his lips
off
OK, that would be Krav Maga 2000, right?
Right.
OK, cool.
And then damage. OK.
We'll see here. Damn.
Yeah, you don't kill him, but you do.
You know what you don't do?
You don't gouge his eyes out, but you do rip his thumbs off.
Can he he has no lips?
No lips.
OK, good.
You won't be telling anyone about what happened.
At least not using any explosive consonants.
All right.
Can I curb stomp Shiny Andrew and then leave?
I would say the the private security force, the guy at this point
is like out of commission, like he ripped his lips off.
He's freaking out.
If you want to curb stomp Tiny Andrew,
He is kind of like mobile right now and just kind of cowering so it will be tough like he's okay
Can I can I put him in my inventory?
No, no, no
All right
This sucks
Maybe give him give him a bunch of Xanax so he blacks out. That's a good
Xanax roll a strength contest against him. Okay, see if you can show Xanax in his mouth
the
Yeah, you just shoved the Xanax right in his fucking mouth.
He gets real woozy real fast.
You see the light starting to dim.
Oh, I should have done this earlier.
Yeah, and
and what do you want to do with Patrick Yoda?
I definitely put him in my inventory.
Yeah, you can just pick him up.
You can wait in the cops.
The cops are dead.
One of them is dead.
One of them is freaking out because he has no lips.
Oh, yeah.
I asked Yoda.
Do you want to go with the other cop?
He is knocked out.
the
we just saved all this time.
And yeah, I mean, I think just based on time, let's end it there.
A couple things in the air now.
You guys got away with it.
You have his thumb, you have his passcode.
So you can get his money, you can get his money, you can get his house, you can get
his car.
You can also get his credentials.
So that's two things off the list in one.
you cause a little bit trouble
uh... two things off the list
so
i have been using all pretty good
uh...
happy yeah it was a good day
west african
[outro music]
[MUSIC]