Ho ho ho!
A merry Gun City Christmas to one and all!
It's me, Santa Patches!
I'm here to bring you some holiday cheer.
I hope you have your favorite Christmas cybernetic enhancement and hot cocoa at the ready, because
today is a very special episode of gun city
because not only is it christmas
but we're on tv
hi mom
hi mrs. claus i'll see you later tonight
but first it's christmas eve
wait did you say you're gonna fuck your mom?
your mom is also technically mrs. claus
your mom's name
Mrs. Claus?
I guess that's right.
You're Santa Claus, Mrs. Claus is also your mom's name.
Oh my god, is Mrs. Claus Santa's mom the whole time?
But first, it's Christmas Eve!
Shhh!
All the good little boys and girls, and worse, are asleep.
Except for three very, very special ones.
Patrick Yoda,
Floatas Piss,
and Ray William Johnson.
Wide-eyed and breathless with excitement,
their...
Their friendship has taken them across the planet E-Bomb,
all the way to jungle-infested Earth,
into the virtual world, and even into each other's penises.
Oh yeah.
And now, they're in space!
That's right, on Leo the Collector's, I mean King Leo of New England's space station.
King Leo's Pleasure Palace, the finest space station of its kind,
a city in and of itself, and a perfect holiday getaway.
we'll get more on that though later. But now it's time for something a little
less interesting. It's time to read some Christmas story classics. Gun City
Christmas story classics. "Plotas, Ray, and Patrick each have come prepared with
their own Gun City Christmas tale to read and there are so many great ones to
choose from. Another list joke here. Okay. Risky the Ho-Man, A Christmas Carol
Baskins, that's right because Santa never forgets, and Rodolfo, the red-nosed
Latin King. And to whom will they be reading these stories? Well, they're
reading them to the greatest gift of all, a son created in a lab who is a penguin
with a water bottle jutting out of his head that holds his brain. And he's
wearing a leather jacket, I think. That's right. We should get figurines. It's New
New Sullivan!
Aw yeah!
Yeah! New Sullivan!
Woo!
Aw yeah!
In the remote village of Hoo Town by our humble three
while on an adventure searching for the fabled N-Word Pass
just so you know
he quickly became beloved by all
(laughter)
I guess I almost wrote that, right?
A college student who is also eternally four
who is also eternally four and forever silly.
There's no one more fun and more awesome than New Sullivan.
Forever silly.
Oh, would you look at the time.
I better get going.
I have to fly all over earth except for Syria to hand out toys to good little boys and girls.
Why don't you spend some time with our heroes on a relaxing low-key holiday adventure in
in a cozy Christmas hotel room,
probably just what you need during your stressful,
anxious, and very lonely holiday.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Yeah, so you guys are in a hotel room,
you're chillin' with New Sullivan.
New Sullivan is going like, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going like, he's really happy.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, Sullivan, go, Sullivan, go, Sullivan.
Doing a head spin in the water bottle.
Sullivan, come hit this, it's crack.
Okay.
And he starts waddling over.
It's a crack pipe.
I'm crying.
From Earth.
Yeah, I'm crying.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
I love him so--
I wish he was real so bad.
Yeah, I guess he takes a hit of the crack pipe.
It doesn't really affect it.
It makes you better at doing head spins.
At dancing.
Go Sullivan.
Go, go Sullivan.
He's doing like a little side to side.
He's trying to work it into a head spin.
And then that crack hits.
And what does he do?
He head spins even better.
Holy crap.
- Oh, it's true.
- So yeah, you guys--
- It makes you better at head spinning.
- You guys have just started cheering on New Sullivan
while he's doing his little dances.
You guys--
- That's all, let's do the wave right now.
- What presents, what, but do you guys
get presents for New Sullivan?
He doesn't have to know yet.
You shouldn't tell him, obviously.
It's Christmas Eve.
- Yeah, I got a present for him.
- Yeah, what'd you get him?
- I got him a gift card.
- Oh, okay.
- He's kinda lost. - He's kinda lost to where?
- I got him a gift card to Target.
- Okay, yeah, he'll love that, actually.
- That sounds fine.
I can't go wrong with a gift card to Target.
No.
I got him a sous vide.
A sous vide?
Yeah.
It's $350.
Above and beyond this fucking--
Yep, I got you a sous vide.
I don't know if you know how to cook or anything,
but I fucking hope you know.
I really, I really fucking hope you know how to cook.
I get a little--
I spent-- I went a little bit out of my budget this Christmas.
And I'm really fucking hurting right now.
He's picking up on none of it.
He's like, "Yeah, yeah."
- I get a little bit self-conscious
about my gift card gifts.
- So the gift card, that's part of your gift,
but the rest of it's actually in the mail right now,
and it'll be here soon.
- I got him a sweater that you guys have seen me wear
like a hundred times before,
and you're thinking like,
"Oh my, he's giving him a sweater that he already owns.
"That's a lame gift."
And then I'm like, "Look, Sullivan,
"I got us matching sweaters."
And I actually got him a brand new one
of the one that I always wear.
- Oh my God, that's so fucking awesome.
I take out the one I always wear and I put it on I was really fucking hoping one of you
I was really fucking hoping one of you got a I don't know like a vacuum sealer. Oh, I got that too
Yeah, I also got him a vacuum sealer thank Christ because you can't really use it without that vacuum sealer so yeah
He's fuck. He's uh he goes over to his little play area
He has his three favorite toys with him which are all action figures of you guys
- Aw.
- And he's going like, "A la la, a la la."
He doesn't know what you guys sound like.
- Guys, he's singing our song!
- He's singing our song!
- Yeah, and he's having a good time.
- A la la la, a la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
- He turns around, he starts smiling,
he's like so happy to see you guys doing it back.
What are you guys, do you guys have any food around?
- I just cherish him.
- What are you guys eating?
- I'm eating his little button nose.
- Mum mum mum mum mum.
- I'm snacking on some doubled eggs.
- What the hell's a doubled egg?
- It's from the future.
- Oh fuck.
- It's a deviled egg that has a--
- No, I don't break my brain if I hear what it is.
- Alright, it has a deviled egg filling.
- It's an egg from the future.
- What about you, do you have a deviled egg?
- No, I'm just smoking crack.
- Okay, so yeah, this is all it goes,
he kinda like tugs at your, like,
asking for the deviled egg or one deviled egg.
- He's saying up.
- Okay, I throw him up in the air.
- Ah!
- And I catch him, and then I throw an egg up in the air
And then I throw an egg up in the air and I hold him out.
Does he catch the egg?
We roll actually to see if I'm staring at Sullivan like the
straight drop video.
Something about doubled eggs is they have a special type of
gravity where they can be caught by anybody.
Yeah, he rolls.
We rolled well.
He rolled fight.
And then we should be clear when we should be saying new
Sullivan.
Yeah.
Yeah, because the other we don't want to talk about.
Yeah, we don't want to confuse.
Yeah, I gave old Sullivan a hit of the crack pipe and he is
terrified.
He's not here.
Yeah, he's not here.
No, no, you guys.
You guys parted ways.
- Yeah, we haven't seen him in fucking forever.
- I should have read up on the lore.
- I should honestly make the lore available,
I feel like, to you guys.
But anyway, so yeah.
- Somebody should make a wiki.
- It was made, it was made,
and then it was updated a little bit,
then I think it got deleted.
- Somebody should not have deleted it
so that I would have a resource.
- Yeah, 'cause I'm not good at providing information.
- I ate one double dig.
- Okay, well, New Solvent ate 15.
So New Solving goes over and he starts like,
(chewing)
he starts eating them, he takes another hit
of the crack pipe, he's like, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Makes him able to eat more food.
- Yeah, oh yeah, and he has more of it.
And then he sort of like lays back, he's like,
(groaning)
- I look at him, I just go--
- What's wrong, little buddy?
- I look at him and I'm paranoid as shit.
- He's got a-- - Got my hand on the wall.
I'm like, stop it.
- Tommy.
And he goes, he takes his three favorite toys,
He puts them away in his little basket and he says, "Goodnight."
And he goes over to the bathroom.
He knows how to say goodnight.
That's cute.
That made me not scared of crap anymore.
I'm gonna smoke some more.
And when he goes, he goes over to the bathroom and, um...
What he does, you just, uh...
You feel a chill in the air.
And the lights flicker, just slightly at first, and then...
Total darkness.
So it goes, it's Kurt Vonnegut.
The arity bomb, drained of all its color and verve,
save the apolescent eyesore that is a one-gun city.
From up here on King Leo Space Station,
it's a smoky mess of nauseous light,
artificial to its silicone bones and ugliness
in its hot plastic guts.
But up here, things are new, too.
Shiny, still derelict, still made from the recycled parts
of ancient attempts at similar space stations, but new.
You'd think the trouble wouldn't follow any of us up here,
but I'm telling you this tale from beyond the grave.
There's a killer on this space station,
and they go by playtime.
They usually look for childless couples.
They usually wait for one of the freak outages that occur
on the space station.
They usually slit their throats,
and when the lights come back,
They've usually left atop each victim's corpse their favorite toy.
Could be a new video game, an action figure, a sex toy, hell it could be a book.
They somehow know, Playtime always knows what your favorite toy is.
What was my favorite toy?
Well I wasn't killed by Playtime, there was a bit of popcorn kernel stuck between my teeth
and I was really digging in there trying to get it out and so my elbow hit the airlock
and I took about a hundred people with me
into the cold, inky blackness of space.
[laughing]
I really liked Crazybones, though, if you want to know.
Now, playtime, he always kills his victims,
but he didn't this time.
Well, we don't think he did.
But New Sullivan is gone.
No!
Goddamn.
Snatched from his hotel room
during an idyllic Christmas Eve
with his adoptive parents and uncle.
They thought they were out of the game, Blotas, Ray, and Patrick.
They haven't solved a case in years.
Actually, they've done several B&Es since then.
But up here, things are new, shiny, still degenerate, still made from the recycled parts of ancient
attempts at being funny, but still new.
And the trouble followed them up here, too.
So maybe it's time to don the hats and silly voices.
In the D20s.
time for gun city a broad city playtime continue fun that's good that is really
good Wow listen late time continue fun yeah no you have to go you have to keep
there so badass yeah it's gonna just be a like Bill Hicks right now yeah I feel
like I feel like the white Bill Hicks you do look exactly the leather jacket yeah
where'd you get that yeah so you guys have been in your hotel room on Leo's
pleasure palace for days months actually completely despondent okay yeah sorry
Sorry. So you guys have been in your hotel room for months, completely despondent after
New Sullivan's disappearance. Oh, we did a flash forward. Oh yeah, we're flash forward.
Oh my god. Okay. Did I miss my birthday? When is Ray William Johnson's birthday? It's my
birthday. Okay, you didn't miss your birthday. When is my birthday? Your birthday is in April
sometime but I don't remember what day. What's the date though? I just told, I don't remember
the date I'm sorry. Alright. So I know the date.
12th? 10th?
You're gonna do every single number?
17th right?
Real friend. I knew that too.
I knew that because I used to have a Paul Blart Mall Cop 2 poster.
You should know that because I didn't memorize.
I'm a very close friend of yours.
No that's why. Because in my head when I think of you I think of Paul Blart.
April 17th 2007.
2007. I wish. I wish I was 15. Well anyway so uh... Christmas went by without a thought
in your head, New Years, even Martin Luther King Day didn't register. Probably because
he's been dead for many years. Probably thousands of years. 300 roughly. 300, okay. But awaking,
Awaking from your comatose state in this decidedly not holiday themed campaign, you have found
a resolve to find playtime, stop his grisly murders, and most importantly, recover your
beloved son, New Sullivan, and nephew.
Heard that.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
My nephew?
Your nephew, yeah.
They're the parents.
You're the uncle.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, I remember this now.
I paid off all my debts.
Mom, dad.
Yeah.
Or does this take place before?
So okay this falls canonically after this is after the heist so you paid off your debts
Yeah, you guys were just here to celebrate Christmas. You were you did your one last job
You solved your one last case did your one last so we're technically you thought you were done with all hiding
No, no, no. No. I thought we were in hiding away. I'll explain at the end of the campaign, okay
Yeah, tell me more of the lore
I need to know the space station of pleasure palace was erected a few months after you'd helped Leo the collector locate the temple of
to Penguin of Doom and complete his epic toy collection with the N-Gage.
He first invaded Sky Ireland and turned the leprechauns into his slaves, then used them
along with his royal guard to continue invading the numerous sky islands that exist above
Gunn City and Planet E-Bomb. He had declared himself King of the Skies and struck a treaty
with Gunn City, including both the government and the oligarchical board controlled primarily
by Papi Chuko's Technoslime Corporation.
The relationship between King Leo and the city is contentious, but if they were ever
or go to war, there'd be destruction, you know, all this,
you know, they don't wanna do it.
So they have proxy battles,
and they have a sort of healthy, unhealthy relationship
kind of. - Okay.
- Yeah.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- I don't have a drink. - Do you want one?
- Yeah, I'll have a drink.
Yeah, thank you, man.
- All right.
Continue, proxy battles? - Oh yeah, yes, absolutely.
- Wait, now we gotta-- - We gotta do the cheers again.
- Okay, cheers. - Oh yeah, hold on, cheers.
- Wait, can we get the toy cam?
- Can you get the toy cam?
- Cheers. - Lower.
Where do I should go?
the Dungeons and Dragons
That's not right it's not be fitting and it's not right. I'm sorry all right anyway um oh
Yeah, so all this is say that after Leo had carved a significant enough portion of the land above for himself
if he took to space, where he could finally create his pleasure palace and include all
the toys Leo the Collector, before he was King Leo, has ever collected and wishes to be enjoyed
by all for an astronomical fee, political favor, or blackmail.
Or in the rare case of you three, a combination of a sizable chunk of change you got from
your heist, but overall at a discount because Leo actually kinda likes you guys.
Though since he's become king, you can't really get in touch with him.
He's sort of doing his own thing.
Ghoster.
A little bit.
around in the future. Ghosting. Thought they'd have abolished it by then.
Me too. I thought it would have been criminally punished by death. Or worse.
We'll talk through what's in the Pleasure Palace as we explore it. Right now you guys
are in your hotel room in the resort, the Ten Seasons. There's ten seasons on Planet
Yvonne. Okay, list them. Winter, spring, summer, fall, salt, pepper, paprika. He knows. And
And then cumin and monsoon season. Those are the 10. I thought about this.
God, he's good.
Wow. Yeah. So yeah, you guys are in your hotel room. Well, let's see where you guys are, actually.
Okay.
Sorry for anyone who's listening. Go to patreon.com and check out a video from us.
Uh-huh. Because I made my own character.
That's right. Start over here.
He did. I checked that out, if you can even see it. It's so small. Put that up to the
camera. That's right, it looks beautiful. Holy crap. Patrick Yoda, I made him out of my old
Mike Winscreen and a Grogu that I bought. Did you? Wait, you dressed like him today? Yeah,
I did. On purpose. On purpose. Wow. Whoa, look. Oh my god, I didn't even process that. Holy crap.
Patrick did something so high effort. That's incredible. Yep. This is unreal. I put so much,
I have so much super glue stuck to my fingers. He got an outfit. Wow, I'm proud of you, man.
I build all this yeah, and I wore a costume
Okay cool, so we got we got Patrick you know where is he yeah, so wait
Yeah, so this is this this what's right now right now for you guys. You know this whole area is just your room
This is just your room
It's basically like the it's like the holodeck so we have to just say whatever oh whoa something on it
I'll add some shit here, isn't your bed?
Okay.
Impressor.
Whoa. Hold on.
Yeah, raid your room. Let's do some Sims.
Whoa, this is sick.
I never thought that this would happen.
What else do you guys want?
It's your fucking room.
Okay, so this is my corner.
Yeah, you're in the barracks.
That's yours, and then that's Cameron's.
Whatever we're doing now, this is gonna...
is
I don't want anything though. I don't want anything.
Yeah, you guys have like a suite.
Yeah, that's what your computer. You're like Odo from Deep Space Nine.
You're like a demon with a computer in your back.
This is my stuff.
Do you have to do stuff for your demon though?
I don't know. Let me see him.
I haven't even seen my character.
Where is your character?
I mean, I thought we were going in order.
Alright, so let's go to Blotoss.
Okay, Blotoss.
Pull your guy out.
So this is, I actually, well I went to the store today to get my guy.
and I actually was able to find, I didn't know, think that I would be able to find this, but I actually found an officially licensed US Army Grinch Hunter figurine.
Whoa!
You can see he has the little, he has a who knows and who whiskers and his gun says Grinch Gun on it, which I thought was crazy because that's the name of my character's gun.
It's kind of amazing.
It's really cool too, I mean, I just, I'm really happy.
Put up to the wide, yeah.
I'm pretty happy with this toy that I was able to find at the store.
Yeah, it was a Dollar Tree.
Wow!
And as you can see, there's even a look at that holographic sticker says official licensee.
Yeah, this is just like I was right you got that for a dollar and this was a dollar. Yeah
So, how are you gonna fit that motherfucker in that little ass my guys big?
That's a yeah, that's the size of a Yoda. This is the size of a guy. Yeah, come on. I'll take that. Come on now
But I want out while I was at the store - we also fast and loose a bit with the sizes
Yeah, well as we'll soon learn through you were at the so you just got everything in Dollar Tree you what else did you get?
there yeah well I just got two things I got one toy for myself but I knew Caleb
was busy building all this stuff so I decided to get him a toy for his it's so
kind of you yeah I just want to say one thing before you go any further I was in
Manhattan for three hours looking for that and I was in Dollar Tree for four
hours deciding what DVDs to buy and I actually didn't buy any they do have
some really good ones but I did get Kayla I couldn't find cold I couldn't
find a reverse cold. They don't have any computer demons. So I did. I found the
next best thing for you. So this is going to be your character. That's ballet
Peppa. You know what my character is? That's Peppa the ballet dancer. But my
character's I have I brought a whole I brought a whole set of like, well, we
Showed this one so this one is I mean
I showed you all the ones that I brought earlier dressed out
I was thinking about all that I can't even hold it. I was thinking about all the different shit
I was thinking about how to make him look super cool
Come on. I had others showing you all of the no you know what hey camera mine also comes with a motorcycle
Mine, maybe because I haven't getting to talk about this at all mine actually has a music system
We will it's got a music boom box, okay, so Peppa Pig
Maybe is actually kind of cool, and also I have guns you can have that I just recently got can I have some you can have?
this one
But basically
Ray William Johnson will be like around here. Yeah, I would say that's kind of his sweet
I have that pistol and that's your sweet, so this is the
Kitchen bathroom, we'll have the front door
I'm not done hold on kitchen
in
matter
unboxing video. This is cute. This is very cute. Okay. My room's all set up. I really
like your room. Thank you. This is my computer, my secondary computer and this, and this is
my monitor. And so I go over here and I do technological hacking against my enemies.
So, and my guys in his motorcycle hanger.
Here's your gun.
Don't forget your gun, dude.
Here, can you zoom in on that camera just a little bit?
This one? Yeah.
Is the super glue over there also?
I'm not giving you super glue
while we have a live recording.
Okay.
I could have just super glued all of our guns into the hands, but...
No, you wouldn't be able to do that.
Yeah, we'll do that later.
You don't have to be too close with it, Kim.
Alright, the gun,
and
barely even get up. Yeah and so and so finally we're all we're all so sad.
I haven't heard your voices in a while we have a little
conversation. Let me hear that.
Fuck. I'm so fucking depressed. I hate my life. And then your voice sounds like...
Uh, my face is in the ground.
*Mimics the sound of a dog barking*
I'm- I'm going-
Knock, knock, knock at the front door.
Who- who is it?
Who's there?
Fuck off!
Hello sirs.
Uh, here are the towels you requested.
Uh- Oh, what's up butler?
Inside of which- no, I'm just-
just a person who works at the hotel
uh... that's not what i want to know
it's called
it's just a few times a week
canada
all right
we won't
you're going to do it though you know you should look at the issue it play with
the
help the way God made me sir. God didn't make that. He's got, he's got scoliosis. True. You
don't remember that about him? No. I don't either. I don't even remember who that is.
I don't remember the last couple of fucking months. I'm just one of the attendants at
the hotel, not an important character. That's Mr. Attendant. Mr. Attendant is my name, how
did you know? Because I have a good relationship with you. That's right, we do have a good
relationship. Rub my back. How far back do, okay just rubbing your back. I paid you to
rub my back and my thighs. You know I do that for free, you don't have to pay him. I pay
him because he's good at it. Here are your towels you requested along with the various
candy treats you wanted inside of them. I also have a message from a one Belinda Crokes.
She works for the king so I'd take a look if I were you. He presents a small UMD cartridge
which projects the image of a
a royal guard member of Leo's Royal Guard
(laughter)
okay what does he look like?
he looks sorta like this.
but he's also decked out. He looks like a pop star. He's got a space marine armor. Is this our Roblox guy?
yeah it is. Oh wow.
all of all of her uh... leo's royal guardia roblox guys
while some of them will be other kinds of guys but that's the main kind of guard
on a new type of guy roblox type
and i know that
sunday greetings belit belinda croaks head attendant of the king of the leo
the magnificent has requested an audience with patrick you know the
blowtoss piece in ray william johnson
she says it is urgent and she'd have you come to the world district immediately
he uh... the u_n_ deep
slots out like she said
three tickets and uh... like like uh... they're made up like let me grab that
metal
these should allow you to
these should allow you have a lot of friends
to the royal
to the royal district on the city loop
uh... the city loop trains so
just come straight away and all that
I didn't decide if he was British or not.
This will now self-destruct and it explodes.
The guy explodes?
Well, the UMD cartridge he was coming out of.
Oh!
Oops, I shot it!
That's why it exploded.
So you guys have been summoned by Belinda Crokes, who's the head attendant to the king,
about an urgent matter.
So if you guys want to start going there, because that's kind of a wrap.
Even if Belinda Crokes tells me to do it.
Oh!
I don't fucking care.
I should put this gun to my head
and pull the trigger and kill me.
[Laughter]
You should line it up so it shoots me in the fucking head too.
Okay, let's line it up and kill all three of us with a single bullet, guys.
So who... so you have the Grinch gun, so if you want to roll an attack roll...
Oh, and I fell down.
Oh.
Stand up straight, you fucking hammerhead.
I'm so drunk because of my painful depression.
I hear another knock at the door.
Oh, I'm saved!
Hello?
Hi, I'm the guard from before.
Oh, okay.
Could you please-
Wait, if you were here, why did you use the UMD thing?
I thought it would look cool.
I really did.
I thought it would be sort of like, "Who's that?"
What do you want?
I really do need you to come-
Well-
Okay, we'll go.
I'll explain.
Hold on.
It's concerning playtime, the killer who stole away your boy.
Why are you saying that?
So at least have a little bit of- How do you already know that he did that?
The king knows many things.
So he knows who playtime is.
No, no.
I feel like there's supposed to be a hole in the story already.
No, no, this is a whole issue.
This is a larger- Yeah, there's a whole issue.
There's a hole in the plot.
No, no, well, there might be.
I haven't finished it yet, so we'll find out together.
Guys, I can't stop falling over.
Okay, here's what we'll do.
Oh my god, Bluetoss has the Grinch gun to his fucking head.
No, Bluetoss, don't do it.
What?
Don't shoot yourself, please.
Oh my god, this space station must be zero gravity, we're all so clumsy.
Oh my god, we're so clumsy.
Okay let's go.
Alright, let's go.
Let's keep going.
Alright, can we clear this out?
Yeah, we do that. Yeah, strike it wait. Okay, so I didn't mean my fucking cool shit. I was bringing with me to wherever we're going
This is the stage. Yeah, that's how you get around. Oh, do you have nothing I have lots of things don't
so King Leo's Pleasure Palace Space Station
Is the single largest man-made entity ever launched into space roughly the size of gun cities Lockheed District
It has a slick, U-shaped design that billows at the ends and constricts in the center.
The dark, glossy outer layer in the blackness of space, those yellows and reds are the docking bay lights,
remind the station of its shape.
The many massive windows that line the thing help give residents the greatest view known to any living creature
of Ferry E-Bomb and of the universe itself.
There has never been a project like this since the earliest expeditions from Earth to E-bombs
from 300 years prior.
There's many areas.
You guys are in the resort area right now, as I said, the Ten Seasons, which is in the
middle.
On either side of you now is New Gun City, to the north, and to your south of the resort
is Newer Gun City.
You'll be going towards New Gun City to get to the Royal District, which is at the very
top of the space station.
Further in from the space station is Leo's Thunderland, which is his massive arcade mall
amusement park connected by a series of jungle gym-like obstacles, which acts as both a museum
dedicated to Leo's finest toys and an amusement center for all visitors.
Then there's the station's operations, the crew quarters, the leprechaun slave quarters,
a number of other locations which we will all uncover together throughout this adventure.
uh...
are you have so that's great
bringing that one back so i've been bringing it back to just the way
uh... wait
as you guys entered the uh... main resort area
uh... is a beautiful
uh... it's a beautiful resort although one one of these days of the scribe it
to you
uh... i have i have a description renaissance i've been insisting too much
uh... so
uh... you see a familiar face approach you
it's john carlo the bullfrog
all
you guys are in its john g_m_ yes
and as per the domains frog and
you guys remember john carlo the bullfrog from the
of
very
interesting.
I
think
it's
a
very
interesting
story.
I
think
it's
a
very
interesting
story.
I
think
it's
a
very
interesting
story.
I
think
it's
a
very
interesting
face right now. It's pretty Dwight of you. God, my hand looks old. So yeah, John Carlo
the Bullfrog comes up to you and he says, "How are you?" With that face he's John Krasinski
the Bullfrog. "Oh my goodness, Patrick, Blotas, Ray, it's been so long. How you guys doing?"
I don't remember if that was your voice. It was basically my voice. Okay. "We're doing
pretty good. We all tried to kill ourselves with one bullet about 90 seconds ago." I'm
so sorry the last the last thing we're doing that but we stopped so that means
we're doing but we stopped because we thought that we went to a different room
yeah distracted over fell over again a lot of a lot of the people on this ship
what's all it over what's the deal with this shit man I think they're still
working out the king put up a wet floor sign in the very least Jesus Christ is
Is it that the floor is wet?
I don't know.
Probably.
I've been meaning to talk to you guys.
I came up here about a week ago.
I figured something out.
What's up?
What's going on Patrick?
This better be worth it.
Okay, that was not worth it at all.
Now you won't tip over.
You can move that thing.
As you guys may know, I am now CEO of Papi Chuko's Techno Slime.
So thanks for killing the other guy.
Oh yeah, we did it for you.
Really?
Pay up.
Let's have the first roll of the campaign with the deception check.
I forgot this isn't an action figure.
Not yet.
Playtime.
It really feels so crazy to me.
We're gonna give it like three sessions until it just becomes an action figure.
The second we started doing the character voices and also doing this, I was like, oh
no.
I don't know if dice are gonna make it that much longer.
Okay, that's a 16, deception.
Okay, he's like, wow, I can't believe you did that for me.
and
Hold on, wait, I can pick it up.
Did you drop your new phone?
Hold on.
[LAUGHTER]
OK, wait, hold up.
Here, make sure you hold on to that.
So anyway, while you're putting your feet in my zone--
[LAUGHTER]
I'm sorry, I just slipped.
I'll get up in a second.
This guy's comfortable.
That's no problem.
We slip all the time on this ship.
So anyway, I have to thank you for that.
But the other thing is, if you're ever
looking for any extra cash I can always use guys like you real the guys of the
makings to be corporate agents so you ever need me you can find me here at the
resort I wasn't invited
I'm
that is a game changer
that is pretty fucking cool
that's yours now
yeah
yeah yeah I'll take that
yeah I guess that's
that's basically
that's the computer
yeah that's the computer
that's the demon
alright yeah
cool yeah
here wait
oh man that is a game changer
they don't
wow
nope
okay Pat
my thing was cooler
yep Pat you're making it too much about toys
that's not bad
we'll take it
no mine was cooler
oh yes well
alright
so anyway he says if you're ever looking for that kind of work
while you're on board here. You let me know. I wasn't invited to the uh...
Oh shit. Sorry.
Oh my god, you just chopped that guy in half.
Oh my god, another one of his victims!
What the fuck is going on?
Another one of Playdate's victims!
Wait, I'll stand up and sort this out.
Really? Yeah.
Oh no!
Whoa, what's going on over there?
Y'all are acting crazy. Turn out a little bit though.
Anyway, if you ever need- I guess I don't know how this happened, but
if you ever need any extra money, you know I'll be here at the resort.
I wasn't invited to the Royal District, despite my status as a-
Can you please- What are you doing to my leg?
Leave me alone!
Please no longer mount me.
But yeah, that's all I kind of wanted to say.
Also, my cousin is here, by the way.
He's definitely been looking for you guys.
Oh yeah, weren't you cousins with like a puddle of piss from a puppy?
Wait, is he dead in this world or no?
That's the other one.
Oh, fuck.
I don't think so, yeah.
And you guys see--
Wait, that means we could kill him.
On the Schlitterbahn water slide repurposed
by Leo the Collector, part of his collection of toys,
which he has sort of like a high concept understanding of that,
you hear a familiar--
[GROANING]
Oh, no.
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck on the slide.
Show us the vitrine.
And then a really fat guy slides down the slide and just knocks him out into the pool.
And he goes, "I'm splashed!"
"I'm splashed!"
Oh my god, dude.
He's so small!
That's Solomon.
That's Ludiculo.
Hi! Hello!
Look how small he is even compared to Patrick Yoda.
Well thank god, because I was about to have a complex if Sullivan was bigger than my character.
Hey you guys!
Hey!
It's been a while.
We did the heist, remember?
Okay.
Sort of like old times.
Only worse.
Okay.
I'm just not, I'm gonna, this is not canon.
I'm gonna put you in a canon.
How'd you get on this ship?
Well, John Carlo invited me.
That's your cousin?
Yeah, wait, how are you two related?
He's suave.
Yeah, I mean, uh...
Well, you know, uh...
Cousins come in all different shapes and...
Yeah, I can't deny that.
[laughter]
Cousins do come in all different shapes.
I got some nicely cousins.
Well, anyway, I know Sol is...
I'm gonna leave you guys...
of
Like good Sullivan, yeah, is it your name is yours turd or something? Yeah, it's dirt right? It was crud
You got it on crud. I think it was crud and then dirt and then nothing
Yeah, it was nothing when I was relistening to the older episodes to make sure there was a lot of fun sort of oh yeah
Did you guys hear something? No, I heard nothing. It was good
Okay. Well, you're back to being nothing. That's just reminded us how funny it was. No, it was
It hurt a lot, but it was pretty funny. Okay, now I missed you guys get on this block. Okay, guess what?
That's the gay block
You just stood on the gay block
You just got back on it why'd you get back on it? I don't seem like the right thing to do. Oh
You are so stupid. I missed you. Okay, Stan now stand on this block
Okay, well, can I just know what kind of- can I know what kind of block this is?
It's not the gay block.
No, it's not- well, obviously you can only-
In the camera?
You can only have one gay block, obviously.
It's not, though, it's not that gay block.
Are you familiar with Lucy and the Football?
What?
Shut up.
Why'd you get on the other gay block?
Bro just stood on the lesbian block.
Oh my god.
He's a lesbian.
It's particularly it stings you are so so stupid
Okay, so why are you here? No? I was just here cuz John Carlo invited me. It's like a fun vacation
It sounds fun our son died
New find that was dead. I'm sorry. We're gone at the very lane. Oh, no was it by or he's still alive
I can't really tell play time
Yes, it was my plate knows the other serial killer. Yes, it's play time. Oh, yeah
There's other okay. Well killers. Well. There are other things going on
I mean there's been monsters escaping from the guts of the ship, and it's been all kinds of stuff going on
Oh, yeah, you guys will learn that as we travel. I guess it makes it together
We were as we are three months right yeah, you were we are gonna travel together, right?
I mean we will travel and I guess you'll know
Help I can still see him through your legs
gang is back together. It's a lot more. Yeah. Do you remember these characters?
Isn't this exactly how you always imagined them?
This one probably.
And our new friend, Bikie.
Oh yeah, by the way, Sullivan, or nothing. This is our new friend, Bikie.
He's so cool. He's so cool. He's cool as fuck.
I'm
Bikey is tired and doesn't want to be played with right now guys.
Yeah.
Bikey needs to take a break so that we don't hurt Bikey.
Okay, so what should we do?
I think you guys should head towards the Royal District.
That's a good idea.
And see what Belinda Crokes has to say.
Okay.
Yep, I'm down.
I'm hella down.
There's a universe A and a universe B, so they don't know each other.
Hey, I'm gonna be real with you, no one's ever listened to that.
A lot of people have.
No, I don't think so.
I think nobody even knows that shit exists.
Universe A, universe B.
I'm looking at you.
A, be normal.
Nerd.
Yep.
A, B.
A, be normal and let's see what D Belinda Crokes has to C.
Let's see Belinda Crokes double D's.
Okay.
F yeah.
E.
So you guys leave the resort and go on your way.
I'm glad we left the resort.
I, for one,
think we should
keep leaving the resort.
Leaving the resort, you follow a path that circles
around a semi-holographic
statue of Leo the Collector,
dressed in his new metal finest,
kneeling before another statue of King Leo.
Standing tall and proud, dressed in a sleek
form-fitting suit, black and metallic,
rather than his usual dirty, high-luxury
brand trench coat. His head now
adorned with a thin gold crown, his hair
now cropped neatly in the fashion of the time, rather than a dangling collection of dreads.
It is Leo passing the torch of his former... What are you doing?
Just keep talking.
Just keep talking. Life is an eccentric collector into that of a king.
Along the path of the familiar...
Along the... Okay, alright.
Okay, this is a little... You know, I don't really want people to know how clean or not clean my teeth are.
Oh!
As you get nearer...
Nope, I'm skipping parts because I'm getting distracted by the camera.
Along the path of familiar dingy glow...
Dingy glow... Dingy.
Dingy.
Dingy dingy.
Dingy glow of Gun City's staple techno-slime neon
grows sharper and more dominant as you approach new Gun City.
Now you're leaving the resort, you're walking towards new Gun City.
The stars you'd normally see out of the massive windows atop the ship
that line the Pleasure Palace grow dimmer,
as Technoslime's unique qualities suck the character out of nearly everything.
As you get nearer, the similarities stop.
While Technoslime powers a city, it doesn't have the haphazard architecture
and urban planning of a city at the whim of the market.
Rather, it looks like the Gun City by way of Gadsville,
a centrally planned autocratic vision for what Gun City could be.
White buildings made of a super-hard plastic and unusual metal,
sections of which seem fitted together by dark grey interlocking edges which meet to
form from any regular distance cool black lines that run along the structures like traces
on a circuit board.
A faint prismatic rotation of technoslime glow emanates from these interlocking edges suggesting
some kind of chemically powered architecture.
The path beneath you, or sorry before you, is made of some kind of asphalt, but as an
adbot flies by it tells you that it is not asphalt but a synthetic material meant specifically
to prevent cronation and make walking in New Gun City like a dream.
So it says. So on top of a few of these buildings is the flag of New England,
which is King Leo's New England, which is what looks like the United Kingdom flag,
but they swapped the blue for the green and the red for the black. United Kingdom flag.
Is there a name for it? What is it? Does it have a name? Why do you know that, huh? Union Jack. It's called Union Jack. Shut the fuck up.
Bro's a punk. You should probably not know that. Fake punk. The Union Jack! The Union Jack!
Yeah, exactly I was trying to make sure that this storyline is punk rock mostly humanoids walk the streets here
We're gonna have to figure this out one day here. They are walking the street
Cultural differences how people walk up here. I mean they can't beat him join them
Oh, yeah, and the and Leo's Royal Guard and the occasional Mecca Brit
Which is these guys?
Who are piloted by Leo's guards?
There's storefronts, residential buildings, yadda yadda yadda.
If you guys want to shop, you can. There's food here, you can buy more techno-slime refills if you want to.
But anything that's really that relevant to your adventuring needs,
where you'd want to spend money on, say, upgrades to your weaponry or new...
What are you eating?
That's going to be here at night, or it's going to be in New Orgun City.
No, that's fine, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
Oh, just...
Please ignore him.
The camera didn't cut to me. You don't have to know.
I'm not used to this. This is my first video.
That's true.
It's Patrick's first time playing with toys.
And I'm having the best time of my life.
I really, I did
have a serious moment of panic
about two minutes in when I realized that we
will now be doing D&D
with toys in front of Patrick
the entire time.
It really,
it really is scary. Check out what I did for Cam.
You gave him, you see
like right there, you pointed it at me.
I can see already.
He has cake in his hand.
So I'm just sorry if you're listening to this at work.
I just realized how much crap you're probably missing.
Yeah, you gotta watch it on your iPod.
It sounds like a wagy to me.
I think, you know what, Patches, I believe in you and I think we can strike a perfect
balance.
I think you're right.
I think I can do that.
So if you guys want to...
So yeah, you guys are in the new gun city.
You guys are probably going to be looking for the Zippy Loop Station.
Yeah, I mean that's basically it.
You guys can head right there, you can go to some shops, you can talk to some of the people
in the crowd here.
This is really meant to be a space for entertainment.
What is that lady doing in the crowd?
You can't do that in public.
That's not your...
Hey, that's not a sharpener.
Is this a character?
It's me, Pencely!
Oh, well bye.
Get him out of here.
Oh my god, he's infinite.
Jesus Christ.
Wait, that was mine.
Good.
I'm glad I threw it away.
I'm sorry I'm full of these.
Let's go to the Zippy Loop.
Yeah, let's go to the Zippy Loop.
So you guys go to the Zippy Loop train.
It's a system that will easily and quickly transport you to each part of the space station
as we play through the campaign.
You guys will get familiar with the Zippy Loop as long as you have the proper credentials.
As it stands, you can use the Zippy Loop to get to the station.
It's a system that will easily and quickly transport you to each part of the space station
as we play through the campaign.
You guys will get familiar with the Zippy Loop as long as you have the proper credentials.
Zippy Loop Train is a system that will easily and quickly transport you to each part of the
space station as we play through the campaign.
You guys will get familiar with the Zippy Loop as long as you have the proper credentials.
As it stands, you were just granted access to the Royal District, which very few of the
tourists who are here on the Pleasure Palace are able to do.
You can still go to New Gun City, Newer Gun City, the Resort, and Thunderland right now.
You might get access to the Command Center later if you want to go talk to the Captain
the ship. The train itself resembles a small chain of capsules you would use to
take for depression or anxiety. Each capsule is meant to hold 15 people at its
maximum. There are comfy seats that line each car to assure maximum comfort for
those who ride in it and most importantly no leprechauns allowed. You can flash
your Royal District Pass and ride in the appropriate capsule which you know you
guys can do that. You do that. You're on the capsule now let's move this. Oh my
Let's get you guys seated.
I want to get some rolls in.
Yeah, we're going to do that. Oh, it's coming up now.
I already did a roll, so I'm pretty much set for the rest of it.
So you guys can take the rest of the rolls.
Thank you! That's very actually fun.
Arrange the guys where they're sitting.
Where are you guys sitting inside this capsule?
Here are some of the passengers who are sitting here.
I'm sitting on this guy's lap.
I am a serious fucking hoe for attention,
so I'm going to stand opposite,
looking at everybody.
everybody basically on a stage and I will you know what I'm doing ballet up there
as well but not because I have a ballet character it's because my character Ray
William Johnson is re has it's how he's coping with this death of his son
there's a new ballet program you download all right why don't you do a
performance check you want some rolls yeah I want to yeah now we're talking
in
My performance is...
I forgot how to do D.
So look at...
The skills, there should be a number next to the word "performance".
I add that?
Yep.
But these look way too high.
Oh, you guys are a much higher level than all your other characters in this.
What number are you adding?
Three.
That's too high?
That's not that high.
For me.
One of them is nine.
That's so high.
Investigation.
You have really high intelligence.
And tech savvy!
You have really high intelligence and you're proficient in both.
Okay, then I have an 18 so I do an amazing job
I probably do though if people in the audience or the audience people on the cams or clapping for you
I lay at first normal ballet
Then I go then I come over here
My god
(laughter)
Yeah, wait, roll an attack roll.
Roll an attack roll.
(laughter)
What do you get?
I'm gonna go with this guy.
Okay, yeah, add your strength to that,
which I believe is three.
So it's your raw strength, so that's 18.
So yeah, you attack that guy. Roll a
d4.
I'm gonna add your strength to that as well.
Six.
nine damage that guy is almost dead
uh... he's not got a pass what is this girl was coming
uh... i don't know if that's canada and i don't think that's a girl
and their scouts right
yeah i know it's got a cloud stress can you
whatever
so yeah uh... the airstrike in a way out of the girl
i get my balloon i want to hear that
so you guys are one of the group of world are those a take it easy that
balance on bali
knock it off
Knock off what? My amazing performance that basically the entire-
Look, I knocked out the entire crowd with my performance because it was so goddamn good.
Yeah, why don't you lay off him, laddy?
Yeah, that guy liked it.
Yeah, who's this little yellow guy? I like him.
Wait a minute.
I like his attitude.
I like his whole thing.
Wait a minute.
Set these up.
You're a leprechaun.
Wait, no. No, uh, uh, uh...
No, he's yellow! Look at him!
He's a simpson!
*laughter*
not a little con
and what he's got a simpsons accent on the next stop we're gonna take you off
the train
and the uh... that's my cousin
that's my cousin
role deception
i just wanted to rule
mhm
that's fair
we can read it
me neither
that's the word but nobody can read that word that is an a
he chose the white that's an e
Your deceptions that is uh, that's an 11 8 plus 5 is 11 pet 13. Yes. Okay, that's okay
Leave him alone
So he goes he's laughed I would just ask you a simple question it doesn't matter if he's you
Yes, or no, and he has
HIV
And this is his final dream is to go to the Royal Palace no leprechauns allowed that's dying
from it and roll deception he's done look at him in his eyes look at how look at
look at how terrible this fucker looks look at him in his eyes he looks
fucking disgusting he has he has HIV what are you doing after say that's about me
do you the truth no what are you trying to fuck this guy no I'm not trying to
fuck anybody security guard elf all right look you're being you're being really
weird but you know what's weird dying young he's only nine years old all right
what just just why don't you just just just keep him under control and keep
your other friend dancing on the controller just just don't I don't want
to go you don't want me to lose control well then don't put no music on brother
tell you that I'm gonna take you boom but I'm just gonna take the boom books
yeah pride for my cold dead fucking hand you take one more step and I'm icing
in
a
roll to know he just rolls twice because all right all right fine just just all
right the guard sort of walks away dejected you see that the the the Royal
Guard is who guys I was so scary talking to that guy oh my god the Royal Guard
doesn't seem to have the sway that they pretend to have on this ship mm-hmm you
see this little the little leprechaun comes up to you and he says thank you
kindly
really appreciated
which
uh...
it
you guys actually it's a good
uh... there
it's not a lot of it but i guess he does
part all over the place
uh...
i would need to take this train trip
about the droughts
stomach up
cake always breaks before too
you know part of this phase
well anyway money
my name is a shame is
of not all
great poll
but you don't know list of irish names are a shame is it's like sort of like
he's ashamed of those
uh... this year
should have said you don't need to be a day of your h_i_v_
since yeah
right all you gotta do is make sure you take
You guys weren't lying about me having AIDS. You know I don't have AIDS, right? Or HIV.
Oh, I just said believe anything that that guy says, so I didn't know that you did.
Yeah, and that's because he, uh...
has a small penis.
Well, if you ever...
I don't know.
If he believes anything that I say...
Well, if you ever wish to stand up to these royal guards once and for all,
you can meet me at the guts of the ship one day, and we can take care of these guys.
So, uh, I'll see you on the next stop.
And he walks off the train.
So he got, he tells you about the guts of the ship.
Go there, ask for a Seamus.
Guys, we gotta go warn the ship
that some little guy with HIV's
trying to get up in its guts.
With no protection.
And you guys land
at the Royal District.
Uh, after your train ride.
I'm over here and I'm like,
"Guys, my reflection looks crazy, there's something wrong
with this mirror!"
Oh my god!
What happened to me?
Nope, that's what you look like.
Oh my god! Hold on, let me look at this real quick.
Does that look...
Can you see that? I'm too small
to see it!
Can somebody point the mirror down?
Oh my god, I'm beautiful!
I'm so
beautiful!
Okay, then we're at the rural district. Yup, and
it looks nothing like the sterile plastic
golden yellow stately baroque buildings that house guards and important
residents but its biggest
*laughter*
Fucking yellow.
Could be Spongebob.
Spongebob!
Hey, don't look now,
but they got Spongebob in the royal castle.
Marge!
It's Marge!
Holy fucking shit!
*laughter*
This is the greatest place
The fucking over that is Homer's the greatest place in the whole fucking world kodo and Kang
Yeah wider blue man
What's that
But it's biggest differentiator
I think he thinks I'm gonna like this fucking castle
No, okay, is that it's filled with real plants vibrant and green
That's it a top terraformed plots of land so the rest of the green was supposed to be
yeah, the rest of the
Space station has kind of artificial
most things artificial air artificial water
These are sort of generated through honing techno-slime.
And you guys happen to have pretty good doses of it, because of where you are in the ship.
But folks who are in the crew, like the Leprechaun and even some of the ship's crew, have to have sort of the runoff of that.
But here in the Royal District, it's all actually terraformed real fake trees.
So you guys can walk towards the Ambassador to the Kingdoms building, which is where Belinda resides.
You see there's a separate ship that follows alongside, behind rather, the Pleasure Palace,
and that is Leo's actual sort of floating space castle.
This is just sort of like the ambassadors area where he can come here where they'll have warships come in and things like that
So are all the terraformed
Trees are they the
From that the trees that smell like nut from that Mitchell and Webb sketch
I've seen I've seen Mitchell and Webb I have not seen that trees that smell like as soon as you said are so all the
Terraformed trees I knew because the sketch is about that park in England where the trees do smell like jizz right yeah
Yeah, they smell like jizz okay, okay?
Why don't you roll for jizz?
He's gonna do
I got a
You got that jizz
Guys, it smells like cum here.
Cool.
The head's not always great.
You keep walking and you go to the Ambassador's Palace, um, where...
Ah!
You swept away Patrick. Patrick, come back.
Holy fuck, my fucking leg!
My fucking leg is broken!
I'll heal it, don't worry.
Okay, it's healed now!
But where's this queen?
Completely forgot Sullivan in that last scene.
Um, so...
He does, yeah.
Okay, so...
Whoa, look at that. That's crazy.
How'd you guys walk in here?
This is the entrance over here.
You guys are walking in to Pleasure Palace.
Ah, shit.
Oh...
My...
I can't see anything. I'm face down on the floor
You see a hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah guys. Let's crawl on her. She'll think we're bugs
I am a bug
So you see a Gumby superior the captain
Yeah, yeah, if you want to control, thank you.
I want to control.
Captain of the space station.
A handsome man in his late 30s
who is completely green
with a blonde crew cut.
This is the best I could do right now.
He's wearing a white
space marine outfit, which is more important I guess to me.
Intricate and decorated,
which it isn't. He's a war hero
from the Transylvanian wars, retired
now and commanding Leo's Pleasure Palace.
He's a gun city native.
And Leo securing him as a captain was like a local legend leaving their home team for a rival team.
That's my simile there.
Gumby is saying too.
Belinda Crokes, who you see here, who looks...
She looks like a frog girl, but...
Yeah, that looks like a frog.
Yeah, she looks like frog-like to me.
"I'm just saying my crew would feel a lot more secure, especially if playtime can't be dealt with,
that we shut down Huge-Ass Facts once and for all."
And Belinda says, "Captain Gumby, I understand very much what you're saying, but you know just
as well as I that things like that take time, and know that our Royal Guard are working on
building a case, and that all of this we should discuss next time when there aren't visitors in
Fine, fine, I'd like to see your frog legs walk on over to the command center every once
in a while.
So you can inspect it.
Make sure everything is...
Inspect this.
(laughter)
- Yeah, and inspect this too.
Can't really do mine, I don't have a poseable figure.
- Yeah, and I will inspect this.
All right, so where's the--
Oh, I fell.
You can inspect this.
- Get that away, no.
(laughter)
He is a character.
Oh, okay.
I thought you were just trying to scare me.
No!
Okay, I'm saying inspect this and then I don't realize he leaves.
And you see walking behind you a tall, strong, big man who is looking at you.
That's a man?
He is a man.
I clipped.
So, his name is Shark Eyes.
And he has a...
Couldn't have just like...
And he has literal sharks in his eyes.
is
okay
like
all
now it's a guy
does that is that a that is
so
the uh...
sort of uh...
picks you up off of the linden uh... sort of by the the need to do
is now you're talking to him
and uh... which is puts you down gently
i'm i'm i apologize
low tossing
couldn't reach you sooner.
While playtime has given us trouble, there has been more recent problem.
The huge-ass fax is growing under city.
Yeah, I'd like to fax a huge ass.
No.
Managing the leprechaun bondsmen, sorry, bondspersons.
And to be quite frank, the celebrity of playtime has its own benefits.
We now need someone to stop this charismatic syriac.
And I thought you three, with your experience as the detectives that precede you, I was hoping
you could help.
So I can pay you for this, and the King would pay you for this as well.
We need you to find and ideally apprehend Playtime.
This is...
She's talking.
Apprehend Playtime.
We don't want to have an outright execution, unless it happens publicly.
Though even though, even then, we'd prefer that to be officially sanctioned by the Queen
in some capacity. Either way, we believe you have the skills and motivation with your missing
son to get this done. You'll be given an allowance of 1000 tokens daily for your work, enough
to continue covering your stay at the resort with some pocket change left over for meals
and any other uses you may have. All I ask is that you report to me any new findings
on the case so I can align resources on the Kingdom's End to help you. I don't wish
to get in your way. I'm familiar with how you work. If you complete this, not only will
you be given an additional lump sum of 100,000 tokens each, but you will also be knights
of the New England Empire.
Ma'am, I'm sorry to interrupt, but you have been sitting on Sullivan the Frog the whole
time.
Oh, I apologize, I didn't...
Hey, come over here, Sullivan.
You look, you look, come on.
Come over here, come over here.
I've been trying not to talk to you guys, but okay.
(laughing)
Keep going, Belinda.
Not sure if I have to tell you boys
that there is a growing tension on E-Bomb
between Gun City, the board, and our kingdom.
I do not wish to pressure you to ally with any faction.
Rather, I see your amelioration of playtime
as vile crimes to help de-escalate tension.
I'm not looking so I can't tell what's going on.
Nothing!
[Laughter]
Nothing's going on.
This is an interplanetary news story waiting to happen.
If everyone finds out soon about how long Playtime's been killing people on this here
sh-damn space station, we could be in serious shit.
This is really not looking, I can feel, because I can feel something's happening.
Nothing's happening.
So are you detectives in,
or what?
We're in.
We're in deeper than you can imagine.
We're in so deep already.
You guys leave
the ambassador's
area
it's more complicated
the work of our kids and later episodes
but i can't leave this room
so that i have a word i think i don't know that
uh... shits
for the people who are listening
we jumped in her hair
yeah i guess it's gotta be all that's a big barbie yet the big barbie
i will say uh... what's up
the people who are listening of already had it's so bad for so long with these
uh... the weed
yet really is
i don't think this is much different from what we know it was a very uh... through
you know we hope we hope all this does is add
uh... as you guys leave
uh...
you see a uh...
you see a uh... you hear scream outside in the royal district
what does it sound like
probably the
that was released the wind guys
Yeah, I don't care about that.
Roll a dexterity saving throw, all of you.
We're back, baby.
Oh my god, no, that was a 10.
I live for this.
Yeah, 10.
I got an 18.
I also got a 10.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't fill out the dex.
The dex save?
Just look at your-- do you have your other sheet?
Yeah, it's on the floor, though.
All right, that's fine.
Also, just what's your dex?
What's your modifier?
my
actually
roll something for me as a reference to wrap
earlier
very dramatic with your face
just get the don't need all this get it
two ones
yet to once
to do it to one thing to do is to eliminate upstairs to ones
You're right.
Uh, you two...
That's what my nephews say.
Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson, you take 8 damage.
Fuck.
You take 4 damage.
Okay.
And you two are gonna take 1d4 damage for the next 3 rounds,
because you just got acid spit on you...
Oh, fuck you, I did!
...by a beast that came from below!
Whoa!
Blah!
Great, I knocked my shit over.
Roll for initiative!
This thing's crazy.
Let's fucking do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Got a six.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, that's enough of the yeah, yeah, yeah, beast.
Um, I got a 14.
I got an 11.
Not only are you a bastard, you beast.
Whoa!
You're annoying.
What'd you get, Pat?
Yeah, you got a drawing laptop.
That's crazy.
Six.
You recommended that?
Yeah.
Can you recommend that to me next?
No.
[Laughter]
You take eight.
And you're gonna take 1d4 in the next round.
I knew it!
Who got the 14?
Me.
That's so funny. I knew it.
Shuffling through all your prints.
Like an accountant in a meeting. I knew it.
Okay, how many points of damage do we take this quarter?
I knew it.
Yeah, I had a 14 initiative.
You're gonna go first.
Ray William Johnson.
Alright.
You see some of the guards you see some of the guards
You really got to stick to the mic if you're talking I'm sorry battle mode battle graphics
Well, it looks like it's fucking he's made it a come
Wouldn't say that's the best. Oh, yeah, I thought the same thing and I ate the other one. Oh, come on
No, not gay humor for me
Cut that out. Sorry. I'm cray today
Okay, there we go you get my
as well as... Get the fuck away from me.
One of the Mecha Brits is gonna fight on your side.
This is a real big fat fight.
You have to talk into the mic.
You guys are in for some serious shit right now.
Can you put the Mecha Brit up as best as you can?
It's not gonna happen.
No, I had it earlier. He is in lying down mode.
Nice. That's cool.
Every once in a while they should stand.
So yeah, you're up Ray William Johnson.
Okay. Okay.
So, I mean, I guess.
Uh, give me my bitch back.
So each of those squares are going to be 5 feet right now.
We're just going to have...
Oh, I'm 10 feet wide.
We're just going to...
We're going to...
You're all...
We're going to ignore some of the size things that are happening here
during any of the battles.
We're going to try to pretend that things are normal.
That means I'm 5 feet wide.
That's normal for you.
Can I ask you one question?
What's up?
I have day veins still.
Yeah, it doesn't affect you.
Yeah, no, you're good. I'm crossing that out. Yeah, this is a
Might come in later, but yeah, okay, don't worry. I'm gonna use my I think I'm gonna throw my sexual grenade right about here
Okay, manage it. What is a splash damage on?
The splash it is
That's a 10-foot radius.
Right, so where are you going to throw it?
Oh, you said each of these are 5 feet?
Yeah, so you should try to aim it here.
Yeah, I'll do that.
And the range on that I think is what, 60 feet?
Yeah, so mostly I guess I'll be hitting these guys.
So let's see, can you reach that though?
Let's draw that diagonal, let's imagine this together.
Yes.
Yeah, that's about right, you got that.
Okay, go for it.
About.
Alright, that is...
I add my attack bonus?
Yes, so it should be plus 6 I think, right?
Plus 9, oh yeah, I forgot how strong you are. 24.
Roll for damage. 2 D10s.
We're playing in the big boys. I forgot which one is a D10, man.
Looks like two guys on top of each other.
2 d10's, a 10.
Cool.
And now he's gonna also have to roll a dexterity saving throw to see if he gets any of the sticky burning cum on him.
He does.
What does that do? I believe it gives him, he's gonna take some extra damage.
Let me take one little look-see.
Um, the sticky cum reduces their move-
[Laughter]
These are their movement by half for one round.
For each additional two tablespoons of sticky gum.
Let me explain. So what you guys have for a lot of these abilities, what I've done,
so also subtract the Techno Slime points it takes on your...
So you have your Techno Slime resources there, so subtract what you use there, not the refills.
So what I have is a lot of these can be kind of upcasts by you spending additional Techno Slime points.
So if you see the plus symbol next to the requirements,
you'll be able to start to figure out what those upcasts are.
We'll figure that out together over time.
So yeah, it just reduces the movement. I thought that was actually good.
That's fine. Okay, cool.
So that's pretty good. It's a good start.
And now it is the Beast's turn.
The Beast is going to start—
the Beast is going to sort of like clench,
and you see its tentacles atop its head start to wander around,
start to flail around, and that's it.
That's all it's going to do for its turn.
Cool. Wow. That was so cool. Nice flail.
So now these guards are going to run up and try to attack them with their lightning spears.
Oh, they're on our side?
Yes, they are.
Oh. I thought that they were on the monster's side.
How did you not know?
These are the beasts coming to invade the world of history.
Because they were fighting us earlier on the train?
Well, it's because you guys were being mean.
They were pointing this way.
They were pointing at the monster.
That's true. I should have ascertained the situation.
I'll describe things better.
AD did ascertain what he did.
So I'll be the sore loser about it.
I said I should have ascertained.
Wow.
Wowie zowie.
You had sarcasm.
I had no sarcasm in my voice.
You had way more sarcasm than me.
What role would they do?
I'm about to tell you.
So, okay, where's my de-sensors?
So these three guys approach this beast.
Oh, these three guys approaching this beast.
That was a good poem.
Good.
And they take a bow.
That was a good poem.
And they take...
This guy manages to dodge out of the way as he's tentacled.
As everything falls the fuck over.
These tentacles are gonna have to just...
We're just gonna have to roll with this for a little bit.
These two guys end up taking damage as these tentacles lash out at him.
It seems that anybody who comes into range of him right now is gonna get attacked by these tentacles.
And if they do get attacked...
Except for me.
Do we get to know how much damage they take?
No.
Okay.
You'll know if you get hit though.
Yeah, I know.
I was just checking if we got to know beforehand.
But then this guy did manage to dodge.
Does it look like it really hurt?
Okay, yeah, that I can tell you.
I mean, it looks like it's not hurt hurt, but it looks like it could have hurt a lot more.
Okay.
All right.
That ain't too bad.
Thank you.
No problem.
So this guy did make it past the tentacles, ducking and weaving and then falling over.
And he does manage to land an attack on the enemy.
So he's got a lot of health.
He's got a lot of health.
So this guy did make it past the tentacles, ducking and weaving and then falling over.
And he does manage to land an attack on this guy with the lightning spear.
He does 7 damage, I'll tell you that.
So this guy is still looking pretty good. He doesn't look too hurt, this beast.
But these two guys have to stop in their tracks before they can approach.
It is now, who got the 11?
That was me.
It is your turn, Blotas.
Did the beast's turn go already?
ready? Yes, he did. Okay. I'm sorry. No, that's okay. I'm not even mad about it. I'm just
gonna shoot my Grinch gun. I think I'll... Can I tell how far... Like, can I tell at
what point did the tentacles... Roll an insight check. Just do a free insight check. Okay.
Ten. Okay. I mean, you can tell that where you are, it's not gonna reach you. Okay, I
wanted to see if I could... But I can't tell if I can move any closer. You can tell that
you can move a little bit closer. Yeah. I'm gonna move to here. You're fine. Okay. Yeah.
And I'm going to shoot my Grinch gun twice.
All right. Cool. Go for it.
Okay. That is a 24.
That hits.
Okay. That's 5 damage.
And then that's a 23.
All right. That hits.
And that is 7 damage.
Okay.
Pretty good. So, yeah, you shoot at this beast.
You can lodge the bullet in what amounts to its chest.
It lurches forward.
and you lodge another bullet just a bit lower
into where you imagine maybe it's sort of like a sternum is
and it sort of lurches forward again.
But it still is up.
And again, it seems pretty resilient,
whatever this thing is.
So now, it is Patrick Yoda's turn.
- I'm gonna use Yoda's mind.
- Okay.
So you wanna read the mind of this beast?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Yeah, I believe that was a wisdom saving throw on my end,
right, you wanna read the description
for
When the surface thoughts of the target target what is most on its mind in that moment, as
an action, Patrick Yoda can either shift his attention to another target's thoughts or
attempt to probe deeper into the same target's mind.
If you probe deeper, the target must make another wisdom saving throw.
If it fails, you gain insight into its reasoning.
Alright, so, there's other stuff there, but that's all we need to know right now.
You are able to probe into its mind, so you can get the surface level thoughts.
And it is saying kill me.
Can I probe deeper and ask why?
Because that would take another action.
I get a bonus action.
It doesn't funnel in.
Since we're here I get an extra attack.
So the way that works is that you...
Oh right because that's not an action.
It has to be an attack action then you do an extra attack.
But you did hear kill me which you...
I mean yeah.
Use that to your...
Hey I just read his mind this fucker wants to be dead.
Do your best.
(laughter)
Okay.
Alright, now it is the mech's turn.
The Mecha Brit.
The Mecha Brit is going to approach.
And stay- that's actually exactly right.
And it's going to shoot its spear out
towards the beast.
And it's going to miss.
It shoots the spear out, and you can see that it has like a long
steel cable- beautiful.
It sort of lands-
Whoa!
it lands next to the beast and sort of ricochets back
it's gonna shoot it one more time
and it misses again
so uh...
it's just way above the beast's head
uh... and it's the end of its turn
and it is now your turn again Ray William Johnson
okay now that i know that i don't want to kill those little fuckers
i want to use my matrix beam on this muh
okay wait should we kill it or should we uh...
Yeah, it wants to die, but why does it want to die?
I will abide you.
You could find out next turn.
Yeah, because I could also...
As long as you maintain concentration, you can probe deeper.
I don't know that.
I don't know that, so I'm going to keep killing this.
You also might not care.
I don't care.
You can say anything.
I just don't want to die.
So, here's the thing.
If you do Matrix Beam, it will hurt these guys too, probably.
I don't care.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, it can...
Casualty of war, you can explain it later.
No, I did it on purpose.
You won't even do it?
Read Matrix Beam for the crowd.
Matrix Beam.
Five...
100-foot cone.
Making me hungry for ice cream.
Duration, instant plus.
What does that mean?
It means that you can actually, if you...
You can charge it, and it'll do more damage and go a little bit further.
If you want to, like, charge it and hold it for a few rounds.
Roll a spell attack to deal 4d8 psychic damage and a 60-foot cone.
Each creature in the area who sees the Matrix Code must make a Wisdom saving throw.
On a failed save, the creature is put into a Matrix Daze for the duration.
While in a Matrix Daze, the creature is incapacitated and has a speed of 0.
The spell ends for an affected creature if it takes any damage or if someone else uses an action to shake the creature out of its stupor.
For every 6 seconds RWJ takes to charge his Matrix Beam, it can shoot 10 feet further than what I'm at.
Roll that d20.
And that's a four.
Okay, even with your spell attack.
Oh, with my spell attack?
It's gonna be plus nine, which is very good.
That's cray.
He's pretty OP now.
I'm pretty cray.
Everybody manages to get out of the way,
thankfully for them.
Spend your Techno Slime points on that too.
You know what else is cray?
Green salad in a blue bowl, y'all.
That's why you have the Techno Slime refills.
And we have to remember the techno slime addiction system and remember techno slime refills cost a bonus action during combat
So that you can use it and then use an action the same turn
So you can use it now if you want to use the room like a beautiful
You are up now
monster the monster
Is going to retract its tentacles. I like the sound of that and going to chomp at one of these guys
- Nice.
Good God.
That hits.
That's gonna do a lot of damage.
This guy's dead.
- Whoa!
- He chomps him.
You see as he bites down in him
that sort of a milky, acidic substance.
- I knew they were made of gum.
- No, it's not gum this time.
and washes over this guy.
[SCREAMING]
And he slowly dissolves into his mouth.
Well, actually, pretty quickly.
And he is swallowed.
He now chomps at this guy.
But that's it.
Yeah, he's dead.
[LAUGHTER]
Wow.
That's kind of scary.
Yep, this guy's tough.
There's only one soldier left.
So his tentacles aren't whipping around.
Oh, I'm sorry, this one soldier has to go.
He is running away.
He's made of green foam.
He is a coward.
"I'm too young to die!"
And he runs away.
What if he dies of a different thing?
Can we try to attack him while he runs?
He's running by you.
You can use your reaction to attack him.
attack him. You can use your reaction to attack him. So roll, use your hoagie. Speaking of
hoagie, keto blueberry sandwich with lettuce bun. That hits. So I add a +8 to that? Oh
yeah. You guys are beast in this campaign bro. Yeah that hits. Or no, 23. No, wait. Yeah,
21, you were right. 13 +8 = 21. Roll for damage.
You also add your... I don't remember if I made it your wisdom instead of your strength.
But it's whatever is there.
Five.
Okay. You still whack this guy. He's like running away.
He's like, "I'm too young to...!"
You like just fucking whack, whack, whack him in the stomach.
Like sort of his air... you know what I mean.
The wind knocked out of him.
Yeah, the wind. Everyone has wind in them.
And this guy falls over and he keeps running away.
And he gets back up.
And now it is your turn, Botas Piss.
So the tentacles are no longer whirling around.
Okay. I'm going to run up to him.
I'm going to get as much behind him as possible to be away from
that scary mouth.
And I'm going to swing my dual pipes.
Do it.
Which that is a 13.
Okay. It's not good.
Ricochets off of the scaly backside. Oh great. That's a 26. That definitely hits. Okay 2d6
That is uh 8 damage nice oops my mirror
Oops
You did that on purpose
It is now
Imagine if I rolled these for 2d6
I'd be like i'd be like, uh, that's yellow. Yeah double yellow
Matt, it's your turn.
[Laughter]
I feel like I'm wrenching his mind.
Um, okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna probe deeper into his mind.
Okay, do it. Pause.
Oh no, no, no, no, no. He's sorry. He has to roll an additional wisdom save.
Oh, well I gotta...
If I did that with my wisdom,
um, well,
then I would've gotten a 19.
It is, but I wrote the rule.
Yeah.
He does, he is able to say "fuck" so he's able to cast you out of his mind.
Sort of like "Urgh, urgh, urgh" and he sends you out in the last year's place counting.
As you leave his mind.
Yeah he made like some pussy eating sounds or something so I gotta kill him.
Um, so I'm gonna use my uh, my lightning.
That was your action.
That was my action? I can't attack?
Shit, okay.
Um, someone else use my lightning.
Okay, it is now, uh, now it is now the robot's turn.
Oh, bastard. Fuck you, robot.
And, and...
While you make this move, remember that he does have a little wrench thing in his arm.
He's gonna use his jet-propelled legs to move a little bit more forward.
And he's gonna whip out a Gatling gun.
And launch it at the bad guy.
Launch the gun?
No, he's going to launch bullets at me.
And that does not hit.
This guy is one of the worst robots of all time.
He's going to try again.
And he's a really bad robot.
Yeah, you can do whatever you want to him.
He missed again?
Yeah, he did.
Now it's my turn again?
It's your turn, but we wouldn't have time.
I think that it makes perfect sense for me to use my Matrix Beam again.
I
You're also welcome to upcast that if you want to do more damage.
No.
Um, that is a 16.
Okay, he's also going to have to, well, your matrix stupor, right, so he's going to have to roll against that.
Yeah.
It's wisdom, right?
It is a, yeah, a wisdom save, right?
On a failed save, the creature is put into a matrix daze.
I'll explain that tomorrow.
So what, uh, what's his wisdom?
And what's your save?
What?
It's right next to your spell cast modifier on the first sheet.
It was a wisdom save. I think it's 17.
Your spell's DC.
Hmm.
That does sound pretty interesting.
It looks like 17.
You see where it says death save?
Yeah, 17.
He just did...
Nice.
So he is in a stupor.
Yep, so he is now paralyzed.
So he's incapacitated and has a speed of zero.
So he's sort of like, "Urgh."
And he's seeing just sort of like waves of code wash over his vision.
He doesn't know where he is or what's going on.
So he is now incapacitated and he's got an attack of advantage on him.
Yup.
So, which should help you.
So let's go to your turn. That was a very good strategy.
That's my turn?
Yeah.
Oh no, I'm sorry. You're right. It's the monster's turn.
He is still--
Okay.
to
and
I'm just going to believe you. You're God.
You're right. I should.
You just gave him too much.
That is 13. No. Yes. 13.
Okay. Now I'm going to attack again.
Okay. That was 16.
Okay. Cool.
Can I try to probe again?
How much damage did you do by the way?
Whatever I said. 13.
13, right? Sorry.
He's looking bloody.
That means half, guys.
I think you shouldn't probe anymore, Patrick.
I think you should finally do some damn damage.
I use my lightning.
You're farting around.
Okay, what is your lightning? It's a spell attack, correct?
Why don't you describe it to me?
You also have the ability to go into --
It's a spell attack. I can shoot lightning out of my hands
at a single target dealing 4d8 damage for every two tablespoons.
I don't know why.
Teaspoons.
Oh, Techno Slime Points.
Yeah, for two Techno Slime Points,
my lightning can reach one additional target
for the same damage for every six seconds I use.
To charge the attack,
I can reach ten more feet,
but I think I'm just going to use...
You can just use it, you can upcast it if you want.
Yeah, because I have an extra attack every time I do...
I can also do an additional.
You also have the bonus action with that.
But that you only get if you go into...
What are my other attacks here?
Because I don't have the...
I used to have the hoagie attacks and stuff.
You have the hoagie attacks still, you have the hoverboard attack.
You have a battle meditation mode.
Oh, you know what I'm going to do? I'm going to use the hoverboard boomerang.
And then while it's going, I'm going to shoot my lightning at it.
So it's an electric boomerang.
I'll allow it.
(laughter)
Let's do it like this.
There's no way I haven't done that already.
You haven't.
Okay.
But, I'll allow it.
So what you should do, roll a regular attack, roll with the hoverboard, so add your attack to that, whatever that is, and see if that succeeds first.
Oh, so that's plus eight?
No, no, no, no, no. So look at your sheet on the top left, is where all of your sort of go-to attacks are.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
a
the
I'm going to re-roll because that might have switched.
Wait, what the fuck does that mean?
I thought it said 8.
It might have switched.
I lifted this up and I don't remember if it said 8 or 16.
But I got a crit one just then.
So maybe I should have lied.
Yes, I'm always welcome for you to lie to me.
Okay, yeah, it misses.
That was a valiant effort, you're doing better reading minds.
It is your turn now, Mech...
Britmechabrit.
Mechbrit is going to open his chest open.
Open his chest open.
No way he will.
He's doing it.
And a chest rocket is flying from his chest.
That's right.
And this monster's gonna have to roll a dexterity saving throw to avoid this freaking blast.
saving blow yo yo yo and he misses
Oh hold on cowboy
he does take quite a bit of damage though as this guy finally does his job
oh my god he's getting fucking owned
okay he takes 15 damage
I'll tell you that
And the monster
Initiating boots and cats
Damn, he's a hip-hop robot
Yo, yo, yo
Motherfucker, he's a he's a British. He's a British hip-hop robots right that fucker. He's doing drill. Yeah
But some a cat I'm meme up. Oh, you're up
well, man
I think that I will use my awesome...
I think I will use my matrix.
You could also...
I'll use my dong blade I guess.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll use my dong blade.
Use your dong blade.
Run up to him.
Well actually I don't think he'll make it if you run up to him.
Alright, I'll use my sexual grenade again.
Use that.
Blow him up.
Uh, okay.
That is an eleven-eyed fry.
Nope, it's not gonna happen.
Okay.
Alright, we'll lower your-
Moving on, moving on.
Yep.
Alright, the monster's turn.
Sorry for even trying, guys.
The monster's gonna turn to face you.
That's okay, I don't mind that you tried.
We gotta kill this guy, dude. We're taking too long.
Yep.
This is what happens in Dungeon & Dragons.
He's going to attack you.
He's gonna try to eat you.
He's not gonna do shit.
'Cause I'm super-powered.
That hits you.
I'm Superman. I'm Superman. I am Superman. I'm Superman. I am Superman. Oh yeah.
Does 25 damage to you. Oh my fucking god. What the heck?
He chews you up and as you feel his teeth pierce your hoo flesh.
Hoo's flesh?
It feels like a hot, hot knife going in.
And when the acid seeps into your body,
it feels like it's sort of just burning the veins inside of you.
I feel like you might even be continuing to burn for some
turns after this as well.
Oh, no.
All right.
Bad to the stomach.
And you actually are going to start burning right now because
it is your turn.
Oh, actually, I'm sorry.
He has to attack.
Oh, I maybe will.
What's your AC?
16.
If that hits me, I'm going to wait up.
No.
21 damage.
Oh my god, fuck me man.
You're making the first fucking guy so hard.
I did stay, I went behind him.
He wants to die so bad.
Why does he say stay away from his mouth then?
Oh, wow.
Let's just stay away from him in general.
He looks like he's going to try to eat you soon.
Ah, shit.
It is now your turn.
If there's any time for this to happen, it's the first episode.
Alright, well,
I'm going to...
You can also heal with your
fourth skin. I can heal...
him with your fourth skin. I will do that.
Okay, so you cast your fourth
skin, coming from your
uncircumcised penis.
Roll, I believe it's 1d10
10 plus 4 to heal?
We need something on this to simulate Patrick's uncircumcised penis.
What could we use?
What could we put on the table right now?
To simulate an uncircumcised penis.
I mean yeah, you can do whatever you want.
If you honestly wanted to show your penis, I wouldn't care.
WAKAAA!
Yeah, he heals you, you're up.
I'm up?
Yeah, remember to get rid of your Technoslime points for that too.
How much did I get healed by?
How many Technoslimes?
Roll the d10.
You're gonna be up either way.
Did you roll it?
I did but I don't remember.
Ok.
Is that a d10?
I did say.
It's a 10.
Ok, is that a d10?
I can't see what it is.
It is.
Ok, it is?
No, I don't know what that is.
Yeah, that is a d10.
That's correct.
You got a 10 on that?
Nice.
10 plus 4, 14.
You're back at 14 health.
You'll have to use a strength check to break through the foreskin that has draped over
you.
That's fine.
But you are healing from its nature.
And that doesn't count as an attack.
No, but it doesn't count as your actions. We're back to the top of the yield.
We're back to the mech.
So...
The mech is going to try to shoot its rocket once again.
Wow. And this guy does avoid an unfortunate...
God damn this fucking monster, man.
You are up.
I gotta piss. Julio has to leave.
I know.
Come on. Alright, here's what we're doing.
Wait, doesn't he get two tries?
He does get two tries.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Fast, fast, fast.
You bastard. You cool-ass bastard. Stop looking so damn cool.
damn cool. He missed again?
Oh yeah!
And what does he do?
And it lands like this though?
Oh hell.
Describe your kill.
I shot my rocket at him and uh
blew him up.
Okay, this guy is dead.
Wow!
Why did he want to die?
Probably because he was suffering.
If you were that ugly,
I mean, let's be real.
You are.
Don't you want to die?
All right, you guys did it.
Hooray!
Oh my god, another monster.
(imitates monster growling)
(laughing)
All right.
It's time to read.
The corpse of the beast lies at your feet.
High-handedly defeated by,
why don't I just read normal?
Let me try one more time.
The corpse of the beast lies at your feet.
You sound like Report of the Week.
Handedly defeated by you three,
in the litany of gods who fought alongside you.
As leprechauns arrive to the scene to clean up the mess,
you feel a chill in the air.
The heat is out again. Flicker. Blackness.
You hear the stutters and starts of a knowing panic,
the guards marching urgently.
Nothing is turning on, but there's serenity in the blackness.
There's an honest peace on Pleasure Palace.
Because when no light shines, you can actually see the stars above through those windows.
The whole allure of this station is to be among these things.
Now you can make them out the way you can't anywhere else.
But the stars are no sun, they offer no clarity or warning.
Just a humiliating cold regard.
Flicker, pop, the lights come back on.
A shriek from the mess hall.
You rush over.
Playtime had never killed the royal guard before, but before you lies two.
Dead.
And they got strangled to death.
Strangled to death, their throats slit, and there's a bunch of yellow goo on the bottom of them.
childless couple and jutting from each of their mortal wounds their favorite toys a
Gumby superior action figure and the children's book the day. I saw my father cry by Bill Cosby
Part of the little bill books for beginning readers series
When we'll play time strike next and who and one thing before we finish the episode out
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Running On Empty Food Reviews.
Say that right here into this camera.
He didn't say it exactly.
How does he say it?
Who is it?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Running On Empty Food Reviews.
You dress like him too.
(laughing)
- You look badass.
- That's so crazy.
- You're whizzy, you're whizzy.
- You don't know our report of the week?
- Is that review, bro?
- Yeah, yeah, you'll know.
- Running on empty?
- Food.
- I've never watched the reviews.
- And then one more thing for me.
Go on this camera.
- Fud block.
- Popcorn.
- Or butter.
(laughing)
- No, this is butter.
- All right, bye.
- Bye. - How'd that go?
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(electronic music)