Mm-hmm, okay
Last time on gun city stories a broad city the uncle's Falcon
Our intrepid detectives made their way to mommy good legs club where the eponymous mommy asked them to meet her in her dressing room some
Alone time and to gather some information on famed activist Sean McElwee's disappearance
McElwee's
Before they could get there, however, the lads found themselves face to face with a fearsome
stag party obsessed with snogging mommy good legs.
They duped it out, as it were, Blowtoss beating a few of those limey punks to death with his
pipes, Patrick Yoda used his trusty hoverboard boomerang and hoagie to wham bam Margera a
couple others, and Ray William Johnson threw his patented sexual grenade to annihilate
and humiliate the rest.
In the process, they saved a young British orphan's soul from the allure of being an English soccer
fan type, and from being covered in Ray William Johnson's deadly seed, avoiding a disastrous
Chris D'Elia type of situation for the podcast.
After taking care of business, the gang rolled up to Mommy's dressing room, where she divulged
some additional intel about Sean's activism before his disappearance.
#AbolishCox
Feeling friskier than Caroline Calaway when anyone is paying attention to something other
than her, Patrick Yoda started bounding about Mommy's dressing room looking for coins.
He found a few and him and Rey had a brief spat over these precious quarters.
Mommy told the gang to meet her at the club tomorrow in the AM, where they'll have more
time and perhaps more privacy to talk.
The gang left the club and were confronted by a one Michael the Crawler.
He told them to come to the abandoned porno factory because his employer was interested
in their activities.
In Yoda's mind, Patrick Yoda learned that the Crawlers' new tent was nefarious, and
he and Blotas began a little impromptu interrogation of their own.
Meanwhile, a despondent Ray William Johnson wandered the lonely highway of Gun City, unsure
of his detective abilities and dividing my attention between the two scenes.
Subdued, Michael the Crawler was ready to talk, but before he could, his body exploded,
cock first.
The gang, incensed, made their way to the abandoned porno factory, where they saw two V-like,
you know, virtual, like, iron warriors guarding the facility.
Using their wits and wiles, they made their way in, and now stand face to face with a
mysterious door, somehow less decrepit than the rest of this forgotten-
Excuse me.
You idiot.
Alright, just go again.
I'm sorry.
That was involuntary.
You could've at least turned more away from the light.
that was a volunteer police department
what do you think
i did not even know that i was going to have to talk about it
does it have to do it
i'm leaving that in
the
somehow less decrepit the rest of this
what is behind the door
what is the hashtag abolished tax
where is sean mckelvey
Why is the Milwaukee Police Department allegedly running a pedophile trafficking ring?
Maybe we'll find out on Gun City Stories.
A Broad City, The Uncle's Falcon, Part 3.
Which is uh, where we're at now.
Woo!
That's what's up.
Yeah, so that is what's up.
You guys are, so yeah, that's what happened.
So last time, you guys were sort of goofing around, doing a little deception on those two
sort of hulking, seemingly sort of like virtual guards.
And Cameron, you told them, I believe, that you were repairmen.
Yes.
Of some kind.
And they believed it.
So you guys are standing in front of this door that was like less broken down than the
rest of the abandoned porno factory so what do you what do you guys want to do
what's what's going through your heads I'm gonna walk I want to walk into the
door wait is there a doorbell yeah that's a good question there's no door
bell all right that's all that's always my first question I just have to make
sure is a knocker though okay I use the knocker I'm gonna use your knockers but
Don't don't use the knocker. Okay. Why why not can well we can
We can is there a window what can we do come on spit it out?
Is there a window can you do you see a window I
Don't know. Maybe we should investigate another way in
Okay
Hey man, go for it. Sure. You go ahead, you go ahead Patrick. What Patrick, I have an idea.
I'm gonna investigate. Patrick, why don't you go into some distant room and just yell from really far away.
Okay. To have a conversation with us like you do every time we're investigating something.
That's a good idea. That's not a bad idea. Okay yeah, so what are you doing Pat?
I'm probably gonna go... Or you want to investigate or see if there's another way in?
I get self-conscious about them saying that so
So I stay with the party
Because you told me it was a bad idea I think you I think you are
You know embarrass you get embarrassed and you were kind of like you're two older brothers and you just do what we say
I'm no, I'm the oldest you do not use the knocker wait
Years old
Do a push-up right now. No. Do a push-up.
Dude, wait, wait. No. Oh wait, I'm getting a call.
I take out my phone and I put it to my head.
Right, yeah. Oh my god, it's the chief.
He says that you have to do a push-up right now.
I don't have to do a push-up.
Chief is right. He said you have to get me a glass of water, but I'll time it.
Retired. You don't have to get a glass of water from me.
No, you have to do a push-up.
You are not, you're not gonna get water.
Now you're just proving a point.
I'm telling you that now. You're getting no water.
- No water. - Just knock on the door.
- Touch the knocker.
- I'm not touching it. - Touch it.
- You touch it. - If you don't touch it,
you're gay. - I'm gonna touch you.
- Don't touch me. - I'm gonna touch you.
- Don't. - I touch Patrick.
- Ah!
(laughing)
- Okay, yeah, you can-- - I'll just knock on the door.
- I knock on the door.
(laughing)
- Okay, yeah, you knock on the door with the knocker
and there's no answer.
- Great.
- I try to open the door. - Wait, wait, Patrick, you try.
It might work if you do it. It might work. I try the doorknob. Okay yeah the door is
open. Fuck. Yeah so yeah you open the door and before you is a... the room before you
is dark. Nearly too dark to see but what you can make out is a laboratory of some
kind. Test tubes, beakers, Bunsen burners, diagrams and equations, a 24 by 36 inch
poster of Marie Curie riding the Sibian, all the trappings of a fully functioning
lab. Also there's a Technoslime linear accelerator, isolate synthesizer, as well
as a full thermal ablation device. You can roll your intelligence in a moment
to see what these things are, but the room seems to be recently abandoned. It's
one of the Bunsen burners is still on, bubbling what appears to be raw Technoslime
cooling during the tail end of the thermal ablation process.
On behalf of this, don't tell him what'll happen.
So yeah, you guys are in here.
Um, actually let me see...
I walk up to you and I drink the slime.
Okay, yeah, you drink the slime?
Yeah, the pure Bunsen burner slime.
Okay, yeah, so, uh, uh, do you, do you, okay, yeah, you roll up and drink the slime.
Um, uh, oh man, okay.
Uh, so.
So, uh, anybody else engage with the slime or is it just Gale?
If you do, I'll kill you.
Yeah, I don't, I don't engage with the slime.
So, I did the whole thing.
Okay, so let's, let's resolve, uh, let's resolve the slime and then I want to do Patrick's investigation.
Yeah, and I want to, I want to look at the equipment too after that.
I want to see what's there.
That's investigation.
No, it's different.
I'm determining what it is.
It's determination.
You're still investigating.
Why don't you just investigate with me?
No, I don't want to do anything with you.
Let's do the slime.
Wait, what's that about?
He didn't do push-ups.
He also yelled when I touched him.
And that was not cool.
I am sensitive.
I'm sensitive.
I'm sensitive, you see.
Yeah, like a girl.
We're gonna work this out over the course of this episode.
Hey, nice boobs, girl.
I don't have boobs like a girl.
You have to roll them.
Caleb is saying this
this well drinking the slime so it's just a bubble. I'm doing like a ventriloquist trick.
You've got sort of really tiny boobs. I don't have two tiny... One is a four and one is a six.
A cup. I don't have boobs. Well what am I staring at and drooling over right now then?
You're looking at my penis. You're staring at and drooling at nothing because you just drank.
No, you're hallucinating.
You're hallucinating.
Oops, I'm Patrick.
A panorama of colors, lights, and gnarled subspace
flood your senses.
Wait, you had something written for me drinking the whole thing?
Oh yeah.
I was pretty sure one of you guys
were gonna do that.
So I was just in case I had something ready.
As you attempt to move your body,
you feel each cell vibrate and stutter
as if you're slipping through
vast primordial humming. Your bones and muscles weaken, melt and shiver back
together, re-render not reform within each moment. Space and time feel observable
like seas of swirling plasma clouding what remains of your sense of self. Is
this ego death? Ray William Johnson, you see one of the fat bitches you love so
desperately fall through the sky almost forever. The weight of their ass carrying
them towards something. To where are they falling? And from where have they fell?
Tell me. Where are they falling? Where are these fat bitches falling from? And
from where have they fell?
Oh my god. Also at the same time you're like not you don't feel any sense of
self anymore so you're sort of just trying to cobble together what you are
okay you the only stuff is time inches because I'm I'm just a computer ones and
zeros no soul no love just fat bitches
fuck dude I feel like I'm tripping in real life now they've yeah the I see
nothing but beautiful big bitches all I've ever wanted yeah you know and
they're and they're falling out of a giant coke zero can and they're and
they're falling into into a very cool pool from the chameleon airs episode of
cribs and I'm crying yeah so my demon is crying okay I'm writing this down for
later not let's end this yeah I feel you were you're almost too prepared this
episode yeah the two weeks patches DM is dangerous I cannot believe that I walked
into your fucking trap did he said and there's no telling what will happen if
you drink this and that's pretty much the trigger phrase for you to do something
he just told us what exactly happened when I drank it
it caught me so off guard I'm flustered yeah and yeah you you sort of come to and
you feel your um I come three you come three and as you as you come as you come
three your soul sort of reforms you for you feel your soul whatever that is
reform and your sense of self sort of it makes makes reforms again as it exists
again and you're you're sort of drooling over Patrick Yoda's what you think are
his giant tits as this happens and you're gonna have advantage on checks
any any ability check until tomorrow morning that's all fucked up damn you
said you'd kill us if we had any so kind of that's how you the fucked up a fuck
I'm sorry well let's resolve that investigation we might find yeah
additional tonight some of the goodies in here mm-hmm yeah so do you guys both
want to roll an investigation and like sort of support each other I want to do
the intelligence check to look at the equipment oh yeah you said Pat you can
investigate something else but I'm doing my thing uh let's do Pat let's do you
first I roll an investigation yeah just roll investigation see what you
could find around here what I guess you got a seven which is is not the best but
yes you do you try to do your due diligence around the room you find I
roll again yeah I need to investigate harder no you can have you know one of
or other I think you'd have one other guy on the team also check do an
investigation with you and and you could take the higher role okay should I do
that well I'm the one with advantage oh yeah you have advantage on all checks so
you would get to roll twice and pick the higher one yeah you're basically right
now vibrating at a frequency that is kind of akin to a god yeah yeah I'm just
walking around shaking and I'm like I I should I'm thinking I'm gonna go back to
college to finish my degree. I'm having a lot of ideas right now. Yeah, you're about to
open a small business. It's gonna happen. Yeah. Alright, investigation, right?
There's one and there's two. What did I get? I can't see. Goddamn. Yeah, you got, yeah, you
rolled an absolutely beastly one. Yeah. So yeah, Patrick, you sort of
look around you sort of flip some books over and you sort of look at the test
tubes more closely and you don't quite get a sense of what's going on.
Ray William Johnson, you're sort of, yeah yeah exactly, yeah you're sort of
hyper, hyper PCP coked out brain is just like your irises are vibrating, you're
scanning the room and you can see pretty much most everything that's going on. You
find there's a bug over there yeah there's a weird bug he's on the desk get
him he's gone yeah yeah you saw you saw a weird bug it was you guys smell water a
centipede with a sombrero on and you saw that just sort of crawl by you look at
the you look at around and you find all sudden you sort of realize that there's
tons of Maxim magazine scientist edition just sort of scattered around you find
you find also underneath those magazines you can almost like see just barely
peeking some sort of blue paper and you rush over there and you look at it and
it's a blue print and it looks like it's for something called the
Coculus Rift 2.0 the Coculus Quest Cordless Experience. And there's also a
a name at the bottom of the blueprint that says designed by Dr. Tool Lateralis.
You also, you also sort of like your head exorcists around and you see something
else and you walk backwards over there and you see some of these pens these like
men in black style pens and Patrick Yoda you would recognize those immediately
actually as the ones that Gavin shit Tommy gun clippy guy was using to get
everybody high by seeing spots oh so you'd see both of those things sort of
there the cowboy bebop drug and I just and I just said that I just said that I
knew that so yeah yeah we'll fix it we'll have Patrick say that in post we'll
use a computer to generate his voice to switch Patch's voice to Patrick's voice.
Can I roll intelligence to see to look at the tool the drug making tools?
Yeah. I can figure out how they work. Yeah roll straight intelligence. Alright I got
eight. Okay yeah so you look in... Can I come out again? Yeah you can. I got an eight I look at
them and I say guys I think this is a boombox.
boombox I've been thinking of getting into music myself music is my life
investigation Oh at 20 not a good nation sorry what am I in my roles are so good
I I would say yeah yeah that's fine cuz I was gonna say you should add your
proficiency anyway um yeah so you look at so who's I'm cracked right now yeah
- Yeah, you're absolutely-- - This is crazy.
- Yeah, your roles are insane right now.
So with that 26, I mean, you can observe these things
and you could whip up more raw Technoslime
if you needed to.
- Do it. - Basically.
- Do it! (laughing)
- So yeah, if you wanna do it, you can do it.
- I'm doing it right now.
- Okay, yeah, you whip that up.
- I'm in the kitchen cooking Technoslime.
- Yeah, yeah, you're in the kitchen, you're cooking it up.
Yeah, you cooked that up.
So you have about, you know,
two more sort of offerings of that Techno Slime
that you can slurp down
with what you were able to scrap together.
- What should I put my Techno Slime points at?
- Let's see what you're talking about.
- 'Cause I've definitely eaten a lot of them.
'Cause I think I'm low on Techno Slime.
- Didn't we recharge them in the last session?
- I'm at four.
- Oh, yeah, well that's 'cause you failed the roll,
so you got half of it, I think.
- True.
Was that what happened? Yeah, yeah. Yes, right? Yes. Okay. Yeah. So I mean, I would say you're at max at this point because it's just you're like kind of buzzing.
That's right. But yeah, I mean, you would also know and I'll tell this to you as a kind DM that the come down could be fierce. If you can do. Yeah, no, yeah, you're not. Yeah, you're gonna be awesome. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, okay, sick.
Yeah.
So, yeah, you have these two other sort of pints of raw Techno Slime that you can do whatever
you want with.
And you would also know that these are just from your, you would probably search your database
since you're fucking computer.
And you'd see that, like, in particular, some of these, the thermal ablation device seems
like a newer model.
that like, like wouldn't have been published yet as like, "Hey, product update from, from
uh, uh, Poppy Chuko's Techno Slime Company."
Unreleased? Is that what you're saying?
Whoa.
Yeah. Yeah.
Can I, can I, uh, does it have like a, um, uh, some sort of production mark on it? Can I see,
does it say made by whatever?
Yeah, um, yeah, I mean, it says that it's it's like Papi Chuko's like,
Oh, it is.
property. Yeah, it's just it's just like a it's clearly though, like a, a, if not a
prototype, it's like, you know, it's the, like alpha before release of this guy
just saying, so somebody is doing something with it ahead of time, I guess.
Hmm. Very interesting. Yeah, I don't know. This is all this is all a fella
poppy Chuko again this has all been Caleb realized all this but didn't tell any of
us yet so I'm trying trying to turn on the boombox and I'm putting my ear to
the machine and pressing a bunch of buttons on it yeah yeah it's just sort
of like stopping and stuttering I hate this song this is intelligent dance
music yeah what is this apex twin yeah it sucks wait guys the I think this is some
sort of advanced a model of a babble blaster whatever that is that it was
called yeah yeah I knew that I was definitely knew that it's it's not a
boombox and and IDM is actually a very valid genre when you think about it yeah
I know I was joking when I said that.
I don't think he was joking.
I was joking. Shut up Patrick!
You're probably just not smart enough to get that kind of
IDM dance music. Yeah, it's called
intelligent dance music. Yeah. Let me tell ya.
Blow toss. You gotta be smart.
You're too quarter shy of a dollar.
Yeah, you're not so sharp in your shit.
I miss, I don't understand that
Patrick is, it's a figure of speech and I take out the 12
quarters from my pocket and I have a ton of quarters man I don't know what the
fuck you're talking about. You're super smart you have a ton of quarters
how many dollars is that? Seven. All right I think we're done here. Let's call it
Papi Juco. Wait can we take a closer look at the blueprints before we do that for
the Coculus Rift 2? Yeah for sure. I just want to see if it has what is it what's the deal
with it. Yeah so what it looks like is that there's a drawing of a vivisected
penis. And there's a, where a device, and you see like a sort
of a device being inside of the vivisected penis and arrow
pointing to it, right? And then you see a big X over that image.
And then you see a different image of a penis. And then what
it looks like some sort of like satellite. And then, and like a
big checkmark underneath that and and that's really it okay they're trying to
make a penis satellite they're gonna bend our penises into check mark shapes you
wait they're gonna let you get direct TV with your wiener I'm going home you're
You're not, you're pro?
You're okay with this?
I can watch NFL Red Zone with my penis.
Don't you already have wifi in your brain?
You're a computer.
No.
Yes, yes you are, you're a computer.
Can you guys relax man,
I'm seeing some weird shit right now.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Either of you have my mom's phone number.
Yeah, and the weird shit you're seeing
just comes, uh, uh, you hear thumping coming in, you hear, you see the two guards appear
at the doorway of the room at this point.
Are you guys seeing this?
And you guys over there.
You hear like a lightsaber type of "mmm" right, with the energy sword drawn from one of them.
And that first one says "Motherfucker, this is an abandoned porno factory, why would there
be repairmen?"
And the other one says "You tricked us, bitch!" and they're just overlapping, they keep saying
"You tricked us, you tricked us."
And we need you all to roll for initiative.
Aww.
Oh.
I hate fighting.
God, why can't we all just get along?
Why can't we all just get along?
I'm gonna say that to the cards.
My rolls are so good.
Yeah, they uh.
I did better than you.
Yeah, but I have minus one.
My rolls are terrible.
I got a 15.
I got a 14.
And Patrick got zero, clearly.
What am I rolling? You already rolled initiative. What did you get? Say I got a three. I got
a three. Nice, thanks for the clean take. Dude, that's a good Charlie Brown Halloween
reference right there. I got a three. Yeah, so you guys are in the, yeah, so they're sort
of, and I'll do a little freehand drawing here. So it's sort of like door, right? Looks
like a complete shit brother. Right yeah okay you know what like I just didn't
have time to prepare environments. Okay yeah that's fine. So so I I have using my
drawing skills right. We're only paying you a million dollars. Yeah well it's a
million it's a maybe maybe a maybe a couple extra dollars you can get. A million and five.
A million and five dollars. Oh yeah that's all I need. Yeah so they're in front of you and it is your turn Cameron. Oh
Oh nice, alright so how far can I move? How many squares? Let's see here. It doesn't say
on my character sheet so I don't know. So squares are like 5 feet a piece. Yeah but it doesn't
I don't have a speed on my character sheet. You don't? It's 30 feet away from us. It should
be 30 yeah. Alright they're 30 feet away. It's a big ass lab. Alright you know what I'm not
gonna run up to them I'm gonna take out my freaking gun, my Grinch gun and I'm gonna pop
one in them do it all right let me hold it sideways yeah I hold it sideways and
it's a and it's a big sniper rifle style thing and I hold it okay that's an eight
on the attack roll yeah the whichever one you're shooting dodges it pretty easily
okay I shoot it I have an additional or no wait I have advantage because it's a
say I have my assassinate ability oh so I get to roll again yeah I just noticed
that when I was looking for my extra attack ability can I do that is that yes
okay can I just realize you have that that's 11 so that's not much better no
and it's not it's not enough to hit all right but Aaron I I say from the sideline
airball obviously you have an extra attack I have my extra attack I'm gonna
to spin the gun around on my finger like it's like like a cowboy would do right
and then shoot again it's the ground it's cool I'm gonna let it slide it
kicks up no it's badass all right and I say yee-haw - right okay do I still have
advantage on the second attack yeah cuz they still haven't taken a turn okay
that's a 21 then damn this is like a that shirt being underneath that sweatshirt
is so crazy and I got I got hot dogs shirt yeah my
reveal dog it's lunchtime that's that click right now yeah just hit the Grinch
gun there we go for damage nice okay cool yeah so you which one do you shoot at by
the way just for my purposes folks the one on the left okay the one on the left
as the energy sword staged left the one done when you're looking at the map the
one on the left. So you'd never say stage left again man. Stage left. So yeah you shoot at
them so you shoot it and you can see that the bullet sort of like does this weird
thing where like it lodges into it and it sort of like disintegrates almost but you
can tell that it got hurt from the attack. Whoa. And so the guy like you know he's
just like and just sort of like it lurches back a little bit. Caleb it's your
turn your up bro I offer them my two extra servings of techno slime that I have okay
what do you say I say yo this this shit will get you fucked up come on bro take
a break come you earned it you deserve it I'm hanging out man okay let's let's see
let's see how the persuasion check goes okay yeah with that ten there and there
the one of you one of them already got shot it's not happening hey amen more for
me bro okay cool yeah so it's your turn now that was a free action so you could
still do yes whatever okay I kill them instantly let's see I I'm gonna use my
to a kid away can I use sexual grenade again yeah I'm gonna use my sexual
grenade again. Alright, hell yeah, do it. So do I roll attack first? Yeah, just hit the
sexual grenade button in your... yeah. Nice, that is just enough to hit... to hit them.
So... Nice. Yeah, so this is gonna... Now roll for damage now. What do I do to do that?
Just hit the sexual grenade in the chat. Oh, nice. Nice.
dude I guess it yes you throw it at them and there they are just like oh they're
just like they're like getting covered in calm and just like lighting on fire
and you could see again that the fire and the semen sort of just like fades into
them almost in this weird way like kind of absorbs in but they are still clearly
getting hurt okay so I'm gonna say to the other two real quick mm-hmm I feel
I feel like we're missing something here.
Why is everything that we do, why are they absorbing it?
'Cause they're virtual.
Oh.
(laughing)
Sorry man, I'm fucked up, bro.
Sorry, dude.
Did you see that rip I took earlier?
Yeah, it was sick.
I saw that too.
That was a heroic dose of techno slime that I did.
Anyway, I'm gonna go over here,
Then I walk over to the corner.
Okay, yeah, okay for sure.
Uh, and uh, uh, yeah.
It is now your turn Patrick Yoda.
Despite your three, you actually did quite well compared to them.
Alright, um, so they're still 30 feet away.
Could I, no, why would I use Yoda's mind?
You could if you wanted to.
Oh shit, I accidentally hit hoverboard boomerang.
I meant to minimize it.
I'm sorry.
I meant to minimize it well that's a good roll you could just go with that yeah
you know what I'm just gonna go with that yeah I launch it I launch it 30 feet
away yeah go for it okay roll for damage then all right you obviously got him
crap which one do I hit for damage again just click the name in the chat yeah oh
yeah chat - nice yeah so you swing it you throw that hoverboard boomerang it
It, uh, what move do you do, uh, when you do it?
What's the, what's this, what's the skateboarding trick you do?
I'm curious.
Um, I do like a, like a spin, like I do like a, like the Rodney Mullen, like
one wheel, like spins that he would do in those videos and I do one of those to,
uh, get speed on the hoverboard and then I launch it across the room.
Yeah, you launch it across the room, it like, is spinning around and it's just like breaking
a bunch of test tubes and shit.
Uh, just, and like, catches him off guard and just whips one of them across the face.
And his head knocks it to the other one.
And uh, one, the one that you hit Cameron is looking pretty fucked up.
The other one is still holding together.
But uh, it's their turn now.
So let's see how they try to fucking manage this.
So the one guy with the energy sword, he runs up to you guys and he draws his energy sword
and he's going to try to slash at you Cameron.
He's going to try to like just see how he does though.
Oh yeah I don't think, what's your AC?
Oh I think I just see.
My AC is 15.
Oh that's just enough, yeah.
So he swings his energy sword at you.
How do you try to get out of the way and how does he hit you before I roll for damage?
Oh, well I try to do a limbo, but I lean back about one inch.
I'm very inflexible.
Yeah that's just one inch shy.
If I had gone two inches it would have missed me.
Oh yeah it would have changed everything.
Yeah but instead you went one and you take eight damage from this energy sword attack.
Damn.
just slashes through you. Damn I'm at 4 HP. Yeah and uh now what he's gonna do is he's
going to use his additional action to stare at you Ray William Johnson and I
need you to roll. I'm in the corner bro leave me alone I'm fucking up. I need you to roll a
deck saving throw right now it's not enough so manage it's still not enough
now so he makes perfect eye contact with you and like a please stop a be I
seriously can't handle this right now a beam that is imperceptible to everybody
else like kind of comes out of his eyes and goes a little rule you know whatever
the fuck like that kind of shit like please man I'm serious and you take let's
see what happened you take is never a good start to a sentence in D&D yeah you
take a slice of cake and it's delicious you take five psychic damage and you
You have disadvantage now on checks because you are paralyzed.
What?
Dude.
Oh man.
So you have disadvantage on any relative checks.
You are paralyzed for one minute of in-game time.
So each round in a battle is six seconds.
But you have at the end of each turn, you have a chance to break out of this paralysis.
Okay.
I'm chilling then.
Yeah.
So you're, that's where you're at.
And then this other guy, he's going to take out the needler and he's going to shoot right
you
my mouth can still move and I'm just like,
yeah, if I wasn't paralyzed right now,
I would pretty much dodge that pretty easily.
- Yeah, so a couple of the needles go into you
and I need you to make a constitution saving throw.
- Okay. - So just go to your con.
Nice, good, okay.
So you feel like, you know, what is that noise?
- I got an 18.
- You guys have a needler noise?
- Yeah, it's Cameron. - I'll put it in.
I mean, I'll just edit it in.
- Yeah, Cameron, can you put that in?
Okay. - I'll put it in.
there Caleb just so I have it. It's like meow. Okay yeah so it is a really random meow noise and
the needlers go into you and you feel your body start to vibrate but then it
stops you master resist it using your your your just your fortitude and your
whoa your pure Yoda wisdom. That was cool man. Yeah that was awesome. But you
still take respect you still take a damage though never mind yeah you're a
loser wait so how much damage do I take a just
a it could have been more you take a okay so Oh current and so now it is your
turn Cameron all right the one with the energy source the one that's near me
that's the one that's looking pretty bad right yeah all right I'm gonna whack him
in
one of them you can swear actually just phases through him.
What the F?
I say, "What the F?" and then I try again with my extra attack.
That's a 17.
Yeah, that's gonna hit.
Alright, okay.
So, I mean, I'm gonna tell you now, describe your kill.
Seven damage, oh, alright.
Describe your kill on this guy.
Okay, well, I start drumming.
I start using the two, the lead pipes like drumsticks.
Absolutely.
And I'm drumming the intro to Numa by Tool where it goes like...
And I turn to Kalo, to Ray William Johnson, I go, "Hey, I bet this pretty much sums up
how you're feeling right now, pal."
And then...
Okay, and I just go, "What?"
And I say, "It's, you know, it's Numa by Tool."
You're just beating this guy to death and turned the other way, explaining.
Yeah, and my eyes are like, are like spirals like in a cartoon when someone gets hypnotized.
Yeah, and I'm just like, "I... can you please just leave me alone for a few more minutes?"
It's kind of, honestly, this is taking a bad turn for me.
And I turn back to the guy.
And he's just a blob of meat, of virtual meat.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think listening to Tool will help you calm down?
Do you have like an iPod Nano?
I've got a...
Or something?
I have a SanDisk Clip.
Yeah, that's in your inventory.
Absolutely.
Okay, sure.
Just add that in.
Do you have 26 and 2 on it?
I have 25 to 6 to 4.
I don't think that's a Tool song.
that's Chicago it was an accidental download I thought I was downloading 26
- I guess I'll take it it would be one of the most jarring sonic either way
yeah if you thought I was Chicago and you got the tool or if you wanted the
tool and got Chicago just make it run give up listening the music if that ever
I guess I'm never using a line wire again.
Oh man.
Oh crap.
I just realized most of the files on this Sansa clip, they're all the Bill Clinton iFreeClub.com
ad.
So you're going to have to sit there and go through the tiny buttons.
You're gonna have to press the tiny button and find the ones that are actual songs.
That's about 8 gigabytes of video.
I free club.
I'm free club.com clips.
I free club.com clips.
Okay, just give it to me.
Okay.
It's got a clip on the back so you can clip it to your shirt.
Thank you, that is such a great feature.
I love when I clip my mp3 player to my shirt.
I'm gonna need it back after this.
You're never getting this back.
I need it back.
The other guy just shoots himself during this.
No, yeah, it's actually, Caleb, it's your turn.
You're still paralyzed, so there's not much you can do right now.
I challenge you to a battle of wits.
Well...
He says, "I accept."
Okay, riddle me this.
There is a man in the desert.
He's dying.
Okay.
The only thing near him is a rock.
The country?
No.
Please let me finish the riddle. A rock.
He was never attacked and he took no sort of poison.
But he is dying.
Who is the man?
Uh...
I don't know.
Is it Drew Drees?
Would you like a hint?
Yes.
His name is Clark.
Okay, it is Clark Kent from Superman.
Fuck yes, you're right.
Yes, you were right.
Okay, good.
So...
The Rock is Kryptonite.
So I guess I lose.
All right, well you can keep fighting my friends then.
Okay.
Yeah, roll a, roll a...
That went so badly!
Yeah, roll a Constitution saving throw to see if you can sort of shake yourself out of this.
Oh, that's our Nat 20.
Yeah, you are free. You're free of paralysis, so for your next turn you'll be free.
Awesome.
Yeah, and now it is Patrick's turn.
Okay, so the guy... did the guy shoot himself?
No, he didn't.
That was not canon.
Okay, yeah.
So what I'm gonna do... Okay. Do I have like a... no, Caleb's the only one who has the free moves.
Okay. Well you can still move and do stuff, you just can't do a second attack.
Yoda's mind doesn't cost any techno slime. Please just kill him or he's gonna kill me. Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna kill him. Who are you talking to? I'm gonna make him kill himself.
No, Yoda's mine. I'm gonna make him kill himself. Yoda's mine does cost techno slime point. Oh, it does
It costs I think
Your full amount. Oh shit. Okay, but you also have
Excuse me Yoda force
Okay. All right that I
Fucking how many techno slime points does that cost that cost? I have a bunch of techno slime
Yeah, we can just smoke whenever we need to recharge it. That's true. Killed it whenever you can okay, then I use Yoda's mind
mm-hmm and
I
Try to find the most embarrassing thought
He has in his subconscious. Okay. Hell. Yeah, I'm gonna that's that's definitely what's happening here. We roll for him, okay?
This is wisdom. I gave him wisdom.
Oh yeah, nice.
Okay. Hopefully this goes your way.
No, he got a crit.
Uh, 20.
Uh.
So he just like, you try to enter his mind and it's like a perfect prison that just like, boots you right the fuck out.
He says, "Don't go in there."
Okay. So is that my only move?
Um...
I'm screwed.
You can still, you can move around if you want to.
okay then I'm gonna where is he right now he's all the way over here you can see
him on the map he's at the bottom okay I go over here no I run it down so you can
move all right you could move like this I'm behind Cameron okay good okay
perfect okay yeah it is now that guy's turn and yeah he is gonna shoot at you
Cameron so let's see how he does it that you guys do not respect me at all I respect
you and then why are you protecting me I am here can I jump in or is it not my
turn no you made you made your choice and the message is clear but all right
no he he misses though he shoots needler at you and he misses and he hits Patrick
to
action to try to just like ram into you. Oh. Oh no. You got a crit. Oh no. You're so dead.
I'm dead. Yeah I mean yeah you're definitely gonna be knocked out. I hate
I hate to say it let's see how he does though I mean it's gonna happen. I mean
you're already you're definitely knocked out I want to see how bad. Yeah let's do
it. Yeah, it's not great. You take 14. What? Yeah. Okay, so I'm at negative 10. Yeah, so
the way death works in D&D, people have different rules for it, but we would do death saving
throws, so we're gonna do that on this turn. I think we did that actually in our very first
one too. Yeah, you know how you gotta make three successes or three failures, right? Yes,
Exactly. And the only other way that death works, or not the only other, but one of the other ways is that if you...
And yeah, also if you get a crit 1, you take 2 failures. If you get a crit 20, you take 2 successes.
But also, if you lose... if your hit points are in the negatives, up to... that's like your negative of your maximum.
So if your max is 35, if you have -35, then you're just dead. There's nothing but death.
Okay.
now it's your turn so you have death saves you can roll okay your monkey is
just like crying trying to wake you up oh I forgot I had a money yeah yeah yeah
you should have thrown him at the guy damn I should have all right so I make a
death save that's all I can do die and learn all right oh no that's okay die on
the third absolute failure okay you got two failures in oh my god okay see if you
get one more failure you're you're you're kaput yeah yeah make a new character
Patrick I'm gonna kill you in real life I can do anything you didn't go behind
me this wouldn't have happened it's your turn Caleb so it's my turn yeah
okay use our death days on him no what can I do to help my girlfriend
uh... he he he you have a a healing ability i believe
uh... and then use
so it
you should be able to use that if you have enough time to sign what you do
what is my what is my healing ability
where is this
senior spell used it last time i think i'll
to save that child from being covered with commerce on the new
okay
yet it gets called going viral and i a last time you posted a about a
classes
or something. Oh yeah. Okay I used going viral. Yeah so what that means is that you are able
to disperse 10 hit points amongst your crew. So what are you at Cam? Negative 10. Fuck!
I can only get him to zero?
Oh no.
I guess so.
I'm gonna die.
Oh my god, I'm so stupid.
Okay, I mean.
You don't have to use it then if you don't want to.
Okay, yeah, I don't use it.
That sucks.
Just kill the guy and then heal me after.
Yeah, okay, I just, I am going to destroy this guy with one of my awesome abilities.
Yeah.
I'm gonna use, uh, I'm gonna use my dong blade.
*laughter*
You have advantage on everything right now.
True.
Oh no wait, yes.
Yeah, yeah, I still have advantage.
Yeah, you do.
*laughter*
It's just not enough, man.
Oh my god, Keem.
Yeah, you run up to him.
Oh shit, I made you wide.
You run up to him.
*laughter*
You run up to him and you try to swing your
dong blade at him.
And he just sort of deftly steps
aside and he says he says another riddle okay all right I have another riddle for
him mm-hmm okay I get down on one knee I say here's a riddle for you will you
marry me okay I guess I'll allow it roll persuasion let's see why not all right I
still have advantage right yeah he's like absolutely not killed my friend
Yeah that was a that was just part of the proposal he was I planned that he's
alive he's just pretending. Let me ask him let me ask him he picks up his friend's corpse he
says hey were you a part of this proposal was this a part of it? And I go yes I totally was.
Okay I could you're moving your mouth more. I was a part of the proposal. You're moving it more than you were when you were just talking.
I can't wait for the wedding.
I will be the ring bearer.
Yeah, he just, he just, a single tear rolls down his face and he puts his friend down.
Patrick Yoda, it's your turn.
Patrick, kill him.
Yeah, do I just kill him?
I mean there's no, you could try.
Patrick, get between me and him.
I'm not gonna kill him in mobility, just jump fight him.
Yeah, kill him.
Yeah, use your-
I jump over Cameron.
Okay.
And uh, how many Techno Slams-
You're standing on me.
many techno slam points do I have now yeah you see on your bio yeah I know I just
used the hoverboard no you use Yoda's mind which used up all your techno all
your tech okay so you can just kind of punch him huh I gotta say boys this one
is you know going on do all of my moves do need techno slime no your your hoagie
attack does not okay all right then I am gonna roll you guys did a lot of damage
to him in the beginning so so could go okay
hoagie surprise that's seven seven that's it okay yeah damage 10 oh yeah baby
describe your kill wow okay yeah describe it wow I was like I wonder how I'm
gonna fucking do this yeah I was like I was I was so afraid I was gonna have to
come up with another idea I say I say hey idiot as soon as I kill you it's
It's gonna bring Blowtoss Piss back to life.
No guarantees, but that's what I think is gonna happen.
Oh, okay.
And you say that in a completely different accent than you have been talking the rest
of the game.
Yeah.
Okay, hold up.
Now listen here, buddy!
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for listening.
I've been pretty accommodating, all things considered.
Will you marry me?
Shut up!
second time's a charm. It's not gonna work this time unless... unless what?
hold on try it again. Will you marry me? yeah let's let's see if you could get
him to marry you before he kills it. Do it. I want to just let's just do it let's play
this and play this game. Roll persuasion. Oh you got a crit! That's what I was
waiting for he says I I don't know it seems so sudden but but he looks into
your swirling druggy eyes yeah and I say I yeah I mean he's hypnotized I love
love where love abides by nobody's timeline love is love love is love is
love wins love wins that's what I always say that's that's I've never said that
But maybe I should start saying that more say it. Yes. Yes love wins. Yes. I'll marry you
Well, this is great because I'm ordained
That's your what's your name? My name is Ray William Johnson. I get what your name with that
It's a iron man number two Ray William iron man number two
Great has a certain ring to it. Yeah, it's great cuz I'm ordained and I can get this all done right now
I'm also a notary. Oh, so I can get this all done. Please perfect. All right, so just one more thing
Quick Patrick while he's trying to get married to me kill him
No, we're gonna go through kill him. No, I have a kill him kill him right now
This is cold feet that was a joke. Okay. I'm sorry. I was kidding
No, I understand cuz when my last my last partner had cold feet and they tried to kill me too.
Are you a boy?
I'm I'm a robot
*laughter*
Wait, I'm a ro- I'm a computer.
Do you have a gender?
No
*laughter*
Okay, this is fine then
I'm also an evangelical christian
*laughter*
Okay, well we're gonna-
evangelical while also being a demon yeah so I mean I'm anyway I'm gonna have a
seed but we'll figure it out we're gonna have a nice Christian wedding yeah we
know yeah we don't have like a glass and a blanket so yeah it's gonna be a
Christian wedding so anyway do you you know we go through with this stuff we go
through with it dearly beloved dearly beloved we're gathered here today to
make these to this computer and this robot get married I just wish my mother
was alive to see this do you do you do I do and that was to both of you so you
can both answer Iron Man number two so we can speed this thing up I do all
Alright, um, I- now, uh, you're married?
And we're gonna get, um,
started on the will!
*laughs*
What?
We're gonna get started writing each other's wills!
Oh, oh yeah, I guess we should write wills, I mean we are married now, after all.
*laughs*
Okay, I'm- I'm uh, I'm a virtual robot, so I don't really- I don't have any assets, is that okay?
But you do have, probably like, information, right?
Uh
I mean he has a needler right?
I'm like, I'm like hired you
Yeah he has a needler and he has information stored in his brain
I was not hired I was created
Yeah but you know who created you of course
That's a truth bomb right there
Uh I have a vague understanding of who created me
Okay so maybe just like include that in your will or something you know
Yeah
Yeah sure okay
And he writes down
And the needler and your money
Yeah you can have the needler
- Okay, okay. - And the hard drive.
- To make it-- - And the hard drive
in your brain.
- True.
And to make it fair here, I'll write my will too.
And I start writing and I say,
"First of all, a big bag of poop."
(laughing)
And that's pretty much it.
- All right, and I'm a notary,
so I have notarized your wedding certificate
and I have notarized both of your wills.
- Okay, good.
And now that that's all settled, how about you turn around for a second?
Yeah, sure. I'd love to do that.
Hey baby, yeah, turn around.
I love turning around. Yeah.
This is part of the evangelical way of turning around.
You wouldn't know this because you're Hasidic.
[laughter]
Yeah, you wouldn't know as a Hasid, but basically evangelicals, the wife always turns around at the end.
Exactly.
Hasids taste water.
Water has a flavor to us.
So then I immediately pull out my my Italian job hoagie that is so it's so much older now
Mm-hmm. It is it's like a couple hours older. It's hard. Yeah. Yeah, and I I just just knock
Just knock his head clean off
At least I knew love
goes flying away and yeah you guys I mean you guys and now we get everything I get
the needler because I don't have a weapon. Take the needler. Combat is over.
Yeah combat is over that's right and you have these two these two heaps. Wait wait wait.
Did we get everything off of the body's corpse? Oh yeah for sure. I have the
needler I don't we have to get the hard drive out of its head. Yeah so you get the
well that was written how about you just bring me back to life instead well we
got we got to get all this stuff we have we have a bunch of stuff to do actually
talking to I didn't say that in a game you guys are acting crazy I'm talking to
you in person and I'm telling you that maybe look at this little bitch blowtoss
he fell asleep in the middle of a fight I can't believe it he must have come
down with narcolepsy or something. He can't even handle his shit. He's like Rowan Atkinson
in Rat Race. Oh look at him, he even looks a little bit like Mr. Bean too. Now that I
think about it, you're completely right. As soon as he fell down, he put on a nightcap
too. I'm so mad about this. And what kind of noises is he making? He's going *snores*
Okay, so you get the needler, you get the will that says who made them, and it just, it says
a man.
You guys got owned.
But we still have the hard drive.
You did roll the persuasion check after he was technically dead, so I couldn't give you
too much.
Oh my god.
But, that was good.
But also, god damn, okay.
Well, I have a weapon now. I don't give a shit.
Yeah. And I'll give you the stats on what the Needler is too.
Okay.
Yeah. But, uh...
You see the broken bodies of the Iron Men before you.
They seem to almost be phasing out of existence as they lie in a crumpled heap.
Instinctually, you all light a cigarette and say some variant of "God damn it."
You hear the familiar French sirens of the Jollibee Peter Thiel private police force pull up to the abandoned porno factory.
Due to all the commotion.
Flashing the traditional Jollibee colored lights of red and I think white and yellow.
I didn't look at the logo when I was writing this. As you gather yourselves,
you see a few Jollibees file in to inspect the scene.
And coming up in the rear is the familiar shape of Jollibee police captain Filipino Mr. Bean.
*laughter*
I can't believe you thought of Mr. Bean.
Holy crap! He looks exactly like Blotos but Filipino!
This is crazy!
Am I still asleep this whole time?
asleep this whole time?
Yeah, you're alive.
Oh, I'm awake.
I wake up?
Yeah, as you're all finally in.
We definitely didn't say you looked like Mr. Bean while you were asleep.
I never said that, but I did say it just now.
I say, I just had the craziest dream where Ray William Johnson got married to a robot
and then the robot's head flew off and then you guys call me Filipino Mr. Bean.
But it's a good thing it was just a dream because...
Yeah, thank God.
Yeah, no, we would have said you look like regular Mr. Bean.
I'm actually Filipino Mr. Bean.
(laughter)
You have an amazing ability to speak.
Cool.
Incredible.
Thank you.
And he just sort of tries to waddle up to you
and he's just knocking shit over and being clumsy.
He's like pointing to one jolly,
be like, "Put that in the bag for evidence."
And he knocks it over before the guy can put it in the bag.
he's like "grrrr" and he comes up to you and he says "I should have suspected the top
tens tattle agency would send their finest to a place like this"
"You kinda sound like emo Phillips"
I was looking up how he talks and there's only that one scene where he sells the painting
and it's sort of like that it's like "uhhh"
"No?"
"Can you guys wanna workshop this with me now?"
I think you're doing well.
I am Mr. Bean.
It's more like a...
Mr. Bean.
I think it's a little something like...
Hello, it's me, Mr. Bean.
There you go.
It's gonna hurt.
It's me, Mr. Bean.
Nobody's gonna know who's talking anymore.
who's talking anymore cuz yeah so perfectly so you're all sick girl oh my
god they got mr. bean as a guest yeah we got him four times
holy crap yeah so that's what he says to you he says how do you do Bruce good I
just come back from the brink of death and I see the world in a whole new light
you had a dream don't tell him that don't tell him we know how to do that I
I see things haven't changed much since Lenny's retirement hmm same old antics
did he used to do this shit cuz I feel like we're being kind of weird he used
to do that but just with himself
Everyone knows Lenny had a few screws loose.
Let's put it that way.
That's news to us.
I would try to keep that under wraps I suppose.
Then he does the thing where he licks his lips.
Classic.
Classic Mr. Bean behavior.
This appears to be an illegal techno-slum lab.
If that's what you're implying.
It's not ours.
How do I know it's not yours?
Because we're telling you. We're telling you!
Okay, roll a persuasion check with advantage.
It's very unlikely that it's yours. I got a 14.
Yeah. Yeah, he believes you. He sort of says, "Mmm, fine, but what are these two here? Who are these two?"
No, it was terrible.
Oh, you're talking about those dead guys. I thought you were talking about me and Blotas.
us
that we got here hold on don't need to relax and he sort of lifts up one of
their he's like hmm these are these sort of like he's like lifting it up and he
he accidentally drops and he gets a little spooked and he makes his little
mr. bean face about it and he says these are that face is crazy yeah I just start
laughing handle this oh my god you are you see one of the Jollibee officers
like this fucking shit again just like he says these are hmm V folks are not
supposed to be able to hurt people what do you mean by that by that by that
dual-time noise that you yeah what what was that I didn't know they weren't
supposed to be able to hurt people oh yes that's folks are meant to be able to
to exist in each world, the virtual and ours, but they're not supposed to be harmful.
These are, seem to be V Spartans.
Puuuups!
See, you did it again right there.
You gotta stop.
It surprised me again.
Do you have something in your throat?
No, I just, all this new information.
I'm trying to be more excited about things because I just suffered a near death experience
and I'm trying to now live each day like it's my last.
So I'm kinda...
- Well, you get this further from Sullivan's voice.
Hmm, how do I...
There are...
It's got to be maybe a bit more British, like...
- That's it.
Good work, Mr. Bean.
- Good work.
Thank you.
- Thank you for leaning more into British than Filipino.
- Yeah.
Oh, I wouldn't even dream of doing that.
[laughter]
So...
- Hmm.
And you just came upon them in this abandoned porno factory.
Yeah, we smelled them from outside so we came in to see what was up.
We were outside and we smelled some moldy digital data.
Just roll deception to see if he believes you smelled them.
Ten.
Yeah, alright, he's sort of like, "Okay, maybe that's how he does it."
You see this who knows?
Yeah, he nods, he nods.
Now, who are known for their sensitive senses?
[laughs]
Hmm, this is interesting.
If I may ask, what were you boys doing here?
What does the Top 10's Tattletail Agency want with this?
An abandoned techno-slime lab and two illegal V folks.
And that's with an X, of course.
Patrick Yoda over here wanted to see if there was any porno left in the abandoned porno factory.
That- yeah, he's a real pig.
I'm a little pig man and I'm disgusting.
He- we can't stop him even if we try.
Look, we were in the neighborhood, I smelled the porno from far away.
He's been caught in the broom closet at work like five times.
Oh, I- for this scenario, I'm an absolute pervert.
Okay, just roll deception.
Until we leave!
I'll say it, Patrick is an absolute pervert.
Nope! The Yoda!
Patrick jacks off at work.
Everybody roll deception.
Oh god.
Uh, let's see. Deception.
I still have advantage.
Nice, yeah.
Let me roll his insight.
He eyes you up and down
with his Rowan Atkinson
looking ass eyes.
He nods and he looks over
and he looks over to Patrick Yoda and he says "You should be chased."
"I should be what?" "Chased." "What are you saying?"
"Alright, come on Ray William Johnson, let's chase him."
"Well, either way." "You better, you have the count of three. One,
two, three, I'm getting you." "I'm not going anywhere."
"Yeah, I tackle Patrick Yoda." "Fuck!"
You tackle him, you just crash in front of a Jollibee detective that is just,
just that is like taking notes just crashed right in front of him he's like
well and just sort of starts to back away yeah you better back away pal you don't
want no part of this yeah you know I don't know this is terrible I start
tickling Patrick ah roll a Constitution saving throw to see if you're tickled me
yeah you're absolutely tickled ah you're laughing dude you are laughing I hate
this so much I don't hear any laughing buddy
this is a cool laugh where'd you get that laughs out Yoda's laugh so he's
The Filipino Mr. Pete is observing this.
And he sort of looks to you all and he says,
"Well, regardless of what you're doing here,
thanks for tracking down these V-Spartans.
And looks like also some illegal,
or at least prototype, TechnoSlime."
And he sort of holds up the pens that shoot the lights.
And he says, "I don't think these have been approved for production yet
by Stakem's Federation of Bodies and Spaces."
Wait wait wait wait wait a second those are that's gel pens those are my gel pens
I need to put those into my backpack you don't even have to roll deception
looking at them right so why are you telling me that you don't know that
you're he's right those are pilot g2s man that I don't know what you're talking
expensive five-pack just not give them back to me please give them back these
I dropped those on the ground when I walked in because I was trying to drop a picture
We're detectives, we need to write down our clues!
Hey, Mr. Bean, fellow Mr. Bean, look over there. There's a banana peel.
What?
It's a slip on it.
It's a banana peel. Somebody has to slip on that.
Okay, I want to do a couple of things here.
I want to do a persuasion check with disadvantage for Cameron,
but then I want to do a persuasion check with advantage for for Caleb for
interesting use of banana peel to so so first Cameron let's go 12 okay yeah he
believes that they were yours and you should be more careful with them and he
he hands you back one of them and then he says ooh a banana peel and he just
wanders over. Okay and then I look I look to Patrick and blow toss and I'm just
like run we get out of there before yeah before he gets wise. Yeah yeah he
slips you guys book it out of there. He slips? Can you describe what is he slip on?
The banana peel what are you talking about?
Yeah what are you talking about?
Oh yeah shit I guess it doesn't exist does it?
Um yeah he slips though
He uh walks up and he
upon not seeing a banana peel
he grows like
freakishly angry
and sort of just conjures up what he
thinks would be a banana peel
in his minds eye and he
slips on nothing
and you see his brain he starts twitching
he's like delighted though
he found a way to be Mr. Bean in this moment. Even with no banana pill. Yeah, he just-
With no banana pill, despite no banana pill, he persisted. Yeah, that's right, that's exactly it.
And he, the other Jollibee cops sort of just like look, look, look around and see
that you guys have gone and you're sort of booking it out of there. So at
this point, you know, it's sort of nighttime. You guys can head back to your
abodes wherever that is take a little nappy poo I'm sleeping outside yeah where
do you guys go to sleep it's his bedtime huh so oh yeah unless you want to keep
exploring no it's sleepy time but you guys would probably be better off doing
that so you can recharge your health and so what I'm gonna do yeah I got a
recharge my freaking house so my mommy in the morning my hoverboard I can lay
down on my hoverboard and then when I lay down on it a little like case goes
around it like a security case right that has a bunch of guns on that has a
minigun on the side just in case anyone tries to break in where do you lay down
in like is there a location in in gun city that you do that anywhere just
anywhere you go yeah you just run till you get tired yeah and you just fall
asleep yeah outside of just like outside of a tattoo parlor something like that
yeah something like that and yeah what about you two do you guys have homes oh
yeah I got a home yeah yeah I have a home and a wife too I go back to my wife
and my kids what's your wife what are your wife and kids like my wife's name
is Cameron and she's my honey she's the most beautiful girl in the world
hi honey and I walk in and I put my I put my pinstripe fedora on my coat rack and
my in my trench coat on there as well and I and and I I walk in and I say hey baby
sorry I know I was out late long day at work I know my big strong detective man
do you think I'm big and strong this is fucked up yeah yeah my name isn't
Cameron shit over in this girl get over here you fucking big second shit give me
give me some pussy
here it comes
back that ass up on me
back that big fuckin ass up
get back that big
yeah, give me that big Dominican ass
she's Dominican also
I married a beautiful Dominican woman
yep, I'm Dominican
(laughter)
- Yeah, yeah.
Pablo and Francesco, go to your shared bedroom.
- Okay, Dad.
- The kids are there the whole time?
- Yeah, they're just there.
- Oh, there you go.
- Go play games.
Mommy and Daddy have to do our taxes together.
Go.
- Yeah.
Roll a deception check on your children.
- Oh, come on, dude.
They're my fucking kids, man.
I don't care if they believe me.
What are they gonna do?
They're gonna stay in the room.
Well, okay, are you trying to deceive them?
Yes.
Yeah, I guess I am.
Okay, if you're not, you don't have to.
If you're just saying shit, you don't have to.
Yeah, they're stupid as shit.
They're just like, yeah, okay dad, and they just like go up to their room and start, and
they put on their, you know, their VR headsets and shove their PSPs inside their chest and
they're hooked into some amazing new kind of Sims dude they're playing
battlefield 7,000 while you do taxes yes I'm with Cameron I'm basically fucking
her big ass this is not okay I love giving you back shots I'm gonna leave
about the name my favorite part - okay so and then I finally I finally busted my
wife and I say I hope that I hope we make a third kid and then I fall asleep
okay and my California King bed she's so I'm rich she sort of looks looks up and
and she says, "God, I hope we don't."
And we cut to Cameron, what are you doing
when you go to bed, where do you go?
- So I assume there's some kind of public park somewhere
in Gun City, yeah.
So in whatever the equivalent of Central Park is,
I have a big tent set up.
- That would be, yeah, that would be the, let me see.
That would be the, okay, cool.
Just looking at shit on my desk.
- Chemtrail Park.
- Yeah, the Chemtrail Ticonderoga Park.
So I got a big tent and I go inside the tent.
- Chemtrail Park, I like, yeah.
- Taking up the entire tent is a snow globe of Whoville,
my home that I emigrated from and I miss very dearly.
And there's a little door on the side of the snow globe
and I go inside the snow globe.
And then inside the snow globe,
there's another smaller tent.
And I go in there and I go to sleep.
and I have Christmas dreams like from that one Christmas poem of the fairies and stuff.
That's really nice.
Because at the end of the day I'm still a Christmas based character even though I don't talk about
Christmas at all or mention bridges or anything.
That's still kind of my theme.
Yeah that's cool.
I basically came in one of the wives' pussies.
Yeah and then I go to Caleb's house, then I go to Ray William Johnson's house and I
kill his wife.
I kill him and I kill his kids.
Please take it back.
And then I suck his dick.
And then you suck my penis because you're my wife!
Yeah but you're dead so.
Nah.
I was really mad.
I go back to my tent and I go back inside my snow globe and I go back inside the tent and
then I go to sleep and I have a really good sleep.
And it was all a dream but then I wake up and I go to Raylan Johnson's house and I kill
him and I kill his wife and I kill his kids and I go back.
I don't suck his dick this time and then I go back to the tent and I go to the snow globe
and I go into the tent and then I go to sleep.
And that wasn't a dream and Caleb's character is actually dead.
No, I'm not.
Where does Sullivan sleep?
Let's hear Sullivan's story.
Sullivan been doing this whole time this is wife is named Cameron he's been
sitting in the car quietly praying hoping you guys are okay because he loves you
and he's and he just sort of falls asleep in the car and I'm sorry I'm
taking notes on these little elements of your characters yeah right down the
Caleb has zero HP and he's dead.
No matter how throw away they may seem, I believe in them.
So yeah, it's the, uh, it's the...
You guys all go to sleep in your respective locations,
nutting in your respective spouses.
Yeah.
Wait, what's my spouse's name?
Uh, it's Cameron.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Yeah. And you wake up the next morning
in your California king bed, in your...
You're in a snow globe, right?
In my wife's still.
Yeah.
Still in.
That's unsanitary.
Yeah, I have like a pit bull's penis that just latches on.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
That's pretty good for you.
It is awesome.
Are you in a snow globe, Blotas, if I get that correctly?
I'm in a tent in a snow globe in a tent, and I'm holding a snow globe also.
Okay, cool.
And Patrick Gote, you're just like sleeping outside of wherever on your hoverboard.
Yeah.
yeah so it's the next morning and Patrick Yoda you hear a horn honk it's a
La Cucaracha but in minor so it's really it's really awful so yeah you hear that
and you see it is the it is the 2007 Ryan Dunn mobile and you see Sullivan and
it's the next morning and Sullivan looks at him and says I was looking all over for you
Come on in we gotta go to mommy's. All right well shit. Yeah do you hop in? Yeah I hop in.
Yeah you hop into the car he's like I got you some snacks in case you need
something. Oh thank you for the snacks Sullivan. What are your favorite snacks?
What's Patrick Yoda's favorite snacks? Digital jerky. Yeah that's what he's got for you.
He's got digital jerks.
They were all out of the teriyaki flavor, but uh...
Jack's Hyperlink.
Yeah, Jack's Hyperlink.
That is good.
At least it's not...
As long as it's anything but digital biltong, I'm fine.
Okay, well, it's definitely not that, then.
Okay.
He's like sweating under his collar. He bought another supply of...
He bought digital biltong.
I'll give it to you later.
But yeah, he...
So anyway,
he drives and now he's driving up to
your place, Cameron.
He drives into the park
and he knocks on your tent.
Yeah. And knocks on your snow globe
in the tent and he knocks on the tent in the snow globe.
He's just trying
to find out how to get to you.
Yeah. Blotas! Blotas!
What's up?
Come on, we gotta get in!
We got to get in
Gotta get in the car. We're going to mommy's this morning. Oh, we're good. Okay. She's already reached out to me
I get into the car and I turn to Patrick and I say man, that's the craziest thing. I thought my mom was dead. I
Had the craziest night last night I fell asleep in the car and I woke up I was covered in in covered in Pringles
which is not always my favorite way to sleep. He's just like rattling on about this.
His little frog legs trying to reach the gas pedal and he drives up to your house
which what does your house look like by the way Ray William Johnson? Does it just look like a
1950s like? No it's like a huge like like Malibu mansion. It's like it's like all
glass in the front you can see you it's all glass in the front there's no
privacy you just see me fucking my wife in the living room. It's like the house in the
bling ring. Yeah exactly yeah. Just like a big cube. Yeah your children are just
upstairs. Yeah it's like it's it's almost like it's cut in half for a sitcom. Yeah
yeah yeah so he pulls up to your sitcom ass house and he sees he sees you with
just like giant morning wood and he's like "Ray! Ray!" "What's up? What's up? Sorry, sorry I've
been fucking my wife all morning and night." "No, I know, I know." "I'm extremely feral."
"Yeah, can you, do you mind getting in the car? We gotta get to mommy's." "Yeah, one second, let me
just fuck my wife one more time hold on I'll wait yeah yeah I took my wife just
absolutely nice throw a big rock at this glass I just go I just go actually monkey
on my wife's thing and then I and then I walk out and I go all of your old
Constitution saving throws and then I you yarts are not seeing that okay I got a
I got a 17. I got a 21. Yeah, you're both fine. He does this all the time.
And then I walk out, I walk out holding my balls and like swinging my left hand like
right to left, walking like a pimp. And then I open the door and I get in and I say, "What's
up, fellas? How was your night?"
I'm fine.
- I'm fine.
- Yeah, I had this--
- Fine reminds me of my wife.
(laughing)
- At this point, I'm just sick of seeing it.
- Yeah, me too.
- Okay, yeah.
So Sullivan keeps driving and he's saying,
yeah, mommy contacted me early this morning
about a plan she has,
but I'm just gonna take you guys there now.
and uh... i got all your favorite snacks and should have done that for
for each of you. Oh you have my wife's pussy?
That's awesome.
Yeah, he hands you your wife's pussy.
Wow, just like I remember it.
Oh you have Ray William Johnson's wife's pussy? No, he only has one copy.
He hands you one too, Cameron. Fuck you. That's right.
Yeah, so you two, he's eating beef jerky, you two are eating a vagina.
And you drive up to Mommy Kid Grocery.
These guys look the same!
We're sharing the same one.
We're...
Yeah, you just handed us all the same...
We're Lady and the Tramping.
Hold on!
I think I got Blowtoss's snack.
I need to exchange.
I need to exchange this.
Why do you...
Oh, are you saying you don't like it?
Well, I'd rather have some beef jerky right now.
I...
All right.
I'm very hungry.
You don't like the flavor?
No, I just...
You don't like the cheesy, the cheesy, gooey flavor?
He picked me up first.
I had to skip breakfast.
Yeah, it tastes like fried salami.
So, yeah.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm looking at my notes.
I will commend you, though.
This tastes exactly like Cubano.
down that Caleb's character's wife's pussy tastes like cheese is that what
you're writing down in the notes? No it tastes like tastes like mungu. It tastes like
porcini mushrooms. So yeah you guys are arguing about what pussy tastes like.
No you don't understand it tastes like the back of your hand. See Nick, the back of your
And you drive up to uh to Mommy Good Legs so
You get back through the Lockheed Martin shopping district down sepia alley to Mommy Good Legs Club
The feet on the end of the legs are now fuzzy morning slippers instead of red stilettos and the door slash pussy is now closed
But you can walk in and when you do you same this you see the same seedy nightclub as before
Except the lights are turned all the way up and the V folks are in but most of them are relaxing or getting ready for the
Opening shift in the early evening
Some are serving breakfast to the more senior staffers like mommy herself
Mommy sits at a private booth at the far corner of the clubs
Sipping on a morning mimosa and reading the Epoch Times the only news organization left
Welcome boys, please have a seat
She calls over I now that I could see this place in full light. There are stains everywhere ma'am
I just got to tell you that
yeah, we do our best to clean it up, but uh
Boys will I can't tell what's blood and come a
Lot of it is yeah, the solid mix between that stag party is still here. Did you guys even try?
Yeah, I can smell it. It's been a couple hours
and I think that you guys didn't even you guys didn't even unhandcuffed Jamal and
you didn't clean the shit off of his head it seems like nothing has changed except
the lights well generally we sort of hope that it sort of works itself out that's
sort of Jamal isn't moving is he dead probably hasn't had water or something
to eat in quite a while I mean you wanna he could have just eaten the shit off of
Yeah, you could investigate Jamal and see if he's alive or dead.
Let's see.
I poked Jamal with a slipchip.
Wait, do I still have advantage on stuff?
No, it's the next morning.
Oh, which reminds me.
Let me not do that.
Oh no!
Yeah, you have, with your, with the next morning by the way, I should say, I forgot to even mention this.
Yeah, Caleb, after drinking the raw Techno Slime,
Just fucking the shit out of your wife.
Just fucking the absolute life out of my fucking dumb wife.
Murdering your wife and your dick.
Yeah, but you wake up the next morning and your head is throbbing.
And everybody looks almost like, they look like they're made of colored pencil.
Like everything's so indistinct and it's just like a mess.
So you're going to have a disadvantage on dexterity, any sort of dexterity based ability check.
or saving throw for the day.
Because your head's just throbbing.
Yeah.
I got hired in a motherfucker.
And we get to recharge our HP and shit, right?
Yeah, all your HP is fully--
That's technically a long rest, so everything is fully--
Full HP,
full Techno Slime recharge,
as well.
And...
Yes.
So, yeah.
What do you do? Investigate. Okay, yeah.
Yeah, Jamal's alive, he's just like...
He doesn't breathe when he sleeps.
[laughter]
Just that, obviously.
'Cause he's a worm.
'Cause he's a worm, yeah.
Yeah, and you can obviously try to wake him up, too.
Okay. I kick him in the head.
Yeah.
It's like, "Gah! Blugh!"
And he's sort of like, the shit falls off his head and lands in his mouth.
[laughter]
"Ha ha, you ate a boob."
"Eat a..."
He's trying to say, "No, I didn't."
- It's in your mouth right now, I can see it.
Breakfast is served, Jamal.
- Oh look, he thought it was a Twix bar.
- No.
- You ate a poop like a Hershey Kiss.
- You ate a Hershey's poop.
- No, I didn't, no.
- This is Ray William Johnson's poop.
- Why'd you, okay, so you still ate poop though.
- You still admit it, he still admits it, oh my God.
- You spit it out right then, what was that about?
- I did, I spit, because it's poop
and I don't want it in my mouth.
- But it was in your mouth.
So you admit that you had poop in your mouth?
So why'd you put it in your mouth in the first place?
I didn't put it in my mouth, somebody kicked me in the head.
Hey man, listen, between you and me...
What's up?
It's fine, right? It kind of tasted normal.
I heard that! I have very strong ears!
No, poop is so disgusting to me!
I heard what you said!
Poop is seriously so bad!
I heard what you said! I have the greatest hearing in the world!
Listen to me, Jamal.
That's canon in the game!
If you liked that taste, you can always call me.
call me you just said you can always call him if he likes the taste. Oh poop is so
gross I'm wanting to vomit even thinking about it. I can still hear you I can hear every whisper I hate this taste and smell of delicious poop. I like that.
Well this is all going. Mommy called you over and you guys instead. Yeah well
then well. Kicked your bartender in the head and started arguing about shit. Well this
is all going on I go up to mommy good looks and I'm like hey do you want to go
get like brunch or something like I like romantic brunch like a roll roll I
heard that - persuasion I heard that he has a girlfriend they're gonna get
married I got a 15 yeah she sort of says yeah maybe sometime I go I go like yes I
scream yes right into her face yeah okay she sort of wipes a bit of your spittle
off her face. Can you get your other two friends over here? They seem to be
berating and savagely beating my bartender. Oh no it's cool they're just
they're just playing around with him. Okay. They'll be fine. I do I do want to
I do want to speak with them. No let's just let this play out let's see what
happens. Sure yeah yeah so you guys continue your shit argument. And then five
Five hours later.
Five hours later, it's the next,
20 hours later, it's the next day.
So you guys go over, you sit down with mommy good legs.
What do you think poop tastes like?
You know what it tastes like!
Is it good or bad to you?
You said that it's good, you said that it's good,
I heard you say it.
You're talking about this as you're walking over.
I heard you say it, you said it was good.
I hate poop.
You like it! I heard you say you like it!
If you don't like poop, then be not a Yoda.
Okay, I'm looking around the room, I see...
Oh, Patrick, it seems like you're a Yoda, so you like to eat poop, yes?
It does not work that way!
I just said it works that way, and I think it does.
It doesn't work that way.
It does work that way.
I start tickling Patrick again.
Rope persuasion.
Alright, let's see.
Let's see.
Yeah, do it.
With disadvantage because he's hungover.
Yeah, why am I fucking here?
Do it.
10.
All right.
Yeah, I guess this would really be, I guess Patrick Yoda, what you would do is roll, I
guess roll a wisdom check against it, I guess.
It's really insight or something.
Yeah, 22.
yeah so I guess Caleb you didn't persuade him. I don't really remember what that was for.
sorry I'm hungover. Disregard. No you said you made your bed you better lie in it
yeah you wish I would lie in it. Listen I'm gonna listen I'm gonna lie in both
of your beds if you don't shut up right now. Yeah you would like to lie in my bed
And then you would love to lie in it. I'm gonna lie in your bed
With you no yeah, you would like that, huh?
Mommy hey mommy good legs. What's the deal?
Yeah, yeah, she sort of was just like doing something else
And yeah, she sort of sees you guys come over. She says well boys. It's good to see you
When any of y'all care for some breakfast?
No, yes. Yeah. No. No, actually Patrick Yoda just told me he wants a poop for breakfast. I don't want poop for breakfast
Yeah, why'd you tell me that then I didn't say it you did. He said it all confidence
I could get you poop if you need oh you could
I'm sure you'd like that. Yeah, you would know you would
You would I'm looking at your Wikipedia page right now. Hey William Johnson. I want you to try to to try to
to try to roll a stealth check to see if you could secretly order poop without
anybody noticing and Patrick you had a roll roll in a a person I didn't check
the sea and I roll a perception check - yeah try to see if you can hear well ah
damn your perception so good I got a 20 dude I got him what do you say what do
you say Ray William Johnson's you're secretly trying to order shit yeah can I
please haven't wanted have a serious poop for my friend here no it's not true I
turned I turned to Ray William Johnson I say your secrets safe with me thank you
friend and then I turned and then I turned to mommy good legs and Patrick
Yoda I say this MF eating poop lol I'm not talking you're so stupid you're so
stupid I I pick up Patrick Yoda and I throw him across the room and then I
turn to mommy good looks and I say okay what's the deal mommy good legs I'll
just get us all some pancakes that you know it's not poop it's fine you know
He's being coy. Do you know why when each of you look at me you only see what is
most beautiful to you? Because you're cool and beautiful? It's because of those
cocky-less riffs you have installed. What? I have something installed? Yeah yeah so
you all have cocky-less riffs installed. Everyone when they turn 13 in gun city
gets a coculus rift installed into their penis.
So that is canon.
In this arc at least.
They allow me to change what can be seen.
How each individual sees me.
Using virtual reality superimposed on my form.
Now, I'm quite the looker myself,
but if I can make everyone see exactly what they want,
well, that's where the money is.
However I can only be mommy.
She sort of smokes a cigarette and ashes it out on a pile of poop as it's served.
That's the strength of V-Girls like Haseki Tsune.
They can be whatever you want them to be, because they ain't even real to begin with.
And sometimes I think that's what happened to Sean.
He got lost in a world that promised him infinite possibility.
He got a small taste with that whore wife of his and from there got hooked on the stuff.
Into Matrix 2 you can do whatever you want, be whatever you want.
I think that might be where Shawn is.
Come with me boys.
And she sort of gets up from her booth and starts leading you back towards the dressing
room where you guys first went in to see her.
I think she's gonna have sex with us.
Okay, this is seriously awesome.
I'm not ready.
Oh, is it your first time?
Yeah.
Wow. I'm 899 years old and it's my first time.
Here, let me show you how.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, the three of us start having sex.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
We can end it there, if you want to.
Four.
Yeah, fuck it
It's like it's like yeah eat you mama tambien style though. Yeah, right
Yeah, like Cameron is just kind of like we first all three of us start having sex together
But then Cameron slowly is kind of pushed out and then it's just me and Patrick fucking
And I'm recording. I'm recording it the whole time. Yeah, turn that off
Yeah, that's called revenge porn and it recently got banned from born up
Yeah, I'm sure it did
Yeah, I'm sure it's gone
I
Guess you guys have like a e2 mama
Whatever kind of sex time excuse me what kind of moment me to mama?
Was that movie you say me to moment me to moment?
Eetu Mamatambiyan, yeah.
Alright, let's just clarify that.
Yeah.
And, uh, yeah, you guys have that, I guess, in the middle of the club.
And then you move on.
I'm just gonna put into my inventory
really quick video of Patrick and Caleb having sex.
I'm just gonna type that in.
That's in my inventory, canon.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, speaking of inventory, do I still have the...
You have the needler, and I'll give you that.
needler and I'll give you the needler no I have the needler but from the previous
game the I made a backup of the the whatever the oh that's that's actually a
good question so let's figure that out next let's figure that out after we
finish recording yeah we'll talk yeah we'll talk about that because I think
that's gonna open up some other talks in a good way yeah so um yeah so uh yeah you
You guys go and you follow mommy into the back into the sort of back green room area or whatever and
you see she sort of walked all the way down to the end of the hallway and
It's a it looks like sort of a just a blank, you know gray wall
but she presses, you know a tile in it and it's sort of a unfurls and
There's a door and now it's sort of a staircase a spiral staircase and she walks you down the spiral staircase
and I trip you trip okay I trip and I fall the entire way down yeah you fall
the entire way down yeah just everyone you're like oh just all the way down
yeah and while and while and while you're uh you're falling she's talking
she's talking okay yeah I'm falling at the exact pace
You're like, "Ow, ooh, ow," while she's saying, "Doing business in Gun City isn't easy.
Maintaining your enterprise means being ruthless, calculating, and jacked in.
The problem with being jacked in is that's hard to do.
There are only a few working portals into the Dev Matrix 2, and they're only accessible
if you have the money to spend."
And yes, she's telling this to you guys Sorkin-style, walk and talk.
You get to the bottom of the spiral staircase.
Ow.
And you see a circular room with like electrical paneling and a control center and like lights and lasers are shooting around the room calculating things.
In the middle you see a raised platform and it has three awesome race car beds in it.
Whoa.
Okay.
She looks to the race car beds and she says, "This is how Sean would get into
D-Matrix 2 when he was frequenting my club. This bunker is essential to my
business. It's where I recruit V-Folks, and that's what the next of course, and
snuff out the virtual competition. It's also how I expand and monitor the rest
of the virtual world. Sean would come in here and make race car noises until he
came. Then he'd go into D-Matrix 2. However, these things," and she slaps one of
on the race car beds.
They haven't worked in the last couple of months.
- So why not?
Sorry.
(laughing)
- No, that's fair.
That's a good question.
I don't know actually.
They've either ran out of power,
they're missing a piece,
or sometimes I think sabotage.
But to get the-- - Did you sabotage it?
- No, so that, no.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, I believe you.
We just have to check on everything, you know,
like we're detectives, so.
- Exactly.
I'm just doing my job.
If we didn't ask, it would just, it would look bad.
Right, no.
And that leads to my next question.
Do you know, like, the answer to the whole mystery?
She doesn't, believe it or not.
Okay, well, you know, we just have to ask.
Yeah, it's just like, it's policy, you know.
What kind of detective would I be if I didn't ask?
Like any good noir, everybody only has bits and pieces of what's going on.
True.
I
my taste.
There is something else we need to do before we even risk trying to find another way in,
or find a way to even repair these things.
We need to know if Sean got lost in Da Matrix 2, if that's where he even is, if he's alive,
and the only way to find that out is to look through the Jacked In Archives and Records
offices in the United Health Group incorporated in Marlboro District.
Those records are publicly available, but only to those who can privately afford it, and
it costs about 10 million tokens to view.
WHAAAAAT?
So you can either break into the records, or get an insane amount of money very quickly.
I personally don't want to know which one you choose to do, but once you get it done
you can meet back here and figure out a way in.
I sent your frog scouting earlier this morning to draw up some plans to help with the heist,
should you choose to do so.