(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City
A Broad City
Playtime continue fun
You thought you'd have a simple
Christmas celebration on a luxury
getaway space station called
Pleasure Palace. What the fuck are you
doing? He's playing
He's playing with his phone. I'm moving all the shit around
so that my phone doesn't get onto
the cables and doesn't make a noise. Thank you
That turned into a disaster
Sorry, that's the next part of the
That was fine what you did, I'm sorry
Alright, Pat.
Your boy, New Sullivan, stolen from you.
Catatonic, you slept for months.
Now, you awaken, disturbed, but ready for action.
Belinda Crokes, Leo's gal Friday, contacted you to handle the case of Playtime.
The man who's been terrorizing Pleasure Palace.
Who stole away your boy.
Ah, well we don't know if he's a man, now that I think about it.
Oh, clue.
It's my-
Uhhhh, clue.
clue you gave it up you sucker give up and it was a clue pad it's not I'm ready
to write we got you buttercup is actually give me your forehead I'm gonna
write it's sort of a incidental red herring I might be doing well it's
writing do not write your forehead says man you got a papery forehead you got a
paper it does say man does say man people will know when you walk down the street
which these days they probably want they probably need that yeah I probably had
name tag. Probably. Caesar. Caesar. It says Caesar. Man. Man. So you went to the royal
district in the pleasure palace and you took the job. And then you were attacked by a nope
mysterious monster. Don't hype. Stop that. Yep. Fuck you. Okay. Buttercup. Afterwards
Playtime struck again, another childless couple, but this time members of the Royal Guard, a grave crime.
Now you have a new murder on your hands. I'm directing our attention to the new murder.
It's right here on the table. Oh shit motherfucker. Oh!
And some leads to track down.
Damn!
So I'm gonna give you guys a little bit of a, just a little bit of a
kind of a little recap, it's been a little bit.
So you're on space station Leo's Pleasure Palace
Courtesy of King Leo who you guys knew as Leo the collector yeah back in the day. He's had that gully
Mali yes, so we get a galleon galleon go
your son
New Sullivan was kidnapped right you hope by playtime
Mysterious serial killer who's been targeting primarily childless couple so how would he why would he be killed?
We've lost all hope because no serial killer in their right mind
Kidnaps a kid that serial killer kill a kid before or only adults so yeah
You guys are gonna get the debrief on this so he's trying to get us to come get it so that we fall
So we'll be so we will be abandoning our child. Yeah, so yeah you three are detectives, right?
You decide to do one last job again, right?
To make sure
Cool, so what happened recently and we'll talk we'll talk through some of the app
I kind of want to like I feel like a lot of time
I kind of do a little bit too much of a like so what do you want to do so I want to actually like
Kind of curtail your options here make it clear what you have going on
So you just killed a monster that seemed to rise up from somewhere inside the space station
Yeah, it's been like three weeks. Yeah, it's been a minute. So nope. It's been three weeks. I just said that okay
That's you know what I'm sorry you're right is what you just said. It's not a minute was a minute ago
Okay, fancy man with your literal
ideas
So you're standing right now in the mess hall where that childless couple was killed this time their members of the Royal Guard
Playtime has killed two other couples
so
Is killed so it was kidnapped or killed?
New Sullivan then you guys were catatonic and then he went on
They went on a little spree of killing other couples. Tell me he did not get Tom Holland and Zendaya
No comment
Play time has killed two other couples. So both of them were new gun City residents
so you guys are on the state plates the the the the space station and
But so they were just residents of that of this the space station, but they were never like actual members of Leo's Royal Guard
That's where it's kind of like now like Elvis is getting kind of serious. They're getting kind of bold
Every time they've killed them the space station has had like a like a blackout
Like so not like the lights are out, but like the powers down which happens in massive like
Space stations that can happen on occasion, but it seems to be literally this happens then somebody dies
Okay
Yeah, the lights the lights go out like the power goes out basically like there's like among us like among us
What's among us?
And me
Plays it with my damn neck. No, I don't play with adults only
Can you show the adults only?
Patches plays a special copy of the game called among kids
It's not true. His character is two times bigger than everyone
It's not true
Glass it's not Julio. Can you please put up the the thing I wanted to have put up?
No
Yeah, thank you. Oh here. I'll so
This is a basically a sort of a map of
So cam is leaning over so that people can see the space station
But so I can't a station is on the back of our that's one that's usually out of this window. Yes, that's correct
So one that we're on yes the one that you're on
We talked about the logic here you guys are controlling
Oh, we're in a control booth. You're in a control. We are that's like yes sitting right and we're controlling these
These guys are in the table where we're playing is in the thing in the window
All right, so makes perfect sense only one look it looked cool. I just look that's what I wanted. Okay. Let's okay
No, you're fine. So um
Sorry, I'm pulling it up on my end as well. Just so I can well. It's right there. Oh, it's a good point so nope
Nope, that's pretty good.
It is there though.
Okay, I believe you.
Why does this spaceship look like the things you see in the ads that are like,
"This thing will suck the shit out of your clit"?
If you had to guess why.
If I had to guess why?
Yeah.
Is it supposed to?
I thought maybe it was supposed to be a shrimp or something.
Shrimps will also suck the shit out of your...
Is that what you said the first time you saw one of those?
Like, "Ah, it's like a fucking purple shrimp!"
"Ah, it's like a shrimp for your pussy!"
Yeah.
It was like a, uh, a stranded, like, uh,
a sailor stranded at sea.
It's like a woman used to masturbate to cucumbers for decades
and for hundreds of years they put shrimp
in that one when a woman called the top artist a quid.
I wanna know, I wanna know why it looks like that
for the story.
He's going into the... He's a pleasure pal.
He's going into the back of the... Also, it's a sex toy.
Leo loves toys.
No, you're not.
There's lots of things going on here.
- Pat's going into the sex toy shop at the mall
and he's looking through the window
and everyone sees him drooling.
But they're all morphing into shrimps.
(laughing)
- Oh.
- So you guys can see the,
so where you are now is that royal district
on the top there.
So, and you can see there,
there's New Gun City, the upper district,
and there's New Gun City, the downer district.
- Weatherman vibes.
And then there's the resort, the Ten Seasons,
which is in the middle over there.
- I'm just pointing random spots I can't tell.
- Then there's Funderland, which is temporarily closed,
which is the amusement park mall,
fun zone where Leo's, majority of Leo's collection is.
I think the pointing is helping somebody, keep doing that.
Then we've got the command deck,
that's where Gumby Superior, who you met earlier,
the captain of the space station is,
and his crew are among the station operations
and also in the command deck.
- Hey, here's a question.
Why do you need a captain?
Doesn't that space station just kinda fuckin' sit there?
- Well, yeah, it's a good question.
Well, I think he's kinda running the space station.
- It's like Deep Space Nine, it's because they have a--
- So he's a president.
- He's sort of like a president.
- There has to be a military presence.
- Yeah, he was, yeah, so he was a war hero
in the Vampire Wars, who now works as a contractor
for this kinds of things.
- No, that's all you need to know.
- That explains everything.
- Yeah, so he was hired kind of on contract.
It's also kind of a political move by Leo to be like,
look, I can get the general from your Vampire Wars
and just bring him onto my space station.
- Leo's badass for that.
He's like Commander Sisko.
- Yeah, I haven't seen Deep Space Nine.
- You're like Commander Crisco.
- Come on, come on.
So then you have the ship crew quarters over there,
then you have the leprechaun slave quarters.
Then you have the undercity.
- Interesting creative choice.
- The undercity is not--
- Wait, underwear?
Oh, did I do that?
Fuck!
- So the undercity isn't like an officially sanctioned part
of the space station, but it is,
if you go through the downer district,
you will eventually get towards the undercity.
There's obviously, there's a couple docking bays,
One for freight, so like for supplies that are brought in by the Downer District.
Then you have docking bays for military ships by the Royal District.
And then docking bays for tourists who are right inside of the Ten Seasons Resort.
In between the ship, so that sort of like spot between the top half and the bottom half.
Lots of goods and folks, in this case leprechauns and ship crew,
fly through there sort of an anti-gravity kind of like section of
maintain to hold their breath
I know so they put on space suit and they like will help shepherd goods up and
also travel that way like in that movie
that's a dope ass basically that ways they don't ever interrupt anybody at the
resort so you guys go you guys have to kind of go through space I don't have to
take the long way around
yes they also have to take a long way around there is all hey now I want to
take the fucking long way around
Well, you can't. We do.
I mean, you should have to take the long way.
Well, you guys get to use the zippy loop, which is the automatic.
You guys used that earlier. It's sort of the like kind of like super fast train inside of the space station
that gets you to wherever you want to go.
So where the leprechauns are not allowed on the zippy loop.
That's why you had that altercation last time.
If you remember, the ship crew can ride the zippy loop.
But if you're transporting goods or, you know, for speed,
it makes more sense to move through that little chamber there.
Finally, there's the guts of the station.
And you basically just have the entrances to them.
The whole station has the guts inside them, right?
It's just like places for the plumbing, electricity,
the power cores that help power the station.
All of that exists there.
The ones that are visible to anybody who's works at the,
or is on the main area of the ship,
or just the upper and lower section of it.
But there's a separate map entirely for the full guts of the station
That's where the crew and where the leprechaun slaves do most of their work maintaining the ship
Sometimes moving between certain places my guts are full of ship, too
So where you guys so I want to give you guys that that kind of overlay because right now we're moving into sort of the
Investigation portion right so you have the the the dead couple here in the mess hall you guys are the detectives
There's also a dead monster outside that might you might want to look at as well
You can do that and then this
It's that the puppy no, it's not quite that it was that's not the puppy. No is this guy?
Yeah, yeah go down here
Yeah, I remember that guy
So you can start to examine the bodies and then figure what to do from there examining
You can also go to the previous murder scenes as well after you do that.
And then you can also go to the space station, the command deck as well and visit with Gumby Superior.
You can talk with some of the ship crew and some of the people who are in the inner workings
so you can get other information from them.
So that's kind of... And then you can also go back to the resort.
If you remember, Giancarlo also said, "Hey, if you ever want extra money,
I have some things I could ask you to do."
So he kind of has like side quests for you basically.
You guys get a thousand tokens a day as a stipend.
It costs you each 500 to stay in the hotel every night every night
So we get so you basically get 500 token is like 25 cents arcade token
So it's not that much money you guys you guys are also there are shops in the upper
District the lower district and in the under city. I'll just tell you that where you can get some
Exclusive gear to your characters if you save up
Appropriately, and if you do side jobs for Giancarlo as well
But so that's kind of lay of the land
Do you want to start investigating here that people are kind of around you kind of looking expectantly you guys are the detectives who were just?
Hired where there's a dead couple so you guys right now at the mess hall the royal district
There's I was just gonna say I want to go to Auntie Anne's
the Auntie Anne's would be in
Funderland here there is
Unky Ben's and says and he just has rice
Yeah
Call me Gary C. Enterprise. What color is he? He's purple like everybody else. Okay. Thank you asshole. Thank God
Yeah, you weren't being the racist. Um, I would know go down to the table cuz I'm already here
I'm is Ian like hello. Hello. Hello. Hello there. Let me drive. Hello. Hello
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello
Hello. Hello
Hello
Wait that worked. That's all move
So yeah, I mean you guys okay wait. No. I'm investigating them right now. Okay, cool. Yeah, roll just roll it you can roll investigate
Investigating like that threes company before the crowd oh my god. They fuck you oh
There's yellow
Yellow legit on the betrothed I can't
Guys I'm noticing something
There's no is a semen on the body. No
Don't eat the yellow come Jingleheimer who is the head of the Royal Guard?
But the division specifically around investigations as there is no yellow jizz on there. Hi
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, you're very good
25 Wow okay with the 25. Give me a second
That's pretty good, so yeah, okay
Looking at these corpses you can see the same types of wounds that you probably heard from the dossier
Red from the dossier that you receive from Belinda and other authorities have described no struggling
Clean cut almost like from the ether. It's like it's like almost like a slice from nowhere
There's no like entrance or exit that you can really tell it's like a clean just like
very very neat
There's no blood coming out of there. Oh, there's blood
There's blood gushing and there's the toys that are sticking out of there if you remember Gumby superior action figure sticking out of one
Oh, and and the Bill Cosby children's book sticking out of the other
The victims are in their late 30s
And Jingleheimer would be telling you this.
Sorry.
Jingleheimer would be telling you this.
They joined the god together.
It didn't seem like they'd have kids anytime soon or at all.
Which makes sense why they'd be victims.
You look through their wallet and you see pictures of them with their dog.
Oh.
And a freak.
Their dog must have put fucking yellow booger jizz all over their fucking bottom.
And a freak, their freak who must have been their attendant.
Who appears part fungoid. Freaks, for those who don't know,
and for you guys who also don't know,
are sort of, they're kind of like Futurama-style, like, you know,
mutants that live in the sewers of Gun City.
But on Leo's Space Station, they've been given a little bit more.
Yeah, that's sort of what they look like.
Pull that one up. Yeah, pull it up. Yeah, you pull that up
Good
Yeah, yeah, that's
Sort of like yeah, like a facial tattoos. Yeah
Yeah, kind of like a tattooed delinquent type of guy mutate. Yeah, so like you guys met sentient Tommy guns
In the first adventure you've met fat cricket guys. That was papi Chuko and those aren't freaks though freaks are
basically have a genuine deformity and impurity.
It's a very racist designation.
- They're impure, you say.
- Basically, it's a mic, they're literally like mixed race.
- I thought you were going to say a mic.
- Yeah, I thought so too.
- That would be horrible.
That'd be way worse than mixed race.
- This crowd is not, we don't take too fondly to that.
- By mixed race, I mean fungus, fungoid and human,
which their freak is, Yanni.
- You should've said mixed species.
Mixed species, thank you.
I should have said that way earlier.
- Specious.
- Speciously.
- Pesaur, Pesaur, help me out.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- What is happening?
- Help me.
- I'm catching whatever he caught.
So yeah, butt freaks are treated well.
- Butt freaks.
(laughing)
- Okay, everybody let's be quiet for 10 minutes.
- This is impossible.
- Go on.
- Literally you're not gonna have--
I could be quiet for 10 minutes, watch me.
- Okay.
Now I'm being quiet, hold on.
He's, Cam's tickling Caleb.
For those listening.
- Okay, now let's, okay.
- All right, so other things that you see
when you're examining their body,
what's that?
(laughing)
Okay.
- Let's wiggle these giggles out.
- Cleanse.
- Come on, wiggle 'em.
one two three four five six seven eight nine zero is what we get for for not
being in the same room for three weeks
what this is what i get
yeah
ever really catch another
yeah yeah i like that so
you would notice that uh... the stories inside of the wounds
are
seem to have
deformities themselves
no poop
There's no poop on them.
Please stop.
Come on.
This is, is this what it's like?
- No!
(laughing)
No.
- So, and the Cosby book has like misspellings on it.
Like there's something off about these toys.
- Yeah.
- Which, that's sort of what you notice about it as well.
- Do they seem like rip off knockoffs?
- Not quite rip off knockoffs.
They seem like not,
- They seem like, it's like misprints,
more than like rip-off knock-offs.
- Indeed.
- But yeah, so I mean, that's basically
what we were able to tell with that 25.
I mean, otherwise, I mean,
if you talk to some of the witnesses,
I'd say with that 25, investigation is kind of encompassing.
So you would hear that there was some,
the only kind of sound that that people heard,
'cause again, it was a blackout,
was some kind of metal against metal scraping.
Very light.
- Demons, their bodies are metal.
And they're actually robots.
- Robos.
- So we need to remove their skin
to reveal their cybertronic insides.
- Let's do that, but let me cue an action first.
We found their wallet.
Can I do see everything in there?
Can I just, I would like everything in there.
- You wanna, so there are a lot of people around.
- I'm not, okay, I'll take what I can take,
but I mostly, I also just wanna see everything.
- Aren't we investigators?
- Yeah, we're detectives.
- Don't we have badges?
I mean, yeah, but you know what that's we gotta put a police officer could never check somebody's wallet
Well, you could check somebody's wallet, but I'd wear it in light a hand if you're gonna take money
I never said I was taking money. I said I said I'd see everything in there. I said you wanted everything
Oh wait, I think I dropped my wallet over is anyone see a fucking wallet. Oh, I think I saw it
It's right in that pocket. Oh my god. What are the odds of dude perfect shit?
I pick it back up or not back
I pick it up for the first time but they don't know that and I open it and what do I see dear patch so
- So you saw pictures inside of it,
you see a credit card of their family.
- Their fannies?
- No, there's no butt pictures.
- Oh, goddammit.
- It was, changed it for the UK viewers.
- You see 300 tokens also in one of the wallets,
and 50 tokens in another wallet.
- Fanny's butt here, but it's pussy there.
- I'm taking the credit card,
and I'm gonna basically do a trace back
and see everything they ever bought in their life.
- And I'll take the money.
you could do a trace back on that all
name
well he looked dropped his wallet i dropped my purse
the
can someone see it i think it up
all right is it right there and his bitch has it
all bargain these criminals are just a lot of water and that's why i had to
go back to the
it what
uh...
sh we're just getting shot up with a list of the law there might be we didn't
I try to show my badge and I say "professional detectives" but I just show the guy's credit card.
Belinda Crokes told me that I was to accompany you on your...
She told you? Now that's rich.
That's good, but it's not what she said. She told me that I'm to accompany you on your investigation.
Alright, roll with us.
Is Sullivan here?
Yeah, I'm over here!
Actually, where's my figurine?
Hello
I'm over here now stay over there, okay?
Yeah, you know what you can come with us you replace this fucking little piece of shit. Oh, man. Come on
Can I get out of here you turd no don't oh?
Did you hear that cuz I'm walking around?
Every time your fucking foot hits the ground I hear a fart
All right, I guess I'll just I'll walk if I'm gonna be so stinky. I'll walk I'll walk far behind you
I don't have to walk right now. Let me just pick you up
Please don't pick me up. No, I'll pick you up and I'll just why you always picking. Okay, just wait
Yeah, I need you to investigate something for me here
Yeah, get up in there
Inside these people
Listen yellow slime what what's so Belinda doesn't trust us. What's going on?
It's not that she doesn't trust you. It's that she wants to make sure there's oversight on the investigation from a royal guard
Okay. Well, he's doing a card tracker
Trace trace back with a card and I'm looking at the money to see if it's counterfeit or fake
I'm gonna test it out at a couple of stores around here and I'm wearing a purse to disguise myself as a woman
Okay, well here's what here's what he's doing actually I just decided for him
He's gonna dress up like each of them individually and walk around the spaceship to see if the killer thinks that maybe they survive
Try to kill him again. That's what I'll do. Yeah. Yeah now. Let me take off the
I'll do one of the broads clothes. I'll do one half
Male clothes and then the other half that's team is close. You look like Lady Gaga. Yeah
All right, no, I I'm going to have to forbid you from doing that are you gonna try? Oh, no we got forbidden
All right, yeah, I mean like okay, but like why though also what what you don't want this to be investigated
There's protocol to consider what?
Like not undressing the victims making sure we'll don't go do it in a lab. We're not undressing
We're just combining their clothes together.
We're only gonna take half of both their clothes.
It's not undressing, it's just combining half of the two shirts.
We'll take 49% of each and we'll put some random white cloth down the middle so you can see the line.
Who's the leader of this ship, us or you?
None of us. None of us are the leader of this ship.
That's what I thought, so don't tell us what to do.
I mean, okay. I mean he's gonna try the Royal Guard there are going to try to stop you from taking the clothes
Well, then we won't do it patches. I'm just saying I'm if you want to do it. Let's go to do that trace back
That's what I'm yeah, okay cool what they were doing before they got to this so if you want to
You can go back to your resort room. I guess that's where oh, do you know what actually we need?
I just as a it it feels weird to not have something
But can we can someone just put their credit card on the table so I can use it like to play it just
For the game, I mean, yeah, yeah, cuz I just it just feels weird my wall. It's not with me though. Yeah, I don't know if I
Apple pay is fine. Well, you just pull up your Apple pay I could use I mean that that works. It's probably futuristic
Yeah, just pull up his Apple just pull up your Apple pay. Maybe and I we can use that
Yeah, I left my all my it's like we're doing like it. We're doing a visual component
Yeah, yeah, this will work perfectly.
Man, I wish I could steal all the money off his phone.
Cool, so where do you guys, you guys want to go, you guys can go to your resort, you
guys, like your room you can turn into sort of a makeshift crime lab is what I was thinking.
Okay, so are we actually like, we're detectives hired by the ship or no?
You're hired, yes.
So they don't give us anything?
I mean they will give you equipment to build the lab.
You can also do it in the like lab here, but like okay. No, what is I just yeah?
I just wasn't sure our last interaction
I mean wondering if anyone in West water does are we allowed to take the are we allowed to take the toys out of there?
the
Decident yeah, yes, you could definitely do a DNA test. Yeah, that'll solve it. Yeah, you could definitely do that
Guys remember my pen
You guys hit me remember my pin at home one one one one I remember my pin. I'm sorry hey
I'm my damn character one one one zero one one one all right. I'm back okay
So where do you guys?
Dark, hey you guys get the toys you go you're gonna head over to you guys can go to the crime
I go to the crime lab yeah, definitely all right cool. I want to be make our presence known that makes more people
You want me more characters?
Okay, cool. I don't even think of them as characters anymore. They're fucking fleshed out as fuck and plus they have physical representations, okay?
So you'll see you guys
Sounds good
So you guys head over the crime lab let's make it a little let's make it like crime lab II looking right like every crime
You're gonna have a desk right you're gonna have some computer station a giant pencil to take notes. Yeah
Let's say all right. I like that. Let's get rid of the green couch
I'm
pretty nice crime lab I mean for it for kind of you just made it I mean like
compared to other crime labs you've been into which you've been in many crime
labs sir just a jackass I have a little bit yeah and yeah this is the only crime
Wow
You have the research the head of the of criminal research at the of the Royal Guard
This fucking blue gopher. Yes, this blue gopher. His name is name is blue gopher. Okay, and
He says, oh dear
What do we have here? He sees you bringing in the victims. He's you bringing in the toys. I'll pop it. Hello
You're a fellow Englishman. Yes
roll deception
(laughing)
- You're not English at all.
- Yeah, I am.
- In fact, I think you're from Dagobah.
- No.
- You swallowed something?
- Plymouth.
(laughing)
I'm from Plymouth.
- From Plymouth?
- Yes, Space Plymouth.
- Space Plymouth.
Yeah, he doesn't believe you anymore.
He's over you.
He's not like that you just came in here and made fun of him.
listen this is a nice lab you got here
what do you like a really nice lab
who
from the helium planet
come on that's pretty i mean role deception yeah i mean you don't have to even
it's so easy
sixteen plus something
plus something wow plus minus one
the helium planet
you know helium is a limited resource got you yes
Oh, you're fired.
You can't.
No, please.
This is my life's work.
We've been testing you the whole time and I mean you got me pretty good.
You got me past one test.
You passed the one test, you immediately failed the second test and it's like...
This is terrible.
But now you have to pass a third test.
Yeah.
Okay, bring it on.
Where is this coming from?
Well, he's a demon with a computer tower on his back.
Wrong, I'm from Cincinnati.
Oh no, I didn't even...
I definitely wasn't going to guess that, so...
- Hello, you got me. - Listen up, listen up.
- What's up? - You fucker.
We, basically two people died.
We need to do a trace back on a credit card.
- Okay. - So, and we were told
that you maybe have some technological capabilities.
- I do indeed, I do indeed.
And what's, what are you?
- I'm a frog. - I don't care.
Get off the computer.
Okay, and he gets onto the computer.
He takes the credit card, he runs it through.
- Here's the credit card.
- Okay, cool, thank you.
He takes the credit card, which is a, okay.
He takes the credit card, he runs it.
Fuck.
All right, he can stay here?
Yeah.
And the credit card, he can just--
And the recent purchases are for--
Can you swipe it?
Yeah, can you swipe it through the--
Okay, cool, now it's scanning.
It's scanning, okay.
The recent purchases are for a,
hmm, what did they recently buy?
Probably what they bought was a crackpot.
It's just like random purchases.
It's like random human purchases.
Nothing clueful.
Not a single clue.
Can we investigate further?
I mean, I will say, okay, here's another,
I mean, I will say that it is very clear
from their purchases, nothing about having a kid ever.
Nothing about having a kid,
so they're definitely childless.
Definitely childless.
And no intentions of having a kid.
No intentions either.
They're dinks.
They're getting stuff like...
Double income, no kids.
Yes, they're dinks.
They must have been from planet dink.
I think they were just from...
I believe they were just from
New England. The New England Empire.
That's fine. Yeah, that's what I said.
So listen, we basically ran out of
fucking shit to do in there.
Can you tell us... here, wait.
Can you run some kind of test?
Whether it be DNA or...
Yes. You could maybe put these in a microwave.
- Hold on, I got a question.
- Can you run these on this toy in this book?
- He runs the test on the toy in the book.
- And also, have you ever seen a bunch of yellow jizz
on a dead person?
- Yellow jizz.
- Okay, I've piqued his interest.
- Roll insight.
- Oh my god.
- Two.
- He doesn't know anything about yellow jizz.
- Oh, goddammit.
- Okay, I'm gonna ask you again
if you know anything about yellow jizz.
No, no, no, no, you don't know. Okay, do you know anything about color different types of jizz run the test?
He's running the test. He says yes, of course I do yes, of course while he's running the test and
So he says strange the DNA on these toys
Been handled by nobody in our system
No, and he looks at the serial number on the must be must be a terrible test cuz I was touching them all over
Well, yeah, I mean I put him in my mouth I
Was washing them with water besides you three we will come up a thousand times when I look at the toys
And only in that the half-life on that would suggest you did it in five seconds actually this one says you you're going to eat
The toy again. I don't know how it's doing that
Spit it out. No, please
He gets on his face and he throws it back in the thing now. He's got my DNA on it. Yeah, no these
These toys don't exist I
Mean not not these toys these kinds of toys exist, but there's no trace of these toys in the system
Nobody's handled them. Nobody's touched them. It's like they were plucked from thin air
hmm, is there some kind of where would these toys if they were if they were real and
Traceable, where would they be from so are they manufactured somewhere on the ship or is there a toy store?
somewhere around or in the world Santa
Or did Santa Claus deliver these in a poor way maybe to a poor child who didn't get wasn't good enough for a real toy
And hold on let me try to see
You see all the same typing
It's like when old people type into Google, and they do a full sentence
- He's got a question mark at the end.
He's doing typing exactly what we just said.
- Well, I would say the only place
where you could find untraceable objects
such as this would be,
and I'm not supposed to say this, but--
- Then don't say it.
Whoa, come on.
- We don't wanna know what's wrong with you.
(laughing)
- Okay, I'll write it down.
And I'll write it down in code.
You have to decode it.
- That sounds hard.
You can get in trouble, just tell us.
- Okay.
The undercity.
At least as far as objects that are untraceable.
Underwear? Oh, he got me! Oh shit!
He's dead. He's dead now. I'm just playing.
I'm just playing. Yes, the Undercity.
At least as far as objects that would be untraceable that would be on this ship,
everything else is accounted for. Occasionally, some goods will slip through our system.
But the fact that there's no fingerprint traces on this is what,
besides of course all the saliva you guys put on it, but,
is peculiar. But I would start there if we're talking about goods that don't seem to come from anywhere in particular.
So the undercity is the very tip of the bottom part.
See the undercity, the way to get there is, there's no zippy loop to the undercity.
So does that mean we can ride the gravitator?
You could definitely ask for authorization to do that.
But, you can't just ride through the gravitator.
Says you or what? Here's the thing, the gravitator...
Funny it's just encapsulated in exchange.
because it is that means you can ask for authorization to do that
so i can bureaucratic here's what i would say i got a lot of talk here's what i
would say
uh...
there's two ways you get there yes
the gravitate will go back to that the first way
that would be most normal people's way he would be take the city look to the
downer district in gun city
and walk
through to the other side of the editor i just said that
uh... it was not called but i love that name so i was i didn't even given name
didn't wasn't as important to me
as it is to you guys.
- That's some more than shit to me.
I wanna ride that bitch.
- So I gotta change the sleep timer on my laptop.
Sorry.
So the undercity, to get to the Gravitator,
and to get access to the Gravitator,
you could go, again, you guys are detectives,
you work with the Royal Guard,
you could head over to Gumby Superior
and talk to the cap, talk to him.
He'd be able to give you access.
- I don't wanna do all that, I wanna just get on.
- You just wanna get on?
- I just wanna try to get in there.
- You just wanna try to get in there?
So the way you could just try to get in there, you would still have to go through the station operations and the command deck.
Do you have the map up? You have it up? Can you pull it up?
For them? Or at least... yeah.
Aw, yeah.
Yeah, I see it.
Yeah.
So you could...
Maybe like soda or something?
I'm genuinely like... I'm so sleepy.
I think you'll make it.
We'll get you soda next time.
We should have more soda and snacks now that we're doing this in person.
The burden of soda is on the drinker. I just came up with that.
That is beautiful.
So, you can see here, if you go through the station operations, you could get to the...
Oh shit, I'm an idiot, sorry. You're trying to get to the undercity, right?
Or you're trying to get to the Gravitator.
Well, we're trying to get to the Gravitator to go to the undercity.
Right, so where you are now in the Royal District, you could go...
You could take the zippy loop to the station operations area,
And then you'd still have to kind of go through the command deck, but if you just avoid
You know you you would have to just avoid
Alerting people get to the ship crew area and from the ship crew area you could ride
I feel like we could definitely do that because we're sneaky as fuck you guys are sneaky you have disguise abilities
Yeah, you guys are charming what you guys both bully me Linda's
Belinda whatever name is she's given us some
Yeah, you guys do whatever we want a little guys. Yes. Yes, I would say justice. Oh, yes
I would say you have more license than like yes normally even if we get caught nobody's gonna be that pissed off
If you want to ride the gravitator, let's ride it. You can ride the ground here some kind of
Lethal weapon thing they yell at us in an office. Yeah
Yeah, as long as we don't get a desk job oh
I will say that maximum punishment is desk job. Okay. That's maximum
So if we fuck up getting a play time gets caught if we fuck up the next like 12
Episodes or us is patches saying like and then you fill out that report I
Mean you guys think we should really shut up, okay, I just say
Okay, oh, why don't you here? You're right. That's actually a great point turd. Why don't you it's credit?
Sorry did somebody did somebody hear a mouse fart just now
You're right, we're not we're not gonna go do that so we will get the authorization
So why don't you go on ahead and start talking to them about the authorization for you, and we'll catch up
Later and we'll talk about the other
Go get your authorization do your thing listen because we're pretty much celebrities on this ship at this point
Nobody's gonna stop us you you're basically the lowest of the low right Craig. You're like you need an
Great. Yeah, you said your name was Craig earlier there. You're basically like a worm
Okay. Yeah, I'm open to that. So
Okay, I'll go get authorization. Sorry
It's your worm if you wouldn't mind kind of inching away from us because it would make us smile. Oh, absolutely
Now your name is Craig the worm
There we go. I'm Sullivan the frog to Craig the worm
What a life
Here I go. You like it
See you guys later
Alright yeah, he's gonna go get authorization
No, there's no Craig the worm actually how did you get on the ship?
Make a note that's all
We got that fucking piece of shit out of our hair cool. Yeah, so you guys can ride the zippy loop over to
You can ride it all the way to the command deck
It opens up
Yeah, you guys ride the zippy loop you get to the command deck
You know the doors of the zip you live with open up, and you see a pretty sweet-looking
command deck station you know very
Enterprise very Mass Effect very stately looking place this command deck is
You see lots of crew members walking around and hurrying along you see occasional leprechaun slaves as well trudging along carrying
Which ones
Okay, yeah, they they nod back to you mm-hmm. Yeah, I'm doing the princess Diana wave to them, okay
They're ignoring you a little bit more because there's confused
Stately he looks and I start picking up the leprechaun the kind of smooching them on the forehead and you're kissing the slaves
Okay, so no dancing
And I'm jealous. Thank you, sir. So I'm turning it into a dance. Okay copycat
Okay
And then what and then what happens and then we just keep moving yeah, no, that's fine. Yeah, I think we're all dancing at some
Okay, so you guys are all dancing down through the through the through the command center
And you guys are gonna want to try to so here's the thing once you've arrived here. It's gonna be kind of like
Noticeable that you're here, so you just kind of as long as you just move quickly through it
Yeah, we'll do that you move quickly through it you get to the ship crew area
Now somebody is there and it's like they're just they just like don't recognize you they look up and go hey
Sorry
What what what team are you guys on?
Listen, we're on a team. Oh, we're in a special
investigation
from the red team
And we're set by either a Melinda or a Melinda and
We basically so basically people are getting murdered. It's this whole thing and we are going to leave now. Goodbye
You're just gonna about a walk right by you
What just just just I just need some just some ID every second that you hate somebody dies
Here's our ID. Oh
Somebody else's credit card. Oh, yeah. Okay. Oh, no, wait
Unless that's your do we have IDs yeah, I mean you guys would have my hand over my idea
I know ID okay, all right you guys all have very funny IDs
Okay Peter Griffin
All right, this is all very funny all right you guys said you're sent by Belinda all right
Let me just check with her and he goes to a little terminal
His back is turned. He's checking on the terminal. He's typing that in
Yeah, no, they said they're here for to investigate a murder. They said every second
They said every second. I don't let them in somebody's dying
Yeah, you one of them handed me a someone else's credit card
Okay
Yeah, you guys are clear to go
That's what we thought so I bet you feel like a murderous asshole now that you know how many people died with your second
Yeah, and then look at this
Don't know who that is
It says, should I say it out loud?
Are you covering the name?
So for the folks at home, Patrick has a picture
of a man in a V-neck he's holding.
- It's a pit bull impersonator.
- Is that a pit bull impersonator?
- It's a business card of a pit bull impersonator.
- A piss bull.
- All right, so we'd like to--
- Yeah, you guys walk through.
- I'm getting that Gravitron, mother--
- All right, cool.
- The Gravitator.
- The Gravitator, okay, cool.
- Oh, but I would like to ride the Gravitron.
- Yeah.
- So you guys get to the,
get to where the, sort of, there's like these little like,
pods that like, are kind of look like escape pods,
But they open up and you see ship crew members jump through.
You see really large ones where there's like huge pieces of cargo just like kind of floating through.
They float gently through and then they like kind of land on like a track and then they get carted away.
But you guys see the pedestrian ones. You guys want to jump in?
Oh hell yeah!
Make sure you have your gear on.
So you go there, you get your breathable gear, your space gear.
can jump through before you do should set your destination to downers downers
be which will lead you to the interest of our we do that you guys set that and
yeah you're floating through space now oh my god as you're floating through
you're seeing all the goods and services go by you see leprechauns holding on to
objects and pushing them through you see crew members pushing things through
you see like all the splendor of
of planet E-Bomb like below you
it's a pretty uneasy feeling you can see why
this is usually reserved for people in the crew and leprechauns but it also
feels really really sweet. Yeah I've done this before
yeah you floated through space before? I've floated through space it's funny
What's it like?
Fucking gay, I don't care.
[Laughter]
I don't care.
Oh, that's so cool.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
You think that? You think it's fucking gay?
[Laughter]
That's tight, man.
Oh, wow, fire.
Oh, man.
Um, yeah.
*laughter*
Alright, cool, yeah. I mean, you guys do float through the gravitator, and now, I will say you now have permission. You guys are gonna be able to float through the gravitator.
Oh, fuck yeah. Back and forth one more time.
Yeah, okay.
Revolving door style.
I'm just yawning.
You're just yawning? You're yawning, you're just like, "This is gay."
This is gay.
You're yawning about it.
I wanted to take the stairs.
*laughter*
You go back and forth a couple more times and then you end up in the undercity.
Underwear?
Oh my god.
How did each of us get got by that?
Motherfucker.
It is one of those things.
You get got by.
Hoe ass.
Yeah.
It is.
You showing your hoe ass?
No.
Oh, motherfucker.
Shhh.
Cool.
Underwear?
Oh.
Under where?
I remembered it.
Sorry. Yeah, the Undercity. Give me a second. Another one?
Yeah, you're gonna build it with fucking blocks? Nope, two seconds.
So, where you guys are, you guys
are arriving at the entrance of the Undercity. So you're in the Downer District first.
It shares some of the same architecture where you guys were going through last time was
the Upper
Gun City District, if you remember, it had all that kind of a
like kind of like white plastic-y kind of thing and like kind of circuitry
motherboard-y looking. PS5
yeah PS5 style. PS5-esque aesthetic.
yeah but the whites
here that were uniform throughout start to have like a blueish hue
there's the artificial sunlight that is in which is why your
your day bane is fine. The artificial sunlight is a bit dimmer in the Downer District
There's less spare in powering the ship and you see some of the buildings that have the
darker brown or black look to them and almost bulbous in shape.
These are refurbished parts taken from earlier space station attempts as well as space material
found in New England's exploits above E-Bomb.
So some of the scattered alien parts that were found and helped build this space station
together.
You start to see more of that architecture.
You see also more of England, New England's architecture that resembles more of the New
England sky cities that you had seen before, as well as elements of Old England.
So there's pasty shops here and tea houses and theaters, there's roundabouts.
It's kind of like much more of a hodgepodge, it feels much more of an organic city, kind
of like built rather than where the upper district feels much more like kind of created.
So the killing in the Downer District that took place,
so the killing, the first killing,
just to let you guys know if you want to explore
where the killing was in the Downer District,
it was on the very edge, kind of where you're gonna be.
And I just realized, you guys also bypassed
having that guard follow you, which is pretty smart.
So now, what's his name?
- I don't know.
- Jingleheimer doesn't know where you are.
I just realized, I was just like,
"Oh, would he know?
"He wouldn't be here."
So the couple was admiring,
So what you knew about from the dossier about the murder in the Downer District, the couple
was admiring one of Leo's life-sized toys.
These are found more often in Thunderland, but can also be seen in the Downer District.
So Leo's Sky Cities often have these life-sized toys that are like statues that are put up
and they'll sometimes have retractable heads and will pull out little guns.
It's like these fun attractions in New England.
So they were admiring them.
When the lights went out, the couple's throats were slashed, their toys were jutting from
them, they were slumped over. This couple was in their 50s, each long time
bachelor bachelorettes, they finally found the right person, or at least they felt
they did, and didn't last long. This was the first killing, too, where you are
right now. So there's no, I mean you guys can investigate this area too, or you can
just go right to the under city. I'm gonna investigate. Yeah. So in this area, again so,
the beginning of the under city, because the under city has a bit of a
different look. There's almost like an informal...
I'm gonna ask my character to tell him to investigate.
There's like a couple lamp posts to kind of create an informal
almost like gate entrance.
And also you'll notice that there's less
guard presence now.
So as you move further away, the guards
are not as present. So, um, yeah,
Caleb, you want to investigate? Yeah. This is a lamp post.
Hold on.
Whoa, I just saw the new
uh, image.
Whoa! Are those TIE fighters?
Holy shit, I got an 18.
No, they are surveillance drones courtesy of Huge Ass Facts.
Oh, they're too scary.
Um, you got an 18?
It looks like they're saying "LOL" with their bodies.
So, uh, with that 18, I mean, you can see that there's, you know, this is, uh, uh, there was no...
Bloodstains, hear me again, this was like after the fact.
Mm-hmm.
Um, uh, you can, you talk to some of the folks who were witnesses there, um, and they talk about the sound of a scream,
And there's also a shopkeeper nearby who you haven't talked to yet, but he was there present his name's O'Neill
He's a shopkeep in this area. He's the only other person who was there. I'm gonna talk to him. Hey
Hi, what do you guys want when you when these people got murdered did you hear metal?
No, I didn't hear any metal didn't matter
Like that kind of metal no I didn't hear that kind of middle you
Did you which kind of metal did you hear I didn't hear any kind of metal when this happened you're acting a very
Suspicious not acting what caught what type of skin is your body have?
What type of skin is your body have answer the man?
Human skin roll inside
I got a 13.
He seems like he's lying about the human skin part.
He does look human.
Android.
You're lying about the human skin part.
I want to do a magnet over his head.
Okay, you don't have a magnet.
I definitely have a magnet.
Roll to see if you have a magnet.
on a fucking spaceship everybody probably has a magnet. I probably have so many devices.
Let's roll d20 and see if you have a magnet. I definitely got a magnet. Eleven. You have
a magnet. Okay I take out my red and grey magnet. This is my fault. It's shaped like
this. I can't complain. I have with me. U shaped magnet. And I go *whistles* horseshoe.
That's what I was, the word I was looking for. Like this. *whistles* Why are you making that
noise? What noise? You're making that noise. You're making a noise. Is there an android?
I'm not an animal. I'm gonna investigate his body.
I wait. Please don't do that.
Wait, this guy just fucking, he shouldn't have given us this clue.
Cause this is tipping the whole house of cards now.
I'm going to stub his toe.
Okay. With my foot.
I'll roll an attack roll.
But I don't wanna hurt him.
Yeah, I guess it's not an attack roll.
Roll a sleight of hand then. Let's do sleight of hand.
I'll roll sleight of foot.
Can we have a separate sleight of foot stack on for one?
You're trying to surreptitiously stub his toe.
Gage's reaction.
Uh, I got an 11.
Okay.
You kinda like stumble a little bit.
I actually stubbed my toe.
But also his.
And he's like, "Ow!
Ugh!
Why'd you do that?
Look, do you wanna buy something or what?"
Why did you lie about having human skin?
I have human skin!
No, we know for a fact you do.
Wait, wait, wait, no, no.
He has human skin, but it's what's underneath that counts.
No, he lied specifically about having human skin.
Maybe he has human skin in a box.
Yeah. What's your biggest secret?
I was going to ask you that.
I'm not going to tell you guys anything.
I'm going to use Yoda's mind.
Yeah, mind reader. I'm coming up with toe-stubbing abilities.
I don't have my paper.
I got you, though.
What I have to do is roll a resist.
Your mind reading is what it is.
So it's really just me rolling.
give
Yeah, he's able to he's able to artificial until you're you're you almost get in and he's able to kind of like block you out
All right, listen, do you want to go on a date sometime? No
What?
No, you guys have been really going to date with my sister
Yeah, or my sister or my brother if you had to pick one of the three of us to go on a date with who?
Would you pick?
I'm doing this. I'm biting my lip. I'm putting my lip like this
*makes weird noises*
I use lips too.
*laughter*
Uh, no, no, I don't
I'm lifting up the back of his shirt.
I'm lifting up the back of his shirt and looking at his skin.
*laughter*
Uh, you lift the back of his shirt, you notice
uh, red curls
in his back hair. Oh my god.
You're a mother of- You're a leprechaun!
You're a leprechaun. No!
Please don't! We exposed you!
Hey everybody!
Please don't please I'm only half please wait you're like your name's fucking O'Neal. You're free. Yeah, why didn't we?
Don't know you guys took out a magnet and ran it over across my head. What are you like footsie?
Okay, you devil you red devil. Tell us everything you'll never enter the metal of heaven
But listen, we need you to send us over to the under city
Or we'll tell everyone your secret
We need to find out we have a we're blackmailing you okay, okay? I I just like to blackmail
I don't really know anything. I just don't like to draw any attention to myself, okay
Well, how do we sir fucked up today? Yeah? You don't like to draw attention?
You really fucked everything up today didn't you out Neal stupid motherfucker?
You're going to fucking jail for the rest of your life you piece of shit. I don't want to go to jail
What you should have thought of that before you were half leprechaun. Okay, I'll tell you in front of my angry ass
Okay, I've seen him bite someone. He's a psycho. I did I did hear a metal sound. Why did you lie about that?
I just don't want any trouble. There's gonna be trouble either way
I heard it on the roof up there and a little bit of ways in the under oh, that's a roof roofs of mostly metal
there's a
What?
Yeah, what you're saying doesn't help us. It was a scraping sound and okay wait and
Raving on a roof there was this scream, and then it was oh my god. I just
It's reindeer every reindeer on the roof right Santa Claus. It's toys. It's reindeer. Oh my god
Guys it's reindeer
Santa Claus reindeer and it's Santa Claus on the roof. Maybe we already cracked it. We just stopped the campaign
Someone pretending to be Santa need we definitely
Look at him right now
We think okay old man, I would like to put out a plate of cookies and carrots
Just while we're talking just put it just on the ground off to be like I'm just gonna leave this here
While we do with the rest of the campaign and I'm gonna set up this camera in front of it
Because I have this camera in the game. They don't look up read my finger looks. Oh
Just lying and I get access
Cameron's red finger you can you can get access to the roof if you go to the building you just
Say you're with baby gad and they'll let you in uh
Maybe dad run that shit back you guys were to recognize baby gad. I remember baby gad. Yeah
From when we were in his gad village or whatever
Did we trying to downplay a lot of those elements, but I liked his care. Yeah, he was good
What did we do with babe we sold Sullivan? What do you do with baby?
Get sleazy now with the Coliseum baby gad baby gad had a fight club
Yeah, yeah, and his dad did not approve and then baby gad exposed his fight club. No no no you helped him out
And then we didn't like him very much.
He left and he left for bullet town last you heard to go a place that would be more accepting of his sort of
entrepreneurial ways. Okay. And Sullivan had a perfect blue experience at the in Gadsville.
We would like to go up to the roof. In the meantime. We'd like to go up to the roof.
So the roof is in the undercity you said?
Yeah, so it's like basically what he's saying is like the line that makes it clear that you're going from downer district to undercity the
building is on the other side of that. Okay. It's like it's like it's like it's
it's
I was just about to say that I'm not Scottish so you guys
You guys walk to the building you see it's like it's got it it's a metal door
It has like a little slot like a metal slot. Yeah, we all know doors that type of slot. I know exactly right yeah
Yeah, yeah, okay the password slot. Yeah
So what's the pattern what?
You know
Well when it closes it does not does not do that
You could not be a fool
I wouldn't use my mouth you are a fool except for the chewing sounds like a low low go back to
Near in the front of the door. It's like clopping
Don't clop it's it's closed the door is closed. That's the way to get in. What do you want to do?
I knock three times on that bad boy
Position yourselves in front of the door. Let's bring back. Well this shit's about to go fucking modern warfare 2 on me explode in slow motion
He's here the you hear the as the slide slides open
We just got those installed. What do you guys want?
We know baby Gary little dad and there baby dad and we need to come see the roof
We're we're sitting on an assignment from Linda red team red team Melinda croaks rocks
We don't want any feds we're not fed listen, we don't give a listen we kill people we fucking fuck everybody. All right, what's up?
He opens the door yeah, you guys be able to walk in we're honestly we're way
We've had way, we've killed way more people than this serial.
Yeah, you guys are, you guys are biometric ton.
You guys are crazy murderers.
Yeah, yeah.
You also like had like a, you were like a crime guy.
Yeah, this is our most, these are the most, I think of any of the campaign stuff we've done.
We were in jail.
This is definitely, these are the three most evil guys.
It's funny because the fantasy one we set out to, we specifically made evil characters.
Yeah, and they instantly became kind of sweet.
Yeah, they have like more heart and like, I mean they did have like a, they're plucky.
Yeah, they have like they do or fuck these three are just complete
They're bad actors
With actual chips on their shoulder bad bad hombres remember that yeah, these are bad hombres
These are better embrace and these bad hombres are walking up the stairs to the roof, okay?
You get to the roof you can see all of the under see you can't see all that you can see a lot of the
Under city and all it's a grimy splendor
You can see that it's it has more neon lights
It looks more like gun City like as you know it except again
It has those like weird black and gray and brown kind of bulbous II buildings that were
Parts of that old alien ship you see, but you know people are living there enjoying their lives already in yeah partying
It's like a real place music on the streets. Yeah. Yeah, they're just living in line. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, everyone in the streets going. Don't give a fuck. They don't get what tomorrow you hear somebody down there
I don't give a fuck about tomorrow!
That's right, live for the night.
Live for today, live for tonight.
I'm good, yeah I'm feeling alright
Baby I'm having the best
You know that song Patches?
It sounds like Blue Dabba Dee Dabba Dabba
Yeah but it's actually
Baby Rexha
You guys always teach me something new
I don't fucking know. And David Gutta, right?
Yep. Oh, I know that song.
David Guetta
You guys are on the roof, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing unusual on the roof.
You do see kind of a, like one of those metal, like, you know those little, like a little
bit of metal piping that's kind of sticking out of the roof, kind of like what lets exhaust
out of, of, of, of buildings.
Yeah, as in, the kind of thing that maybe Tim Allen and Santa Claus might look at and go,
I ain't fitting in that damn thing and then get sucked in too.
You don't know though.
Oh we don't know.
You don't know.
Alright, yeah yeah yeah.
Fuck you.
We'll see.
Yeah you're plucky.
I am plucky.
Fuck you man.
I can't even look at you right now.
I'm so ashamed.
I'm sorry.
Alright I'm dropping my magnet down that.
Roll for initiative.
Woah!
We're about to fight a hole?
A snake jumps out of the hole.
i'm dead serious
can i get a surprise round of of my magnet falling on its head
there's a snake
i'm dead fucking serious i have this plan
i got a sixteen
now he's just mad that we figured out the entire thing
you fucking snake
you didn't figure it out i promise
i got a ten
i have a negative one initiative
What the hell? That's some bullshit. I got a damn three.
Three? Oh no wait, I have a one. Uh oh. So I got a 17.
He took my point.
Sorry, say your initiatives one more time.
Three.
Ten.
Beautiful. I got a 17. Was it you? Yes.
Okay, cool. Let's position you correctly.
You are like right in front of the fucking snake.
Does my magnet at least hit it?
No, it doesn't hit it.
It kind of like...
It's a metal snake.
You lost your gun.
Well, actually...
I actually forgot it.
Well, because it is...
It's a metal snake.
It's not just metal.
It's metal, it has flesh, and it has plastic.
It's more like a straw than a snake, if you ask me.
And so it pops up when it hisses and you see its teeth.
Its teeth look like little gears.
Oh, man.
And where did the magnet go?
The magnet went like on its like upper neck, like it like like stuck to.
Oh, I'm sure that's the noise a magnet makes.
Right, guys.
Well, it's like sticking like better than what you did.
You know, this is what a magnet makes.
No, no.
OK, so you're up.
Yeah, it's on my turn.
All right. I'm going to
probably just hit it as hard as I can.
OK, you have a few abilities that do that.
So you have your hoagie surprise. Do it.
So you're going to run up to him.
And your attack to that,
you're going to add your attack to that.
So I got a I got an eight attack.
Oh, you add you add you just add that number to that number.
And I heard your stomach was 19.
Yeah, that hits the snake.
So you run up and it's like it winds out. It's like really long
It's like a lot longer than you thought it would be
feet in feet like 15
Okay, it's like thin it's like you know it's like anaconda. Yeah
And so you go up and you you whack it on the side with the hoagie
Dealing damage how much damage?
No, it's not you got a
I
Believe that I think I believe the button yeah
Okay
All of the poop colored dice so that I can not use them and stack them one time make a poop tower to make myself hungry
So I fall asleep
He said yep, he said yep
Didn't work in the app. He's taking a selfie
As your hoagie
Connects connects with the same images don't worry about it as your hoagie connects with the snake doesn't make sense on this app
Pat yes
The lights flash
They go out
They come back on
They go out again. No come back on no
in space right way it can we like all can we get a reaction we
notice the route the lights go can we we eat look in a direction or something
yeah I'd say you can do that look around I wanna look at O'Neill
you look towards O'Neill I'm overwatch on O'Neill while this lights are
flickering
right where you guys gonna look you are gonna kinda connecting with the snake
with your hoagie you're kinda locked in with the snake
well I'm looking at my pants you're looking at your pants I look
at my hands because I suspect that I might be the killer.
- Okay, cool.
You hear a laugh.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh.
- No, you hear, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee!
And you hear it again.
But I'm not gonna do it again, it's really loud.
(laughing)
And just a moment. - O'Neal Jackson.
- Cam, you for just a moment,
'Cause you're looking over at O'Neal.
You see a glimmer of something.
- Oh no.
- And then you hear a horrible scream,
but it doesn't sound like a victim.
Sounds like something else.
- Doesn't sound like a victim to me.
- Doesn't sound like someone getting stabbed.
It sounds like somebody, something that's angry.
- Does it sound like they like it?
I can't tell.
All I know is that's not a victim.
- You see O'Neal holding his neck.
- Oh, blood.
- Okay, let me guess what it is.
A lucky charm.
You see a copy of Hungry Hungry Hippo.
Oh, okay.
Stabbed in his neck.
A copy.
I wrote a copy.
A copy of the game Hungry Hungry Hippo?
You see, yeah.
They got it on Xbox.
You see a-
It's the future.
They got every game on the Xbox in the future.
You see an Xbox's Hungry Hungry Hippo.
Okay.
And-
I believe you.
You see him like on the ground.
You see somebody over going to help him.
But you guys are not gonna be able to look at that right now because you're gonna be in the middle of a fight with a snake.
And next time we'll finish the fight with the snake and see what's going on with O'Neal, maybe.
I would like to quickly yell, "Do not help him, he is half leprechaun."
He does not matter. We're gonna ignore him when we come back.
Look at his back. Look at how cool our fight is.
I'm hitting the snake with a sandwich. I love it.
OK.
Who loves it?
That's it.
I love it.
Oh, you love it.
Me.
Not you.
Wait, underwear?
Was it short?
Alright, and?
And go.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(dramatic music)
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]