Batman voice
Gotham
keep in when he says Batman voice to
that's incredible. That is great. It is a sick city,
Gotham, at least those cities faced justice. I pick at the scab and make the
think bleed more and more. This place, the people here, they need something to
believe in. I frighten them, the weak and the strong, the innocent and the guilty.
Excuse me.
That was a train passing by, just saying that.
The trains in Gotham belch by me while I talk.
(laughter)
I can't believe how loud that was. I didn't think that would get picked up.
I don't know if it's...
Maybe there's no hope for Gotham.
Last night I threw three of the most dangerous criminals behind bars.
Mr. Wonderful, a powerful technologist, I assume.
He uses invisible tech, I think, to cast spells against the innocent.
He's tough, but I was tougher.
All this tech uses voice commands, so I silenced him, bound and gagged, and sent him to the slammer.
Then there's the cook, a chef.
As dangerous as his meals are delicious.
I give him a taste of his own medicine or his own dinner
okay
bound him gagged him and threw him directly into the prison.
Finally the rambler a
Man who can torture the most mentally disciplined to a psychotic state of rage through ceaseless rambling
The only way to stop him bound him gagged him through him into the prison
What prison do you ask?
Arkham
Hold on
Arkham Asylum, I know it's really insane
fine, but for the weird and freaky prisons are asylums.
He's very reactionary that way.
Archimedes and change.
What if you took Gotham's most vile hearts and minds and force
them to spend every waking moment together?
Now, what if you cover them in whipped cream and candy?
And what if you put that in a bowl of vanilla ice cream and
a scoop of pistachio and coffee and then a fried banana?
Now you add some sprinkles, rainbow color and a bit of caramel.
now, then you have an ice cream sundae. Arkham, though, is a tough place, not
like an ice cream sunday.
You're starting to sound like the cook right now.
Sunway
criminals constantly try to break out, but Arkham it's not easy to break out
of not since the recent updates. It's old Victorian architecture now flanked
by modern additions to turn it into a fortress of doom that keeps prisoners in
and rather than soldiers out with the fuck
man damn okay,
it's gotten be the
size of a small neighborhood
with the amount of psychos. I throw in there
and the size of the psychos. They get bigger and bigger because of advances in
nutrition.
Truly some of your best
just
just right. I saw the toilet. Because of advancements in nutrition,
that was your big line. That's an implication about the cook or no,
it's just nothing. It's just I was finding words. Okay, let me just I'm
almost I'm proud of some of us done. Okay, three one hundred foot high stone
walls surround the place. Titanium doors on each wall require facial and genital
scanning to enter and exit deadly dogs patrol the ground snapping at anything
it smells of super villain
yeah and patches asked me to add a sound effect to the soundboard called angry
dog. That is twenty two seconds long, so we're going to sit here while it plays
out
hold on
wait
it's done now. Okay, just finish okay with robot snipers that line the wall. So
We don't have a I don't think we have a sound. Okay, I'll take that and wait and
and yeah, what else?
I am a robot sniper.
That's one of the robots snipers. Oh shit. Oh God, I feel naked. Oh
say that say that the robots snipers name is Darren. His name is Darren the
robot sniper
And the recent removal of spoons means no digging holes to get out.
Guys like Drill Face, whose face has a drill on it, he's gagged.
And guys like Drill Hands, who has drills on his hands, he's bound.
So he can't get out either.
The only way someone could get out would be, well, I don't want to say it or
think of it, if I do, someone might figure it out, because that's how it
works.
People can hear my thoughts.
hmm. I doubt anyone could pull it off. Interesting, there's definitely no way
someone could break out of Arkham Asylum.
Yeah, I'm done being Batman. All right, cool. How naked do you feel with that?
Who man you're a real voice? You wish you sound like your real voice on right
now. It's
yeah. I mean usually usually I just yeah, your real voice
Yeah, no, usually I'm like I'm always mistaken for like a kid, but like when I
when I was Batman, that was I felt fucking incredible. Yeah, yeah, you guys
ever okay, good.
So yeah, you guys are the these three of Batman's most violent villains, his
greatest foes, his ever faced. Most famous ones too that he would have
yes, so many times. The rogues gallery, yeah. So I imagine, you know, you know,
all three of you are in Arkham Asylum, you're probably imprisoned in different
ways to be quote unquote rehabilitated. We all know Hugo strange isn't really
about that kind of life, though, right? He is not no he's not and he is about
revenge. So so why don't we get get a sense of where you are in the prison,
who you are? Let's start with Mr. Wonderful. We'll start with the chef,
because Mr. Wonderful point at the cook, the cook, the cook, sorry, who is a
chef, the cook, who is a
so basically title that's what is a chef. Basically, I started out as
a cook and then I became a chef. Right. And shortly thereafter a super villain who
was bent on destroying Gotham. Okay. How did I do that? I was doing, I was
poisoning meals that were going to the mayor's office because I had a lot of
catering jobs. Wow. I would, I had my, my knives were extremely sharp and I would
use those to kill people and murder. I was a serial killer. Okay, I was a, okay,
I got it. I was a serial killer. He's got it. And then I would make my victims in
into food. That's right. That hasn't happened. So that's cool. Well, I may I
may use to do that. I used to make them it, but I did, but it wasn't ever like I
made them into food that somebody would want to eat. And I did like I tried to
trick people into it. It was always like I just had an arm, a barbecue or maybe a
foot. I was picked the least appetizing parts of the body. As far as where I am
in the prison, I think I'm in the kitchen. You're in the kitchen working in
the kitchen. I think I have kitchen duty today. Yes, I think so. And boy, am I
happy about it. You're chopping it up with the other prisoners. Chopping it up. Yeah.
So, hopefully not chopping them up. Yeah, like a fricking onion. Well, hopefully I am
for me. For you, but for them, you don't want that. No. No, and your abilities, so we have
your, we're our friend character sheets here, and your abilities, you have chef knife, so
that is a range attack. Your cleaver is your melee attack. Right now you don't have this
because you're in prison right now. They've de-knifed you. But I used to have these. You
did used to have these and so you might have them again. And then finally you have gumbo.
Gumbo is your ability to, we're going to roll a d20 whenever you want to use gumbo and you'll
take a point off your ingredients list and you'll have to gather ingredients to cook
up more gumbo. Gumbo has a random effect.
I thought you said gunbo.
I have a table of 20 effects for you.
Gunbo would be good.
Gunbo.
Yeah.
Well, but I don't use it.
Can we add a gunbo thing where he makes a meal out of bullets?
I don't want that.
Yeah, he doesn't want that, so I can't do that. That's how it works.
Yeah, and so yeah, you're in prison. Batman found you chopping up some
local teens. Yeah, a bunch of kids. A bunch of stupid kids. Chopping them up.
And he was like, "Stop that." And you were like, "No." And then he bound
you, he gagged you, and he threw you right into prison or Arkham Asylum.
And now, who else do we have here? And you guys are all... You guys know
each other, by the way, right? From previously trying to fight. No. From
high school. No, we've never met each other. From high school. These two know
each other from high school. No, no. Oh, okay. You're going to this. My girl.
Okay. Okay. You heard of our go ahead. Our secret identities are no each other
from the neighborhood. And we also went to high school together. Okay. My guy
did not go to high school. We all live in the Arkham projects. Okay, that's
right. We're poor. Yeah. Now, now who feels bad? Probably Batman. Yeah. No,
probably Mr. Wonderful. Okay. Talk to me. I don't know what voice to do.
My name is Mr. Wonderful. How's that? You knew exactly what voice.
No, I was thinking maybe doing a high pitch one. You knew exactly what voice to do.
No, because I was thinking of also my original idea was like, Mr. Wonderful.
I don't know. Either one of those is going to work. My name is Mr. Wonderful.
I think I'm going to go for it. You sound like a brownie. I grew up in a
small hamlet in...
A brownie. I grew up in a small... A brownie. I grew up in a small hamlet
just outside the castle walls when my village was ransacked by orcs and my
my parents were slain. My brothers and sisters were sold into slavery in a
faraway land. I became a questing adventurer. I posted up at the local
tavern to search for quests. I that's right. I slay I slew goblins. I slew
dragons. I slew zombies until I gathered enough gold pieces to finally take an
airplane to Gotham City, where I became a villain and I'm a wizard wizard and
my brother is the other Mr. Wonderful.
With Kevin O'Leary? Yeah. My name is Mr. Wonderful, one relation. My name's
Devin O'Leary. Oh, my God. So, he's also Irish. We took on different life
paths. That's true. I think Kevin O'Leary is Jewish. Is he really? With
everything else about him? Was it because of money? I think he's Canadian.
Actually. He's Canadian. Yeah, he's Canadian. Oh, he's Canadian. I'm also,
I'm from the Kingdom of Canadia. Yeah, right.
And yeah, so you have like, you're sort of this like,
I mean, Batman thinks you're a technologist of some kind.
- Yeah, he's stupid.
- He's really dumb.
- I'm a wizard.
- Well, Batman's one weakness is magic.
So I think Cameron was actually the smartest one.
- Is that true?
- Yeah.
- His one weakness.
- Holy fuck.
- The one thing that Batman is not good against is magic.
- If you do this, he just like, pan.
- Whoa, what are you doing?
(laughing)
- That's why he's not good against Ra's al Ghul.
- Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
- 'Cause Ra's al Ghul has magic.
- Yeah, he can bring himself back to life.
- Yeah.
found a youth.
Found a poop.
I hate Rachel Gould.
All of us,
the three of us, even though we don't know each other,
we kind of gravitort
towards each other because
we're the type of villains where we're like, "Fuck all these
other villains. These other villains are real."
We're the three guys who know what's up.
Two-Face, the Riddler,
and Penguin, they all like,
they're boys and then we're like,
We're like, "We'll show them."
They've been fumbling the bag over and over and over again.
You guys don't know what you're doing.
You guys took a crack at it.
You did pretty well for the first go.
You're in the asylum.
They have a good grasp on the underbelly of the city, but we got the overbelly.
The overbelly is all ours.
We've got the overbelly.
And the mid-belly as well.
Really, it's total white space for you guys.
It's totally untapped.
People haven't tried with the overbelly.
They got the criminal underbelly.
that we have the criminal. Nobody's tried with the overbelly. Nobody's tried.
Nobody's even tried. Nobody's tried Walgreens. No. That's what we do.
That's what, that we go into Rite Aid and we are doing basically kind of...
It's all Rite Aid, Walgreens, Duane Reade, CBS. We're doing, we're basically,
we call ourselves the Boonk Gang and we're doing... We're Wizers in Adderall
short. We, exactly. We're stealing the show out of Adderall. Exactly. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And your, your abilities, what, what powers or, or, or
rather, what are your super villain powers? It looks like my super villain
powers include agonizers, scorcher,
protection from evil and good fairy fire and
mage hand. Okay, among others,
he's got a lot of powers. So right now, yeah, you are, you are in your, you're
in the kitchen, you're, you're, you're having a good time. I'm in the study,
you're in the study, you're in the
reading scrolls. I'm in the hot tub. You're your scrolls, Mr. Wonderful.
- Yeah. - You ordered a Scrolls Special.
- Yeah. - Thank you.
- And you, that was a good scene, who are you?
- Man, I don't even know where to start and where to begin.
Man, I fuckin', just got fuckin' bangin' in here, man.
I don't even wanna get bangin' in here.
Look, look, all right,
so you get me into "Arkham Asylum," right?
- Right, yeah.
- Before this, I was just hangin' out.
I was hangin' out with Michael, I was hangin' out with Phil,
hanging out with Tony, you know, we were just fucking just going around, going around town,
going around Gotham. And what do we see on the side of the road? What? Little guy selling
oranges. And we're like, what the hell? What the hell kind of guy? What the fuck? This
wasn't the first time you saw a little guy selling oranges, right? I saw a little guy
on the side of the highway selling oranges. I said, what the hell are you doing on the
side of the highway zone. And I'm like, all right, he needs to get in my car. He
needs to get the hell in my car right now. So I pick him up, I get out of the car,
pick him up, put him in the bed of the truck. I fucking take the car, we drive
back down to the overbelly of Gotham. We're going around. What's going on here?
Just keep talking. This doesn't concern you at all. Well, no, because I get
distra- there's stuff that in my life, if I see it, then I got to make note of it
and I gotta look at it and I gotta start talking about it
because you know what that reminds me of right there?
The guy next to you in another cell next to you, "Oh my god, shut the fuck up!"
That reminds me of right there is what the guy was doing with the oranges earlier.
No!
He was selling, he was giving the oranges, no, wait, no.
Was he selling them or was he not?
The rambler rambles on and on and on ad nauseum,
causing pain and misery to anyone who can hear him.
You have a few powers.
You have to decipher what the hell, like the Riddler,
you have to decipher what the hell his original point was. Yeah,
he has babble blast where he unleashes a rapid fire stream of words at a target
target has to make a DC wisdom save real take psychic damage. It's got verbal
distraction where the rambler engages anyone in an extended conversation
distracting them from other matters and they will be incapacitated if they keep
talking with him that they fail the wisdom DC. I mean he has endless
rambling where he can make any creature within 30 feet of him
but get confused and distracted and have been disadvantaged on
attack roles. So he's sort of this kind of like just torture
par excellence, but he doesn't ideas. Does the Rambler know
that I was going to call him the Punisher, but there's already a
hero pretty good name. The Punisher right? Is he a hero?
It seems like it switches. Well, it's a second. He's an officer
of the law. He is a hero. The Rambler was put in a cell as far
far away from everyone else as possible, but I have, but here's the thing they
forgot. There is a phone in my
why would they do that? Why would they give you a phone? It was an accident. It
was an accident. It was a complete over. Where does the phone go to the phone
connects to the loudspeaker?
You did the morning and out. Yeah, my job is morning announcements. Nobody
knows
basically what you get. Arkham should operate exactly like a middle school.
Yeah, that's declassified.
Yeah.
And what happened this morning?
The bell rings, actually.
Now that you say the bell rings.
Uh-huh.
And you guys all go out for prison yard hangout time.
Okay.
So yeah.
So you guys go out.
Man, last time I was out in here, I fucking saw a guy like eat a scorpion off the floor.
It's like a guy eat scorpion off the floor.
I'm going to forage for ingredients.
Okay, cool.
Go for it.
So just roll.
I wasn't even trying to like a chocolate scorpion or any of these kind of.
Just roll brain for that.
Roll brain for that?
Yeah.
And then just add your brain bonus.
Eighteen.
Nice.
you
you guys are in the yard like who do you hang out with who do you chill with I
have a shop or any kind of
one of these little yeah. What about you, Mr. One
just kind of ate it just kind of ate the scorpion
and I was like what the hell are you doing?
No, I just got I eat scorpions all the
sound effect right now is me walking in circles.
What the hell you don't yell at me like that, because you know I got I got
I'm going to shut the fuck up or I'm going to make you shut the fuck up.
You can't yell at me right now because you know I've got bad ears.
I've got bad ears because I was going at a bunch of concerts.
I was at a lot of concerts in my...
You versus Thug.
Roll for initiative.
By the way, you asked what I was doing and I'm levitating.
How tall are the walls? 100 feet?
I'm levitating but I can only levitate 99 feet so I can't escape
and they don't get me in trouble for it.
God damn it again.
What did you get?
I got a 19.
Yeah, you get to attack first.
Don't forget we have a beautiful dice camera.
I forgot about the dice camera.
Oh yeah.
You have a regular attack too.
You'll see them.
You have a range attack and a regular attack.
Right now you just have the regular attack.
Okay.
So what do you want that to be?
What does the Rambler use when he attacks somebody just regularly without his talk?
He's just speaking but like...
Karate chopping.
Yeah, it's karate chopping.
He just uses karate.
Yeah.
What the hell are you doing coming at me like that?
Maybe you get the fuck out of here.
I'm fucking...
You don't know what the fuck I know.
You don't know what the fuck I've learned.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I know you don't know the fuck I've learned. Oh my God.
All right, roll attack roll.
You look stunning in the shysty.
13.
13? Okay, that does hit this guy.
Oh wait, 13.
Plus two.
Plus two, right?
Yeah, that hits. That hits.
Either way.
Yeah.
Yeah, so now roll for damage.
What did it say?
It's the--
One D6 plus two.
Yeah, do it.
That was a four.
Nice, yeah, okay.
So you just like karate chopped this guy up
and everyone is so upset.
They really want the Rambler
to get the shit kicked out of him,
but it just has not happened yet.
- Yeah, Vulcan nerf pinch.
That's what the fuck I'm doing right now.
That's the fuck I'm trying.
You remember that movie, "Graphic Con"?
- All right, and this guy's-- - Ricardo Montalban.
- This guy's gonna try to attack you back.
He does not clear your AC.
He's just swinging at you, and you're just like--
- What the hell, what the hell?
You get any kind of punches or things?
He's the worst kind of punch in the world.
- Yeah, do you guys, you guys should just roll initiative
just 'cause you're in the turn order.
- All right, I'm gonna use the dice game.
- You don't have to do anything, though.
- Yeah, I ain't doing nothing.
you got a twelve and then you rolled it into an eight. That didn't work either.
Okay, mine was a four plus one, which is five. Cool. All right. Yeah. I mean,
so either way, yeah, let's just, we'll just like,
and then we'll just reincorporate you into the main turn order.
Is there anything you want to do? He doesn't want to do anything. You know,
I don't want to help him at all. I don't want to even work with him. Cool.
All right. You're going to die as soon as possible in this campaign.
You're up. I have the second worst character and mine is the chef.
You're up for it. I feel good. I'm the best. You're the best. Yeah.
you
about it. We were making all the moves and stuff. We talked about this for a while. We
did text about this actually, yes. We texted about it. I did think it was a good character
idea. I just, I wasn't thinking though guys, I'm sorry. I mean it is a good idea. It's
just that like, how he, no, the execution is really wrong. What do you mean about the
execution? The execution is what's going to happen to this guy once I'm done with it.
roll a DC Constitution saving throw. Sorry, everyone roll a DC heart. Roll a heart. Roll
20 die and add heart. I got a 12. I'm going to try to do a successful dice cam roll. Somehow
you're first time listening to this. We have fun character sheets where we call things
different things. I'm sorry. I got a 7. Wow. What did you get, Rambler? I got a 12. Did
did you add any heart? Yes, I did that is adding the ten plus to nine nine,
four, seven, seven, nine, seven, twelve, okay,
so suddenly
actually this is pretty funny you're hovering like by the wall and I just
like the wall just
open in front of you and you go spiraling downward, you're going to
take
you take you take in damage, ten damage. You just go fuck you just got half my
yourself to cuss yeah. I wouldn't just be a really curse, but everyone else can
he can't kill or curse that man curses. He says what the fuck when he or he
says like I'm going to fuck you, Selina Kyle, I'm going to fuck you doesn't he
does yeah,
when he fucked yeah, Catwoman, I remember when he's he's holding the guy
by the leg over that that fire escape and he goes suck my dick. No, he does
I'm going to finger you my fucking
I'm going to finger. I'm going to fucking finger blast you cat woman
anyway. So this the wall to God, my dick, my finger, stinky
smell my finger. That's what I did last night
and outcomes a giant fucking robot. Oh great, but again and it points at at you
three goes like to points to each you of to all three of you. Hey, what's up man?
I remember you got go out from it puts its hand down and scoops all three of
you up all these guards and these barking dogs come out.
All right,
this is your fault patches yeah, just wait till we get to some of the other
effects
pretty long. Yeah, it is long. It is long
okay
continue. So you guys get all get scooped up by this giant robot, okay,
and
and it puts you like inside. It's like sternum whoa and you enter into these
like into like these kind of little pods
inside of it. Well, on we're in a little pod right now. That's right, but cast no
doubt, no is out
cool
and you reappear in these pods. They're gently kind of jostling you around as
you hear the mayhem outside mayhem, the mayhem outside mayhem, the mayhem. Oh
yeah, okay, sorry I was I was watching Julio watched Rex play a video game.
I'm going to go ahead and play the mayhem sound effect
and can you may really love you about it. I'm going to lower the volume a
little bit, but let's just listen to the whole duration of this okay.
it.
Another one for patches. Yeah, I think they're all for patches. Yeah, I think we're almost
ten percent. No, not quite. So hold on. No, no, wait, play it out. Wait till it plays
out. You know, I wrote a lot for this campaign. We don't have we're about an eighth of the
way through the sound effect. I killed time with this. I wanted this to be background
background noise. This one is over two minutes long.
I thought background noise to create a background noise, background noise
go go okay, okay, as it turns into a muffled din the bay him outside of that
yeah
and that now it's over though. So now it's so
it's over. Oh, it's done so yeah to hit that one
dog park again. The crowd gets the dog,
the dogs, the dogs, scare the crowd
sort of the vision to have for this.
So
yeah and a half hour or so passes and then you and you hear robotic shifts and
feel your stomach drop as you've been sort of jostled around inside this giant
robot and a spiraling metallic door that sat outside of each of your pods
opens like a camera lens and spills you out into a dark room. There's a long
wooden table and a monitor about the size of a small theater screen sitting
at the end of it. The room is otherwise seemingly featureless. You'd swear it
was the bat cave at first glance, but before you get to take it in
the screen turns on
no and you see it can't be so it can't be. I say that before the screen turns
on. You see a silhouetted face
Hey man how you doing?
Oh no.
Yeah what's up how you doing?
Please don't.
Just hold on one second.
Who are you talking to me or them?
Yes.
Yes?
Yes you.
Yes me?
Alright shit fuck I thought that we were just making conversation man I didn't think you
were going to get all weird about this fucking shit.
Yeah.
What?
Um.
It's good to see all of you.
I broke you out of Arkham.
My name.
Hold on.
I broke you out of Arkham.
I'm not a fly, let go.
But it's a good name.
I'm not.
No.
No. Different.
Different.
Different from Batman.
No.
You can't laugh at my name, okay?
Can't laugh at my name, okay?
You promise not to laugh.
Seriously, you promise not to laugh.
We won't laugh at your name.
uptown what easy uptown easy, easy uptown, easy uptown. Yeah, I'm not
really laughing at this. I'm not sure I would laugh at that. Yeah, not like
laugh out loud. Easy. Is it a pun? May May Z up? Macy's uptown. That's oh well,
I don't think I think we just just let me read. This was supposed to be so much
better. Okay,
okay.
I invited you all here. All three of you here. He didn't really invite us. He
kind of
no, no, man. Yeah, man. I was in there. Everyone liked me.
yeah i like the robot almost one valedictorian in their minimums looking
and we had every side of my brother makes robots on t_v_
more
and
bullshit man has forgiven
all kind of decision i gotta make a man i gotta make a down payment on my
fucking
has no African new has been
and and and and
to kill Batman.
Yeah, no, I'd like to kill Batman, yeah.
You have a plan.
I have a plan for you.
The fucking credit score has gone down.
Well, just shut the fuck up.
What's up, man?
You gotta stop.
Wait, what kind of...
Are you...
You're just a robot?
You're the only one who hasn't said yes.
Do you want to kill Batman
or do you want to put a down payment on your house?
Man, I don't know.
It's every single which way about this fucking stuff.
It's all kind of new kind of things and thoughts and ideas
that I got to have about this.
I've got one thought.
I have one idea for you, shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up.
Can you just lower him? You have to, you have to.
Okay.
So here's how you're gonna kill the bat.
First, you three will infiltrate the mayor's mansion.
He's having a dinner this evening.
Mayor Peach, the mayor of Gotham.
Mr. Wonderful, you will use your magic powers to make the security detail disappear.
Sure, that's a good start.
The cook, you will infiltrate the kitchen and cook up a deadly meal as you have in the past.
Oh my god, that sounds amazing.
Yeah.
Okay, fuck.
And you will kill everyone except the mayor, that's important.
Why?
I'm sorry
It's a little bit
Yeah
(deep breath)
dead except for you and the mayor. You will use your rambling powers to torture the mayor
until he reveals the code and the location to the emergency bat signal in the manor.
Once you've obtained it, you will press it on my mark. Understood?
I remember Mark. Mark was like a 5'2" little guy.
guy. Why don't we just build our own bat signal? My brother, big salsa type of
stuff he baked stuff makes and bakes he makes things that makes things he bakes
stuff. He makes baking things. This is done the cook and Mr. Wonderful head to
the zoo via goth. Wait, do you mean me or my brother? You okay, the guy in the
room who can hear me
And which cook?
There's a lot of cooks.
The cook.
Oh.
Hey man, the size of this robot, you can be a short order cook.
I'll tell you that for free.
That doesn't make sense.
What?
Come on now.
Come on now, we're just having fun.
Okay, so the cook and Mr. Wonderful will leave.
Leave the manor and you'll head to the zoo via Gotham City Rails where you shall meet
with my associate disguised as one of the zoo animals, currently captive and performing
reconnaissance.
He will give you the location of the animal.
You will be given a brief description of the animal and a brief description of the location
of the animal.
You will be given a brief description of the animal and a brief description of the animal.
You will be given a brief description of the animal.
where you shall meet with my associate disguised as one of the zoo animals
currently captive in the form of reconnaissance.
He will give you the location of the all animal release button
and the cook will remain at the zoo and press it on.
And I'll cook all the animals.
You can also do that if you want.
Oh, well, it's your oyster or in this case, the oyster is your world.
It's a zoo with oysters in it.
is
is not
but there is
that's the biggest
okay, that's that's the bad part about the Gotham Zoo is that it's right next
to Arkham,
can't get funding all the all the lions in the zoo died. So they just put
oysters in there. They're like we don't know what to do. I was in closure. You
you can go in and shuck of yourself, but there's one lion that's still alive.
Once the zoo has been secured, Mr. Wonderful, wait, you mean me? You
yes,
you shall head
to the parents day parade.
As you all know,
every time this time of the
around this time of year, every year in Gotham, which is what month we've been
prison. I don't take keep tallies on the on the wall. Not a freak. You don't
listen to my morning announcements man. I fucking tell them every single day.
It's May.
It's gonna be May.
Oh hell no man. Get your ass over here man. I gotta give you a dollar for
that.
Oh yeah.
Who's Bruce Wayne? He's Batman.
I figured that out long ago.
I don't know, you don't know that.
I figured that out.
That's a crazy accusation.
That can't be true.
Nah, I just kept talking to him one night.
You know, you had one of those conversations
that you have when you're sitting on those two plastic chairs on your back.
Okay, don't worry. It's different.
It's way different.
Mr. Wonderful, once the scene has been secured
you shall head to the parade.
There you will stand upon the highest float
and cast the most glorious spell
the jungle of Seshwana. Only you will have the skills to cast it. When you do, it shall
turn the parade into your own personal army. You shall march to the Mayor's Mare, where
by now the Bat shall be, because Rambler, you will have to set off the signal, set up
a final trap to capture the Bat, hold him long enough for when the parade arrives, and the
the
you go to like Pepsi world like big bradels, you're already here
and also to go to my voice and as he says that
yeah, oh shit now. I know yeah the dark sort of dome around you opens up.
The robot is somehow gone from what you can see must have somehow slipped out
while you guys were chatting. The robot is the hundred foot robot slipped out.
Okay.
And you're on top of a roof in the outskirts of Gotham,
overlooking this garish Art Deco manor where the manor is. Wow!
It's beautiful! No, it's not beautiful, it's bloody garish.
Man, I used to live over by here, man, back in the day. It's just too garish.
It's... You see guests beginning to arrive. Gosh! It's his gosh. Gosh, you're
about ghost. I used to know ghost. I used to know a guy named ghost. An orc named ghost.
That was my parents. That's the guy that I used to know. Prison uniform. Do you have
socks? Yeah. I put two in his mouth. Yeah, thank you. Unfortunately, the only thing we
have to do from him is you, Rambler. So you have a dossier of the party handed for you.
I can drink this. He can't. Oh, this one's actually the guests who are going to be
at the party are Cassandra Blackthorn, a wealthy socialite. Oh, the two people
that socialist. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
a quick from the criminal underworld or rumored because my character was going
to have to smash.
Then there's Dr.
Dr. Dick Eisenhart, Victor Eisenhart, Victor Eisenhart, a scientist and
inventor is working on some secretive projects. My brother is an inventor or I
mean, no, he's on a TV show where he talks to inventors.
I got some invention ideas that I gotta start passing by your brother. Lady
Isabella Davenport, an aristocrat,
Senator Jonathan Monroe, a charismatic politician.
These are sort of the... These are all the people that... Are gonna be at the
party. That, oh, okay. General Victor Thornwood, he's a
my ranking military officer.
I thought these are the people that I have to pretend to I'll tell you the two
and a second Doctor Malcolm Stroud, Mark Cuban, respected psychiatrist. Can Mark
Cuban be there? I try to make it pretty all about pretty please pretty please
dragons, then just give me one
Mark Cuban and underworld kingpin is, I guess what he is now who commands a
private. No, he just is Mark Cuban. Mark Cuban is there Alistair crumb, a
mysterious fortune, no a mysterious and underworld kingpin. He's a for secretly
a fortune. No, that's mad. It's a fortune. It's Madame Celeste and then
there's Dylan, who wears a blue shirt.
I like
we like Dylan say Dylan's think what Dylan wears a shirt. He has a felt
gold, so he's the type of guy where during the week he wears maybe graphic
tea, cargo shorts and on Friday he's like I'm stepping out. I'm right on my
home.
start loading t shirt and friday here we go friday. It's my
golden star hitting the club, maybe blue shirt. He's at the
forty forty club, vip red rope around on stripper. He's looking
up the hottest stripper. No, no bottle service. Yes, water to
other people's vip sections. He's getting their bottles. He's
saying check my shirt and then he's not drinking. That's the
coolest shirt. I've ever seen drinking. He does not drink. He
said he just pours it on the ground. He pours on the women's
glasses. Yeah, he rubs it in sex like suns. Yeah, yeah, he says my shirt girl.
He hates drugs. I made the star myself when I bought the shirt from Amazon and
he loves his shirt from Amazon. It's a medium.
But it's kind of big, right? It's a medium, but it's a medium, but it's
me. It should be a large, but it's tight as shit. It shows up. Yeah, there
are two people you can you can choose to in person. I am obsessed with Dylan
right now. I can't even think Dylan will be there at the party, so you can talk
to Dylan. I choose to can I choose to impersonate someone you can, but you
will be taking out security guards of the roof. I will be impersonating
Gordon Ramsey.
I would like to impersonate Mark Cuban. He could impersonate Mark Cuban, so
Mark Cuban actually isn't there all along. He's not there he's so take that
strike that I didn't realize we're even going to have the opportunity to
impersonate people. There's Lila Renard, a renowned art collect written art
I did what I did and then there's Raphael de la Croix. Okay, what are
their descriptions? Lila Renard is a renowned art collector. Okay, sounds
about right. She's been a she uses her extensive network of contacts and a vast
knowledge of the art world, art world, to help funnel money for the mayor's
schemes, allegedly, because the mayor is corrupt, of course, Mayor Peach,
Mayor, Peach Boucher Jag. No, his name is damn. You know, this was 2018. Holy shit. That would
have been fucking fire. But Raphael Delacroix is a foreign diplomat known for his silver
tongue and shrewd negotiation skills. Does he have a silver tongue for real? Yeah, it's
silver. Okay, shit. So I just paint my tongue silver. So the reason why he chose to dispose
of these two though is because Lila and Raphael are new to the Mayor. Lila is a friend of
a friend who he's been trying to get to be a part of his sort of art collection circle.
And Raphael Delacroix is a foreign diplomat who is new to the US and is new to the, to
being an ambassador from the Isle of Monaco.
Okay.
So.
So I think I'll probably pick Raphael because of the silver tongue and I pull a little jar
of Warhammer paint out of my pocket and I started painting my tongue very silver.
Okay, so they will ask you probably if that's a condition.
Well, he's supposed to have a silver tongue.
Yeah, you said he has a silver tongue.
There's only one guy that they know who has a silver tongue, so they're going to assume it's him.
And I'll tell them it's like a Monikin.
Moniko? He's from Monaco?
Monokin?
I have no idea.
It is a Monikoin.
Monikoean?
Monokoean.
It feels like there's something that's like...
Google it. It's probably Monacan. Like Monation? There's like something weird. Monotian. Can
you look it up? Somebody from Monaco. Yeah. Our producer's Monacan. Word for Monaco adjective.
Monacoan? It's probably Monacan. There's no word? What is it? Is it Monacan? Manican?
Mono? Monoan. Monoan. Monoan. Monoan. Maybe it's just Samoan. Monagask. Monagask. Okay,
It's way harder.
What?
So...
That can't be right.
Yeah, that can't be right.
I think your phone is glitching.
Yeah.
It seems like it's...
That's a bug.
So it's a Monagasque ritual that all boys go through when they're 14.
Because overtime.
Yeah.
And I'll tell people that, but they won't even know that I'm saying it because they'll
stop listening after halfway through my conversation.
So you guys can make your way to the front area of the manor.
you want to blend in kind of with the crew that's a good fucking news,
because I'm already wearing my chef's outfit. Perfect
awesome and then how many spells do I get to cast
so that see that? Oh, hi. So you have oh, these are my spells. Those are your
spells. I mean, you have four potions that just replenish spell. So, okay,
cool. Yeah. All right. I know how I'm going to take out the guards, but we
can get to that when we get to it. Cool. Oh my goodness. I'm dressed. I'm
a
He was at the Dallas...
He wears a suit on the show though.
He's known as a t-shirt guy.
But not at a high party where he's meeting the mayor.
Maybe the...
How about the NBA finals?
Okay, why don't you wear a t-shirt?
That's a game.
He owns the Dallas Mavericks.
You don't know shit about Cuban.
You don't know shit about Cuban other than his shirt.
It is more than a game to him.
More than a game.
So you guys, so there's like, so how do you want to, how do you want to
approach the, here, are you all, you're all, well, I have to do, I walk up to
the, before they go in. Yeah, I walk up to the valet guy. No, don't let them
do anything. He can still go in. He can still, yeah. I can go in 'cause I
have a silver tongue. I'll explain, the reason why. Then why am I even taking
out the guards if we can just go in? Let's just go in. 'Cause, well, hold on.
Let's all go in together. Hold on. Yeah, let's just go in. I'll say that
they're my guests. The reason why you take out the guards on the roof is
because... Oh, they're on the roof, they're not out front. Yeah, sorry.
Okay, we go in and so when he he goes in the front, there's no guards to stop us.
Yeah, they're on the roof. I guess it's a party. The problem with the guard,
he's gonna kill everyone. Well, I can just say that they're my guests. Yeah,
I'm gonna go, okay, I'll make a beeline for the... I'm in. Or you can say that,
you can try to do that too. I'm in as well.
So we're in. Okay, we've gone in. Okay, so there's this... Okay, and then...
Well, no, what do you guys wanna do? What do you guys wanna do? So you guys
are my guests? Okay, I'd like to walk up to the DJ booth. Cut to us being
in.
Okay, you're in. I'm walking up to the DJ booth. All right. Yeah, I mean,
there's a DJ booth at this dinner part. Hey
hey man what's up? Can you play that one? You're a you're supposed to be Gordon
Ramsey. How you fucking don't? Can you play that one song this lot? Welcome to
my house and I'm in too loud. Yeah man sure just
play that fucking music. Yeah I'll play that in a second man. Just give me one
second. I got to play it right fucking now.
I walk up and I show my tongue.
(laughter)
- Let's roll your first roll.
Let's roll speech, let's roll talking.
- Talking?
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, he got a natural 20.
- Nice.
- Get that.
- Nice, okay, yeah, he's like, all right.
- 60 plus, minus one.
- All right, all right, man, yeah, I'll play it.
Yeah, he plays the song.
- Welcome to my house, play my music.
- And yeah, you see, so you're in the house now, right?
Okay, cool.
I got a yeah I am in the house you're in the house in my house.
All right hold on I gotta read a thing.
Welcome to my house.
So yeah Gotham's Mayor Lionel Peach is a noted what's so funny he's a noted philanderer.
Actually put on the Batman voice.
He's a philanderer.
Homer's a fucking neighbor.
He's Homer's neighbor.
That's what it is.
What's a philanderer?
Homer's neighbor.
Google that.
Yeah can you google philanderer.
work for philanthropist. They fuck around. Yeah, they're just like
frequently. Somebody fucks around. They're frequent fuckers. Oh, that's
the opposite of Homer's fucking neighbor who's Christian. Yeah, that's like
Homer, a scumbag.
I have to rub shoulders with him from time to time, and I always feel like
taking a shower afterwards. 'Cause your secret identity is Bruce Wayne.
This is imagine this is being said while the mayor walks down to greet all
the guests. Are you on the fucking roof or what? I don't know. We're in.
you're doing a narration, but I just wanted to know where you're going to be.
I didn't do okay.
I will say I walked to the I walked to the
kitchen after I just wanted to hear okay, then I'm on the roof. I suppose
you can so you you're not on the roof. You'd be like outside scouting to try to
get on the you can't just like get on the room, but he can levitate. He can
levitate right up to the floating disc yeah
we can come back to you. I just don't know finish your narration. He got to we
locked in and then we didn't even get a chance to say anything about what we
were doing, but I got a request. I know that's what I'm saying. That's why I'm
confidant.
I think that somebody here is playing for five seconds. Did you convince you
press the transition button? So I was like I guess this is kind of happening
now, but are you are you going to be are you going to tell because you guys are
not guests who are in like your chef, so you would have to
work back out.
We left
which is one. I feel like I'm I feel like I'm fucking up right now. Are you
are you actually going to try to like get them to come in from the front
entrance and be your be your party guests? You're okay. Maybe no. Here's
what we're going to do. This monologue is happening. We just we retcon all
that what just happened. We're walking. We're stepping out of our limo. It's
like song. It's like they're playing the song. It's twenty one jump street,
slow motion. Okay, right again. It's just a touch tunes and he figured
you up and we're walking in. We're currently walking in in slow motion.
Yeah, we're crossing the threshold. All right, the guard is now going to come
up to you and just be whoa, hey,
Ambassador de la Croix. Who are these two guys? We're Mark Cuban. We're just
two guys. My name is Mark Cuban. I'm on TV with my brother.
So
it's
make me laugh
and I'm here to cook the food for the whole role persuasion
and that would that be my talking yeah roll talking sorry.
That is a fourteen okay yeah he's like come on
with us mark Cuban chef tongue
let you in now Batman voice. We're inside now. Okay, Gotham's Mayor Lionel
Peach was a noted philanderer scumbag. I have to rub shoulders with him from
time to time and I always feel like taking a shower afterwards. The man is in
the pockets of every will freak in the city and he barely hides it the way
flaunts his corruption works in two ways. He shows he's powerful and he shows
that he doesn't care. So neither should you I guess damn peach himself as a
a man of about 60 with a dollop of blonde sitting unconvincingly atop his mushy
head.
His beady eyes somewhat crossed with a stylish goatee failing to draw the eye
away from his blotched cheeks. His third wife, Nuna, a drunken former beauty
queen.
Nuna?
Nuna Peach.
And his daughter, Sandy Peach.
A law school student paints the perfect family picture.
Two women sick of a man they depend on
in one way or another.
Peach's manner is garish.
- Oh God.
- Bygone nouveau riche art deco with rounded arches
and loud marble slates and ceramics.
His own Baroque flourishes involve winding lattice gold
across transoms and some East Asian pieces.
- Not Baroque flourishes.
it's broke. Oh, it's and he's got lettuce all over the place. He just says it's
not me and my crew. When we see Baroque flourishes
anything, you know, like he's got like a little like sort of my dog. When he
sees Baroque flourishes
look man, I took creative writing. It's not my fault. I'm going to shoot this
shit out of this. You should shoot me yeah. Oh the party, I'm Batman hold on
He said I'm Batman.
I'm Batman.
Oh yeah, and some East Asian pieces he collects on his frequent trips to mainland China.
I've scouted the place a few times myself and there's always been something up with
it, something lurking in the corners.
The rooftops filled with guards, men in suits with concealed carries walk the halls, not
too typical for a mayor.
From the ceiling hangs supernova chandeliers and fractured glance mirrors, more funhouse
than dining room high arch chairs with alabaster backs and rounded marble bases
along with a rug of spiraling cow print and the occasional white Buddha. Each
depiction more alienating than the last someone raised gold plates hanging
askew or full marble statues in a Greco Roman style. So very chaotic hodge
podge. And let me guess he also has a fucking Jeff Koons. Yes. Oh, fucking
Oh, fuck no! And it's the dogs. It's all the dogs. It's just the dogs, all in pink.
Oh, bloody God! And I'm not Batman no more. And as he sort of, he prances down
to greet everyone, he says, "Oh, it's so good to see all my lovely guests!"
Hey yo, Peach.
Ah, you must be Ambassador de la Croix.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
(growling)
Yes, I've heard about the Monag-- Monag-- Monag--
Monagweeze.
Monagweeze tongues.
Look at my shit.
And who are your two guests? Mr. Ramsey, I presume?
Gordon Ramsey and Mark Cuban.
And Mr. Cuban.
I'm Mark Cuban. I speak to inventors
on TV with my brother.
We're gonna invent a new kind of tongue.
like, oh, no, there's an invest time. So we are inventing a new kind of tongue
that's gonna be silver. Watch for the episode. It's gonna be silver and gold
tongue. I'm just so surprised. Shark Tank season 20, episode 15. How quickly we
added Shark Tank back into the whole thing we do. It was pretty fast, right?
Do you think? It's been maybe- It's been a long time. It's been two years since
Shark Tank was in here. Has it been two years since that? It's been maybe a
year since we- No, it's two years. I think it's been two years. I think he's
Yeah, 2021 we did Shark Tank.
Anyway, so let's all sit down for some dinner, right?
Oh, yeah, I got to go cook it now.
He's going to go cook it and then he's going to go distract.
No, he's going to not going to.
I have to. I'm searching for talent.
He's going to go look for my TV show.
You got to go to the top floor.
He's going to look for young, talented women.
The C suite.
Okay, I'll go check it out. Young, talented women is what he's looking for.
And I like I'm Mark Cuban. I like when the women pitch inventions on my show.
Yeah, we say bitch inventions. He wants women's bitch inventions like the
Scortatron. I like bitches. That's right. The Sliz machine. I'm Mark Cuban. I like
bitches. I like when they pitch the Sliztronics. The Scortatron. The Sliztronic
Robot 3000. Scortatron and the Sibian. And the Vagina Machine. Okay, I'm gonna
I go to the
tracker behind you. I actually was the one who green lit the period tracker on
the shark tank and I
use it. You guys file out to your respective locations. You I was really
mad when when when one of the women shark tanks who I can't remember her
name stole the I like old shock. Yeah,
stole the remote control vibrator from me. Yeah, I wanted to invest in that so
bad.
yet,
but I couldn't
okay. I'm in the kitchen, so he's going to look for young girls. He's going to
look for younger. I can say you're in the kitchen. Wait say you're in the
kitchen again. I'm going to the kitchen.
Oh my God, I'm here all right. He's in the kitchen and your dinner is started
I'm at the table. Are you going to the roof? Are you going to I'm going to the
roof?
Okay, cool, so yeah, we're at the let's start with being at the dinner table.
So all right, I'm sitting next to Bruce Wayne
Bruce Wayne is not there. Why not? I don't know. He doesn't like Bruce Wayne
very much. The mayor, the mayor, Bruce Wayne doesn't like Bruce Wayne very much
in the new movie. Something in the way I don't like myself.
if you want to do who does who do you sit next to the second? Who's the second
closest to Bruce Wayne? Alfred Wayne is not
who at this dinner?
I can't believe you're going to this
- Master Wayne, it's gonna be finger sandwiches.
- It's gonna be too fun, Master Wayne.
- It's gonna be finger sandwiches and a water slide.
I have to go.
- Master Wayne.
(laughing)
- Master Wayne, I have to read some arrows.
- It's an open bar, Master Wayne.
I have to go.
(laughing)
- We'll talk about this when you get back.
- I'll only go for about an hour, Master Wayne.
- Master Wayne, Master Wayne.
- I'll probably be back by 11 p.m.
- Master Wayne.
- I want to check it out, that's all.
I want to see how lame it's going to be.
- There's a bowl of Chex Mix, Master Wine.
- I think I'm going to be a little longer.
(laughing)
- They have Chex Mix at the party.
- You're not having too much fun, are you?
- No, it's, Master Wine, it's horrible here.
It's not fun at all.
- Alfred, get back in the pool!
- Alfred, come here!
- Get back in the pool!
- Master Wine.
- That's just my friends being funny, Master Wine.
(laughing)
- This is one of these prank phones they gave me.
- Who are your friends, Alfred?
Who are your friends, say?
- I'm here with Derek.
what up yeah,
this way,
yeah,
well, I'm gonna oh man, we could do that forever, but here are the people
I'm going
to go low.
I am without you master way, you're going to create my style master. The
party is sponsored by Casamigos.
I have to go the closest to there's Alfred and you can sit directly between
Alfred and Dylan. Okay, if you oh I'm sitting in between Dylan and Alfred for
sure yeah cool. So yeah, I'm turning to Dylan. I'm like hey man where the hell
do you get that blue fucking blue shirt? You got that on Amazon Prime. I made it
myself. You made it you okay, so yeah, I bought this shirt on Amazon Prime and
then I made the felt star myself. Holy shit, man, you're like one of the most
creative people in Gotham.
That's what I like to think.
One of the things that I love about you is your bulk.
That's Gotham's art scene.
They don't have anything else.
They have custom shirts.
One of the best things about you Dylan is you're doing it like nobody else, man.
You're putting felt in t-shirts, you're putting your hair in a bowl,
you're cutting around the bowl.
Yep, that's just the quickest way to do it.
Man, Dylan, you're like basically like Gotham's Picasso.
Thank you.
He's got a circle go to.
but he's not known as an artist. He's only just people just like him. Yeah,
he's a socialite. He will be an artist and he does thumbs up like that. Yeah,
that's how we just
he says pound it and then he gets confused and he tries to shake your hand
after he says pound it
he was like what's up man. Yeah, yeah, he goes. I didn't know what we were
going for
hugs people first time he meets them. Yeah, also every time you meet him for
the first time, I don't think it's anything wrong with that. Yeah, hiccups
unexpectedly. He's like sorry. I just have a
check my shirt, though
yeah
sure he does that every like once in a while to his I turn to I turn to I turn
to out like a nerd, but like yeah yeah yeah I turned out for the he also does
the big blink yeah yeah yeah
turn Alfredness didn't get a lot of sleep. You so you know that guy's Batman
right, you know, fucking
I don't know what you're talking about come on me. You can tell me Dylan is
Batman
you mean to I used to think it was Bruce Wayne, but now I've been thinking maybe
is who think about it Batman. I'm not here, but I'm just
I'm said talking to myself think about it. Batman must have had to make his own
costume. Who in this city is better at making clothing than Dylan and I turned
I turn to turn to Alfred, it's like a split screen and we're saying the same
exact thing. I used to think it was Bruce, but think about it. There's only
one person in this city who's good enough at making their own clothes and
what better secret identity than a socialite.
Nobody would ever suspect you're all you're saying that, like to the
it cuts in and to me. I think Dylan might be Mario.
My God, you to say that at the same time as Alfred and the and a guard, just
like ran it was like like that's a good point. That's a good point. Like
staring like looking around
I mean go hey wait a minute and he turns around roll for roll for me. Cut to
you
all right. He heard you just chatting to yourself, so you better start rolling
your
cardboard. No, that's always how I got to trouble before the cardboard.
There's a gap in the
I'm holding it now. Okay, that's even worse for camera wise, but it's a twelve
plus my balance ball, which is one, which is thirteen total. Okay, we'll
figure out the dice cam another time. Yeah, we'll make a box for it. So the
guard sort of is moving around. There's like kind of these like little, this was
a last minute addition, like these kind of like
some old style buttresses that
peeling around and a girl's but a buttress is a waitress that that gives
you the food out of her, but
the whole table laughs.
The Homer Simpson dinner party scene.
Yes, that's a brilliant idea.
I do immediately. I try to light my own fart
okay. Can I can't? Yeah, you can cast a spell at them, so press the
digitation. This is still going to cost me a slot,
even though it's a level zero. Yeah, thank God I'm going to cast it. How
many guards are there? There's four on the roof, four times and I'm going to
read you one sentence from this and maybe you can guess where I'm going with
this. Okay,
you instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than one cubic foot.
Oh, you're going to do their wieners. Oh, and he's pretending to be mark cubic,
so he's gonna exactly yeah. So this makes total sense. He gets advantage
and check this one out this one. I'm not going to use, but listen to this.
You chill warm or flavor up to one cubic foot of non living material for one hour.
I think you should play
I think you should flavor a for so I can flavor something that is not a
life. What are you going to know? Okay, okay, so you're going to make them
shit. I can flavor anything. It doesn't have to be food. You're going to make
them shit themselves, right? I'm going to make their pants dirty. Yeah, you're
going to make me
but but use the
flavor their
say you're going to make you know, I'm really shit spicy so that their butts
hurt. Okay, all right. Oh my God, yours. Okay, so here's what I'm going to do.
so since I can cast this unlimited times, I'm going to cast this basically a
hundred times.
Okay, so
they will. It does require first. I saw in right, so okay, I say do so you have
to roll
your flavoring. There do I would start out by soiling. Okay, so you have
advantage on rolling for stealthier because you got away from this guy, but
if you're let me just say what I want to do, let him cook and then you tell me
I need to roll, but let me cook for a second here and the chef told I soil
each of their pants, their unders
unders to the outside soiled through that's less than a cubic foot. So I can
see it. You have to be able to see it doesn't say so. All right, I guess
what they just says within range. Okay, and then I flavor I okay. I chill. I
chill it
okay, really cold. They do. Yeah, okay, but I also I chill it, but I flavor it
spicy yeah, so it's like an icy hot kind of sensation that they've never
experienced before when it comes to do that's perfect. Then I also create a
non magical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in my hand
and I make a toy to play
a toy race car race car race car. Yes, no, I do all in cup and I flavor it
sweet
and then I create stop stop stop and then I snuff out a candle.
there's a candelabra. There's a candelabra. There's a candelabra at the
dinner table and I'm trying to light my fart right, but then I him snuffing at
the candle makes it look like my fart blew out all the
on the candelabra in front of me. Oh wait, I can have up to three
effects active at a time, so I was how is giving you stuff to read, make it so
that things get derailed. You're the only one here who it's going to get
derailed because you're reading. What am I derailing? Hold on let's start with
the real he's doing I'm doing a
one thing at a time. I sing there, okay, then I buy a new do I flavor it? I
chill it okay, so first to make them do
let's
I don't need to roll anything. I end up here
for stealth is what I mean, because you do have to talk
okay. Tell me that a guard is going to react to this
do
we say it twice and I cover my mouth. When I say it, say do you just make them
you convince me, make them to okay. I'll roll though.
You have advantage. I've been already snuck around. Can you say it like
Rammstein
okay? That's a nineteen. Okay, whatever you do, I mean you're but let's see if I
create them to do yeah. Okay, I didn't crit cool. All right, so yeah, you they
they all are there. All their pants are soiled like our pants. They all know
maybe I think they'd all if you let me step into your your shoes for a second.
Yeah, I think maybe they'd all since their guards and they're tough, they
would be too shy to tell each other, but as they walk around, but they're all
kind of shattering because it's also frozen. It's not frozen. It's just
chilled. It's not chilled. Yeah, she'll do chilled. Yeah, but they all they're
all kind of like I have to go. Maybe they're all they all like to go, but
they don't think it all smell it. Maybe they all go like
they all they all sort of like slowly like one of them goes like you got this
by the way, yeah, yeah, I got yeah, yeah and they like shoots a grappling gun
barrels down
another one goes the other one goes like hey
you got this I'll be right I'll be right back with you yeah and they all do
them and there's one up there and he's just sort of standing there yeah and
he's like trying to find a way down right now, but he's not sure if he can
leave he's got do he's got do he doesn't feel good okay, probably get him pretty
bad.
I flavor his tongue
what's spicy. He's freaking out now. He's freaking out. Can we before we go any
further? Can I create an odd odor?
Can we
can we list all the flavors he's able to do? I mean, it's anything right? Okay,
do flavor. Okay, exactly. Can I create a flavor so bad that he has to vomit?
Yeah, yeah, of course. Okay, I do that. I do that. You make it do
he did not succeed in his constitution saving through he vomits
on to I should have had that to the sound of a board onto the roof.
That's a pretty easy one.
Yeah,
sounds like a
crazy.
They smell the
and he just he goes down.
So the guards are clear. They're off the roof right now. So
you in the kitchen. Yeah,
it's your turn to try to poison the stuff. So to do that, you're gonna
have to do some gum. Do I have poison? You have poison. Can I make a
suggestion?
Maybe try to get some of the guards chill to do
and add it to the... I can just make more chilled dew. I can do it
infinitely. I already have poison, he says. I don't think I need dew. I
mean, if you have the poison... The concern will be that the guards will
come back from... He's like a douyaan. Yeah, yeah. Use chilled dew as a
douyaan. But it lasts for an hour, so they're gonna have to go and
get change for an hour. They change and it's going to stay
clean it
put on their pants. They shit themselves
it's a spell of endless
the one hour goes by and it's all gone. Okay, so you said something about my
gumbo yeah. You should use
You should use your gumbo to cook up the poison.
So, roll a d20 and we'll see what gumbo you get.
You might have to keep gathering ingredients.
- 16.
- Okay, I'm gonna look at your gumbo list.
- That's my modifier, right?
- No, that's just the gumbo.
- Oh, okay.
- That's just for the gumbo.
- 16, what do I get?
- You see what you get.
Okay, nice.
Fortifying broth.
- That's the opposite of fucking poison.
- Roll again.
- Okay.
- You can't control the gumbo.
seventeen
confusion concoction. Okay, I'll take that. Okay, cool cook crafts a liquid
that induces confusion. The cook makes a range of take away two ingredients from
your from your ingredients list. Which ones are you taking away? Well, it's
just it's like a bar, but like say what you're using yeah. What are you using
though for confusion? Yeah,
salt and pepper
together. Yeah, yeah, right for what did you do for four and not supposed to mix
Fortifying broth was a, it was bone broth.
That makes total sense.
Nice expensive bone broth.
Cool, and I'll tell you what the effect of that is too.
So, a cook or a chosen creature within 30 feet gains resistance to all damage
except psychic damage for the next minute.
So, if you want to strengthen yourself up, if you get into a fight,
you can always drink fortifying broth.
So you have that.
And I'll put a little asterisk next to that so that I remember for next time.
And then for confusion concoction,
the cook crafts a liquid that induces confusion.
The cook makes a range attack against a target within 30 feet.
But in this case, you're just going to pour it into the food.
The target must succeed on DC wisdom, 14 saving throw,
or be affected by confusion.
- So is the food going to roll?
- What'll happen is, no, no, no.
What'll happen is you'll put in the food.
Everyone will eat it. - What is the food, by the way?
What's on the menu for tonight?
- You're Chef Ramsay.
- Well, I'm not, the foods aren't,
you said dinners are you gonna-
I have an idea. Quail eggs? Quail eggs? Those are this big. It's a confusion concoction,
right? And it's a gumbo. What if it's a soup that lifts above the bowl, but it retains
the shape of the bowl? What? Are you describing like a magic trick kind of thing? What are
you talking about, man? So when you try to go in? Yeah. When you try to open -- yeah.
so I don't know. No, no, I mean, I'm no, I think that will stick with eggs and so
I'm going to, I guess, inject my confusion into the yolk of the egg. Yes,
you do that
and yeah, they have to roll a DC wisdom saving throw. So
that's perfect. So the guards are gone. You guys drank at the same time you're
married.
If you, if you want to before you do that, you can still use two more and see
if you get another kind of thing you want to use. I like, are we good with
confusion is confusion. Okay, I think confusion. Yeah, roll one more confusion
is also easy. If you confuse them, I feel like and they don't die. We can
easily mow them down. You know what? I'll just try again. I have four
ingredients. Okay, but don't you want to save them for maybe another task?
Don't didn't have another other tap. We could probably do like a long rest at
some point. That's a whole four that will get you healing delight. Okay,
don't want that one. And last one seven
Speedy preparation. Okay, I'm doing the fuck is speedy preparation. These are
fucking poison speedy preparation means that he can can he can he just means he
make it made it fast. Can he? No, I don't know. It's called healing. You
like the light? Yeah, the cooker chosen creature gains three. Okay, we're going
with confusion. You're healing. The light's gonna be useful because you
don't have healing. Okay, I have all these made. Okay, cool. So So now you
have those in your I'll just put a little asterisk next to them and you can
you can gather ingredients after you do like a rest, which maybe you'll do on
the train or maybe you'll do here, depending on how things go. The train?
Well, you're going to take a train, I mean, we're on your way to the zoo. The
railway. Oh, yes. You can also take the Gotham City Express.
Cool. So we're at the dinner now and there's a toast
from me. Wait, how long is this one?
Okay, that was pretty funny right. Hello, hello, excuse me. Oh wait yeah sorry. Hello
everyone. Hello everyone. Everybody look at me the mayor. I'm doing this. Dylan's like
Oh, sweet going finger trick. Why Dylan's doing it? Oh, Dylan. Well, I showed
Dylan how to do it and you know what? Honestly, what I think happened is that
you went to do that. Your hand started moving together and he instantly got to
it before you. Yeah, he's and then he did and then he did blood and then I
went, Damn, Dylan, everybody. Look at what Dylan's doing.
Everybody look at Dylan.
Thank you all of you for coming here today to my lovely dinner
and let you know that this is the beginning of something spectacular.
We're going to change Gotham forever.
It's going to be a place where I shall rule with an iron fist
and the criminal underworld shall work for me, courtesy of Alistair here,
and it will all start at the parade.
And, well, before I go on, let's eat. Let's eat some quail eggs.
And so the quail eggs are brought out.
[Tapping]
[Ding ding ding]
Yes, Mr. De La Croix.
I just want to say one thing before we go any further with this dinner.
You can eat during my speech.
And that's...
Check this out, y'all.
you have to make a noise.
I like it so much better when you
a natural noise. Yeah, look at my tongue. Y'all. I just turned sixteen.
I just turned sixteen. Look at my silver tongue. I will sing this song.
Here's my sail for
everyone is everyone's rolling because everyone's eating
Some of these people are getting actually good.
Wait, you have to stop the mayor from eating.
He's not supposed to die.
The mayor's not supposed to die?
Well, he's going to be confused.
Oh, right.
God, I feel like an idiot.
You should.
And also check this out.
I'm going to make this dog really angry.
Everyone's mad at you for trying to make the dog angry.
It didn't work.
I forgot I had Alfred.
I forgot.
I forgot Alfred's there now.
Everybody rolled pretty good, guys.
I'm not going to lie.
most of them failed, not looking good. Most of them failed to some people
weren't confused. The only people who succeeded, by the way, all of your for
the mayor.
Oh, that's not a good rule. He failed. The only people who succeeded
were Dylan
no joke,
Dillon and
General Victor Thornwood. Okay, that's easy. I can take out Thornwood pretty
well. Cool. Yeah, so everyone's like and Dylan's probably on our side over
falling over, but we think he's Batman Dylan is the leader of the over belly
yeah Dylan sort of looking around confused. He's got his hands on his
hips, but too high. Yeah, he's like sort of like yeah
he's like he's doing like this kind of thing this yeah yeah yeah
yeah and he's doing this with his shirt
because he's a little over heated because of the felt before dealing
address, moving the quail eggs around his plate with his fork and he's like
Okay, so yeah, everyone is now most of our confused like oh, no, what do I do
now? What do I do? They're just hanging in different voices and the mayor. What
do I do? That's okay. Here you go. Go, go, go, go, say, Oh, what do I do? Oh,
I know I'm a girl. What do I do? I'm so confused. Oh God
and those are all the different voices. Yeah, I did it wrong. I
didn't know what was happening. It's my fault. Yeah, you didn't
know so and when you rambler you approach the mayor, the mayor
who's like sitting he's sitting. He looks like like when you're
knocked out of a mini game in Mario party and they're just
sitting there like like and he's just sitting there. I pick him
I pick him up by the lapels and I go, "Man, listen right here, man. I'm gonna tell it to you right now, right fucking straight.
I'm gonna say it one way, I'm not gonna say it the other way. I'm gonna look at you, I'm gonna just say, 'Hey, man, let's get the F out of this fucking...'"
And next time, we'll see what you do to the mayor's mind.
Cool.
(dog barking)